Uncle: Push, tohru!
(Grunting)
Push!
Uncle,
unlike the ox,
tohru does not
have super strength.
Then help tohru push!
We must leave quickly
before daolon wong's
warriors return for the ox.
Maybe this will
speed things along.
Mmm! Crunchy,
energizing goodness!
Finn: Hey, folks...
Hate to interrupt
snack time, but--
fetch!
Huh?
I guess one should
never come between
a hungry ox
and its vittles.
Grrr.
Pterodactyl snatches ox!
Uh-oh.
Aah!
Bwaa!
To the plane,
quickly!
Come on, boy!
Hunh! Huhh!
Thunder fist!
Bwaa!
Huh?
Yah!
Go, go, go!
Uh, what he said.
(Panting)
Jade:
Jackie, come on!
Hak foo: Tiger lands
on eagle's back!
Bwaaa!
Tohru! Help Jackie!
(Gulps)
Out there?
Tohru: Jackie!
Gah! Eee!
Bwaaaa!
Hyuh!
Hit it!
Aah!
(Gasps)
Jade: Sit back
and relax, Jackie.
You've been upgraded
to an indoor seat.
Welcome to your new digs.
Hey, everyone!
Say hello to the mightiest
member of the zodiac gang.
Jade of the jungle.
Hiya, boy.
This is scruffy.
(Barking)
Look, scruffy's
herding again.
He's gotta be
part sheepdog.
Smart doggy.
(Purrs)
And this is Sasha.
She used to be
a Vegas show girl.
Good Sasha,
pretty Sasha.
Ahem. You can
finish introductions
later, Jade.
It's almost
time for school.
(Gasps) School?
All good things
must come to an end,
even spring break.
No, I totally spaced!
I am so in trouble.
Teacher: It seems
every other student
managed
to prepare an exhibit
for tomorrow's
school fair.
What is your excuse
this time, Jade?
Um, would you believe
I had to help rescue
a super-strong ox
from the dark warriors?
What, no
invisible rabbit?
Put a sock in it, drew.
And it's
a super-speed rabbit.
Jade, luckily
you still have one day
to put
an exhibit together,
which shouldn't be
too much of a problem
considering
your imagination.
You could always bring
your magic animals.
(Students laughing)
Yes, I could,
couldn't I?
My enemies possess
9 talisman powers
and I only possess 2?
I have you
to thank for that.
Hak foo.
Sheesh.
Get with the program,
will you?
Grrr.
I meant all of you!
Pah!
I must locate
the remaining animal
and find a way
to tip the balance
of power in my favor.
(Hoofbeats)
Hmm?
(Hoofbeats stop)
Good invisible snake.
Rabbit power!
Easy does it, fellas.
Bwaa!
Jade!
Oh, can you believe
these strays wandered in?
Section 13 is so
turning into a barn.
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
Oh, Jade,
have you come up
with anything
for the fair yet?
I cannot wait
to come see.
The f-fair?
Uh, you really
don't want to come.
I don't?
No!
Um,
I decided to make
an exhibit of...
Uh, mashed potato
sculptures.
Snoresville.
Heh heh.
Well, uh, gotta
cook up some spuds.
Later!
Potato
sculptures?
Young Jade has
a very unique mind.
Whew! Ok, haiku,
change 'em back!
Head count!
1, 2, 3, 4,
1, 2, 3, 4--9.
We're off to the fair.
(Children chattering)
Now remember:
Ix-nay on the agic-may, ok?
If anything goes wrong,
uncle Jackie will
ground me for life.
No way!
A petting zoo?
Look. don't touch.
Where did you
get all of these?
These, drew, just happen
to be the animals I,
um, borrowed from
my cousin, the zookeeper.
Hey, these are the magic
animals, aren't they?
No. I mean, heh heh.
You got me, drew.
I was making all
that magic stuff up
the whole time.
Heh. Heh heh heh. Uh.
Me and
my imagination.
Ahh, yes.
Reveal yourself to me.
Uhh?
The dog?
There must be some mistake.
They are vulnerable again?
Jade will be
very surprised
to see us.
Ooh, games.
Who wants to play
whack-a-mole?
We are here
to whack real animals!
And this time,
we will not fail.
Come on, Jade.
I've never seen
a magic animal trick.
Uh, shouldn't you
be annoying people
at your
own booth, drew?
(Gasps)
(No audio)
(Woof woof)
Drew, buddy!
Hold the fort
for me.
And whatever you do,
don't touch anything.
Sure thing, Jade.
Step right up!
Ring the bell!
Pick a prize!
I will win
something for Jade.
Pfft. Games
are rigged.
Uhh!
(Clang)
Supermoose.
Jade's favorite.
Hey! What are you guys
doing here?
Tohru: Surprising you.
We can't wait to see
your potato sculptures.
Potato? Oh!
I mean...Uh...
Duh...Too bad
you missed 'em!
They were delicious.
Ashley's booth
features her
key chain collection.
Oof!
(Gasps)
Dark warriors!
What are you
doing here?
Come on, bunny.
Show me your tricks.
(Falling bell
- whistles through the air)
(People screaming)
Yaaah!
Whoa! I wonder what else
Jade's been saying
that's true.
Grrr.
So you have come
for the animals?
Uh, what animals?
Uh, yeah. Heh.
I don't see any
animals around here.
No! Come back!
Scruffy!
Rahr! Oof!
Rrrr.
Ohh! Dark warrior!
Daolon: Enough dallying.
The animals!
Evil on the loose?
Here comes supermoose!
Heh heh.
I bet you're wondering
why all the animals--
I know why.
Which way
did they go?
Ohh! Every way!
We must split up.
Remain here.
But, Jackie,
there are 9 animals,
4 evil dudes,
and only 3 of you!
We need to even things--
Jade, you have
caused enough trouble.
(Sighs)
You're right. I have.
Which is why I need
to make things right.
Tourists: Aah!
Help!
Let's get outta here!
A tiger!
(Kissing) Pussy cat,
want some fishy-fish?
Hand me the tiger.
Funny, I was gonna
say the same thing.
Come to papa.
Huh?
No, no, no!
Do not eat the astroturf!
Whaddya know, chan?
You're on a roll!
Aah!
Chow: We're on astral-turf!
No.
I was not expecting
to feel that.
Guess it's 'cause
we're both astral.
There you are,
little fella.
Come on. Let's
get you some cheese.
Eeyah!
Whoa!
Uh-oh.
I will take the rat.
(Supermoose
tootles fanfare)
Antler action!
You will take the moose
on the jaw!
Grrr.
You the man, supermoose.
Supernova
incinerates super--
evil on the loose,
you do not want
to mess with supermoose!
Uncle: So, do you
want a piece of uncle?
(Chanting)
Aah!
Nobody messes
with the "do."
Ha ha! Time to jet!
He is one
slippery character.
Please, come
to uncle Jackie.
Baa!
Good sheep.
Huh?
Uncle and tohru are busy
devising a locator spell
to find
the remaining animals.
Let us hope
- that it is not too late.
(Sighs)
Jackie, I deserve
to be grounded for life,
but I'm hoping you'll
settle for a month or 2.
Scruffy!
Just like
I trained you.
But how?
Told you scruffy
was part sheepdog,
and I taught him
the way home.
Good boy.
Good boy, scruffy.
Jade, would you mind
explaining exactly
what happened
at your booth yesterday?
Uh, would you believe--
the dark warriors,
like, appeared
from out of thin air,
and--and then the--the
magic animals ran off
and turned
invisible and stuff!
Oh, drew. I think
you may be spending
too much time with Jade.
(Supermoose
tootles fanfare)
A flying moose!
Gee, Ms. hardman,
and I thought  I
had quite the imagination.
- Hey, Jackie!
- Yes.
Have you ever worked
with any dangerous animals?
Oh, yes. I remember
when I make the movies,
it's a leopard.
Every time--grrr--
he try to attack me.
That is scary.
Then I remember
the animal really
can recognize the people.
Not everybody.
Except me. Only me.
I don't know why
every time the leopard
see me, he say attack me.