Jackie: Hello,
my reptilian friend.
Aah!
Aah. Unh. Aah, aah.
Bad day.
Waaah!
Jackie: Waaah!
Unh! Unh!
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
So sorry.
Vanessa:
Remember us, chan?
You snatched
the nebilla opal,
the sword of badang,
and now the silver iguana
of yorumba
right out of our
greedy little hands.
Jackie: Yes, heh.
Nice to see you
all again, heh heh.
How've you been? Heh.
Bye-bye.
Unh, ho!
Aah!
Waah!
Jackie: Heh heh.
Pleasant day for a hike.
Jade: Jackie!
Welcome aboard
Jade airlines.
Jade: And that's how we
returned the silver iguana
to the museum of yorumba.
Comic fans: Cool.
Larry: Wow.
I wish I could
go on an adventure.
Scott: You could start
by movin' out of
your mom's basement.
(Laughs)
Jade: Come on, Larry.
You're going
to the super duper
convention this weekend.
That's exciting, right?
Larry: Duh. Everyone
who's anyone in comics
is gonna be there.
But just once,
I wanna go to the con
with a story like
the silver iguana of yorumba.
I wanna be a hero
like super moose or you...
Or Jackie.
Jackie: Oh ho. Hero.
You've been listening
to too many of Jade's stories.
Jade: I know
how you feel, dude.
Larry: Ow!
Jade: Jackie tries
- to leave me out of the action
all the time.
Larry: But you don't
take no for an answer.
You go after what you want.
Jade: You could do
the same thing, Larry.
Be like super moose.
Free the hero inside.
Larry: Ah. I don't know
if there's a hero in there.
(Rumbling)
Uncle: Earthquake.
(Gasps)
Demon chi is loose!
The demon chi is still near.
Tohru and I will repair
the containment unit
while you find all 5 missing
demon powers.
Tohru: Remember,
the chi-o-matic holds
only one power at a time.
You must come back
to the containment unit
after capturing each one.
Jackie: Ow!
Jade: Hey!
Uncle: Evil does not sleep!
Captain black:
I'll put on some coffee.
(Jade gasps)
Chi at 12 o'clock high!
Jade: Good aim, Tex!
Jade: Gotcha.
(Captain black snoring)
Uncle: Water, moon,
sky, wind.
(Jade yawns)
- Now back to snoozeville.
Uncle: Aiyaah!
- Earth demon chi is not here!
Tohru: Mmm. The chi-o-matic
does not detect the power
within section 13.
(Drago snores, grunts)
(Ice, fist, cobra snoring)
(Clanging)
Strikemaster ice: What? Yaa?
Yo, why you gotta
wake me up, dawg?
My dream was off the hook!
Drago: We have work to do.
Kids: Yeah! Watch out, man!
Whoo! Whoo!
Larry: How am I ever gonna
free my inner hero?
(Sighs) Maybe I should read
some  super moose
àback issues.
Larry: Hey! Watch it! Whoa!
Oof!
(Larry shivers)
Tingly.
(Larry gasps)
Lizard men!
Just like in  astonishing
à  moose tales number 157!
Drago: You have
something I want.
And what I want, I take!
Strikemaster ice:
What's the dilly, yo?
Drago: He's using
the power of dai gui,
the earth demon!
Larry: Aah!
Mc cobra: Huh? Ooh!
Larry: Bleah! Bleah!
Wh--what's goin' on?
Larry: Please--
please don't hurt me!
(Rumbles)
Strikemaster ice: I'm so
gonna burn your crust!
You know what I'm sayin'?
(Inhales)
Strikemaster ice: Unh! Ooh!
Larry: Unh! Ow.
Drago: Playtime's over.
Drago: Aah!
Jade: Step back,
lizard lips.
Larry, you have
the earth demon chi?
Drago: don't worry,
little missy.
He won't have it for long!
Jade: Leave my friend alone!
(Ice crew grunting)
Drago: Why are these fools
still breathing?!
Tohru: Whooaaahh!
(Crash)
Jade: Larry, listen--
you have
these weirdo powers
because some demon chi
got into your body.
Larry: Demons? Ha!
There's no such thing.
Uh, fire breathing
lizard men, maybe.
But not demons.
Ok, I'm outta here!
Jade: Larry, wait!
Drago: Let's go, boys!
The chi's gone underground.
Jade: We gotta
go after Larry!
Jackie: No. The tunnel
could collapse with
you inside.
Tohru: Jade is right.
We must find Larry
before drago does.
Uncle: And before evil chi
corrupts Larry's own chi,
turning him into a demon.
Larry: Something's
definitely different.
That stuff I did
with the ground
and these...Muscles.
I--I have super powers!
I've finally unlocked
the hero within!
(Dog pants, barks)
Larry: But
- these new powers mean
I have
great responsibility. Yes.
It's time--time to fulfill
my destiny!
Strikemaster ice:
- Yo, we would've had that chi
if you hadn't tried
that inverted 720
off the vert ramp.
Fist: Whoa!
Strikemaster ice:
Whoa, hey, unh!
Drago: Quiet!
That earth demon chi
is still out there.
We're going to find it,
take it, and bury chan!
Jade: This is where
the comic shop owner
said Larry lives.
Jackie: Thank you, Jade.
I will take it from...
Larry's mom: Yes?
Jade: Uh, hi. Can Larry
come out and play?
Larry's mom: Lawrence
is trying on his new costume.
He's going to fulfill
his destiny, you know.
Come in.
(Rumbling)
Jackie: We are too late!
Uncle: Very strong reading.
Demon chi
- must be above ground!
Jade: I hope Larry's
not doing anything crazy.
Larry: This is my city:
San Francisco--
the city
I've sworn to protect.
I am...Uh...
I, uh, ooh.
Spectacu-Larry!
(Mayor speaking)
Vandal: The mayor
doesn't deserve a statue!
Vandal: We're here to show
his true colors!
(Rumbling)
Vandals: Aah!
Larry: Spectacu-Larry
at your service, mayor!
No need to thank me.
It's all in a day's work
for the seismic superhero.
Larry: Nothing bad
happens to art
on the amazing
spectacu-Larry's watch.
Larry: It's back
to the big house for you,
compliments of the stupendous
spectacu-Larry!
Can ya dig it?
(Sirens)
Jade: We're getting warmer.
Uncle: Not warm enough!
Jackie: Rather than trying
to catch up to Larry,
perhaps we should attempt
to get ahead of him.
Tohru: Where would
a superhero go?
Jade: I know!
(People chattering)
Jade: Cool!
Uncle: We must hurry.
Split up and look
for teenager in a costume!
Jackie:
That is everyone here.
Uncle: Do not argue
with uncle!
Jackie: Ooh!
Krampon warrior Scott:
Nok-cha! Blork gup-ta!
Jackie: Uh, excuse me?
Krampon warrior Scott:
You have offended our honor!
You must apologize!
Jackie: Ooh, I am sorry.
Krampon warrior Scott:
In our language!
Tohru: Oh.
Sumo girl was
- my favorite show growing up.
Sumo girl: Mine, too.
(Giggles) What's your name,
big boy?
Tohru: Eh, uh, uh,
I must keep searching.
Sumo girl:
A man on a mission. Ooh.
I like that.
Lisa: Ok, I'm attacking
your wizard with my swordsman.
Danny: My wizard casts
a melting spell.
Your sword is slag! Ha!
Uncle: Aiyaa!
Magic must defeat magic!
Up! Up!
You want a piece of uncle?
(Jade gasps)
- Super moose number one!
Jade: I'll give you
20 bucks.
Booth owner: Ha!
Are you kiddin', kid?
It's worth
10 times that, easy.
(Rumbling)
Larry: Behold!
Spectacu-Larry!
Jackie: Ah, Larry, please,
you are not a superhero!
Jade: Yeah, you have
all these powers
because the demon chi
is taking control of you!
Larry: You're wrong, Jade!
I know what's happening!
I'm, uh, I'm...
I'm turning into
super moose!
Drago:
What you're turning into
is a major pain in my tail!
Krampon warrior Scott:
Dude, weak costume.
I could totally
see the latex.
Jackie: Tohru, do you have
the chi-o-matic?
Tohru: No, uncle
was carrying it.
Jackie: Find uncle.
We will try to keep drago
from absorbing
the demon chi.
Jade: But, uh--
(drago growling)
Jackie: Waah!
All: Unh!
(All cheer, applaud)
Jackie: Aah! Hot, hot, hot!
Jade: How about
I go find uncle?
Larry: Nice block,
Larry-lad!
Now let a real hero
do his job!
Larry-lad?
(Drago growls)
My hero ain't nothin'
but a sandwich...
Mama's boy.
Larry: ¶ do do do do do ¶
antler action!
Larry: You are more powerful
than I expected, villains.
But spectacu-Larry
has mights to spare!
(Drago screams)
Aah!
Jackie: Aah! Please, do not
touch the celebrity guest!
Strikemaster ice:
Yo, we ain't playin'
dress up, mama's boy.
Ice crew: Hywaah!
Tohru: Rrrah!
Larry: Who wants
spectacu-Larry's autograph?
Strikemaster ice:
Yo, it's time to make
this big chunkie
into a lot
of little chunkies.
Ice crew: Unh!
Sumo girl: May I join you?
Tohru: Oh, by all means.
Danny: My plus-3 elvish sword
paralyzes your cleric ranger!
Uncle: Ah, but
- my cleric ranger has a...
Uncle: Blowfish.
(Danny gasps)
(Crowd laughs)
(Jade panting)
Uncle! Jackie...Larry...
Uncle: In a minute!
Uncle is busy kicking Booty!
Jade: Drago...Demon chi...
(Uncle sighs)
- Uncle will be right back.
Do not touch uncle's cards.
(All yelling)
Jackie: Larry! Stop!
Larry, earth demon voice:
Stand aside, Larry-lad,
while I eradicate
these evildoers!
Larry: Huh?
Jackie: Unh!
(Rumbling)
(All yelling)
Larry: You raise your hand
against me, Larry-lad?!
I'm the hero!
Uncle: Yu-mo-gue-guai-
fie-Dee-tsao...
Larry:
What trickery is this?
Jade: He's taking away
your powers, Larry.
It's for your own good.
Larry: I thought
I could trust you.
But you have betrayed me!
All: Aah!
Larry: Once my friends...
Now my enemies!
Uncle: His transformation
into earth demon dai gui
is nearly complete!
Jade: No!
Larry's still in there!
I know I can reach him!
I know it!
Hey, uh, spectacu-Larry!
This isn't how
a superhero acts.
Larry:
How do  you know, Jade?
You're not a superhero!
Jade: No. But I've read
a lot of  super moose comics
just like you.
Remember  the terrible traps
à  of the toilet master?
Larry:  Spectacular
à  super moose number 39.
Jade: Super moose's mind
was taken over
by the toilet master
who turned him against
the animal avengers.
But when super moose
remembered
to trust the hero inside,
he was able to save the day.
Larry: Hero...Inside...
Jade: Look around you,
Larry.
Would super moose
trash this place
and scare everyone?
Is this acting like
the hero inside?
Larry: What have I done?
Jade: It's not you.
It's the demon chi.
We can help you.
Larry: Mustn't give in...
To demon.
Still a hero...Inside,
and his name...Is...
Larry.
Uncle: Yu-mo-gue-guai-
fie-Dee-tsao,
yu-mo-gue-guai-
fie-Dee-tsao.
Larry: Aaahhh!
Jade: Larry! You ok?
Larry, normal voice:
I--I think so.
I feel all tingly.
(Booth owners grumbling)
Booth owner: Hey, who's gonna
pay for this damage?
Jackie: Wait! No.
I didn't...
It wasn't...
Uncle: Uncle is
new grand master wizard!
Sumo girl: Call me.
Sumo girl: Mmmph!
- We'll go out for a big lunch.
(Tohru laughs)
Jade: Come on, Larry.
Let's...
Hey! How much?
Booth owner: Go ahead,
take it, kid.
It's worthless now.
Jade: Not to me.
Jackie: After
all we went through,
you want more comics?
Jade: Tch.
Not just any comic.
Scott: Could you sign it,
"to my best pal?"
Jade: Hey, Larry.
Larry: Jade,
ya made it!
Check it out.
Jade:  The adventures
à  of spectacu-Larry
with his sidekick larr-ina.
Jackie: What about
Larry-lad?
Jade: Awesome! Hey, I have
a million story ideas.
How about
larr-ina saves the city?
No, wait, the world!
Stay with me here.
Dragon-boy
and the lizard men
- shoot a missile into the sun
to turn the earth
into a reptile's
only desert planet!
Spectacu-Larry
tries to stop 'em.
But he gets captured,
so it's up to larr-ina
to get the self-destruct code
before it's too late.
Oh, and larr-ina
should be able to fly,
and how about X-ray vision?
Jade: Hey, Jackie, what do
you do to relax?
Jackie: When I relax,
I have, like, a loft,
and I call up some friends.
We sit down,
listen to music,
watch TV, yeah.
Because from TV,
I can learn so many things.