Hyah!
Aah!
(Exhales)
Not bad, Mickey,
but your form
needs work.
Spar with, uh,
someone else
while I confer
with captain black.
Sorry about
the hard knocks,
my friend,
but since section 13's
officially out of
the dark hand business,
I had to devise a way
to justify your overhead
to my superiors.
Did you put me on the books
as personal trainer,
or punching bag?
Jade: Hyah-ha!
(Gasps)
Jade!
What?
Oh, I, uh, told Mickey
to work on that form.
Shendu: Ah, ah...
Gingerly.
Watch your step.
Place it over
to the left...
Valmont:
And into the incinerator.
We could use some firewood.
Shendu:
Silence!
With some sprucing,
this fish heap
will be worthy of housing
a demon sorcerer--
valmont:
Ex-demon sorcerer.
Shendu:
- I may be vanquished,
but I am still
in charge, valmont,
as you can well see.
Valmont:
- This is my hideout,
and my body, shendu.
Which reminds me,
I have a change
of wardrobe
in mind for us.
(Gasps)
You wouldn't dare.
Aah!
That is a thousand-year-old
heirloom
from the ling dynasty!
Well, maybe if
game geek over there
would have helped.
Oh...
Chow.
Shendu: Ah, yes.
Directions to the door
which contains tchangzu,
the thunder demon.
Hey, Cali-for-ni-yay.
We are here--
and we are to go south,
to--
you got that,
didn't you?
Uh...
Pretty much all of it,
before we, uh,
ran out of tape.
(Growls)
Dude, run.
(Shendu growls)
Aah!
(Gasps)
Water!
That's right, big v--
swimmin' pools
and movie stars.
We're headin' for...
Jackie: Hollywood?
I'm on my way,
captain black.
Jackie, can I come
with, please?
Jade,
the dark hand is there,
no doubt searching
for a demon portal.
But rafaello dicapezio
is getting his footprints
in cement
at the Chinese theater
this weekend.
Who-faello di-who-zio?
Hello?
Rafaello dicapezio
is only
the greatest movie star
in the history of...
History.
Uncle: Ahh...
I guess you have never
heard of John Wayne.
Ahh, the Duke.
(Imitating John Wayne)
Saddle up, pilgrim.
Hmm, I suppose
this is one time
you could come along
and not be in the way.
Yes!
Hey, what's that
supposed to mean?
Jackie: Tohru will
be your chaperone,
while I search
for the dark hand.
Well, the festivities
aren't till tonight,
so why don't we
just take a minute
and help you find
the demon door?
Happy sightseeing.
I am so sorry
that I screamed, Jade.
Yeah, uh,
Frankenstein did look
pretty lifelike, t.
Must be all that wax.
Uh, maybe we should bring
back a souvenir for uncle.
Do you have any photos
of John Wayne?
Tohru.
Aw, we're
wanderin', anyway.
I want to see
Clark gable's old house.
Frankly, ratso,
I don't give a darn.
And who's wanderin'?
We got directions
right here.
Chow: Yeah. Halfway between
"the pools of despair"
and "the trail
of treachery."
It's all so clear.
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Jackie,
the dark hand guys
are right outside
the wax museum.
Uh, Jade,
how do you do that?
Never mind.
Do nothing
until I get there.
Can't hear you.
(Imitating static)
You're breaking...
Up.
Jade? Oh!
The wax museum--quickly!
Which do you think
uncle would like best?
Jade?
Jade: Look,
the 3 stooges!
Where?
Duh.
All: Hey!
Heh.
You must want this, huh?
Say "cheese," Princess.
"Cheese, Princess."
Tohru!
Maybe he'd
like to see
some real stars.
Finn: Chan!
Does this qualify
as being outnumbered?
Works for me.
Jade, are you all right?
Peachy. Jackie, I got--
what part of "do nothing"
didn't you understand?
But Jackie, I got--
watch her.
(Moans)
(Gasps)
I have waited
for this moment.
Prepare to meet
your doom.
I didn't know
the dark hand
had a new enforcer.
Hyah!
(Grunting)
Aah!
(Both grunting)
Wires?
Nigel: Cut!
Who are you?
This is a movie set?
Awesome. Are you gonna
put Jackie in your movie?
Oh, sure, after
I have him arrested!
Nigel, Nigel, calm down.
Larry Franklin, producer
of  ninjas in the hood.
That was quite
a display the way you--
"bam" and "bam, bam!"
(Laughs)
- You have an agent?
- Uh...
That would be  moi.
Bam, bam. This town's
gettin' younger every day.
Look, lar,
Jackie chan here is
going to be the next
big action superstar,
and you have
the opportunity
to get in on
the ground floor.
Jade.
Right, Jackie. Did I
mention that he does
all his own stunts?
Oh!
Give me a jingle.
If jc can act, bam--
we're in business.
(Scoffs)
Act? Jack--whoa!
Say bye-bye to
the nice man, Jade.
Jackie, play
your cards right,
and you can be a star.
I don't want
to be a star.
I want to find
the demon portal
before valmont's men do.
Oh, that.
It's in the bag.
Jade, how do you do that?
Jackie: If "the pools
of despair" are
the tar pits...
And "the trail
of treachery" is
the cahuenga pass...
Halfway should be
right here.
"Megagalactic studios?"
Boy, talk about
your co-ink-I-dink.
As long as we're
gonna be on the lot,
why don't we
"do lunch" with lar?
Because "we" had
a big breakfast.
Pass?
Uh...
Hey, you're
talkin' to the star
of  beach babewatch here.
Oh, uh, sorry.
Go right ahead.
Oh! The dark hand?
Pass?
Yes, I would like to.
No, can't
let you on the lot
without a pass.
(Ring)
Good afternoon.
Jade arts talent agency.
Jade, I--
I can't get onto
the studio lot.
Yes, but--
yes, b-but--
ok, I'll do it.
(Telephone rings)
Jade? Hello?
Megagalactic studios.
Hey, sipowicz.
See the human
action figure
with the million-dollar
smile outside your gate?
He's Jackie chan,
the next big thing,
and he has a meeting
with  the Larry Franklin.
So let me
give you lar's number
so you can explain
how we're about
to sign a deal
with another studio,
because you wouldn't let
the man who does his
own stunts onto the lot.
Uh, your pass?
Uh, sorry about
the inconvenience,
Mr. chan.
How does she do that?
You gettin' anything?
It's got to be
somewhere around here.
Sorry I can't
bring it back!
Thank you!
Chan!
Get him!
(Buzz)
Yes?
Oh, put her through.
Jade, what's up?
Lunch? Well,
let me check my--
whoa!
What goes up.
Woodchuck Chucks wood!
Whoa...
Aah!
Bam! He really does
do his own stunts.
Uh, of course he does.
So, Larry baby,
we're on for tomorrow?
You bet--heh--
unless your client's
in traction.
Jackie has a meeting.
I'm da bomb.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Um, we're going to be late
for the footprint ceremony.
Rafaello, right!
Oh...
Ah, oh.
How come everyone
can do that?
Ah! Oh!
Huh? Wha--
the portal!
Greetings, tchangzu.
What took you so long?
Just the usual
interference
from Jackie chan.
Then he will
interfere no longer.
(Roars)
As the thunder claps,
so do I applaud
your skill, brother.
Shendu, you may
call me "master."
Of course...
Master.
Ooh, sss...
Now, take me
to my palace.
Oh, rubber is
an excellent insulator.
The surroundings
may not seem familiar,
but I assure you--
my palace!
These humans have
paved my paradise
and constructed a--
parking lot.
(Roar)
I will rebuild my palace.
For the time being, shendu,
you shall find a dwelling
place which befits me.
Uh, how 'bout
that one?
Hmm...
That will do.
Isn't he the dreamiest?
He's all right.
(Crowd murmuring)
Uh-oh.
Away, infidels!
(All murmuring)
Why do they not flee?
They think you are...
Entertainment.
Hmm...
Jade: Who's in charge here?
We specifically asked
that crowds be kept
at least 60 feet away.
What are you
talkin' about, miss?
How are we supposed to film
with all this interference?
Do you know how much
that animatronic suit cost?
Film?
They told us it was
a footprint ceremony.
Let's go.
Crowd control.
Wow, these agents are
gettin' younger every day.
Uncle: The immortal who cast
the original chi spell
on tchangzu,
the thunder demon
was patron deity
of actors.
And the portal was located
in a movie studio?
Weird.
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Where are you?
Duh. Chinese theater?
But so's
the thunder demon,
and he's packin'
serious boltage.
How do you do--
oh, Jade, do nothing
until I get there.
Jade never
does nothing.
I know, but I feel
I have to say it.
Jade: So raf, here's
all you gotta do.
When Jackie chan
comes running in--
Jackie who?
(Sighs)
Will you sign my arm?
I'm callin'
my manager.
He's not
so dreamy anymore.
Relax, t. Raf'll
come crawling back
once he reads about this
in tomorrow's papers.
Lar? Jade.
If you want to catch
Jackie in action,
come to the Chinese
theater pronto.
Where is the demon?
Inside.
Uncle,
the chi spell's ready?
I cannot prepare
the spell.
What?!
Need ingredients.
Why don't you have
ingredients?
How am I supposed to
gather chi ingredients
when you steal
my apprentice?
"Chaperone." Pahh.
Oh.
Chinatown. Hurry.
I'll try to keep
tchangzu inside.
Jackie!
What?
Please, Jade,
stay here.
Uncle: One more thing.
Powder of komodo
dragon tooth.
One more thing.
Tincture
of tortoise shell.
One more thing.
Castanets, the symbol
of tsao kuo-ch'iu.
(Crash)
In Chinatown?
Tchangzu: I will scorch
this city to the ground
while the sound
of thunder resonates!
Heh. Guy's
a regular Olivier.
Welcome to
the cheap seats, chan.
You!
I shall prove that lightning
can indeed strike twice.
Baah!
Aah!
Oh...
If life gives you lemons...
Lar, glad you could make it.
Show's about to start.
What show?
Aah!
Bam!
Rhymes with chan.
State of the art.
You guys go all out.
Jade: Uncle!
Must prepare chi spell.
Hold these.
Who's the old guy?
Cranky co-star--
occasional comedy relief.
Forget chan!
If that accursed old man
completes his chi spell,
you will be cast
back into limbo.
That would
be our cue.
(Tohru grunts)
(Roars)
Aah!
(Gasps)
Uh, bam?
Oh!
Jade, play castanets, now!
He's also
our musical director.
(Uncle chanting)
(Grunts)
No!
Ole!
(Growls)
So, uh, lar, I'm
thinking buddy picture?
Chan and dicapezio,
dicapezio and chan.
There is no picture,
and Jackie chan
will never do lunch
in this town again
ever!
Lar didn't say anything
about dinner.
Come on, my treat.
We know of
- a Mexican restaurant
where uncle found
the castanets.
In Chinatown?
Hollywood is a strange
and mysterious place.
So we didn't get
a movie deal.
Jackie chan has definitely
made his mark in Hollywood.
Hey, Jackie,
have you ever met
anybody famous?
One year I was
doing, uh, Oscar.
I was standing
in the green room.
There's so many big stars
I see--wow, John Travolta.
Tom Hanks.
Oh, my god--
Sidney poitier.
I don't know what--
what should I say?
Suddenly,
- there's a voice--
"Jackie chan,
can I shake your hand?
I turn around--
Robin Williams.
He said, "Jackie,
I'm a big fan of yours.
You are great."
That makes me proud.