Jackie chan, it was
nice knowing you.
Gorilla fist!
Horse kick!
Weasel strike!
Otter slap! Huh?
Perhaps you should
save it
for the real
Jackie chan.
Towel off and grab
your shoes, hak foo.
I have located
the next oni mask.
I shall wear it proudly,
master tarakudo,
and with its magic,
summon vast armies
of shadowkhan!
Oh, incidentally...
Floating head
annihilates
punching bag!
Jackie! Scruffy hates
puppy prison.
How long do we have to
keep tormenting him
this way?
Jade, scruffy must
attend obedience school
until he learns
to listen.
No doubt he takes
after his master.
Har har.
Look, I can prove
scruffy obeys
all my commands.
You ready, boy?
Play dead!
Whoa!
Heh! "Dead"
needs work,
but he has
the "play"
part down.
Uncle: It is
your move, tohru.
Hmm. No.
Huh!
Who's winning?
Jade, the Hana fuda
cards are no game.
Huh! Huh!
We are attempting
to make cards reveal
location of
next oni mask
before forces of
darkness find it.
(Scruffy sniffing)
Aiya! No animals
in shop! Shoo, shoo!
Uh, 52 pickup
is no game?
Whoa!
Ohh! It is
the next mask
we seek.
Jackie: And this card
shows us where to find it.
Right here
in San Francisco?
And it looks like
the mask removal
spell ingredient
is Japanese rice!
Tohru, boil rice!
Jackie, find mask.
Jade, read sign.
Sign?
The one
in shop window.
No pets allowed!
(Banging on door)
Mordecai!
Howdy, y'all.
Egbert!
Farmer MacDonald?
Did you not see sign
in uncle's window?
The one that says,
"stop on by
"if you're ever
in this neck of the woods
for a big city
tractor pull"?
Uh, farmer MacDonald,
we were just in
the middle of--
well, deal us in!
Mordecai and egbert
haven't had
much real fun since
y'all left my farm.
If you ask me,
they miss them crazy
magic powers they had.
You mean, heat-beam eyes
and levitation?
Float like a butterfly,
sting like a...
Hot-eyed pig.
Please,
farmer MacDonald,
Jade is very
impressionable.
Jackie!
Right, unc. Time to
play find that mask.
Say, y'all don't
mind if we bunk
here, do you?
Aiya!
Well, strap on
my feed bag!
What's for
supper?
Uncle was thinking
pork or chicken.
Oh! Heh heh heh!
Jade, why don't
you stay here
and help uncle find
farmer MacDonald
and his friends
more...Appropriate
lodgings.
Ohh!
(Growling)
Aah! Ohh!
Huh?
Wrong museum, Jackie.
The mask is Japanese,
not Jurassic.
Jade! I thought
I told you
to help farmer MacDonald
find a place to stay.
Tsk! Did!
(Squawking)
(Alarm)
Hey, there he is!
Hey, where's he going?
Hey, pig!
Come here, pig!
He's up there!
Fancy supersecret
underground base
you got here,
captain.
So where do you keep
the flying saucers?
Jade! Section 13
is not a hotel.
And ancient artifacts
are not doggie treats!
Scruffy, heel!
Heh!
He thought I meant
"dinosaur heel."
Jade, the card is
leading me to...
Jackie...
Unh!
Ohh! The oni mask!
I always said
scruffy was
part bloodhound.
They didn't teach
you that
at obedience school,
did they?
Did they,
you good boy?
Jade, we had better
leave before--
grr! T-Rex
decapitates dodo!
Go, go, go!
Give me the mask,
chan.
Uh-uh-uh!
Only if you promise
never to wear it.
Then suffer
extinction!
Jackie, I'm open!
He so never
obeys me, either.
Tarakudo Rex,
king of the shadowkhan!
Jackie, heads up!
Waah!
Lobster claw
pinches mask!
Hak foo,
show me a face
only a demon's
mother could love.
At last! Unh!
Check it out!
Scruffy's
totally helping.
No, he is
totally playing!
Ugg!
Unh!
Oof!
Hyah!
- Argh!
Jackie, go wide!
Drat!
Nice catch!
That is not a frisbee!
Not exactly who
I had in mind.
(Growls)
Um...Bad doggie?
Scruffy?
Tiger tears mask
off pooch!
Friendly reminder,
muscles,
the only thing
that can separate
a mask from
its wearer is--
blecch--good magic.
Now go enjoy
a protein shake.
Waah!
Here, boy!
Jade! Scruffy
could be dangerous.
Tsk! My dog loves me.
don't you,
scruffy-wuffy?
Huh?
Scruffy!
Oh, no.
Aah!
- Jackie!
Scruffy, stay!
Please?
Jackie!
Seems it's time
to walk the dog.
(Jackie groans)
Jackie,
are you all right?
(Moans)
No broken bones.
Come on!
We have to
find scruffy.
Before tarakudo
teaches him
any new tricks.
Both: Like
summoning shadowkhan!
Chan to section 13,
requesting
transport for Jade.
What?!
But...My dog!
I'm sure egbert
and mordecai
just loped on down
to that silo you
mentioned for some grub.
It's a missile silo,
not a grain silo.
Scruffy's all
mondo-megamonster-powered,
which means Jackie's
gonna need help.
Superhelp.
Farmer Mac did say
you guys miss the magic.
Levitation!
Heat-beam eyes!
Motion for
a motionless moose!
Duh-huh!
And superstrength
for t-girl!
Whoa.
Talismans.
They do a body good.
Scruffy! Here, boy!
(Whistles)
Wha?! Eww!
Huh! Pee-yuu!
That is the largest
poopie I have ever--
I must be on
the right track.
Well, doggie park
certainly has been
invigorating.
But it's time
you answered
a different
call of nature.
(Howls)
(Gasps)
Scruffy, no! Stop!
Scruffy?
don't you think
he looks more
like a spike?
Spike,
unleash your pack!
Supermoose, humming  charge:
¶ doodle-la doo-do-doo ¶
hang on, Jackie!
Say hello to t-girl
and her amazing t-troop!
The animals!
Your moose!
Your muscles.
Heh heh.
Joined a...Gym?
This is your team,
Mr. chan?
A child, a ham,
a stuffed moose?
Ha ha ha!
And a flying
chicken?
That's levitating rooster
to you, fat-head!
(Howls)
Take 'em, t-troop!
¶ Doodle-la doo-do-doo ¶
antler action!
I got your back, Jackie.
Titanic t-slam!
Whoa!
I so totally don't know
my own strength.
Jade!
Uh-huh!
Who da moose?!
Me da moose!
You da chicken!
Reinforcements,
spike!
His name's scruffy,
you no-necked demon!
And he obeys me!
Oh?
Here, boy!
(Whistles)
(Howls)
(Sighs)
¶ Doodle-la
doo-do-doo ¶
bad dog!
And growing worse.
Soon the mask
will take hold
completely,
making doggie
a demon forever.
Not if I pull it
off him.
don't you listen?
Even your biceps
don't possess
enough strength
to remove
a demon mask
from its wearer.
Duh.
That's why
I swung by uncle's
for a little
rice potion.
(Gasps)
Good magic!
Huh? Hey!
Give it back!
Whoa!
(All groaning)
Playtime is over,
child.
Spike!
Jade!
(Pig snorting)
What?! Timmy's trapped
at the bottom of a well?
Help! Please!
Pull me out!
I must rescue Jade!
Shh!
You don't wanna
reveal t-girl's
secret identity,
do ya?
T-girl? I--
I am debating
with a stuffed moose.
T-troop away!
Whoa!
I just hope your
barnyard buddies
haven't
wandered into any
highly sensitive
off-limits
quarantined areas.
Well, instead
of frettin',
why not try cluckin'?
And a-soowee-in'?
Uh, come again?
Talk to the animals,
son!
Works like a charm.
(Quietly)
Soo-wee.
Come on! Sound off
like you mean it!
Be the hog!
Relax, missy.
Strength is no match
for the power of shadow.
(Grunts)
I want my dog back,
tarakudo!
There they are.
We must retrieve
uncle's mask
removal potion.
Scruffy, help me out, boy!
Scruffy can't hear you.
His transformation
is nearly complete,
which I shall
demonstrate with
a little obedience test.
Spike, be a good demon,
and make a meal
of your former master.
Not gonna happen,
taradoo-doo.
Dogs never turn
on their masters!
(Gulps) Do they?
Good work, egbert!
Now I am
complimenting
a rooster.
Scruffy, don't
you remember me?
I walked you,
fed you!
Funny, you're about
to feed him again.
Supermoose:
¶ doodle-la doo-do-doo ¶
t-troop is in the house!
Supertroopers!
Aah!
You people
are giving me
quite a headache!
Oh?
Bring it on,
my feathered foe.
¶ Doodle-la
doo-do-doo ¶
ninja knockout!
Jackie: Sit!
Heel! Stop!
Jade!
Hello?!
Secret
identity!
Scruffy, I'm gonna
say it one more time.
Stay!
Aah!
Ok, the kid gloves
are off!
Welcome to
obedience school,
t-girl style!
Stay!
Anytime, Jackie!
Your...
Talisman magic...
Is no match
for...Huh?
Shadowkhan!
Got it!
Scruffy! Good dog!
I am a sore loser,
t-girl.
Scruffy!
Oops.
Missed.
Scruff.
He was a good dog,
wasn't he, Jackie?
A very good dog.
Well, what
do you know?
He does
play dead.
Hopefully,
farmer MacDonald
isn't too worried
about his missing
animals.
(Everyone clucking and
snorting like chickens
and pigs)
Whoa!
What'd I tell ya?
Works like a charm.
Hey, Jackie,
if you could be a dinosaur,
which kind would you be?
If I were a dinosaur,
I would be
a brontosaurus,
because big,
but only eat vegetable.
Nobody can touch him.
Even the t-Rex.
The t-Rex, too violent.
And...Yeah.
I want to be
a brontosaurus.
Ah, difficult!