Previously on
Jackie chan adventures
this is Jade, your niece.
I have a niece?
I cannot read
these inscriptions.
Very old writing.
The dark hand
has connections
to nearly every criminal
activity in existence.
Their leader is valmont.
You're telling me
one man stopped you?
Tohru, bring me the shield.
Uncle: Jackie!
I have found what
the inscriptions mean.
They are incantations,
but the shield
not important.
Of course the shield
is important, uncle.
Everybody I meet today
wants the shield.
Shield not important.
The talisman in the center
of the shield is.
That is where
the magic lies.
Shendu: Valmont,
are your men blind?
It would seem
- those possessed of sight
might have taken note
that the shield
contained no talisman.
Why's the boss taking guff
from a statue?
Uh, 'cause it talks.
Now, if my promise to you
of unspoiled riches
were as empty
as that shield...
Rest assured, shendu,
you  will
have your talisman,
and I  will ensure
that Jackie chan
never again interferes
with the dark hand...
Ever.
Jade: Chinese food?
I just moved here
from Hong Kong.
Can't we get
some Tex-mex?
Jackie...
The rooster talisman
possesses enormous power.
What's it do?
Manners, Jade.
Ancient legend
speaks of 12 talismans--
one for each animal
of the Chinese zodiac,
each possessing
a different magic.
What  kind of magic?
Jackie: Jade...
Legend also says
the talismans were scattered
to the 4 corners
of the globe.
If this or any talisman
should fall into evil hands...
Jackie'll
give 'em smackie
with his lightning
fists of steel!
Hey, when are you gonna
teach me some of your moves?
Later, Jade.
Humph.
Uncle,
do you really believe
in such a myth?
Ow!
Does that answer
your question?
Jade: Jackie,
check me out!
I got the moves!
Hee-yah!
Jade?
Not indoors!
Aah!
Fire!
My niece
is very sorry.
Whoa!
Aren't you,
niece?
I am such a dork.
I was just
trying to get you
to teach me, Jackie.
The wise seek power
within themselves.
The foolish seek it
within others.
Until you
harness the power
within yourself,
I cannot teach you.
Huh?
It means you must
have the discipline
to behave yourself.
Now eat your food.
Power within.
Got it.
Mmm.
Don't eat
like a baboon!
You should
chew your food.
(Swallowing and gulping)
Hello? Chew soup?
Help me out here.
She's your niece.
(Swallowing)
Ahh.
Tastes like chicken.
Ooh, dessert!
"Danger looms
in your future."
We must be very cautious.
Pff.
You listen to a cookie?
Evenin', chan.
Never mock the cookie.
Where's the talisman?
Come on, let's go.
Man: Check, please.
Hgggh!
Go, Jackie!
Unnh!
Ha!
Leave the rough stuff
to Jackie.
(Grunts)
Go, uncle.
Thank you
for dining with us.
(Gasps)
The talisman!
It was right there.
They took it!
Come on.
We can catch 'em.
Stay with uncle.
Come. Sit.
(Gasps)
The restaurant manager!
He looks  very angry.
Where?
Ayah.
Mr. valmont, sir.
It didn't go
quite as planned.
Regale me.
Well,
- we stomped chan.
Stomped him good.
But we didn't
see any talisman.
You will be punished.
Shendu: Hindsight, valmont.
But perhaps the blind
can be made to see
with the eyes of a dragon.
"Stay with uncle."
Tcch.
- Didn't say  which uncle.
Who has the keys?
He's coming!
(Jackie panting)
Hmm.
(Screams)
What's the big--
oh. Uh, hi.
You followed me?
What do you hear
when I talk?
Tell me, does it
sound like blah blah,
blah blah, blah blah
blah blah blah?
Jackie.
This is not funny.
This is dangerous.
(Muffled)
See?
Dangerous.
Come on!
Aren't you
gonna whomp 'em?
(Panting) Ancient
Chinese proverb--
do not fight
when you can run.
(Panting)
You go that way.
But--
go! You'll be safer
away from me.
(Panting)
Huh?
Why are they chasing  me?
Please have 4 wheels.
(Grunting)
Yes!
Nooo!
Jade!
Sorry. I'll bring it
right back.
Whoa!
Ohhhh!
Jackie, you rule!
(Gasps)
Aaaah!
Whoa! Hey, kid,
watch where you're going!
No!
Huh?
How'd I do that?
Whoa!
Jackie!
No cutting in line.
(Grunting)
Jackie!
Grab on!
Help.
Why do you want the girl?
Unnh!
Oh, ninja-man...
(Grunting)
I don't understand
why they were after--
Jackie, the coolest thing
ever happened.
I went right off the bridge,
but I didn't fall.
I, like, stopped in midair,
and then I ran back
just like in cartoons.
I can fly.
Jade,
enough fooling around.
Fooling around?
I just saved your butt!
Language, Jade.
The dark hand
is after you,
and I want to know why.
Unh.
The talisman.
I don't have it!
You guys have it.
Don'tcha?
Ungh.
Oh, uh...
Tohru: The tracker
points to the girl,
but she does not
have the talisman.
Well, it must be hidden
on her  somewhere, tohru.
I'm sure she didn't eat it.
Shendu:
Man  is much the wiser
when he looks within.
I understand.
And while you're at it...
Eliminate Jackie chan.
Jade: Hello?
Let me out of here!
I mean it!
Just wait'll
- the jackinator comes to.
You guys are gonna get
so creamed.
Jade?
Jackinator?
(Elevator bell rings)
Tohru: Aha.
Aha, what?
What's aha?
What are you
gonna do with that?
Oh, boy.
The rooster thing's
in my stomach.
But when did I--
the restaurant!
- The restaurant!
How could you not notice
you swallowed a golf ball?
I told you
to chew your food.
It was soup!
Never mind. We have
to get you out of here
before he gets
the talisman out of you.
The  magic uncle
was talking about.
I'll fly out!
(Groaning)
(Straining)
Jade,
even if you could fly--
and I'm not saying you can--
you are tied down
to a big, heavy table
which is bolted
to the floor!
Jade: Grrr!
Jackie: Jade?
Whoa.
Oh...You're
tele-tele-tele--
you can move things
with your mind!
No, with my stomach!
(Gasps)
Hold still.
Focus, focus,
focus, focus, focus.
Grrrrrr!
Why do you growl?
Heh?
Ungh!
Guess I have that
"power within"
you were talking about.
Not what I meant.
Now cut yourself free!
Uh, right.
(Grunting and groaning)
(Elevator bell rings)
Yo, big t, what's all
the racket down--
chan.
Jade,
run...Fly...Something!
Whoa!
Huh?
Get the girl.
Payback time, Jackson.
Nyah-nyah!
I  hate fish.
Why fight
when you can run?
You're learning.
This way!
(Elevator bell rings)
And when
you  can't run?
Don't watch.
Tcha. Like I'm
not gonna watch.
Nooo!
Unh!
I can take him!
Hee-yah!
Uhhh-uhhh-ahh.
(Grunting)
Whoa!
Stop helping!
Heh. Sorry.
Jackie!
Gotta hit tohru
with the biggest thing
I can find...
Himself!
Hoowahh!
Huh?
(Grunts)
He's big.
Can't hold much longer.
Oh, no.
(Grunts) Unh.
Whoa!
Heh, sorry.
I'm telling you,
uncle was right.
The talismans  do
possess magic powers.
Of course they do,
Jackie.
Now, why don't you
get some sleep.
All my stuff?
How'd it get here?
Until we can take down
the dark hand,
it's safer for you here
inside section 13.
I hope
it feels like home.
But...What about uncle?
Good magic is stronger
than  bad magic.
He refused to move.
Something about
messing up his
feng shui something.
Uncle is
very stubborn.
Stomach successfully pumped.
(Groaning)
Cock-a-doodle-do.
What about her?
I trust you'll keep
your niece in check.
(Jade gasps)
Does this mean
I'm a secret agent?
No!
- No!
Ohh!
Emmanuel: Hey, Jackie.
Why do you do all your
own stunts in your movies?
I was doing stunts
so many years.
The audience see
the actor or the bad guy--
they do all the stunts,
then the audience
just clapped.
Then I look at my friend,
"hey, that's not the actor.
That's me."
Then I promised myself,
one day,
when I become a star,
I want to do my own stunts.
I will turn around,
let the audience see
that's me,
that's not the double.
And also, I want
to show my children,
my grandchildren,
look, that's
your grandfather.
That's your--your father.
And besides...
I just like it.