Previously...
I am the one and only
king of the shadowkhan.
But tarakudo's rein
came to an end
when the spirits
of his generals
were trapped
within masks.
9 oni generals,
9 masks.
9 different tribes
of shadowkhan?
We must remove
demon mask
from host
in order
to defeat
shadowkhan!
Unh!
Whoa!
Getting warm.
Warmer.
Boiling.
Cooked.
This seems
way too easy,
doesn't it?
Easy?! We are at
the bottom of the ocean!
Yeah, but this is
the last oni mask.
Where are tarakudo
and his goons?
Where's the ultimate
good-versus-evil
battle royale?
I, for one,
am not complaining.
So our quest
is complete?
As you have
researched, tohru.
9 masks,
9 demon generals.
Which means
we won't be needing
these Hana fuda
cards anymore.
(Gasps)
Then why does tohru
have the willies?
(Gasps)
The masks...
Are destroyed?
That's a good
thing, right?
Oni.
How is this
happening?
Uncle not sure.
But it
must be your fault!
Many thanks
for our freedom, chan.
Now it is time
to surrender yours.
Aah!
Eat dragon heat!
Ungh!
Go, go, go!
Summon the dark ones.
Shadowkhan's
greatest hits.
Aah!
Hyah!
Whoa. New guy.
Ninja number 9.
What?!
(Pounding on door)
Captain black,
we have a breach.
Alert your agents and--
magic must
defeat magic.
We must
do research now.
Whoa, Nelly.
Uh, think
we can take 'em?
Uncle: Dark forces
are not attacking?
The combined power
of the 9 masks
can summon
enough shadowkhan
to engulf the earth
in eternal darkness.
(Chanting in Chinese)
Chi spell
will protect shop
from dark magic.
Sensei, none
of this makes sense.
I have reviewed
every inch of the legend.
Every inch?
Uh...It is a warning.
"Never conjoin
the 9 masks
in one location."
Hence the scattering
across the earth part.
Aiyah. The darkness
is already
taking hold.
All good magic
will soon fade
to nothing.
(Pounding on door)
(Gulps)
Something
wants in.
El toro!
Viper!
What are you
doing here?
Well, it looked
as if the world
was coming to an end...
And we
figured you four
might know a thing
or two about it.
So, we're supposed
to put a kibosh
on a vast army
of ninja magic how?
We must gather
the spell ingredients
to defeat
their leaders.
Japanese steel,
silk--ow!
Did you not
see the 9 masks
destroyed before
your very eyes?
The spells
which originally
defeated the demons
will no longer work
because the masks
which imprison them
no longer exist.
Our only hope
is to defeat tarakudo,
lord of all oni,
king of all shadowkhan.
But how do you beat a big
floating spirit-head?
Mm-mmm-mm.
(Cell phone rings)
Captain black,
are you all right?
Been better, Jackie.
We're operating
from a mobile unit.
The oni
seized headquarters.
Satellite
surveillance indicates
they're on their way
out of town
in teams of 2,
heading north, south,
east, and west.
No doubt to stake
their claims
to the 4 corners
of the globe.
Unless the j-team
stops them before
they get that far.
Be careful,
my friend.
Battle the oni?
Without the special
spell ingredients?
The fight
may be more fair
than you think, tohru.
The oni generals
will be unable
to summon their ninjas
without disrupting
the shroud of darkness.
Besides, t,
we're still
packin' t-power.
Snake has
my name on it.
I call dragon!
Dog and rat?
Oh! You're gonna hog
all the cool ones!
Jade, you will
remain here.
What?! No way!
Jade, please.
I could not
live with myself
if something
happened to you.
Aw.
Uncle: Today...
Dark forces must pay!
This bridge is closed.
(Growling)
Watch out, boys.
Snake in the grass.
(Moans)
Sensei?
The willies?
Ha ha.
Pardon me.
- I dropped something.
Antler action!
Oh, yeah!
I'm bad! You're sad!
Supermoose?
Jackie!
Jade, you were
supposed to be--
I decided I couldn't
live with myself
if something
happened to you.
Supermoose: Can you
feel the love?
Well, can ya, punk?
Many thanks
for removing
that ghastly
onion spell,
general ikazuki.
Section 13
- is far more inviting
with you
running things.
And our
shadow armies
are advancing
as we speak,
master tarakudo.
Within hours
this planet
will succumb
to the forces of--
ooh.
The forces of ooh?
I'm picking up
some...Interference.
Aah!
Ya-ha!
Surf's up.
What?
Hmm.
You're quite a catch.
Yah!
Ah-choo!
Why did you
choose kittens?
Uncle is allergic!
All aboard!
Aiyah!
Ungh!
Uppercut!
Right hook!
Left antler!
(Jade cheers)
Getting...Weak.
Oh!
(Chuckles)
Nice try, gang.
It would seem humankind's
last line of defense...
Has reached
the end of
their line.
Allowing our
generals to resume
their progress
toward making
this world...
A much darker place.
(Groaning with strain)
Gel or no gel,
my hair won't cut it.
Anyone have
a Bobby pin?
Credit card?
Hana fuda card.
Whoa.
It cannot be.
A tenth mask.
Jade: Look who it is.
Tohru: Tarakudo.
But tohru's
research indicated
there are only 9.
Maybe tohru messed up
that part, too.
Each mask was created by
ancient good chi wizards
to imprison the demon
generals within them.
What if a tenth mask
were forged?
Intended to
trap tarakudo
like the others.
But the king
of the shadowkhan
got to it first.
If a tenth
mask exists,
the cards will tell us
where to find it.
(Gasps)
Uncle,
what is it?
Tarakudo
concealed the mask
in the one place
no mortal would
dare enter:
The shadow realm.
But how do we
get out of here?
And into there?
We need not
leave this cell.
All: Huh?
All shadows lead
to the shadow realm.
All that we need
is dark magic
to take us there.
Easy!
As any ex-queen
of the shadowkhan
can tell you,
wearing the sign
of tarakudo
gives you control
over ninjas.
It's tattoo time.
No, Jade.
It is far
too dangerous,
even if you have
done it before.
I volunteer tohru.
Wha--wha? M-m-me?
(Spits)
There is no better time
to face your fear of oni
than when
fate of world
is at stake.
Now, enter shadow
realm quickly!
How do I--
call upon darkness,
which now lies within you.
(Groans)
You're
the boss, t.
Just tell 'em
what to do.
Um, ahem.
Take me to--(Gulps)
The shadow realm.
Aah!
One more thing!
Uncle never leave shop
without magic socks.
He cannot
be serious.
Be thankful
he's not talking underwear.
This thread will
be your lifeline
to our realm.
Tug firmly
when you find mask.
(Moans)
Whoa!
Tohru had better
find mask
before we run
out of sock...
And before evil
within tattoo
consumes his
very being.
Whoa!
Tohru has mask.
Reel him in quickly!
Come on back, t.
Tohru!
You did it!
You have located
the tenth mask.
(Roars)
Tarakudo!
Aiyah!
We have lost tohru
to dark forces!
Who calls my na--
(Gasps)
I shall
destroy you all!
Aiyah!
All: Aah!
(Groans)
No one
touches my face.
Ikazuki!
Argh!
Oof!
Ooh!
Oni cream sandwich.
Jackie!
Uncle needs ingredient
to complete spell!
What ingredient?!
Hair of
Japanese samurai!
Heh heh heh.
A shame
that ancient Japan
is ancient history.
Argh!
Tohru's Japanese.
Think he has
any samurai blood?
One way
to find out.
Sorry, big guy.
Argh!
Just a little
off the topknot.
Oh, no, you don't!
Going up, handsome.
(Chanting in Chinese)
Whoa!
Whoa.
Tarakudo has legs.
Did your spell
do this, uncle?
Of course.
It is the only way
for mask to
stick to face.
Over my demon body.
No mental powers,
tarakudo?
It is about time
you fought fair.
Aah! Whoa!
Hyah!
Oh!
Now, Mr. chan,
if you'll hand over
the mask,
I'll take care
to dispose of it
once and for all.
Jade: Tarakudo?
Heads up!
No!
Noooooo!
Jackie.
Ohh.
10 demons and
a gajillion ninjas
in one teeny
tiny mask?
Cozy.
So...There are
no more masks?
Does tohru
have willies? No?
Then there
are no more masks.
Thanks to
the winning team.
Hey, Jackie,
do you ever go fishing?
Very, very little chance.
I never go,
like, call my friends,
"let's go fish today.
Holiday." Never.
Only when we are
- on the filming, on the boat.
Then I fish a little bit.
I'm not
this kind of person.
First, I hate water. Why?
Because I get seasick
when I'm on the boat.
Besides, I don't like
to spend so much time
to waiting, waiting.
I'd rather...Training.
But I do go,
but little time.