Ah. Always come back
from Reno estate sale
with good finds
for shop!
Yes, uncle. And always
such big finds.
You should buy
bigger car!
More trunk space.
More trunk space
is so not a bad idea.
Jackie: Look!
Old west ghost town!
Oh! We must visit.
Ay-eee-ahh! Ghosts are nothing
to trifle with!
Tch. Ghost town
just means
old and deserted
and boring.
I've heard that my
great-great-grandfather
came out west and lived
in a cowboy town.
I'm curious to see
what one looks like.
Driver's privilege.
Any ghost here
better not show face!
You do not want to mess
with uncle's herbs!
Hmm. Not much here.
Duh!
(Gasps) Ghost!
(Gasps)
Ayyy-yaaa!
Ghost?
Kind of.
The ghost of Jackie.
"The Hong Kong kid."
Ahhh-yaaa!
Do not scare
uncle like that!
Amazing! The picture
looks just like me!
This book must be about
my great-great-grandfather.
Fine. Take home.
Make good bedtime story.
I wanna hear it now.
Me, too.
Ahem.
"It was the end
of a long day
for the men and women working
to build the new railroad."
(Toot)
Ok, people.
Time to knock off.
Whew! This is
thirsty work.
I'm going to town for
a nice frosty ginger ale.
Care to join me, friend?
Railroad workers
are not welcome in town.
Oh, don't be silly.
We are in America now.
We can go anywhere
we please.
(Humming)
Oh, hello.
Good day.
Hot one, isn't it?
Ah...A cafe.
(Boisterous
conversation)
Uh...Howdy,
partners?
Well, looky here,
boys.
We got us
a railroad worker.
Railroad workers ain't allowed
in this here establishment.
Ain't that right,
Maureen?
I don't want
no trouble here.
Oh, no trouble, ma'am.
I would just like a ginger ale
with lots of ice, please.
Very thirsty.
I've been working
on the railroad, uh...
All the livelong day?
We can't have no lawman
sticking his nose
in our business, mayor.
And you shan't.
I took care
of the last sheriff,
didn't I?
Yeah. Well...
It's the next one
we gotta worry about.
Can't risk nobody
putting the kibosh
on our big plan.
Hmm. I see your point.
So why not pick
a patsy for the job?
Someone who'd offer
no resistance...
A bumbler. A fool.
Someone like...
That was not very
nice of you--
ooh!
Him.
This is a very
great honor, Mr. mayor.
But why me?
Well,
because you're...
A railroad worker!
And railroad workers
always make
the best sheriffs.
I did not know that.
I won't let you down.
No, I'm quite sure
you won't.
Niece: Uncle Jackie?
Uh...I am Jackie.
I am your niece...
Just arrived
from Hong Kong.
This is so cool!
She's my long-lost,
great-great something
or other!
I betcha she looked
exactly like me.
Actually, it says here
that the sheriff's niece
was very tall
and 15 years old.
Must be a typo.
I trust the preparations
are complete?
Indeed they are, shendu.
The stagecoach
comes through town
tomorrow morning,
and the gold
and the antiquities
bound for the new
San Francisco museum
shall be on board.
And among those
antiquities
the horse talisman,
possessing the power
to free me from this
miserable stone casement!
You do remember
our little deal.
Once free,
you will help us
get even more gold.
Uh, at your earliest
convenience, of course.
You'll probably
want to freshen up,
stretch the old legs--
and what steps
have you taken
to prevent
any interference?
I've handpicked
a new sheriff.
A real find.
Yeech. I hate unpacking.
It is  such hard work.
You should try
building a railroad.
"The sheriff
"soon earned the respect
of the townspeople
because of his bravery
and heroism."
Oh, it's black Bart,
sheriff!
He's loose!
Oh, bad outlaw?
My cat!
He won't come down
off that roof!
Here, kitty kitty.
Got you!
Whoa!
Whoa-oa-oa!
Uh--
old lady: Oh!
Naughty little
black Bart!
You had mama
worried sick.
Oh, thank you, sheriff.
You're welcome.
Niece, I will see you
when the big hand
is on the 6.
"The town had never had
a lawman like sheriff Jackie.
"No lawbreaker was immune
from his tough
but fair brand
of frontier justice."
You will have to
pick those up.
We have very strict laws
against littering.
Just feedin'
my mule, sheriff.
I can appreciate that,
but I was hired
to clean up this town, so...
So you either throw 'em
in the trash can,
or we throw you
in the pokey.
Ha ha! Yeah, sure.
Whatever you say,
girlie.
Girlie?  I happen to be
his deputy.
Niece, you are not
my deputy.
But she is right
about--oh!
"The job sometimes
got rough,
"but wet or dry,
the sheriff would
always get his man."
Perhaps a night in jail
will make you think twice
before breaking
the law again.
Uh-oh.
I would like you
to go talk
to the mayor.
Deputy business?
Uh...Yes!
Jail cell
needs repair.
Tch! Fine.
Doubt Annie oakley
started out like this.
This new sheriff's
a real burr
in my saddle, mayor.
Thought he was
supposed to be
a patsy.
Oh, please.
Apprehending
litterbugs?
Saving kittens?
This fellow's nothing
but a dim bulb
with a shiny badge.
I guarantee
our stagecoach heist
will go off
without a hitch.
Well, well, well.
We've got us a no-good,
snoopin' little varmint.
What do you think
we ought to do with her?
How's about we tie her
to a cactus out
on the prairie,
let the buzzards decide?
Jackie, reading: "There
she was, the sheriff's niece,
"caught red-handed
spying on the bad guys.
Suddenly, she opened
her mouth and--"
(speaking
Chinese)
She obviously
understands no English.
Let her go.
Whoa! Now, that was
one smooth move.
"The niece tipped off
the sheriff
about what she
had heard."
The mayor?
Those nice men?
Oh, you must have
misunderstood.
Hello!
I was the one
talking Chinese,
not them!
I understood
perfectly!
Uh, yes.
I am heading out
to pay a visit
to an old friend.
Please mind the office.
Right! And work
on the case.
Hey, quite a load
you're carryin'!
Payroll for every town
from here to Tahoe,
plus some
far-east artifacts
for that new museum
in San Fran.
Well, thanks, partner.
See you next month.
It's so shiny!
I Polish it often.
Ah...From
railroad worker
to sheriff.
It seems...
Impossible.
Actually, railroad workers
make the best sheriffs.
I did not know that.
Hey-yah!
Tch, tch, tch.
Speeding in a railroad
construction zone.
Please, stop the--oh!
(Coughing)
You are speeding!
Pull over!
Oh!
Uh-oh.
(Small voice)
Ow.
Hey, this stage
is carrying
government--
aah! Oof!
Deputy niece
to the rescue!
must wait here.
I'm talkin' some
serious dinero!
Please pull over!
He said please!
Yeah, right!
I guess here is where
I earn my pay.
Ow! Oh--gaaah!
Oh--oh--ow--ow!
Bad day!
Wha--aah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
You are in
very big trouble!
Not as big as you!
Uh--ravine!
Hit the brakes!
Sorry,
railroad worker.
I'm off this train!
Aah! Bad day at black rock!
Jackie, reading:
"It looked like curtains
for sheriff Jackie,
when--" huh?
Why did you stop?
What happened next?
The page is missing!
Boring story,
anyway.
Baa! That is the fate
of my great-great-grandfather
that you are using
to clean your glasses!
(Clears throat)
"In a spectacular feat
of derring-do,
sheriff Jackie
took control of the reins."
Thank you, sheriff.
There's
a whole lotta folks
counting on that cargo
for their paychecks.
Just doin' my job.
I grow impatient, valmont!
I trust your men
were able to pull off
a simple robbery.
Rest assured, shendu,
my boys will be
rendezvousing
with us momentarily.
You see?
Uh...Ran into
a little trouble.
That sheriff you hired.
You didn't get the gold?!
Shendu: Fools!
Hey, hold on,
shen-dude.
Ain't exactly
like we came back
empty-handed.
(Clicks tongue)
Got the horse
off the stagecoach,
just like you asked.
I didn't want the horse!
I wanted the horse talisman!
Oh. Uh...
What's a talisman?
Valmont: You have
my word, shendu.
They will be tarred
and feathered.
But first things first--
this meddling sheriff
must pay.
Count me out.
That guy ain't human.
And that is why
you shall use magic
to defeat him.
So...How do we
work 'em?
You don't.
The magic works
by itself.
Neat-o.
You dare to spy on  me?!
Uh-oh...
Whoa!
The stagecoach company
will probably give you
a big reward.
"Meet us for a showdown at
the lucky corral at high noon.
Signed, the bad guys."
Oh, this is very bad.
What are you
talking about?
You bushwhacked 'em
last time, didn't you?
You'll do it again.
No. They will be using
powerful...
Unh...Unh.
Powerful what?
Tell me!
"Sheriff Jackie
was very worried,
"certain he would
lose the showdown
"now that the bad guys would
be using powerful something.
"But then his niece
saw something
through the window
that gave her hope."
Who is that?
A very wise man
from the old country.
Who will be the first to try
my Shanghai surprise elixir?
Very powerful.
Good for digestion.
Hi. Remember me?
Ah, girl from Hong Kong.
Look different.
Thought you were 15
and taller.
It was a typo.
Ahh...Now story
getting interesting.
See? I told--ow.
Keep reading.
"After he finished
selling 10 bottles
"of good-for-digestion elixir,
"the peddler took
the sheriff and his niece
into the back
of his wagon."
Oh, what is that,
an immortality potion?
Green tea. Drink.
Uh, no, thank you.
I--I do not mean to be rude,
but as I told you,
I have been challenged
to a big showdown
at high noon.
We were sort of hoping
you had some of that
wise-wizard-from-
the-old-country
kind of advice.
I do. Don't go.
That's it, "don't go"?
Best I could do
on short notice.
I have to go.
It is my sworn duty
as a sheriff.
Soon to be ex-sheriff.
"The old clock tower
struck high noon
as sheriff Jackie--" oh...
What's up, Jackie?
Keep reading.
I can't.
I never learned what became
of my great-great-grandfather.
What if this
was his last roundup?
Give it here!
Uncle hate suspense.
"Old clock tower
struck high noon
"as sheriff Jackie started
long walk to lucky corral.
"From opposite direction,
outlaws headed
that way as well."
"Let's do this,"
said the bad guy.
"T?" What's that
supposed to mean,
he wants some tea?
Time-out.
No firearms, ok?
A fair fight.
Fair fight? Sure.
No problem-o, amigo.
Gotta tip my hat
to you, sheriff.
Anytime now.
Ahh, magic.
Oh, more bad day,
more bad day!
You forgot your hat.
Huh?
(Muffled grumbling)
Oh, this ought
to be good.
Daaaaahhhhh!
Ohh, ohh, ohh.
Wee-hah! Hog-tied
like a heifer.
Ohh.
Hold this, please.
Huh? What the--
whoa, whoa. Guuh.
(Grunts)
Uh, we had an agreement--
no firearms.
Guess I missed that meeting.
Ever been locked in
a 4-foot stall with
a bucking bronco?
Once.
Jade:
¶ oh, Mr. mayor... ¶
huh?
Hmm, Shanghai surprise
good for digestion,
bad for everything else.
I hope you all
enjoy your new home.
I reckon we had you
wrong, sheriff.
You're ok.
Like to thank you for
cleaning up the town.
Oh, well, you know
what they say--
railroad workers always
make the best sheriffs.
Speaking of which...
Please welcome
your new sheriff.
New sheriff?
Hmm, shiny.
I am retiring.
I miss the fresh air,
the open spaces.
I am going back
to the railroad.
Looks like peddler
has new assistant.
Really?
Cool. What do I do?
Make tea.
Ach...
Uh, old peddler man,
where are you heading?
Railroad is the other way.
Forget railroad.
Plenty more bottle
of elixir to sell.
Yeah. And plenty
more towns
that need
cleaning up.
"And off they rode,
into sunset. The end."
Oh, it is nice to know
that my ancestor
was such a hero.
-Jackie a hero?
Hoo!
- Ha!
It was old-west Jade
who saved his butt.
You're crazy.
Old peddler man saved day.
Hey, Jackie?
Yes?
What's your Chinese name?
My real, real, real name
is called fong shu lo.
In the school
in Australia,
they asked me,
"what's your name?"
I said, "my name
Chang Kong sun."
"No, no, no.
Ok, your name Steven."
Yeah, I becoming a Steven.
In the factory,
the building bilker
asked me what's my name.
My friend said, "Jack."
J-a-c-k.
Then, after I know
a little bit English,
then a j-a-c--Jackie.
I think I like rhythm.
Jackie.