[Grunting]
[Grunt] Oh...
Sensei, perhaps
we should rest.
What? Uncle
has barely
broken a sweat!
Too...Weak.
Can't...Go on.
Uh, have an
energy bar, Jade.
Can't...Chew,
no energy.
Uncle, the high altitude
of the himalayas
requires a slower pace.
But forces of darkness
require a quicker pace.
We must find the ox
which possesses the power
of super-strength
before daolon wong does.
[Gasps]
Locator indicates
ox is on opposite
side of mountain.
We must go back down
and come up other way.
[Both groan]
don't you
have a spell
that'll just
poof us over there?
Anything?
Abracadabra?
Uh-oh!
All: Avalanche!
Come on!
Sensei.
Jackie: A yak?
A super-strong yak.
A yak is a type of ox.
And this yak
is the ox we seek.
But why did it
plow through
the mountain?
He wants
my energy bar.
He must have
a super-strong
sense of smell, too.
We must bring the ox
to the sanctuary of
the Ben shui temple
before the forces
of dark chi
descend upon us.
[Chuckles] Yo!
Consider yourselves
descended upon, gramps.
You know how much
we care about you guys,
but daolon wong's
been riding us
to get rid of you,
once and for all.
We're sure
gonna miss ya.
Say goodbye,
chan.
Uh, goodbye, chan?
Uh, where'd they go?
We blew it! Again!
All in favor
of keeping
this little
setback quiet
say, "aye."
Fools!
Give me just one reason
why I should not
destroy you instantly!
'Cause, things
are about to change?
No more
embarrassing
defeats.
Cross our hearts
and hope to--
aah!
Flying elephant
stomps rat!
An intruder?
Hak foo! What
brings you to town?
Woodchuck
Chucks weasel!
Most impressive.
Dude, dude, dude,
you're making us
ook-lay ad-bay
in front of
the oss-bay.
Shark bites
bottom-feeder!
I understand you
have been seeking
the powers of
the talismans,
witch doctor.
Allow me to suggest
you end your quest
for the ox,
as it is a power
I intend to obtain.
Ung!
Then obtain it,
dear warrior, for me.
Aah!
Uncle has been
devising a spell
to transfer
the talisman powers
from the animals
we have collected.
Tohru,
as my apprentice,
you will seek
proper vessels
with which
to contain the powers.
How about
putting the speedy
rabbit power
in wristwatch form?
That way, if you see
you're running late,
boom! You're there!
Or the healing
horse thermometer?
By the time you check
your temperature,
you're already better.
The sheep-powered
pillow...Stay cozy while
you astral project.
[Moans]
Uh, ok,
scratch the pillow.
No, daolon wong is near.
We must
protect the ox.
Ox not important.
Power within ox is.
I will attempt
to keep the magic
from daolon wong's reach
by casting new
transfer spell.
May I assist
you, sensei?
Yes, while
I am in trance,
please keep
birds off me.
But where will you
transfer the power to?
Uncle?
Ahh, the power
of super-strength.
Olly olly oxen free.
Hyah!
Zhen!
All: Hak foo?
So, you have met.
Acquaint
your friends
with the new you.
With pleasure, master.
Phoenix flies to moon!
Meteor brings
mass extinction!
Jade, please keep
the birds off your uncle.
Aw.
Tornado decimates
trailer park!
Oh, boy.
Ha ha ha!
Huh?
Does the good wizard
think he will
outsmart me?
I don't know what
the anti-uncle's up to,
but this'll teach him
to drop his guard
when Jade
is in the house.
Hyah!
Oof!
Huh? Invisible
force field? No fair!
[Uncle chants]
[Gasps] Daolon wong!
Good! You have not
completed the transfer,
nor will you.
Hot cha!
Hyah!
Ooh!
Tohru: Hak foo!
This is where
you go poof.
I do not poof.
[Slaps and grunts]
Your turn.
Hurry, uncle.
You are headstrong,
wizard.
But not for long.
[Chants]
Step away
from the yak.
Yes.
What?
The talisman power
is no longer here!
Where is it?
Ooh, outsmarted
by the uncster.
Was I?
Jackieeee!
[All gasp]
Your uncster
and myself have
much to discuss.
Uncle?
- Sensei?
Say something!
- Wake up!
Wake up!
But how can daolon wong
have uncle's head
if uncle's head's
still on his body?
Ah, the dark wizard
possesses your uncle's
spiritual head...
Essentially
his life force.
Without it,
he is doomed to remain
in this dormant state.
We have to rescue
sensei's life force!
And we must do so
before daolon wong makes it--
uh, uncle, tell him
where he hid the ox's power.
Daolon
can't get the power
if we find it first.
But we cannot find it
without sensei.
The locator
was destroyed
in the avalanche.
Tch! You're uncle's
apprentice.
You'll whip up
a new one.
But I have not had
much practice at such
complicated spells.
Tch! Piece of cake.
Come on, Jackie,
we're goin'
head-hunting.
Uh, Jade, perhaps
you should remain here
and be
tohru's apprentice.
Oh, right.
Hak foo's, like,
all mondo-mega-
super-turbo-charged.
Way dangerous.
Yes, it is.
So, do you want
a piece of uncle?
I will just require
my other pieces first.
If you ever want to see
your pieces again,
surrender the location
of the ox power.
Very well.
You may find
what you are looking for
in a secret place,
very close to...
[Blows a raspberry]
Fool! The orb
of q'uan lo will
reveal your secrets,
exposing those thoughts
you hold most dear.
Mung bean sandwich?
Uncle is hungry.
Ha ha!
I shall peel
back the layers.
What is this?
[Cries]
Your destiny, evil one.
Pah! I shall
travel deeper
into the recesses
of your mind.
Yeeeees!
Zhen!
Retrieve the power.
And, finally,
a new cowbell.
Nothing
happened.
[Gasps]
Sir, you are crazy
if you think
big mouth hak foo
will obtain ox power.
Oh? And who
will stop him?
Jackie!
Your nephew has
already demonstrated
that he is no match
for my most
savage warrior.
Why has your
incessant mouth
suddenly
grown silent?
[Imitates uncle]
Uh, one more thing...
Who am I kidding?
Gan! Ren! Chui!
Stop chan!
Who, us?
Why don't you ask
your precious hak foo?
Why don't I turn you
inside out?
We're on it!
You say, "jump"...
We say, "how high?".
Jackie, you are
going wrong way!
I know where
I am going. Wha!
See? Wrong way!
Aah!
Uncle: Stop my head!
Aiyaaah!
Jackieeeee!
My ball!
Catch!
Jackieeee!
Hhbbrrrbbb!
Are you trying
to give uncle
headache?
I am trying to release you!
The orb is magic!
Magic must open
magic!
[Sighs]
Of course it does.
Now, don't worry, t.
The tenth try is
usually the charm.
You did it, tohru!
No. It should only glow
when the power is near.
[Both sigh] Ohhh...
Duh!
Unc hid the power
the last place
anyone would think
of looking!
Himself!
You did do it, tohru!
We did it.
Hak foo: Happy time...
Is over.
Leave uncle alone!
No!
Uncle, why does hak foo
have your body?
Because that is where
the power of the ox
resides.
Of course it is.
Sensei, are you all right?
Does uncle look
all right?!
Quickly, tohru,
you must find a spell
to release me!
Uh--m-me?
But isn't it Jackie's
turn to cast a spell?
Jackie must retrieve
the rest of uncle
from hak foo!
[Gulp] Yes, I must.
Do you have the old man?
Indeed, master.
Good. My Patience
wears thin.
You will pay
for your cleverness,
good wizard,
for once I absorb
the power within you,
I shall see to it
that your spirit head
has nowhere to return.
Tohru: Uh...One pair
of dried bat wings.
Check!
Uh...One cedar leaf.
Check.
3 spines of urchin.
Uncle: 3 spines?!
Do you want uncle's
head to explode?
But the spell book says--
book is only a guide!
Good chi wizard
makes spell his own!
[Groans] Oh...
[Daolon chanting]
Uh...Wait, uh...
Time out!
Look at yourself,
hak foo!
Daolon has made you
his lackey...His slave.
Is this really
how you want to be--
a freak?
Yes.
Rrrahhh!
Daahh!
[Cough, cough, cough]
Pah!
One more thing...
Be sure cauldron
bubbles at proper rate.
One more thing...
Do not forget to channel
good chi.
One more thing...
Do not rush chanting!
Release the talking
head already
before he comes up
with 3 more things!
[Inhales]
[Chanting]
Why could uncle
not have transferred
the super-strength
to my body?
Shall I...Make a wish?
Hot chaaaa!
Huh?!
Pffft!
Hello!
And goodbye!
Aah!
Who wants
a piece of uncle?
Aah!
Tyrannosaurus swats fly!
Bbblllbb!
Volcano blows top!
Uncle: One more thing...
Aah!
What do you know?
He does poof!
Hey! Welcome
to loserville.
Aw, don't look
so sad, big guy.
Yeah. You're one
of us now.
[Growls] Shut up!
Strength cannot
withstand heat.
Tohru: Daolon wong!
Go, chi wiz!
Well, muscles...
Perhaps we should get
your super-strength
back to section 13
while the going
is good.
I will transfer
the power back into
the ox
with tohru's help.
My apprentice
will make a fine
wizard some day.
[Scurrying
sound]
[Chuckles] Yes...
Some day.
Hey, Jackie,
how do you control
your anger?
I always forgive
somebody.
But when I'm young,
no, I'm not--
they harm me,
I harm them back.
The whole day--
[Breathing hard]
"This guy..."
No. Right now I just...
Forget it.
I really control
my anger.