(Chanting)
The 12th and final
locator spell
has located nothing.
Duh!
It couldn't
find a dragon
'cause
they're extinct.
The only one left on
earth was shendu,
and he's doing afterlife
in the inter-dimensional
slammer.
Jade, we had to be
absolutely certain
that the power of combustion
has not found a host.
With no dragon
to inhabit,
the power
remains lost...
Safe from
the forces of darkness.
As long as daolon wong
roams the earth,
nothing remains safe.
Your answer,
most malevolent
of fire breathers?
It would seem
you have summoned me
merely to humor me, wizard.
For to obtain the power
of combustion,
you would require
- a living, earthbound dragon,
which I am not.
You underestimate
my talents, lord shendu.
As the most malevolent
of dark chi masters,
I know a multitude
of ancient spells,
some of which
might restore you.
Ah.
Then you may have my
rightful power, daolon wong,
if you find the spell that
will allow me to live again.
Heads up!
Move it or lose it!
Uh, Jackie?
Research, captain black.
We have to be prepared.
With no more talisman-powered
animals on the loose--
it's only a matter of
time before daolon wong
comes after the ones
in the vault.
I'll beef up security
and--ow!
Magic must defeat magic!
And the powers will be
difficult to safeguard
until they are
- transferred from the animals
into new talismans.
(Uncle chanting)
The first of the new talismans
has been empowered.
All right!
Let's beta test--
oh. That was
my best one.
The making of a talisman
is very tricky business.
The spells
which created them
have been lost
for thousands of years.
Hey, Jackie,
when uncle gets the powers
out of these guys,
we still get
to keep 'em, right?
Jade, the animals
have owners,
or natural habitats.
don't you think
we should return them?
What? No, they're my pets!
Who has a pet ox?
Can we at least
keep scruffy? Please?
He belongs at section 13.
He's a natural-born
crime fighter,
and he's already
housebroken, and--
(growls and barks)
And he keeps
the neighbors awake
with his barking.
(Gasps) Jackie!
(Gasps) A dragon is near.
(Chanting)
Return to us, shendu.
Rise again!
Jackie: First it says
there isn't a dragon.
Now it says there is?
Are you sure the locator
is working properly?
Uncle wishes
that it were not,
but clearly,
it guides us.
If the locator
detects a dragon now,
someone must be
conjuring one.
Tch. And I'll
give you one guess
which someone that is.
Jade, this
is too dangerous.
We could be
facing a dragon.
Not just any dragon.
(Gasps)
Aiyaa!
No.
Jackie: Shendu!
Awaken!
(Chanting)
Uhh!
Gan! Ren! Chui! Zhen!
Hey!
Backyard barbecue.
What are
we grilling?
Jackie chan!
Let's tenderize him.
Volcano incinerates
field mouse!
Gotta stop this spell
before the barbecue
becomes a birthday party.
You are too late, child.
Urrr--
uhh!
Sorry.
Cannot hear you.
You must have a frog
in your throat.
(Ribbit)
Ptha!
Cheap tricks.
(Chanting)
Uhh!
Whoa! Hot--hot--
hot--hot--hot--hot!
Duh, Jade.
Hurricane kick!
Earthquake fist!
Asteroid belt!
Meteor pummels mountain!
Hot bath?
Cold shower.
(Chanting)
Uhh! Ah! Uhh!
Jackie!
(Daolon chanting)
Aaahhhhh!
Greetings, everyone.
It is great to be back.
Yo, shendude.
Uh, long time
no breathe.
Yeah.
Chui: Happy, uh,
re-birthday. Ha ha.
Yes.
My prize approaches.
The power of
combustion--
belongs to me!
Mega bad day.
Ahh.
Feel the burn.
Aah!
- Aah!
But brother of darkness,
we had an arrangement.
I may be a noble dragon,
but I am also
a demon sorcerer
and not known
for keeping promises.
Aaaahhha.
Quickly!
I have a plan!
I still possess
2 talisman powers
with which
to destroy you.
(Gasps)
Levitation!
Heat-beam eyes!
What thoughtful
birthday presents.
No!
Uhh!
And you will tell me where
to retrieve my other powers,
after I have
had the pleasure
of quick-frying Jackie--
uhh...
Jade: Bolting for it?
That was your big plan?
Shendu will attempt
to reclaim what once
belonged to him.
The other talisman powers.
P.A.: Condition red.
Security lockdown initiated.
We're on full
tactical alert.
I know,
magic must
defeat magic.
Which is why you must
buy uncle all the time
he requires.
Tohru!
Jade!
Research!
You heard him, men.
Engage heavy artillery.
Radar operator: Sir,
we have a bogey approaching
from the perimeter.
A big one.
This is it.
If the demon breeches
the outer defenses,
we make our stand here.
Protect that vault.
(Explosion)
Captain black,
it may not be possible
to defend the vault.
Aiyaa!
Cannot find spell
I'm looking for!
Uncle needs
more time!
I will buy uncle
as much time as I can.
Jackie?
(Rumbling)
Hold your positions.
Fire.
Someone say "fire?"
Ahh!
Surrender the animals, or--
you want them?
Come and get them.
(Roars)
Stop fooling!
Help uncle research!
Everyone,
grab a book.
Nice monkey.
Please climb off
my head.
Power of levitation,
right.
Tch. Just be glad
he doesn't have
super-speed.
Dwah! Jade!
Are you crazy?
If anything has ever
been too dangerous,
this is it!
Hey, where
my pooch goes, I go.
(Ruff)
Aah!
I know
you are hungry,
but I need this
to drive.
Huh? Dah!
The astral projection
talisman.
Jackie!
Not a good time
for a nap!
Aahhhhh!
One cannot begin anew
without burning
a few Bridges.
Bwaaaaa!
- Bwaaaaa!
Shendu's hot on our tail.
We gotta jump it!
It won't go any faster!
Hello? Rabbit power!
Too fast! Too fast!
Aah!
- Bwaa!
(Tires screech)
Everybody out!
Keep moving!
(Sighs)
At least we put
some distance
between us and--
aah!
- Bwaa!
Both: Hurry, uncle.
Uncle: Hot cha!
You found a way
to take down shendu?
Shendu not important!
I found way to defeat
the person who knows
how to defeat shendu,
even though
that person does not
yet know he knows.
Jade!
Take the animals!
Run!
Jade: Trying!
Jackie!
Eat heat beams!
(Oink)
(Nervous laugh)
Sorry. Wrong pig.
Uhh!
Bad day! Bad day!
Bad day!
Hey, what do you get
when you cross an ox
with a rabbit?
A ram!
Uhh!
Go! Quick! Run!
(Ruff ruff ruff)
Uhh!
(Gasps) Scruffy! No!
At last, it is time
to reabsorb my powers!
Daolon:
Gan! Ren! Chui! Zhen!
Prepare for battle!
Wow!
- We rock!
I'm feeling
prepared!
That thieving
lizard shendu
will pay dearly
for his betrayal.
(Uncle and tohru chanting)
Going somewhere?
Attack!
(Chanting)
All: Aah!
(Gasps)
No!
We are weak.
We're human.
We're free.
Nah-uh.
Busted.
Uh--
phaa--
wh--(Whimpers)
Mr. wong,
you're under arrest.
You may be disenchanted,
but I believe
you still know many
ancient spells.
I will tell you
nothing!
Do you want to have
your revenge
upon shendu? Yes?
Then start talking
to uncle!
(Grumbling)
(Grunting)
And tiger makes 12.
Both: Whoa! Uuhh!
Which means I now possess
so many ways
to make you suffer!
(Crowd, chanting)
No! No, not again!
(Chanting)
Stop!
(Moans)
The extraction spell
is working!
The powers are gonna
go back into
the animals?
Wait and see.
Aarrrrgghhhhh!
(Cheering)
Uncle, was that--
the very same spell
which turned shendu
to stone ages ago
and separated
his powers from him
in the form
of 12 talismans.
Courtesy
of daolon wong.
(Grumbling
under breath)
Hey, Jack--
um...Can we keep him?
Who else'll
fetch my slippers?
Yes!
But he will have to
move out of the vault.
Need to make room
for some...New arrivals.
Shendu: Chaaaaan!
Hey, Jackie,
where do you like
to go in Hong Kong?
If my friend
coming to Hong Kong,
there only few place
I can take them...
Here, my restaurant,
across Hong Kong side. Harbor.
Really see beautiful
nighttime
and also the mountain.
Hong Kong's a very,
very beautiful place.