Haven't you
found it yet?
Uh, not yet, uncle.
But tell me,
why am I researching
Celtic pig goddesses?
Do not waste time
asking questions.
Read.
One more thing.
Jade is--
bored!
Uncle Jackie,
when are you going to
score us a mission?
Jade, I am not
a secret agent.
I am a researcher.
But do not worry.
When I come home,
we will make
a big bowl of popcorn,
and you can help me
proofread my notes.
(Dial tone)
Hello?
(Exasperated sigh)
Doing homework all day?
Somebody around here
must believe in
life after breakfast.
Gentlemen,
we have an emergency.
Black: Criminal mastermind
Dr. ashby necrosis is back.
Dr. necrosis,
the kingpin
of techno-crime?
The same.
Reports are
that he has developed
a cutting-edge
high-tech doomsday device.
The entire world
is in jeopardy.
We've located
what we believe to be
the doctor's base,
the necropolis,
- inside this dormant volcano.
Someone must infiltrate
the necropolis
and destroy
the doomsday weapon.
I suggest Taggart mcstone.
Unfortunately,
- agent tag retired last year.
He left the spy game
forever.
Never say forever.
Agent tag!
I'll require the standard
infiltration package--
my briefcase
and a fresh suit.
Italian, of course.
Of course.
Good luck, tag.
If I'm not back
by 8:00,
cancel my reservation
at Chez Louis.
(Vibrating)
Hmm. Running rough.
Cargo must have shifted.
Aah-aah-aah-aah
aah-aah-aah aah...
(Grunt)
510...
511...
Captain black,
I cannot find Jade anywhere.
Uhh! Whoo!
Good. We have a major
operation going down
and I can't risk
her being underfoot.
Yah!
Jade is always underfoot.
If she is not under my feet
and not under your feet,
whose feet is she under?
Oh, no.
Comm-one,
get me agent
Taggart mcstone.
Yes, sir.
Homebase to outfield.
Jade.
No can do, sir.
Agent tag is flying
under radio silence.
Hmm. 34 down, 6 letters.
Celtic pig goddess.
(Beeping)
Computer:
Approaching target.
Autopilot off.
Yaah!
Aah!
I spy with my little eye...
Something beginning with...
Secret base.
Uhh! Ooh! Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Aw, come on.
How am I supposed to
keep up with that?
Hmm.
Sledding in July.
Cowabunga!
Works better with snow.
Wha--ohh!
(Jade gasping)
Hyah!
Mission log:
Enemy unconscious.
Borrowing crudely tailored
jumpsuit as a disguise.
Note: Orange is not my color.
(Gasp)
Whoops!
A blast!
Hurry!
Jade may be in
terrible danger!
I'm sure tag has
everything under control.
You think so?
No.
Jackie, are you sure
you want to do this?
I'm sure.
I think.
Yaaaahhh!
Who are you?
Why are you
following me?
Uh...
Captain black sent me.
Hmm. A little girl
with dark hair
who tags along
and is an obvious liar.
I've heard of you.
You're Jade.
Section 13
has classified you
as the ultimate
security risk.
You've jeopardized
my mission!
Whoa.
And you need to calm down,
captain blood pressure.
Mission log: Aborted.
I'll take you back
to San Francisco
at once.
Ohh...
Let go of her,
you big bully!
Jade! I'll be back!
Jackie?
Yeeaaaahhh!
(Crash)
(Moaning)
Huh? Ohh...
Uh-oh.
Jackie! No!
Agent tag!
Wake up!
Huh? Tag?
Now who's going to
defeat Dr. necrosis
and destroy
his doomsday device?
Uncle Jackie?
Oh, no.
Destroying
a doomsday device
sounds too dangerous.
Well, sure, if you
say it like that.
I told you,
I am not
a secret agent.
I am a researcher.
All you have to do
is save the world.
No.
I'm taking all 3 of us
back to section 13
right away.
See? This is why
we can't buy you nice things.
Whoopsie! Incoming!
Get 'em!
Bad day, bad day,
bad day!
Agent tag, please,
wake up.
Admit it.
This is better than
doing homework all day.
No, it is not.
Now--uhh!
Uhh--ooh! Uhh!
(Grunting)
Uhh!
Ooh. Careful you don't
hurt agent tag.
Him?! What about me?
Gohh--
uncle Jackie!
This way!
Jade, no!
Daahh!
Get him!
Whoaaaaa!
(Coughing)
Automated voice:
Intruder alert!
We gotta find
that doomsday device!
Come on!
Ohh! Why do you refuse
to wake up?
All right, then.
Stay here.
Try not to attract attention.
Perfect.
Jade?
Jade?!
Ohh!
(Footsteps)
Shh! Someone's coming.
Jackie?
Whaa--
doomsday device.
You fools!
You need me!
I spent 20 years
designing the laser Cannon.
Huh! Last year's technology.
Dr. necrosis has a new
doomsday toy,
all packed up
and ready for transport.
Transport?
Loading dock.
Hoyle.
I have deduced the identity
of our intruder.
Taggart mcstone.
That wild card
still in the game?
But I thought
he folded last year.
There is no one else
it could be.
He is the only human
capable of infiltrating
my necropolis.
Oh, how I long
to meet my Nemesis
face to face.
You won't ruin his face,
will you, hoyle?
No promises.
For years he has foiled
all my techno-plans,
but this time
we have the druid stone,
and even agent tag
cannot defeat
its ancient magic.
The world is ours.
We hold all the cards.
We have the upper hand.
We--
we could take it
down a notch
on the card puns.
All that matters
is the druid stone.
It is the heart of
my new doomsday weapon.
Guard it well, hoyle.
As the doctor orders.
Whoa.
The doomsday weapon
is ancient magic?
This is big.
Uhh!
Ohh-whoa!
Jade?!
Jackie?
Stay here!
Stay here?
Tch.
When will he learn?
All right, easy.
Easy!
That is a doomsday device?
But it is just a rock.
Daahh!
All hands on deck,
agent tag.
Ohh!
Yuuh!
I am not agent tag!
Don't try to bluff me.
It doesn't  suit you.
(Grunting)
Gahh!
The druid stone is secure.
And inform the good doctor
that we have
a bonus jackpot on board.
A certain joker
who claims he  isn't
àagent tag.
You are not
what I expected,
agent tag.
Although your disguise
as a buffoon
was most convincing.
But I am not
agent tag.
I am Jackie chan,
a researcher.
Of course,
if you were agent tag,
you would deny it
emphatically.
No. I would claim
to be agent tag,
assuming you would not
believe me.
But I would anticipate
your assumption
that I would not
believe you.
I would foresee
your anticipating
my assumption
of your not
believing me.
But how could you predict
I wouldn't expect
your foreseeing
my anticipation of your
assuming my not believing?
Hah! Answer me that.
I do not even know
what you just said!
Precisely what
I expected you to say...
Agent tag.
Dr. necrosis, the druid stone
has been installed.
Jackie: Ohh!
It is a druid stone.
But a druid stone
is ancient, weak magic.
It is hardly
a doomsday weapon.
(Chuckles)
Ancient, yes.
But coupled with the world's
largest radio telescope
and a global satellite system,
it is no longer weak.
Aah!
With this remote control,
I can target multiple beams
to any square inch on earth.
Remote control, eh?
Time for a little
channel surfing.
Aah--
yaahhh!
Pick a card,
any card.
Thank you.
Uch. Dealer calls
a new game.
Huh?!
Crazy eights!
Uhh!
One of these has gotta
shut this puppy off.
Putting litter
in its place.
Ooh!
Jackie! The doctor's
making a break for it!
Excuse me, doctor,
but it hurts
when I go like this!
Blast you, agent tag.
I am not--
(groan)
Oh, never mind.
Mission log:
Mission accomplished.
Not yet.
We still have to retrieve
the druid stone.
And that's how I reached
arecibo in time
to rescue the chans.
That's why you're
our top agent, Taggart.
Rescue the chans?
We did all
the hard stuff!
It's all right, Jade.
Let it go.
Now, if I can finish
my crossword,
this day will truly
be a success.
6 letters--
a Celtic pig goddess.
(Yawns)
Moccas.
M-o-c-c-a-s.
Mr. chan,
you're a genius.
Jade: Nope.
Just a researcher.
Hey, Jackie.
Yes.
Did you ever work
with Bruce Lee?
Yes.
There's a scene.
I remember,
there's a scene.
He--it was a 2 stick.
I comes in, he just--phoom!
He hit me one stick,
then I fall down.
He just--pahh!
He give me one stick
right on here.
I was this big
with all, uh,
bruise going on.
After cut, he turn around,
just--"ohh! I'm sorry,
sorry. What's your name?"
"My name is Jackie."
"I'm sorry."
I said, "ok, fine, fine."
You know, stunt guy.
Suddenly
the stunt coordinator,
"Jackie, you continue
for 24 hours shooting."
I--I know
it's Bruce Lee
put in the order--
special order--
"I--I--I want that guy."