I am the one and only
king of the shadowkhan.
(Gasps) Oni.
My mother told me
tales of the oni--
hideous horned
demons.
Tarakudo: It was
from this mask
that shendu drew
the power to control
his shadowkhan army.
Tohru: Ancient warriors
once cast a spell
to defeat this oni.
The key ingredient
was Japanese steel.
Tarakudo's reign
came to an end
when the spirits
of his generals were
trapped within masks.
9 general...9 masks.
9 different tribes
of shadowkhan?
Whoa.
"Captain black,
"do not allow anyone
to wear this mask.
Jackie: Please lock it
in the vault
immediately.
Jade, uncle, tohru,
and I are currently
in Tokyo, Japan,
where we hope
to discover a lead
to the location
of the next oni
mask.
Karaoke break, anyone?
Jade, the first rule
of research is Patience.
Uncle: Can you not
read faster, tohru?
Cobwebs are forming
on uncle!
My Japanese is rusty,
sensei.
Hmmhh! At this rate,
new forces of darkness
will locate
8 other masks
before we leave room!
(Jade shouts)
Jade!
Why do research
when you can
come on down to
the oni mask
superstore!
Oni!
Until a cursed one
is worn,
these
are merely masks.
Then why do I have
a strange,
clammy feeling
down my spine?
You...
Have
the willies?
Usually
a pretty good sign
that the king of all oni
is in the house!
Tarakudo!
- Tarakudo!
(Shuddering)
Ohhh!
Henchmen!
Lend a hand,
won't you, and
fetch the mask.
Ratso: Uh...
Which mask?
The magic one!
No! Stop!
Nope.
- Nope.
No.
- That's not it.
Nuh-uh.
Ho ho.
Nah. Nope.
That's
not it.
Nope. Nope.
Jade:
Hands off!
Quickly, tohru!
We most devise
locator spell
so we may find mask
before they do!
Back! Back!
Easy. You could chop
someone's head off
with that.
What are you doing?!
Uh...Lookin'
for the mask?
Try  this fellow.
Hak foo:
Kangaroo hop!
Nice grab.
Ratso:
Gotcha!
Huh?
Heee-yah!
Ratso: Ooh!
Oopsy.
(Groaning)
Ohhh...
Whoa.
Oh,  I wanted
that mask!
Ow!
Too late
for locator spell.
We need
mask removal spell.
Good thing
Japanese steel
ingredient
very handy
this time.
Oh, man! I feel like...
Summoning shadowkhan?
Yeahhhh!
So...Do I just
yell for 'em,
or what?
You must feel
the power, ratso.
Call upon
the darkness within.
Oh, ok. I got it.
Uhh! No!
No feeling!
No calling!
Gohh--uhh!
Come on, shadowkhan!
(Gasps)
Unhh!
Whoa!
Sweet.
Go, ratso!
9 masks...
9 different tribes
of shadowkhan.
Uncle, how is
your mask removal
spell coming?
All done.
Aiiyee!
The sword did not
work, sensei.
It must be
wrong ingredient.
Each mask must require
a unique removal spell!
Which do we need
to remove  this mask?
You are Japanese expert!
That is  your department!
Ahem.
Oh. Right.
Make papa proud!
You hit him high,
Jackie,
I'll hit him low.
Awpp!
D-uhh!
Uhh!
Uhhh! Uhh...?
Aah!
Come. Let us seek
more masks
while ratso summons
more shadowkhan.
Hah hah hah hah!
The more, the scarier.
Urrrhhh!
D-eeeee!
Uncle:
Oh, Mr. ninja!
Eat chi magic!
Uncle's regular magic
does not work
on these new shadowkhan!
We must devise
new stun spell.
Uhh! Euhh! Uhh!
(Metal clang)
Heh. Sayonara.
Jackie! Sensei! Run!
Come on, come on,
come on!
Ooowahh!
Darkness within.
Unhh!
- Uhh!
Ohhhhh...
Boy...
Yes! I am good!
Get chan!
Huh?
Ohh...
Grab on!
D-uhhh...
Yaahhh!
Aaahhh!
Tohru: Aaahhh...Uhh!
P-uhhh.
I hate fish.
Ratso: Hey!
Where'd everybody go?
Tarakudo:
A job well done, boys.
For our next trick...
Whoo-o-o-o!
Whoa. Are you
all right?
What is it,
big kahuna?
I think I...
Have the willies.
Sensei...
The scroll speaks
of the legendary
Hana-fuda...
An ancient deck of cards.
My mommy told me
of these cards
when I was young.
Phewww!
More fairy tales.
Cards not important!
But legend indicates
that the cards are magic...
And may point the way
to the remaining oni masks.
I am telling you,
cards not important!
Tohru?
Let me guess.
Your old pal Willie?
So...
Hoping to find
the Hana-fuda cards?
Well, I can't
let you do that!
Ok...
Maybe cards important.
Back!
Onion?
Do not be
foolish, tohru.
Use garlic.
Whoa! Easy
with that veggie,
big fella.
Aaahh! My eyes!
It  does work!
I think it is
checkout time.
Rahhhhhh!
Mommy always told me
onions keep
the oni away.
I used to
sleep with one
under my pillow.
You da man, t!
You da man!
Yes...He is.
The best thing
about makin'
your own team of ninjas?
Is makin' enough
for 2 teams!
Ratso: Ooh,
high fly!
If  I wore
the mask,
all of Japan
would be under
my rule by now!
Oh, ball boy...
Ohhh...Get it
yourself.
You don't want
to spoil our fun...
Do you, hak foo?
Tarakudo: Ratso!
Gather your
shadow minions.
You must see to it
Mr. chan fails
to acquire a certain...
Deck of cards.
Let the games
begin.
We must take
the train to matsue.
The Hana-fuda cards
are housed
in an ancient shrine
there.
Legend indicates
that the cards
contain the spells
which originally
defeated the oni.
Handy-dandy
mask removal
action.
Oh, uncle, that
is not our train.
It is mine.
Uncle must go
to airport now.
What?
Why?
Bein' away from shop
for so long
makes me...Nervous?
Uncle...
(Sighs)
I am only
getting in your way.
Tohru has knowledge
of Japanese legends...
Which uncle does not.
Tohru gets willies
from oni,
which uncle does not.
Tohru knows tricks
with vegetables,
which uncle...
I require
your guidance.
I offer you
my confidence.
Jade, go with uncle.
Ohhh...
Jade:
I miss him
already.
Jade! I told you
to go with uncle,
not stay
with...Uncle.
Tch! No wonder
I got confused.
Too many uncles.
Ratso:
All aboard...
The shadowkhan express!
Gonna make you cry,
demon boy.
(Munching)
Mmm, mmm. Yummy.
Uh, ratso
is still
part human,
and his human side
likes onions?
Quick! Inside!
Darkness within,
darkness within,
darkness within...
You have a train
to catch!
Huhh! Uhh!
Unhh!
Heyyy-yuhh!
Uuurrrhhhh!
Uncle told me to devise
a new stun spell...
So I did.
This is it.
That's a shrine?
If it was,
it is a factory now.
Wait.
This  kanji meaning
Hana-fuda...
Is also
the factory logo.
Jackie: Hello!
Anybody here?
Oh. You do not
work here.
Uh, maybe you
can help us, sir.
We are looking
for some...Cards.
Hana-fuda cards?
Those would be the ones.
Thus, the cards
were handed down
from my ancestors.
As you can see,
I based
my company logo on
the Hana-fuda  kanji.
So...Why  are you
so interested
in my family's
deck of cards?
Are you familiar
with...Oni?
Of course.
My grandmother
would read me stories
when I was a child. Why?
Some very bad oni
know of your cards.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
(Laughing)
Oni are not real.
They are stuff
of children's tales.
What is it?
The girl...
Her shadow.
Uh-oh.
Hiya.
Oni! (Sobbing) Ohhh!
Ohhhhh!
Take the cards!
They are yours!
Hand them over!
Here you go.
Oh, gee, thanks.
Hey!
Sorry I would not return them.
Thank you.
Get those cards!
The old fake hand-off.
A mask removal spell
is the only way
to stop ratso's
shadowkhan for good.
They're all blank?
Did the scroll
say anything
about how to play?
No.
Then we need to figure out
how to play...
Fast.
(Grunting and shouting)
Hmm.
Hooahh!
D-ohh!
D-ohhhh!
D-ohh.
Aaahh!
Bye-bye!
Drive safely!
Uhhh!
D-oohh! D-oohh!
Uhh! D-oohh!
Uh...Gin rummy?
How about...Crazy 8s?
Whoa! Look!
It's showing us the mask!
But we already
know that part.
This one's telling us
where to find--
er, where we found it.
And...For
a lifetime supply
of grape soda...
The mask removal spell
ingredient is...
Tohru: Japanese silk.
You mean like
in a kimono?
Where can we find
a kimono
at this time of...
Game...Over.
Ohhhh!
Leave him alone,
you bully!
Tohru didn't invite  me
to play cards.
You can play
my favorite--
go fish.
Hel-lo.
Uncle!
Hmm.
Very good stun spell.
Yeah? Well, I got
more ninja bad boys
where  they came from.
Mmhh!
Unhhh...Hhh!
D-ohh!
- Ooh!
Uncle!
You're back!
Only because
I realized
I do not have
keys to shop!
(Keys jingle)
Oops.
(Chuckles embarrassedly
keys not important now!
Did you discover
ingredient for
mask removal spell?
Japanese silk?
Blended wool
and polyester!
Uncle does
not wear clothes
of movie star
or male model!
Or...
President
of car company?
Ruhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Uhh! Ohh!
Uhh! Uhhhh!
Uhhh!
- J-uhh!
(Chanting)
Hey!
Urrrhhh!
Uhhh! Gahh!
G-uhh! G-uhh!
Ohhh! Gahh! G-uhh!
Uhhh...
Yes!
Ohhh...
(Stupidly) I was havin'
the weirdest dream.
Waaahhh!
Yaaahhh!
Oh! Ooh! Ooh!
My turn at bat!
It would appear
chan possesses the cards,
since  you no longer
possess horns!
Ohhh...
Yeah.
(Chuckles
embarrassedly)
Two down...
7 to go.
Well...Anyone
up for some slapjack?
Sensei, what
will keep tarakudo
from penetrating
the vault?
Urrrrhhh!
Uhhh!
Ohhh...
Aahh!
My eyes!
Oni magic cannot
defeat onion magic.
A little trick
I learned
from my...
Apprentice.
Jade: Hey, Jackie,
do you play baseball?
Of course I like baseball.
You know what?
I'm the honorable chairman
baseball captain
in Hong Kong.
Uh, I do play baseball,
but I'm--actually,
I'm not really good,
because when I look at TV,
it just easy.
But you really
try to hit it,
it's difficult.
I love...Baseball.