Nice day for a Tsunami.
Too nice.
Why here?
The water demon
will need a palace
from which to rule
her new undersea
kingdom.
Here she comes, uncle.
Bai tza.
Uncle: Jackie,
take the gourd.
I will prepare
the  chi spell.
Right--wah!
Jade?
Uh, no. I'm a moose.
Marlon moose.
Jade, you were
supposed to wait
back at section 13.
(Scoffs) I've been
at every demon
send-off so far.
Did you really think
I was gonna sit out
the last one?
Besides, then we can sell
our story to reality TV.
Shall I turn back?
No. Please, just keep
out of harm's way.
(Chanting)
The  chi wizard!
No!
Ooh, fish fry. Yah!
Jade!
Jackie!
Uncle, we have
to get Jade!
You have to re-open
the portal!
The  chi spell has
sealed the portal,
like it has sealed
all the others...
Forever.
(Hiss)
Uh-uh-uh.
Uhh! Uhh!
Uhh! Hurry, uncle!
We must fly to Rome.
Jade is not
in Rome, Jackie.
She is trapped
in the demon netherworld.
Oh, why couldn't it
have been me?
Aah!
There must be something
we can do, uncle!
A counter spell!
A stronger spell!
Some way to--ow!
I cannot think
with all your noise.
The eighth door.
Uncle?
We have permanently sealed
7 portals belonging
to 7 demon sorcerers,
but not the one
belonging to shendu.
It is Jade's
only hope of escape
from the demon
realm.
But how do we find
shendu's door?
There is
only one way.
The pan ku box.
But shendu has it.
How do we find him?
Our hideout!
It's the helms
fish cannery!
Oh.
Uncle: Quickly.
We must find
the eighth door
before the demons
find Jade.
Jade:
"The demon netherworld:
"Where demon sorcerers go
when they've been bad,
where no human has
gone before...Until now."
My ratings will be huge!
(Sighs) If I ever find
a way out of here.
Uhh! Long way down.
Whoa!
Whoa.
We have liftoff.
(Snoring)
Hsi wu: Sister po!
Uh-oh.
Sister po!
(Snorts) Hmm?
Dinner time?
Meeting time.
Our sister bai
has returned.
I see.
Well, perhaps she brought
hors d'oeuvres.
Mmm, I love
the taste of humans.
Oh, boy.
Over here!
Double oh, boy.
Shendu: You may
take your leave, hak foo.
Valmont's voice:
I order you to stay!
Shendu's voice: Leave!
Valmont: Stay!
Shendu: Leave!
- Valmont: Stay!
Shendu: Your ruffian
has outlasted
his usefulness
to me, valmont.
Get rid of him.
Valmont:
And be left alone with you?
I think not, shendu.
On the contrary,
the both of you...
Are far from alone.
Shendu:
Brothers and sisters,
so good to see you.
Your sentiment will
quickly subside, shendu...
Once your punishment
is underway.
P-p-punishment?
Before I've finished
securing your release?
And how do you plan
to do that
with all of our portals
permanently sealed?
Yeah. How?
Why, through my portal,
dear sister.
The eighth portal?
It remains unsealed.
All I need do
is unlock it
with the pan ku box,
a task for which I have
retained the services
of a mortal servant,
who may touch
good magic.
Grr.
What is mine is yours,
demon brethren.
Uhh...Uhh.
Uhh.
Uhh!
What in the netherworld
is wrong with you, po Kong?
Uhh...Itch.
Cannot reach.
Hsi wu, scratch
your sister's back
so we may get on
with our meeting.
Uhh. There's
a lot of back.
Could take a while.
So, you want
a back scratcher?
Ahhh...
It passed.
Now, about
the eighth door,
shendu.
It is the portal
of  your banishment.
Only  you may
pass through it.
That once
was true, bai tza,
but now that
I am a spirit,
my portal is vacant...
Waiting to be filled
by others.
You mean  another.
Only one may pass
through each portal.
That is the rule.
Do you think
I have been
dallying here?
I have discovered a spell
which will keep
the portal open
until the last of you
is freed.
In fact,
I was just preparing
to journey to it
when you called.
Hak foo...
Bring me...
The pan ku box!
Shark snatches bait!
Bai tza: What shark?
Xiao fung: What is
he talking about?
Jackie!
Shendu,
what is happening?
Uh, hak foo
always sounds the gong
as we take our leave,
which reminds me...
See you all
at my portal!
Shendu!
Can he be trusted?
Of course not!
Yet we have
no other options.
But all of eternity
to punish him
should he again
deceive us.
Hsi wu: Then let us go
to the eighth door.
Yes...Let's.
Hyah! Hyah!
Ohh...Ohh!
Why the interest
in the box, chan?
You have sealed
the portals.
I want a keepsake
of our time together.
Hyah!
Uhh!
Unh!
Jackie: Uhh!
Buffalo tramples
field mouse!
(Hisses)
You want the box,
shendu?
It's yours!
Aah!
Uhh!
(Groans)
Angry crow takes--
unh!
(Sighs)
What is
taking so long?!
Let's go.
Uncle:
In ancient times,
shendu ruled
what is now China.
I'm betting that
that is where
we will find his portal.
But even  if we are
able to make this box
provide the
portal's location,
how will Jade find it
from the demon side?
With proper guidance.
That is why
I have brought research.
Ohh, nothing.
Ahh...
Jade is
good at puzzles.
She could
figure it out...
If she were here.
Uhh.
(Sighs)
I thought this rock
looked familiar.
I'm going 'round
in circles!
Valmont: And we are
on our way to China why?
Chan has stolen
the pan ku box.
Clearly, he wants
to find my portal
so he can seal it.
Now why would chan
go to all the trouble
if he knows you don't
need the portal to
pass between the realms?
For good measure,
I suppose.
Meanwhile,
my brothers and sisters
are expecting me
to open my door
and free them.
I brought
your spell book.
You brought
the phone book,
you simpleton!
I was bluffing!
So there is no way
to free all of them.
Of course there is!
I...Just need to find it...
That's all.
Uncle: Hotcha!
Uncle?
He is in a trance.
He's looking for Jade.
Day number...
Ohh, I haven't
the foggiest.
The good news:
The demons have left
to find
the eighth portal.
The bad news:
I lost their trail.
Jackie, toru, uncle.
I may never
see you again,
but in case
you ever find
this footage,
edit this mushy part out
before you sell it
to a TV show.
Just want you all
to know I miss you.
I even miss
uncle's garlic breath.
Jade!
Aah!
Uncle? How did you--
not important,
and garlic
is  good for you!
Are you ok?
(Scoffs) Just lost.
Listen closely.
We are trying
to find the eighth door.
Shendu's door!
You know about that?
The demons are
looking for it, too.
Shendu told them
he's gonna open it up
so they can
all break out.
(Gasps)
Shendu deceives them.
Only one being
can now exit
through that portal,
and that being
must be you.
So how do I find
the portal, uncle?
When I know where it is,
I will lead you there myself.
Go, uncle.
One more thing:
I cannot know
where it is
unless I know
how the pan ku box works.
Jackie said
you are good with puzzles.
Hmm...
Those little lines
on the pan ku box!
The tri-grams?
Yeah, those!
Tell Jackie
the tri-grams
must be the key!
I will do that, Jade!
Time flies
when you're waiting
for a cell door to open.
Where's my camera?
Oh, Jade...
Say "chi spell."
Uhh!
The tri-grams
must be the key.
What could
Jade mean?
Shendu's tri-gram
representing "fire"
is a broken line
between 2 solid lines.
The tri-grams
could be a morse code.
Or the combination
to a lock.
If a solid line
is a half turn...
And the broken lines
are quarter turns...
(Sighs)
Um, perhaps
the unbroken lines
tell us
to turn it the long way?
Half...
Quarter...
Jade knows
her puzzles.
And I know
my demons!
Shendu's portal
is in Hong Kong.
Jackie:
Nothing yet, uncle.
According to
the pan ku box,
the eighth door
should lie just
beyond this tunnel.
Oh! It is near!
You have
to be kidding.
It is as if Jade herself
guided us here.
Jackie: Hong Kong
moose world.
Uncle: I will alert Jade.
Hsi wu:
Brothers and sisters,
I bring you
the mortal called...
Jade!
Mmm, yummy!
Uh...
If you think
you're  all
getting out,
well, I hate
to break it to ya,
but shendu's lying.
Only  one of you
can go through
the portal.
End of story.
How do  you know?
Uncle told me.
The chi wizard?
So shendu
did deceive us.
There's a surprise.
So, uh...
Which one of you
is it gonna be?
Surely there must
be a simple way
to resolve this.
Like what,
alphabetical order?
Jade awaits us!
We must open
the portal
immediately!
Shendu:
So that is why
you wanted the box!
Well, I assure you, chan,
the only thing emerging
from my portal...
Will be a demon.
Hyah!
Gorilla grip!
Unh!
Jackie!
There is more
than one way
to skin a cat!
And 2 ways
to open a portal!
(Chanting)
The symbol
of the immortal
who defeated me!
Sword slays dragon.
Aah!
Brothers and sisters!
Bai tza: The portal!
Every demon for himself!
Unh!
Age before beauty.
Hsi wu?
One goes through,
that's the rule.
No!
Uhh!
Jade!
Did you miss me?
Not at all.
Uncle: Jade.
Dai gui:
That is number eight.
Tso LAN:
Which would make us
fresh out of portals.
Hsi wu: Say, "chi spell."
Perhaps we should
seek a tear
in the time-space
continuum?
All 8 portals
are finally
sealed...
Forever!
Whippee!
He's gone! He's gone,
gone, gone!
I've got my body back,
¶ la Dee da Dee da ¶
¶ boom-shaka-laka-laka,
boom-shaka-laka-laka ¶
¶ oh, I've got
my body back ¶
can we, Jackie?
We're not really...
You're kind
of early, but...
Awww--
(like bullwinkle)
Welcome to moose world!
Hyuk!
Through
- the portal we go.
Yay!
It's gone.
I've got my body back!
(Cheers)
Hey Jackie, do you play
an instrument?
Yes, I do.
Harmonica,
when I was very,
very young...
And also I know
how to play...
Chinese guitar.
(Humming)
But now I forget.
But I do sing.
Yeah...Actually,
I'm a pretty good
singer.