Previously on Jackie chan
adventures...
The new year approaches.
It is essential that I have
all 12 talismans before then.
Narrator:
When the talisman broke,
Jackie's yin was separated
from his Yang.
Bring me the talismans,
and I will make you
rich.
Works for me.
The bad me stole
the talismans!
Jade:
Most of 'em anyway.
Wait! If the dark hand
gets all the talismans,
then something really,
really bad's gonna happen!
Ooh!
Oh!
I...Live!
At long last,
my powers...Restored!
Speed, invisibility,
astral projection!
That thing's why
valmont wanted
the talismans?
And my personal favorite...
Combustion!
Aah!
Jackie!
Aah--huh?
Whoa.
Oo-ooh! Ah-ha-ha!
Jacki-I-I-ie!
Grab my legs!
Whoo!
Call captain black!
Once I reach
the top,
you head
for the bottom.
Aw!
Whoa!
Shen-dude!
Uh...Welcome
to earth?
Good to see ya
up and around.
Well, the office
is a shambles,
but the lost treasure
of q'in shi'huang
should more than cover
the cleaning deposit.
Regrettably, valmont,
you did not provide me
with the talismans.
Jackie chan did.
A technicality.
Read my lips...
No treasure for you.
Tohru...Make this
deadbeat pony up.
You go, bro.
Yeah, we're
right behind ya.
In spirit.
But master--
do it!
Hee-ahh--
w-uh!
Need I remind you
that I possess
the power of levitation
and super-strength?
Uhh!
All: Whoa!
(Huffs) Fine.
Treasure's yours.
Aah!
You...
All: He ain't even singed.
That, gentlemen,
would be our cue.
Too bad about
the lost treasure of...
You know,
whatchamacallit.
Will this affect
our bonuses?
You get a bonus?
Shut up!
Surprise.
Come on!
Who--what are you?
I am...The keeper
of the talismans.
I am the apocalypse
of which legend speaks.
And I am...
For once and for all
your executioner!
Bad day, bad day,
bad day!
Aah!
Uh--oof!
This way!
Jade...Please explain.
I think it used
the power
of the levitation
talisman combined
with the speed talisman
so it could fly.
What? What did all that
so it could fly?
Got me.
But it used to be
a statue.
Did the demon have
any specific markings?
Red eyes, great big claws,
and razor-sharp teeth
isn't specific enough
for you?!
(Growls)
Thousands
of demon sorcerers
have existed
throughout history!
I need more information--
a symbol, a name,
anything!
Chan!
Oh! Go away!
We have no more
talismans.
The demon's name...
Shendu.
Uncle: "Shendu was the evil
warlord of a vast kingdom.
"He was imprisoned
by his subjects,
"and the 12 talismans
from which he drew his powers
"were scattered
to the winds.
"He vowed to return one day,
"not only to resurrect
his palace
"but to conjure
dragon minions
"to wreak his vengeance
upon the descendants
"of those who rebelled
against him...
"By destroying...
All of Asia!"
(Gasps)
Mom...Dad.
Shendu's former palace
is located near
what is now Hong Kong.
His vengeance is to begin
at the toll of midnight,
ushering in
the Chinese new year.
Chinese new year?
That gives us only
a couple of days.
Less. Hong Kong
is 16 hours ahead
of San Francisco.
We'll take section 13's
fastest transport.
Finding the demon
is not enough.
One must have a means of...
Defeating it.
Thank you.
I will come with you.
I will come...(Grunts)
Too.
Um...That's ok.
Tohru...Why help us?
I am told section 13
serves donuts on Thursdays.
I am sorry,
but you must stay.
No.
Ow!
You stay here!
Someone must watch
the shop!
Good.
Now...Let me
gather some things.
Well...Whaddaya say
we save some lives?
Jackie, I  have
àto come with you!
I'm an essential part
of the j-team--
the cunning one.
Jade, this
is not a movie.
You know that.
This time it is
too dangerous.
Hmmph!
(Jackie sighs)
Your mother and father
will be safe.
I will see to it.
And I will
see to it that
he sees to it!
Don't let your guard down.
Jade's, uh...Cunning.
Oh, guard!
Tell me, why hasn't
jolly captain black
graced us with
his presence of late?
I so miss his good humor.
Black's in Hong Kong
on a...(Laughs)
Demon hunt.
I see...
Big v, what--
what are you
doin'?
Raising cane.
(Water running)
What the--
I gotcha!
Huh?
Psst!
Guards: Hey! Let me out!
Open up! (Pound on door)
(Alarm)
Whoa. Jackie was serious
about me not going.
Valmont's escaped!
Seal all exits!
(Clanging)
Voice: This way,
I think.
Goin' to treasure
island.
Treasure island...
Hong Kong.
Uncle: Go away!
I am busy!
Uh...You've been
in the lavatory
since takeoff.
That is right!
Laboratory!
Do you want Jackie
to defeat the evil
demon? Yes?
Then go away!
Let uncle work!
Don't worry,
mom and dad.
I'm coming.
The palace!
Where?
Here...Where
the inscriptions
indicated.
Look...It's almost
midnight.
Oh!
Whoa!
What is it?
An earthquake!
Never question
the inscriptions.
Whoa!
What is that?!
What is shendu
doing, uncle?
Releasing his dragon minions.
Let's turn up
the heat.
No! Shendu is immortal!
Magic must defeat magic.
Men...
Jackie, this balm
will enable you
to penetrate
shendu's demon shell
and remove
the talismans.
Remove? All 12?
Not if you are cunning,
like Jade.
Certain talismans
offer shendu
not firepower
but sustenance.
For example,
without the reanimation
that the rat talisman
provides,
shendu would revert back
to being a statue.
Shendu: Soon, my warriors.
Midnight draws near.
What?
(Grunts)
The sheep talisman.
How many lives
do you possess?
Sheep, sheep, sheep.
Which power was that?
Huh?
Oh! The astral
projection talisman!
Of all the useless--
what am I supposed
to do with that?
He's out cold.
Men...
No! Magic must
defeat magic!
(Groans) Ah...
(Inhales)
Mmm. Fresh meat!
Huah! Huah!
My talismans!
You cannot harm me, chan.
The horse is the healer.
Ohh...Uhh...
And the rabbit is speed.
Buaah!
That tears it. Men!
Uh--ohh...
Who else wants
a piece of uncle?
Chan better keep
Rex the magic dragon busy
long enough for us
to line our pockets.
Jackie!
Monkey? I was hoping for--
rabbit!
Cute.
(Gasps) Invisibility!
It's the Chinese
zodiac hit parade!
Monkey see, monkey do!
The strength
talisman.
Good one.
I know, Jade.
Whaa--Jade!
How did you--
your hands!
I get it! That must be
some uncle magic!
(Gasps)
Ughh--talk later!
At last!
Well, boys.
Let's dig in.
The playing field...
Is almost even...Shendu.
You may have the ox,
but relative to me,
all that makes you
is a very strong
mouse!
No! Mom and dad...
All of Asia
are counting on you!
And me!
Pity you will not live
to witness my reign
over your world.
But you shall
be the first
to visit theirs.
Eee-yah!
What--da--
little Jade horner...
Pulled out a dog.
Rat!
No-o-o-o!
(Cheering)
What happened?
See?
What have we
learned?
All, annoyed:
Magic must defeat magic.
I  will have my revenge,
if it takes another
900 years.
Tch. No rat means
you're just a statue.
And no dog means
you're not immortal.
But the talismans!
Never mind!
No-o-o-o!
Happy new year, Jade.
Happy new year, uncle.
Ow!
You destroyed
the demon yin and Yang.
Now the world
is out of balance!
Nobody told you
to destroy the demon!
Jade did it.
Now there is a void
for a new...
Stronger evil
to fill!
(Coughing)
I know how much
the treasure meant
to you, big v.
But how 'bout
a consolation prize?
You should visit
your parents.
They...Might want me
to stay with them.
Would that be so awful?
Tch...For you.
Uncle!
Come, Jackie!
Give tohru a hug!
Don't.
This...Will take
some getting used to.
Ahh...This and Jade
not being around.
(Sighs) I know.
Ah! That reminds me!
A letter from Jade's
parents arrived yesterday.
They are very pleased
with how much she has
learned in America. Ahh...
One  more thing...
They're  so pleased,
they want me to hang here
for another year!
Jade!
Jackie!
Jade: Hey, Jackie.
Do you think
you'll act
for the rest
of your life?
I know...I cannot always
on the...In front of screen,
but I can be a director,
a producer,
help the people how to editing
all the action scene.
A writer. Some other things
I really don't know.
Only thing I know is,
uh...Film.
I will be in the film industry
all my life.