My tattoo just has to be
gnarly.
This is a symbol
of great evil.
Awaken from shadow!
Serve your new master!
Gan! Ren! Chui! Zhen!
Prepare for battle!
Wow!
We rock!
Uhh!
Yah!
Ooh!
Uhh!
(Gasps)
Busted.
(Jade sighs)
Dullsville.
No. The capital
of Georgia is Atlanta.
Jade, your geography test
is tomorrow.
Let's try Oregon.
Why does tohru get to
study the fun stuff?
Uncle is waiting.
I know this one.
That is a symbol
for a conjuring spell,
one which requires
garlic and...Ginger?
Correct...
If you are making
chicken chow mein!
Do you plan on
becoming chi wizard,
tohru?
Then you must
prepare for day
when new evil
enters our world.
Bon appetit.
Want gruel with that?
Today's special.
Hey, how's that
special sauce coming?
(Chanting)
This had better
work, "wizard."
While I no longer
possess my full powers...
I, daolon wong, have amassed
the spell ingredients
required to make our escape.
(Chanting becomes feverish)
Come to me. Yes!
Liberate us, shadowkhan!
Rise, my army of darkness!
Tarakudo:
Your army?!
Huh?
I am the one and only king
of the shadowkhan!
Tarakudo?
Awakened?
And ready to reclaim
my ninja magic,
a task for which I will
require "assistance."
Ratso: Uh...
Finn: We have to go
check on dessert now.
(Roars)
Aah!
Yahh!
Uhh!
(Escape sirens)
Jackie, the dark hand thugs
have escaped from prison.
(Gasps) Daolon wong!
Good news is, the "wizard"
is still in custody.
(Cell phone rings)
Black.
Miller airfield?
Send in every
available agent.
Huh?
Your assistance
will not be necessary!
Magic will defeat magic!
Good-bye.
Uncle: Daolon wong
or no daolon wong...
A new, greater evil
has forced its way
into our realm!
When we find
dark hand thugs,
we will find this evil.
Hurry!
Yes!
50 states,
50 capitals.
Uhh!
Serve me well,
and your reward
will be great.
Yeah...About that.
We appreciate you
busting us out and
all, tarakudo-San,
but the truth is,
we're kinda burnt out
on the whole
- henchman-for-hire thing.
Ah! You require
motivation, then.
Aah!
Ok.
When do we start?
Ready to work!
Phew!
(Sighs of relief)
That's the spirit!
Now, where is
this "dark hand jet"?
Visitors?
Jackie chan
and friends!
He's always
gettin' in our way.
So now would be
an excellent time
to bring on the ninjas!
Not just yet.
Ready the plane.
(Roars)
(Gasps)  Oni.
(Gasps)
Uh, "new evil,"
right?
The symbol
of the shadowkhan!
What fun is a "symbol"
without drums?!
Tohru!
Come on, big fella.
Trying to save you
a nasty bruise here.
Uhh!
(Gasps)
Captain black!
(Moans)
Uncle: Jackie! Quickly!
Floating head!
Aah! Dahh! Ooh!
Ehh!
Hey, Jackie.
Bwaaa!
Before you get mad,
listen.
The capital of Kansas
is Kansas City.
The capital is
Topeka, and that
is not the point!
Uh-oh.
Whoa.
You.
Ah! The former "queen
of the shadowkhan."
Returning to
the forces of darkness?
Thank you, no.
Not today!
Er--what Jackie said.
In time.
You're young.
Find cover.
Enforcers: Come on!
The spells
are not working!
Aah!
That is because
you do not study
hard enough!
Hmm. Spell work
after all.
No. Something tells me
big head got on the plane.
Black: Jackie!
You want a barf bag, chan?
'Cause you're about to
experience some air sickness.
Aah! Whoa!
Buh-bye.
Aah!
Bad day, bad day,
bad day, bad day!
It's Jackie,
and he doesn't appear
to have a parachute.
Tohru,
catch Jackie!
Uh...
Happy trails, chan.
Huh?
(Yells)
Jackie would  so not approve.
Aah--aah--aah--
aah--aah--aah--
aah--aah--aah!
Hey, Jackie!
Bwaaa! Jade!
Never exit an aircraft
without one of these!
Good catch, tohru.
Quickly now! We must
follow floating head!
(Groans)
(Grunts)
Mommy!
(Panting)
Tohru?
Heh! Bad dream.
Lemme guess.
Mr. creepy head?
Jade, you are supposed
to be with captain black.
Thought I should be
here in case you fall
from another plane.
The head.
It reminded me
of the oni.
The who-ni?
When I was a child
growing up in Japan,
my mother told me
tales of the oni--
hideous, horned demons
who would sneak
into the rooms of
disobedient children.
And what did they
want with these
disobedient children?
The oni would--(Gulps)--
Eat their souls! Eww!
So these oni are
like Japanese bogeymen.
Pfft! Fairy tales!
Floating head
cannot be "oni."
It can't?
Of course not!
Everyone who has
controlled the shadowkhan
has been  Chinese!
Shendu, Chinese!
Daolon wong, Chinese!
But oni are  Japanese!
(Beep)
Radar indicates
the dark hand jet
has landed in Hong Kong.
See? Hong Kong! Chinese!
Jackie: Shendu's palace?
Shendu collected many
artifacts possessing
great magic.
Floating head may be
seeking one of these.
Check it out! Rabbit hole!
Uh...I will
stand guard outside.
don't be afraid, t.
It's just
a silly old head.
(Gulps)
Just a silly old
soul-stealing,
shadowkhan-controlling head.
Tarakudo: Ahh!
Consider it a gift.
Oh, just like Christmas!
Bet there's a ton
of treasure in it!
Dude, you brought us
all this way for a mask?
It was from this "mask"
that shendu drew the power
to control
his shadowkhan army
and through which
daolon wong's magic
channeled
- that very same power.
Why don't you
see how it fits?
(Gasps) Jackie!
I know.
Yes!
Peek-a-boo!
Seagull shucks oyster!
Aah!
(Grunts)
(Growls)
Aah!
Uhh!
Ooh!
Again?!
Who  are these people?
Well, Jackie chan's
some kind of do-gooder,
and the big guy
over there used to be
one of us,
but now
he's on their side,
and the old guy pointing
the blowfish--uhh!
Who else wants
a piece of uncle?!
You have no idea
who you are dealing with.
Enlighten me.
Bow before tarakudo,
king of all shadowkhan,
lord of all oni!
(Gasps)
So you  are Japanese!
Uhh!
Consider yourself
enlightened.
Tohru!
Uhh!
Huh?
Tarakudo: Mind over matter!
Mine!
Not so fast!
Hey!
What's going on?!
Grr! I wanted that!
Handsome devil,
isn't he?
Chow here will stick
around and familiarize
himself with his new powers
while we make
further preparations.
Aah!
Uhh!
What does he mean by
"further preparations"?
(Grunts)
Aah!
Four against one.
Now, that hardly seems fair.
(Roars)
Uh...Jackie?
I'm getting
the feeling
this masked thing
gives chow the power
to summon...
Shadowkhan.
(Efforting)
Uhh!
Boo!
Face your fear, t!
(Growls)
Uhh!
Light as a feather!
Waaah--uhh!
Uhh!
Aiyaaa!
We must remove
demon mask from host
in order to defeat
shadowkhan!
Jackie, one more thing!
Keep shadowkhan busy,
so uncle can cast
proper spell!
I am trying, uncle. Aah!
What spell
would that be, sensei?
("I don't know" sound)
Hey, lookee here.
Maybe this picture
book can help.
Catch me if you can!
Chan hunt!
What do the
inscriptions say, unc?
These are  Japanese, kanji.
Uncle only reads  Chinese.
Uh, I read Japanese...
But it has been many years.
In fact,
I am probably too shaky,
so forget
that I mentioned--
tohru, read kanji now!
Yes, sensei.
Uhh!
Aah!
(Efforting)
The kanji tell
of ancient warriors
who once cast a spell
to defeat this oni,
trapping its spirit
within the mask.
The key ingredient
was Japanese steel...
Specially forged
for a samurai sword.
Aiyaa! We will
not find steel
of samurai sword here
because shendu
is not Japanese!
Hmm.
Bwaaa!
Well, it doesn't say
"made in Taiwan."
Smackdown time, chan!
Waaah! Daaah!
Uhh!
Daaah!
You've been
working out, chow!
Jade, what
makes you certain
this is Japanese steel?
Uh...I'm not.
Haaah!
Daaah!
Diiih!
Ohh!
Daaah!
Uhh! Ohh!
It's over, chan.
(Tohru and uncle chat)
Yes. It is.
(Chant finishes)
Jackie, remove mask!
Uhh!
Get him off me!
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Aah!
Ohh!
Why isn't it
coming off?
Patience!
Aah!
Uhh!
Destroy him!
"Boo."
Aah!
Perhaps this would
be safer in the vault
at section 13.
New evil
has been defeated.
Um...One more thing.
Oh, no.
Guys?
Guys?!
Hey, guess this means
I'm finally a free
henchman. Heh heh!
Aah!
(Pants)
don't do that!
You have failed me.
Do not fret.
It is but a minor defeat.
That's cool.
Tarakudo's
an ok guy.
Besides, our mission
has only yet begun.
Uh...
It has?
It goes on to say...
That tarakudo once
terrorized the land with
his trusted oni generals.
Each demon general
controlled its own army
which were comprised
of a different tribe
of shadowkhan.
Uh, different how?
I would prefer not
to have to find out.
Tohru: Tarakudo's reign
came to an end
when the spirits
of his generals were
trapped within masks.
9 generals, 9 masks.
9 "different" tribes
of shadowkhan?
What are we
waiting for?
There are
8 more masks
which we must find
before forces
of darkness do!
Let me guess.
The masks were scattered
across the earth?
Yep. Uh, one more thing.
Should the 9 masks
ever be revived,
their combined power may
summon enough shadowkhan
to engulf the entire earth
in eternal darkness.
Aiyaa! Tohru
must do research!
He must?
You were told
childhood tales
of oni by mother.
You read Japanese.
You  are Japanese,
so  you must do
research!
(Gulps)
Yes, sensei.
Yes! New adventure,
uh-huh! Find the masks,
be the shadowkhan...
Hey Jackie do you ever get
tired of traveling all over the
world?
Yeah, I do get tired of
traveling around the world.
I've been--
the last 20 years,
I've been travel,
travel, travel.
One day I want to
settle down,
have my own studio,
just shoot everything
in the same place.
Then I don't have to
travel anymore.
But, put another way,
travel is good.
I learn so many things--
different cultures,
different cities.
Everything's different.
Yeah. That's the good thing.