Jackie: Traveling
through Scotland
is like walking
in pea soup.
How can you
think of food
when the forces
of darkness
are near?
I meant
it is difficult
to see in this fog,
uncle.
Fog not important!
Locator spell is.
The enchanted moth
is drawn
to enchanted wool.
Its light leads us
through the fog
toward the power
of the sheep.
Ha ha ha!
But we are heading
toward the lake.
I do not think
that the loch ness monster
is one of the animals
of the Chinese zodiac.
(Gasps)
What is that?
Loch ness monster!
(Gasps)
Jackie: Jade?
Hey, Jackie. Uncle.
You are supposed
to be at
the bed and breakfast,
where there
is no daolon wong,
no dark chi warriors--
no cable.
Jade: Whoa.
Whole lotta lamb.
We must seek
the most noble
of the beasts.
Baa, baa, black sheep,
have you any magic?
Eh...Next.
One down, 199 to go.
Jade: don't start countin'
sheep yet, Jackie,
'cause I see one
woolly bully.
We found it?
Tsk! We?
Quiet!
Startling the beast
may activate its power
of astral projection.
Finn: Evenin', chan.
I'll have
the roast lamb.
(Gasps)
Dark chi warriors!
Wow.
Dude fainted.
The sheep released
its astral form!
Hyah!
Hee-yah!
Ohh!
(Laughs)
You've been fleeced!
Uncle: Jade...
Uncle
must borrow this.
Uh, you're welcome?
Uncle needs this.
My belt?
Ohh!
Ohh. Like a--uhh!--
baby elephant! Ohh.
(Gasps) Oh, no!
The loch ness monster!
Where?!
Phthht!
Made ya look!
She--uhh!
Whoa. Ohh--uhh!
Ohh, ohh!
Time-out.
Yo, yo. Careful
with lambchop.
If we mess this one up,
wong will have our hides.
No kiddin'.
Last time I brought him
the wrong tea,
he turned me
into an ottoman.
Daolon wong: Minions!
Have you claimed
my talisman power?
Wrapped in wool
and ready
for winter,
d-master.
Uh, it's
just hard to lift
when it's sleepin'.
It is not sleeping,
you fools!
It has released
its astral form!
Uhh!
Ohh!
Heads up.
Aah!
Uhh!
The sheep!
Mine!
Ohh!
Big d!
Hiya!
Uh, we're pumped
for round 2.
Daolon wong:
I have no further use
for those
who allow themselves
to be waylaid by
unconscious livestock!
So...
We're free to go?
Uh, when
the wongmeister said
he had no
further use for us,
you think
he meant today?
Or forever?
Ohh! Why are we leaving
the sheep here, uncle?
Sheep not important.
Astral form is.
That is where
the power lies.
So we just wait here
for Casper
the friendly ram
to trot home.
No.
We must find
its astral form
before daolon wong does.
How will we find
an astral sheep
if we cannot see it?
With proper eyewear.
(Reciting incantation)
Awaken from shadow.
Serve your new master.
Take this...
And bring
the astral sheep to me.
Cool specs!
They're better than 3-d.
Ohhh.
They are 4-d, Jade,
and they
are not a toy.
If I were
an astral sheep,
where would I go?
Lookin' for
some astral turf?
Hot-cha!
Sheep flies
this way!
(Man snoring)
Sheep has entered
Shepherd's head.
Why would
a sheep do that?
To drop in on a dream.
I was
astral once, remember?
We must
maintain contact.
(Reciting incantation)
Whoa, uncle!
Your spells keep
getting more awesome!
Must keep up with
forces of darkness.
Tasty grub you're
serving here, laddie,
though it's
not as filling
as the real McCoy.
Say,
what's this I hear
about shaving me
in winter?
Talking sheep?
Cool!
Uh-oh.
Jade: Shadowkhan.
Aah!
All: Aah!
What's happening?
Who invited ninjas?
Aah!
(Gasps) The cube
of tang shan!
It absorbs astral forms.
The shadowkhan
are working
for daolon wong?
Larry, moe, and curly
must be
on spring break.
I am needed.
I'll cover you. Wha--
too dangerous.
Grrr!
Eh, you wouldn't hit
a guy wearing glasses,
would you?
Grrr.
Now we are
even Steven.
The astral form did
not return to its body.
Poor fella's probably scared.
What do we
do now, uncle,
lead it back with
an astral sheepdog?
We talk sheep.
Ohh. No exit.
And
no magazines.
Maybe the wong-man's
just tryin'
to make a point.
I bet he calls us
back any minute.
Yo!
We're waiting!
Wanna play
charades?
Well?
Ohh! Why is good help
so hard to find?
Jade will lure
the astral sheep
to her dream
so that she may
communicate with it.
Uncle, even if
the sheep returns,
the shadowkhan
may be right behind.
You're right, Jackie.
Why don't  I mix it up
with the legions
of darkness
while  you get
some shuteye?
You are the first
line of defense,
and, failing that,
shadowkhan cannot
physically penetrate
a tae ho han circle
as long as
Jade sleeps.
Ohhh.
Time to count sheep.
(Snoring quietly)
Jade as sheep: Baa! Baa!
(Snoring)
Uncle!
(Clicks tongue)
I haven't
seen you before.
I'm baaab.
I'm Jade,
and I'm not from
around here.
Yaa! The old wolf
in sheep's clothing ruse!
'Cept I'm no wolf.
You have
to trust me, baaab.
You're in danger,
and the only way
I can help is
if you get back
to your body, asap.
Now, where's
the fun in that?
I like flying about.
You won't be flying for long
if those guys in black pjs
get a hold of you.
I'll explain everything
on the way to section 13,
where you can
mingle with other
exceptional animals
like yourself.
This section 13
is like a club?
A very elite club.
12 members only.
I thought the shadowkhan
couldn't penetrate
your circle!
They have entered
Jade's dream
through
the shadow realm.
We must wake her.
Uhh!
Uncle, I can't
penetrate your circle!
Uh...
Might I request
bagpipes be played
at our dream funeral,
Lassie?
Oh, no! The
loch ness monster!
Didn't think
that thing existed.
It does in my dream.
Now, hurry!
We'll meet you back
at your body
in 2 shakes
of a lamb's tail!
Let's move.
Ahh.
Come on, uncle!
(Wheezing)
You two run.
Uncle
- will power walk.
(Gasps) Ohh!
(Chants)
The power
of astral projection
now belongs to me.
Tsk! That didn't
hurt one bit!
Hee-yah!
Ha ha ha!
Jade, get back here!
We must return
to our--ohh!
Uhh!
A little finishing spell
to seal
your human forms
makes both of you
as good as ghosts.
Ha ha ha!
Jackie!
No sleeping!
No "ow"?
Uncle,
we're right here!
Hello? He can't
see or hear you.
Then how will he know
where we are?
(Gasps)
Daolon wong now
possesses the power
of astral projection,
which he has inflicted
upon Jackie and Jade
and then applied
a finishing spell
so that they cannot
return to their bodies!
And you doubted him.
Returning astral forms
to your bodies
will be
very complicated.
(Reciting incantation)
Ohh.
It worked?!
Jade's voice:
Uncle, you rock!
Now let's find
daolon wong
and kick
some shriveled--aah!
Jade's voice:
Why are there 2 of me?
Jackie's voice:
W-why is your voice
coming out of my body?!
Aah!
I told you
spell complicated.
Jackie's voice:
Uncle, you returned
our astral forms
to the wrong bodies!
You must
switch us back!
No time.
With the power
of the sheep,
daolon wong
can travel
the astral plane
and easily seek
the location
of the other
talisman powers.
Jade's voice: Hyah!
Hyah!
Jade's voice:
I'm ok with this.
The moth indicates
that the sheep's power
lies in there.
Jackie's voice: There
is only one way inside.
Jackie's voice:
Ohhh. Uhh!
Jackie's voice: Eh.
I forgot who I wasn't.
Jade's voice: Tryin'
to do this, Jackie?
Jade's voice: Cool, huh?
Jade is better
at being you
than you, Jackie.
Jackie's voice: Ohhh.
Jade's voice: Yoga?
Daolon
is in a trance.
Jade's voice: The better
to turn his lights out!
No! His astral form
wanders,
but the sheep's
is trapped within.
I must free
its astral form
before daolon wong's
returns.
(Blowing)
Jackie's voice: Jade,
how do you keep these
out of your eyes?
Jade's voice:
Uh-oh.
Jackie's voice:
Stay back, Jade.
Jade's voice:
Yes,  Jade,
maybe you  should
stay back.
Jackie's voice: Uh...
Ok,
but I am giving
you permission
to defend us--(Blows)--
This one time only.
Jade's voice:
I'm gonna do you proud.
Hee-yah!
(Reciting incantation)
Jade's voice: Oohh.
Jackie's voice:
Ooh, I'm going
to feel that tomorrow.
Jade's voice: Ooh!
Now I know
why he does that.
Jade's voice: Who da man?
I da man!
Wha--
heh. You wouldn't
hit a little girl?
Jackie's voice:
Tsk. When in Jade,
do like Jade.
Hee-yah!
Jade's voice: Cool!
Jackie's voice: Jade,
do not try that at home.
Jackie's voice:
Bad day, bad day, bad day!
(Chanting)
Jackie's voice,
gasping: Oh, no!
The loch ness monster!
Jade's voice:
Nightie night, ninjas.
Jackie's voice:
What do you know?
I made them look.
(Chanting)
Baa!
The sheep
has been released.
Phthht!
Huh? (Gasps)
Jackie's voice: But,
uncle, what about him?
Uhh!
Daolon wong
is not the only one
with recipe
for finishing spell.
Grrr.
Shadowkhan--pah!
Gan! Ren! Chui!
Big d! Dude, I knew
you'd take us back!
Did you lose weight?
Looks good!
You should
apologize to us.
I will pulverize you
if you do not assist me
in reversing the old man's
finishing spell!
Apology accepted.
Works for me.
Mm-hmm.
Jade's voice:
So, uncle,
can I keep the skin
a while longer?
If Jackie agrees
to do your homework
in the meantime.
Jade's voice:
Please, Jackie?!
Jackie's voice:
Eh, no, Jade,
you cannot.
Jade's voice: Ohh!
Hey, Jackie? What's
your favorite dessert?
Ice cream
with tiramisu.
I eat everything.
I eat all junk food.
Ice cream, tiramisu,
ice cream, tiramisu.
But, most important,
exercise.
Exercise--you can
beat all the calories,
all the bad food.