Jade: Previously on
Jackie chan adventures...
Uncle: It is t'changzu,
the thunder demon!
Drago: And now
for the main attraction!
Uncle: Aiyaah!
Drago's absorbing power
of t'changzu!
Drago: Now that I possess
the thunder chi of t'changzu
and my own fire chi,
there will be
no stopping me.
Strikemaster ice: Yo,
you're going down, clown!
Mc cobra: Yeah, you wish.
Be droppin' you
like a bad habit.
Yo!
Drago: Now do I have
your attention?
Strikemaster ice:
- This dude needs to chill.
Drago: Grr!
Mc cobra: S'not really
convertible weather, d-man.
Drago:
Time to dump this dump.
Tohru: I hate rain.
Uncle: Quiet.
Chi-o-matic senses presence
of duel demon chi.
Drago must be near.
Jade: So let's throw 'em
a little surprise party,
chan style.
Jackie: Jade, I told you
to stay by the car.
Jade: Hello!
You didn't say which car.
(Tohru shudders)
Drago: Sounds like
we have junkyard rats.
Time to put you all
out of my misery.
All: Aah!
Strikemaster ice: Yo,
it's time to throw down.
Uncle: Jackie, must get closer
to remove thunder demon chi
from snotty-nosed dragon!
Uncle needs distraction.
Jade: Nice timing, t.
Mc cobra: Yo, girlfriend.
You disrespectin'
my hizz-ouse.
Jade: My bad.
I meant to dis you!
Mc cobra: Ha ha ha!
You can run,
but you can't hide.
(Jade imitates buzzer)
Wrong!
Jade: Peek-a-boo!
Jackie: Bwaaa!
Strikemaster ice: You're way
out of your league, gramps.
Uncle: Smarty-pants teenager
want a piece of gramps?
Strikemaster ice: Ha ha ha!
Jade: Up high.
Down low.
Mc cobra: Too slow.
Drago: 2 chans
for the price of one.
Jade: Uh, how come scale face
isn't cooked cajun-style?
Uncle: Thunder demon chi
has allowed drago
to absorb storm's power!
Drago: Rraah!
(Horns honking)
Jackie: Find something that
won't conduct
drago's lightning.
The tires!
Strikemaster ice: Ho ho ho!
Epic light show, d-dude.
(Mc cobra coughs)
Whoa.
They gotta be charcoal
briquettes under there.
Drago: Let's go.
It's moving day.
Jackie: Is everyone all right?
Uncle: Aiyaah!
Uncle not all right!
The longer punk demon
possesses thunder demon chi,
the more difficult it will be
for uncle to remove!
Drew: Oh, yeah.
Float like a butterfly.
Sting like a--
right jab!
Right jab!
Ha! When I'm through,
you're gonna be nothing
but spare parts!
Jade: Dream on, tin man.
Drew: Have a nice trip.
Winner and still
robomercs champion.
Learn from the master,
young one.
Jade: T'ch, right.
Rematch, drew. Now.
It wouldn't be fair.
Face it, Jade,
- you need a lot more practice.
Uncle: Creating fire chi
removal spell is
a very difficult task.
Only much Patience
and concentration
will yield success.
Jade: Please, please,
please, please, please.
I'll do all my chores.
Jackie: You'll do all
your chores regardless.
Jade: Uncle Jackie,
I'm like the only kid
in the world
who doesn't have robomercs.
Jackie: Ohh.
Video games will distract you
from your studies.
Jade: That's not true!
Program in
your mondo cool sayings,
that's creative writing.
Keeping score, that's math.
Honestly, robomercs is
more educational
than homework.
Jackie: We will see.
Jade: Translation:
Fuggedtaboutit.
Tohru: Perhaps a drop
of black widow saliva.
Uncle: Tohru, no!
Aiyaah!
Does uncle's shop
look waterproof?!
Tohru: Ohh.
Security guard:
Keep it movin', boys.
Building's closed
for renovations.
Drago: Right. Ours.
Security guard: Uhh!
Strikemaster ice:
Yo, major d.,
why don't you let me
and the posse
trick out your new digs?
Drago: As long as it doesn't
interfere with my plans.
Strikemaster ice: Sweet.
Capt. Black: This was taken
by a surveillance camera
at pacific steel
outside of Seattle.
Sheet metal, steel girders,
cast-iron pipes.
And that's not all.
Similar crimes have been
reported throughout the area.
Roller coaster cars,
a prefab swimming pool,
even the sound system
at sea breeze stadium.
Jade: Talk about your shop
till you drop.
Jackie: But why is
strikemaster ice stealing
those particular items?
Capt. Black:
No se, compadre.
But, I'll bet where there's
ice, there's a
fire demon.
Tohru: It is very gray here,
very, very gray.
Jade: Cheer up, big t.
It's Seattle,
home of grunge rock,
mega-mocha grandes, and--
Jackie: And soon
the thunderstorm of
the century,
if the weather reports
are correct.
Tohru: Grr.
Jackie: Oh, sorry.
Jade: Come on, t.
I'm treating.
What'll you have?
Tohru: Hmm.
Double mocha latte,
or chocochino
steamed Espresso,
or double decaf half-caff
with a twist?
Uncle: Hot  cha!
À coffee is coffee!
Police radio: All units,
robbery in progress.
Clarksman aircraft
manufacturing.
3 youths on skateboards,
appear armed and dangerous,
possibly using
some sort of flamethrower.
Jackie: Ice.
Tohru: No, thank you.
I prefer my coffee
piping hot.
Jade: Your attention,
please.
This flight has
been grounded.
Strikemaster ice: I thought
we put you dawgs to sleep.
Mc cobra: Ha ha ha!
Uncle: Uhh!
Jade hyah!
Jackie: Where is drago?
Strikemaster ice: Kickin' it
in his new digs, where else?
Love to stay and jaw,
but we've burned
too much daylight as it is.
Peace!
Jade: That's one way
to get more legroom.
(Whooshing)
Jackie: Uhh!
Bwaaa!
Dj fist: Uhh!
Jade: Ooh.
That's gonna leave a mark.
Strikemaster ice:
We outta here.
Jade: Uncle Jackie,
they're getting away!
Jackie: Jade,
what are you doing?!
Jade:
Is this a trick question?
Strikemaster ice:
One chan ka-Bob, coming up!
Strikemaster ice: Yo, d.
Check out the windage
we snagged.
Jade: Gotcha!
Jackie: Jade!
Jade:
I really gotta work on that
"look before you leap" thing.
Jackie: Drago could have taken
Jade anywhere in the city.
Uncle: No. Drago came
to Seattle with a purpose.
Discover purpose, and Jade's
location becomes clear.
Tohru: He certainly did not
come to Seattle
for the weather.
Jackie: Perhaps he did.
Uncle: Jackie, explain.
Jackie: Drago's power
was magnified
when he was struck
by the lightning
at the junkyard, so--
tohru: So his new lair
would be easily accessible
to the power of Seattle's
frequent thunderstorms.
Uncle: One more thing,
taller is better
for lightning rods.
Jade: No way.
Drago's new crib is
the space needle?
Jade: So this is what all
those freaky robberies
were about.
(Whooshing)
Jade: This place rocks!
Mc cobra: Waah! Ooh! Aah!
Jade: Whoa.
Life-sized robomercs.
Strikemaster ice:
Rule number one--
there are no rules.
Mc cobra: Yaah!
Dude,
you're seriously wack!
Strikemaster ice: Word.
Drago, on intercom: Ice!
Strikemaster ice: Yo.
Drago: Playtime's over.
The storm's almost here.
Finish securing
the lightning rod.
Mc cobra: You got it, dawg.
I mean, sir, dawg.
Dawg sir!
Drago: Once I absorb
the storm's lightning,
I'll be able
to wipe out entire cities.
No one will dare oppose me!
(Alarm beeping)
Drago: Except for those chans!
I'll make the adjustments
up on the roof.
You three can deal
with our party crashers.
(Sniffs)
Jade: I gotta warn
uncle Jackie.
Jade, on p.A.: Uncle Jackie!
Come here, uncle Jackie!
Jackie: Jade,
where are you?
Jade: Uncle Jackie,
if you can hear me,
it's a trap!
Ice and his crew are--aah!
Jackie: Jade?
Jade?!
Strikemaster ice: Yeah,
nothing like a roaring fire
to warm up a rainy day.
Strikemaster ice:
Give it up, runt.
No way you gettin'
outta this room alive.
(Music blaring)
Strikemaster ice:
Aah! Aah! Uhh!
Jade: What, no earplugs?
Uncle: Aiyaah-ah-ah-ah!
(Dizzy)
Uncle doesn't feel so good.
Tohru:  Sensei!
Àjackie: Uncle!
Uncle: Can't uncle have
one moment to clear head?
Mc cobra: Uhh!
Ohh!
Uncle: Must uncle
do everything?
Mc cobra: Uhh!
Jade: Uncle Jackie,
drago's up on the roof
tryin' to get supercharged
by the storm.
Jackie: Uncle and I
will stop drago.
Tohru, take Jade outside
to safety.
Tohru: Uh, but it's
raining out there.
Jade: Ohh.
(Elevator music playing)
(Elevator chimes)
Drago: No visitors.
Jackie: Whoa!
Uncle: Aah!
Jackie: I suspect
drago knows we are here.
Tohru: Uhh! Jade,
this is not helpful.
Huh?
Strikemaster ice:
Yo, peewee.
You and me got
some unfinished bidness.
Tohru: Jade, run!
Jade: I got your back, t.!
Tohru: No!
The other way!
Whoa!
Strikemaster ice: Looks like
it's just you and me, homes.
Mano a sumo.
Uncle: This is why uncle's
shop on ground floor.
Tohru: Uhh!
Strikemaster ice: Ha ha ha!
Ah, snap!
Game over.
Jade: Hey, why don't you pick
on somebody your own size?
Think you got game?
Bring it on.
Tohru: Whoa!
Strikemaster ice: Waah!
Jackie and uncle:
Bad day! Bad day!
Jackie: We're pulling
your plug, drago.
Uncle:  Yumo guay guai
à  fie Dee tseio!
Yumo guay guai
Drago: Too late!
The storm has arrived!
Uncle: Jackie!
Jackie: I know!
We need a distraction.
Strikemaster ice:
Not bad for a short stack.
But today, first is best,
and second is dead last.
Jade: Think I'm ready
for that rematch now, drew.
(Gasping)
Jade: Aw,
the ice man's all wet.
We'd better get
you dried off
before you catch
something nasty.
(Whooshing)
Jackie: Bwaaah!
(Gulps)
Uncle:  Yumo guay guai
à  fie Dee tseio!
Drago: Uhh!
Uncle:  Yumo guay guai
à  fie Dee tseio!
Yumo guay guai
Drago: No! Not now!
Aah!
Jade: Ohh!
don't tell me we missed
all the fireworks?
Drago: You can't defeat me!
I'm on top of the world!
Jackie: Jade,
I have reconsidered.
If you promise to play
only after your homework
is completed,
you may have
the robomercs game.
Jade: No, thanks,
uncle Jackie.
Been there. Done that.
Jackie: Well, I am
very proud of you.
Tohru: Jade, I do not believe
this will fit
in the overhead compartment.
Jade: Hey, Jackie, do you like
riding roller coasters?
Jackie: I do like these kind
of exciting games.
Roller coaster, airplane,
everything high, fast.
It makes my blood go fast,
then I like it.
I don't know why I like
these kind of things.