(Gasps)
The infiltration spell
was successful?
Yes.
Now evil shall
truly prevail.
What's uncle
doing now?
Jade,
- if you listened
once in a while,
you might not
need to ask
so many
questions.
What was that?
The incense ritual
honors uncle's teacher,
chi master fong.
(Gasps)
A spirit is among us!
Cool.
It is chi master fong.
He wishes
to tell me something.
He's gonna
have to speak up.
Shh.
To communicate
with the spirits,
we must open
all of our senses.
Darkness approaches.
(Chiming)
An ill omen
from the north.
The falcon
leaves its perch.
What does it
mean, uncle?
Like the falcon,
we must take our leave
northward
to suppress
the forces of darkness.
Duh.
The hidden valley.
Its location has
remained secret
for centuries.
What's
the big whoop?
Looks like any
another misty
monkey valley.
There.
Whoa. Mount chimpmore.
The great idol
of the 3 wise monkeys.
Legend tells that it is
filled with dark chi.
The idol is evil?
No. The 3 wise monkeys
are guardians.
Good wizards
sealed the dark chi
within them long ago
so that humanity
may neither see, hear,
nor speak of such evil.
Hoo.
What is it,
sensei?
The willies.
No doubt the forces of light
have summoned you here
since I possess
the only existing map.
Daolon wong!
The anti-uncle.
So, you have come
to steal the dark chi!
Not steal it,
good chi wizard,
unleash it.
But that will
upset the balance
between good and evil!
Indeed.
(Chanting)
Jackie,
daolon must not
complete his spell!
Go, uncle.
(Chanting)
Unh.
(Groans)
Daolon is gone!
Uncle: As is the idol.
Whoa.
Mount chimpmore
is gone, too!
That is what
I just said.
Daolon is gone,
and he took
mount chimpmore
with him!
Stop shouting, Jade.
I am old, not deaf.
Speak up, Jackie!
I cannot hear you!
How can you see
through this cloud
of dark chi?
There is no dark chi cloud.
Then why
can I not see you?
Uncle, no sound
is coming out
of Jackie's mouth!
Because Jackie is mute.
Uncle, no sound
is coming out
of  your mouth!
Jade is deaf.
Sensei?
And tohru is blind.
What is it?
What'd
uncle say?
We are like
the 3 wise monkeys.
What?!
- Speak up, tohru!
I said,
we are like--
yo, tohru,
over here!
I don't think
"t" can see!
Why were you
not affected,  sensei?
As a student of master fong,
I am protected by
an abundance of good chi.
If I'm deaf
and tohru is blind,
that means uncle
must be mute!
Jackie,
I can't hear you! Duh!
I cannot read your lips.
Your accent is too thick.
Uncle, what are
we gonna do?!
Find daolon wong
and stop him
before he unleashes
more dark chi.
More dark chi?
Your afflictions
are but a demonstration
of its power.
Under daolon's control,
multitudes will be
rendered senseless.
(Yelling in fear)
(All gasp)
Dark chi of ages past,
I summon you forth.
Spread your plague
upon the land.
(Concerned murmuring)
Dark chi, I summon you.
My spell worked before.
Something is missing.
(Chanting)
Of course.
The dark chi
may only be released
in the presence
of a good chi wizard.
Gan. Ren. Chui.
Bring the old man to me.
How can we hope
to defeat daolon wong
in our condition?
By not relying
on your missing senses.
For instance,
I do not see
so well anymore,
so I have strived
to sharpen my hearing.
But you do not
hear so well, either.
So must you 3 strive to
sharpen your other senses.
Whoo. Garlic!
I think we're
downwind from uncle.
See? You are
not handicapped.
You are handi-capable.
Learn to listen
to nature.
Feel the wind
on your face
and the earth
beneath your feet.
Form an image of the world
in your mind's eye.
Ahh.
Maybe we should work
on some alternative
means of communication,
Jackie.
Ok, when you want me
to use my chungking express
maneuver,
give me one of these:
You are
doing very well, tohru!
Yes,  sensei.
It is as if I can see.
Whoa. (Grunting)
Aiya.
Do this for
the high-flying whirlygig.
No. This.
Jackie,
the dark warriors!
They're after uncle!
Let's get 'em!
You want a piece
of uncle?
Hoo.
You will pay for that,
dark warriors!
Dark warriors?
(Tohru yells battle cry)
Dark warrior, be gone!
Whoa.
(Grunting)
(Chanting)
Uncle!
Why would they take uncle?!
Probably to
disable us further.
How will we stop daolon
without  sensei's guidance?
How will we find him?
Whoa.
Chi master fong
will help us find uncle.
We just gotta
open all our senses
like uncle did.
Good idea.
(Bird caws)
East! East!
East!
All: East.
Oh. (Grunting)
Unhand me.
Only once
all of the dark chi
is released--
with your humble
contribution,
my accomplice.
(Grunting)
You will be so sorry!
With the senses
of humankind dulled,
evil shall roam freely.
(Concerned chatter)
I can't see!
Man: Oh, it's dark.
It would appear
you are the appropriate
yin to my Yang,
good wizard.
(Laughing)
Let us venture forth
and spread
more darkness.
No sign of uncle.
Maybe
chi master fong
was
chi master  wrong.
Whoa!
Flying monkeys!
Where?
Daolon's up top,
front and center!
And see that wee bitty
thing next to him?
I'm pretty sure
that's uncle's head!
Hey, my other senses
are sharper!
Ok, team, this is what
we've been training for.
Let's haul deaf,
mute, and blind butt
up that rock!
(Grunts)
Uh, what's that,
Jackie?
You want to join
a bowling league?
(Groans)
(Concerned chatter)
Man: I can't see!
Second man:
Oh, it's dark.
Straight up?
Ready?
(Grunts)
Oh, my mind's eye
sees trouble.
(Tohru grunting)
Whatever you do, "t,"
don't look down.
(Groans)
Oops. Heh.
(Chanting)
I know, I know.
But this time,
it's different, Jackie.
I can be t's eyes
and your mouth.
Besides, do the math.
3 wise monkeys,
3 of us.
And 3 dark warriors.
Whoop.
Ok, you run
interference, Jackie.
We'll get uncle.
(Tohru grunts)
Charge!
Get ready.
Hop!
Your disabled disciples
cannot possibly defeat me.
Not disabled.
Handi-capable.
Whoa! Turn!
Stop! Stop!
Turn.
1, 2, 3, catch!
Jump!
Daolon: Aah!
Hi, uncle!
Looking for these?
Thank you, Jade.
Wave them over--
can't hear you!
(Muffled chanting)
(Spits)
(Daolon coughs)
Very well.
You shall suffer
the same fate
as chi master fong,
good wizard.
I do not think so.
One more thing:
Chi master fong
says hello.
No.
Aah!
No!
Hey, yell
in your own ear!
Whoa. I can hear.
Tohru, are you ok?
(Gasps)
I can speak!
Wah!
I can see!
(Loud)
Where'd mount--
(softer)
I mean, where'd
mount chimpmore go?
Back to the hidden valley,
where it will hopefully
remain for
many more centuries.
How can you
be certain,  sensei?
Have you
learned nothing?!
Chi master fong
tells me so.
And he also tells me
he's pleased
that the balance
between light and dark
has been restored.
Not without casualties.
Look out.
Ooh.
He should've
listened.
Daolon has been cursed
with all 3 afflictions.
He will have
to train very hard
to become
handi-capable.
(Villagers cheering)
Yes.
- Hey, Jackie?
How high can you jump?
After I've broken my ankle,
and also I've
broken my toes.
Right now,
I cannot bend my toes,
and I lose a lot of,
you know, bouncing things.
So, this way,
when I'm making a movie,
I know my own problem--
my broken ankle.
My knees get hurt
because--from the injury.
So, this way, when I run,
it's like, uh,
running, running,
maybe one step
on the chair,
then I jump
to another things.
But I'm fine.
I still can--
still do a lot of things.
And bouncing,
bouncing, bouncing.