(Breathing hard)
A Chinese talisman
in the tip of Mexico.
Uncle wasn't kidding
about the 4 corners
of the globe thing.
Finn: He's
in the pyramid.
Let's move.
Uh, don't pyramids have
mummies inside them, sir?
Only in Egypt.
Why don't we just let chan
find the talisman?
Just take it from him
when he climbs out.
Listen, new guy,
we don't know what power
this ox talisman has.
Chan might come bustin' out
of there 50 feet tall
with laser eyes.
I don't want to fight
giant laser eyes!
Everyone after him!
Now, now, now!
Huh?
Where is it?
Arrghh!
Augh!
Finn: Thanks for all
your hard work, chan.
Hey, where is it?
I don't know!
Finn:
Liar.
Where is the talisman?
Someone else
must've found it.
Years--centuries ago!
I do not believe you.
(Spooky voice)
Ooh-h-h-h-h!
Ooh-h-h-h!
Mummy!
Mummy: Oooh-h-h!
Oooh-h-h-h!
Mummy! Run!
Oooh-h-h!
Jade?!
Qu pasa, Jackie?
Chan!
Run!
(All panting)
After them!
Why are you here?
You are supposed to be
back at the hotel
doing your homework!
Lucky for you
I breezed through.
Tohru was gonna bust you
like a piata.
Thank you, but don't finish
your homework early again.
It's too dangerous.
Whoa, dude!
I'm sorry! I'll bring it
back! Thank you!
Whoa!
- Whoa!
Jade: Oh, yeah!
Aah!
- Aah!
(Sputtering)
Think--think there's sharks?
The ancient pyramids,
the hang-gliders,
the churros!
Mexico is
mondo-coolio, Jackie!
The talisman could be
a million miles away.
Let's ask around,
see what the locals know.
Ooh, mariachis.
Ok, but don't go anywhere.
Uh-huh.
:Hola! I am paco.
What might a charming
seorita such as yourself
be doing this evening?
Eeyeew! Are you
asking me on a date?
Oh, no, no, no.
I am gathering an audience
for El toro fuerte.
El who-o what-e?
El toro fuerte,
Mexico's mightiest wrestler.
He has never lost a match.
I want to grow up to be
just like him.
Wrestling? Tsst!
Everyone knows
it's all fake.
(Gasps)
El toro fuerte is no fake.
El toro fuerte's
undefeatable,
because El toro fuerte
is the best!
Oh, really?
See that guy over there?
He's the best wrestler
in the world.
The mouse man?
He can smack
your boy down.
Cannot.
Can too.
- Can too.
Cannot.
Then the 2 best should meet,
don't you think?
I will see you  and your
mouse man tonight, seorita...
Jade.
Adios, Jade.
Jackie, we  have to go
to the wrestling match.
Nice 'brero.
I'm glad you like it.
They had your size.
Gracias, amigo.
Anyway, I told this boy
that you're the best
wrestler in the world.
You have to prove it.
Jade, one should not fight
for the sake of fighting,
but only when one has
no other choice.
Makes sense.
When you get in the ring
and this El toro guy
starts wailing on you,
you'll have
no other choice.
Uh, you have an interesting
mind, young Jade.
Jackie! You've nothing
better to do tonight.
Oh, I don't?
How about search
for the ox talisman?
But you said yourself
it could be a million
miles away.
Or right under our noses.
Humph! Didn't peg chan
as a sports fan.
What sport?
Wrestling's fake.
Everybody knows that.
You came all the way here,
and you're  not going to
get in the ring?
Jackie!
Buenas noches, Jade.
Paco! Hi.
I see you have
brought a challenger
for El toro fuerte.
Not exactly.
Paco, can you tell me
what this is?
Of course.
It is the sign
of El toro fuerte,
for he is strong
like the ox.
(Whispering)
I would fear him, too,
if I were you.
Come, Jade. We have seats
right in front.
Um, El toro fuerte?
Si.
Uh, I'm from housekeeping.
There's been a mix-up.
Your mask has not been
properly cleaned.
What? El toro fuerte
never removes his mask.
Uh, that's what
I told my boss,
but he won't listen.
He insists you cannot fight
with a dirty mask.
You--
hello, chan.
The talisman?
Huh?!
Get him!
Where'd he go?
Whoa!
- Seor!
It is time.
Amigos, welcome
to  lucha libre!
Tonight 2 titans will clash
here in this very ring.
El pollo enmascarado...
And the undefeated
champion...
El toro fuerte!
Tonight one shall drink deep
from the cup of victory,
and the loser
shall be unmasked!
Where'd they get
this mouse man?
Jackie?
Awesome!
You're gonna do it!
Only because I have
no other choice.
If I win, El toro
will be unmasked,
and I can take the talisman
before valmont's thugs do.
Grrr!
Ooh!
(Chanting)
Tor-o! Tor-o! Tor-o!
Ok then.
Hyiii--oh!
(Groans)
Uno...Dos...Tres!
The winner!
Jade, do not watch.
This is the part where
Jackie must lose his mask
and, regrettably,
his dignity.
It's chan! Get him!
No.
He does not have
the talisman.
Remember, Jackie,
each talisman possesses
a different magic.
Yes, yes, uncle.
12 animals, Chinese zodiac.
One more thing.
What happened
to you?
You lost that match
so fast,
and he gave you
such a whupping!
I know.
He was strong.
Hmm. Perhaps the power
of the ox talisman
is strength.
Oh, of course!
Strength!
One more thing.
Ow!
Jackie! Jackie!
Wake up!
Where is El toro?
He left.
Everyone left!
The match is over.
How could you not win?
Jade, the ox talisman
gives El toro
superhuman strength!
Knew it!
Wrestling is so fake!
Ha ha ha.
Another autograph, paco?
One for your every victory,
seor fuerte.
Gracias.
Finn: El toro.
Meet tohru.
Tohru, toro.
Toro, tohru.
Tohru--
the mask.
El toro fuerte
never removes his mask.
Then I will remove it
for you.
Arrhh!
Aah!
Unnh!
That's it.
New guy quits.
He nailed tohru.
Nobody nails tohru!
(Whistles)
El toro's been
eating his spinach.
The dark hand
will send more.
Paco: More?
This is too exciting!
Aww!
- Aww!
El toro, sir!
Uh, seor.
Ahh, I trust you had
a pleasant siesta.
Listen, bad men
are after you.
They want the talisman.
They know it is magic.
What talisman?
That one.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
On your head.  There. Ow!
Never touch the mask.
You are in danger.
Jade, sing-song:
¶ oh, Jackie ¶
¶ they're here ¶
wrestlers?
Shadowkhan.
Hyah!
Unh!
Told ya Jackie rocks.
Indeed, but El toro
is better.
Is not.
- Is too.
Arrggh!
Hoowah!
Unh! Ohh!
Sorry.
Ha ha! Again?
Unnh!
(Gasps) The mask!
El toro fuerte never
removes his mask!
No!
Jackie!
Put him down!
Put him down
put him down!
Pu--ack!
Oh!
A souvenir for valmont.
Jade was right.
You  are a fake!
Jackie.
Mr. toro, we've  got
to help Jackie.
Paco is right.
I  am a fake.
Come on, come on, come on!
Up we go!
With the power of the ox,
I was undefeatable.
Hah!
I think I hear Jackie
screaming.
You know? The nice guy
you knocked out twice!
He's in big trouble,
and you owe him!
But without the mask,
I can help no one.
Hey, lookee here!
You're golden!
And without the talisman,
the mask is useless.
Forget about the magic!
Look, Mr. toro,
Jackie once told me
the wise seek power
within themselves.
The foolish seek it
within others.
Que?
Yeah, I don't know where
Jackie gets this stuff either,
but what I think it means is
you're not gonna
let a little girl
go fight those bad boys
all by herself, are you?!
Now his legs.
Jackie?
I'll teach that kid
some manners.
Psych!
Auut!
Unh!
- Unh!
Hola, Jackie!
No, no, no! The talisman
is onboard in a box!
Don't let them take off
with it!
Jade!
Huh?
Wha?
(Huffing)
(Gasping)
Aa-aa-aa-aah!
Situation.
(Both grunting)
Jackie: Help!
(Gasps)
Whoa!
Pull me in!
Unh!
I'm not strong enough!
Not strong enough?!
The talisman, duh!
(Both grunting)
Huh? Hey!
Hyah!
Unh!
Well, look at me!
I'm Jackie chan!
And...You're the pilot.
Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
Aah!
(Gasping for breath)
Oh! Ahh.
(Both grunting)
If that is the pilot...
Who's flying
the plane?!
Unhhh!
Aah!
- Aah!
Tsst!
A little help here?
El toro fuerte,
you are no longer my hero.
Mr. toro!
Gracias, Jade,
but I would rather
lose with dignity
than win
by deception.
El toro?
Whatever.
Unh!
- Unh!
Ohh!
- Ohh!
Now tell me...
Who is the mightiest?
Jade:
Give you a clue.
Hyah!
Ohh!
Can I keep it, Jackie?
No.
Aww!
Paco: El toro fuerte!
Will you teach me
the ways of the wrestler?
With all the wisdom
of my experience.
You are the greatest!
Jade: No.
Jackie's the greatest.
No. El toro.
Jackie.
- El toro.
Hey, Jackie,
how do you keep
in shape?
Most important
is the training and
training and training.
All kinds of exercise--
like swimming, boxing,
badminton, tennis, jogging
is good for shape.
Remember,
it's the exercise.
Exercise.
Then you keep in shape.