Wrong, as usual.
The United States' lack of action
in Eastern Europe...
...proves that the Soviet Union's aggression
at the Afghan border...
...will not be opposed publicly
by the United States.
Issue: The Soviet Union continued
its recent series of military exercises...
...conducting a bomb test today
in the Bering Sea...
...just 1500 miles
off the southern coast of Alaska.
President Richard Nixon
issued this warning to the Soviets:
The United States does not start fights.
Let it be clear we maintain our strength...
...in order to maintain peace...
...so any adversary
should ask themselves:
"Do the consequences
of attacking America...
...outweigh the potential benefits?"
As a result of the Soviet activity...
...the watchdog group
of nuclear scientists...
...moved the Doomsday Clock
up to five minutes until midnight...
...destruction by nuclear war.
Question:
On a scale of zero to 10,
zero meaning impossibility...
...10 meaning
complete metaphysical certitude...
...what are the chances the Russians
will actually attack the United States?
Pat Buchanan.
Zero.
The Soviets
would never risk going to war...
...when we have a walking nuclear deterrent
on our side.
You're referring, of course,
to Dr. Manhattan...
...but does Dr. Manhattan's existence
guarantee world peace? Eleanor Clift.
Well, it hasn't
stopped the Soviet Union...
...from stockpiling record amounts
of nuclear weapons.
You don't think it's just posturing?
Maybe the reason
why the Soviets...
...are doing these bomb tests...
...is because they feel threatened
by Dr. Manhattan. Of course.
Maybe the whole world feels like that.
Soviet ships have violated
the territorial waters...
Just a matter of time, I suppose.
It's a joke. It's all a joke.
Mother, forgive me.
I was a hero, goddamn it!
...an act clearly meant to send
a signal to the government in Saigon...
...that violence and oppression
is not the way to peace.
Fuck you, pigs!
Good luck, Mr. Gorsky.
Get out of here, vigilantes!
No!
Edward Blake. Sixty-seven
years old. Six-two, a solid 225.
Guy was built like a linebacker.
Yeah, I saw the body.
For a guy his age,
he was in terrific shape.
You mean apart from being dead?
That's plate glass.
You'd have to step on the gas
just to put a crack in it.
Had to have been thrown.
Check the bedroom?
Yeah. Drawers opened, tossed through.
Mattress flipped. Probably robbery.
Or made to look like one.
See this?
- Shaking hands with the president.
Whoa.
Think Blake was a spook?
Government or black ops?
I think...
...this is way bigger than both of us.
Rorschach's journal, October 12th, 1985.
Dog carcass in alley this morning.
Tire tread on burst stomach.
This city's afraid of me.
I've seen its true face.
The streets are extended gutters...
...and the gutters are full of blood.
And when the drains finally scab over...
...all the vermin will drown.
The accumulated filth of all their sex
and murder...
...will foam up around their waists...
...and all the whores and politicians
will look up and shout, "Save us".
And I'll whisper, "No".
Now the whole world
stands on the brink...
...staring down into bloody hell.
All those liberals and intellectuals...
...and smooth talkers...
...and all of a sudden,
nobody can think of anything to say.
Beneath me, this awful city.
It screams like an abattoir
full of retarded children...
...and the night reeks of fornication
and bad consciences.
Huh.
Tonight, a comedian died in New York.
Somebody knows why.
Somebody knows.
It all started with the gangs.
You know, people tend to forget that.
Pirate outfits, ghosts.
They thought it was funny:
dress up and pull heists.
As soon as we'd arrest them,
they'd be back on the street.
Nobody could pick them out of a lineup
because of the damn masks.
So a few of us cops, we get together...
...and we figure, what the heck,
we'll mask up, too.
We'll finish what the law couldn't.
Pretty soon, the papers get wind of it.
They ran with it...
...and oh, boy, we're a national pastime.
It was me, Dollar Bill, Mothman...
...Captain Metropolis, Hooded Justice...
...Silk Spectre and the Comedian.
Oh, don't get me started on him.
I must be drunk already,
telling you this sob story again.
I think you were trying to make a point.
Well, my point is that we had it too easy.
It wasn't fair what happened to you guys...
You guys who picked up where we left off.
- with Nixon forcing you out.
Nixon, oh, that prick. To think I voted
for that prick five times.
Hey, it was him or the commies, right?
Oh, wow, it's almost midnight.
Gotta go.
Truth?
You were a better Nite Owl
than I ever was, Danny boy.
- Hollis, we both know that's bullshit.
- Hey.
Watch it with the language.
This is the left hook
that floored Captain Axis, remember?
Yeah.
Next week?
Well...
...you know, you don't have to
keep humoring me like this.
If you got a hot date or something...
Hey, us retired guys
have to stick together, right?
You ever miss it?
No. You?
Oh, heck, no.
Be seeing you.
Hello, Daniel.
Rorschach.
Helped myself to some beans.
Hope you don't mind.
No, no. Course not.
You want me to heat those up for you?
Fine like this.
How have you been keeping?
Out of prison.
So far.
Daniel...
...look at this.
Is this bean juice?
Human bean juice.
Badge belonged to the Comedian.
Blood too. He's dead.
Let's talk downstairs.
It could have been a burglary.
Maybe the killer didn't know
who the Comedian was.
An ordinary burglar?
Kill the Comedian? Ridiculous.
I heard he'd been working
for the government since '77...
...knocking over Marxist republics
in South America.
Maybe it was a political killing
or something.
Maybe.
Maybe someone's picking off
costumed heroes.
You don't think that's a little paranoid?
That what they say about me now?
Paranoid?
Look, Comedian made
a lot of enemies over the years...
...even among his friends.
Speaking of friends, how's Hollis Mason?
He wrote that book. Said some bad things
about the Comedian in it.
I don't like what you're implying,
and I like being followed even less.
Maybe I was keeping an eye on you,
in case someone's gunning for masks.
- You were never that sentimental.
- Attack on one is attack on all of us.
What do you suggest we do about it?
Retribution.
- Watchmen are over.
- Says Tricky Dick.
Says me.
Nobody knows who you are.
You can give it up,
try and have a normal life.
That what you have now?
A normal life?
When you walk down the street
in a city dying of rabies...
...past the human cockroaches...
...talking about their heroin
and child pornography...
...do you really feel normal?
Least I'm not the one
still hiding behind a mask.
No.
You're hiding in plain sight.
Be seeing you, Dan.
A maintenance hatch
will let you out two blocks north.
Yeah, I remember.
Came here often,
when we were partners.
Those were great times, huh,
Rorschach?
- What happened?
- You quit.
Mr. Veidt...
...to date,
you're one of only two Watchmen...
...ever to reveal their true identity
to the world...
...the first being Hollis Mason.
And you've certainly profited greatly
by it...
...turning your superhero alter ego,
Ozymandias, into a billion-dollar industry:
Toys, lunchboxes, genetic engineering.
I understand there's a movie
in the works.
- I'm not hearing a question, Mr. Roth.
- I'm sorry. Do you think...
The Watchmen resent me
for prostituting their struggle?
It's a fair question.
Yes, it's crossed my mind...
...some of my old colleagues
might see it that way...
...just as you're clearly aware
that biased journalism...
...sells more magazines.
The merchandising arm of Veidt Industries
is funding our work with Dr. Manhattan.
We recently expanded our research facility
in Antarctica...
...in the hope of developing cheap,
renewable sources of energy...
...that we might eliminate
the world's reliance on fossil fuels.
Now, it doesn't take
a political scientist...
...to see that our Cold War
with the Russians isn't ideological...
...it's based upon fear.
Fear of not having enough.
But if we make resources infinite...
...ah...
...we make war obsolete.
I would hope the other Watchmen
understand that...
...wherever they may be.
Thanks for your time.
- You look good, Adrian.
- Dan.
It's been too long.
So Rorschach thinks
someone's hunting the Watchmen, huh?
You think it's possible?
Statistically, one murder
doesn't equal a trend.
Rorschach's a sociopath, Dan.
And so was the Comedian.
He was practically a Nazi.
You know that better than anyone.
I'm not here because I miss him.
It's occurred to Rorschach...
...that we're the only ones
who know each other's identities.
Actually, the whole world knows yours.
That's why I'm warning you first.
Thank you, Dan...
...but I fear there's something
much more real to worry about...
...than Rorschach's mask killer.
If the Russians do launch their nukes,
can Jon really stop them?
The Soviets have 51,000
warheads stockpiled.
Even if Jon stops 99 percent of them...
...the 1 percent that get through could
still kill every living thing on Earth.
Even Dr. Manhattan
can't be everywhere at once.
Rorschach's journal,
October 13th, 1985...
...8:30 pm.
Meeting with Dreiberg
left bad taste in mouth.
A flabby failure who sits
whimpering in his basement.
Why are so few of us left active...
...healthy and without
personality disorders?
The first Nite Owl
runs an auto-repair shop.
The first Silk Spectre
is a bloated, aging whore...
...dying in a California rest resort.
Dollar Bill got his cape stuck
in a revolving door...
...where he got gunned down.
Silhouette, murdered...
...a victim of her own indecent lifestyle.
Mothman's in an asylum in Maine.
Only two names remain on my list.
Both share private quarters
at Rockefeller Military Research Center.
I shall go to them.
I shall go tell the indestructible man
that someone plans to murder him.
Good evening, Rorschach.
Dr. Manhattan, you know why I'm here.
Yes...
...but you're going to leave disappointed.
Rorschach. You shouldn't be here.
You're a wanted man.
Nice to see you too, Silk Spectre.
I have a real name I've been using.
Try it.
Whatever you say, Laurie.
What are you doing here?
The Comedian is dead.
Rorschach wants me
to look into my future...
...see if the killer is ever
publicly identified.
Already warned Dreiberg.
Came to warn you too.
Even if I wanted to help...
...my future is blocked
by some kind of temporal interference.
- I cannot see it clearly.
- Interference? Caused by what?
In all likelihood, nuclear holocaust.
If the United States and Soviet Union
engage in all-out war...
...the resulting blast wave would produce
a sudden burst of tachyons...
...particles which travel backward
through what you perceive as time...
...therefore obscuring my vision
of the present.
I must return to my work.
Wait a minute.
What if that's why
someone wants us out of the way?
So we can't do anything to stop it?
Goodbye, Rorschach.
Took a lot of effort
to get in here to see you.
I'm not leaving...
...till I've had my say.
Seems like there's a lot of things
you don't tell me these days.
I didn't wanna worry you prematurely.
If Adrian and I can solve the energy crisis,
war may be averted.
But you always say time is simultaneous.
If that's true,
then how can you change the future?
If only you could perceive time as I do.
Please let me show you.
Magic. Dreams. That is what I had before.
I was a hero, goddamn it!
It's not my fault you got old.
What do you have to complain about?
I'm putting food on the table
for you and your child.
Call your friend Eddie.
Maybe he can give you a better life.
- It was a mistake. One time.
- Man tries to rape you...
Stop!
Your mind goes to dark places...
...and you wonder
why I keep the worst from you.
- Say hello to Dan for me.
- What?
You wanna ask me
to go to dinner with you...
...like we used to...
...but you won't.
You know I can't.
So you'll call Dan...
...which is only natural.
You deserve the comfort of an old friend.
Dan Dreiberg's table.
Did you know that
he and H.J. were-? I had no idea.
You remember that crazy guy?
What'd he call himself?
Captain Carnage.
Used to pretend he was a supervillain
just so he could get beat up?
Yeah, he tried that on me once.
I just walked away.
He starts following me down the street
in broad daylight...
...yelling, "Punish me! Punish me!"
I'm just saying, "No, get lost".
God, whatever happened to him?
Oh. Um...
He pulled that on Rorschach...
...and Rorschach
dropped him down an elevator shaft.
Oh, my God. That's not even funny.
- It's a little funny.
- Yep.
I'm glad I ordered
the four-legged chicken.
It's really good to see you again.
It's great seeing you too.
Why'd we do it, Dan? Dress up like that?
- No one else would.
- Yeah, but do you remember my costume?
All that tight latex?
I mean, it was awful.
Uh... Yeah, yeah, awful.
But didn't wanna disappoint Mother.
Wanted her little girl to be just like her
and fight bad guys.
I think the Keene Act was the best thing
that ever happened to us.
Well, we'll live longer anyway.
What?
Jon thinks, unless he can do something
about it...
...that there's gonna be nuclear war.
Soon.
But I don't know what to think.
I mean, it's all...
...quantum mechanics
and parallel realities with him.
I never even know
what universe he's actually seeing.
He just keeps getting further away
from me.
Everyone.
I can't even tell
if he actually cares about me anymore...
...or if he's just pretending.
If he's pretending, it means he cares.
Hold on, I'll get the door.
Thanks, Dan.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I invite you out to dinner to catch up
and have a few laughs...
...but there don't seem to be many laughs
around these days.
What do you expect?
The Comedian's dead.
Laurie? Is that you?
Thought you'd be used
to traveling that way by now.
Well, I'm not.
I hate it when Jon teleports me.
Well, it beats flying coach.
Margarita?
Mother, it's 2:00 in the afternoon.
Mm.
Remember that guy
that writes me letters?
He sent me an item of memorabilia.
It's a Tijuana bible.
This little eight-page porno comic
they did in the '30s and '40s.
- He sent you this? - Sure.
They're very valuable, like antiques.
Mother, this is gross.
I think it's kind of flattering.
Why do you always call me Mother
when you're mad?
I know why you're here.
I can still read, you know.
I saw it in the paper.
Eddie Blake's funeral is today.
Finally got his punchline, I guess.
- Poor Eddie.
- Poor Eddie? After what he did to you?
Oh, Laurie, you're still young.
You don't know.
Things change.
What happened happened 40 years ago.
I'm 67 years old.
Every day, the future
looks a little bit darker.
But the past...
...even the grimy parts of it...
...keep on getting brighter.
I've got spots in my eyes.
Stop it, Eddie.
- Thank you, Weegee.
- Thank you, Mr. Owl.
Tomorrow, 3:00, my studio.
- Little place on 21 st.
- Sounds good.
Wow, a real photo session.
Wonder how my hair will look?
Oh, go ahead. I'll be there in five.
Eddie.
What the hell are you doing here?
You knew I was changing.
Sure I did.
Come on, baby.
I know what you need.
You gotta have some kind of reason
for dressing in an outfit like this.
I said no, Eddie.
- No spelled Y-E-S.
- No spelled N-O.
- All right?
- Come on, sweetheart.
Eddie...
You little bastard.
This what you like?
- This what makes you hot?
- What?
Things are tough all over, cupcake.
It rains on the just and the unjust alike.
The Comedian was a little bit of both.
And he always thought
he'd get the last laugh.
Thou knowest, Lord,
the secrets of our hearts.
Shut not thy merciful ears
to our prayers...
...but spare us, Lord most holy,
O God most mighty...
...O holy and merciful savior.
Thou most worthy judge eternal.
Suffer us not
at our last hour for any...
Fireworks. You gotta be kidding me.
You know, you'd think this goddamn
country had had enough fireworks.
You know, if we'd lost here in Vietnam...
...I think it might have driven us crazy.
You know, as a country.
But we didn't, thanks to you.
You sound bitter.
Me? Bitter?
Fuck, no. I think it's hilarious.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Mr. Eddie?
- Just what I fucking needed.
The war is over now.
We must talk about this baby.
There's nothing to talk about.
See, I'm leaving.
I'm gonna forget about you...
...and your horrible, sweaty,
little piece-of-shit country.
Get the fuck out of here.
- No.
- Get the fuck out of here.
You will remember.
You will remember me and my country...
...forever!
My face!
Blake. Don't.
Blake!
She was pregnant...
...and you gunned her down.
That's right...
...and you know what? You watched me.
You could have turned the gun to steam,
the bullets to mercury...
...the bottle into goddamn snowflakes,
but you didn't, did you?
You really don't give a damn
about human beings.
You're drifting out of touch, Doc.
God help us all.
Medic!
Most holy and merciful savior.
He cometh up and is cut down,
like a flower.
In the midst of life, we are in death.
Welcome to the first meeting-
- This is bullshit.
For a guy who calls himself the Comedian,
I can never tell when you're joking.
Watchmen. That's the real joke.
It didn't work 15 years ago,
and it ain't gonna work now...
...because you wanna play
cowboys and Indians.
Maybe we should agree
on no drinking at meetings.
Rorschach and I have made headway
on the gang problem by working together.
A group this size seems like a publicity
stunt. I'm not in it for the ink.
We can do so much more.
We can save this world...
- ...with the right leadership.
- Yeah.
And that'd be you, right, Ozzy?
I mean, hell,
you're the smartest man on the planet.
It doesn't take a genius
to see the world has problems.
But it takes a room of morons to think
they're small enough for you to handle.
You know, mankind's been trying to kill
each other off since the beginning of time.
Now we finally have the power
to finish the job.
Ain't nothing gonna matter once
those nukes start flying. We'll all be dust.
Then Ozymandias here...
...will be the smartest man
on the cinder.
For as much as it hath pleased...
...almighty God to take onto himself
the soul of our dear departed brother...
...let us therefore commit his body
to the ground.
Earth to earth, ashes to ashes...
Watchmen! Police!
Police to protect the people!
Attention, citizens.
We are trying to maintain order.
You must clear the streets
until the police strike is over.
If you could-
Please, there's no need for violence.
Goddamn it. All right.
That's how you wanna do it?
There's no need for violence.
Fuck you. Fuck you!
Oh, this is getting heavy.
Goddamn, I love working
on American soil, Dan.
Ain't had this much fun
since Woodward and Bernstein.
How long can we keep this up?
Congress is pushing through some new bill
that's gonna outlaw masks.
Our days are numbered.
Until then, it's like you always say:
We're society's only protection.
- From what?
- Are you kidding me? From themselves.
- Son of a bitch.
No, Comedian, wait!
Get your stinking hands off me.
What the hell happened to us?
What happened to the American dream?
It came true!
You're looking at it.
Edgar William Jacobi.
Also known as Edgar William Vaughn.
Also known as Moloch.
What are you talking about?
I'm a retired businessman...
Lie again, Moloch, I break another finger.
I did my time.
I'm not Moloch anymore.
- What do you want from me?
- Heard you attended Blake's funeral. Why?
I just felt I should...
...pay my respects to the Comedian.
- How'd you know he was the Comedian?
- He broke in here. A week ago.
He had his mask off.
- He was drunk.
- Enemies. For decades.
- Why should he visit you?
- I don't know.
I woke up in my bedroom
and there he was.
He was upset.
He was crying.
Crying? The Comedian?
He was babbling, not making any sense.
I was pissing in my pants.
I thought he was gonna kill me.
What did he say?
It's a joke.
It's all a fucking joke.
You know, I thought I knew how it was.
I thought I knew how the world was.
I've done some bad things.
I did bad things to women. I shot kids.
In 'Nam, you know.
But that was fucking war.
This...
I never done anything like this.
God, here I am...
...spilling my guts...
...to one of my archenemies.
But the truth is...
...you're the closest thing to a friend
I got. What the fuck does that say?
Shit.
And your name...
...your name was on the list...
...along with Janey, you know,
whatever the fuck her name is.
Manhattan's old girl.
Mother, forgive me.
And then he left.
I swear I don't know
what the hell he was talking about.
Funny story.
Sounds unbelievable.
Probably true.
So that's it?
- I'm clean?
- You?
Clean?
Amygdalin.
This phony medication
made from apricot pits.
- It's illegal.
- Come on.
Please don't confiscate that.
I'm trying anything.
I have cancer.
What kind of cancer?
You know the kind
you eventually get better from?
That ain't the kind I got.
Rorschach's journal. October 16th.
Want some of this?
Fifty bucks, I'll suck your cock.
- Thought about Moloch's story.
- Come on.
Could all be lies.
A revenge scheme
planned during his years behind bars.
Fuck you. I make more in a week
than you make in a year, you fucking homo.
But if it's true...
...what could have possibly
scared the Comedian...
...enough to cry in front of Moloch?
What was it he saw?
And that list he mentioned.
Edward Blake. The Comedian.
Born 1918.
Buried in the rain.
Murdered.
Is that what happens to us?
No time for friends?
Only our enemies leave roses.
Violent lives ending violently.
Blake understood.
Humans are savage in nature.
No matter how much you try
to dress it up...
...to disguise it...
...Blake saw society's true face.
Chose to be a parody of it. A joke.
I heard joke once.
Man goes to doctor, says he's depressed.
Life seems harsh and cruel.
Says he feels all alone
in threatening world.
Doctor says treatment is simple.
"The great clown Pagliacci is in town.
Go see him.
That should pick you up".
Man bursts into tears.
"But doctor," he says. "I am Pagliacci".
Good joke.
Everybody laugh.
Roll on snare drum.
Curtains.
What time do you have to be
at your interview?
Don't worry.
We've got plenty of time.
Your finger's like licking a battery.
God, Jon, stop. What are you doing?
Please don't be upset.
I always thought you liked this.
No.
I don't- No.
I don't want that.
I don't know
what stimulates you anymore.
Look, I know you were just trying...
Are you working in here
while we're in bed together?
My work with Adrian
is at a critical stage right now.
- I didn't think it was necessary to-
- To what?
To what? To tell me which one of you
is giving me a pity fuck?
My attention was completely focused
on you.
If you think there's a problem
with my attitude...
...I am prepared to discuss it.
You know how everything in this world
fits together except people.
What am I to you?
Another puzzle to be solved?
Have your men stand back.
I'm teleporting the reactor to Karnak now.
You're my only remaining link
to the world.
I don't want that responsibility anymore.
He's all yours.
Don't worry, Jon. She'll be back.
No, she won't.
He's been called
many things: Hero, weapon...
...linchpin of our national security...
...deterrent to nuclear war,
or a man to end worlds.
Later tonight, Dr. Manhattan...
...will answer my questions and yours
in an exclusive interview...
...brought to you commercial-free
by Veidt Enterprises.
Who is it?
It's Laurie.
Sorry. I just had this new lock installed.
I didn't know where else to go.
Oh, it's okay. Come in.
What's wrong?
I left Jon.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know why I'm here. I just...
I don't know anybody else.
I don't know anybody
except for goddamn superheroes.
That's okay.
You probably just had an argument
or something.
No, Dan.
You don't know what it's been like
living with him.
The way he looks at things now,
it's like he doesn't...
...remember what they are.
It's like this world, this real world...
...to him,
it's like walking through mist.
And people are just shadows.
Shadows in a fog.
God, how did everything
get so tangled up?
I'm sorry, Dan.
This is twice now
I've ruined your evening.
Come on. I'm glad you came over.
I was just gonna see Hollis
for our weekly beer session.
You're more than welcome to join.
In fact, I insist.
Terrific. Dr. Manhattan arrives
and no one thinks to tell me.
He just-
- We don't have time for makeup.
That blue is too light for television.
Is that dark enough?
Yeah, that's dark enough.
Seymour.
Bernie, how's tricks?
See this guy behind me?
Been bugging me all week.
Girl.
What we got here?
Here's a list of Pentagon-approved
no-go areas.
Afghanistan will obviously come up,
but just play it cool...
...and try not to get
into any tight corners.
...a renowned nuclear physicist,
who, through a terrible accident...
...was gifted with extraordinary powers,
capable of bending matter to his will.
Today, the world knows him
as Dr. Manhattan.
Welcome.
Thank you.
That's right.
Ms. Black, you have the first question.
Dr. Manhattan, as you know...
...the Doomsday Clock
is a symbolic clock face...
...analogizing humankind's proximity
to extinction...
...midnight representing the threat
of nuclear war.
As of now, it stands at four minutes
to midnight.
Would you agree that we're that close
to annihilation?
My father was a watchmaker.
He abandoned it when Einstein discovered
that time is relative.
I would only agree
that a symbolic clock...
...is as nourishing to the intellect...
...as a photograph of oxygen
to a drowning man.
So you're saying there is no danger.
Even in a world without nuclear
weapons, there would still be danger.
And would you say, as so many claim...
...that you are, in fact, a god...
...given you see the past
and future simultaneously?
I can only see my own past...
...my own future. I am not omniscient.
Doug Roth, your question?
Speaking of your past, Dr. Manhattan...
...do you remember a man
named Wally Weaver?
Yes. We were both physicists together
at the Gila Flats Research Base.
He died of cancer.
- He was a good man.
How about Edgar Jacobi...
...also known as the supervillain Moloch?
You encountered him several times
in the '60s: battles, conflicts.
Did you know that he has cancer as well?
I wasn't told.
And what about
General Anthony Randolph?
He was your handler when you first
started working for the government.
Cancer.
You're suggesting I was the cause.
From where I'm standing,
it's starting to look pretty conclusive.
Even if that's the case, it's irrelevant.
A live human body
and a deceased human body...
...have the same number of particles.
Structurally, there's no difference.
All right. Let's settle down, please.
What about Janey Slater?
You think it makes a difference to her?
Janey?
Your ex-girlfriend?
She was a physicist too.
You saw each other for 11 years.
Doug, one question at a time.
She has cancer as well.
Doctors have given her six months.
Isn't that right, Miss Slater?
You were the world to me, Jon.
You were my whole life.
Do you remember how many times
you said you loved me?
Janey, I wasn't told.
I stuck by you after the accident.
I gave you everything.
This is how you repay me?
- Janey, I wasn't told. I didn't know.
- Damn you, Jon. Goddamn you.
Janey, wait.
- That's it. This interview is over.
Get up there.
Get those cameras off.
Everybody back off.
I need some backup here. Leave him alone.
Please, if everyone
would just go away...
...and leave me alone...
Do you care to comment?
I said, leave me alone!
I am looking at the stars.
They're so far away...
...and their light takes so long
to reach us...
...all we ever see of stars
are their old photographs.
It is July, 1959, and I am in love.
That's great.
- You can pick it up tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Seventy-five cents.
- Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Gosh, Jon, I wish he gave us
a little notice. I'm sure I made a face.
Oh, no, no.
I'm sure that you'll look beautiful.
Her name is Janey Slater.
She is a physicist, like me.
I am 30 years old.
We were introduced by a good friend
of mine from college, Wally Weaver.
It is February 12th, 1981.
Wally dies of cancer,
of which they now say I am the cause.
That night, Janey and I make love
for the first time.
A month from now,
the accident awaits me.
Oh, I'll catch up with you guys.
I think I left my watch inside.
Hey. Let's just wait a second.
I cross the room to the
Intrinsic Field Center. I find my watch.
When I get to the door...
...Wally is turning white.
The program's locked in.
We can't override the time lock.
I am terrified.
Jon?
I'm sorry, Jon...
...but I can't...
Janey, don't leave me!
Don't leave me!
It is May 12th, 1959,
when I'm introduced to Janey.
She buys me a beer...
...the first time a woman
has done this for me.
As she passes me the cold,
perspiring glass...
...our fingers touch.
Yes, Jon, good.
Now it's just a question of reassembling
the components in the correct sequence.
I feel fear...
...for the last time.
A token funeral is held.
There is nothing to bury.
Janey frames the snapshot.
It's the only photograph of me
anyone has.
A circulatory system is seen
by the perimeter fence.
A few days later...
...a partially muscled skeleton
stands in a hallway...
...and screams for a moment
before vanishing.
Oh, God.
Jon?
Is that you?
Nations around the world
reeling from this morning's announcement...
...possibly the most significant event
in recent history.
We repeat, the superman exists,
and he is American.
They call me Dr. Manhattan.
They explain the name
has been chosen...
...for the ominous associations
it will raise in America's enemies.
They are shaping me
into something gaudy...
...something lethal.
In January, 1971...
...President Nixon asks me to intervene
in Vietnam...
...something that his predecessors
would not ask.
A week later, the conflict ends.
Some of the Vietcong forces
wanna surrender to me personally.
Hollis Mason, a retired costume hero,
writes a book.
In it, he calls my arrival
the dawn of the superhero.
I am not sure if I know what that means.
You see, at the time, I was misquoted.
I never said, "The superman exists
and he is American".
What I said was, "God exists,
Now, if you begin to feel an intense...
...and crushing feeling of religious terror
at the concept...
...don't be alarmed.
That indicates only
that you are still sane.
It is Christmas, 1963.
Janey tells me she is afraid, and worried.
She says I am like a god now.
I tell her I don't think there is a God...
...and if there is, I'm nothing like him.
I tell her I still want her...
...and that I always will.
As I lie to her, it is September 4th, 1970.
I am in a room
full of people wearing disguises.
A very young girl looks at me and smiles.
She's beautiful.
After each long kiss, she plants a smaller,
gentler one upon my lips...
...like a signature.
Janey accuses me of chasing jailbait.
She bursts into angry tears,
asking if it's because she's getting older.
It's true.
She's aging more noticeably every day...
...while I am standing still.
I prefer the stillness here.
I am tired of Earth.
These people.
I'm tired of being caught
in the tangle of their lives.
They claim their labors
are to build a heaven...
...yet their heaven is populated
with horrors.
Perhaps the world is not made.
Perhaps nothing is made.
A clock without a craftsman.
It's too late.
Always has been...
...always will be...
...too late.
Mr. President...
...the Soviets have moved their tanks
to just short of the Afghan border.
They are testing us...
...to see if we manufactured
Dr. Manhattan's disappearance...
...to coax a move out of them.
How soon can we be ready
for a preemptive strike?
Two days.
We have a 54 percent chance
of wiping out the entire U.S.S.R...
...before they get their missiles airborne.
Assuming conservative projections...
...of how many Soviet warheads
we destroy beforehand...
...we'll lose all of the East Coast.
The last gasp...
...of the Harvard establishment.
Let's see them think their way
out of fission.
With anticipated wind patterns,
the fallout drift would head south.
Mexico would catch the worst of it.
Most of the farm belt
might remain unaffected.
Not so bad...
...all things considered.
Mr. President...
...what would you like to do?
Take us to DEFCON two.
Begin fueling the bombers.
Dr. Manhattan has two days.
After that...
...humanity is in the hands
of a higher authority than mine.
Let's just hope he's on our side.
Without Dr. Manhattan around...
...to bully the Russians into peace,
Mr. Veidt...
...people are going to need good,
old-fashioned energy to rely on.
You can understand.
The world can't just quit on oil
and nuclear power cold turkey.
You'll dismantle
our entire economy overnight.
You're right, Lee. And why free energy?
Well, "free" is just another word
for "socialist".
We might have to
make a public inquiry...
...into any past communist affiliations
you might have had.
Mr. Lacocca, gentlemen...
...I respect your position...
...and what you've accomplished
as captains of industry. I do.
You wanna know my past? Hm?
Okay. Happily.
It's a matter of public record that by 17,
both my parents were dead...
...leaving me alone.
I guess you could say
I've always been alone.
They say I'm the smartest man in the world,
but the truth is I've often felt stupid...
...at being unable to relate to anyone.
Well, anyone living, that is.
The only person
with whom I felt kinship...
...died 300 years
before the birth of Christ.
Alexander of Macedonia,
or Alexander the Great, as you know him.
His vision of a united world was...
Well, it was unprecedented.
I wanted...
...needed to match
his accomplishments...
...so I resolved to apply antiquity's
teachings to our world today.
And so began my path to conquest.
Conquest not of men...
...but of the evils that beset them.
Fossil fuels, oil, nuclear power...
...are like a drug, and you,
along with foreign interests...
- ...are the pushers.
- Now, listen.
No.
You listen.
The world will survive...
...and it deserves more
than you've been able to provide.
So let's cut to it, shall we?
I'm worth more
than all of your corporations combined.
I could buy and sell you, something
you should factor into your decision...
...should you choose
to make our disagreement public.
I think you know the way out.
Gentlemen.
The toy people wanna talk to you about
new villains for the Ozymandias line.
- Seems all the old villains are dead.
- Mr. Veidt?
- I think I have some ideas.
I think we got off on the wrong foot.
He's got a poison capsule.
Don't bite down, you son of a bitch.
Who sent you? I want a name.
Give me a name!
Suicide pill.
Potassium cyanide.
Guy was dead before he hit the ground.
Thanks, hon.
Then Rorschach was right.
This wasn't some lone nut.
It's an organization:
well-funded, well-equipped.