But who'd wanna kill us now?
I don't know, but it's not safe out here.
So no word from Jon?
No.
Well, listen...
...why don't you come stay with me?
Oh, no.
That's sweet, but I wouldn't wanna impose.
Oh, no. No.
Think of it as doing me a favor.
I wouldn't have to worry about you
being out there.
Okay.
Rorschach's journal, October 21 st, 1985.
On 43rd and 7th, saw Dreiberg
and Jupiter leaving diner.
They didn't know me without my mask.
An affair?
Did she break Manhattan's heart
to engineer his exile...
...make room for Dreiberg?
Does Manhattan even have a heart
to break?
Veidt's assassin was a local lowlife
named Roy Chess.
At his apartment, I found clues.
Seems he worked
at Pyramid Transnational.
I've seen the logo before...
...at Moloch's.
Someone tried to shoot
the world's smartest man today, Moloch.
Guy worked for Pyramid Transnational.
More than a just delivery service,
I take it.
Last time I was here, I saw a pension check
written from the same company.
I'm guessing it's a front set up
by whoever wants us masks dead.
Now, no more lies, Moloch.
Who runs Pyramid?
Rorschach.
This is the police.
We know you're in there.
No. No!
If there's anybody in there with you,
send them out unharmed.
No. No, no, no!
Framed. Walked right into it.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Never, never surrender.
All right.
I hope you're ready, hero.
When you are.
One...
...two...
...three.
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
- Christ, he stinks.
- Get that mask off him.
- I got it.
- No. No!
My face! Give me back my face!
The masked vigilante Rorschach
was apprehended...
...and identified
as Walter Kovacs, a 35-year-old white male.
Little's known about Kovacs,
but he was charged with the murder...
...of Edgar Jacobi, found shot in the head
in his home in the Bronx.
Police officers were injured
and Jacobi's home was set ablaze...
...during the violent course
of the capture.
Rorschach!
I'm gonna fuck you
like I fucked your mother!
Come on out, Rorschach!
Walter Kovacs.
Is that your name? Walter?
Well, let me explain
your situation here, Walter.
You cooperate with me...
...and I may be able to convince them
that you should be treated medically.
In a hospital. I believe
that would be good for you.
But the authorities wanna put you
with the general population.
- Prison's a prison.
- Uh-huh. Yes.
But the difference is, down there...
...you'd be eaten alive.
You're responsible for a lot of them
being in prison here, Walter.
Tell me what you see.
A pretty butterfly.
What about now? What do you see here?
Mom?
Is he hurting you?
You got a fucking kid in here.
I get that at home.
Bastard.
I should have had that abortion.
Some nice flowers.
I heard this guy's mom's a whore.
Did you catch any diseases from her?
Huh? Whoreson. Listen to me, retard.
Hey, you think she'd suck my dick
for a dollar?
Clouds.
Tell me about Rorschach.
Will you do that, Walter?
You keep calling me Walter.
I don't like you.
You don't like me.
All right, why is that, exactly?
You're fat.
Wealthy. Liberal sensibilities.
You wanna know about Rorschach?
I'll tell you about Rorschach.
I was investigating a kidnap case.
Blaire Roche.
Six-year-old girl. I was young then.
Too soft on criminals.
I let them live.
Broke a man's arm to get a tip.
Led me to the missing girl's location.
I knew the girl was here...
...but when I searched the place,
I saw nothing.
And then I found her.
It was dark when the murderer got back.
As dark as it gets.
Oh, God.
Who's out there? Who is it?
Who is it?
What? What the fuck?
Who the fuck are you?
What the fuck do you want?
You killed my dogs, man!
You think I had something to do
with that girl? I found that.
What evidence have you got?
That's nothing.
Okay. I confess.
I kidnapped her. I killed her.
Arrest me.
What? Arrest me!
I did it! I said I did it!
Christ.
Look, I've got a problem, man.
Fucking take me in. I need help.
No, don't. Don't do that.
Take me in. Don't! No!
Men get arrested.
Dogs get put down.
Tremors of impact shook my arm.
Warm blood splashed my face.
Whatever was left of Walter Kovacs
died that night with that little girl.
From then on, there was only Rorschach.
See, doctor,
God didn't kill that little girl.
Fate didn't butcher her
and destiny didn't feed her to those dogs.
If God saw what any of us did that night,
he didn't seem to mind.
From then on, I knew:
God doesn't make the world this way.
We do.
Hey, Rorschach.
Hey, you're pretty famous, right?
Rorschach, I heard your mother
was a whore.
Hey, you know what?
I'm pretty famous too.
- Ain't that right? That's right.
That's right.
Maybe I can give you an autograph.
What you say, big boy?
None of you seem to understand.
I'm not locked in here with you.
All right, that's it!
You're locked in here with me.
Laurie!
Shit.
Hold on.
- Fuck.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I'm so sorry. I was snooping
and must have hit the wrong button.
- Are you hurt?
- No, no.
- Okay.
- I'm fine. I just feel so bad.
No, don't worry.
It's happened before.
Comedian did it back in '77.
Archie survived that.
Archie?
Oh. Well, uh, short for Archimedes...
...Merlin's pet owl.
Stupid nickname.
How did you ever afford
all this stuff, anyway?
Well, my dad was in corporate banking
and left me a lot of money when he died...
...which always surprised me.
I mean, he was...
I think he was disappointed
I went into crime fighting...
...instead of following him.
Guess I was just more interested in
birds and airplanes, mythology and...
Must be nice having a secret identity.
A secret place that nobody knows about.
You can just come down here and hang out
without anyone checking up on you.
Nobody watching you.
Wanna try those on?
There we go.
Wow, these rock.
They amplify the spectral range.
Thermal imaging.
They work even better in the dark.
You can see me, right?
I can see everything.
I remember, no matter how black it got...
...whenever I looked through those goggles,
everything was as clear as day.
This must be the way Jon sees the world.
We should probably head up.
Food's getting cold.
Put those away when you're done.
Soviets are
finding themselves bogged down...
...in bloody house-to-house fighting.
Casualties on both sides
are said to be in the hundreds.
Civilian deaths are also alarmingly high.
Dan.
Jon sees a lot of things...
...but he doesn't see me.
Well, uh...
Oh.
Sorry.
Come here.
What's the matter?
- If you could just move a little...
- Okay.
Yeah. There you go.
Soviet ambassador to the U.N.
had no comment...
...when asked if Dr. Manhattan's
disappearance...
...has fueled Soviet aggression
in Afghanistan.
Dan, what's wrong?
Sorry, I...
Yeah, I just need a couple minutes.
Oh, hell.
It's been a long time, Rorschach.
Big Figure.
Small world.
I like that.
But you know, it is a small world in here.
And I've been in it for,
how long now, Lloyd?
Almost 15 years, Mr. Figure.
That's right.
Fifteen years since you
and that Owl fella put me away.
So...
...Rorschach, that guy you burned is dying.
Could go any minute.
You know, by my count, there are more
than 50 people in here that you put away.
I been talking to every one of them
and they're all dying to get a piece of you.
This place is gonna explode!
Then, you die by inches.
Tall order.
I'm gonna tear this guy a new hole.
Relax, Lawrence. Soon.
Come on.
Dan?
Is everything all right?
I'm tired of being afraid.
Afraid of war...
...afraid of the mask killer...
...and afraid of this goddamn suit...
...and how much I need it.
Me too.
So to hell with it.
Let's take Archie out.
You're serious.
I used to be a masked avenger too,
remember?
I'm used to going out at 3 in the morning
and doing something stupid.
Rapid burner. Be advised, all units.
Tenement fire at 5th and Grand.
Rapid burner.
Let's go.
I can see it.
All right, hold on.
Dan, there are kids in there.
Everyone, stay where you are
and remain calm.
We're gonna get you out of there.
The roof's starting to cave.
Get me in there.
I'm gonna get you close.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
All right.
We're all set.
Is that everyone?
Bye.
Bye!
I can't believe we did that.
- They'll lock us up with Rorschach.
- Who cares?
World War llI could start tomorrow.
Right?
Right.
Come back here!
He's dead, Rorschach.
While everyone's distracted, we thought
we'd bring you a housewarming gift.
Something from the machine shop.
Hey, boss, you notice?
None of that "small world,
tall order" crap.
He knows once we slice open his lock,
he's next on the block.
Fat chance.
You're dead, Rorschach!
We got a prison full of killers out here.
What do you got?
Your hands, my pleasure.
Can't reach the lock. Should I cut the bars?
This riot won't last.
I been waiting 15 years for this.
I'm sorry, Lawrence, but you're in the way
of my revenge.
Nothing personal, big guy.
Boss! Wait!
Now you find out what the score is.
One-nothing. Come and get me.
Come on.
So I've been thinking.
I feel that we have an obligation
to our fraternity.
- I think we ought to spring Rorschach.
What?
Someone set him up.
And this whole cancer thing with Jon,
it just doesn't make sense.
You didn't get it.
Yeah, but breaking
into a maximum-security prison...
- ...is a little different than putting
out a fire. - Yeah, you're right.
It'll be more fun.
Hurry, Lloyd. I wanna
smell this son of a bitch cooking.
Yes.
No.
Never disposed of sewage
with a toilet before. Obvious, really.
Two-nothing. Your move.
Get out of the way!
No. No.
Where's my face?
Don't kill me.
Your turn, doctor.
Tell me, what do you see?
Don't move!
Rorschach.
Daniel. Miss Jupiter.
Excuse me. Have to visit men's room.
Oh, for chrissake.
Are you all right?
Yeah. Just...
...heavy, you know?
War, jailbreak.
Don't worry about it. Okay?
Everything's gonna be fine.
- Hello, Laurie.
- Jon.
- TV said you were on Mars.
- I am on Mars.
You and I are about
to have a conversation there.
What are you talking about?
You're going to try to convince me
to save the world.
- Laurie, don't.
- Dan, trust me.
I have to go.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Forgive me. These things sometimes
slip my mind.
It won't happen again.
That's comforting.
Oh, my God.
I'm on Mars.
We need to hit up
underworld contacts, squeeze people.
Sure, why don't we just pick names
out of a phone book?
You forgot how we do things, Daniel.
You've gone too soft. Too trusting.
Especially with women.
Okay, no. Listen, I've had it with that.
God, who do you
think you are, Rorschach?
You live off people
while insulting them...
...and no one complains because they think
you're a goddamn lunatic.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that, man.
Daniel...
...you are a good friend.
I know it can be difficult
with me sometimes.
Forget it.
It's okay, man.
Let's do it your way.
Oh, God.
Pyramid Transnational.
Anyone heard of it?
Oh, you bastards.
I buy everyone a round
and you sell me out like this?
Back off, or I'll stick this glass
in your squidgy face.
Everybody stay calm.
We'll try to keep this brief.
Roy Chess. On Pyramid payroll.
Tried to kill Adrian Veidt. Dead now.
Did you know him?
No.
Yeah, yeah!
- I hired him. I knew him from the inside.
- You're a felon.
I was. I've been straight
ever since I got out, I swear.
I barely knew Chess that well,
but I was told to hire from the old life.
- Told by whom?
- My contact, Miss Slater.
Janey Slater works for Pyramid too?
Yeah, she was real nice. She said hiring
ex-cons was part of the company program.
Give people a second chance.
God, please let go! I'm telling the truth!
Janey Slater, Manhattan's old girlfriend.
Adrian might help us
find out who's underwriting Pyramid.
Follow the money.
This is where we hold our conversation.
In it, you ask me
to stop the imminent nuclear war.
But why would I save a world...
...I no longer have any stake in?
Then do it for me.
If you really care.
When you left me, I left Earth.
Does that not show you that I care?
My red world here, now...
...means more to me than your blue one.
Let me show you.
Bombers are fueled and ready, sir.
It's time, gentlemen.
Take us to DEFCON one.
Not in penthouse. Not in office.
What nocturnal proclivities
entice a man with everything...
...out into the night at this hour?
I'm gonna look for Adrian's itinerary.
Maybe he keeps on file.
- Something's not right.
- Agreed.
Janey Slater, Moloch, Roy Chess
all work for Pyramid.
Moloch said the Comedian mentioned list
with his and Slater's name on it.
Whoever owns Pyramid
could be giving these people cancer.
Setting Manhattan up.
Funny.
Ancient pharaohs looked forward
to the end of the world.
Believed cadavers would rise,
reclaim hearts from golden jars.
Must currently be holding breath
in anticipation.
Pharaohs?
Got a psych profile on Manhattan.
See what the corporate head-peepers say.
"Subject continues
to retreat emotionally.
If the only remaining ties
were to be severed...
...we predict total detachment
from the human condition".
I'm in.
No.
Congratulations, Mr. Veidt.
Dr. Manhattan's energy reactor is online.
Your support and your enthusiasm...
...is what has led to this triumph.
On behalf of the research team,
we salute you.
- Cheers.
What in life
does not deserve celebrating?
This is the new Karnak.
This represents the culmination of a dream
more than 2000 years old...
...a dream now assured
because of your unquestioning assistance.
And for this...
...I am ashamed...
...ashamed that you must now share
such inadequate a reward.
To the pharaohs...
...their greatest secrets
entrusted to their servants...
...buried alive with them
in sand-floored chambers.
Sleep well, gentlemen.
Our new, peaceful world
will be indebted...
...to your great sacrifice.
Bubastis.
Rorschach's journal. Final entry.
Veidt's behind everything.
Why?
What's his endgame?
I cannot imagine
a more dangerous opponent.
Used to joke he was fast enough
to catch a bullet.
He could kill us both alone in the snow.
That's where we're going now:
Antarctica.
Whether I'm alive or dead
upon this reading...
...I hope the world survives long enough
for this journal to reach you.
I live my life free of compromise...
...and step into the shadow
without complaint or regret.
Rorschach, November 1 st.
Can't you just tell me how
this ends and save us the trouble?
It ends with you in tears.
Tears? So you don't come back to Earth.
At some point, yes.
The streets are filled with death.
Jon, please.
You have to stop this. Everyone will die.
And the universe will not even notice.
In my opinion, the existence of life...
...is a highly overrated phenomenon.
Just look around you.
Mars gets along perfectly well
without so much as a microorganism.
Here, it's a constantly changing
topographical map...
...flowing and shifting around the pole
in ripples 10,000 years wide.
So tell me...
...how would all of this be greatly improved
by an oil pipeline?
By a shopping mall?
So it's too much to ask for a miracle?
Miracles, by their definition,
are meaningless.
Oh, God, Jon!
- Only what can happen does happen.
- Just stop your bullshit.
Land this thing. Now.
As you wish.
You know what?
You can send me back to Earth
to fry with Dan and my mom...
...and all the other worthless humans.
But know that you were wrong.
You said this ended with me in tears...
...and look: nothing.
Maybe you were wrong about everything.
You complain that I refuse to see life
on life's terms...
...yet you continuously refuse
to see things from my perspective.
- You shut out what you're afraid of.
- I'm not afraid.
You want me to see things your way?
Go ahead, show me. Do that thing you do.
Magic. Dreams. That is what I had before.
I was a hero, goddamn it!
It's not my fault you got old.
What do you have to complain about?
I put food on the table
for you and your child.
Call your friend Eddie.
Maybe he can give you a better life.
Even the grimy parts of it...
...keep on getting brighter.
You're Sally Jupiter's kid.
You're the Comedian, right?
You were pretty cool in there.
You know, your mom, she was one
of the all-time champion beauties.
- You got her eyes, you know. You got-
- Take your hands off her.
Hey, doll. Long time no see.
Not long enough in my book, Eddie.
Get in the car.
Now.
Are there no depths you won't sink to?
Jesus Christ, Sally.
Can't a guy talk to his...
...you know, old friend's daughter?
Drive.
It was a mistake. One time.
Guy tries to rape you, and years later,
you let him finish the job?
What? Were you drunk or just lonely?
Am I ever gonna live this down?
Laurie.
No.
No, not him.
The Comedian...
...was your father.
No.
No! No! No!
My life is just...
...one big joke.
I don't think your life is a joke.
Yeah, well...
...I'm sorry if I don't
trust your sense of humor.
Will you smile...
...if I admit I was wrong?
About what?
Miracles.
Events with astronomical odds
of occurring...
...like oxygen turning into gold.
I've longed to witness such an event,
and yet I neglect...
...that in human coupling...
...millions upon millions of cells
compete to create life...
...for generation after generation...
...until finally, your mother...
...loves a man...
...Edward Blake, the Comedian,
a man she has every reason to hate...
...and out of that contradiction,
against unfathomable odds...
...it's you...
Only...
...you.
...that emerged.
To distill so specific a form...
...from all that chaos...
...is like turning air into gold.
A miracle.
And so...
...I was wrong.
Now dry your eyes, and let's go home.
We got a bearing on that artificial
structure. Heat signature's off the charts.
- Veidt.
- I don't like the way Archie's kicking.
- The engines.
- They're icing up. Hold onto something.
Daniel, you're coming in too low.
Don't wish to interfere,
but perhaps should pull up sharply...
I know! I'm trying.
I'm trying to pull him up, goddamn it!
I'm gonna redirect the heat from
the flamethrower to speed up deicing...
...but it's gonna take a while
and we don't have time to wait.
You need something warmer.
Fine like this.
What is it, girl?
Mm.
Adrian's a pacifist.
He's a vegetarian, for chrissakes.
He's never killed anyone in his life.
Hitler was vegetarian.
You're squeamish, leave him to me.
We won't get second chance.
Gentlemen.
- Welcome.
- Adrian, we know everything.
Then what's there to discuss, Dan?
Plenty. You killed Comedian.
May he rest in peace.
Blake figured it out first.
Nixon had him keeping tabs on us,
making sure we weren't rocking the boat.
Blake found out what I was doing
here in Karnak...
...and by the time he visited poor Moloch,
he was cracking badly.
Even I couldn't predict he'd be the one
to have a change of heart.
So...
...I had to kill him.
Then I neutralized Jon. No easy task.
I put roughly $2 billion
into tachyon research...
...to block Jon's vision of the future.
You used his psych profile
to manipulate him.
Got him to leave the planet.
I've known Jon long enough
to see he isn't devoid of emotion.
His subtle facial twitches wouldn't be
noticed by the layman, but to me...
...he might as well have been sobbing.
All I needed to do was tug on the thread.
The sudden flood of emotion Jon felt...
...when he came to believe
he'd given cancer to the people he loved...
...was all the excuse he needed
to leave Earth.
Your bullshit assassin.
You paid him to throw us off.
Mr. Chess gave his life
in the service of a higher cause, Dan.
I put a cyanide capsule in his mouth...
...leaving only one loose end:
You, and your mask-killer theory...
...one you followed
with the tenacity of a true sociopath.
I tipped off the police.
Once you were in prison,
I was able to move forward.
Sorry to disappoint you.
We were supposed to make the world
a better place.
Dan, that's exactly what I am doing.
Nuclear war?
Human extinction?
Of course, my moral safeguards
gave me pause at the necessary sacrifice.
A few key regions around the globe...
New York, Los Angeles, Moscow,
Hong Kong.
...disintegrated in an instant.
Fifteen million people killed...
...by Dr. Manhattan himself.
The world's punishment
for flirting with World War III.
Jon wouldn't do that.
A fact no one outside this room
ever has to know.
The energy breakthrough I was working on
just came to fruition.
All these years, Jon was helping me
replicate his power...
...unaware of how I planned to use it.
You see...
...the Comedian was right.
Humanity's savage nature
will inevitably lead to global annihilation.
So in order to save this planet...
...I had to trick it...
...with the greatest practical joke
in human history.
- Killing millions.
- To save billions.
A necessary crime.
You know we can't let you do that.
"Do that," Rorschach?
I'm not a comic-book villain.
Do you think
I'd explain my masterstroke to you...
...if there were even the slightest
possibility you could affect the outcome?
I triggered it 35 minutes ago.
Jesus Christ, Henry.
Why the hell
didn't we get a launch detection?
It's not the Soviets, sir.
Intel indicates the energy signature...
...was generated by...
...Dr. Manhattan.
Jon.
Interference.
Cataclysmic interference.
I can't believe it happened.
This wasn't caused by nuclear warheads.
It was me.
I...
...did this.
- What do you mean, you did this?
- Not directly.
It was made to look like I did it.
Adrian.
Speak of the devil.
Jon-
I know.
Must stop him.
Killed Blake, killed millions.
Wait here.
Adrian, stop this.
The tachyons were clever...
...but even if I can't predict where
you are, I can turn the walls to glass.
I should thank you.
I'd almost forgotten the excitement
of not knowing...
...the delights of uncertainty.
Forgive me, girl.
You're such an asshole.
Veidt, you bastard.
- If you've hurt her, I'Il-
- Dan...
...grow up. My new world
demands less obvious heroism.
Your...
...schoolboy heroics are redundant.
What have they achieved?
Failing to prevent Earth's salvation...
...is your only triumph.
I'm disappointed in you, Adrian.
I'm very disappointed.
Reassembling myself
was the first trick I learned.
It didn't kill Osterman.
Did you really think it would kill me?
I have walked across the surface
of the sun.
I have witnessed events
so tiny and so fast...
...they can hardly be said
to have occurred at all...
...but you, Adrian, you're just a man.
The world's smartest man...
...poses no more threat to me...
...than does its smartest termite.
What's that?
Another ultimate weapon?
Yes.
You could say that.
...came under attack.
Millions of lives were suddenly ended...
...in an act of evil
perpetrated by Dr. Manhattan himself.
Since the attacks,
I have been in constant contact...
...with the premier of the U.S.S.R.
Putting aside our past differences...
...we have both pledged to unite...
...against this common enemy.
With the rest of the world...
...we will prevail.
This is a day we shall never forget.
And yet we go forward
to defend the human race...
...and all that is good
and just in our world.
Thank you. God bless us all.
Do you see?
Two superpowers retreating from war.
I've saved the earth from hell.
We both have.
This is as much your victory as it is mine.
Now we can return...
...do what we were meant to.
We were meant to exact justice.
- Everyone's gonna know what you've done.
- Will they?
By exposing me, you would sacrifice
the peace so many died for today.
- Peace based on a lie.
- But peace...
- ...nonetheless.
- He's right.
Exposing Adrian would only doom the world
to nuclear destruction again.
No. We can't do this.
On Mars...
...you taught me the value of life.
If we hope to preserve it here...
...we must remain silent.
Keep your own secrets.
Don't even think about it.
Rorschach.
Wait.
Never compromise.
Not even in the face of armageddon.
That's always been the difference
between us, Daniel.
I've made myself feel every death...
...see every innocent face
I've murdered to save humanity.
- You understand, don't you?
Without condoning...
...or condemning...
...I understand.
Out of my way. People have to be told.
You know I can't let you do that.
Suddenly you discover humanity?
Convenient.
If you'd cared from the start,
none of this would have happened.
I can change almost anything...
...but I can't change human nature.
Of course
you must protect Veidt's new utopia.
What's one more body
amongst foundations?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Do it.
Do it!
No!
I'm leaving this galaxy
for one a little less complicated.
I thought you said you cared
about life again.
I do.
I think maybe I'll create some.
Goodbye, Laurie.
Come on.
Come on!
Dan...
...a world united and at peace.
There had to be sacrifice.
No! You haven't idealized mankind,
you've deformed it.
You've mutilated it.
That's your legacy.
That's the real practical joke.
We repeat, there is
nothing wrong with your television set.
You are about to participate
in a great adventure.
You are about to experience
the awe and mystery...
...which reaches from the inner mind
to the outer limits.
Sure you don't want a drink?
I'm okay.
Cheers.
There's something I need
to get off my chest.
I know that Eddie Blake was my father.
Laurel.
What you must think of me.
I'm sorry I never told you.
I should have...
...but I don't know, I just felt ashamed.
I felt stupid.
It doesn't matter.
People's lives take them strange places.
They do strange things...
...and, well,
sometimes they can't talk about them.
I know how that is...
...but I just want you to know...
...that you never did anything wrong
by me.
You asked me why I wasn't mad at him.
Because he gave me you.
Thanks, Mom.
I love you.
- Hello, Miss Jupiter.
- Oh, Sally, please.
Excuse me. Gotta go freshen up.
I'll be right back.
- So how's it going up here?
- Good. How's it going down there?
Good. I think I've got everything working.
All of Archie's systems are upgraded.
Finished the tinkering for now...
...so all we gotta do is take her out.
Well, that sounds like a date.
Are we gonna be all right?
Long as people think Jon's
still watching us, we'll be all right...
...in the end.
I know what Jon would say:
Nothing ends.
Nothing ever ends.
Seymour, we got nothing
to write about anymore.
Everyone in the country...
...every country in the world
are holding hands...
...and singing songs
about peace and love.
It's like living in a goddamn
global hippie commune.
Well, Ronald Reagan says he's gonna
be running for president in '88.
We could run a piece on that.
Seymour, we don't dignify absurdities
with coverage.
This is still America, damn it.
Who wants a cowboy in the White House?
Okay. I could look for something
in the crank file.
Crank file.
Whatever. Take some initiative.
Run whatever you like.
I leave it entirely in your hands.
Rorschach's journal, October 12th, 1985.
Tonight, a comedian died in New York.