♪♪♪
Ahh!
[LAUGHING]
Will you please stop
bothering my kid?
Sorry.
Arthur,
I have some bad
news for you.
[LAUGHING]
This is the last time
we'll be meeting.
You don't listen do you?
You just ask the same
questions every week.
How is your job?
Are you having any
negative thoughts?
All I have, are
negative thoughts.
[TV PLAYING]
-And finally...
in a world where everyone
thinks they can do my job,
check out this guy.
When I was a little boy
and told people I was
gonna be a comedian,
everyone laughed at me.
Well no one's laughing now.
You can say that again, pal.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
♪♪♪
It's so awful isn't it?
For my whole life,
I didn't know if I
even really existed.
But I do.
And people are
starting to notice.
Do you think this is funny?
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
-Is this a joke to you?
-Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Eh...Murry,
one small thing.
-Yeah?
-When you bring me out,
can you introduce me as Joker?
♪♪♪