Listen.
OK, you win.
But can you turn off that music?
You know I hate that song.
Why won't you say anything?
Say something, damn it!
You're there.
And you're watching me.
What do you think?
You think you can fool me? No.
No. You can't fool me!
I can feel your presence...
and your movements.
I can even smell you.
And if you think, you son of a bitch...
that I'm going to hang myself
while you're there...
We should ask for more time
with the Hubble telescope to study.
- What's up?
- She fainted.
- What happened to her?
- Julia? What is it?
- Julia, are you OK?
- Bring some water.
It's OK, Julia.
- Let her breathe.
- Julia, what happened?
- She fell down.
- Call a doctor.
- No. I'm OK.
- You sure?
It's my sister.
This is Sara. I can't take your call...
Is it wise to turn up like this
after six months?
I just need to know she's OK.
Sara!
Maybe she's gone out.
No. Something's happened to her.
The power is out.
The fuses seem OK.
I'm going to look upstairs.
Sara?
Isaac, she's not here.
Let's ask the neighbors.
- Don't come down.
- Why not?
What is it?
Isaac, what is it?
- What is it?
- Julia.
- What is it, Isaac?
- Come with me.
Inspector.
I'm sorry.
No, thanks.
The forensics team say Sara took her
own life last night during the power cut
but we need to find out why.
I hear she had a degenerative disease.
Yes, a progressive loss of her sight.
Like my wife.
But Sara went blind a year ago.
How was she coping with that?
She wasn't depressed,
if that's what you mean.
In fact...
she was going to have an operation.
She was waiting for a donor, but...
she hoped to regain her sight.
Perhaps she got tired of waiting.
All right.
Yes, thank you.
Dr. Román can't come to the funeral.
He sends his condolences.
He also said he'll check your eyes
before we go.
Isaac, the power is back on.
Darling, are you listening?
The CD player. Did you hear it?
- Yes.
- Don't you think it's weird?
That Sara was listening to music
before she...
And she hated that song.
- Julia...
- What if she wasn't alone?
- What if she was with someone?
- Julia, please.
We'll never know why your sister did this.
We hadn't heard from her in months.
But it's strange,
I need to know what happened.
Don't work yourself up.
I'm not thinking about myself now.
Somebody has to.
Stress could cause an attack of blindness.
Isaac, I've had two attacks in five years!
And you've lost 20 percent of your vision.
Oh, not again!
Any luck?
Nothing. Not even a candle.
It's time to meet the neighbors.
OK, hurry.
Isaac?
Julia.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry for your loss.
My name's Blasco. I live next door.
I didn't really know
your sister very well, but...
Lía really liked her
and she asked me to give you these.
- Lía?
- My daughter.
Sara used to lend her books.
The poor girl is really upset...
and she didn't even want
to get out of the car.
Right, OK.
Excuse me.
Lía would like to know
if Sara left a note.
We don't know anything.
I understand, I understand.
Well, I won't disturb you any longer.
Shall we continue?
A neighbor and his daughter?
I didn't know she was so alone.
But I forgave her...
and I also forgive you.
Now I have to forgive myself
for not being there.
Although I did all I could, didn't I?
The autopsy shows nothing unusual.
You checked every fingerprint
in the house?
And we only found ours and hers.
Yes, but...That song...
And what about at the cemetery?
Julia, there's nothing to suggest
anybody was with your sister.
And nobody saw or heard
anything suspicious.
If you like, you can ask Soledad.
- Who?
- An old lady who lives opposite.
She helped your sister a lot
when she went blind.
Don't be long.
Where did you say she lives?
Follow the rope in the yard.
What rope?
The old lady doesn't know anything.
Apart from you, nobody else knew.
But you must talk to your wife.
She'll find out sooner or later.
I'm waiting for the right time.
Mrs. Soledad?
Hello?
Who is it?
I'm Julia, Sara's sister.
I'll be right out.
Excuse the mess.
I'm sure the house is quite disgusting.
Hello.
- Are you there?
- Yes.
Sorry. I didn't know you were...
No, I'm sorry.
I wanted to go
to your sister's funeral, but...
it took me an hour
to find a matching pair of shoes.
That's all right.
You were Sara's friend, weren't you?
When she started losing her sight...
a year ago, we had some long chats.
But lately, she hardly spoke to me.
She'd made new friends.
What new friends?
Younger people, you know...
From the Baumann Center.
The Baumann Center? What's that?
A center for the blind, not far from here.
One of those places where they tell you
you can still do anything you like
despite being blind.
If you can't hear, you're deaf.
If you lose an arm, you're a cripple.
If you can't see, you're blind.
And nothing is like it was before.
Mrs. Soledad, can you tell me
where to get a taxi?
Thanks.
BAUMANN CENTER
- Yes, go down the stairs.
- Thanks.
I'm going to miss her.
You didn't even like her.
No, that's not true.
I don't understand why she did it.
Poor Sara. But to hang yourself
in the basement?
How about a minute of silence?
- Don't be cruel, Nora.
- Cruel? None of us could stand her.
But don't you think it's strange?
No.
We've all thought about doing it.
Dela!
Nora is right.
I once considered slitting my wrists...
with candles and opera playing!
Me too. Throwing myself out the window.
OK, we've thought about it
but we haven't done it.
Because there's always a reason
to keep living, right?
Sara obviously didn't find one.
And isn't a boyfriend a good reason?
Sara had a boyfriend?
She told me she'd met a guy.
- Who?
- No idea.
They'd been going out
for a couple of months.
They even spent a week in Bellavista.
What's in Bellavista?
Hotel rooms!
Quiet, you lot!
That's strange. Shit!
What?
There's someone in here.
I think it's Sara.
Shut up, Nora! That's not funny!
I can smell her too!
Something moved!
I've got her! Call security!
I'm Sara's sister! I'm Sara's sister.
Julia?
Yes.
Why were you spying on us?
No. I just didn't know how to interrupt.
- And who's he?
- Who?
- The man with you.
- I came alone.
There's someone else here. A man.
And he's behind you.
Wait!
Shit!
Who's there?
Turn around.
I said turn around!
No. No!
Isaac?
"Hotel Romeo, Bellavista."
What happened to you?
You're soaking.
I got caught in the rain
when I left Soledad's house.
You were with her all this time?
She offered me tea. I couldn't say no.
Julia. I went to find you.
I know you left there an hour ago.
Where have you been?
Now you're controlling me?
I could also ask what you're looking for.
OK, fine.
Fine.
I'm sure there's something
strange about Sara's suicide.
Someone is watching our every move.
Julia, for god's sake. Who?
Her boyfriend.
Sara had a boyfriend?
- Yes.
- How do you know?
I went to the Baumann Center,
and someone was spying on us.
- How do you know?
- I chased him.
- You chased him?
- Yes, I chased him.
Isaac!
- Isaac, what are you doing?
- We're leaving this house.
If I have to play
the controlling husband, I will.
And I'll drag you out of here
if I have to,
but I won't let you have another attack.
I could never forgive myself.
What happened with your sister
was bad enough.
You're right.
But I really don't want to go home.
Why don't we go somewhere nearby,
just me and you? Alone.
Where would you like to go?
WELCOME TO BELLAVISTA
Sure you want to stay here?
The guidebook says it's cozy.
Nice view, isn't it?
- Julia?
- Yes, yes. Delightful.
Thank you.
Julia, I'm going to park the car.
Yeah, OK.
Are you sure you don't remember?
A blind woman?
Ah, yes. A colleague told me about her.
I know this might seem odd, but...
could you check the name
of the man she was with?
It's not on the bill.
Sorry, I don't remember a man with her.
My sister is dead,
and so I need to find him.
Let's see, I don't understand.
There's no record of her reservation.
It's as if the details have been deleted.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sorry.
It must be a computer problem.
Try at the Harlequin.
It's a restaurant
we recommend to our guests.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
God knows why
they recommended this restaurant.
I like it.
It's not really your style.
And that waiter
can't take his eyes off you.
Yeah, right!
It's your imagination.
Maybe.
My reading glasses...
In your coat? How strange!
I'll go and get them
and go to the bathroom.
OK.
If he tries anything, scream.
That's quite a change.
I like it. It brings out your eyes.
By the way, I knew they were green.
You're confusing me with my twin sister.
She was here last week,
with her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend?
She was with a man, right?
Yes, I think she was, yes.
Do you remember his name?
No, no idea.
He was very reserved, very plain.
- Could you describe him?
- Yes, he was...
I don't know, he was just normal.
But was he tall, short, fair, dark?
It's funny, I couldn't tell you.
How come you remember my sister
but not him?
It was hard not to notice her,
because of the bandages.
Bandages?
From the operation.
- My sister had had an operation?
- Yes.
I guessed the color of her eyes.
She said when she'd recovered
she'd come back,
and if I got the color right,
then maybe...
- Pablo, will you come here a moment?
- Of course.
Excuse me. Give her my regards.
I couldn't find them.
We'll have to manage.
Is something wrong?
Sara was here last week.
Julia, what are we doing here?
Isaac, the waiter says
she had a bandage over her eyes.
Don't you see?
If she'd had the operation
and was hoping to get her sight back,
why would she kill herself?
Tell me, why?
Because the operation didn't work.
What?
It didn't work.
Dr. Román told me yesterday.
I was waiting for the moment to tell you.
That man exists.
- He exists.
- Julia! Julia!
- What else haven't you told me?
- I wanted to protect you.
- From what?
- From the truth, Julia.
And what is the truth?
Sara killed herself because
she couldn't bear being blind.
Julia.
You know she came here with her boyfriend?
That doesn't prove anything.
Then why is he hiding?
Why didn't he come to the funeral? Why?
He probably left her.
He probably left her when
he found out she wouldn't see again.
Just like that?
- Just like that, huh?
- Well...
- And you're a psychologist.
- Julia!
God!
What are you doing?
Julia! Julia! Didn't you see it?
You didn't see it, did you?
How many attacks have you had?
- Two.
- Shit!
Shit.
If...
If I go blind...When I go blind...
No! That's not going to happen.
Not wanting it to happen
doesn't mean it won't.
Isaac...
You once told me that...
you could see the universe in my eyes.
And I still can.
What if that universe goes dark?
Close your eyes.
What?
Can you see me?
Of course I can't.
How do you know I'm still here?
Because I can hear you.
And if I'm silent?
How do you know I'm still here?
I can touch you.
And you can smell me.
And kiss you.
Promise me that if the day comes,
we'll return to the desert.
Yes.
You know why?
The last thing I want to see
is that sky...with you.
- Julia.
- Promise me.
Promise me.
I promise.
But you have to promise me...
that you'll stop chasing ghosts...
and that you'll see Dr. Román.
Tomorrow.
OK.
I'll put the cases in the car.
I'll meet you at the entrance
in 15 minutes.
Miss Levin.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
My name is Créspulo.
I read about your sister
in the obituaries section.
Thank you.
I have something of hers.
A few hours after your sister left...
I found a key under the bed in her room.
I think I put it down here.
Thank you.
Mr. Créspulo? Oh, sorry, sorry.
Mr. Créspulo...
My sister was here with a man, right?
The invisible man.
Pardon?
The man who came with your sister,
nobody remembers him, right?
Well...
That doesn't mean he was invisible.
Some people have no light.
Do you know what it is to enter a room
and have nobody look at you?
Or to walk along the street
and have people stumble into you?
Or to ask something three times
and nobody answers?
That's the man you're looking for.
A silence. A void.
An absence.
That's why nobody remembers him.
Nobody except you.
In a way, I'm kind of invisible too.
It's been years
since anybody remembered me.
That man...
Do you know where I can find him?
What are you afraid of?
He had his van parked up
in a garage two streets down.
There's a security camera on it
24 hours a day.
Thank you.
Wait!
Be careful.
The man who was with your sister
had a lot of rage in his eyes.
He knows how to be a shadow.
And if somebody feels invisible
and is angry at the world...
they're dangerous.
He has no light. Nobody looks at him.
He could get close
without you realizing and...
- Where were you?
- Did anyone come out?
- I've been waiting for ten minutes.
- Wait.
He's here. And I know how to find him.
No! I'll go and ask the security guard.
- OK. Calm down.
- No. You wait here, OK?
Shit, no need to be like that.
Let me remind you that you made a promise.
- OK, OK.
- I can't take this, Julia!
- Stop shouting.
- I've had enough!
- Listen...
- There's no mystery!
- I want to know who she was with.
- You want this video? I'll get it!
But this bullshit ends here,
you understand?
Jesus Christ!
You've reached the voicemail...
Excuse me? Did a man come in here
asking for a security video?
Look, I don't want any trouble.
The guy came, gave me money
- ...and promised he wouldn't tell.
- He's my husband.
I've been waiting for him.
Do you know where he went?
He left as soon as this bad boy
made the copies he wanted.
And...was there anyone else here?
- Are you sure?
- Nobody.
If you want, we can check the monitors.
What the hell?
I'll be right back.
Fucking hell!
What is it?
It's OK, it's me.
Somebody shut off the power.
This can't be happening.
No.
My husband has been abducted
and he's in danger.
At the moment, all we know is
that someone took the security video.
No! I'm telling you.
The man who was with my sister
is behind all this.
You have to find him before it's too late.
How can we find a man
who nobody seems to have ever seen?
Not even you.
Créspulo.
He was the only one who knew.
There's no sign of violence,
it looks like an accident.
It's the invisible man.
- He's covering his tracks.
- What?
You've got to find him!
My husband is in danger!
- Calm down, ma'am.
- Isaac!
- Call a doctor!
- My husband...
We need a doctor here, now!
Isaac!
The process is irreversible.
How long do I have?
I don't know.
It could be hours, days, maybe weeks.
But less than a month.
We have to find a donor
and operate as soon as possible.
Did you meet Sara's boyfriend?
No, I never met him.
Julia, I know you've had a rough time...
but you have to think of yourself.
Please try to avoid
any more emotional strain.
And don't force your sight, OK?
Iván! Iván!
Iván!
A boyfriend?
Sara never mentioned a boyfriend.
She didn't trust men.
Not like me. Or you.
I'm sure Isaac hasn't left me.
That's what we all say.
I invented a story too
when my husband left me.
My husband couldn't stand my son Ángel.
But my son was more important to me
than anything.
Then my eyesight degenerated and...
I went blind.
Fortunately, Ángel looked after me
for 10 years.
Then, one morning, I woke up and...
he'd gone too.
My Ángel had gone.
What kind of son
abandons his blind mother?
I had to invent another story.
And I still stick to it.
How humiliating. I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
Hello?
The hotel is automated.
There are no staff,
guests check in using an ATM.
The bank called me this morning.
A transaction was carried out
with your husband's credit card.
I searched the room
and I found this on the bedside table.
Julia, there are things
you don't know about your husband.
He hid Sara's operation from you.
He did it to protect me.
Dr. Román told him.
Román says he didn't
tell anyone about the operation.
So how did your husband know?
Inspector, a patrol car
just drove by Sara's house.
They saw lights on inside.
Isaac?
Wait here, Julia. Don't move.
Hello?
Isaac?
Julia!
Shit! I have to get out of here!
Where is it?
Relax.
Where is the exit? Calm down.
Julia? Julia?
Inspector! There's somebody down here.
Inspector!
Julia, calm down, it's me.
Somebody is here!
What is it?
Turn on the torch, I can't stand the dark.
Please, say something.
Why won't you say something?
Thank you.
Hello.
There's something you need to know, Julia.
Your husband left a note.
We checked the handwriting,
it was definitely written by him.
Listen...
Sara and Isaac
had been lovers for six months.
He asks you to forgive him.
This explains the calls
to your sister's number
that we found on your husband's mobile.
Did you know that
they had been in contact?
Think, Julia.
It was Isaac who insisted
on getting the security video.
Probably because he was on it
and he didn't want you to find out.
Then when he went to the motel,
he decided he couldn't live without Sara.
I'm sorry, Julia,
but everything make sense.
We've found a donor.
We can operate tomorrow.
You just have to sign here.
Thank you.
Calm down, Julia.
Calm down. Sleep a bit more.
Listen, Julia.
Everything went well.
But we have to be very careful.
Your eyes must be protected
from all light for two weeks.
And you mustn't ever remove the bandages.
If you take them off too soon...
there'll be no cure.
But don't worry,
they'll look after you here.
No.
I'd prefer to go home, please.
I hate hospitals.
Well, I'm afraid that's not possible.
You need to be under supervision.
OK...I can go to my sister's house,
where I know my way around.
Julia, I don't think it's a good idea.
Right. If I can't see, I can't feel.
Look, I tell you what.
You can go to your sister's house...
but a caregiver
will visit you every day, OK?
Julia, there's something else.
Your husband's body
is still in the hospital.
- You want me to deal with it?
- No.
No, I'd prefer to do it myself.
Can we keep the body
until I can see again?
I need to say goodbye to him.
Let's go to the sofa.
Keep going, a bit more.
- Here are your things.
- Thank you.
- Careful, don't worry.
- It's OK.
It's all there.
Shall we wait until the caregiver arrives?
- Can you do me a favor?
- Sure. What is it?
I'd like to know what this key is for.
Whatever this key opens,
it's not in this house.
- Are you sure you tried all the locks?
- Yes.
Do you need anything else?
No, thank you. You can go now.
- It's OK.
- OK.
- Hello?
- Hello. You must be Julia, right?
I'm Iván, your caregiver.
Sorry I'm late, the traffic was terrible.
I called but I got cut off.
I would have preferred a woman.
Well, you can call Dr. Román...
What happened to your hand?
It's only a superficial cut.
By tomorrow morning,
you won't even feel it.
Now I'll make dinner and tidy up.
You stay there.
By the way...
what should I do with the glasses?
Throw them away.
While you were eating,
I had a look around the house.
Julia...
- Julia. Sorry.
- What are you doing?
It's time for me to go now.
What time is it?
Nine o'clock, Julia.
The first few days,
you lose track of time.
I'll leave you some sleeping pills,
just in case.
And I'll leave you a pager.
If you need to contact me,
press the button. Give me your hand.
Here, this is the button. OK?
- Come on.
- What?
I have to put you to bed.
No, I can do that myself.
Are you sure?
Are you all right?
All right, all right. You win.
Put me to bed, then you can go.
Who's there?
It's OK.
It's OK, darling.
It's me.
Isaac?
Isaac.
How can this be?
Don't say anything.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing?
- Take it off.
Take off this dirty bandage...
so you can see me better.
No!
Get off me!
Let me go! Get off! No!
Don't resist, little sister.
It's two against one.
No! No!
- Stay still!
- No! Stop it!
No!
Let me go!
Oh, god.
Iván, Iván.
Julia, is everything OK?
I think there's somebody in the house.
What?
In the room next door.
- Don't move, I'll call the police.
- No, Iván. Iván!
OK. Are you still there?
Yes. Get me out of here.
- Where are you?
- In the guest bedroom.
OK, find the door
and walk out of the room.
Find the wall, to your right.
- He's there.
- Calm down.
OK. Two paces in front of you,
there's the banister.
- OK, yes.
- Hold on to the banister.
There are six steps to the first landing.
Now, there are nine more.
Julia?
I'm down, what do I do now?
Find the wall, then follow it to the door.
- Who are you? Who are you?
- What's going on?
- I don't know!
- Get out of the house. Get outside!
There's no sign
that anyone entered the house.
Someone was inside.
They were looking for something.
I'm sorry, but that's all I can do.
- Shall I call the hospital?
- What for?
Perhaps you shouldn't stay here,
after what's happened.
You don't believe me either?
No. But in your condition...
it's normal for your senses
to confuse you.
Don't open your eyes
under any circumstances.
You can let go now.
What is it?
My eyes could get damaged.
No, I just want to change the bandage.
I'm being careful.
I've done this hundreds of times.
Don't worry.
You know, when I was 20,
I had a car accident
which left me blind for two months.
And like you, I imagined things...
and I had nightmares.
And I refused help.
I couldn't bear the idea of going blind.
In the end, I got my sight back...
but during those two months...
I understood what it meant
to live in the dark.
That's why I became a nurse.
You invented that to make me feel better.
No. Call the hospital
if you don't believe me.
Julia, I know you're frightened,
but the only way to lose your fear...
is to fight it.
What do you say?
Will you let me help you?
- Julia. Hold it over...
- Let me do it. Let me.
- What happened?
- You spilled a bit.
Try and get to the door.
Follow the wall with your hand...
Exactly, from the wooden chest
to the glass cabinet.
And then, from the glass cabinet...
- It's really difficult.
- What can you feel?
My eyes, my nose...
My nose is easy,
it's the biggest part of my body.
I've got it. You're going to love this.
You'll love this,
it's Beethoven's summer hits.
Yes, I've had my low points.
But I've managed to sleep
through the night.
Iván has been very patient
with me all week.
Yes, he looks after me well. I will.
I will, yes. Thanks for calling. Bye.
- Are you leaving?
- Yes, it's getting late.
Why not stay a bit longer?
Just a while.
- Are you still afraid?
- No.
No, it's not that.
It doesn't matter.
OK. A special dinner for two?
- Watch TV, I'll do everything.
- That could be difficult.
- Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
- I'll help you.
You've drunk a lot.
I'm celebrating something.
What?
That in four days' time...
they take my bandages off
and I'll be able to see.
It will be all right, Julia.
You know what?
If the operation doesn't work,
I couldn't complain.
I've already seen all I wanted to see.
What is the most beautiful thing
you've seen?
That's funny.
It's ironic you should ask me that.
Why?
Because I've spent my life...
looking for invisible planets.
My eyes have seen amazing things...
but nothing...
compares to the night sky over the Sahara.
That was where I met Isaac.
We were on the same excursion
and we spent a whole night...
contemplating the stars.
I asked him if it was
the prettiest thing he'd ever seen.
And he said yes.
When I turned around...
I realized he'd been watching me,
and I got really nervous.
And so I asked him...
why he wasn't contemplating the universe.
And he said...
"I don't need to look up to do that...
I can see the universe in your eyes."
And what happened?
I came closer.
I touched him.
And I noticed that he was nervous too.
At that moment,
it was as if we became one.
I wanted to know if he felt the same.
What did he say?
Nothing.
He answered me with a look.
Why?
Why did he have to look at me like that?
- Would you have preferred he hadn't?
- I don't know.
When he had the affair with Sara,
I thought it was just a mistake, but...
I swear I don't know anymore.
I don't know what to think.
Everything will be OK, Julia.
Do you promise?
I promise.
No, no, I can't.
I can't do this. It's not right.
- Iván! Iván...
- No, don't say anything.
- I'm sorry, very sorry.
- You don't have to say anything.
I'll ask the hospital to replace me.
Is that what you want?
And you?
If you don't say anything,
I'll come back tomorrow.
If not, you can tell me with the pager.
Help! Help!
Help!
It's OK! It's Blasco, your neighbor.
Lía's father.
Call the police! Please!
It's OK, you could use a drink.
No, call the police first, please.
Why do you want to call the police?
To explain another nightmare?
- They didn't believe you last time.
- No!
There was somebody next to my bed.
I swear this time it's true.
And what did he want? To rape you?
It's my daughter. She can't sleep.
What did I tell you about spying?
Get back to bed right now!
And shut the door!
Mr. Blasco.
Can you call now, please?
Yes, of course. Don't worry.
That's strange. The line is dead.
It's OK. I'll get the mobile.
The mobile battery is flat.
It will take a few minutes to charge up.
You sit down here. Sit down.
Sit down. Sit down.
What do you say?
Shall we have that drink
while we wait for it to charge up?
What do you say?
Could you bring me some water, please?
Water?
Yes. I've got a dry mouth.
Yes, OK.
Julia, where are you going?
Hey, hold on!
Hey!
Miss, where are you going?
Miss.
Iván, please answer.
Iván!
- Answer, please, Iván...
- Julia, what is it?
- My god, Julia!
- Iván!
Come on, let's get you home.
No! Not my house! Your house!
- Calm down!
- My house isn't safe!
Please, take me to your house!
OK.
OK, thanks. Bye.
What did they say?
Inspector Dimas isn't on duty till 7:00.
You should try to sleep a bit
and I'll go with you tomorrow morning.
Julia, I won't let anybody hurt you.
Calm down.
- You can sleep in my bed.
- And you?
I'll get the fold-out bed.
- No!
- I'll only be two minutes.
- I'll come.
- You're safe.
- OK.
- I'll be right back.
OK.
Iván?
- Don't scream.
- Who is it?
- It's Lía.
Lía Blasco.
- Get away! How did you find me?
- I followed you. I was Sara's friend.
I don't care! Get away.
My father has nothing to do with all this.
- No? Your father lied to me.
- He's lonely and you're attractive.
Why should I believe you?
Because it was me who took the key
and was spying on you.
- Do you have nightmares?
- What?
Sara had them too.
She dreamt someone stabbed her
in the eyes with needles.
There's a monster out there.
Nobody can see him
because he hides in the dark.
He made her blind
and he'll do the same to you!
- That's enough, Lía!
- It's him, Julia. I followed him.
And today I saw the needles again.
- It's your nurse, Julia.
- No!
Listen to me!
Do you think Isaac committed suicide?
He loved you.
- He loved Sara more.
- They didn't want you to worry.
- No!
- That's why they didn't tell you.
- Sara told me.
- Isaac left a note, leave me alone.
- The monster forced him to write it.
- Monsters aren't real, Lía!
This one is.
He collects images.
He has a wall full of photos,
of you and Sara.
- He took your eyes.
- Enough, Lía, enough!
Get off me!
What are you doing?
If you don't believe me, use the key.
- The key! Where is it?
- It was him.
- No, you took the key.
- Me? Why?
I don't know! To protect your father.
- It's him. Don't tell him I'm here.
- Lía! Lía!
- Iván?
- Julia, what are you doing?
I'm really scared.
I'll make you a herbal tea.
It will help you relax.
- Iván?
- Yes?
I can't find the key.
It's the only proof I have against Blasco.
Did you take it?
It was on the floor.
- Yes. Give it to me.
- I'll keep it, you're too nervous.
I'll make you that tea.
You sit down and relax.
He's lying to you. He had the key.
- We have to get out of here.
- No, I don't want to.
Don't you believe me?
It's impossible, he's a good nurse.
- Shit.
- What's wrong?
It's locked.
- Julia?
- Yes?
- Sugar?
- Two, please.
- He wants to drug you and blind you.
- What?
- Can you take off the bandage?
- No! Why?
Then we can't go out the window.
I have to get the key.
Get away from him somehow
and meet me in the bathroom.
Lía.
Here you go.
Come on, I'll show you to bed
and sit with you.
I'd like to go to the bathroom.
OK.
Thanks.
Julia, is everything OK?
Yes, what was that noise?
I don't know, I heard it too.
I thought it was you.
Your tea is getting cold.
Yes, OK. I'll be right out.
Lía, please, Lía, Lía.
Four days, only four more days.
Only four more days.
No.
Julia, I'm going back to the basement.
Are you OK?
Yes, I'll be right out.
Lía.
What are you doing here?
Why are you crying?
Answer me, Julia, please.
A girl...There was a girl here.
Lía, Blasco's daughter.
And I got scared.
Why did you take your bandage off?
I couldn't see.
She said horrible things about you.
And I was scared.
Of me?
You wouldn't hurt me, would you?
No.
I needed to see your face to be sure.
And what did you see?
Nothing...I can't see anything.
Are you sure you can't see?
Sometimes the eyes take time to readapt.
The operation didn't work, Iván.
I'm very sorry, Julia.
That girl was probably lying
to protect her father.
Tomorrow, we'll talk to the inspector
and it'll all be over.
No! No.
No, please, let's go to the hospital now.
- We'll call Dr. Román first.
- Please!
We'll call Dr. Román, Julia!
- Now.
- Julia, trust me.
Dr. Román? It's Iván.
I'm sorry to wake you at this hour.
We've got a problem with Julia Levin.
She accidentally took off her bandage.
Understood, yes, I'll tell her.
Thank you, and sorry to bother you.
- Well?
- He's at a conference in Geneva.
We can't do anything now.
- Then take me to the hospital.
- No, Dr. Román said you have to rest.
I need a second opinion.
Julia, the damage is done.
If you don't do as I say,
it'll be irreversible.
OK. OK.
Why did you get up?
The kettle was whistling.
No, no. I'll do it. You sit down.
Careful.
That's it.
This is almost ready.
Here you are.
Thank you.
What is it?
Why are you doing all this, Iván?
What do you mean?
Why all this attention?
What do you want from me?
Look, Julia, I...
When...
When you kissed me...
I wasn't expecting it. No.
I wasn't expecting it.
It's not that I don't like you.
Because...that's not true.
I just wanted to give you time.
You've suffered a lot, and...
you need to heal your wounds.
What I'm trying to say is...
that I want to be with you.
Drink your tea.
Did you put sugar in it?
I'll get it for you.
Two, right?
As always.
OK?
Can you come with me for a moment?
What for?
I have to get something from the freezer,
I need your help.
Come on. Leave that here.
Open the freezer.
Why?
Do as I say.
Open the freezer!
Liar.
Are you afraid?
No, no, no!
You don't know what fear is!
You've got no idea what fear is!
Real fear of being ignored or rejected,
fear of indifference.
Julia, look at me! Look at me!
You don't know what it is to live
in darkness, and hide in another world,
a silent world without looks,
getting used to a life
counting your steps.
Always wearing the same clothes...
using your voice, one voice and no voice,
and your eyes, two eyes and no eyes.
It's been so long, Julia,
that in the end you become a shadow,
until one day you discover
that blind people
know you're there,
that you breathe,
that you're still alive.
You can offer them your eyes for theirs,
your hands for theirs.
That's why we're so perfect together.
That's why we have to stay this way.
If you're not Iván, who are you?
Where are you taking me?
My eyes hurt, something is wrong.
Take the bandage off, please.
Please!
Please, take it off.
Please. It really hurts.
- Take it off.
- Shut up!
I beg you.
Let me see.
Ah, it's started again, hasn't it?
This time...
it'll be more intense.
Get out of the car, Julia.
We have to pack your bags.
Open the door.
Open the fucking car!
Open the door, Julia!
Julia, open the fucking car!
Julia!
Who's there?
Is the front door locked?
It's you, Julia, you scared me.
- Is it locked?
- Yes, of course. What is it?
- There's a killer out there.
- A killer?
Yes, we have to call the police.
Where's the phone?
Over there in the corner.
Under the picture.
Quiet!
Silence.
- What is it?
- Don't move.
- It's him.
- Who?
Don't come any closer, you son of a bitch!
Who are you talking to?
With a man who thinks he's invisible.
He blinded Sara
and now he wants to blind me.
You're scaring me.
Don't come any closer!
Call the police, Soledad.
- Quickly! Call them.
- Don't do it, Mom.
Don't...
Ángel?
Is that you, Son?
Yes, I've come home.
This woman says you're following her.
This woman is crazy.
- Your son is a killer.
- Shut up.
Don't listen to her, Mom.
- He killed my husband.
- She's lying.
- He killed my husband and Sara.
- Shut up.
He lead a blind woman to a noose.
I loved Sara.
She killed herself because
she wasn't able to live in darkness.
"Able to"?
Nobody is able to get used to that!
You bastard! You made her blind!
- You killed her!
- Is that true, Son?
Mom, Mom, you know me...
Don't move, I said. Don't move.
Call the police, Soledad. Call them!
I knew you'd come back...
and you'd realize that
you could only be happy here.
I told you you'd be nothing without me.
Less than nothing.
Invisible!
How long have you been able to see?
But you're still my son.
And I won't let anything
or anyone take you away.
Mom, I asked you a question.
How long have you been able to see?
Ángel, what are you doing, Son?
What are you doing, Ángel?
Son, no, no.
No, no!
It's OK, Mom.
- Mom, it's OK.
- No, no!
Look, Mom. This liquid attacks
the optic nerve without causing any pain.
Mom, don't worry.
And these needles are also useful.
- It won't hurt.
- Don't, please!
I have to do it. I have to.
My boy.
No, no, no!
What are we doing here?
I won't use it on you.
Your optic nerve must be very damaged.
It won't take long.
It can't end like this. It can't.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Don't worry.
When the darkness comes...
I'll be by your side.
I've packed your bags.
We'll go far away, we'll disappear
and nobody will ever find us.
We'll start again.
Don't touch me!
No, you son of a bitch!
I'll never ever love you,
I'd rather be dead!
- Don't touch me!
- You want this?
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
Let me go!
Let me go! Get off!
Do it, do it. Do it.
Stay with me.
Do it.
Do it! Fucking do it!
- Do it!
- I can't! I can't!
Of course you can't.
Because, although you don't know it...
you love me.
Because you know, Julia,
that without me you're nobody.
And without you, I'm only a shadow.
Julia, why did you lock the door?
- Yes? Hello?
- Inspector! It's Julia.
- Julia, is that you?
- Shut up!
This will be the last time I call you.
Calm down. What's the problem?
- He's locked me in my house.
- Calm down, Julia.
He'll kill me.
If you don't come now, it'll be too late.
You have to believe me, please.
- Julia, calm down...
- Are you listening to me?
Inspector?
Julia!
Julia, it's the police!
Cover the stairs and that corridor!
Julia, are you there?
It's Dimas! Julia, can you hear me?
- What the hell! Julia!
- Shut up!
- What's going on?
- Shut up, I said!
You see him? You see him, Inspector?
- Police! Drop the knife!
- There he is!
Hands on your head!
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me, please.
Don't look at me!
Throw the knife down!
What are you doing?
No! Throw down the knife!
I'm going to go blind, aren't I?
How long have I got?
You won't see the dawn.
I need you to do me a favor.
Can you leave us alone, please?
What happened to his eyes?
He donated them.
And where are they?
Where he would have wanted them.
Isaac, why?
I miss you so, so much.
You promised.
You promised me.
You said that
when you looked into my eyes...
you could see the universe.
And I still can.