There he is!
Superman! Superman! Can
we ask you some questions?
- It's for our podcast.
- Well, in that case...
How many people that you
saved... have you saved?
- I...
- Never mind.
Does your thing really
stand for hope?
Yes. It does.
But it looks like an "S".
Yes, it's meant to. It's
meant to wind, like a river.
It comes and goes.
My fa...
A man I knew, used to say...
that hope is like a car keys.
Easy to lose, but
if you dig around...
...it's usually close by.
Did you ever fight a hippo?
That's dumb!
But hippos are the most deadly!
What is... What's the best
thing about planet Earth?
MAKOTO77
What are you doing?
Wait! No, wait!
Wait! Wait!
Please! Please,
man! Please!
What do you want from me?
Fear.
They could smell it.
What the hell?
- What was that?
- A scout.
From space?
Like an alien army?
Alfred, are you seeing this?
I am. Matches the
other sightings.
And that pattern is
all over Luthor's notes.
Prep the jet. I'm
going north tonight.
Good. It's
time, then.
It's 'cause they
know he's dead, right?
Superman. He's gone.
Where does that leave us?
Drop your guns now!
Excuse me?
- Move it. Move!
- Don't shoot!
Get down.
Line them up along the
wall. Keep them quiet.
Who are you?
The lasso of Hestia compels
you to reveal the truth.
Now, who are you?
We're a small group of
reactionary terrorists.
We know that sinners brought
- on this plague of...
- Why the hostages?
You're too late. The
countdown's already begun.
In a few minutes,
4 city blocks...
While the world watches.
Shut up!
This is man's best hope.
Down with the modern world.
Back to the Dark Ages.
And the safety of holy fear.
This would've been
over quickly, but...
No! Don't!
I don't believe it.
- What are you?
- A believer.
I'm asking for your help.
I believe there's a stranger, comes
to this village from the sea.
He comes in the winter
when the people are hungry...
and brings fish.
He comes on the king tide...
That was last night.
Icebergs in the harbour.
Four months since the
last ship got through.
Well, this stranger...
Doesn't come by ship.
There are enemies
coming, from far away.
I need warriors.
I'm building an alliance,
to defend ourselves.
Look, I'll give
you $25,000 to...
talk to this man right now...
outside.
Something tells me that of
all he will give them to me.
Tell me what those 3 boxes
are and I'll make it 30.
You should get out.
Can you at least
point me to Atlantis?
Arthur Curry.
Also known as the
Protector of the Oceans.
The Aquaman.
I hear you can talk to fish.
So let me get this straight...
You do it dressed like a
bat? Like an actual bat?
It's worked for 20
years in Gotham.
Oh, that shithole.
The fight comes, we'll need you.
- Don't count on it, Batman.
- Why not?
Because I don't like
you coming here...
digging into my business,
getting into my life.
People from Atlantis
tell me, "Do this."
Now, you say,
"Do that."
I want to be left alone.
That why you help these people
out here in the middle of nowhere?
Because you can just leave?
I help them 'cause
no one else does.
You wanna protect them,
you need to work with me.
A strong man is strongest alone.
You ever heard that?
That's not a saying. That's the
opposite of what the saying is.
Yep. Doesn't
mean I'm wrong.
You ever hear of Superman?
- He died fighting next to me.
- My point exactly.
What's in the 3 boxes?
It's ancient history.
Mankind's melting
the polar ice caps...
Destroying the ecosystem,
they got it coming?
Hey, I don't mind
if the ocean rise.
How about if they boil?
Dressed like a bat.
You're out of your
mind, Bruce Wayne.
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
So, you say you have no way
of reconnecting with this...
Aquaman.
I put a tracking
device in his coat...
He left without it.
It may, in fact, not
have been his coat.
Those squares,
from Luthor's notes...
I think they must be
containers of some kind.
- Of what?
- I don't know.
Money, power. Something
worth starting a war over.
Well, we had luck
with one person...
on the team list.
Barry Allen, of Central City.
He's completely off the grid.
Squatting, I think.
Moves suddenly and often.
- Disappearing act?
- But he does visit his father...
...in prison.
- For murdering his mother.
- Jesus!
Young Barry always protested
his father's innocence...
But he was 9 and
nobody listened to him.
We have somebody at the prison?
Oh, yeah. We'll
find the address.
- What about, Diana?
- Well, you have her number.
You could've called her.
Perhaps I should fly to Paris
with a handwritten note?
"Will you be
Bruce' teammate?"
"Check: Yes or No"
I'm only interested
in her skill set.
- I'm sure you are.
- Can we?
Well, facial recognition's
a bit dodgy on this one.
But it's got a partial match.
A Victor Stone.
Genius I.Q., football
scholarship to GCU...
And deceased.
Figures. Fairy tales
and ghost stories.
One misses the days
when one's biggest
concerns were exploding
wind-up penguins?
The simple life.
I don't recognize this world.
I don't have to recognize it.
I just have to save it.
Here to see Henry Allen.
Sign.
Hurry it up, will you?
What, you got a problem?
No. There's
no problem.
Better not be.
You know where to go.
Are those prescription...
Or you just trying
to look brainy?
Because you're holding yourself
back. You're going in circles.
You're working 3 dead-
end jobs. Going on four.
Where do you even have the time?
I make the time.
And this is all to pay for a
criminal justice degree, huh?
Okay. I really don't want
to talk about this again...
The investigation was botched.
Give me your hand.
I want you to
listen to me, Barry...
Because I mean this.
I want you to
give all of that up.
And I want you to stop
coming to see me.
I am a drag on your life.
Please don't ever
say that to me again.
Please?
You can be whatever you
wanna be. You're a brilliant man.
Absolute best of the best.
I can't sit here...
and watch you run
in place in Central City...
for some old dude...
- who's not going anywhere.
- Dad...
- That's not true.
- It's time.
- Let's go, Allen.
Allen!
I want you to make
your own future.
Living in the past...
Make your own future.
Open gate!
Lab's all yours, Howard.
11:30. Early night
for you, Silas.
Yes. Early.
I never got to say...
I'm very sorry about
what happened.
Victor was a wonderful kid.
Thank you.
Victor.
Victor, you're not
stuck up here.
You can have a life.
You can have more than...
- If you stay up here brooding...
- I'm processing.
I can access everything.
- But I can't put it all together.
- Not yet.
But if you work with me, if
we had the change engines...
So you did to someone else.
What you did to me.
No. The box
stays hidden.
If you could see what we're learning
from the Kryptonian ship...
I think the change engine
can integrate with its energy...
- get it powered up...
- Does anybody know?
What?
At the lab... Does
anybody know I'm alive?
I...
I didn't think you were
ready for them to...
For what?
For them to see the monster?
You are not a monster.
It's weird that you
thought I meant me.
What I did...
I lost your mother
in that accident.
I wasn't about to...
I couldn't bear to lose my son.
But you did.
I got a language in my
head that I don't speak.
It's not just
digital... It's alien.
Everyday, I wake
up, different...
Modified.
How do you...?
Couldn't do that last night.
Ever since we got
visitors from Krypton,
people have been waiting
for the next alien invasion.
Now I got to wonder if I'm it?
- Any changes today?
- No, my Queen.
The Mother Box has awoken...
Yet, nothing has happened.
It has slept for thousands
of years, since the first age.
Why did it wake at all?
Amazons, on your mark!
Steppenwolf.
Mother...
Millenia in exile...
Searching.
At last, you call me home.
You will not like your welcome.
Oh, I think I will.
- Gather the legions.
- Seal the cage!
Go!
Flank right!
Yes...
Run.
Seal the gates!
Keep it moving.
Got it! Go!
Noble Queen, why do you fight?
After the Unity, you
will join my Legion...
and you will know the
righteousness of power.
You will love me.
You all will.
We have to light the
ancient warning fire.
The fire has not burned
for 5,000 years.
Men won't know what it means.
Men won't...
But she will.
Listen to me, Diana.
What did you do
this weekend, Diana?
Me?
Nothing very interesting.
That's all you ever tell us.
Whay can I say?
I'm not that exciting.
...Shrine of the Amazons...
an enormous bonfire
burned right behind me...
baffling absolutely everyone...
from locals, to government
authorities alike.
- The fire could be seen for miles on end...
- Invasion.
On the local scene...
This janitor's wife
had some strong words...
for the aliens she says,
stole her man.
My Howard is a good
man. He's a provider.
And these aliens are gonna
(beep) probe him?
Come down to the Lakeview...
And I'll stick a (beep) probe
up your alien (beep) ass, you...
I found a little place.
By the diner.
Suits me just fine.
I wish you'd said something.
Oh, no. I got behind
in the payments.
And you know the banks. Jump
like a cougar if you miss by a dime.
Place was too big for me anyway.
Shuffling around
like an old ghost.
Well, I might have been
able to, talk to someone, or...
You had enough to deal with.
Don't need to add
mother-in-law to the list.
- Not that I was ever...
- Hey, Lane...
Who is your source? The
activist in that university...
Look, it's my source.
I got tapped for
the kidnapping story.
There were all those
student protests. Anyway...
I'm thinking it's political,
so... Who's your guy?
Well let's see if
she'll take your call.
So, it's a she.
It's not a she.
Sounds like you should
be working that story.
I'm... I'm
not ready yet.
I'm perfectly happy, doing fluff
pieces about kitten grooming.
For a while...
It was hard coming
back here at all.
Well. I can hardly read
the news anyway.
So much bitterness.
'Course, I think it's all
because he's gone.
But I suppose a mother does.
But it's not like there's any
less that needs reporting.
And Clark promised me, you were
gonna bring home another Pulitzer.
- Oh, did he?
- Oh, yes. He did.
He said you were the thirstiest
young woman he'd ever met.
- Hungriest.
- Hungry. Yeah.
He said you...
could smell a story. Further
away than he could hear.
Well stories, made sense.
It was more than just a puzzle.
It was about the truth.
It was about seeing the
engine of the world...
While it still ran.
Victor Stone...
Deceased.
That one...
Pretty sure that's what
made the alien go crazy.
I'll see about weaving
something to the suit.
Won't be quick.
Anything to give me an edge.
You know, I paid
millions of dollars...
for this building's security.
Yeah. It looked
expensive.
Hi.
A new toy?
Prototype troop carrier.
I once knew a man who
would've loved to fly it.
Yeah, well we're gonna
need more than a pilot.
I think there's
an attack coming.
Not coming, Bruce.
It's already here.
They called him Steppenwolf.
The End of Worlds.
He lived only to conquer.
Millions fell
before his blade...
And rose again as
his Parademons.
Nightmare creatures,
who feed on fear.
Yeah, I think I've met one.
We didn't hit it off.
Here in Gotham?
They're all over.
They're looking for
his... Boxes?
- The Mother Boxes.
- Mother Boxes?
I guess Steppenwolf
sent the winged people
that leaves two more.
- I'm impressed.
- Don't be.
I have no idea what's in them.
A weapon? Some
kind of power?
They don't contain power.
They are power.
Carried from planet to planet...
The Mother Boxes combined
to form the Unity.
An apocalyptic power that
not only destroys worlds...
...but transforms them into
the primordial hell's gate...
...of Steppenwolf's birthworld.
We should have died...
But we formed our own Unity.
Amazons, Atlanteans...
All the tribes of man
fought side by side.
Warriors of legend.
Allies from other worlds.
Even the gods themselves
all acted as one.
Laying down their lives to
drive Steppenwolf away.
Some say it drove him mad...
.. the disgrace of
his first retreat.
He swore our alliance
would crumble.
That darkness would
cover the Earth...
And that he would
return when it did.
Left behind...
The Mother Boxes
were too dangerous
to be kept together.
One was entrusted
to the Amazons.
One, to the Atlanteans.
Both sealed and guarded
in secure strongholds.
The Box of Man
was buried in secret.
So that no tribe would be tempted
to use its power over another.
Such harmony out of such horror.
It was truly an age of heroes.
Something tells me we're not
getting the band back together.
The Atlanteans were
a force under sea...
And the Amazons, to an
island they can never leave.
I wouldn't count on
the tribes of men.
We tend to act like the doomsday
clock has a snooze button.
- How long until we...
- Days.
At most.
Steppenwolf's mistake last
time was attacking us.
He wanted to make the Earth
kneel before he destroyed us.
This time he'll just
go after the Boxes.
I got a location for
one of our recruits.
- Barry Allen.
- What about the other one?
Victor Stone?
I was hoping you
would dig him up.
We're asking people we
don't know to risk their lives.
I know.
That's how this works.
Barry Allen.
Bruce Wayne.
You say that like it explains...
why there's a total
stranger in my place...
sitting in the dark, in
my second favorite chair.
Tell me about this.
This is a person who
looks exactly like me...
but who is definitely not me.
Very attractive Jewish boy.
Somebody who, I don't know,
stole your pocketwatch?
Or railroads?
I know you have abilities. I just
don't know what they are.
My special skills include...
Viola, web design,
fluent in sign language...
gorilla sign language...
Silica-based
quartz sand fabric,
Abrasion resistant.
Heat resistant.
Yeah, I do...
- Competitive ice dancing.
- That's what they use...
on the space shuttle, to
prevent it from burning
up on re-entry.
I do very competitive
ice dancing.
Whoever you're looking
for, it's not me...
You're the Batman?
So you're fast.
That feels like an
oversimplification.
I'm putting together a team.
People with special abilities.
You see, I believe
enemies are coming.
Stop right there. I'm in.
You are?
Yeah. I need... friends.
People are difficult. They
require a lot of focus.
They have like a rhythm that
I haven't quite been able to...
Like, Brunch?
Like... What is Brunch?
You wait in line for an hour...
for, essentially, lunch.
I mean, I don't know.
People are...
a little slow.
I'll try to keep up.
Can I keep this?
It's like this layer of
dimensional reality...
that seems to
manipulate space-time.
I call it the Speed Force.
Causes me to burn tremendous
amount of calories...
So I am just a black
hole of snacks.
I am a "snack hole."
How many people are
on this special fight team?
Three. Including you.
Three? Against what?
I'll tell you on the plane.
Plane?
What are your superpowers again?
I'm rich.
The program always gets
twitchy with this footage.
Why are you and Bruce
Wayne looking for me?
You know who we are?
And I also know where you are.
Are you Victor Stone?
Was.
I need to speak to you.
You are.
No, face to face.
I'm old-fashioned that way.
Why would I trust you?
If I was going to attack you,
I would've done it by the lake.
Looks like you have
a date, Ms. Prince.
About time somebody here did.
Face to face.
I've been doing some tracking.
What you're looking for is
sticking to the dead zones.
It gets in front of a
camera, causes a surge.
- I'll let you know.
- That's not good enough.
Not good enough?
For you.
Look, I don't know you...
And I don't know how
you got these gifts.
Gifts?
No one else can do what you do.
No, if these are gifts...
then why am I the
one paying for them?
We need you, Victor.
And maybe you need us.
I'll be fine alone.
I told myself the
same for a long time.
I lost someone I loved once.
I shut myself off
from... From everyone.
But I had to learn to
open back up again.
The truth is I'm
still working on it.
And if you agreed to meet me...
...you're working on it, too.
Trust me, Victor.
Mayday! Mayday!
Something came
down from the sky.
Please, help me!
Whisky.
And one for Ahab there.
...from the sky...
I heard a cannon.
- It's ocean's rage.
- Then they came...
Monsters.
...from the sky.
Tore right through my boat.
Monsters...
It's on him.
You took a hell of a hit.
You all right?
At last...
The firstborn of beloved
Queen Atlanna.
Wait.
Please.
I knew her.
That makes one of us.
When my parents
fought in the wars...
- She took me in.
- What a saint.
You dare speak of Queen
Atlanna that way?
Your Queen left me
on my father's doorstep
and never gave
me another thought...
Your mother left
you to save your life.
You can't imagine
how it hurt her.
What it cost her.
But you're not a
defenseless child now.
It would've been
her responsibility...
to follow that monster
to the surface and stop it.
Now, it's yours.
Then I'm gonna need
something from you.
Leave that.
Leave it. It will never work.
I see, Mother.
I see why you
waited to summon me.
That Kryptonian's death
plunged this timid world...
into such terror.
Amazons. Atlanteans. Each
stands, and falls, alone.
I know Mother. You've waited
too long for the Unity.
I know. But
you will feed.
And my exile will
come to an end.
I will take my place
among the New Gods.
Find the last one.
Its power will
cleanse this world.
For the Unity!
For Darkseid.
Victor.
Asshole!
Eight kidnappings. 6
in Metropolis, 2 here.
All the vics worked
for STAR Labs.
Attacked by a flying vampire.
Suspect was a giant bat...
with huge fangs.
One of them was
a little kid, scared.
Won't say a word but drew this.
- Looks like...
- I know what it looks like.
Come on. You think he fights
criminals for 20 years here...
and then he goes to Metropolis
and kidnaps eight people?
I'll talk to him tonight.
The world's gone crazy,
Jim. Maybe he did, too.
You find the Cyborg?
We spoke.
Give him time.
You must be
Barry. I'm Diana.
Hi Barry, I'm Diana...
That's not right. Great.
So this is us?
Yeah. This is us.
Oh! Awesome!
That's the Bat-signal.
That's your...
Oh. Sorry.
That's your signal. That
means we have to go now.
- Yeah. That's what that means.
- That's so cool.
How many of you are there?
Not enough.
Eight people abducted
from or near STAR Labs.
Here's the potential perp.
Parademons.
Okay...
The demons must have caught
the scent of a Mother Box.
They carried people away to
find out what they know.
- So the eight might still be alive.
- Nine.
The head of STAR Labs
was taken as well.
You made it.
So then. There must
be a nest nearby.
I plotted all the sightings
in Metropolis, Gotham...
No pattern I can see.
The lines on the
map don't converge.
On land.
These lead back to Braxton Island,
between the two cities.
Gotham Harbor.
These are air vents...
they all lead down to the
tunnel from Metropolis...
project that was
abandoned in '29.
Do you really think that...
Wow. They just... They
really just vanished.
That's rude.
- Where are we, Alfred?
- Braxton Island.
You should be...
directly under the venting
tower for the tunnel.
Now, look to your left,
you should see a staircase.
It will give you access
to the machine room.
Define access.
One at a time.
The bridge may not...
...hold.
- Just tell me the truth.
- Please, just let us go.
- I have a family!
- Wrong answer.
Humans...
The stench of your fear is
making my soldiers hungry.
Shall I feed them?
You've been near the Mother Box.
- The scent is on you...
- Please.
We have families.
Why does everyone
keep telling me that?
Okay. Here's the thing...
See, I'm afraid of bugs, and...
Guns. And obnoxiously tall people.
And murder.
I can't be here.
It's really cool, you guys seem
ready to do battle and stuff, but...
Full transparency,
I've never done battle.
I just push some
people and run away.
Save one.
One?
Save one person.
Wait, which one?
Don't talk. Don't fight.
Get in. Get one out.
And then?
You go.
Okay.
Useless!
You then.
Where is my Mother Box?
I'll die before I tell you.
At last, one that doesn't whine.
But you will scream.
Dad.
Victor.
You were born of her.
A creature of chaos.
Not how I see it.
Give it time.
Amazon!
Okay.
Save one.
This one is mine.
You overestimate yourself.
Child...
My axe is still slick with
the blood of your sisters.
Alfred, I need the Nightcrawler.
I thought you'd never ask.
Crawler's on the way.
Initiating remote mode.
You good?
At the end of the hall
there should be stairs.
Okay.
Go!
He's after the change engine.
His Mother Box.
- You have to keep him from it.
- Help people get to safety.
- Promise me.
- Go!
Finish her!
Sorry guys,
I didn't bring a sword.
Jesus. He is tall.
So...
You have the blood
of the Old Gods in you.
The Old Gods died.
No!
Heads up!
Thanks, Alfred. But
I'll take it from here.
Do I know you?
Primitive beings.
What are we under right now?
Gotham Harbor.
You all need to move.
- You get him out...
- Diana, there's no time.
Also among my fears is drowning.
You are a distraction.
Mother is calling.
Diana, come on!
Come on.
The change engine.
Did he just bail?
Millions in structural damage.
You haven't lost your touch.
But it's good to see you
playing well with others.
Dressed like
a bat? I dig it.
It may be temporary.
So...
What made you change your mind?
Steppenwolf.
He took the Mother
Box from Atlantis.
All he needs now is
the last box of man.
If he doesn't already have it.
He doesn't have it.
We need to get away.
No. We are
safer here.
What happens when
we run out of food?
Someone will come.
Who will come for us?
Wow. It's
like a cave.
Like a Batcave.
Barry!
My father called it
the change engine.
It was found by the British
during World War I.
They studied it...
but they couldn't
even date it. It's so old.
It was shelved, until the
night Superman died.
Then she lit up like Christmas.
They brought it to STAR Labs...
where my father recognized it...
as a perpetual energy matrix.
That sounds cool.
I thought it was
like a nuclear bomb.
A Mother Box destroys
as it creates.
It's a cycle of life, but
a million times faster.
My father thought it was the
key to unlimited energy.
New formulas,
cellular regeneration...
But it's too
volatile to control.
He used it on you.
I was in an accident.
I should've died.
My father thought that he
could use the Mother Box to
rebuild the broken parts of me with
a few cybernetic enhancements.
Instead, he built
a living machine.
I may be stronger than its host.
Too much.
Too much life.
What's on your weird mind?
Muscles. Coordination.
Basic cellular integrity.
A human being can
only absorb so much.
The Mother Box was
designed to reshape a planet.
So?
So...
What if you were
stronger than a planet?
Your cells lying dormant,
but incapable of decay.
If you were in a
conductive field...
A boost from the Mother Box...
...could bring "him"
back to life.
The Kryptonian ship has
an amniotic chamber...
- Which would be a perfect...
- No.
- Diana.
- Bruce, no!
You have no idea what kind
of power you're dealing with.
Even if there was a
fraction of a chance...
That what? That we
could raise a monster?
Like Luthor did?
We have tech Luthor's
never even seen...
Superman is dead.
We all wish he weren't.
We don't know
what state he's in.
We know we can't bring him back.
But this is science
beyond our limits.
And that's what science is for.
To do what's never been done.
- To make life better.
- Or to end it.
Technology is like
any other power...
Without reason, without
heart... It destroys us.
You're risking lives.
Theirs and maybe countless more.
We don't have time
for a control group.
Is it a risk? Yes.
But it's necessary.
Why? Because
of your guilt?
Bruce, I was there.
You didn't kill Superman.
At some point, even you...
have to learn to move on.
Did Steve Trevor tell you that?
Superman, was a
beacon to the world.
Why aren't you?
You're an inspiration, Diana.
You don't just save people.
You make them see
their better selves.
And yet, I never heard of you...
Until Luthor lured you out
by stealing a picture of
your dead boyfriend.
You shut yourself
down for a century.
So let's not talk
about me moving on.
You know...
That if she kills you,
we'll cover for her.
We are not enough.
Each of us in our own
way has held back.
And I promise you, Steppenwolf is
not out there talking about ethics.
He's trying to burn
down the world.
The way we're gonna stop him...
...is by using
his power.
This power,
against him.
I agree.
I don't like the idea of reintegrating
with the Mother Box...
But I was running the numbers
while you're being an asshole,
and there's a high probability
that we can bring him back.
Right, but we mean
bring him back, in like a...
"Yay! He's back!"
way. Not in like a...
Like a Pet Sematary
scenario?
You lose something when
you die. Even Superman.
Maybe not his mind.
Maybe his soul.
I'll have a contingency
plan for that.
If he wakes up and you're
the first thing he sees...
You'll need one.
Well that was fun
while it didn't last.
She could've stopped me.
I practically dared her to.
I don't see why
you're pushing her.
We'll have to boost the signal.
Put it through the
Batmobile's speakers.
Now you're changing the subject.
I have a contingency.
Diana was right about the risk.
If the plan goes south, we're
gonna bring in the big guns.
But that's not...
Those are very big guns.
You got a team here.
Superman could bring this team
together better than I ever could.
- His strength...
- It doesn't matter how strong you are.
Or what abilities
you might have.
He was more human than I am.
He lived in this world.
Fell in love, had a job.
In spite of all that power.
The world needs Superman.
And the team needs Clark.
And what does Clark need?
Maybe he's at peace.
He'll get over it.
You know, I can do
this a lot faster. I just...
Is it weird that it
feels disrespectful?
Yep.
Do you feel a
sense of confidence
that we're not doing something
horribly wrong
and macabre here?
Not really.
- Okay then why are...
- Because I saw Steppenwolf up close.
The stories Diana told us?
And I believe them.
But we're gonna stop him.
That's the plan.
That's the plan!
Okay, we're not ready
for... Racially charged...
You got struck
by lightning, huh?
Yeah... That's the
abridged version.
- And you...?
- Explosion.
Woke up in a lab.
We're, we're the accidents.
Yeah, that's us.
Hey!
We're approaching
the Kryptonian ship.
ETA, 30 seconds.
I'm here for him.
- I swear, I would never...
- Save it.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Okay.
This is amazing.
This is crazy.
What, now it's crazy?
You lunatics better
know what you're doing.
Lex Luthor fried the circuits
bringing his creature to life.
There's not enough charge
to wake the Box.
I might be able to do it.
I might be able to
jumpstart it, I...
If I can get enough distance...
I can conduct a significant
electrical current.
I might be able to wake the Box,
if that's still what we want?
We have to try.
This must be the
end of the line, so...
I'm in position.
The Mother Box is ready.
You have to charge it the
moment it touches the fluid.
- Five.
- Five...
Diana's right. This
is a bad idea.
Four.
Three.
Three...
Two.
One.
Give us an ETA on
all additional units...
He's back.
He's not all right.
He's scanning us.
What?
Arthur, you need to relax.
Your adrenaline's spiking.
Because he's not all right.
Oh, no.
Should we bow?
Or show our bellies?
Victor...
Victor, stop.
- Shit!
- What are you doing?
Victor.
- It's my armor's defense system...
- No.
It's stronger since
the interface...
- I can't control it.
- Victor, no!
- Shut it off!
- Think of happy thoughts, Victor!
Kal-El, no!
He's confused, he
doesn't know who he is.
Pet Sematary.
Arthur, we need to restrain him.
I got him.
Kal-El, the last
son of Krypton...
Remember who you are.
Tell me who you...
Clark...
I know you.
Please don't make me do this.
Alfred, I need the big gun...
- You did this...
- I had to.
You won't let me live.
You won't let me die.
The world needs you.
But does it need you?
Tell me...
Do you bleed?
Clark.
Please...
Please.
Please,
just go.
Yeah?
Let's go. Yeah...
Yeah. Something's
definitely bleeding.
The Mother Box.
He has the last one.
You brought us here.
You remembered.
This is home.
You smell good.
Did I not before?
Don't do that.
We just got our
asses handed to us
and Steppenwolf
has got the third Box.
So we find them.
If the Boxes are even
close to each other
there's going to be some kind
of energy surge.
And Steppenwolf's gonna be keeping
them somewhere where they don't read.
No internet, no
satellite coverage.
That narrows it down.
Not enough.
See, you can't find them...
...or maybe you
don't want to.
Arthur.
Yeah, that was a great way
to get rid of Superman.
Man, I'm not doing
this on purpose.
Right. Because you can't
control the machine.
Right, so is this a bad time
to bring up my blood sugar?
Very hungry...
Victor...
You can find the Boxes.
You share their energy.
I know it's frightening.
But if you go under...
I promise, we will
pull you back out.
Just keep the Little Merman
away from me while I work.
Barry, go find Alfred
in the pantry.
Then come back, get online.
Everybody check
everybody else's work.
Listen,
just wanted if you
could, put out a,
if you were, an aquatic...
You know...
Do you, talk to fish?
The water does the talking.
Of course.
If the current comes in strange,
I'm gonna point the way.
Okay.
Wait.
Let me.
Isn't this a little
out of place.
So, Clark seemed to share
your view on being woken up.
He could've killed you.
I was willing to make the trade.
And bringing in Lois Lane?
Remember what you told me
about heart, in the hangar?
I bet you...
...thought I
wasn't listening.
Thank you.
You know you can't
do this forever.
I can barely do it now.
Steppenwolf...
This is the job.
It's my job.
And I haven't been doing it.
I've been reacting.
Not leading.
You know, what you said
about Steve Trevor...
That wasn't my
business. I'm sorry.
You were pushing
me to lead the team.
But leaders get people killed.
I fought...
Always...
When I was needed.
But to lead, to
step into the light...
And to say to people:
"This is worth your life?"
When it's your fault...
They're all Steve Trevor.
We make it through tonight...
You can stay in
the shadows forever.
Dressed up like a bat.
I won't even sue.
If... we get
through the night.
Are you okay?
You brought us here, but you've
hardly spent a minute in the house.
I know... I...
Just got out of a wooden box.
What was it like...
Coming back?
Itchy.
I mean, honestly...
Weird,
in so many ways.
- But, mostly just...
- I wasn't strong.
I didn't...
You would've been
very disappointed in me.
I wasn't...
Lois Lane, dedicated
reporter. I...
I just...
It's okay.
I'm the idiot who left.
But I'm back now...
And I'm gonna make things right.
You called mom?
Of course.
Thank you.
I was hoping it was
gonna take you longer to...
...recover.
Why?
Because now, I have
to send you away.
Bruce.
He needs you.
Fate of the world. I think
that's the deal. He was...
Pretty tense.
Well, I guess I do owe him one.
Right.
But no dying.
And I get the exclusive.
Yes, ma'am.
- You're really you?
- I'm really me, ma.
At last.
Praise to the Unity.
The three is one.
Praise to the Mother of Horrors.
Is Steppenwolf there?
Sorry.
It's Porzenov.
In Northern Russia.
The Nuclear Plant.
Had a meltdown 30 years ago.
There have been some
attempts to resettle nearby...
...but it looks like
really rough sledding.
Who picks this place
to put down roots?
People that are making
it count everywhere else.
The Earth starts changing...
...it'll hit them first.
How long have we got?
A few hours.
Transport won't fly that fast.
It will for me.
The Unity brings all three
boxes together in perfect sync.
Its power builds
until it can't be contained.
But if I can cause a
delay between each box,
even for a nanosecond...
Its energy will cascade.
Form a loop.
And they'll feed on each other.
And that's it? We
just pull them apart?
No fuss, no muss?
Separating the boxes is still
gonna cause a massive surge.
I have to be there.
But you guys should
think about getting clear.
We're with you 'till it's done.
Honestly...
I think we're gonna be
dead way before that.
And you know what?
I don't mind. It's
an honorable end.
But we've gotta shut
Steppenwolf down.
Superman's
a no-show.
You've got no powers.
No offense.
This guy might be working
for the enemy. We don't know.
You're tripping over
your feet, and mine...
You're gorgeous.
And fierce...
And strong. And...
I know we went to war
with the Amazons, but...
but that was before my time.
You know what?
I don't wanna die.
I'm young. There's
shit that I wanna do.
I just feel like...
I didn't really embrace
the sea or the land.
I've been a loner my whole life.
But being part of
something bigger,
like this...
Maybe I'm scared because...
I'm meant to...
I think that was beautiful.
You say a word about this,
and I'll meet every prawn I know.
I honestly didn't hear anything
after "We're all gonna die."
Let them come.
I'm gonna take out that tower
and knock down that shield dome.
You get to Steppenwolf.
Don't wait for me.
Just do the job.
Alright, Alfred. Are we
set to broadcast?
Playing all your favorite hits.
Come on, follow me,
you damn insects.
They're coming.
They're all coming.
We might not have
thought this through.
He's clearing the field.
He won't last three minutes.
Then let's use them.
On my lead.
They're leaving.
Papa.
Everyone, get out!
Son of a bitch.
This isn't the plan.
No, Master Wayne...
...this is the team.
Hey, blame the lady.
We would've left you
but she didn't ask for our vote.
So your genius move is dying?
You really are out of your mind.
I'm not the one who
brought a pitchfork.
- Ride ain't over yet.
- My man.
Is this what conquering is?
Hiding from the fight?
Oh, no...
You're all mine.
- Thanks for the lift.
- Yeah, no problem.
You got this?
These things are
gonna keep coming.
You get technical.
I'm on bug duty.
Let's do it.
Yes! That's gross.
Thank you.
This is not...
Now,
do you see it?
Whatever you're
in the middle of...
It's spreading for miles.
Satellites show
civilians moving east.
They're not gonna make it.
Barry...
I need you to take a walk.
God, I hope this is east.
Diana.
You're not worthy, to touch.
Mother.
She's power.
And power,
is the only law.
They're all too weak
to see the truth.
Well...
I believe in truth.
But I'm also a
big fan of justice.
All right!
Kryptonian.
So. How
do I help?
We buy him some time,
he can stop that box from
destroying all life on Earth.
We hope.
Well, I knew you didn't bring
me back 'cause you like me.
I don't... not...
Civilians...
- Barry is headed...
- There's too many of them.
Oh, yeah. This is
definitely east.
Slowpoke.
Oh, it's on.
I'll take the ones on the right.
It's okay.
Hold on. Hold on.
Dostoyevski!
Is this guy still bothering you?
Superman!
We gotta pull
these things apart.
A couple of more seconds...
you'll see her opening.
Any blow-back?
Big-time.
But I think we can take it.
Good...
Because I really
like being alive.
So do I.
Clark.
I take it back...
I wanna die.
Man, my toes hurt.
I don't even understand the
physics of how my toes hurt.
Children.
I work with children.
Have you guys seen
what's going on outside?
I am the end of worlds.
Who are you,
to defy me?
This world...
...is my right!
You will never...
No!
This cannot be...
Recognize that smell?
Fear.
No! Leave me!
Get off me!
I command you!
No!
No...
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
Booyah!
P_S_A_G_M_E_N_O.COM
Glad I didn't miss this.
So am I.
Yeah.
Now she's glad.
Thank you, Bruce.
Not enough for what you did.
I did a mistake.
That's all.
How did you get the house
back from the bank?
I bought the bank.
The whole bank?
Slow your reflex with me.
I'm old.
What?
It's actually the,
worst job you can
get in a crime lab.
But, uh...
My foot's in the door.
Yeah. I got a recommendation
from a friend.
This is like a "job" job?
"Job" job.
Look at you go!
Darkness.
The truest darkness...
...is not the
absence of light.
It is the conviction
that the light...
...will never return.
Must be 150 feet.
Must be.
Big round table.
Six chairs.
Right there.
With room for more.
But the light always returns...
...to show us
things familiar.
Home.
Family.
And things entirely new.
Or long overlooked.
It shows us new possibilities...
And challenges us
to pursue them.
Yeah. And Johnny Menasco
runs the whole thing.
I mean, he did the
Bilbao job 2 years ago.
As are all the
storage in Croydon.
- The Belgian.
- Right, yeah. The Belgian.
This time, the light
shone on the heroes.
Coming out of the shadows
to tell us we won't
be alone again.
Our darkness was deep...
...and seemed to
swallow all hope.
But these heroes were
here the whole time.
To remind us that hope is real.
That you can see it.
All you have to do is look...
Up in the sky...
I can't tell you how much I
appreciate you doing this.
I don't know, Barry.
I'm curious myself.
Yeah. And it's not like a
competition, you know?
Well, it...
It is a competition.
But it's not like a macho-
measuring thing.
But if I win, you're
off the team.
No...
If I win...
Bruce said something about you
having to take us all to "brunch"...?
Oh, see, now that's cold.
That's a betrayal.
I feel stung by that.
Okay.
But if I win, I get to tell everyone.
Deal.
Which coast?
You know, I've never
seen the pacific.
Which is that way, because...
The sun, and it's...
Psagmeno.com
Quality Movies Subs & Info