There he is!
Oh, sorry.
Superman, Superman,
can we ask you some questions?
It's for our podcast.
Well, in that case...
How many people that
you saved... Have you saved?
- I...
- Never mind.
Does your thing
really stand for hope?
Yes. It does.
But it looks like an "S."
Yes. It's meant to. It's...
It's meant to wind like a river.
It comes and goes. My...
A man I knew used to say that
hope is like your car keys.
Easy to lose, but if you dig
around, it's usually close by.
Did you ever fight a hippo?
No. Shh. That's dumb.
But hippos are the most deadly.
What's the best thing
about Planet Earth?
Hmm...
What are you doing?
No, wait. No, wait. Wait. Wait!
Please! Please, man. Please!
What do you want from me?
Fear.
They can smell it.
What the hell?
- What was that?
- A scout.
From space?
Like an alien army?
Alfred, are you seeing this?
I am.
Matches the other sightings.
And that pattern
is all over Luthor's notes.
Prep the jet.
We're going north tonight.
Good. It's time, then.
It's 'cause
they know he's dead, right?
Superman.
He's gone.
Where does that leave us?
Drop your guns now!
Excuse me.
Go!
Move it! Move! Move!
Get down!
Line them up along the wall!
Keep them quiet!
Children, stay close to me.
Who are you?
The Lasso of Hestia compels
you to reveal the truth.
Now, who are you?
We're a small group
of reactionary terrorists.
We know that sin has brought
on this plague of aliens.
Why the hostages?
You're too late.
The countdown's already begun.
In a few minutes, four city
blocks...
While the world watches.
Hush!
Shut up!
This is man's best hope.
Down with the modern world.
Back to the Dark Ages,
and the safety of holy fear.
Quiet!
This would've been
over quickly, but...
No! Don't!
I don't believe it.
What are you?
A believer.
I'm asking for your help.
I believe there is a stranger who
comes to this village from the sea.
He comes in the winter when the
people are hungry and brings fish.
He comes on the king tide.
That was last night.
Icebergs in the harbor, four months
since the last ship got through.
Well, this stranger
doesn't come by ship.
There are enemies coming
from far away.
I need warriors.
I'm building an alliance
to defend ourselves.
Look, I'll give you $25,000
to talk to this man right now.
Outside.
Tell me what those three boxes
are and I'll make it $30,000.
You should get out.
Can you at least point me
to Atlantis?
Arthur Curry.
Also known as
Protector of the Oceans.
The Aquaman.
I hear you can talk to fish.
So let me get this straight.
You do it dressed like a bat?
Like an actual bat?
It's worked for 20 years
in Gotham.
Oh, that shithole.
When the fight comes,
we'll need you.
- Don't count on it, Batman.
- Why not?
'Cause I don't like
you coming here,
digging into my business
and getting into my life.
People from Atlantis tell me,
"Do this."
Now you say, "Do that."
- I wanna be left alone.
- Is that why you help
these people out here
in the middle of nowhere?
'Cause you can just leave?
I help them 'cause
no one else does.
If you want to protect them,
you need to work with me.
"Strong man is strongest alone."
You ever heard that?
That's not a saying.
That's the opposite
of what the saying is.
Yeah.
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
You ever hear of Superman?
He died fighting next to me.
My point exactly.
What's in the three boxes?
It's ancient history.
What is it?
Mankind's melting
the polar ice caps,
destroying the ecosystem.
They got it coming?
Hey, I don't mind
if the oceans rise.
How about if they boil?
Dressed like a bat.
You're out of your mind,
Bruce Wayne.
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
So you say you have no way of
reconnecting with this Aquaman?
Oh, I put a tracking device in his
coat, but he left without it.
May, in fact,
not have been his coat.
Those squares
from Luthor's notes.
I think they must be
containers of some kind.
Of what?
I don't know. Money. Power.
Something worth starting
a war over.
Well, we've had luck with one
person on the team list.
Barry Allen of Central City.
He's completely off the grid.
Squatting, I think.
Moves suddenly and often.
Disappearing act.
But he does visit his father.
In prison for murdering
his mother.
Jesus.
Young Barry always
protested his father's innocence.
But he was nine
and nobody listened to him.
We have somebody at the prison?
Oh, yeah.
We'll find the address.
What about, uh, Diana?
Well, you have her number.
What, you could've called her.
Oh! Perhaps I should fly to
Paris with a handwritten note.
"Will you be Bruce's teammate?
Check yes or no."
I'm only interested
in her skill set.
- I'm sure you are.
- Can we?
Ah, well, facial recognition's
a bit dodgy on this one.
But they've got a partial match.
A Victor Stone.
Genius IQ, football scholarship
to GCU, and deceased.
Figures.
Fairy tales and ghost stories.
One misses the days when one's biggest
concerns were exploding wind-up penguins.
The simple life.
I don't recognize this world.
I don't have to recognize it.
I just have to save it.
Here to see Henry Allen.
Sign.
Hurry it up, will you?
What, you got a problem?
No, there's no problem.
Better not be.
You know where to go.
Are those prescription?
Or are you just trying
to look brainy?
Because you're holding
yourself back.
You're going in circles.
You're working three dead-end
jobs, going on four.
Where do you even have the time?
- I make the time.
- And this is all to pay
for a criminal justice
degree, huh?
Okay, I really don't wanna
talk about this again.
The investigation was botched.
Give me your hand, man.
I want you to listen to me,
Barry, because I mean this.
I want you to give all that up.
And I want you to stop
coming to see me.
I am a drag on your life.
Please don't ever say
that to me again.
Please?
You can be whatever
you want to be.
You're brilliant, man.
Absolute best of the best.
I can't sit here and watch you
run in place in Central City
for some old dude
who is not going anywhere.
- Dad, that's not true.
- It's time.
- That's not true.
- Let's go, Allen. Allen!
I want you to make
your own future.
You're living in the past.
Make your own future.
Open gate.
Lab's all yours, Howard.
11:30.
Early night for you, Silas.
Yes. Early.
I never got to say...
I'm very sorry
about what happened.
Victor was a wonderful kid.
Thank you.
Victor.
Victor, you're not stuck
up here.
You can have a life.
You can have more than...
If you stay up here brooding...
I'm processing.
I can access everything.
But I can't put it all together.
Not yet. But if you worked with me,
if we had the change engine...
So you'd do to someone
else what you did to me?
No.
The box stays hidden.
If you could see
what we're learning
from the Kryptonian ship... I think the change
engine could integrate with its energy,
- get it powered up and...
- Does anybody know?
- What?
- At the lab.
Does anybody know I'm alive?
I...
didn't think you were ready
for them to...
To what?
For them to see the monster?
You are not a monster.
It's weird that you thought
I meant me.
What I did...
I lost your mother
in that accident.
I wasn't about to...
I couldn't bear to lose my son.
But you did.
I got a language in my head
that I don't speak.
It's not just digital.
It's alien.
Every day, I wake up different.
Modified.
How do you...
Couldn't do that last night.
Ever since we got visitors
from Krypton,
people have been waiting
for the next alien invasion.
Now I gotta wonder if I'm it.
Any changes today?
No, my Queen.
The Mother Box has awoken,
yet nothing has happened.
It has slept for thousands of
years, since the First Age.
Why did it wake at all?
Amazons! On your mark!
Yes, soldiers! Fight on!
Ready!
Steppenwolf.
Mother.
Millennia in exile, searching...
At last you call me home.
You will not like your welcome.
Oh, I think I will.
Steady!
Forward!
Gather the legions!
You must seal the cage!
Go!
Flank right!
Yes.
Run.
Seal the gates!
Keep it moving.
Got it! Go!
Enough.
Noble Queen, why do you fight?
After the unity,
you will join my legion
and you will know
the righteousness of power.
You will love me.
You all will.
We have to light the ancient
warning fire.
The fire has not burned
for 5,000 years.
Men won't know what it means.
Men won't.
She will.
Listen to me, Diana.
What did you
do this weekend, Diana?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Nothing very interesting.
That's all you ever tell us.
What can I say,
I'm not that exciting.
...so-called
shrine of the Amazons,
an enormous bonfire burned
right behind me,
baffling absolutely everyone from
locals to government authorities alike.
The fire could be seen
for miles on end.
Invasion.
On the local scene, this janitor's
wife had some strong words
for the aliens she says
stole her man.
My Howard is a good man.
He's a provider.
And these aliens
are gonna... probe him?
Come down to the Lakeview, and I'll stick
a... probe up your alien... you...
I found a little
place. By the diner.
Suits me just fine.
I wish you'd said something.
Oh, no.
I got behind in the payments.
And you know the banks jump like
a cougar if you miss by a dime.
Place was too big
for me, anyway.
Shuffling around
like an old ghost.
Well, I might've been able
to talk to someone, or...
You had enough to deal with.
Don't need to add
"mother-in-law" to the list.
Not that I was ever...
Hey, Lane.
Who was your source,
the activist in that university?
Well, it's my source.
I got tapped
for the kidnapping story.
There were all
those student protests.
Anyway, I'm thinking
it's political.
So, who's your guy?
Well, I'll see
if she'll take your call.
So it's a she. Hmm.
It's not a she.
Sounds like you should be
working that story.
I'm...
I'm not ready yet.
I'm perfectly happy
doing fluff pieces
about kitten grooming.
For a while.
It was hard coming back
here at all.
Well, I can hardly read
the news, anyway.
So much bitterness.
Of course I think it's all
because he's gone.
But I suppose a mother does.
But it's not like there's any
less that needs reporting.
And Clark promised me you were
gonna bring home another Pulitzer.
- Oh, did he?
- Oh, yes. He did.
He said that you were the thirstiest
young woman that he'd ever met.
Hungriest.
Hungriest... Yeah.
He said you could smell a story
further away than he could hear.
Well, stories just made sense.
It was more than just a puzzle.
It was about the truth.
It was about seeing the engine
of the world.
When it still ran.
Victor Stone. Deceased.
That one.
Pretty sure that's what made
the alien go crazy.
I'll see about rigging
something for the suit.
Won't be quick.
Anything that can
give me an edge.
You know, I paid millions of dollars
for this building's security.
Yeah, it looked expensive.
Hi.
A new toy?
Prototype troop carrier.
I once knew a man
who would have loved to fly it.
Yeah.
We're gonna need
more than a pilot.
I think
there's an attack coming.
Not coming, Bruce.
It's already here.
They called him
Steppenwolf, the end of worlds.
He lived only to conquer.
Millions fell before his blade,
or rose again as his Parademons.
Nightmare creatures
who feed on fear.
Yeah, I think I met one.
We didn't hit it off.
Here in Gotham?
They're all over.
They're looking for his boxes?
The Mother Boxes.
Mother Boxes.
I guess Steppenwolf took the one
your people were guarding.
That leaves two more.
I'm impressed.
Don't be.
I have no idea what's in them.
A weapon? Some kind of power?
They don't contain power.
They are power.
Carried from planet to planet,
the Mother Boxes combine
to form the unity.
An apocalyptic power
that not only destroys worlds,
but transforms them into the primordial
hellscape of Steppenwolf's birth world.
We should have died.
But we formed our own unity.
Amazons, Atlanteans, all the
tribes of men fought side by side.
Warriors of legend...
...allies from other worlds,
even the gods themselves
all acted as one,
laying down their lives
to drive Steppenwolf away.
Some say it drove him mad.
The disgrace
of his first retreat.
He swore our alliance
would crumble.
That darkness would cover
the Earth.
And that he would return
when it did.
Left behind,
the Mother Boxes were too
dangerous to be kept together.
One was entrusted
to the Amazons.
One to the Atlanteans.
Both sealed and guarded
in secure strongholds.
The Box of Men
was buried in secret,
so that no tribe would be tempted
to use its power over another.
Such harmony out of such horror.
It was truly an Age of Heroes.
Something tells me we're not
getting the band back together.
The Atlanteans
were forced undersea,
and the Amazons to an island
they can never leave.
Well, I wouldn't count
on the tribes of men.
We tend to act like the Doomsday
Clock has a snooze button.
- How long until...
- Days.
At most.
Steppenwolf's mistake last time
was attacking us.
He wanted to make the Earth
kneel before he destroyed us.
This time he'll just go
after the boxes.
I got a location
for one of our recruits.
Barry Allen.
What about the other one?
Victor Stone?
I was hoping
you would dig him up.
We're asking people we don't
know to risk their lives.
I know.
That's how this works.
Barry Allen, Bruce Wayne.
You said that like it explains why
there's a total stranger in my place,
sitting in the dark,
in my second favorite chair.
Tell me about this.
This is a person who looks exactly
like me, but who is definitely not me.
Very attractive Jewish boy.
Somebody who, I don't know,
stole your pocket watch?
Or railroads?
I know you have abilities.
I just don't know what they are.
My special skills include viola, web
design, fluent in sign language...
Gorilla sign language.
Silica-based quartz sand fabric,
abrasion resistant, heat resistant...
Yeah, I do competitive
ice dancing.
It's what they use
on the space shuttle
to prevent it from burning up
on reentry.
I do very competitive
ice dancing.
Whoever you're looking for,
it's not me.
You're the Batman?
So, you're fast.
That feels like
an oversimplification.
I'm putting together a team.
People with special abilities.
You see,
I believe enemies are coming.
Stop right there. I'm in.
- You are?
- Yeah.
I need friends.
People are difficult.
They require a lot of focus.
They, uh...
They have, like, a rhythm
that I haven't quite
been able to...
Like brunch!
Like, what is brunch?
You wait in line for an hour
for, essentially, lunch.
I mean...
I don't know.
People are a little slow.
I'll try to keep up.
Can I keep this?
It's like this layer
of dimensional reality,
and it seems to manipulate
space-time.
I call it the Speed Force.
Causes me to burn a tremendous
amount of calories.
So I'm just a black hole
of snacks.
I am a "snack" hole.
How many people
are on this special fight team?
Three, including you.
Three? Against what?
I'll tell you on the plane.
The plane?
What are your superpowers again?
I'm rich.
The program always gets
twitchy with this footage.
You know who we are.
Are you Victor Stone?
I need to speak to you.
No. Face-to-face.
I'm old-fashioned that way.
If I was going to attack you, I
would have done it by the lake.
Looks like you have a date,
Ms. Prince.
About time somebody here did.
Face-to-face.
I've been doing some tracking.
What you're looking for
is sticking to the dead zones.
If it gets in front of a camera,
causes a surge,
- I'll let you know.
- That's not good enough.
Not good enough?
For you.
Look, I don't know you, and I don't
know how you got these gifts.
Gifts?
No one else can do what you do.
No. If these are gifts, then why
am I the one paying for them?
We need you, Victor.
And maybe you need us.
I do fine alone.
I told myself the same
for a long time.
I lost someone I loved once.
I shut myself off from...
From everyone.
But I had to learn to open
back up again.
The truth is,
I'm still working on it.
And if you agreed to meet me,
you're working on it, too.
Trust me, Victor.
Mayday! Mayday!
Something came down
from the sky!
Cortlandt, you're cutting out.
Please help me!
Whiskey.
And one for Ahab, there.
From the sky.
I heard a cannon.
- To ocean's rage.
- And they came.
Monsters from the sky.
Tore right through my boat.
Monsters.
It's on him.
You took a hell of a hit.
You all right?
At last.
The firstborn of beloved
Queen Atlanna.
Wait.
Please.
I knew her.
Well, that makes one of us.
When my parents fought in
the wars, she took me in.
What a saint.
You dare speak
of Queen Atlanna that way?
Your Queen left me
on my father's doorstep
and never gave me
another thought.
Your mother left you
to save your life.
You cannot imagine
how it hurt her.
What it cost her.
But you're not a defenseless
child now.
It would have been
her responsibility
to follow that monster
to the surface and stop it.
Now, it's yours.
Then I'm gonna need
something from you.
I see, Mother.
I see why you waited
to summon me.
The Kryptonian's death plunged
this timid world into such terror.
Amazons, Atlanteans,
each stands and falls alone.
I know, Mother, you've waited
too long for the unity.
I know. But you will feed.
And my exile will come
to an end.
I will take my place among
the New Gods.
Find the last one!
Its power will cleanse
this world.
For the unity!
For Darkseid.
Oh, Victor.
Asshole!
Eight kidnappings.
Six in Metropolis, two here.
All the vics work for STAR Labs.
"Attacked by a flying vampire."
"Suspect was a giant bat
with huge fangs."
One of them was a little kid.
Scared. Won't say a word
but drew this. Looks like...
I know what it looks like.
Come on, you think he fights
criminals for 20 years here,
and then he goes to Metropolis
and kidnaps eight people?
I'll talk to him tonight.
World's gone crazy, Jim.
Maybe he did, too.
Did you find the cyborg?
We spoke.
Give him time.
You must be Barry. I'm Diana.
Hi, Barry, I'm Diana.
That's not right. Great.
- So this is us?
- Yeah, this is us.
Oh! Awesome!
That's the Bat-Signal!
That's your... Oh, sh...
Sorry.
That's your signal.
That means we have to go now.
Yeah, that's what that means.
It's so cool.
How many of you are there?
Not enough.
Eight people abducted
from or near STAR Labs.
Here's the potential perp.
Parademons.
Okay.
The demons must have caught
the scent of the Mother Box.
They carried people away
to find out what they know.
So the eight may still be alive.
Nine.
The head of STAR Labs
was taken as well.
You made it.
So then, there must be
a nest nearby.
I plotted all the sightings
in Metropolis, Gotham.
No pattern I can see.
The lines on the map
don't converge.
On land.
These lead back to Braxton
Island between the two cities.
Gotham Harbor.
These are air vents.
They all lead down to the tunnel for
Metropolis Project that was abandoned in '29.
Do you really think that...
Oh, wow. They just...
They really just vanish.
Huh? Oh.
That's rude.
- Where are we, Alfred?
- Braxton Island.
You should be directly under the
venting tower for the tunnel.
Now look to your left,
you should see a staircase.
It'll give you access
to the machine room.
Define "access."
One at a time.
The bridge may not hold.
Just tell me the truth.
Please, just let us go.
I have a family.
Wrong answer.
Humans.
The stench of your fear
is making my soldiers hungry.
Shall I feed them?
You've been near the Mother Box.
Her scent is on you.
Please. We have families.
Why does everyone keep
telling me that?
Please, please.
I don't need to hurt you...
Right. Okay. Yeah.
Here's the thing. Um...
See, I'm afraid of bugs and, um,
guns, and obnoxiously tall people.
And murder. And I can't be here.
It's really cool you guys seem
ready to do battle and stuff,
but, full transparency,
I've never done battle.
I've just pushed some people
and run away.
Save one.
- What?
- Save one person.
Uh... Which one?
Don't talk, don't fight.
Get in, get one out.
And then?
You'll know.
Okay.
Useless.
You then.
Where is my Mother Box?
I'll die before I tell you.
At last, one that doesn't whine.
But you will scream.
Dad.
Victor.
Ah, you were born of her.
A creature of chaos.
Not how I see it.
Give it time.
Ahh!
Amazon!
Okay.
Save one. Save one.
This one is mine.
You overestimate yourself.
Child,
my ax is still slick
with the blood of your sisters.
Alfred, I need the Nightcrawler.
Thought you'd never ask.
Crawler's on the way.
Initiating remote mode.
- Okay, you good?
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
At the end of the hall,
there should be stairs. Go!
He's after the change engine.
His Mother Box.
You have to keep him from it.
- Help people get to safety.
- Promise me!
Go!
Finish her!
Sorry, guys.
I didn't bring a sword.
Jesus. He is tall.
Oh, fuck.
Uh...
So, you have the blood
of the Old Gods in you.
The Old Gods died.
No!
Heads up.
Thanks, Alfred,
but I'll take it from here.
Uh, do I know you?
Primitive beings.
What are we under right now?
Gotham Harbor.
You all need to move.
You get him out.
Diana, there's no time.
Also among my fears is drowning.
You are a distraction.
Mother is calling.
Diana, come on!
Oh, come on.
Whoa!
The change engine.
Did he just bail?
Millions in structural damage.
You haven't lost your touch.
But it's good to see you
playing well with others.
Dressed like a bat.
I dig it.
May be temporary.
So, what made you change
your mind?
Steppenwolf.
He took the Mother Box
from Atlantis.
All he needs now
is the lost Box of Men.
If he doesn't already have it.
He doesn't have it.
Wow! It's like a cave.
Like a bat cave.
Barry.
My father called it
a change engine.
It was found by the British
during World War I.
They studied it, but they couldn't
even date it, it's so old.
It was shelved till
the night Superman died.
Then she lit up like Christmas.
They brought it to STAR Labs where my father
recognized it as a perpetual energy matrix.
That sounds cool. I thought
it was like a nuclear bomb.
A Mother Box destroys
as it creates.
It's a cycle of life,
but a million times faster.
My father thought it was the key
to unlimited energy.
New formulas.
Cellular regeneration.
But it's too volatile
to control.
He used it on you.
I was in an accident.
Should've died.
My father thought that he
could use the Mother Box
to rebuild the broken
parts of me
with a few
cybernetic enhancements.
Instead he built
a living machine
that may be stronger
than its host.
Too much.
Too much life.
What's on your weird mind?
Muscles, coordination,
basic cellular integrity.
A human being can only
absorb so much.
The Mother Box was designed
to reshape a planet.
So?
So, what if you were stronger
than a planet?
Your cells lying dormant,
but incapable of decay.
If you were in a conductive field,
a boost from the Mother Box...
Could bring him back to life.
The Kryptonian ship
has an amniotic chamber,
- which would be a perfect...
- No.
- Diana...
- Bruce, no.
You have no idea what kind
of power you are dealing with.
Even if there's a fraction
of a chance?
That what? That we could raise
a monster like Luthor did?
We have tech Luthor's
never even seen.
Superman is dead.
We all wish he weren't.
We don't know
what state he's in.
We know we can't bring him back.
But this is science
beyond our limits.
And that's what science is for.
To do what's never been done.
To make life better.
Or to end it.
Technology is like
any other power.
Without reason, without heart,
it destroys us.
You're risking lives.
Theirs and maybe countless more.
We don't have time
for a control group.
Is it a risk? Yes.
But it's necessary.
Why, because of your guilt?
Bruce, I was there.
You didn't kill Superman.
At some point, even you have
to learn to move on.
Steve Trevor tell you that?
Superman was a beacon
to the world.
Why aren't you?
You're an inspiration, Diana.
You don't just save people, you
make them see their better selves.
And yet, I'd never heard of you until
Luthor lured you out by stealing
a picture
of your dead boyfriend.
You shut yourself down
for a century,
so let's not talk about
me moving on.
You know that if she kills
you, we'll cover for her.
We are not enough!
Each of us, in our own way,
is held back.
And I promise you, Steppenwolf is
not out there talking about ethics.
He's trying to burn
down the world!
The way we're gonna stop him
is by using his power...
This power, against him.
I agree.
I don't like the idea of
reintegrating with the Mother Box,
but I was running the numbers
while you were being an asshole,
and there is a high probability
that we can bring him back.
Right, right. But we mean bring him
back in like a, "Yay, he's back!" way,
not in like
a Pet Sematary scenario.
You lose something when you die.
Even Superman.
Maybe not his mind.
Maybe his soul.
I'll have a contingency plan
for that.
If he wakes up and you're the first
thing he sees, you'll need one.
Well, that was fun
while it didn't last.
She could've stopped me.
I practically dared her to.
I don't see why
you're pushing her.
We have to boost the signal.
Put it through
the Batmobile speakers.
Yeah, now you're changing
the subject.
- I have a contingency.
- What?
Diana was right about the risk.
If the plan goes south, we're
gonna bring in the big guns.
But that's not...
Those are very big guns.
You've got a team here.
Superman would bring
this team together
better than I ever could.
His strength...
It doesn't matter
how strong you are.
Or what abilities
you might have...
He was more human than I am.
He lived in this world.
Fell in love. Had a job.
Despite all that power.
The world needs Superman.
And the team needs Clark.
And what does Clark need?
Maybe he's at peace.
He'll get over it.
You know, I could do
this a lot faster. I just...
Is it weird that
it feels disrespectful?
Yep.
Do you feel a sense
of confidence
that we're not doing something
horribly wrong and macabre here?
Not really.
- Okay, then why...
- Because I saw Steppenwolf up close.
The stories Diana told us,
I believe them.
Why we gotta stop him.
That's the plan.
Okay. We're not ready for...
It's racially charged.
You got struck
by lightning, huh?
Uh, yeah,
that's the abridged version.
- And you...
- Explosion.
Woke up in a lab.
So we're the accidents.
Yeah, that's us.
Hey. No, no.
We're approaching
the Kryptonian ship.
ETA 30 seconds.
I'm here for him.
- I swear I would never...
- Save it.
- Okay.
Okay.
This is amazing.
This is crazy.
Oh, what, now it's crazy?
You lunatics better know
what you're doing.
Welcome.
Lex Luthor fried the circuits
bringing his creature to life.
There's not enough charge
to wake the box.
I might be able to do it.
I might be able
to jump-start it.
If I can get enough distance, I can
conduct a significant electrical current.
I might be able to wake
the box. If that's...
- still what we want.
- We have to try.
This must be the end
of the line.
So, I'm in position.
The Mother Box is ready.
You have to charge it the moment
it touches the fluid.
- Five.
Diana's right.
This is a bad idea.
- Four.
- Three.
Two.
One.
He's back.
Dispatch, this is 3-Adam-1-6.
Backing up Code Three.
I'm currently two minutes out.
He's not all right.
Copy that.
- He's scanning us.
- What?
Arthur, you need to relax.
Your adrenaline's spiking.
Because he's not all right.
Oh, no.
Should we bow?
Or show our bellies?
Victor? Victor!
- Shit!
- What are you doing?
- Victor!
- It's my armor's
- defense system.
- No!
It's stronger
since the interface.
- I can't control it.
- Victor, no! Victor!
Just think
happy thoughts, Victor.
Go to a happier place.
Kal-El, no!
He's confused.
He doesn't know who he is.
Pet Sematary.
Arthur, we need to restrain him.
I got him.
Kal-El, the last son of Krypton.
Remember who you are.
Tell me who you...
Clark.
I know you.
Please don't make me do this.
Alfred, I need the big gun.
You did this.
I had to.
You won't let me live.
You won't let me die.
The world needs you.
But does it need you?
Tell me.
Do you bleed?
Clark!
Clark.
Please.
Just go.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Yeah, something
is definitely bleeding.
The Mother Box.
He has the last one.
You brought us here.
You remembered.
This is home.
You smell good.
Did I not before?
Don't do that.
We just got our asses
handed to us.
And Steppenwolf has got
the third box.
So we find them.
If the boxes are even close
to each other,
there is going to be
some kind of energy surge.
Steppenwolf's gonna be keeping
them somewhere where they don't read.
No Internet,
no satellite coverage.
- Well, that narrows it down.
- Not enough.
So, you can't find them.
Or maybe you don't want to.
Arthur.
Yeah, that was a great way
to get rid of Superman.
Man, I'm not doing
this on purpose.
Right, 'cause you can't
control the machine.
So is this a bad time
to bring up my blood sugar?
Very hungry.
Victor.
You can find the boxes.
You share their energy.
I know it's frightening,
but if you go under,
I promise we will pull
you back out.
Just keep the little merman
away from me while I work.
Barry, go find Alfred
in the pantry.
When you come back, get online.
Everybody checks
everybody else's work.
Listen...
I was wondering if you could
put out a feeler.
Like, aquatic.
Do you talk to fish?
The water does the talking.
Of course.
If the current comes in strange,
it might point the way.
Okay.
Wait.
Let me.
It's just a little out of place.
So Clark seemed to share
your view on being woken up.
He could've killed you.
I was willing to make the trade.
And bringing in Lois Lane?
Remember what you told me
about heart in the hangar?
I bet you...
...thought I wasn't listening.
Thank you.
You know you can't
do this forever.
I can barely do it now.
Steppenwolf.
This is the job.
It's my job.
And I haven't been doing it.
I've been reacting.
Not leading.
You know, what you said
about Steve Trevor...
It wasn't my business.
I'm sorry.
You were pushing me
to lead the team.
But leaders get people killed.
I fought always
when I was needed.
But to lead, to step into the
light and to say to people,
"This is worth your life."
When it's your fault,
they're all Steve Trevor.
We make it through tonight, you
can stay in the shadows forever.
Dress up like a bat.
I won't even sue.
If we get through the night.
Are you okay?
You brought us here,
but you've...
hardly spent
a minute in the house.
I know. It's...
I just got out of a wooden box.
What was it like?
Coming back?
Itchy.
I mean, honestly,
weird in so many ways.
- But mostly just...
- I wasn't strong.
I didn't, um...
You would've been
very disappointed in me.
I wasn't Lois Lane,
the dedicated reporter.
I just...
It's okay.
I'm the idiot who left.
But I'm back now.
And I'm gonna make things right.
Ah.
You called Mom.
Of course.
Thank you.
I was hoping it was gonna
take you longer to recover.
Why?
Because now I have
to send you away.
Bruce.
He needs you.
Fate of the world,
I think that's the deal.
He was pretty tense.
Well, I guess I do owe him one.
Right.
But no dying.
And I get the exclusive.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you really you?
I'm really me, Ma.
At last.
Praise to the unity!
The three as one.
Praise to the mother of horrors.
Is Steppenwolf there?
Just a minute.
Sorry.
It's Pozharnov
in northern Russia.
The nuclear plant.
Had a meltdown 30 years ago.
Uh-huh. There have been some
attempts to resettle nearby.
But it looks like
really rough sledding.
Who picks this place
to put down roots?
People that have been
kicked out of everywhere else.
The Earth starts changing,
it will hit them first.
- How long have we got?
- A few hours.
Transport won't fly that fast.
It will for me.
The unity brings all three
boxes together in perfect sync.
Its power builds until
it can't be contained.
But if I can cause a delay between
each box, even for a nanosecond,
its energy will cascade,
form a loop.
They'll feed on each other.
And that's it?
We just pull them apart.
No fuss, no muss.
Separating the boxes is still
gonna cause a massive surge.
I'll have to be there.
But you guys should think
about getting clear.
We're with you till it's done.
Honestly, I think we're all
gonna be dead way before that.
And you know what?
I don't mind.
It's an honorable end.
But we gotta shut
Steppenwolf down.
Superman's a no-show.
You got no powers. No offense.
This guy might be working
for the enemy, we don't know.
You're tripping over your feet
and mine.
Oof...
You're gorgeous.
And fierce, and strong,
and... Mmm.
I know we went to war with the
Amazons, but that was before my time.
And you know what?
I don't wanna die.
I'm young. There's shit
that I want to do.
I just feel like...
I didn't really embrace
the sea or the land.
I've been a loner my whole life.
But being part of something
bigger like this,
maybe I'm scared because
I'm meant to...
I think that was beautiful.
You say a word about this, and
you'll meet every piranha I know.
I honestly didn't hear anything
after, "We're all gonna die."
Ah. Let them come.
I'm going to take out that tower
and knock down that shield dome.
You get to Steppenwolf.
Don't wait for me,
just do the job.
All right, Alfred.
Are we set for broadcast?
Playing all your favorite hits.
Come on, follow me,
you damn insects.
They're coming.
They're all coming.
Ah.
We might not have
thought this through.
He's clearing the field.
He won't last three minutes.
Then let's use them.
On my lead.
Critical damage.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, snap!
You're welcome.
Yeah!
This isn't the plan.
No, Master Wayne.
This is the team.
Hey, blame the lady.
We would've left you,
but she didn't ask for a vote.
So your genius move is dying?
You really are out of your mind.
I'm not the one
who brought a pitchfork.
Yahoo!
Ride ain't over yet.
My man.
Is this what conquering is?
Hiding from the fight?
Oh, no.
You're all mine.
- Thanks for the lift.
- Yeah, no problem.
You got this?
Whoa!
These things are gonna
keep coming.
Okay. You get technical,
I'm on bug duty.
Let's do it.
Yes! That was gross! Oh...
Thank you.
This is...
This is a lot.
Now do you see it?
Whatever you're in the
middle of, it's spreading for miles.
Satellites show civilians
moving east.
They're not gonna make it.
Barry.
I need you to take a walk.
God, I hope this is east.
You're not worthy
to touch Mother.
She's power, and power is the only law.
You're all too weak
to see the truth.
Well...
I believe in truth.
But I'm also a big fan
of justice.
All right.
Kryptonian!
So, how do I help?
We buy him some time, he can stop that
box from destroying all life on Earth.
We hope.
Well, I knew you didn't bring
me back 'cause you liked me.
I don't not...
- Civilians.
- Barry's headed...
There's too many of them.
Come on.
Okay, this is definitely east.
Slowpoke.
Oh, it's on.
I'll take the ones on the right.
It's okay.
Hold on. Hold on. Yeah.
Dostoevsky!
Is this guy still bothering you?
Superman!
We gotta pull
these things apart.
A couple more seconds,
you'll see your opening.
- Any blowback?
- Big time.
But I think we can take it.
Good.
'Cause I really like
being alive.
So do I.
Clark.
I take it back.
I wanna die.
Man, my toes hurt!
I don't even understand
the physics of how my toes hurt.
Children. I work with children.
Uh... Have you guys seen
what's going on outside?
I am the end of worlds!
Who are you to defy...
This world is my right!
No!
This cannot be.
You recognize that smell?
Fear.
No! Leave me!
Get off me! I command you.
No!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
Booyah!
I'm glad I didn't miss this.
So am I.
Yeah.
Now she's glad.
"Thank you" is not enough
for what you did.
I just undid a mistake,
that's all.
How did you get the house back
from the bank?
I bought the bank.
The whole bank?
It's like a reflex with me.
I don't know.
What?
It's actually the worst job
you can get in a crime lab.
But my foot's in the door.
Yeah, I got a recommendation
from a friend.
This is like a "job" job?
"Job" job.
Look at you go.
Darkness, the truest darkness,
is not the absence of light.
It is the conviction that
the light will never return.
Must be 100, 150 feet.
Must be.
Big round table.
Six chairs, right there.
But room for more.
But the light always returns
to show us things familiar.
Home, family,
and things entirely new,
or long overlooked.
It shows us new possibilities and
challenges us to pursue them.
Yeah, and Jerry Monasco
runs the whole kit.
I mean, he did the Bilbao job
two years ago.
Yeah, he has it all in storage
in Croydon.
- The Belgian?
- Right, yeah, the Belgian.
This time,
the light shone on the heroes
coming out of the shadows to
tell us we won't be alone again.
Our darkness was deep
and seemed to swallow all hope.
But these heroes
were here the whole time
to remind us that hope is
real, that you can see it.
All you have to do is look
up in the sky.
I can't tell you how much
I appreciate you doing this.
Not at all, Barry.
Curious myself.
Yeah, and it's not like
a competition, you know?
Well, it is a competition.
But, you know, it's not like
a macho measuring thing.
But if I win,
you're off the team.
- No...
- Oof.
If I win,
Bruce said something about you
having to take us all to brunch?
Oh, see, now that's cold.
That's a betrayal.
I feel stung by that.
Okay, but if I win,
I get to tell everyone.
Deal.
Which coast?
Ah, you know,
I've never seen the Pacific.
Which is that way.
Because the sun and it's...
All right, let's keep it moving.
Come on, Luthor. Let's go.
Luthor!
All right,
stop jerking around, Luthor,
or I'm gonna have
to come in there.
Ah! There he is. Welcome aboard.
Care for a glass
of Goût de Diamants?
I was just celebrating
God's return
out of the ground
and back up into the sky.
He and his odd little friends
are forming some sort of league.
You better not
be wasting my time.
No. I have too much to live for
and more important things to do.
We have to level
the playing field, Mr. Wilson.
To put it plainly
shouldn't we have
a league of our own?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resynced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.