Ashwathama is dead.
The elephant.
Salutations to the Creator, Brahma.
The utterance of whose name...
The end of the Pandavas!
Even though Abhimanyu isn't here,
you're carrying the last heir
of the Pandavas in your womb.
Be brave.
Everything will be alright.
If you're here to kill me,
go ahead, Krishna.
I'm not Arjuna
to listen to your teachings.
What you've done,
is a greater sin
than any of the other
atrocities of Kurukshetra.
How could you stoop so low,
in spite of being the son of Dronacharya?
You have no right to utter
my father's name, Krishna!
You were there.
You could've stopped his death
if you wanted to!
You have been the protector
Of creation for ages
You're the assassin of sinners
The one who bestows hell upon them
There is no other savior except you
Ashwathama...
Even Dronacharya
could not escape his karma.
You attacked an unborn baby.
You must face the consequences of that.
Alright then, spin your chakra
and kill me as a punishment.
Death isn't your punishment, Ashwathama.
It's your salvation.
Over time, all the
Pandavas will be deceased.
My body will perish.
This yuga will reach an end.
But you won't face death.
You will beg for death.
But you will never die.
I curse you as such!
Is there no atonement for me?
You wanted to kill me now.
But one day, you'll have to save me.
Me?
Kali Yuga is approaching.
Kali is arriving.
When unrighteousness increases...
and darkness engulfs the world,
I must reincarnate again.
In that yuga,
Kali is going to be powerful enough
to cause hindrance to my birth.
That's when you must
safeguard my birth haven.
When the air is filled with toxins...
When River Ganga is
devoid of its last drop...
When this gem finds
its way back to you...
then you can assume...
that the time has come.
I stand at the end of time
There is dense darkness, it is infinite
There is sin, there is destruction
Keshav, why don't you come here?
The earth is mortal, it demands God
Come as liberation!
It is dark inside
The sky is dark
Tear through time and come!
Take birth from the womb...
of the earth and come
Come, the cycle of creation spins
Come as karma
Keshav...
When will you come here?
What's this?
I don't know.
Brother, do you have some water?
Ma'am, some water, please?
Have you dried out from washing
away all our sins, Mother Ganga?
Where have you come from?
Nobody gives
water for free here.
Did you know that?
No, I didn't.
In fact, I've never stepped
out of my village before.
What are you doing here now?
Come here, I'll tell you.
Do you see that?
A star shining
in broad daylight.
So what?
It appeared three days ago.
It first appeared 6000 years ago.
This is the second time.
So what?
So...
What's up with you two?
Is this your sister?
Can't you see that I'm a boy?
Okay, my boy.
Well, why are you guys going to Kashi?
Do we have anywhere else to go?
Hey!
Look!
We've reached Kashi!
The last standing city in this world.
The first ever city to exist on Earth.
Wow!
When will they open that gate?
Once I have a million units,
I'll definitely get inside.
They have everything there.
They have real flowers as well.
Of course, they will.
After sucking all resources from Earth...
they obviously have everything in there.
Who's up there?
The Guardian of the Complex.
The 200 year old warden.
Supreme Yaskin.
Don't you know God is banned
in Kashi these days, you old man?
The Complex will kill
you if they hear of this.
No, sir. Please.
Why is your God seated on a dog?
What's his name?
I don't recall, sir.
But...
Everyone believes he
is the protector of Kashi.
Boys!
New merchandise.
Hold. Hold. Stop the vehicle.
Pull all the girls aside.
She's positive.
What's wrong?
Where are you taking her?
- Papa!
- Saanu...
- Let her go!
Saanu...
- Saanu...
- Papa!
She's unwell. Please let her go.
- The Complex needs your daughter.
- Papa!
Fertile girls are
worth 10,000 units.
Dad!
Please let her go!
Saanu! Saanu!
Brother...
How many units will you
give me in exchange for a girl?
Where's the girl?
Look.
She was just there.
Everyone, step out.
For tomorrow.
Rumi...
What are you doing here?
I could ask you all the same.
Mariam is so worried about you.
I need to inform her
that we found you.
Everyone at Shambala
is looking for you.
Hi, Rumi. Where have you gone?
This isn't the age
for you to risk things.
How could you just leave?
We lost so many of our
people in the Bombay War.
Your crazy beliefs have
endangered Shambala.
That crazy belief is the
foundation of Shambala, Veeran.
It's the hope for a better tomorrow.
Come back, Rumi.
The kids miss
listening to your stories.
Tell them those stories are
going to come true, Mariam.
The time mentioned in
the Puranas has come!
All the stars and planets
suggest the same.
And so do my instincts.
The Mother is coming.
Please get the woman.
What's your name?
Divya.
- What's this?
- Shambala's belief.
When darkness engulfs the world,
this will show us the way.
When the Mother who carries
God in her womb arrives,
this lights up.
What happened?
It didn't light up.
Sorry.
Carrying a life inside you
is a blessing in today's time.
But there's still time to find
the life we're searching for.
It's never going to happen.
That compass will never light up.
Nobody will believe your stories.
The truth doesn't seek validation, Veeran.
When the time comes,
you'll see for yourself...
that all these stories are true.
God will return.
Raiders!
Let's go!
Hey, careful!
Hurry up!
Careful!
Luke, faster!
Come!
They're opening the gates of the Complex.
Stop.
Come back.
Commander...
these rebels were found
because of my tip.
Can I enter the Complex?
Wow!
A fertile girl.
How did you manage
to escape for so long?
Take her to the labs.
We will extract your
womb and use it freshly.
Let her go.
Okay.
Then show me the
way to Shambala.
Here's Shambala.
Oh! Hello, Mariam.
You're still just as beautiful.
Why did you hide
and send this old man instead?
Show me the way to Shambala.
And I'll send him back.
What are the rebels fighting for anyway?
For these dogs?
They'll kill you for this bitten apple.
Are you fighting for them?
For change.
To end the people
who have turned humans into this.
For tomorrow.
Really?
If I kill today, there will
be no tomorrow, right?
Please.
She has nothing to do with us.
Then show me the way to Shambala.
Do it and I'll let her go.
Don't answer him.
They won't spare me
no matter what you say.
This baby won't
see the light of day.
And even if it did...
this isn't how the world should be.
The world needs to change.
Don't tell him.
Sorry.
Wrong answer.
Forgive me.
Your belief should come true.
You should find the
Mother you're looking for.
Such a waste!
When will you guys understand?
There are no wars left to fight.
Only the Complex remains in the world.
And there's only one God.
Supreme Yaskin.
You're right.
There's only one God.
Are you talking to me?
Darkness has engulfed from all sides.
It's now time for the light to shine.
He is coming!
Who?
Every religion...
and race...
is waiting for his arrival.
Ahura Mazda...
Rudra Chakrin...
Second Coming...
The last avatar in the Dasavataras.
He may have a million names.
But the entity is one.
He will pierce
through the darkness...
and shine light upon...
Rumi!
Catch them.
5000 units for every little rat.
Rumi.
From now on, you must tell
stories to the kids, Mariam.
So, is the tree dead?
No, my love.
It isn't dead.
It's waiting.
It's waiting for the day
that light will shine again.
Ajju, you go! I'll divert them!
Go straight! Don't look back!
Found the baby rat!
You're worth at least
5000 units, right?
One-star bounty.
You guessed it right.
5000 units.
You guys can leave now.
What is this?
These are my handcuffs.
And this is my bounty.
This is my gun.
Hey! Stop it!
Hey!
How dare you shoot me?!
My boss will come
and smash you all now.
Who's your boss?
A kickass soldier in the past wars,
who has never lost
a single fight till now.
The undefeated...
The one and only...
Bhairava!
Ah! He's back!
I wonder what
he'll do this time.
Bhairava, wake up!
I hyped you up big time.
Hey, Bujji. Please.
Five minutes.
The Great Bhairava?
We've heard crazy stories
about his fights, boss.
I've heard about him as well.
A good fighter.
But you're not loyal.
You jump ship depending
on who pays more, right?
This is our bounty.
He fell right into my lap.
That's 5000 units, Bhairava.
Guys, pay 5000 units and take him.
Defeat us and earn the units.
One, two three, four, five, six... nine.
Woah! That's too many guys!
Bujji, return the bounty.
I'm not going to wake up
and fight them for a mere 5000 units.
I was having such a nice dream.
We were inside the Complex.
The table was decked
with unlimited food, Bujji.
You were in the Complex?
But how?
Using units like everyone else.
Do you have one million units?
A few units short.
Current balance. 250 units.
Bujji, did they ask you?
Did they ask you for the details?
I have a special offer for you.
Stop us.
I'll give you
another 5000 units.
As a bonus, you can
have the old man as well.
Are you tempted now?
The total comes to 10,000 units.
It's too early in the day to fight, Bujji.
What? It will be night soon.
Okay.
You should've charged my shoes.
Your shoes.
You should charge them.
How can you be so
irresponsible, Bujji?
Okay, leave it.
Okay.
Play a nice song.
Let me get into fight mode.
Okay.
Hey...
Bujji...
Bhairava!
Go, get him!
Hey, baldie!
Hey, catch!
Hey, you frog!
Enough of this circus!
Come stand in front of me!
Got you! Got you! Got you!
Got scared?
You...
Bujji, are you okay?
Why do you care?
- Does it hurt?
- This man hit me.
And you're jumping
around like a frog.
If you really care about me, go whack him.
Bhairava, we lost our bounty.
That bounty is mine.
Catch him!
There's a staircase, brother.
Hey, hey...
What are you looking at, baldie?
Oh, the whole world is cheating
Why are their eyes fixed on us?
O my playful eyes
They don't get convinced easily
And they are stubborn
See the power of a Jatt boy
He never steps back, my love
He makes progress day and night
Move!
Thanks, boss. You're my hero.
Thanks.
Boss!
Welcome back.
O my playful eyes
They don't get convinced easily
And they are stubborn
See the power of a Jatt boy
He never steps back, my love
He makes progress day and night
See the power of a Jatt boy
He never steps back, my love
How many more to go?
I can't fight anymore.
My Complex...
Hey! Let go! I said, let go!
I want to whistle.
Please take off one handcuff.
- Please, Bujji.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Bujji.
- You're welcome.
Bujji, you see this?
I have fans as well.
Yeah, I know. Rebel fans.
O my playful eyes
See the power of a Jatt boy
-He never steps back, my love
-Thanks, boss. I'll get going.
Hey, kiddo. My units.
This is mine.
You won't get any units for this.
This is Kala Bhairava!
People believed he was the protector
of Kashi once upon a time.
You should protect Kashi now, Bhairava.
Yeah.
I got this.
- Hey!
- Protector, my foot!
Kashi will be fine only if he leaves.
- He collapsed my home.
- He was just complimenting me.
What are you doing here?
Give me some fresh news.
I'm bored to death.
What are you looking at?
A life within a life.
It's so strange, don't you think?
But it won't survive.
Sometimes I wish I was negative.
I could get out of this cage at least.
You won't get it.
You're sad that you're
not positive, right?
There's good food, sound sleep.
You never had the fortune.
Poor girl!
Everyone feels hungry.
If you can't be positive...
you got to be smart at least.
Commander Manas.
We were not expecting you.
I'll get going then.
- Call me when you're expecting me.
- I'm sorry, sir.
When will you fulfill Supreme's wish?
What's the status of Project K?
91 days.
Really?
How many days did Supreme ask for?
150 days, sir.
Have some shame!
You have such a huge lab here.
Thousands of girls at your disposal.
And these...
matching uniforms.
It's such a waste!
Can I... Can I show you something, sir?
Please come.
We're summoning all the fertile women
to the labs like you asked.
Including little girls.
The formula that Supreme has asked for,
is far beyond human DNA.
This formula is so powerful that...
it puts these girls' lives at risk.
Mother!
They can't carry this formula.
Not every girl has the
strength to grow the seed.
They turn out to be negative.
Infertile.
Whichever girl we plant
the seed in is positive.
But not beyond three months.
Supreme wants the serum.
Not your explanations.
Supreme will take my case
today because of you guys.
I'm sure 98 is better than 91.
Extract her.
We should wait a few more days.
Her vitals are not stable.
Supreme ordered to see me today.
Not in a few more days.
Extract her now. It's an order.
Sorry.
You won't get to hit a century this time.
Better luck next time.
Is she dead?
We've been trying for years now.
This experiment can never be successful.
There's only one way to do this.
If we know exactly what Supreme wants,
we will know how to proceed further.
What is Project K?
If you don't know already,
it means that...
you're not meant to know.
Do you know?
I can sacrifice my life for Supreme.
But I cannot do this blindly anymore.
I need his help.
Take me to him.
I'll ask him personally.
Alright.
Counselor Bani.
What a beautiful day, right?
Why is he here?
He's a scientist at the lab.
He has some important
doubts about Project K.
Follow me.
Hand me the serum.
I'm meeting him for the
first time in so many years.
Make sure it's not your last time.
Manas from Project K is here.
Supreme, this is the best serum
from the labs so far.
I got it extracted personally.
No one is living
beyond 100 days.
What's in this serum?
What happened?
It's been so long...
since someone tried to kill me.
I've offered many lives to death.
Death won't come near me.
I feel pity for you.
Why did you want to kill me?
For the greater good.
The greater good?
Do you know how many lives the
greater good has taken in history?
The greater good changes every
time Kings and Kingships change.
Don't be deluded by it.
What do you seek anyway?
I want to save this world.
Isn't that what I'm doing?
All those people waging wars
in the name of God and money...
I united them with just one war.
What?
Is that wrong?
Those who are responsible
for destroying nature...
have been kept away from it.
Is that wrong?
You can't do whatever you feel like.
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you guys to destroy it?
Despite the endless opportunities
spanning over generations,
man fails to redeem himself
and he never will.
It's not your fault.
Human beings were defected to begin with.
You wanted to know...
what this serum consists of, right?
It has the solution to your defect.
The solution to everything.
Don't worry.
A new yuga will rise.
Find a woman who can carry the
formula in her womb for 150 days.
How far along are you?
- Five.
- Five!
That is...
150 days!
How is this possible?
No one was able to
carry the seed beyond three months.
You've always tested negative, right?
As always, I tested negative
in the last seeding.
How is this possible then?
I have no clue.
But one day, there was movement.
What if the Complex finds out?
They will kill it.
If they find out from another source,
they will kill you as well.
- Let's go.
- No! Please!
You've crossed 150 days.
You'll be treated like a
Queen at the Complex.
If you don't tell them, I will.
I don't even remember
my mom's face.
My dad sold me to the Complex
when I was a kid.
I don't have anything in this world.
But now I have this.
That thing growing in your
womb is an experiment.
It's not a baby.
There's no need to get sentimental.
It's born to a lab experiment.
Not a father.
But it has a mother.
So, what's the plan?
How many days can you hide it?
You will be exposed soon.
No, please.
I want to keep this.
What an epic fight, Bhairava!
I've heard so many stories about you.
Is it true that you haven't
lost a single fight to date?
Bujji, I like this one.
Bhairava, please let me go.
I don't like him, Bhairava.
Don't sell me, boss.
You're my hero.
Better kill me.
Sorry, boss. I have nothing
to gain from killing you.
You just called me a hero.
I'll get you a scrumptious last meal.
Such a waste of units.
Chintu!
My best friend.
He sells the best food in Kashi.
Hey, Chints, what's today's special?
- Your death.
- Got it!
You're here for your units?
They are safe with me.
I'll return your money as
soon as I go to the Complex.
You know it!
I swear on you!
I'm 101 percent sure that
you lie 99 percent of the time.
This is what you tell everyone in Kashi.
Give me a break.
What's that?
It's fresh out of the Complex.
I want it.
Don't think so highly
of yourself, mate.
It's worth 5000 units.
Take this inside, Jhansi Rani.
Here. 5000 units.
Wow! Is this egg going to get us
inside the Complex?
It's a real egg, Bujji.
Ditch your dreams of going to the Complex.
We can earn only an egg
with these petty bounties.
If we want to go to the Complex...
we need to hit a jackpot, Bujji.
Boss, can I take a look?
No, you cannot.
We need to preserve this
in a high-security zone, Bujji.
By the way, is Bujji a nickname?
Bionic User Josen Intelligence.
I used to pilot the Complex
ships once upon a time.
Look at me now.
I pulled you out of the junkyard
and gave you a body.
Show some gratitude.
A little.
That is why my body
still resembles a junkyard.
Bhairava, why don't
you join forces with us?
Will you pay me more units?
Come on!
Everything isn't about the units.
Do it for the greater good.
Fight on the rebels' side
for a better tomorrow.
I've fought on all sides, boss.
No matter who wins...
this is how people like us end up.
I finally realized something.
There's only one side
to be on in the world.
Your own side.
Selfish side.
War took both my parents' lives.
A captain saved me.
Apparently, I didn't cry at all.
As if I was acquainted with war.
He taught me everything.
How to survive in this world.
How to fight.
And how to attain victory.
The Complex placed a bounty
on the captain for what he did.
You lost everything.
What's left to give?
Will you send him with me?
He wanted to sell me
and go to the Complex.
Bhairava!
Sorry.
But he forgot that he was the one
who taught me everything.
I'm sorry, Captain.
Before he could sell me,
I sold him out.
You're right.
This is how you're
supposed to live in this world.
Don't change.
Sorry, boss.
I didn't know you had such
a sentimental flashback.
Ask him again next week.
He'll narrate a different flashback.
Forced entry at home location.
Door broken. Three men armed.
- Come.
- Please let me go, boss.
- Move it!
- Boss, please let me go!
Did you find anything valuable?
There's nothing here.
He sold everything ages ago.
If someone were interested...
he would've sold me as well.
Who would buy you, man?
How much will your oxygen mask sell for?
Nothing. Not a single unit.
The cylinder has been
empty for a while now.
He uses it by force of habit.
Of course, it's empty.
You used it all up.
When I rented you this place...
Rent.
Wow!
What a sweet word!
Did you ever pay rent?
Ronnie, did you come all
the way for just 10,000 units?
Hold on. I just got
done with a fight.
As soon as I get the money,
you'll be the first one I'll pay.
What about me?
Hey, Leon.
Where did you come from?
I want my 20,000 units right now.
Otherwise, I'll take your car.
Please do that.
I'll kill you, old man!
What will you do with
this piece of junk, sir?
You'll get your units back.
Trust me.
I promise.
Aren't you tired of making
false promises, Bhairava?
Hey, Roxie!
He'll return my units first.
After that, I don't care if you
whack him or kill him even.
Roxie...
How many units do you want?
Tell me.
I'll take really good care of you.
Anyone else who wants to take care of me?
Bhairava, I got to go, okay? Take care.
Wait up, sir.
Collect your units.
I'll see you later.
Nice. Correct.
He deserves it.
I hope you're not hurt.
Hey, Roxie...
Roxie, I really missed you a lot.
I thought you wanted me.
But you're only after my units.
I will never have
to see your face again.
I got a job at the Complex.
Roxie, Roxie, Roxie... please.
God, take my eyesight away!
Everyday...
I keep thinking about you.
Then tell me where
we met the first time.
He's screwed!
Well, the sand, gate...
You forgot, didn't you?
How could I forget, Roxie?
It's very important.
No way I'd forget, Roxie.
- Bujji...
- Don't involve me, boss.
Roxie, Roxie, Roxie...
Are you really going
to the Complex, Roxie?
Yes.
Please take me along.
Why?
Because I like you, Roxie.
That's a lie!
You only like yourself, Bhairava.
You're the most selfish guy in the world.
Correct. Correct. Correct.
Still, take me along for a day.
Even a minute or a second would do.
I'll do anything to go to the Complex.
Okay, fine.
Tell me you love me like you mean it.
I love you.
That's the best you can do.
Hey, 9:00 a.m. East Gate.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah!
Supreme has sent orders to try again.
We're giving you another chance.
Even if one of you
turns out to be positive,
it means we're successful.
All of you will go through
seeding tomorrow.
If Supreme's mercy is upon you,
you all could be positive as well.
We need to go over there.
What about over there?
Roxie. Work permit for 70 days.
I've registered him as a temporary worker.
Bhairava. Work permit for 60 minutes.
What? Only an hour?
That's more than enough.
Three, two, one...
and lift-off.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Come. This is our floor.
This generator room is
like the sun of the Complex.
This is where all the energy is generated.
It sucks all the energy from Earth.
Bhairava, come here.
Let's get to work.
I can't waste my one hour here.
I didn't come to the
Complex for this. Let's go.
- Come on, come with me.
- No, no, no!
Trying to help you was a mistake.
You're so selfish!
I'm going to lose my job.
Hey! Hello!
What are you looking at?
Hello!
Let's go, Bhairava!
Come.
Where have the destinies brought us
It's a new journey, my friend
Looking at these sights
It feels like the stars have bloomed
Who made all these seasons
These lights and colors
Descend on the Earth
Eyes have frozen
The heavens are in front of me
This place...
This land, these paths are all mine
One day these incomplete
Desires will be fulfilled
These are the signs of time
I want to achieve this in every moment
This is my passion
My dream has come true
There is magic happening
This is my abode from now
I want to spend every moment here
This heart dances joyfully always
Now life smiles
There is no sorrow
It's a flag of happiness flying high
Counselor Bani,
we've found something unusual.
We know nothing about this material.
There's something unusual happening.
What is this?
Please.
Help.
Give it to me. It's okay.
Sorry.
This is a miracle.
Finally, we found a woman who
could carry the formula for 150 days.
The baby in her womb is growing
more rapidly than a regular one.
At this rate, she'll
deliver the baby soon.
Supreme has zero
interest in growing babies.
Prep her for extraction.
Did he shoot you?
You should have died.
Death is certain for the one who is born.
I can't understand your Hindi.
I guess it's the generation gap.
- What's your name?
- Go away!
My name is Raia.
You fought incredibly well!
Rebels will easily win the war
with a soldier like you.
In war...
only death wins.
This isn't my war.
Hello! Do you know what
the situation is like out there?
How long have you been out here?
Do you have any idea how
many people you could save?
My purpose is to save...
only one person.
Only one!
Supreme wanted a 120-day-old serum.
But what you have is even better.
I'll personally take
this serum to Supreme.
Please open this!
Please don't do this!
Oh, no!
Please, let me go!
Please!
Where did she go?
No!
That was close.
Sorry, there was no
other way to get you out.
I thought it was all over.
I was terrified that my baby would die.
You ignored the fact
that you could've died.
That's why you are special, SUM 80.
Come on. We don't have time.
I messaged my people.
They must be waiting.
Your people?
Who are you?
I'm a rebel.
From Shambala.
I was a spy at the lab for two years.
I watched many horrific
incidents and still did nothing.
I convinced myself that
I was on a different mission.
But...
after seeing you, I realized that
there can't be a bigger
mission than saving you.
Let's go.
That was embarrassing.
Don't worry, Bhairava. You didn't
have much respect to begin with.
You don't have a heart, Bujji.
Brother, give my drink back.
What kind of a drink is this?
The Complex has amazing stuff.
Tastes like nectar.
So go drink that.
Give my drink back.
- Hold on.
- Give my drink back.
You gave me liquor.
But I gave you the
chance to give me liquor.
That's how big my heart is.
What's my future, Bujji?
How long should I drink
cheap liquor with the locals?
Do you want to know your future?
Fifty.
Fifty units only.
Start talking. I'll see.
Hey, pretty parrot!
Predict Bhairava's future.
I've never seen such
a card in my entire life.
Your life is about to change.
So I'll go to the Complex. Thanks.
They're all frauds, Bhairava.
Bujji, listen.
Don't demean our culture.
There are so many things
beyond our understanding.
A big obstacle awaits you.
I don't believe in all this.
Let's go, Bujji.
Kashi has an underground tunnel network.
The Complex isn't aware of it.
If you want to leave the labs unnoticed,
this is the only way.
There it is.
My people will be
waiting at that tunnel.
There's no time, SUM 80.
Hurry up! This tunnel is your way out.
Hurry up!
Get out of here.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about me.
Good luck to both of you.
Lilly made contact for the first
time after going undercover.
So it must be something
really important.
Maybe we should go inside.
Shut up and get in the truck.
We've lost so many of us already.
We're returning to Shambala immediately.
It's a sign.
What is it?
The day River Ganga...
is devoid of a single water droplet.
What are you saying?
It's a sign.
This is my Shivamani.
It's time to find her.
Time for what?
You have been the protector
Of creation for ages
You're the assassin of sinners
The one who bestows hell upon them
Shit! The sensors got triggered.
Hey, there's somebody there.
What's with the sudden gush of wind?
You have been the protector
Of creation for ages
You're the assassin of sinners
The one who bestows hell upon them
Hey! My 50 units.
The units for my drink!
What do you guys think of me?
Do you know who you're talking to?
Do you even know who I am?
The Great Bhairava!
Where are you going? Wait up.
Who are you?
I am Guru Drona's son.
Ashwathama.
He is here.
The God of Kashi has returned.
The truth doesn't seek validation, Veeran.
When the time comes...
you'll see for yourself...
that all these stories are true.
God will return.
Something has changed, Bujji.
They're fully fried.
We didn't find the girl, sir.
Should I go look for her?
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
Nobody can find out about this.
Commander Manas.
Bani is calling you.
But, why?!
Did somebody tell him?
I don't know, sir.
Recently,
have you noticed anything
unusual in Kashi or at the labs?
What is this?
- Gaandeev.
- What's that?
A weapon created by the
Creator himself, Lord Brahma.
The man who knows how
to use this can defeat God.
Really?
Since last night,
no human or machine could
come anywhere near this.
Something is happening, Manas.
We need to be alert.
I'm sure everything
has a scientific reason.
This is beyond our
scientific knowledge, Manas.
A new power has been awakened.
You've been in the labs for so long.
The air isn't clean outside.
Put on the oxygen mask.
What happened to Lilly?
I don't know.
Why did she save you?
What do they do at the labs?
What's Project K?
How can you be so clueless?
You must know something!
Hey, slowly.
She's pregnant.
I don't remember the last time
I saw a pregnant woman.
Poor girl. Did you scare her?
How can she say
"I don't know" to everything?
Remember what Mariam used to say.
Do you think she's the
woman from her stories?
I don't know.
How can you say
"I don't know" to everything?
Here.
I'll go say hi to her.
He may come off as harsh but...
Veeran's a good man.
Are you trying to scare her?
Where are you guys taking me?
Listen, it's dangerous for you
to be out there with this belly.
So, we're going to Shambala.
You and your baby will be safe there.
Can I touch it once?
Kyra, stop!
You're creeping her out.
Sorry, I...
I mean, we grew up
listening to Mariam's stories.
She's been waiting for you forever.
For me?
Not just Mariam.
Her mother, grandmother, and everyone
else have been waiting for you.
We know everything about you.
Well, what's your name?
Please don't tell me
that you don't know.
We don't have names.
Oh, SUM80.
Hi. My name is Kyra.
My dad gave me that name.
It means "Good luck" in some language.
He died in the Complex
raid the day after I was born.
Maybe I wasn't lucky for him. Yeah.
That guy, cleaning the gun
like a psycho over there...
That's Ajju. My partner.
- Partner?
- Yeah.
By partner, I mean...
Yeah, he's mine.
Let me see a smile, Ajju.
A small one. Please.
They killed so many of us, Kyra.
As long as the Complex exists,
how can one smile?
From the inside, dude.
This is all we have. Come on, smile.
I'll smile after I kill
everyone at the Complex.
Okay?
He's such a charming fellow.
Nobody understands what
I saw in him in the first place.
We're getting married
after reaching Shambala.
I guess that makes you
the Chief Guest GU40.
GU40. G 40.
What's marriage?
Oh, right.
You're not aware of any of this.
Marriage is an old tradition.
You circle around the fire...
and promise each other
to live together forever.
And then?
And then...
That's it.
We'll live together.
We'll build a house,
have pet dogs, kids.
It sounds silly, I know.
No.
It sounds nice.
I know, right?
Everyone should have their
own person in this crazy world.
Humanity is one big family...
We should fight for the
greater good, that's all fine.
But...
You should have someone
you can call your own.
Someone's hand to hold.
Someone's shoulder to lean on.
That sense of belonging hits differently.
Smile now at least.
You're cute, G 40.
G 40...
Kyra, her name is SUM 80.
What kind of a name is SUM 80?
That's not a good name.
SUM 80.
SUM80.
Sumathi.
Sumathi?
It's a bit old-fashioned.
But it's better than SUM 80.
Don't be scared.
Raider.
Let him come. We got this.
Sometimes, you need to drop this...
and use this to win.
This is so far away from your village.
Tell me the truth.
Where are you coming from?
We came in the hopes of
finding some scrap to sell.
The competition is quite small here.
A woman has escaped from the labs.
Rebels aided her escape.
Do you know where she is?
Sir, we make a living
out of selling scrap.
We don't know anything.
Open the back.
There's nothing back there, sir.
We had a rough day, sir.
We couldn't find any scrap.
Maybe I'll find something.
I can pay you some units if you want.
I said open the back!
Okay, sir. Okay, sir.
- There's nothing here.
- I told you, sir.
Yeah, you're really trash.
Let's go.
There's nothing in there, sir.
Sir, listen to me.
- Sir...
- Wait.
Boom.
He has sent a bounty alert. Get up.
Let's give the brains a rest.
It's time to fire the guns.
Dude...
Tell me this.
The entire house is empty.
So is your car.
Why don't you sleep over there?
Why do you have to sleep here only?
My life is over there.
Hey, old man.
Guess what I'll do once
I enter the Complex.
You will do whatever the hell you want.
But you won't pay my rent.
No, listen.
Once I enter the Complex,
I'll breathe in kilos of fresh air.
- Let me...
- Hey, back off.
You took my food.
You occupied my bed.
Now you want to steal my oxygen as well?
Listen.
Let's come to an understanding.
Find a nice girl and settle down in life.
How long will you stay in my house?
Do you think I love staying with you?
One big bounty. One shot.
- I'll go to the Complex.
- And do what?
I'll live happily over there.
Happiness should come from within.
Go ahead, cough it out.
You'll only get a cough
from within if you stay here.
I can't live here anymore.
I'll leave soon.
Alert! Alert!
Five-star bounty.
Rebels on the run.
It's a jackpot, old man.
It's time to pay your rent.
A raider vehicle is
already headed this way.
I'll handle the raiders.
Here you go.
I'll go after him.
You stay here.
For tomorrow...
Hey, Sumathi. Don't worry.
Kyra means lucky, remember?
I'll be right back.
Where did she go?
Hi, guys.
Catch.
Ah, good catch!
If you don't stop that truck,
you'll be the first to die.
Veeran!
Ajju...
Sumathi, did you get scared?
Didn't I tell you that I'm lucky?
Kyra!
Ajju...
Let me see a smile, Ajju.
Kyra!
Ajju.
What's wrong?
Kyra...
Four teams in pursuit of bounty.
We're last.
Chances of bounty, 0.18 percent.
- Bujji, can you clarify a doubt for me?
- Sure.
How can you fit so much negativity
in that small brain?
Never mind. I'm getting
really good vibes today.
Who's that?
Hi, sir. I haven't seen you in a while.
What's with the shaved head?
Is everything okay?
You took the car parts
promising to work for me.
How long will you keep running from me?
It's just car parts, sir.
I'll dismantle them again.
I don't consent to that.
I'm not here for the car parts.
I'm here for you.
Damn! I'm screwed for
five years if he catches me.
Bujji, full speed.
We're at maximum speed.
Then turn on flight mode.
Bujji!
For once in life, just for today,
just be positive.
It's an order.
Flight mode on.
Hey, Bhairava!
I'll find you again.
And this time, I'll keep
you hooked for ten years.
Ten years!
Yeah, yeah, we'll see.
Always trust your boss, Bujji.
Everything will be alright.
Warning! Warning!
Flight system failure.
Bhairava! Bhairava!
Can I be negative now?
Hey, Ajju!
Ajju, come here.
- Ajju!
- The girl is in the truck.
Go get her.
Will you save her?
Who will save you?
Hi, guys.
Sorry, did I disturb you?
I suggest you drop
the guns and leave.
I'm saying it for your own good.
Should I listen to you now?
No, listen to my teacher.
She's here.
I can sense that she's here.
Hey, old man. You look like you're
retired and approaching death.
You could use some help.
Fire!
I guess your war has begun again.
War?
This isn't war to me.
It's like the worship of weapons
before going to war.
Bye!
Hi.
Is he okay?
How are you here?
Hey.
Where's the gem?
Hi.
My name is Raia.
What's your name?
Sumathi.
Don't be scared.
My teacher has got this.
Mother...
Bujji, what's happening exactly?
We're traveling upside down.
- Who's that giant man?
- Eight-foot angry giant.
He's attacking all the raiders.
He cut down my work by half.
Is the bounty there?
The bounty is in
the back of the truck.
Bujji, ask the Complex
to open their gates.
I am coming!
I'll have a real egg
at the Complex.
And crack open skulls
like they're eggshells.
I'll also swim in the sea.
Massage.
Thai...
massage.
Woah! My Complex.
Hi.
Bye.
That old man hit me so hard.
Woah! My Complex.
Where have you come from, sir?
Okay, don't tell me.
Okay.
That's enough.
Hey! Love you, Bujji!
Now Bujji is here, you old man!
Bhairava!
This old man is a tough nut!
Not again...
Statue!
150 days.
A formula we deemed impossible.
Where's the serum that
was extracted from her?
We could extract only a drop, Bani.
Please don't tell Supreme.
We almost had her.
There was an old man
who was eight feet tall.
He escaped unscathed even after
firing several rounds at him.
Did he have a gem on his forehead?
Yes.
It looked like some sort of light.
Ashwathama!
He wasn't born in this yuga.
He is immortal.
The Puranas are coming true.
Ashwathama, the pregnant woman,
and the Gaandeev.
God created this weapon
when he was on Earth.
After God left, these weapons
lost their power.
If that power has returned now,
that means...
It means that God is coming back.
He is growing inside that woman's womb.
I've heard my fair share
of these silly stories.
Some God will appear on a white horse.
Our ancestors put it quite intelligently.
The white horse refers to his birth star.
The Khadga Ashwini star,
which appears once every 6000 years.
All the planets are going
to align in a few days,
leading to a rare eclipse formation.
The darkest day in 6000 years.
If the baby isn't born before that...
the star won't appear
for another 6000 years.
We need to stop this birth at any cost.
Otherwise, it's a threat
to Supreme's life.
Where are you going?
Hello.
There's no road ahead.
We'll crash into the mountain.
Ashwa uncle, help!
Mariam, Mariam, Mariam!
- Mariam...
- Mariam, a huge...
A really huge giant.
What are you saying? Be clear.
The Mother has arrived.
What happened?
Where's Kyra?
Where's everyone else?
For tomorrow...
Hey, drop him.
Drop him!
- Hey, drop...
- Drop the gun.
Drop it!
Sir, they're one of us.
Sir... Sir...
Hey! I said drop the gun!
Drop it!
Sir.
Come.
Careful.
Veeran, who is this?
I don't know.
But...
he's definitely not our enemy.
Is she the woman who escaped from the lab?
Why did you bring her here?
A five million bounty has
been announced on her.
Thanks to the Complex,
the whole world is after her.
How will you save her?
I will save her.
Who the hell are you?
Being tall isn't enough.
Have you ever been to war?
Excuse me.
He fought a war with Sri Krishna
in the Mahabharata. Okay?
Maybe we can take her to the flux lands.
They can't track us there.
The Nomens will eat her.
Veeran, I want her
out of here this instant.
She will not be going anywhere.
You arrived before my hope could falter.
The Mother has arrived.
She came to her maternal home...
to give birth to God.
Tell Shambala the Mother has arrived.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Has everybody gone crazy?
Do you realize that her mere
presence has put us all in danger?
She's an ordinary pregnant woman
who escaped from the lab.
There's nothing special about her.
Moreover...
how can you claim that this unborn child
is our next God?
Rain?
When was the last time it rained?
For tomorrow.
Ashwa uncle, I can't see anything.
Listen, dear.
Shambala has waited a long time for you.
We're ready to do anything for you.
Tell us, Mother.
What do you want?
I'm hungry.
This tree is like a temple to us.
It's clean water.
You can drink it.
Here you go.
How is all of this here?
The compass that found you was from here.
That's the point this tree grew from.
And that's how Shambala
came to life around this tree.
Just when we were concerned
about losing that life energy,
you showed up.
Shambala's belief came true.
Hereafter, everything will be fine.
Where's the old man?
He's the guy who hit us.
She escaped because of him.
Bhairava, you're blacklisted.
We're seizing all your units.
You're permanently
banned from the Complex.
What's wrong?
I lost.
What? You lost?
Impossible!
I don't believe you.
Go.
What?
Are you letting me go?
When did you become such a saint?
He's a good guy, sir.
Bujji, give him those 500 units.
He'll grab a bite.
Are you going to pay my rent as well?
If so, please inform me in advance.
I don't want a shock.
I'll do some work
and pay your rent, old man.
I fought a great deal to go to
the Complex all these years.
It's all over now.
I finally gained a sense of clarity.
This is my life right here.
I don't have anybody.
Nobody needs me.
We need you, Bhairava.
You shouldn't stay back here.
Come with me to Shambala.
Shambala...
You go.
Who would take me inside anyway?
Hey, I'll talk to them.
You're a hero to so many others like me.
Come be on our side, Bhairava.
Don't hesitate. Let's go.
Damn, those rebels!
They must've taken her to Shambala.
I want that woman!
We've sent raiders in
every direction, Commander.
We'll catch her.
You can't do shit.
You can't do shit as long
as that old man is with her.
Old man?
He's the one who thrashed your men.
Nobody could lay their hand on him.
Except for me.
Who is this guy?
He's Bhairava, sir.
A bounty hunter.
He hit our raiders.
I blacklisted him.
Now that you've blacklisted me anyway,
let me hit again.
The point is, only I can bring her back.
You have no other option.
How can you be so sure?
Check my records.
I haven't lost a single fight till now.
I won't lose this one either.
Alright.
I'll give you one chance.
If you bring her back,
I'll personally hold your hand
and take you inside the Complex.
This light doesn't come
To cross over the darkness
MOTHER
Where everything is barren
May there be a drop in the cloud
The morning sun
Is colored with the blood of the night
This storm is the flight of tomorrow
This is the proclamation...
Be victorious
Give her some space.
Let's throw this cane away now.
We'll get you a kickass
weapon in Shambala.
This isn't an ordinary cane.
It's a weapon from an ancient war.
So, tell me.
What was your war like?
Was it more depressing
than the current wars?
Were there a lot of casualties?
Anyway, I'm sure you
were the best fighter.
No one can beat you.
No, I lost.
Really?
Who defeated you?
The Master of the Gaandeev.
Kunthi's son.
Arjuna.
Ashwathama!
This is the Gaandeev made
by the Creator, Brahma.
Nobody can fight it.
Oh, so Arjuna was the best?
Right?
No.
There was another warrior.
More powerful than Arjuna?
Yes.
He was my friend.
What happened to him?
Karn.
He met with a miserable death.
A warrior like him didn't deserve it.
This weapon belonged to him.
It's more powerful than...
Arjuna's Gaandeev.
Wow!
Then why don't you use it?
It works only in his hands.
Without him...
this weapon is powerless.
Right now, this is as good
as an old man's walking stick.
Your current balance is zero.
You've exhausted
all your units on me, Bhairava.
Bhairava, are you sure?
There's no going back.
Where do you think you're going?
I'll follow you wherever you go, Mother.
Why is everyone calling me Mother?
They say that...
the entire universe resides within God.
But that God resides within you.
What else can we call you if not Mother?
As you please.
But first, I need to get out of here.
The outside is a threat, Mother.
To who?
In fact, I'm a threat to everyone.
People around me end up dying.
I won't die.
The gun was in my hand.
Kyra would've been
alive if I had fired it.
You were born to bring another life into
this world. Not cause someone's death.
Are you listening to yourself?
How can a baby that hasn't
taken its first breath
be responsible for so many
people breathing their last?
Every death has a higher purpose.
This baby will give life to the world.
But why me?
God gives his biggest responsibilities...
to the ones who can fulfill them.
You're carrying God...
in your womb.
Only Mother Earth possesses
that kind of power.
Do you even realize that...
what you're carrying
is not an ordinary life?
Birthing it is your duty.
Protecting you is my responsibility.
Are you sure?
Do you remember the way?
I was born there, Bhairava.
Of course, I remember.
We're almost there.
Bhairava, go straight at full speed.
There's nothing ahead, Bhairava.
All I see is a mountain on my sensors.
Trust me, Bhairava. Let's go.
It's dangerous to be out here for long.
If we crash ahead,
even our parts won't be found.
Let's go back.
No more going back.
Welcome to Shambala.
Luke, is that you?
And who's this?
Relax, guys!
He's Bhairava.
He's a great fighter.
He's on our side now.
Does Veeran know?
I'm taking him to Veeran now.
Okay. Follow me.
What about me?
I'll finish the formalities
and be right back.
Take care of the car.
I fixed it just a while ago.
That's one massive set-up
centered in the mountains.
And the Complex has no idea
that you guys are doing so well.
Come here.
How's everyone?
It rained.
What? Are you serious?
As Mariam said, the Mother has arrived.
Where is she?
She's at the tree.
It rained, the Mother arrived,
and now you're here as well.
You see, Bhairava?
Sorry, kid.
We need to go.
It's dangerous to be here.
I came prepared this time, old man.
Fire!
Hello, Shambala!
I caught you!
Veeran...
Come.
Get out of the way, old man.
There's no time.
Bujji!
Yes! I won!
Oh, no! Force field?
What do we do now?
Go, get her.
Sirius, are you ready?
For tomorrow.
The darkness that we've
been fighting this whole time...
now stands at our doorstep.
What should we do?
Should we run away?
- Or should we fight?
- Let's fight!
- For tomorrow!
Mom...
For tomorrow.
Come on.
We need to get out of here.
Hurry up. There's no time.
Help! Help!
- Help!
- Many people have been left behind.
Our people will
take care of them. Let's go.
Go inside.
What about you, Mariam?
Go. That's an order.
Andrew!
Roger that, Mariam.
All systems check.
What are you doing?
Why did you get down?
Garud One.
Land right now.
I want to kill you right here, right now.
But Supreme insisted...
that he kill you and your
baby with his own hands.
You called the baby God, right?
Is there nobody else to save her?
Oh warrior!
Blow him to hell.
Did I take too long,
Son of Acharya?
Oh warrior!
Brave fighter, come forth!
Bhairava!
Hey! You're the woman from the lab.
Bujji, the old man is trapped.
Let's run away, Bujji.
Please don't take me inside the Complex.
First, let's get out of here, Bhairava.
Brother!
Bujji, the old man is coming back.
Full throttle!
Bhairava, let's go.
Hold up, my friend.
Listen to me!
Don't do it, Bhairava.
Who knows where we'll land?
Who's that?
Ashwathama,
this is the Gaandeev created
by the Creator, Brahma.
Nobody can fight it.
Did I take too long,
Son of Acharya?
No.
You came at the right time, my friend.
You see that, Keshava?
How can he be my equal?
He could push our chariot back
by only two feet,
but my weapon pushed
his chariot back by ten feet.
Listen, Dhanunjaya!
Your chariot is a blessing
from the God of Fire.
Guarding it is Lord Hanuman,
as symbolized on the flag.
You are the son of
Anjani Devi and Lord Pavana
Riding it is me,
the Master of all three worlds.
He still managed to
push it back by two feet.
Think about it, Arjuna.
The one standing in front of you
is not an ordinary warrior.
I see the radiance
of the sun in his eyes.
In his hand is the Vijaya Bow.
History will not forget his name.
The Descendant of the Sun.
Karn!
Oh warrior!
Brave fighter, come forth!
A mistake has been made, Supreme.
The woman who carried
the formula for 150 days
has escaped from the labs.
This is what they extracted from her.
Just one drop of the serum.
Something is happening.
The Gaandeev that nobody can touch...
The immortal Ashwathama...
A force beyond everyone's understanding.
Some...
new power.
If a single drop
encompasses such power...
I completely understand now, Supreme.
I'll get that woman back.
No.
I'll go get her myself.
Jagannatha's chariot wheels
will turn back once more...
It will bring destruction
with every turn it takes.
Born of the womb of Mother Earth...
One yuga will end, and another will arise.