Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Ashwathama is dead.
Ashwathama.
Salutations to the Creator, Brahma
The utterance of whose name...
grants his instantaneous presence.
Upon whose arrival,
all the enemies bite the dust.
The end of the Pandavas!
Even though Abhimanyu isn't here,
you're carrying the last heir
of the Pandavas in your womb.
If you're here to kill
me, go ahead, Krishna.
I'm not Arjuna to listen to your teachings.
Of the sins committed in
these 18 days of Kurukshetra,
your unrighteousness is the worst.
How could you stoop so low,
being the son of Dronacharya?
You have no right to utter
my father's name, Krishna.
You could've stopped
his death if you wanted to.
♪ To suppress injustice♪
♪ There rises a warrior in every Yuga ♪
♪ He manifests as different entities♪
♪ He is en embodiment of Lord Vishnu ♪
♪ To protect and uphold righteousness♪
♪ To cleanse the Universe of evil♪
Ashwathama...
Be it God or Drona,
nobody can escape karma.
You shot an arrow at an unborn baby.
You must face the
consequences of your karma.
Alright then. Spin your chakra
and kill me as a punishment.
Death isn't your punishment, Ashwathama.
It's your salvation.
Over time, all the
Pandavas will be deceased.
My body will perish.
This Yuga will reach an end.
But you won't face death.
Your wounds won't heal
for thousands of years.
You will neither die nor live.
You'll suffer alone, bearing
witness to many sins.
I curse you as such!
Is there no atonement for me?
You wanted to kill me now.
But one day, you'll have to save me.
Me?
Kaliyugam is coming.
Kali is coming.
When unrighteousness increases...
and darkness engulfs the world,
I must reincarnate again.
Kali is going to be so
powerful in that Yuga that...
he can cause hindrance to my birth.
That's when you must
safeguard my birth haven.
When the Sun disappears from the sky,
When the air is filled with toxins,
When River Ganga is
devoid of its last drop,
When this gem finds its way back to you,
remember the time has come.
Until then...
♪ Isn't a path of darkness enough?♪
♪ For righteousness to walk on♪
♪ O' Madhava, why won't you show up?♪
♪ Maybe you've forgotten your promise♪
♪ Earth shatters, making Nature ferocious♪
♪ The world has turned into hell♪
♪ History has collapsed;
Morals have no place here♪
♪ Time holds no significance♪
♪ This is the age of Kali♪
♪ It's time this curse be lifted♪
♪ A sinful world comes to light♪
♪ Isn't this enough bloodshed?♪
♪ O' Madhava...♪
♪ Why won't you show up?♪
What's this?
No idea.
Brother, do you have some water?
Ma'am, some water, please?
Have you dried out from washing
away all our sins, Gangamma?
Where did you come from?
Nobody gives water for free here.
Did you know that?
No, I didn't.
In fact, I've never stepped
out of my town before.
What are you doing here now?
Come here.
Do you see that?
A star shining in broad daylight.
So what?
It appeared only 3 days ago.
It first appeared 6000 years ago.
This is only the second time.
So what?
So...
What's up with you two?
Is this your sister?
Can't you see that I'm a boy?
Okay, my boy.
Well, why are you guys going to Kashi?
Do we have anywhere else to go?
Hey!
Look!
We've reached Kashi!
The last standing city in this world.
The first ever city to exist on Earth.
Wow!
When will they open that gate?
When you have a million units.
I'll definitely get inside someday.
They have everything there.
They even have flowers.
I'm sure.
When you suck all the resources from Earth,
you obviously have everything in there.
Who's up there?
The Leader of the Complex.
The 200 year old warden.
Supreme Yaskin.
Don't you know God is
banned in Kashi, you old man?
The Complex will kill
you if they hear of this.
No, sir. Please.
Tell me this. Why is your
God seated on a dog?
What's his name?
I don't recall, sir.
But...
Everyone believes he is
the protector of Kashi.
Boys!
The new stuff is here.
Hold. Hold. Stop the vehicle.
Pull all the girls aside.
She's positive.
What's wrong?
Where are you taking her?
-Saanu...
-Dad!
Saanu... Saanu...
Where are you taking her?
She's unwell.
The Complex needs your daughter.
Fertile girls are worth 10,000 units.
Dad!
Please let her go!
Saanu! Saanu!
Brother...
How many units will you
give me in exchange for a girl?
Where's the girl?
Look.
She was just there.
Everyone, step out.
For tomorrow.
Rumi...
What are you doing here?
All of us are here on the same mission.
Mariam is so worried about you.
I need to inform her that we found you.
Everyone at Shambala is looking for you.
Hi, Rumi. Where have you gone?
This isn't the age for you to risk things.
How could you just leave?
We lost so many of our
people in the Bombay war.
You can't endanger Shambala
based on your crazy beliefs.
That crazy belief is the
foundation of Shambala, Veeran.
It's the hope for a better tomorrow.
Come back, Rumi.
The kids miss listening to your stories.
Tell them those stories are
going to come true, Mariam.
The time mentioned in
the puranas has come!
All the stars and planets suggest the same.
And so do my instincts.
The Mother is coming.
Please get the woman.
What's your name, love?
Divya.
-What's this?
-Shambala's belief.
When darkness engulfs the world,
this will show us the way.
When the Prophetic Mother who carries
God in her womb arrives,
this lights up.
What happened?
It didn't light up.
Sorry.
Carrying a life inside you
is a blessing in today's time.
But there's still time to find
the life we're searching for.
It's never going to happen.
That compass will never light up.
Nobody will believe your stories.
The truth doesn't seek validation, Veeran.
When the time comes,
you'll see it for yourself.
That all these stories are true.
That God is returning.
Raiders! Let's go!
Hey, careful!
Hurry up!
Luke, faster!
Come!
They're opening the Complex gates.
Stop.
Come back.
Commander,
these Rebels were found because of my tip.
Can I enter the complex?
Wow!
A fertile girl.
How did you manage to escape for so long?
Take her to the labs.
We will extract your
womb and use it freshly.
Don't do it!
Then show me the way to Shambala.
Here's Shambala.
Oh! Hello, Mariam.
You're still just as beautiful.
Why did you hide and
send this old man instead?
Show me the way to Shambala.
And I'll send him back.
What are the Rebels fighting for anyway?
For these dogs?
They'll kill you for this bitten apple.
What are you doing this for, huh?
For change.
And to end you for
turning humans like this.
For tomorrow.
If today ceases to exist,
there will be no tomorrow, right?
Please.
She has nothing to do with us.
Then show me the way to Shambala.
Do it and I'll let her go.
Don't answer him.
They won't spare me no matter what you say.
This baby won't see the light of day.
If you want another baby to be born,
this isn't how the world should be.
The world needs to change.
Don't tell him.
Sorry.
Wrong answer.
Forgive me, love.
Your belief should come true.
You should find the
Mother you're looking for.
Such a waste!
When will you guys understand?
All the wars have come to an end.
Only the Complex remains in the world.
And there's only one God.
Supreme Yaskin.
You're right.
There's only one God.
Are you talking to me?
Darker has engulfed from all the sides.
It's now time for the light to shine.
He is coming!
Who?
Every religion...
and race...
is waiting for his arrival.
Ahura Mazda,
Rudra Chakrin,
Second Coming,
The last avatar in the Dasavataras,
He may have a million names.
But the calling is one.
He will pierce through the darkness...
and shine light upon...
Rumi!
Catch them.
5000 units for every little rat.
Rumi.
From now on, you must tell
stories to the kids, Mariam.
So, is the tree dead?
No, my love.
It isn't dead.
It's waiting.
It's waiting for the day
light will shine again.
Ajju, go! I'll handle them.
Go straight. Don't look back.
Found the baby rat!
You're worth at least 5000 units, right?
One-star bounty.
You guessed it right.
5000 units.
You guys can leave. Bye.
What is this?
These are my handcuffs.
And this is my bounty.
This is my gun.
Hey! Stop it!
How dare you shoot me!
My boss will come and smash you all now.
Oooh! Who's your boss?
A kickass soldier in the past wars,
who has never lost a single fight till now,
The Undefeated,
The One and Only,
Bhairava!
Ah! He's back!
I wonder what he'll do this time.
Bhairava, wake up!
I hyped you up big time. Wake up!
Hey, Bujji. Please. 5 minutes.
The Great Bhairava?
Yeah.
We've heard crazy stories
about your fights, boss.
I've heard about you too.
A good fighter.
But you're not loyal.
You jump ship depending
on who pays more, is it?
This is our bounty.
He fell right into my lap.
That's 5000 units.
Guys, pay 5000 units and take him.
Defeat us and earn the units.
1..2..3..4..5..6..
9!
Woah! That's too many guys!
Bujji, return the bounty.
I can't wake up and fight
for those 5000 units now.
I was having such a nice dream.
We were inside the complex.
The table was decked
with unlimited food, Bujji.
You were in the complex? But how?
Using units like everyone else.
Do you have one million units?
A few units short.
Current balance. 250 units.
Bujji, did they ask you?
Did they ask you for the details?
I have a special offer for you.
Stop us.
I'll give you another 5000 units.
As a bonus, you can
have the old man as well.
Are you tempted now? 10,000 units in total.
It's too early in the day to fight, Bujji.
What? It will be night in some time.
Okay.
You were supposed to charge my shoes.
Your shoes. You only put them on charge.
How can you be so irresponsible, Bujji?
Okay, leave it.
Okay.
Play a nice song.
Let me get into fight mode.
Yes, boss.
Hey...
Bujji...
Bhairava!
Go get him!
Hey, baldie!
Hey, catch!
Hey, Kappa ! Enough of this circus!
Come stand in front of me!
Got you! Got you! Got you!
Hey, furry! Got scared?
You...
Bujji, are you okay?
Why do you care?
Does it hurt?
This furry man hit me.
And you're jumping around like a frog.
If you really care about me, go whack him.
Bhairava, we lost our bounty.
That bounty is mine.
Catch him!
There's a staircase, brother.
Hey, hey! Stop!
What are you watching, baldie?
♪ This world is a deceitful place ♪
♪ Why are all the eyes on me? ♪
♪ My mischievous eyes ♪
♪ Don't listen ♪
♪ They are very stubborn ♪
♪ Look at the pride of the warrior ♪
♪ He never steps back ♪
♪ Day and night making progress ♪
Thanks, boss. You're my hero.
Thanks.
Boss!
Welcome back.
♪ My mischievous eyes ♪
♪ Don't listen ♪
♪ They are very stubborn ♪
♪ Look at the pride of the warrior ♪
♪ He never steps back ♪
♪ Day and night making progress ♪
♪ Look at the pride of the warrior ♪
♪ He never steps back ♪
How many more to go?
I can't fight anymore.
My Complex...
Hey!
Let go!
Come here.
Bujji, I want to whistle.
Please take off one handcuff.
-Please, Bujji.
-Okay.
-Thanks, Bujji.
-You're welcome.
Bujji, you see this?
I have fans too.
Yeah, I know. Rebel Fans.
♪ My mischievous eyes ♪
♪ Look at the pride of the warrior ♪
♪ He never steps back ♪
Thanks, boss. I'll get going.
Hey, kiddo. My units.
This is mine.
You won't get any units for this. Take it.
This is Kaala Bhairava!
People believed he was the
protector of Kashi once upon a time.
You should protect Kashi now, Bhairava.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Protector, my foot!
Kashi will be fine only if he leaves.
-He ate my paan.
-He was just complimenting me.
What are you doing here?
Give me some fresh news.
I'm bored to death.
Why are you looking at me like that?
A life within a life.
It's so strange,
don't you think?
But it won't survive.
Sometimes I wish I was negative.
I could get out of this cage at least.
You won't get it.
You're sad that you're not positive, huh?
You got to do nothing.
There's good food.
They treat you like a Queen.
You never had the fortune, I heard.
Poor girl!
Everyone feels hungry.
If you can't be positive,
you got to be smart at least.
Commander Manas.
We were not expecting you.
Is it?
Call me when you're expecting me.
I'll come back.
I didn't mean that, sir.
Supreme wants to know
the status of Project K.
91 days.
How many days did Supreme ask for?
150 days, sir.
Have some shame!
You have such a huge lab here.
Thousands of girls at your disposal.
And these... matching uniforms.
It's such a waste!
Can I... Can I show you something, sir?
Please come.
We're summoning all the fertile
women to the labs like you asked.
Including little girls.
The formula Supreme prepared
is far beyond human DNA.
This formula is so powerful that...
it puts these girls' lives at risk.
None of the women are
able to carry this formula.
Supreme wants the serum.
Not your explanations.
You said there's a 91 days pregnant woman.
Extract her.
We should wait a few more days.
Her vitals are not stable.
Supreme ordered to see me today.
Not in a few more days.
Extract her. That's an order.
Sorry.
You couldn't hit the century this time.
Better luck next time.
Is she dead?
We've been trying for a few years now.
This experiment can never be successful.
There's only one way to do this.
If we know what Supreme exactly wants,
we will know how to proceed further.
What is Project K?
If you don't know already,
it means you're not meant to know.
Do you know?
I can sacrifice my life for Supreme.
But I cannot do this blindly anymore.
I need his help.
Take me to him. I'll ask him personally.
Alright.
Counselor Bani.
What a beautiful day, isn't it?
Why is he here?
He's a scientist at the labs.
He has some important
doubts about Project K.
Follow me.
Hand me the serum.
I'm meeting him for the
first time in so many years.
Make sure it's not your last time.
Manas from Project K is here.
Supreme, this is the best
serum from the labs so far.
I got it extracted personally.
No one is living beyond 100 days.
What's in this serum?
What happened?
It's been so many days...
since someone tried to kill me.
I've offered many lives to death.
Death won't come near me.
I feel pity for you.
Why did you want to kill me?
For the greater good.
The greater good?
Do you know how many lives the
greater good has taken in history?
The greater good changes every
time Kings and King-ships change.
Don't be deluded by it.
What do you seek anyway?
I want to save this world.
Isn't that what I'm doing?
All those people waging wars
in the name of God and money...
I united them with just one war.
Is that wrong?
Since you're destroying
nature down to dust,
I kept it out of your reach.
Is that wrong?
You can't do whatever you feel like.
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are you guys to destroy it?
Despite the endless opportunities
spanning over generations,
man fails to redeem
himself and he never will.
It's not your fault.
Human beings are defected to begin with.
You wanted to know...
what this serum consists of, right?
It has the solution to your defect.
The solution to everything.
Don't worry.
A new world will rise.
Find a woman who can carry the
formula in her womb for 150 days.
Hey.
Which month?
Five.
Five!
That is...
150 days!
How is this possible?
No one was able to carry beyond 3 months.
You were never positive before, were you?
As always, I got negative
in the last seeding.
How is this possible then?
I have no clue.
But one day,
there was movement.
What if the Complex finds out?
They will kill it.
If they find out from another
source, they will kill you as well.
-Let's go.
-No!
You've crossed 120 days.
You'll be treated like a
Queen at the Complex.
If you don't tell them, I will.
I don't even remember my mom's face.
My dad sold me to the
Complex when I was a kid.
I don't have anything in this world.
But this.
It's not a life that's
growing in your womb.
It's an experiment.
There's no need to get sentimental.
It's born to a lab experiment.
Not a father.
But it will be born to a mother.
So, what's the plan?
How many days can you hide it?
You will be exposed soon.
Please.
I want to...
keep this.
What an epic fight, Bhairava!
We share so many stories about you.
Didn't you lose a single
fight till now? Really?
Bujji, I like this one.
Bhairava, please let me go.
I don't like him, Bhairava.
You can't sell me, boss. You're my hero.
Better kill me.
Sorry, boss. I'll get only
half the units if I kill you.
You just called me a hero.
I'll get you a scrumptious last meal.
No need. It's a waste of units.
Chintu!
My best friend.
He sells the best food in Kashi.
Hey, Chintu. What's today's special?
-Your death.
-Shut up!
You're here for your units?
They are safe with me.
I'll return your money as
soon as I go to the Complex.
You know it!
I swear on you!
I'm 101% sure that you lie 99% of the time.
This is what you tell everyone
in Kashi. Give me a break.
What's that?
It's fresh out of the Complex.
I want it.
Don't think so highly of yourself, mate.
It's worth 5000 units.
Take this inside, Subbalakshmi.
Here. 5000 units.
Wow! You fought so
hard and bought an egg?
It's a real egg, Bujji.
Whatever.
Now forget about going to the Complex.
We can earn only an egg
with these petty bounties.
If we want to go to the Complex,
we need to hit a jackpot, Bujji.
Boss, can I take a look?
No, you cannot.
We need to preserve this
in a high security zone, Bujji.
By the way, what's with the name Bujji?
Is it a nickname?
Bionic User Josen Intelligence.
I used to pilot the Complex
ships once upon a time.
Look at me now.
I pulled you out of the
junkyard and gave you a body.
Show some gratitude.
A little.
We don't need gratitude, Bhairava.
We need units.
Bhairava, why don't
you join forces with us?
Will you pay me more units?
Come on! Everything isn't about the units.
Do it for the greater good.
Fight on our side for a better tomorrow.
I've fought on all sides, boss.
No matter who wins,
this is how people like us end up.
I finally realized something.
There's only one side
to be on in the world.
Your own side.
Selfish side.
I was orphaned at a war.
A pilot saved me.
Apparently, I didn't cry a bit.
As if I was acquainted with war.
The pilot taught me everything.
How to survive in this world.
How to fight.
Everything.
The Complex announced a
bounty on him due to his actions.
You lost everything. What's left to give?
Will you send him with me?
He thought of selling me
and entering the Complex.
Bhairava!
Sorry.
But he forgot that I
was his student after all.
I'm sorry, Captain.
I helped capture him
before he could sell me.
You're right.
This is how you're
supposed to live in this world.
Don't change.
Sorry, boss.
I didn't know you had such
a sentimental flashback.
Ask him again next week.
He'll narrate a different flashback.
Alert! Alert!
Forced entry at home location.
Door broken. Three armed men.
Come.
Please let me go, boss.
Boss, please!
What do you hope to find, guys?
There's nothing here.
He sold everything ages ago.
If someone were interested,
he would've sold me as well long back.
Who would buy you, man?
How much will your
oxygen cylinder sell for?
Nothing at all.
Not a single unit.
It's been empty for a while now.
He uses it by force of habit.
Of course, it's empty. You used it all up.
When I rented you this place,
Rent.
Wow!
What a sweet word!
Did you ever pay rent?
Hi, Ronnie. Did you come
so far for just 10,000 units?
Hold on. I just got done with a fight.
I'll pay you first as
soon as I get the money.
What about me?
Hey, Leon.
Where did you come from?
I want my 20,000 units right now.
Otherwise, I'll take your car.
Please do that.
I'll kill you, old man!
What will you do with
this piece of junk, sir?
Your units are completely safe with me.
I'll pay you back.
I promise.
What's the value of your promise, Bhairava?
Hey, Roxie!
He'll return my units first.
After that, I don't care if you
whack him or kill him even.
Roxie...
How many units do you want? Tell me.
Let me take you home.
What?
Will you take me home too?
Bhairava, I got to go, okay?
Wait up, sir. Collect your units.
It's okay. I'll see you later.
Nice. Correct.
He deserves it.
I hope you're not hurt.
Hey, Roxie...
Roxie, I really missed you.
I thought you wanted me.
But you're only after my units.
I would never have to see your face again.
I got a job at the Complex.
Roxie, Roxie, Roxie... Please.
God, take my eyesight away!
Everyday...
I keep thinking about you.
Then tell me where we met the first time.
He's screwed!
Well, the sand bike...
You forgot, didn't you?
How could I forget, Roxie?
It's very important.
No way I'd forget, Roxie.
-Bujji...
-Hello. Don't involve me.
Don't you want kids, Roxie?
Are you really going to the Complex?
Yeah.
-Please take me along.
-Why?
Because I like you, Roxie.
That's a lie!
You like only yourself, Bhairava.
You're the most selfish guy in the world.
Correct. Correct. Correct.
Still, take me along for a day.
Even a minute or second would do.
Take me to the Complex
and I'll do anything you want.
Okay, fine.
Tell me you love me like you mean it.
I love you.
You can't do any better than that.
Hey... 9 AM, East Gate.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah!
Supreme has sent orders to try again.
We're giving you another chance.
Even if one of you
turns out to be positive,
it means we're successful.
All of you will go through
seeding tomorrow.
If Supreme's mercy is upon you,
you all could be positive too.
Good luck.
Hey, it's this way.
Not this way?
Roxie. Work permit for 70 days.
He's the temporary
worker that I registered.
Bhairava. Work permit for 60 minutes.
What? Only an hour?
Be grateful. Now let's go.
Thank you. Thank you.
Come. This is our floor.
This generator room is
like the Sun of the Complex.
This is where all the energy is generated.
It sucks all the energy from the Earth.
Bhairava, let's go.
We got a lot of work to do.
I can't waste my one hour here.
I didn't come to the
Complex for this. Let's go.
But, no, no, no!
It's my fault that I helped you.
How selfish!
I'm going to lose my job.
Hey, hello.
What are you looking at?
Hello!
Very pretty.
Let's go, Bhairava.
Come.
♪ This is beautiful beyond
this Creations' understanding ♪
♪ I sway between the Sky
and the Earth in exhilaration ♪
♪ I wonder how so many
mysteries have gathered here ♪
♪ Paradise paves welcome
as I set foot on this land ♪
♪ A gentle breeze of Royal
treatment caresses my cheek ♪
♪ The Five Elements
greet me like a friend ♪
♪ My dream of a lifetime
is finally come true ♪
♪ Is this really happening to me? ♪
♪ My quench for joy stays unfulfilled ♪
♪ These breathtaking visuals of serenity ♪
♪ Stand in front of me today ♪
♪ This is going to be my world
for thousands of years to come ♪
Counsellor Bani, we've found
nothing of this kind before.
Despite our team's relentless efforts,
we're unable to identify the material.
What's happening?
What?
Please.
Help.
Give it to me. It's okay.
Sorry.
Let me go! Let me go!
This is a miracle.
Finally, we found a woman who
can carry the formula for 150 days.
The baby in her womb is
growing rapidly than a regular one.
At this rate, she'll deliver the baby soon.
Supreme has zero
interest in growing babies.
Prep her for extraction.
They shot you, didn't they?
You were supposed to die.
Death is certain for the one who is born.
Though you're speaking in
Telugu, I don't understand it.
I guess it's the generation gap.
-What's your name?
-Go away!
My name is Raia.
I've never seen a human being like you.
You fought incredibly well!
Rebels will easily win the
war with a soldier like you.
In war,
only death wins.
This isn't my war.
Hello! How long have you been out?
Do you know what the situation is like?
Do you have any idea how
many people you could save?
My purpose is to save...
only one person.
Only one!
Supreme wanted a 120 days old serum.
But you are...
I'll take this serum to Supreme personally.
Please let me go!
Please don't hurt me.
Please stop!
Where did she go?
That was close.
Sorry, there was no
other way to get you out.
I thought it was all over.
I was terrified that my baby would die.
You ignored the fact
that you could've died.
That's what makes you special, M 80.
I messaged my people. They must be waiting.
Your people?
Who are you?
I'm a Rebel.
From Shambala.
I was a spy at the lab for 2 years.
I watched many horrific
incidents and still did nothing.
I convinced myself that
I'm on a different mission.
But...
after seeing you,
there was no bigger
mission than saving you.
Let's go.
Geez!
That was embarrassing.
Don't worry, Bhairava. You don't
have much respect to begin with.
You don't have a heart, Bujji.
Brother, give my drink back.
What kind of a drink is this?
The Complex has amazing stuff.
Tastes like nectar.
Have that and give my drink back.
-Hold on.
-Give my drink back.
You gave me liquor.
But I gave you the
chance to give me liquor.
That's how big my heart is.
What's my future, Bujji?
How long should I drink
cheap liquor with the locals?
Do you want to know your future?
Fifty.
Fifty units only.
Start talking. I'll see.
Hey, pretty parrot!
Predict Bhairava's future.
I've never seen such
a card in my entire life.
Your life is about to change.
So I'll go to the Complex. Thanks.
They're all frauds,
Bhairava. Don't believe them.
Bujji, listen.
Don't demean our culture.
There are so many things
beyond our understanding.
A big obstacle awaits you.
I don't believe in all this.
Let's go, Bujji.
Kashi has an underground tunnel network.
The Complex isn't aware of it.
If you want to leave the labs unnoticed,
this is the only way.
There it is.
My people will be waiting at that tunnel.
There's no time, M 80.
Hurry up! This tunnel is your way out.
Hurry up!
What are you looking at? Go!
-What about you?
-I'll be fine.
Hey.
Good luck to the both of you.
Lilly contacted for the first
time after going undercover.
So it must be something really important.
Maybe we should go inside.
Come.
Shut up and get in the truck, you two.
We've lost so many of us already.
We're returning to Shambala immediately.
Do you hear that?
Err...
No.
What is it?
The day River Ganga...
is devoid of its last drop.
What are you talking about?
When this gem...
...reaches its way back to you,
It's time.
Time for what?
♪ To suppress injustice♪
♪ There rises a warrior in every Yuga♪
♪ He manifests as different entities♪
♪ He is en embodiment of Lord Vishnu♪
Shit! The sensors got triggered.
Hey, there's somebody there.
What's with the sudden gush of wind?
♪ He manifests as a fish♪
♪ And then a turtle♪
♪ Sometimes an Indian Boar♪
♪ To protect us all♪
Hey! My 50 units.
My drink's units.
What do you guys think of me, huh?
Do you know who you're
demanding money from?
Do you even know who I am?
The Great Bhairava!
Where are you going? Wait up.
Who are you?
I am Dronacharya's son.
My name is Ashwathama.
He has returned.
God has returned to Kashi.
♪ To protect and uphold righteousness♪
♪ To cleanse the Universe of evil♪
♪ His avatar has appeared on the Earth♪
The truth doesn't seek your validation.
When the time comes,
You'll see for yourself...
that all these stories are true.
And that God will return.
Something has changed, Bujji.
They're fully fried.
We didn't find the girl, sir.
Should I go look for her?
Go!
Nobody can find out about this.
Commander Manas.
Bani is calling you.
Why?
Did he find out?
I don't know, sir.
Recently,
did you notice anything
unusual in Kashi or at the labs?
What is this?
-Gaandeevam.
-What's that?
A weapon created by the
Creator himself, Lord Brahma.
The man who knows how
to use this can defeat God.
Really?
Since last night,
no human or machine could
come anywhere near this.
Something is happening, Manas.
We need to be alert.
I'm sure everything
has a scientific reason.
This is beyond our
scientific knowledge, Manas.
A new power has been awakened.
You've been at the lab for so long.
This is how the outside air is.
Put on the oxygen mask.
What happened to Lilly?
I don't know.
Why did she save you?
What do they do at the labs?
What's Project K?
How can you be so clueless?
Say something.
Hey, slowly.
There's a pregnant woman on board.
I don't remember the last time I
saw a woman being this pregnant.
Poor girl. Did you scare her?
How can she say
'I don't know' to everything?
Remember what Mariam used to tell.
Do you think she's the
woman from her stories?
I don't know.
How can you say
'I don't know' to everything?
Here.
I'll go say hi to her.
He may come off as harsh but...
Veeran's a good man.
Are you trying to scare her?
Where are you guys taking me?
Listen, it's dangerous for you
to be out there with this belly.
So, we're going to Shambala.
You and your baby will be safe there.
Can I touch it once?
Kyra, stop!
You're creeping her out.
Sorry, I...
I mean, we grew up
listening to Mariam's stories.
She's been waiting for you since forever.
For me?
Not just Mariam.
Her mother, grandmother and
everyone else have been waiting for you.
We know everything about you.
Well, what's your name?
Please don't tell me that you don't know.
We don't have names.
Serial number SU-M80.
Oh, SUM80.
Hi. My name is Kyra.
My dad gave me that name.
It means 'Good luck' in some language.
He died in the Complex
raid the day after I was born.
Maybe not so lucky for him. Yeah.
That guy cleaning the gun
like a psycho over there...
That's Ajju. My partner.
-Partner?
-Yeah.
By partner, I mean...
Yeah, he's mine.
Let me see a smile, Ajju.
Please. A small one.
They killed so many of us, Kyra.
As long as the Complex exists,
how can one smile?
From the inside, dude.
You can still find a
reason to smile. Come on.
I'll smile after I kill
everyone at the Complex.
Okay?
He's such a charming fellow.
Sometimes I forget what
I saw in him in the first place.
We're getting married
after reaching Shambala.
I guess that makes you
the Chief Guest GU40.
GU40. G 40.
What's marriage?
Oh, right.
You're not aware of any of this.
Marriage is an old tradition.
You circle around fire...
and promise each other
to live together forever.
And then?
And then...
That's it.
They live together.
They build a house, have pet dogs, kids.
Does it sound silly?
No.
It sounds nice.
I know, right.
Everyone should have their
person in this crazy world.
Humanity is one big family,
we should fight for the
greater good, that's all fine.
But...
You should have someone
you can call your own.
Someone's hand to hold.
Someone's shoulder to lean on.
That sense of belongingness hits different.
Smile now at least.
You're cute, GU 40.
GU 40...
Kyra, her name is SU-M80.
What kind of a name is SU-M80?
It's not even a real name.
Umm... SU-M80.
SUM80.
Umm... Sumathi.
Sumathi?
Sumathi...
Sumathi.
It's a bit old-fashioned.
But it's better than SU-M80.
Don't be scared.
I see a Raider.
Let him come. We got this.
Sometimes, you don't need this.
You need this to win.
This is so far away from your village.
Where are you guys
coming from? I want the truth.
We came in the hopes to
find some scrap to sell, sir.
The competition is quite less here.
A woman has escaped from the labs.
With the help of a Rebel.
Do you know where she is?
Sir, we make a living out of selling scrap.
We don't know anything.
Open the back.
There's nothing back there, sir.
We had kind of a rough day, sir.
We couldn't find any scrap.
Maybe I'll find something.
I can pay you some units if you want.
I said open the back!
Okay, sir. Okay, sir.
-There's nothing here.
-I told you, sir.
Yeah, you're really trash.
Let's go.
Didn't I tell you already?
There's nothing in there, sir.
There's nothing, sir.
Boom.
He has sent a bounty alert. Get up.
It's time to pick up the gun.
Now's the time to fire the guns.
Dude...
Tell me this.
The entire house is empty.
So is your car.
Why don't you sleep over there?
Do you have to sleep here only?
My life is over there.
Hey, old man.
Guess what I'll do once
I enter the Complex.
Do whatever the hell you want.
But pay my rent first.
No, listen.
Once I enter the Complex,
I'll breathe in kilos of fresh air.
-Let me...
-Hey, back off.
You took my food.
You occupied my bed.
Now you want to steal all the oxygen?
Listen.
Let's come to an understanding.
Find a nice girl and settle down in life.
How long will you stay in my house?
Do you think I love staying with you?
One big bounty. One shot.
-I'll go to the Complex.
-And do what?
I'll live happily over there.
Happiness should come from within.
It came.
You'll only get cough
from within if you stay here.
I can't live here anymore. I'll leave soon.
Bhairava, five star bounty.
Rebel chase in process. Let's go!
It's a jackpot, old man.
It's time to pay your rent.
A Raider vehicle is
already headed this way.
I'll handle the Raider.
Use it.
I'll go after him. You stay here.
For tomorrow.
Hey, Sumathi. Don't worry.
Kyra means Lucky, remember?
I'll be right back.
Where did she go?
Hi, guys.
Catch.
Ah, good catch!
If you don't stop that truck,
you'll be the first to die.
Veeran!
Ajju...
Sumathi, did you get scared?
Didn't I tell you that I'm lucky?
Ajju...
Let me see a smile, Ajju.
Kyra!
Ajju.
Ajju, what's wrong?
Kyra...
Four teams in pursuit of bounty.
We're the last ones.
Chances of success, 0.18%.
Bujji, can you clarify a doubt for me?
Sure. Go ahead.
How can you fit so much
negativity in that small brain?
Never mind. I'm getting
really good vibes today.
Who's that?
Hi, sir. I haven't seen you in a while.
What's with the shaved head?
No, it looks nice.
Sir, sir, sir!
You took the car parts
promising to work for me.
How long will you keep running from me?
It's just car parts, sir.
I'll dismantle them again.
I don't consent to that.
I'm not here for the car parts.
I'm here for you.
Damn! I'm screwed for
5 years if he catches me.
Bujji, full speed.
We're at maximum speed.
Then turn on flight mode.
It's not ready yet.
To hell with you!
For once in life, just for today,
just be positive.
It's an order.
Flight mode on.
Hey, Bhairava!
I'll find you again.
And this time, I'll lock
you up for 10 years.
10 years!
You can't catch me!
Always trust your boss, Bujji.
Everything will be alright.
Warning! Warning!
Flight system failure!
Bhairava! Bhairava!
Can I sound negative now?
Hey, Ajju!
Ajju, come here.
Ajju! Ajju! Ajju!
Ajju!
There's a woman in the truck. Go get her.
Will you save her?
Who will save you?
Hi, guys.
Sorry, did I disturb you?
I suggest you drop the guns and leave.
I'm saying it for your own good.
Should we listen to you now?
Not me. My teacher.
She's here.
I can sense that she's here.
Hey, old man. You look like you're
retired and approaching death.
You could use some help.
Fire!
I guess your war has begun again.
War?
This isn't like war to me.
It's like the worship of
weapons before going to war.
Hi.
Is he okay?
How come you're here?
Where's the gem?
Hi.
My name is Raia.
What's your name?
Sumathi.
Don't be scared.
My teacher has got this.
Amma...
Bujji, what's happening exactly?
We're travelling upside down.
-Who's that giant man?
-Angry giant man.
He destroyed all the Raiders.
He cut down my work by half.
Is the bounty there?
The bounty is in the back of the truck.
Bujji, ask the Complex to open their gates.
I am coming!
I'll have a real egg in the Complex.
And a plate full of food.
I'll also swim in the sea.
Massage.
At the complex...
Do you think they have nectar?
Woah! The girl from the Complex.
Hi.
Bye.
He's hitting hard, Bujji. Let's leave.
My Complex...
Where have you come from, sir?
Stay there.
Okay. That's enough.
Hey! Love you, Bujji!
Bujji is back, old man.
Bhairava!
He's a tough nut, the old man.
Not again!
Statue!
150 days.
A formula we deemed impossible.
Where's the serum that
was extracted from her?
We could extract only a drop, Bani.
Please don't tell Supreme.
We almost had her.
There was an old man who was 8 feet tall.
He was untouched despite
firing several rounds at him.
Did he have a gem on his forehead?
Yes.
It looked like some sort of light.
Ashwathama!
He wasn't born in this period of time.
He is immortal.
The puranaas are coming true.
Ashwathama, the pregnant woman,
Gaandeevam.
God created this weapon
when he was on Earth.
After God left, the weapons
eventually lost their power.
If that power has returned now,
it means that God is coming back.
He is growing inside that woman's womb.
I've heard my fair share
of these silly stories.
Some God will appear on a white horse.
Our ancestors put it quite intelligently.
The white horse here
refers to his birth star.
The 'Khadga Ashwini' star that
appears once in every 6000 years.
All the planets are going
to align in a few days,
leading to a rare eclipse formation.
The darkest day in 6000 years.
The last day before the
star disappears again.
If the baby isn't born before that,
the star won't appear
for another 6000 years.
We need to stop this at any cost.
Otherwise, it's a threat to Supreme's life.
Where is it?
Hello.
There's no road ahead.
We'll crash into the mountain.
Ashwa uncle, help!
Mariam, Mariam, Mariam!
Mariam, a huge...
A 7 feet tall giant.
What are you saying? Be clear.
The Mother has arrived.
What happened?
Where's Kyra?
Where's everyone else?
For tomorrow.
Hey, drop him.
Drop him!
Drop the gun.
Drop it!
Sir, they're one of us.
Sir... Sir...
Hey! I said drop the gun!
Drop it!
Sir.
Come.
Veeran, who is this?
I don't know.
But,
he's definitely not our enemy.
Is she the woman who escaped from the lab?
Why did you bring her here?
A 5 million bounty has
been announced on her.
The whole world, including
the Complex is after her.
How will you save her?
I will save her.
Who the hell are you?
Being tall isn't enough.
Have you ever been to war?
Excuse me.
He fought a war with Sri
Krishna in Mahabharata.
Maybe we can take her to the flux lands.
They can't track us there.
The Nomens will eat her.
Veeran, I want her
out of here this instant.
She will not be going anywhere.
Sometimes, even my belief was shook.
The Mother has arrived.
She came to her maternal home...
to give birth to God.
Tell Shambala the Mother has arrived.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Has everybody gone crazy?
Do you realize that her presence
has just put us all in danger?
She's an ordinary pregnant
woman who escaped from the lab.
There's nothing special about her.
Moreover,
how can you claim that
God is going to be born?
What's the proof?
Do you remember...
the last time it rained?
For tomorrow.
Ashwa uncle, I can't see anything.
Listen, dear.
Shambala has waited a long time for you.
We're ready to do anything for you.
Tell us.
What do you want?
I'm hungry.
This tree is like a temple to us.
It's clean water. You can drink it.
Take it.
How is all of this here?
The compass that found you was from here.
That's the point this tree grew from.
And that's how Shambala
came to life around this tree.
Just when we were concerned
about losing that life energy,
you showed up.
Shambala's belief came true.
Hereafter, everything will be fine.
Where's the old man?
He's the guy who hit us.
She escaped because of him.
Bhairava, you're blacklisted.
We're seizing all your units.
You're permanently banned from the Complex.
What's wrong?
I lost.
For the first time.
Impossible!
I don't believe you.
Go.
What?
Are you letting me go?
When did you become such a saint?
He's a good guy, sir.
Bujji, give him those 500 units.
He'll grab a bite.
Are you going to pay my rent as well?
If so, please inform me in advance.
My heart is delicate.
I'll do some work and
pay your rent, old man.
I fought a great deal to go to
the Complex all these days.
It's all over now.
I finally gained a sense of clarity.
This is my life right here.
I don't have anybody.
Nobody needs me.
We need you, Bhairava.
You shouldn't stay back here.
Come with me to Shambala.
Shambala...
You go.
Who would take me inside anyway?
Hey, I'll talk to them.
You're a hero to so many others like me.
Come be on our side, Bhairava.
Don't hesitate. Let's go.
Damn, those rebels!
They must've taken her to Shambala.
I want that woman!
We've sent Raiders in
every direction, Commander.
We'll catch her.
You can't do shit.
You can't do shit as long
as that old man is with her.
Old man?
He's the one who thrashed your men.
Nobody could lay their hand on him.
Except for me.
Who is this guy?
He's Bhairava, sir. A bounty hunter.
He hit our Raiders.
I blacklisted him.
Now that you've blacklisted me anyway,
let me hit again.
The point is, only I can bring her back.
You have no option.
How can you be so sure?
Check my records.
I haven't lost a single fight till now.
I won't lose this one either.
Alright.
I'll give you one chance.
If you bring her back,
I'll personally hold your hand
and take you inside the Complex.
♪ Even light doesn't shine
unless it surpasses darkness♪
♪ These deaths become the
gleaming rays of tomorrow♪
♪ Doesn't every victory come
at the cost of many sacrifices?♪
♪ Even our tears act as soldiers♪
♪ A galore of victories
awaits us with this birth♪
Give her some space.
Let's throw this cane away now.
We'll get you a kickass weapon in Shambala.
This isn't an ordinary cane.
It's my weapon from an ancient war.
So, tell me. How was your war like?
Was it more depressing
than the current wars?
Were there a lot of casualties?
Anyway, I'm sure you were the best fighter.
No one can beat you.
No, I lost.
Really?
Who defeated you?
The Weirder of Gaandeeva. Kunthi's son.
Arjuna.
Ashwathama!
This is the Gaandeevam made
by the Creator, Brahma.
Nobody can fight it.
Oh. So I take it Arjun is the best?
No.
There was another warrior.
More powerful than Arjuna?
Yes.
He was my brother.
What happened to him?
Karma.
He met with a miserable death.
A warrior like him didn't deserve it.
This weapon belonged to him.
It's more powerful than...
Arjuna's Gaandeevam.
Wow!
Then why don't you use it?
It works only in his hands.
Without him,
this weapon is powerless.
Right now, this is as good
as an old man's walking stick.
Bhairava, you exhausted
all your units on me.
Your current balance is zero.
Are you doing the right thing?
Are you sure?
Bhairava...
Where do you think you're going?
I'll follow you wherever you go, amma.
Why is everyone calling me 'amma'?
They say that...
the entire universe resides within God.
But that God resides within you.
What else can we call you if not 'amma'?
As you please.
But I need to get out of here.
There's a threat to your life.
I don't think so. In fact,
I'm a threat to everyone.
People around me end up dying.
I won't die.
The gun was in my hand.
Kyra would've been alive if I had fired it.
You were born to bring
another life into this world.
You can't cause someone's death.
What are you even talking about?
For a baby who hasn't
taken its first breath yet,
how many more people need to die?
Every death has a higher purpose.
This baby will give life to the world.
But why am I the chosen one?
God gives his biggest responsibilities...
to the ones who can fulfill them.
To carry God in your womb...
takes patience that of Mother Earth.
Because you possess that kind of patience,
he chose you as the Mother.
Birthing a new life is your duty.
Protecting you is my responsibility.
Are you sure?
Do you remember the way?
I was born there, Bhairava.
Of course, I remember.
We're almost there.
Go straight at full speed.
There's nothing ahead, Bhairava.
All I see is a mountain on my sensors.
Trust me, Bhairava. Let's go.
It's dangerous to be out here for long.
If we crash ahead, even
our parts won't be found.
Let's go back.
No going back now!
Welcome to Shambala.
Luke, is that you?
-Relax, guys!
-Who is he?
He's Bhairava.
He's a great fighter.
He's on our side now.
Hmm. Does Veeran know?
I'm taking him to Veeran now.
Okay. Follow me.
What about me?
I'll finish the formalities
and be right back.
Take care of the car.
I fixed it just a while ago.
That's one massive set-up
centered in the mountains.
Kudos to you for keeping it a
secret from the Complex for so long.
This way.
How's everyone?
It rained.
What? Are you serious?
Like Mariam said, the Mother has arrived.
Where is she?
She's at the tree.
It rained, the Mother arrived,
and now you're here too.
See, Bhairava. Everything's changing.
Sorry, kid.
We need to go.
It's dangerous to be here.
I came prepared this time, old man.
Let's go!
Fire!
Hello, Shambala!
I caught you!
Veeran...
Go.
-Let's go!
-Come!
Let's go!
Come.
Get out of the way, old man.
There's no time.
Bujji!
Yes! I won!
Oh, no! Force field?
What do we do now?
Go get her.
Sirius, are you ready?
For tomorrow.
The darkness that we've
been fighting this whole time...
now stands at our doorstep.
What should we do?
Should we run away?
Or should we fight?
We should fight!
-So, shall we fight?
-Yes, let's fight!
For tomorrow.
Mom!
Hurry up. There's no time.
Garuda One.
Take off immediately.
Help! Help!
-Help!
-Too many of them are left behind.
First you need to get out of here. Move!
Take off immediately!
What about you?
Go. That's an order.
Andrew!
What are you doing? Why did you get down?
Garuda One. Land right now.
I want to kill you right here, right now.
But Supreme insisted that...
he would kill you and your baby.
You called the baby God, right?
Is there nobody else to save her?
Blow him to hell.
Did I take too long, Son of Acharya?
Bhairava, we got to hurry.
Hey, girl from the labs.
What are you doing here?
Bujji, the old man is trapped.
Let's run away.
Please don't take me inside the Complex.
Flight mode on. Ready for take off.
Brother!
Bujji, the old man is coming back.
Full throttle!
Bhairava, we're already running on reserve.
Hold on, brother!
Listen to me.
No, Bhairava! We don't
know where that will take us.
Who's that?
Ashwathama,
this is the Gaandeevam
created by the Creator, Brahma.
Nobody can fight it.
Did I take too long, Son of Acharya?
No.
You came at the right time, my brother.
See that, Kesava?
How can he be my equal?
He could push our
chariot back by only 2 feet.
But my weapon pushed
his chariot back by 10 feet.
O' Dhanunjaya!
Your chariot is a blessing
from the God of Fire.
Guarding it is Lord Hanuman,
as symbolized on the flag.
Riding it is me, the Master
of all three worlds.
He still managed to push it back by 2 feet.
Think about it, Arjuna.
He's not an ordinary warrior.
I see the radiance of the Sun in his eyes.
In his hand is the Vijaya Bow,
which stands undefeated till date.
History will not forget his name.
The Descendant of the Sun.
Karna!
A mistake has been made, Supreme.
The woman who carried
the formula for 150 days...
has escaped from the labs.
This is what they extracted from her.
Just one drop.
Something is happening.
The Gaandeevam that nobody can touch.
The immortal Ashwathama.
A force beyond everyone's understanding.
Some...
new power.
If a single drop encompasses such power,
I completely understand now, Supreme.
I'll go get that woman back.
No.
I'll go get her myself.
The Lord is arriving on his chariot!
I will cause destruction to thee!
I will cause an earthquake!