KHUSHI
It'll be all right
Welcome sir Has the
midwife arrived Sitaram
Greetings
Don't be afraid it'll all be
okay in a little while
Don't be afraid be brave.
Give me that towel
Give me some water
Congratulations
God has given you a baby girl
Praise the Lord!
- Come on in, sir
She's so lovable
Well? My whiskers prick?
This is the world in which every man
lives for just one reason
That they find love in
everyone's heart
Love manifests itself in many ways
Between mother and son.
between brothers
and sisters friends
but there's a love far removed
from all these kinds of love...
a love that is born in young hearts.
A love that brings joy to the heart
Born in the eastern part
of India, in Kolkata...
is Karan
Born in Chamoli village of
Uttaranchal state...
is Virbhadra's daughter, Khushi
Theirs is a marriage
God decided in His heavens
Despite being born in
different castes and regions...
they have one thing in common...
Iove
These are the two children who
are going to fall in love
When will they fall in love?
When will they unite?
That's what this story is all about
Despite the distance between them,
when will these two young hearts...
get to know each other
and accept each other?
Let's witness the miracle
of nature
This is the biggest sari-store
in Mumbai
You'll find every kind of sari here
What do you think of this one?
- Nice
That yellow one. Show me that
I
It
It'
It's
It's a
It's a R
It's a Ro
It's a Roh
It's a Rohi
It's a Rohit
It's a Rohit R
It's a Rohit Re
It's a Rohit Rel
It's a Rohit Rele
It's a Rohit Relea
It's a Rohit Releas
It's a Rohit Release
It's a Rohit Release -
It's a Rohit Release - w
It's a Rohit Release - ww
It's a Rohit Release - www
It's a Rohit Release - www.
It's a Rohit Release - www.b
It's a Rohit Release - www.bw
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwt
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwto
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtor
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorr
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorre
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorren
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrent
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrents
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrents.
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrents.c
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrents.co
It's a Rohit Release - www.bwtorrents.com
Why's she so late? She should
have been here by now
Who? Ram Singh?
- No. Lali!
You start ranting the moment
your daughter's a bit late
Mind your own business.
And don't say I'm ranting
Here comes Lali!
Lali...
Ram Singh, hasn't Lali come?
- No
Moron! You must have
missed her in the crowds
What crowds, sir? There's just a
single railway line and a hut
If anyone ever gets off the train,
it's only to have some water
So what crowds will there be?
- Strange
She told me that she'd be coming
What could have happened?
My Lali has arrived!
Like the flying clouds...
is the kohl in my eyes
Like fragrant winds...
is my disposition
On my lips,
plays a smile
Here comes Khushi (happiness)
I bring khushi
From me flows every cheer
Without me,
they're all fake
I bring the mischief
of Spring
Khushi
The rains come down
in a patter...
it wins our hearts
I wish I could sway
I wish I could kiss
the skies
I tread a new path
towards a new goal
Water, I could turn into a spark
Even a spark would go berserk
at my touch
With my beauty,
I cast a spell
Even the stars
talk about me
Like a fairy in Spring...
here comes Khushi
O little girl...
at your feet
lies the world
I wonder,
so does everybody...
what is it about you?
When you smile,
it ushers in a new dawn...
when you cry,
it plunges us into darkness
I'm a carefree soul
I do as I please
Shade and the dazzling Sun...
it's all about my
stunning beauty
I'm the talk of the town
My bangles tinkle,
my anklets chime
Like a crazy beauty,
I sway in my gait
I'm a bit mischievous,
and a bit shy...
nobody can guess
what it is about me
Like a fairy in Spring...
here comes Khushi
I bring khushi
Lali! My child!
Welcome, sir. Greetings
Madam Lali says they're here
in the village to help us
I've made all the arrangements
they wanted
Where is my daughter donating blood?
- Over there
Moron!
Bloody doctor! How dare you
draw blood from my daughter?
How dare you?
Put that blood back in her! Go on!
Hurry! Get that syringe out
which is drawing her blood
Listen to me...
- Use a syringe to put in the blood
How dare you draw blood from her?
- Donating blood isn't a bad thing
Blood is blood! It isn't water.
- Come on, Papa
Karan...
It'll give me strength
I'll find a girl
who wears short skirts
Love blossoms in my heart...
I see the stars and the Moon
at daytime
I'm about to fall in love...
I'm about to lose my heart
To Tollygunge,
I will get...
how are you?
I'll ask
The girl will ask,
what happened?
Come with me, I'll say
Samosas and rossogollas...
sweet yogurt,
we'll feast on
Life is short
I will find a girl
as a crazy as I am
And then will begin...
our love-story
In the boat, we sail...
across the vast Ganges,
we sail
Whichever girl prefers
Rabindra-sangeet...
will be mate for life
Mother Goddess... please don't
send my son faraway from me
Don't pray like this for me.
- Why're you angry with your mother?
Ma's asking for just the opposite
of what I'm asking of God
God must himself be confused.
Will He heed my prayers or Ma's?
What you've prayed for and
what your Ma prayed for?
I prayed so I can go away to Canada
and she prays that I don't go away
It isn't just a prayer,
she's been meditating
Dad, do you mind?
- Not at all
If my son studies in Canada,
what would be better than that?
How true!
- If it was only for 5 months...
I wouldn't have said anything,
but 5 years?
Just 5 years, Ma!
They'll pass in a jiffy
What haven't I done to
get an admission?
I ran around for the passport
and visa
When I can stay away for 5 years,
can't you do it too, Ma?
She's always crying, daddy!
- Obviously, my son. She's your mother
What? You want to study further?
- Yes
Oh no
We have very few educated boys
in our community anyway
And you want to study further?
Where will I find a suitor for you?
A suitor...? What for?
- To play Cricket with you
Why're you talking about
marriage right now, Papa?
I want to complete my M Sc.
I've filled in the application form
Sign it
Sign it, Papa
I'll pull you by your plaits!
Who do you think you are?
You're always doing as you wish
There are just four boys
who've done BSc...
in our village and the
neighbouring villages
Two of them belong
to our community
One of them is leaving for America.
What for, God alone knows
That leaves Ranvir Chaudhary's son
I've begged him and got him to agree
to live with us after your marriage
I've called them over tomorrow
for your engagement
Called them over?
With whose permission?
Whose permission do I need to take?
- I don't want all this
I want to study
My child, listen to me
After 10 years of prayers,
God blessed us with a child
A baby-girl. If I get you
married in another town...
I'll keep thinking
and worrying about you
Tell me, will I be able to live
if you're far away from me?
Who's marrying and going far away?
- If you study any further...
that's just what is going to happen!
So I've called them for an engagement
So ask them not to come. I want to
study further. Please sign this
You tore up my application form?
That's chap coming to meet
me tomorrow, isn't he?
Just you see!
I'll drive him away!
Just you watch!
Come to bed.
- I'm not sleepy. You go on
It's 2 in the morning. Come...
- I'm not sleepy. You go to sleep!
Lord Hanuman...
please make my daughter
agree to the wedding...
God has heard your prayers.
- What? Really?
You may call them over.
I agree to the wedding
Praise You, Lord Hanuman!
This is my daughter, Khushi.
I call her Lali lovingly
After the marriage, you can
call her either Khushi or Lali
You can even give her a new name.
It's your choice
Do you like the boy?
I'm so happy that you've
agreed to the wedding
But if you don't like the boy,
tell me. I'll find other boys
Now tell me...
do you approve of this chap?
That's chap coming to meet
me tomorrow, isn't he?
Just you see!
I'll drive him away!
Just you watch!
Wow! So you approve of him!
The wedding of Virbhadra Singh's
daughter Khushi...
has been fixed with Ranvir Singh's
son Mahendra
My glasses...
I haven't done anything.
- So who is it?
I'm flying to Canada?
Why're you laughing?
- I'm the one who's going
You?
- My pasport's okay, my visa's okay
Go away to Canada.
I'm going to rot here
God... how could this happen?
Why're you crying?
What happened, Ma?
I don't know...
the groom's sister was crying
after she read this letter
Dear Khushi, forgive me.
I'm in love with someone
Had I told my father,
he'd have killed me
I know, it's terrible to tell
the girl a day before the wedding...
What happened, Lali?
What happened?
Daddy, look at her.
She always sports a long face
Look at dad, Mom. He's so happy
to see me off
But all you know is to shed tears!
- Let me see you off at the airport
You? At the airport?
I want to see smiling faces
before I leave. Not crying faces
My darling Ma!
- Look after yourself
I'll return soon. I promise
Take a careful look at the
guy wearing glasses in that crowd
This man has nothing to do
with our story
But he's the one who's going
to give the story a new twist
Watch out... step on the brakes!
You know whose blood this is?
Yes, it's Khushi's
The blood she donated in Chamoli
has journeyed far to reach here
For Karan
Lali! My child!
Lali, just don't worry
I've told the priest to find
another suitor for you
You're going to be married
next week
Keep quiet, Papa.
- Why, my child?
How can you take such decisions
without even thinking?
Do you know what I've been through?
A groom has just walked out on me
And you're already thinking
of another marriage?
And I want to study further.
But you...
Yes, you wanted to study further.
But I stood in your way
Papa, may I study further?
May I complete my MSc?
How will you study further?
I tore up your application form
You tore up the form
of Pune University
But I've also applied
to the Mumbai University
They've even called me for an interview.
With your permission...
I'll leave for further studies.
- Bombay University?
How about my signature?
Big deal! It's just Virbhadra Singh
Just a fowl-scratch.
I've done it already
Thief!
What's happening?
I saw hands and legs
in plaster...
but not on a whole face!
Moron! Wear your glasses.
That isn't my face
It's over here
Bastard, you're laughing at me
instead of feeling sorry?
You said you were going to Canada
You can't leave me
and go away anywhere
Karan! My son!
- Greetings
Mother Goddess!
What's happened to my son?
Mother Goddess...
Why're you angry? She's crying
because you've met with an accident
This accident took place
because she cried
She cried before I got into the car,
so the accident happened
Thank God she didn't come
to the airport
Had she come there, maybe
the plane would've crashed
Send me to Canada
some way or the other
Rascal! Why're you laughing?
I haven't cracked a joke
It is a joke indeed.
When I broke a little toe...
I was laid up for a week. And you...
you're laid down for 2 months at least
Forget Canada, you can't even
go to the loo for two months
Why must he shut up?
He's right
The doctor says you need bed rest
for at least two months
Dad, what happens of my studies?
You so badly wanted
to go to Canada...
that you didn't apply
to any college here
There's just one way now
The Vice Chancellor at Mumbai
University is a friend of mine
If you wish, I can have a word with
him and have a seat blocked for you
Will you go to Mumbai then?
What difference does it make
when I can't go to Canada anyway?
Be it Calcutta or Mumbai
Looks like you're a huge fan
of Ricky Martin
I follow a rule. I fit in
with whoever's a big hit
Whether it's Ricky Martin
or a rusty tin
Whenever I visit a temple...
I find a lot of peace of mind
I used to visit the temple in the
village every day. I liked going there
Look at the politician. It looks
as if he's asking God for votes
What did you say?
- I was only kidding
I've seen you somewhere
No, that wasn't what
I was getting at. Please
But it's true that boys use this
line when they want to befriend a girl
But that wasn't I was getting at
But I'm speaking the truth.
I've seen you somewhere
I get that feeling too
This is the first time we've met,
but somehow I feel...
as if I've known you for 20 years.
- True. That's how I feel too
You do look happy
You're here to?
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Yes, in our college
In our class?
- No, in the maths section
What's her name?
- Priya
What hankypanky have you been upto?
- I've been upto no hankypanky
It's the same old status problem.
She's the daughter of a rich man
And I was brought up in an orphanage.
- Why do we always have...
this angle in every love-story?
It's very sad!
So now?
- Somehow or the other...
I want to reach this letter to her.
- You plan on killing us, do you?
Madan, please.
- Give it to me
Listen, make him see reason
If he doesn't understand, finish him.
- Sure
You've had it, Vicky. Did you have to
fall in love with this guy's daughter?
Khushi, my dear. How are you?
- I'm all right
How's your friend doing at studies?
- Very well
What are you doing here?
What's that in your hand?
Yes. How did you know?
- It's all over your face
Don't you have any manners on
how to behave with a girl in public?
Don't you realise what people
on the streets will think?
You dress so well but you
behave like a cheapskate?
You're talking any nonsense.
- My mouth, my tongue...
I will say what I want to.
- But my ears can't listen to all this
You're hurting my feelings.
- Feelings, I see!
You get friendly at the first meeting
and pass love-letters the next moment!
What feelings are those?
So cheap!
Madam, I haven't written
this love-letter to you
My friend Vicky wrote it
for your friend Priya
He said that she has a strict father
who won't let her take his calls...
and asked me if I could deliver
this letter to Priya
When I arrived here with the letter,
I found the watchman at the gate
I was wondering what I could do
when these cars arrived
There were these deadly thugs
with Priya's father
I was so shocked to see them,
I didn't know what to do
That's when I saw you
walking out with Priya
Khushi! She's the girl I met
at the temple
I thought my friend's work was done.
I'd send the letter to her through you
But you, you tell me that I don't
have any sense, any manners...
who do you think you are?
Maybe you have a tongue.
But you also brains to think
We've been studying in the same college
and yet we didn't know each other
That's strange, isn't it?
Strange also that we're here together.
- For love
For love?
- Yes. Priya and Vicky's love
What did you think?
- Nothing at all
May I ask something?
Have you ever fallen in love?
You?
Why not?
- Why not?
What will I say?
Why didn't you fall in love?
I don't know.
- You don't know how to fall in love?
So you do?
Shall we leave, Vicky?
What for?
- For dropping me home
You say thanks when a stranger
drops you home
We're not strangers anymore.
So why be so formal?
But I've already said thanks.
What do we do?
You must withdraw the words
Students, the cultural programme
at the college begins very soon!
What happened?
- It's open
The way you reacted over such
a trivial thing, I got really scared
This is how friends should be.
Your friend showed trust in you...
and gave you an open personal letter.
He must have so much of faith in you
That's not such a big thing.
You may read it, if you wish to
Your friend gave it to you,
because he trusted you
You gave it to me,
because you trust me
And my friend has faith in me.
We must never betray someone's faith
What's the big deal?
The letter says, Dear Priya...
I can't take you
to the movies this Friday
I've got to go to Nashik for 2 days,
so please don't be angry with me
I don't know what I will do
without you these 2 days
There's so much I will miss.
You, your voice, your lovely eyes...
your cheeks, beautiful lips,
the ones I kiss...
your lap, in which I rest my head.
I will keep saying...
Must you read someone's letter?
It's a love-letter!
Full of personal emotions
You've let your friend down.
You have betrayed his trust
You're a dirty man...
Are you through?
May I speak now?
Vicky hurt his thumb, not me.
It was bleeding
Can someone write when
he has a hurt thumb?
No? So he dictated letter to me
and I wrote it for him. Get it?
You need more explanation?
You just need an opportunity...
to fly off the handle
and you won't stop
And you even say sorry.
Know what?
Record I'm sorry on a cassette
a thousand times...
because you use those words
often and often. Okay?
What happened?
- The fan-belt seems to have snapped
I had one fixed just yesterday
What do we do now?
- We'll lock it up and walk
The mechanic will take it away
in the morning
Khushi, what are you thinking about?
- Nothing
What are you thinking about?
Khushi, if I ask you a question
will you answer me?
Whom do you like most?
The most...? My Papa
- Of course
Everyone of us loves his Papa.
He's the one who brings us up
Apart from Papa,
who else do you like?
Apart from Papa... my Mummy.
- Who can forget Mummy
Mummy is great. At her feet
lie the heavens
Look outside the house. Whom do
you like, apart from your folks?
Who doesn't like him?
Look away from the film industry.
There must be someone else?
There is...
- There is?
Who?
- Sachin Tendulkar
Khushi, fathers, mothers, actors
and cricketers are all so common
Everyone likes them. But whom do you
like specially and personally?
Khushi... wait
What happened?
- Tell me the name
And I'll say that I like him.
But please don't bother me like this
So what's the name?
Never mind
I was supposed to come, but...
Have you seen Karan around?
Is it your birthday?
- No
Something special at home?
- No. Why?
Your new dress and the sparkle?
Nothing of the sort. Where's Karan?
- He's there in the corridor
He wasn't there.
That's where I came from
Maybe, but he's in
the telephone booth
In the telephone booth?
Please try to understand me
I couldn't come because my friends
asked me to stay back
Hello... Madhu
We have two or three days off
again next month
Yes, I promise
There's still a week, right?
So let me make up for it
Were you waiting for me?
Well? You aren't looking nice today.
- Oh yes, that's what you will say
Oh no, you're really
looking very beautiful
I spoke just the opposite.
- That's how you've always been
I was only kidding.
Why're you taking it seriously?
Khushi's looking for you
Were you looking for me?
- Yes
What for?
- It was something important
But I've forgotten what it was
Who?
- Who and who?
On the phone.
- Madhu
Madhu who?
- My Ma
Ma?
- Yes
But you were uttering her name
That's my mother's name and
I address my mother by her name
Yes, Ma
Get cracking. The show begins in
two hours. I don't have time to waste
Remember your step?
You always teach me the same step.
- Because that's all I know
What? Can you show me
something else?
For the last 10 years, I've been
in this college like a milestone
My juniors have turned professors.
But my friends, my cronies, I...
Enough. I get it
Meaning?
Meaning... she's a friend
If not you...
if not you...
if not you... life's tough
If not with you,
my love...
I can't even die
I get no sleep
If not you
If not you... life's restless
Pining...
overwhelms me...
every moment, I swear
Last night...
in my dreams...
I have seen you, my love
Laughter...
sounds like a wail
if it isn't you
Finding...
is like losing...
if I can't find you
In memories, I was lost...
all night.
I could not go to sleep
Loneliness...
gnaws...
I have no one but you
Rose-gardens...
appear to be barren,
if not with you
This moment...
seems frozen,
if not with you
Were you scared?
- No
What's this?
- A gift
For me?
What's the hurry?
Open it later
Necessary for smokers
Where did you buy it?
- Akbarallys
For how much?
- 5000
5000?
An ashtray? For 5000?
It's no ordinary ashtray.
It's made from French crystal glass
It's expensive because of
its intricate art-work
It's very nice indeed
But you could have given me
another gift instead of this
It's such an expensive
and beautiful ashtray...
I'd hate to drop ash in it
when I smoke
That's exactly why I got
this ashtray
Because whenever you drop ash,
you must remember me
And you must feel that
you're dropping ash...
not in the ashtray, but on me
So you must give up smoking
Karan quits smoking?
Ask me for anything else, and I'll
do it. But give up smoking? No way
If you...
respect me...
you will give up smoking
Happy?
For the exams.
I'm studying
That's not nice.
- What?
That which you're doing
Reading a book is a nice thing.
In any case, it isn't porn.
It's a college book
I'm not talking about
what you're reading
I'm talking about the thing
you've been staring at
Yes, I've been taking a good look
Don't switch the topic.
You...
you were staring at my waist
Don't pretend! You were watching it!
- I didn't
You did too!
- I didn't, I say
And I say you did. You did!
I caught you staring at it!
Well, maybe my eyes wandered
when I was turning a page
But I didn't have any intentions
You haven't been here a minute,
nor have you read a page...
but you looked at it a dozen times!
- Now look, Khushi...
you're mistaking me.
- What...? I'm making a mistake...
or was it you?
Remember all those things! When
I gave you Vicky's open letter...
when I told you about its contents,
what did you say?
One must never look at
other's private affairs
You called me so many names!
Didn't you?
When I told you that he had hurt
his thumb and that I had written...
the letter for him,
you said sorry to me
Didn't you?
Never mind that.
Let's talk about our first meeting
When I gave you that letter
Vicky wanted delivered to Priya...
what conclusion did you jump to?
That I was giving you the letter
You yelled so much at me
Didn't you yell at me?
But when you got to know the truth...
you said sorry. Didn't you?
I know what you want
You want everyone to praise your
beauty, to be crazy about you...
and say I love you to you.
And when someone does that...
you get worked up,
you kick up a fuss...
you start accusing him and say that
he's after girls. Isn't that right?
Talk about me...
not about other girls
What do you know about
girls' psychology? What?
We don't pretend! I don't pretend!
But you do!
You do!
What did you do at the restaurant
the other day?
You deliberately dropped your spoon,
so you could use my spoon to eat!
You did put on an act then.
What were you hiding on?
The other day, you said your car had
broken down and that we'd have to walk
And what did you ask me?
Whom did you like most?
You bored me to death!
And when your daddy come to the
college, you introduced everyone...
Why didn't you say it freely?
Why did you hestitate then?
What feelings were you hiding?
Oh sure, despite
knowing everything...
why've you been acting as
if you didn't know anything?
What will I take that for?
Despite knowing everything,
you gifted me an ashtray
Okay, you gave that to me
as a friend
But when I was talking to my Ma
the other day...
when I was showering kisses on her...
why did you badly
want to know the truth?
You calmed down only after you
got to know that Madhu's my Ma
You presented me an ashtray.
All right, maybe that's friendship
But the restlessness you showed
when you wanted to know about my Ma...
the streak of possessiveness you
showed, what do I take that for?
Let's not stray from the point.
Didn't you stare at my waist?
Haven't you loved me?
No.
- I didn't stare either
I happen to talk to a girl
and she finds faults with me!
I can't ever be friends
with an egoistic girl like her!
Even if we are friends,
it's never going to lead to love
Even if we fall in love,
we'll never marry
And even if we somehow
make it to the marriage altar...
I'll say that I can't marry a girl
like her and run away from there!
What a girl!
You have no right to
talk about my character
I'll forget that I ever
met someone called Karan
You and I have nothing
to do with each other
She looks like a twin-sister
of our master
Excuse me, you're not
our master's twin, are you?
Oh no. There are only
sisters in our family
It's the master himself.
What disguise is this, Master?
What? People go to great lengths
to have an album released
I've only changed my name.
From Madan to Badan Bhosle
So what's wrong?
- Name an album of yours, Master
Don't be stubborn, my love
- How about humming the tune?
The tune? It's fantastic
I've really worked hard on this song.
When it's released...
it's going to kick up a storm.
Want me to sing it for you?
The bud of the night,
blossoms by day
She's mischievous...
she wanders everywhere
What else will I say?
Don't be stubborn, my love
That's a number from Asha Bhosle's
hit album Jaanam Samjha Karo
What nonsense!
That's the title of a movie!
The album of the same name was a hit,
but the film was shit
What's between you and me?
- That's for you to decide, sir
I'll decide later. Now tell me
what do you mean to me?
Your secretary, sir.
- And what's a secretary's job?
You must go out in the market and
find out which album is doing well...
and what the get up is...
so that they don't clash with ours
What sorry?
Well, sir...
- No wells! That's it
Want me to sing another song?
- Sure. Go ahead
What would I do,
if not die?
You're the chosen one
in thousands...
my love
Do not be mistaken.
I haven't come here for a compromise
Why? Is that wrong?
I don't want to...
with you...
I don't want any argument.
I have something important to say
During the summer vacations
when we were not around...
a lot of things have taken place.
Vicky went to meet Priya at her place
He mistook her father for her
and awakened him
He was caught
Priya's father is holding her
captive in the house
Did Vicky attend class?
- No
The love affair we promoted
is now facing problems
I'm talking about Vicky
and Priya's love affair
Did you meet Priya?
I mean, have you?
- Yes
I've come from her house right now.
She was crying
I told her not to worry. To unite her
with Vicky is my duty, I promised her
And you have promised your friend
to unite the two of them
So, to honour the promise
I've made to my friend...
and for you to honour the promise
you've made to your friend, we must...
We must?
We must get together
and unite them
We must... what I'm saying is that
...I want to make it clear
In uniting them, the relationship
we are going to share...
is what I'll decide right now
It will not be love, no friendship
and no relationship at all
Our relationship will last as long
as they are united
I hope you will do that
That you will do it,
I am convinced
What can I say now?
You've said what I wanted to
Shall we go to meet Vicky?
You're the limit! You couldn't
wait for two months
All I want to know is what you told
Priya's old man when you woke him up
Priya darling, here I am?
Or was it...
Sorry, Uncle. Wrong number?
This is exactly why I tell you
not to fall in love!
Look at me. I'm such a happy man!
And why?
Because I'm not in love with someone!
And I don't have any problems like you
Look at your face. You look like
the perfect jilted-Iover
To hide your pain and fake a laughter
is nothing but stupidity
What?
- I'm talking about Vicky's pain
The one you're feeling too
Will it solve the problem by
feeling the pain and crying? No
Just concentrate on your studies,
Vicky. As for your love...
leave it to us. To unite you
with Priya is our responsibility
Can't you trust my words?
All right
But you do trust your love,
don't you? If your love is true...
it'll surely unite the two of you.
Am I right?
If our love is true,
it'll surely unite us
Yes.
- Yes, yes indeed
Where's the need to walk?
I'll drop you home
You needn't necessarily be my
girlfriend for me to drop you home
It doesn't need a relationship at all.
You could say...
you've taken a ride
in a stranger's car
And I'll think I gave a ride
to a girl who was a stranger
If you still want to walk,
it's upto you
What can I do about it?
I live in the hostel now.
Not in that flat
To distance myself from some one,
I had to stay at the hostel
I'll drop you at the hostel then
Two strangers,
where are they headed?
Where are they going?
Angry with each other...
they appear to be,
even as they drive on
Two strangers...
where are they headed?
Where are they going?
Angry with each other...
they appear to be,
even as they drive on
Awake...
asleep...
Iost?
Ask them
Stop faking anger...
be friends again
Do not break each other's hearts,
that isn't a nice thing to do
From a distance...
up close...
they torment each other,
they go together
Desire, hatred...
what exactly do they
want in love?
Yes and no...
is all they say
What's in their hearts?
No one knows
Longing in their eyes,
to see each other...
they're afraid,
they go together
Two strangers...
where are they headed?
Where are they going?
Angry with each other...
they appear to be,
even as they drive on
I have't done anything this time.
It has stalled on its own
The wire of the spark-plug
has come off
God! I haven't seen anything
- What?
Nothing
When a stranger drops me home,
I always thank him
That's a habit of mine.
- Nice habit too
Because of my native tongue, you got
to know that I'm from the villages!
You want to rob me?
- No, sir
Thief! I asked you to take me
to Mumbai University and...
you've been taking me around Mumbai!
You've been driving
around the same place!
Forget it, sir.
It's human to err
Looks like you're
hand in glove with him
Please let him go, Uncle
Come with me.
I'll give you a ride
You don't appear to be a cabbie.
Why will you give me a ride?
He's the one who'll take me there.
You go on
Until you leave, no one else
will be able to move from here
The traffic's come to a standstill
because of you
I study at the Bombay University too.
Come with me, I'll take you there
You take me to be an idiot?
The moron!
Son, how do you live in this city?
Everyone here appears to be
a fraud to me
But you're a nice boy
Guess what I like most about you?
Your smile
Do you know my daughter?
- Who?
How would you know her? There must
be so many girls in the college
There's this hostel near the college.
- Which hostel?
Now what is the name?
Mary...
Right, St Mary's Girls Hostel!
Do you know where the hostel is?
- Know?
I can't ever forget that hostel.
- Why?
There's this girl I know
who stays there
She's no ordinary girl, mind you.
She has a massive ego
What?
- Ego
Meaning?
- Ego meaning...
she thinks she's the last word
Even when she knows she's wrong,
she'll never say sorry
This damn ego...
how will I explain it?
This girl...
she's stubborn, a bit eccentric...
I get it. That daughter
of an ass is arrogant
Yes, arrogant!
I wanted to tell you about the girl,
but you've spoken about her family!
She's just a girl, you know.
If she can be so arrogant...
am I any less?
- Oh yes
Oh yes!
That's the block.
- Thank you very much
I live in Chamoli, son. If you ever
visit the place, do meet me
See you
Lali! My child!
How are you?
- I'm fine
Why're you so late?
- What will I tell you?
On my way, I got into
a fight with a cabbie
It was a terrible fight and
this nice boy really helped me
He... one moment!
Hello son... hello!
Come here
Lali, come here
As I was telling you, I got into
a fight with a crazy cabbie
And a decent boy came along
and helped me. He's the one
This is my daughter, Lali
Have some coffee before you leave.
- Thanks, but I've got to go
Oh no. Back in the village, we don't
let a guest go away without...
extending our hospitality. If you
leave without having coffee...
I'm going to feel bad.
Tell him to stay, dear
Please have some coffee
I'll go and lock my car.
- All right. Let's go
I don't want to get married.
- Why not?
When you wanted to study further,
I agreed with you
And now that I want you to get
married, you must listen to me
Come, son.
Have some coffee
I just don't agree!
- Why not?
Look at her, son.
She's not listening to me
You must listen to Papa, mustn't you?
- Do you know what he's saying?
And this is between the two of us.
You aren't interfering
You'll get a slap, Lali.
He's a guest...
is that how you talk to a guest?
What wrong have I said, son?
I'm looking for a groom for her
and she's refusing me
When a girl keeps refusing to get
married, what does it mean?
It means there is someone else
she loves
I'm not against that. All I want
is for you to have a nice wedding
But how should the suitor be?
He must be just like this boy
Clean-hearted, innocent eyes...
a handsome young man
If there is someone you love,
tell me about it
I'm not in love with anyone
If you really don't love anyone,
you must obey your Papa
Papa, I'm willing to get married.
- Wow!
This is amazing!
I've been trying for so long
and she just wouldn't agree
You spoke to her just once
and viola! She agreed!
Looks like we share the
same birth-sign, son
I had a problem with the cabbie
and you solved
And this problem of her marriage
you have solved too
I'm happy to have achieved
what I set out to do
Lali, I'm leaving by this
evening's train
Do look after yourself, okay?
Come on... drop me on the way
Lali, I forgot to tell you
something very important
There's a girl he knows
who stays here
They have a fight going
between themselves
Never mind, Uncle. Please...
- Now wait a moment
Won't I do anything for all the help
you've extended to me?
What will people say?
She's a very arrogant girl, Lali.
As he said, she's very stubborn too
Not just stubborn, she's...
a bit mental, eko...
what word did you use?
Never mind, Uncle. Forget it...
- Give me the word! What was it?
Yes! Ego!
She's possessed by ego!
Like spirits taking possession
of people's bodies...
this girl is possessed with ego!
Ask the girl not to
fight with him, dear
He's a very nice boy. Even my Papa
believes he's a very nice boy
Bring the two of them together.
Okay?
Will that be enough or do you want me
to stay over for your help, son?
No thank you, Uncle.
You've done so much!
That's all right...
See you
She's a fool to get into a fight
with a nice boy like you
It isn't her fault. It must be
her father who...
has really pampered
the arrogant girl
What has come to be?
And why?
Don't think about it...
Think, how could that girl blow such
a little thing out of proportion?
I can't get this. This little part
of the female anatomy...
Don't remind me, please!
- Everyone gets to look at it
What went wrong if you looked at it?
In Mumbai, girls expose their legs
This is just what
I can't understand!
Your friend Shibu has come all the
way from Kolkata to solve your problem
And I'll solve it too
Look at this. Once this goes in,
your woes will vanish
No thanks. I don't drink.
I don't want it
Drink it up... listen to me.
Just a little... come on
Fun?
I'll now sing a hit song for you
You'll find happiness
Shut up! You make me sadder!
Drink some more. The more you drink,
the more your problems will vanish
You didn't approve of the
Bengali song, did you?
I'll sing a song from Mumbai
for you
Everyone wants a slender waist
If only your heart
could win over the waist
Fun, wasn't it?
The song's over, so is the booze
You have a smoke...
I'll get lots of booze
When you drop ash in this ashtray
you must know it's not the ashtray...
but me it's falling on.
- Oh yes!
What are you staring at?
This way
This way... look here
What?
What are you staring at
with your big...
no, with your two small eyes.
What are you looking at?
All I did was to look
at this little waist
Who do you think you are?
You're very beautiful?
Your face is like a chameleon's,
a pencil-thin nose...
and your body?
It's all right
Your waist is the only thing
one can look at
This little waist
Draped in a black sari,
that little area...
is like a lemon.
No, lemons are yellow
In reds and yellows, if it's shown up
in a romantic light...
naturally, I will look at it.
If you mind...
you mustn't show it at all
Just as your face is a part
of your body, so is your waist
I look at your face, you don't mind.
I see the waist, you mind. What for?
Tell me, darling. Speak
Not just your body, I'm going to
take a look at your whole body now
You have no right to
stand there before me!
You have no right to touch it!
I came here to discuss
something important with you
But neither are you in the mood to
listen, nor am I in the mood to tell
Khushi, I've done nothing.
It's my Bengali friend
He forced me to drink
If people smoke and drink,
why must I care?
It isn't necessary for me
to know why you had liquor
Want some?
I came here because I thought
you were a nice human being
But you're worse than
I could ever imagine
If you'd listen...
You're a performer...
you can't make me dance
When it's your turn...
you'll beat a hasty retreat
Master, that's Altaf Raja's tune.
- Altaf Raja? A foreigner?
He's a famous qawwal. This is
a tune from his famous album
How's that possible?
- It is
You must've heard the tune
and pinched it
But this is a three-year old tune.
- What a thief!
I composed the tune three days ago,
and he stole it three years back!
No more qawwali for me!
How did you know it's Priya
without even looking at her?
The fragrance! I can tell every
beautiful girl from her fragrance
Where's this stink coming from?
Lay off!
You like my wig, don't you?
Here you are
Remember, the cultural programme at
the college is fast approaching?
Join Karan immediately
and start your rehearsals
No, Master.
- Why?
I can't participate in this function.
- Why not?
I've told you. I'm not participating
Mukesh, make a team of Karan and Roma
and send them on the stage
You have my blessings!
Who's Roma?
- You don't know Roma? Roma!
A new student in the first year!
She's kicked up a storm in the college
The students are crazy about her
and go around her like blind men
What for?
Could you help me cross the road?
- What for?
A blind man needs help
You've crossed the road.
- Small road
What?
- You've helped a blind man
Thank you so much.
You are large-hearted
Slipped out of my hands! Damn it!
What is the matter?
- Priya has sent a letter
You can give it to Vicky.
- It's not for him
Is it for me?
- No
It must be for you then.
If not for me, you nor Vicky...
- It's for the two of us!
You read it
I love Vicky so dearly...
I don't think anyone in
the world loves anyone as much
You must think why every lover
in the world says that
It's because they have
true love for each other
And the suffering of separation
those truly in love go through...
only I know about
I'm pining to meet Vicky.
Please bring us together
Yours, Priya
What are we to do now?
Priya has a friend called
Shehnaz, right?
How are you, Rukhsana?
- I'm fine
Be careful, Vicky
The two of you chat,
I'm going to bed
Who's this girl?
It's Shabana.
Shehnaz's friend
Is she coming here
for the first time?
Yes
I see. Go ahead and
chat with Rukhsana...
I'll take Shabana around the house
Come on, Shabana.
- Run away, Vicky!
Car number 906.
Is it yours?
Yes.
- Karan?
Let me do it
How are you related to the girl?
- I...
Help me with the injection.
- All right
In the waist
Give it to her in the arm.
- This is meant for the waist
No, give it to her in the arm.
- The one for the arm...
is given in the arm, the one
for the waist is given in the waist
You don't know anything
about this waist, doctor
This waist has caused
a very big problem already
If I go into details,
it'll take at least 2 hours
Your duty hours will be over
and when the next doctor comes...
I'll have to explain to him!
Have mercy on me...
and give it to her in the arm
That's all right!
You can give it wherever you wish
Give it to anyone. To her,
the nurse or yourself...
I've seen nothing,
I will see nothing
God, why did You make
this waist? Why?
My heart, my love...
I've given to you
My love...
what have you done?
When our gaze met,
I realised...
I'm crazy about you
It's something my heart knows
You're the one
I've taken for my beloved
On your lips, is a smile.
Your eyes hold an intoxication
The sight of you
makes my heart sway
I love you all day and night.
I find peace only after meeting you
Your dark tressses
lend a fragrance to my being
All I wish to say is that
it's your arms I must stay in
Don't ever forget
this promise
Don't make me cry,
now that you make me smile
Don't make excuses...
don't ever hide
anything from me
My heart, my love...
I've given to you
My dream, my desire...
is to adorn your arms
with bridal bangles
These lovely meetings,
I love the way you talk...
Should you consent, my love...
I'd bring the bridal palanquin
to your house
I spend my nights pining.
I dream of marriage
My world of love,
you must embellish...
never leave me ever
Keep your promises
Always hold me in your arms
My heart, my love...
I've given to you
My love...
what have you done?
What is it? What?
I tried several times to
meet you at your office
But you staff wouldn't let me.
So...
My name is Karan
Vicky's my friend, sir.
His past is nothing...
at present, he's a student
and he has a very bright future
You don't know that,
but I do
At my age, my father was
even worse off than Vicky is
At this age, even you...
don't take offense
You used to be a small-time thug
But I tell you, at your age...
Vicky will be far ahead of you,
me and even my father
Apart from all this,
he has a very kind heart
When a boy falls in love
with a girl...
and he finds the girl
without any problem...
imagine how happy it'll make him.
Please don't separate them
Please unite them
Your two minutes are up.
Let's go, Gotya
Did he have nothing to say?
Your two minutes are up, he said.
And left
All right.
Even if he said nothing...
couldn't you guess
what was on his mind?
What?
- I ask...
couldn't you guess
what was on his mind?
If one knew what's on everyone's mind,
there wouldn't be any problem at all
We have these problems
because we don't know
What do you mean by these problems?
- These problems. Period
All right. I must leave now
Did you call?
Yes
What for?
To talk.
- That's what we've been doing
No, there's something else
I want to talk about
What is it about?
She knows... why must she
ask what it's about
The arrogant one!
It's about what you think
I'm thinking about nothing.
You wanted to talk to me
So tell me what you want to
Is that what you called me to say?
- Yes
Your intoxicating eyes...
your lips...
there's a huge list
I have of you
Roma, can you fall in love with me?
Can you really like me?
However...
the possibility of me
falling in love with you...
does exist.
- Thanks
I don't you well, you see.
Let's see each other for a few days...
and then I'll decide about it.
It'll take a bit of time, okay?
What's a bit... take all the time.
All my time is now yours
I feel as if something is
stirred in my heart for you
Your lovely tresses...
your rose-like lips...
and this lovely neck and...
I'm not calling you because
you have a girl in your arms
Neither have I called you because
you're drawing pictures on her body
I haven't called out
to disturb you
We've got to be at Priya's place
at 7:30. You remember that?
Karan, who's she? A friend?
- A friend? Oh no, no chance at all
Is she a lover then?
- Lover? How disgusting!
To be my lover,
a girl needs extra qualities
So who's she?
She's Khushi. There's nothing else
I know about her
Karan, just 15 minutes to go
for 7:30. May we leave now?
When will you meet me again?
- Again?
At lunch?
- Not lunch. At dinner
At night. Candle-light.
Sunday 10, at my place
Shall we?
Today's Sunday.
So?
It was you who said it...
Yes, I did, but...
Whoever you are with,
why must I care?
Sorry, I'm late
What happened?
- Last night... nothing
What did Priya have to say?
- She says forget it
Forget what?
- Love
Whose love?
- The love Vicky had for Priya
Priya asks to forget it
And what did you tell her?
When she herself isn't interested,
what can I do?
What is it with girls? Flirt when you
want to, dump the guy when you wish
Have you girls ever considered
what it does to us guys?
You're acting like
a very decent guy?
Do you think I don't know
the truth about you?
Were you breathing heavily
last night, or weren't you?
What?
Were you breathing last night,
or weren't you?
Breathing? I was breathing last night
and the night before that too
And I breathe every day...
and well at that
It's good for the health.
Is it bad to breathe?
Maybe it's bad to look at this...
but why's it bad to breathe?
How will man live
if he doesn't breathe?
Am I the only one who breathes?
Everyone does. Every single day
Your parents do, so do mine.
Because they breathe...
you are here, I am here...
so's the dog
He breathes every day.
Nicely at that. Right puppy?
See? If you call that bad,
what can I do?
The breathing I spoke about is
different from the one you allude to
It's all the same. If breathing
is wrong, everything is wrong
I'll leave if you talk like this
I know the suffering of one
truly in love
Priya's words, weren't they?
So how can she ask us to forget it?
What does it mean?
We have to talk
Today's the last day at college.
It's time to separate
So come forth and take my blessings
You been in a crowded train?
So many of them have
gone into coma for you
I'm in a coma too. Embrace me
and revive me from the coma, Roma
Priya's wedding has been fixed
What are we to do?
Greetings
Mr Zorawar Singh... over here
Where are you going?
To fetch your daughter?
She's with us right now.
She's marrying the man she loves
From the look of it, it appears
as if you want to give me a thrashing
Don't even think of it.
Pray to God...
that I come to no harm.
If something happens to me...
you'll be the guilty one
in the eyes of the law
I've made arrangements, you know
You're picking up something
to throw at me
Forget me...
you can't even touch my image
Spend a month in Mahabaleshwar
before you return to Calcutta
Dad has found a job for you
over there. Okay?
Spend your lives together.
Be happy
There are problems between
you and Khushi, isn't it?
You know why man faces problems?
Because he hides his feelings
If you speak your heart,
you face no problems
But I don't know why man
doesn't understand that
He loves someone,
but he pretends to hate her
He hates someone and he pretends
to love her. What for?
Poor heart. Why do we burden
it with a thousand worries...
and make life unbearable for it?
If you love her...
tell her that you love her,
or tell her that you don't
God has given you eyes to see,
ears to hear...
and a heart to love
So forget about egoes
and fall in love
Love each other
I've told you how I feel
You've been a great help in uniting
my friend with his beloved
Thanks to you too. In uniting
my friend with her beloved...
you've been a great help.
Thank you
This is Seema here
I'm leaving today
- Okay
I'm leaving and you're just...
- I have another tension, Seema
Sir, the taxi has arrived
Karan?
- He has left for VT Station
Which train is it?
- Howrah Mail at 7:15
Is Khushi there?
- She has left
Where to?
- Bombay Central
Which train?
- Golden Temple Express at 7:10
Karan?
- No one has arrived yet
Was there a girl called Khushi here?
- There's no one
Maybe he has gone to
Mumbai Central to meet me
Maybe she has gone to
VT Station to meet me
And what if he hasn't?
Now?
A girl called Khushi will come here.
Please give her this letter
A boy called Karan will come here.
Please give him this
Karan?
- Yes?
I've been wanting to tell you
something for a very long time
You know?
I love you, Khushi
When we were together,
this is what I wanted to say...
but I never could,
I don't know why
And now that I want to speak,
you are not with me
We said so much to each other
when we fought...
but we couldn't say one single word
to get together. I'm sorry, Khushi
When I freed my hand from yours
after thanking you...
I felt something strange
stir in my heart
I don't know what it was.
But I need you, Karan
I now realise that the fights
we had was all part of our love
I need you, Khushi.
To love me, to fight with me
You're a lucky girl to have
found a father like yours
Ever since you agreed
to the wedding...
all he has done is to
look out for suitors
He decided to have Lali married
the day she returned from the city
Everything is ready.
The bridegroom, the garland...
step forward and be garlanded
Lali! My child!
You're back! Welcome!
Go and get ready quickly.
- But Papa...
Just don't worry, my little girl.
The boy I've chosen this time...
is neither running away
nor leaving behind letters...
and he's not in love with
another girl either
Why're you chanting Papa?
Go and get dressed quickly
Coming!
Lali, take a look
at your bridegroom
Take a look at him
You left this note for him
in the train...
and he turned out to be
faster than you
He halted the train and
took a flight to get here
He has told me everything
Karan's parents will also be
coming here for the wedding
Are you happy now
This is how two hearts met
and accepted each other
They're celebrating their
ninth anniversary
and they're still fighting
What is surprising is that
they haven't one or two kids
they have 17 children in 8 years
Twins every year But how
does it still add up to 17
Confusing, isn't it
They didn't fight for a year
and they had triplets
Khushi's expecting again.
Twins or triplets I don't know
I'm just looking on
and praying for them
May Karan keep giving Khushi
this happiness all her life
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org