KHUSHI
It'll be all right.
Welcome sir Has the
midwife arrived Sitaram.
Greetings.
Don't be afraid it'll all be
okay in a little while.
Don't be afraid be brave.
Give me that towel.
Give me some water.
Congratulations.
God has given you a baby girl.
- Praise the Lord!
- Come on in, sir.
She's so lovable.
Well? My whiskers prick?
This is the world in which every man
lives for just one reason.
That they find love in
everyone's heart.
Love manifests itself in many ways.
Between mother and son,
between brothers
and sisters, friends,
but there's a love far removed
from all these kinds of love...
A love that is born in young hearts.
A love that brings joy to the heart
Born in the eastern part
of India, in Kolkata...
is Karan.
Born in Chamoli village of
Uttaranchal state...
is Virbhadra's daughter, Khushi.
Theirs is a marriage
God decided in His heavens.
Despite being born in
different castes and regions...
They have one thing in common...
Love.
These are the two children who
are going to fall in love.
When will they fall in love?
When will they unite?
That's what this story is all about.
Despite the distance between them,
when will these two young hearts...
get to know each other
and accept each other?
Let's witness the miracle
of nature.
This is the biggest sari-store
in Mumbai.
You'll find every kind of sari here.
- What do you think of this one?
- Nice
That yellow one. Show me that.
Why's she so late? She should
have been here by now.
- Who? Ram Singh?
- No. Lali!
You start ranting the moment
your daughter's a bit late.
Mind your own business.
And don't say I'm ranting.
Here comes Lali!
Lali...
- Ram Singh, hasn't Lali come?
- No
Moron! You must have
missed her in the crowds.
What crowds, sir? There's just a
single railway line and a hut.
If anyone ever gets off the train,
it's only to have some water.
- So what crowds will there be?
- Strange
She told me that she'd be coming.
What could have happened?
My Lali has arrived!
♪ Like the flying clouds... ♪
♪ is the kohl in my eyes ♪
♪ Like fragrant winds... ♪
♪ is my disposition ♪
♪ On my lips,
plays a smile ♪
♪ Here comes Khushi (happiness) ♪
♪ I bring Khushi ♪
♪ From me flows every cheer ♪
♪ Without me,
they're all fake ♪
♪ I bring the mischief
of Spring ♪
♪ Khushi ♪
♪ The rains come down
in a patter... ♪
♪ it wins our hearts ♪
♪ I wish I could sway ♪
♪ I wish I could kiss
the skies ♪
♪ I tread a new path
towards a new goal ♪
♪ Water, I could turn into a spark ♪
♪ Even a spark would go berserk
at my touch ♪
♪ With my beauty,
I cast a spell ♪
♪ Even the stars
talk about me ♪
♪ Like a fairy in Spring... ♪
♪ here comes Khushi ♪
♪ O little girl... ♪
♪ at your feet
lies the world ♪
♪ I wonder,
so does everybody... ♪
♪ what is it about you? ♪
♪ When you smile,
it ushers in a new dawn... ♪
♪ when you cry,
it plunges us into darkness ♪
♪ I'm a carefree soul ♪
♪ I do as I please ♪
♪ Shade and the dazzling Sun... ♪
♪ it's all about my
stunning beauty ♪
♪ I'm the talk of the town ♪
♪ My bangles tinkle,
my anklets chime ♪
♪ Like a crazy beauty,
I sway in my gait ♪
♪ I'm a bit mischievous,
and a bit shy... ♪
♪ nobody can guess
what it is about me ♪
♪ Like a fairy in Spring... ♪
♪ here comes Khushi ♪
♪ I bring Khushi ♪
Lali! My child!
Welcome, sir. Greetings.
Madam Lali says they're here
in the village to help us.
I've made all the arrangements
they wanted.
- Where is my daughter donating blood?
- Over there.
Moron!
Bloody doctor! How dare you
draw blood from my daughter?
How dare you?
Put that blood back in her! Go on!
Hurry! Get that syringe out
which is drawing her blood.
- Listen to me...
- Use a syringe to put in the blood.
- How dare you draw blood from her?
- Donating blood isn't a bad thing.
- Blood is blood! It isn't water.
- Come on, Papa.
Karan...
♪ It'll give me strength. ♪
♪ I'll find a girl
who wears short skirts ♪
♪ Love blossoms in my heart... ♪
♪ I see the stars and the Moon
at daytime ♪
♪ I'm about to fall in love... ♪
♪ I'm about to lose my heart ♪
♪ To Tollygunge,
I will get... ♪
♪ how are you?
I'll ask ♪
♪ The girl will ask,
what happened? ♪
♪ Come with me, I'll say ♪
♪ Samosas and rossogollas... ♪
♪ sweet yogurt,
we'll feast on ♪
♪ Life is short ♪
♪ I will find a girl
as a crazy as I am ♪
♪ And then will begin... ♪
♪ our love-story ♪
♪ In the boat, we sail... ♪
♪ across the vast Ganges,
we sail ♪
♪ Whichever girl prefers
Rabindra-sangeet... ♪
♪ will be mate for life ♪
Mother Goddess... please don't
send my son faraway from me.
- Don't pray like this for me.
- Why're you angry with your mother?
Ma's asking for just the opposite
of what I'm asking of God.
God must himself be confused.
Will He heed my prayers or Ma's?
What you've prayed for and
what your Ma prayed for?
I prayed so I can go away to Canada
and she prays that I don't go away.
It isn't just a prayer,
she's been meditating.
- Dad, do you mind?
- Not at all.
If my son studies in Canada,
what would be better than that?
- How true!
- If it was only for 5 months...
I wouldn't have said anything,
but 5 years?
Just 5 years, Ma!
They'll pass in a jiffy.
What haven't I done to
get an admission?
I ran around for the passport
and visa.
When I can stay away for 5 years,
can't you do it too, Ma?
- She's always crying, daddy!
- Obviously, my son. She's your mother.
- What? You want to study further?
- Yes.
Oh no.
We have very few educated boys
in our community anyway.
And you want to study further?
Where will I find a suitor for you?
- A suitor...? What for?
- To play Cricket with you
Why're you talking about
marriage right now, Papa?
I want to complete my MSc.
I've filled in the application form.
Sign it.
Sign it, Papa.
I'll pull you by your plaits!
Who do you think you are?
You're always doing as you wish.
There are just four boys
who've done BSc...
in our village and the
neighbouring villages.
Two of them belong
to our community.
One of them is leaving for America.
What for, God alone knows.
That leaves Ranvir Chaudhary's son.
I've begged him and got him to agree
to live with us after your marriage.
I've called them over tomorrow
for your engagement.
Called them over?
With whose permission?
- Whose permission do I need to take?
- I don't want all this.
I want to study.
My child, listen to me.
After 10 years of prayers,
God blessed us with a child.
A baby-girl. If I get you
married in another town...
I'll keep thinking
and worrying about you.
Tell me, will I be able to live
if you're far away from me?
- Who's marrying and going far away?
- If you study any further...
that's just what is going to happen!
So I've called them for an engagement.
So ask them not to come. I want to
study further. Please sign this.
You tore up my application form?
That's chap coming to meet
me tomorrow, isn't he?
Just you see!
I'll drive him away!
Just you watch!
- Come to bed.
- I'm not sleepy. You go on.
- It's 2 in the morning. Come...
- I'm not sleepy. You go to sleep!
Lord Hanuman...
please make my daughter
agree to the wedding...
- God has heard your prayers.
- What? Really?
You may call them over.
I agree to the wedding.
Praise You, Lord Hanuman!
This is my daughter, Khushi.
I call her Lali lovingly.
After the marriage, you can
call her either Khushi or Lali
You can even give her a new name.
It's your choice.
Do you like the boy?
I'm so happy that you've
agreed to the wedding.
But if you don't like the boy,
tell me. I'll find other boys.
Now tell me...
do you approve of this chap?
That's chap coming to meet
me tomorrow, isn't he?
Just you see!
I'll drive him away!
Just you watch!
Wow! So you approve of him!
The wedding of Virbhadra Singh's
daughter Khushi...
has been fixed with Ranvir Singh's
son Mahendra.
My glasses...
- I haven't done anything.
- So who is it?
I'm flying to Canada?
- Why're you laughing?
- I'm the one who's going.
- You?
- My passport’s okay, my visa's okay
Go away to Canada.
I'm going to rot here.
God... how could this happen?
Why're you crying?
What happened, Ma?
I don't know...
the groom's sister was crying
after she read this letter.
Dear Khushi, forgive me.
I'm in love with someone.
Had I told my father,
he'd have killed me.
I know, it's terrible to tell
the girl a day before the wedding...
What happened, Lali?
What happened?
Daddy, look at her.
She always sports a long face.
Look at dad, Mom. He's so happy
to see me off.
- But all you know is to shed tears!
- Let me see you off at the airport
You? At the airport?
I want to see smiling faces
before I leave. Not crying faces.
- My darling Ma!
- Look after yourself.
I'll return soon. I promise.
Take a careful look at the
guy wearing glasses in that crowd.
This man has nothing to do
with our story.
But he's the one who's going
to give the story a new twist.
Watch out... step on the brakes!
You know whose blood this is?
Yes, it's Khushi's.
The blood she donated in Chamoli
has journeyed far to reach here.
For Karan.
Lali! My child!
Lali, just don't worry.
I've told the priest to find
another suitor for you.
You're going to be married
next week.
- Keep quiet, Papa.
- Why, my child?
How can you take such decisions
without even thinking?
Do you know what I've been through?
A groom has just walked out on me.
And you're already thinking
of another marriage?
And I want to study further.
But you...
Yes, you wanted to study further.
But I stood in your way
Papa, may I study further?
May I complete my MSc?
How will you study further?
I tore up your application form.
You tore up the form
of Pune University.
But I've also applied
to the Mumbai University.
They've even called me for an interview.
With your permission...
- I'll leave for further studies.
- Bombay University?
How about my signature?
Big deal! It's just Virbhadra Singh.
Just a fowl-scratch.
I've done it already.
Thief!
What's happening?
I saw hands and legs
in plaster...
but not on a whole face!
Moron! Wear your glasses.
That isn't my face.
It's over here.
Bastard, you're laughing at me
instead of feeling sorry?
You said you were going to Canada.
You can't leave me
and go away anywhere.
- Karan! My son!
- Greetings.
Mother Goddess!
What's happened to my son?
Mother Goddess...
Why're you angry? She's crying
because you've met with an accident
This accident took place
because she cried.
She cried before I got into the car,
so the accident happened.
Thank God she didn't come
to the airport.
Had she come there, maybe
the plane would've crashed.
Send me to Canada
some way or the other.
Rascal! Why're you laughing?
I haven't cracked a joke.
It is a joke indeed.
When I broke a little toe...
I was laid up for a week. And you...
you're laid down for 2 months at least
Forget Canada, you can't even
go to the loo for two months.
Why must he shut up?
He's right.
The doctor says you need bed rest
for at least two months.
Dad, what happens of my studies?
You so badly wanted
to go to Canada...
that you didn't apply
to any college here.
There's just one way now.
The Vice Chancellor at Mumbai
University is a friend of mine.
If you wish, I can have a word with
him and have a seat blocked for you.
Will you go to Mumbai then?
What difference does it make
when I can't go to Canada anyway?
Be it Calcutta or Mumbai.
Looks like you're a huge fan
of Ricky Martin.
I follow a rule. I fit in
with whoever's a big hit.
Whether it's Ricky Martin
or a rusty tin.
Whenever I visit a temple...
I find a lot of peace of mind.
I used to visit the temple in the
village every day. I liked going there.
Look at the politician. It looks
as if he's asking God for votes.
- What did you say?
- I was only kidding
I've seen you somewhere.
No, that wasn't what
I was getting at. Please.
But it's true that boys use this
line when they want to befriend a girl.
But that wasn't I was getting at.
But I'm speaking the truth.
I've seen you somewhere.
I get that feeling too.
This is the first time we've met,
but somehow I feel...
- as if I've known you for 20 years.
- True. That's how I feel too.
You do look happy.
You're here to?
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- Yes, in our college.
- In our class?
- No, in the maths section.
- What's her name?
- Priya.
- What hankypanky have you been up to?
- I've been up to no hankypanky.
It's the same old status problem.
She's the daughter of a rich man.
- And I was brought up in an orphanage.
- Why do we always have...
this angle in every love-story?
It's very sad!
- So now?
- Somehow or the other...
- I want to reach this letter to her.
- You plan on killing us, do you?
- Madan, please.
- Give it to me
Listen, make him see reason.
- If he doesn't understand, finish him.
- Sure.
You've had it, Vicky. Did you have to
fall in love with this guy's daughter?
- Khushi, my dear. How are you?
- I'm all right.
- How's your friend doing at studies?
- Very well.
What are you doing here?
What's that in your hand?
- Yes. How did you know?
- It's all over your face.
Don't you have any manners on
how to behave with a girl in public?
Don't you realise what people
on the streets will think?
You dress so well but you
behave like a cheapskate?
- You're talking any nonsense.
- My mouth, my tongue...
- I will say what I want to.
- But my ears can't listen to all this.
- You're hurting my feelings.
- Feelings, I see!
You get friendly at the first meeting
and pass love-letters the next moment!
What feelings are those?
So cheap!
Madam, I haven't written
this love-letter to you.
My friend Vicky wrote it
for your friend Priya.
He said that she has a strict father
who won't let her take his calls...
and asked me if I could deliver
this letter to Priya.
When I arrived here with the letter,
I found the watchman at the gate.
I was wondering what I could do
when these cars arrived.
There were these deadly thugs
with Priya's father.
I was so shocked to see them,
I didn't know what to do.
That's when I saw you
walking out with Priya.
Khushi! She's the girl I met
at the temple.
I thought my friend's work was done.
I'd send the letter to her through you.
But you, you tell me that I don't
have any sense, any manners...
Who do you think you are?
Maybe you have a tongue.
But you also brains to think.
We've been studying in the same college
and yet we didn't know each other.
That's strange, isn't it?
- Strange also that we're here together.
- For love.
- For love?
- Yes. Priya and Vicky's love.
- What did you think?
- Nothing at all.
May I ask something?
Have you ever fallen in love?
You?
- Why not?
What will I say?
Why didn't you fall in love?
- I don't know.
- You don't know how to fall in love?
So you do?
Shall we leave, Vicky?
- What for?
- For dropping me home.
You say thanks when a stranger
drops you home.
We're not strangers anymore.
So why be so formal?
But I've already said thanks.
What do we do?
You must withdraw the words.
Students, the cultural programme
at the college begins very soon!
- What happened?
- It's open.
The way you reacted over such
a trivial thing, I got really scared.
This is how friends should be.
Your friend showed trust in you...
and gave you an open personal letter.
He must have so much of faith in you.
That's not such a big thing.
You may read it, if you wish to.
Your friend gave it to you,
because he trusted you.
You gave it to me,
because you trust me.
And my friend has faith in me.
We must never betray someone's faith.
What's the big deal?
The letter says, Dear Priya...
I can't take you
to the movies this Friday.
I've got to go to Nashik for 2 days,
so please don't be angry with me.
I don't know what I will do
without you these 2 days.
There's so much I will miss.
You, your voice, your lovely eyes...
your cheeks, beautiful lips,
the ones I kiss...
your lap, in which I rest my head.
I will keep saying...
Must you read someone's letter?
It's a love-letter!
Full of personal emotions.
You've let your friend down.
You have betrayed his trust.
You're a dirty man...
Are you through?
May I speak now?
Vicky hurt his thumb, not me.
It was bleeding.
Can someone write when
he has a hurt thumb?
No? So he dictated letter to me
and I wrote it for him. Get it?
You need more explanation?
You just need an opportunity...
to fly off the handle
and you won't stop.
And you even say sorry.
Know what?
Record I'm sorry on a cassette
a thousand times...
because you use those words
often and often. Okay?
- What happened?
- The fan-belt seems to have snapped
I had one fixed just yesterday.
- What do we do now?
- We'll lock it up and walk.
The mechanic will take it away
in the morning.
- Khushi, what are you thinking about?
- Nothing.
- What are you thinking about?
Khushi, if I ask you a question
will you answer me?
Whom do you like most?
- The most...? My Papa.
- Of course.
Everyone of us loves his Papa.
He's the one who brings us up.
Apart from Papa,
who else do you like?
- Apart from Papa... my Mummy.
- Who can forget Mummy.
Mummy is great. At her feet
lie the heavens.
Look outside the house. Whom do
you like, apart from your folks?
Who doesn't like him?
Look away from the film industry.
There must be someone else?
- There is...
- There is?
- Who?
- Sachin Tendulkar.
Khushi, fathers, mothers, actors
and cricketers are all so common.
Everyone likes them. But whom do you
like specially and personally?
Khushi... wait.
- What happened?
- Tell me the name.
And I'll say that I like him.
But please don't bother me like this.
So what's the name?
Never mind.
I was supposed to come, but...
Have you seen Karan around?
- Is it your birthday?
- No.
- Something special at home?
- No. Why?
Your new dress and the sparkle?
- Nothing of the sort. Where's Karan?
- He's there in the corridor.
He wasn't there.
That's where I came from.
Maybe, but he's in
the telephone booth.
In the telephone booth?
Please try to understand me.
I couldn't come because my friends
asked me to stay back.
Hello... Madhu.
We have two or three days off
again next month.
Yes, I promise.
There's still a week, right?
So let me make up for it.
Were you waiting for me?
- Well? You aren't looking nice today.
- Oh yes, that's what you will say.
Oh no, you're really
looking very beautiful.
- I spoke just the opposite.
- That's how you've always been.
I was only kidding.
Why're you taking it seriously?
Khushi's looking for you.
- Were you looking for me?
- Yes.
- What for?
- It was something important.
But I've forgotten what it was.
- Who?
- Who and who?
- On the phone.
- Madhu.
- Madhu who?
- My Ma.
- Ma?
- Yes.
But you were uttering her name.
That's my mother's name and
I address my mother by her name.
Yes, Ma.
Get cracking. The show begins in
two hours. I don't have time to waste.
Remember your step?
- You always teach me the same step.
- Because that's all I know.
What? Can you show me
something else?
For the last 10 years, I've been
in this college like a milestone.
My juniors have turned professors.
But my friends, my cronies, I...
Enough. I get it.
Meaning?
Meaning... she's a friend.
♪ If not you... ♪
♪ if not you... ♪
♪ if not you... life's tough ♪
♪ If not with you,
my love... ♪
♪ I can't even die ♪
♪ I get no sleep ♪
♪ If not you ♪
♪ If not you... life's restless ♪
♪ Pining... ♪
♪ overwhelms me... ♪
♪ every moment, I swear ♪
♪ Last night... ♪
♪ in my dreams... ♪
♪ I have seen you, my love ♪
♪ Laughter... ♪
♪ sounds like a wail
if it isn't you ♪
♪ Finding... ♪
♪ is like losing...
if I can't find you ♪
♪ In memories, I was lost... ♪
♪ all night.
I could not go to sleep ♪
♪ Loneliness... ♪
♪ gnaws... ♪
♪ I have no one but you ♪
♪ Rose-gardens... ♪
♪ appear to be barren,
if not with you ♪
♪ This moment... ♪
♪ seems frozen,
if not with you ♪
- Were you scared?
- No.
- What's this?
- A gift.
For me?
What's the hurry?
Open it later.
Necessary for smokers.
- Where did you buy it?
- Akbarallys.
- For how much?
- 5000.
5000?
An ashtray? For 5000?
It's no ordinary ashtray.
It's made from French crystal glass.
It's expensive because of
its intricate art-work.
It's very nice indeed.
But you could have given me
another gift instead of this.
It's such an expensive
and beautiful ashtray...
I'd hate to drop ash in it
when I smoke.
That's exactly why I got
this ashtray.
Because whenever you drop ash,
you must remember me.
And you must feel that
you're dropping ash...
not in the ashtray, but on me.
So you must give up smoking.
Karan quits smoking?
Ask me for anything else, and I'll
do it. But give up smoking? No way.
If you...
respect me...
you will give up smoking.
Happy?
For the exams.
I'm studying.
- That's not nice.
- What?
That which you're doing.
Reading a book is a nice thing.
In any case, it isn't porn.
It's a college book.
I'm not talking about
what you're reading.
I'm talking about the thing
you've been staring at.
Yes, I've been taking a good look.
Don't switch the topic.
You...
you were staring at my waist.
- Don't pretend! You were watching it!
- I didn't.
- You did too!
- I didn't, I say.
And I say you did. You did!
I caught you staring at it!
Well, maybe my eyes wandered
when I was turning a page.
But I didn't have any intentions.
You haven't been here a minute,
nor have you read a page...
- but you looked at it a dozen times!
- Now look, Khushi...
- you're mistaking me.
- What...? I'm making a mistake...
or was it you?
Remember all those things! When
I gave you Vicky's open letter...
when I told you about its contents,
what did you say?
One must never look at
other's private affairs.
You called me so many names!
Didn't you?
When I told you that he had hurt
his thumb and that I had written...
the letter for him,
you said sorry to me.
Didn't you?
Never mind that.
Let's talk about our first meeting.
When I gave you that letter
Vicky wanted delivered to Priya...
what conclusion did you jump to?
That I was giving you the letter.
You yelled so much at me.
Didn't you yell at me?
But when you got to know the truth...
you said sorry. Didn't you?
I know what you want.
You want everyone to praise your
beauty, to be crazy about you...
and say I love you to you.
And when someone does that...
you get worked up,
you kick up a fuss...
you start accusing him and say that
he's after girls. Isn't that right?
Talk about me...
not about other girls.
What do you know about
girls' psychology? What?
We don't pretend! I don't pretend!
But you do!
You do!
What did you do at the restaurant
the other day?
You deliberately dropped your spoon,
so you could use my spoon to eat!
You did put on an act then.
What were you hiding on?
The other day, you said your car had
broken down and that we'd have to walk.
And what did you ask me?
Whom did you like most?
You bored me to death!
And when your daddy come to the
college, you introduced everyone...
Why didn't you say it freely?
Why did you hesitate then?
What feelings were you hiding?
Oh sure, despite
knowing everything...
why've you been acting as
if you didn't know anything?
What will I take that for?
Despite knowing everything,
you gifted me an ashtray.
Okay, you gave that to me
as a friend.
But when I was talking to my Ma
the other day...
when I was showering kisses on her...
why did you badly
want to know the truth?
You calmed down only after you
got to know that Madhu's my Ma.
You presented me an ashtray.
All right, maybe that's friendship.
But the restlessness you showed
when you wanted to know about my Ma...
the streak of possessiveness you
showed, what do I take that for?
Let's not stray from the point.
Didn't you stare at my waist?
Haven't you loved me?
- No.
- I didn't stare either.
I happen to talk to a girl
and she finds faults with me!
I can't ever be friends
with an egoistic girl like her!
Even if we are friends,
it's never going to lead to love.
Even if we fall in love,
we'll never marry.
And even if we somehow
make it to the marriage altar...
I'll say that I can't marry a girl
like her and run away from there!
What a girl!
You have no right to
talk about my character.
I'll forget that I ever
met someone called Karan.
You and I have nothing
to do with each other.
She looks like a twin-sister
of our master.
Excuse me, you're not
our master's twin, are you?
Oh no. There are only
sisters in our family.
It's the master himself.
What disguise is this, Master?
What? People go to great lengths
to have an album released.
I've only changed my name.
From Madan to Badan Bhosle.
- So what's wrong?
- Name an album of yours, Master.
- Don't be stubborn, my love.
- How about humming the tune?
The tune? It's fantastic.
I've really worked hard on this song.
When it's released...
it's going to kick up a storm.
Want me to sing it for you?
♪ The bud of the night,
blossoms by day ♪
♪ She's mischievous...
she wanders everywhere ♪
♪ What else will I say? ♪
♪ Don't be stubborn, my love ♪
That's a number from Asha Bhosle's
hit album Jaanam Samjha Karo.
What nonsense!
That's the title of a movie!
The album of the same name was a hit,
but the film was shit.
- What's between you and me?
- That's for you to decide, sir.
I'll decide later. Now tell me
what do you mean to me?
- Your secretary, sir.
- And what's a secretary's job?
You must go out in the market and
find out which album is doing well...
and what the get up is...
so that they don't clash with ours.
What sorry?
- Well, sir...
- No wells! That's it.
- Want me to sing another song?
- Sure. Go ahead.
♪ What would I do,
if not die? ♪
♪ You're the chosen one
in thousands... ♪
♪ my love ♪
Do not be mistaken.
I haven't come here for a compromise.
Why? Is that wrong?
I don't want to...
with you...
I don't want any argument.
I have something important to say.
During the summer vacations
when we were not around...
a lot of things have taken place.
Vicky went to meet Priya at her place.
He mistook her father for her
and awakened him.
He was caught.
Priya's father is holding her
captive in the house.
- Did Vicky attend class?
- No
The love affair we promoted
is now facing problems.
I'm talking about Vicky
and Priya's love affair.
Did you meet Priya?
- I mean, have you?
- Yes.
I've come from her house right now.
She was crying.
I told her not to worry. To unite her
with Vicky is my duty, I promised her.
And you have promised your friend
to unite the two of them.
So, to honour the promise
I've made to my friend...
and for you to honour the promise
you've made to your friend, we must...
We must?
We must get together
and unite them.
We must... what I'm saying is that
...I want to make it clear.
In uniting them, the relationship
we are going to share...
is what I'll decide right now.
It will not be love, no friendship
and no relationship at all.
Our relationship will last as long
as they are united.
I hope you will do that.
That you will do it,
I am convinced.
What can I say now?
You've said what I wanted to.
Shall we go to meet Vicky?
You're the limit! You couldn't
wait for two months.
All I want to know is what you told
Priya's old man when you woke him up.
Priya darling, here I am?
Or was it...
Sorry, Uncle. Wrong number?
This is exactly why I tell you
not to fall in love!
Look at me. I'm such a happy man!
And why?
Because I'm not in love with someone!
And I don't have any problems like you.
Look at your face. You look like
the perfect jilted-lover.
To hide your pain and fake a laughter
is nothing but stupidity.
- What?
- I'm talking about Vicky's pain.
The one you're feeling too.
Will it solve the problem by
feeling the pain and crying? No.
Just concentrate on your studies,
Vicky. As for your love...
leave it to us. To unite you
with Priya is our responsibility.
Can't you trust my words?
All right.
But you do trust your love,
don't you? If your love is true...
it'll surely unite the two of you.
Am I right?
If our love is true,
it'll surely unite us.
- Yes.
- Yes, yes indeed
Where's the need to walk?
I'll drop you home.
You needn't necessarily be my
girlfriend for me to drop you home.
It doesn't need a relationship at all.
You could say...
you've taken a ride
in a stranger's car.
And I'll think I gave a ride
to a girl who was a stranger
If you still want to walk,
it's up to you.
What can I do about it?
I live in the hostel now.
Not in that flat.
To distance myself from some one,
I had to stay at the hostel.
I'll drop you at the hostel then.
♪ Two strangers,
where are they headed? ♪
♪ Where are they going? ♪
♪ Angry with each other... ♪
♪ they appear to be,
even as they drive on ♪
♪ Two strangers...
where are they headed? ♪
♪ Where are they going? ♪
♪ Angry with each other... ♪
♪ they appear to be,
even as they drive on ♪
♪ Awake... ♪
♪ asleep... ♪
♪ lost? ♪
♪ Ask them ♪
♪ Stop faking anger...
be friends again ♪
♪ Do not break each other's hearts,
that isn't a nice thing to do ♪
♪ From a distance... ♪
♪ up close... ♪
♪ they torment each other,
they go together ♪
♪ Desire, hatred... ♪
♪ what exactly do they
want in love? ♪
♪ Yes and no... ♪
♪ is all they say ♪
♪ What's in their hearts?
No one knows ♪
♪ Longing in their eyes,
to see each other... ♪
♪ they're afraid,
they go together ♪
♪ Two strangers...
where are they headed? ♪
♪ Where are they going? ♪
♪ Angry with each other... ♪
♪ they appear to be,
even as they drive on ♪
I haven’t done anything this time.
It has stalled on its own.
The wire of the spark-plug
has come off.
When a stranger drops me home,
I always thank him.
- That's a habit of mine.
- Nice habit too.
Because of my native tongue, you got
to know that I'm from the villages!
- You want to rob me?
- No, sir.
Thief! I asked you to take me
to Mumbai University and...
you've been taking me around Mumbai!
You've been driving
around the same place!
Forget it, sir.
It's human to err.
Looks like you're
hand in glove with him.
Please let him go, Uncle.
Come with me.
I'll give you a ride.
You don't appear to be a cabbie.
Why will you give me a ride?
He's the one who'll take me there.
You go on.
Until you leave, no one else
will be able to move from here.
The traffic's come to a standstill
because of you.
I study at the Bombay University too.
Come with me, I'll take you there.
You take me to be an idiot?
The moron!
Son, how do you live in this city?
Everyone here appears to be
a fraud to me.
But you're a nice boy.
Guess what I like most about you?
Your smile.
- Do you know my daughter?
- Who?
How would you know her? There must
be so many girls in the college.
- There's this hostel near the college.
- Which hostel?
Now what is the name?
Mary...
Right, St Mary's Girls Hostel!
- Do you know where the hostel is?
- Know?
- I can't ever forget that hostel.
- Why?
There's this girl I know
who stays there.
She's no ordinary girl, mind you.
She has a massive ego.
- What?
- Ego.
- Meaning?
- Ego meaning...
she thinks she's the last word.
Even when she knows she's wrong,
she'll never say sorry.
This damn ego...
how will I explain it?
This girl...
she's stubborn, a bit eccentric...
I get it. That daughter
of an ass is arrogant.
Yes, arrogant!
I wanted to tell you about the girl,
but you've spoken about her family!
She's just a girl, you know.
If she can be so arrogant...
- am I any less?
- Oh yes
Oh yes!
- That's the block.
- Thank you very much
I live in Chamoli, son. If you ever
visit the place, do meet me.
See you.
Lali! My child!
- How are you?
- I'm fine
- Why're you so late?
- What will I tell you?
On my way, I got into
a fight with a cabbie.
It was a terrible fight and
this nice boy really helped me.
He... one moment!
Hello son... hello!
Come here.
Lali, come here.
As I was telling you, I got into
a fight with a crazy cabbie.
And a decent boy came along
and helped me. He's the one.
This is my daughter, Lali.
- Have some coffee before you leave.
- Thanks, but I've got to go.
Oh no. Back in the village, we don't
let a guest go away without...
extending our hospitality. If you
leave without having coffee...
I'm going to feel bad.
Tell him to stay, dear.
Please have some coffee.
- I'll go and lock my car.
- All right. Let's go.
- I don't want to get married.
- Why not?
When you wanted to study further,
I agreed with you.
And now that I want you to get
married, you must listen to me.
Come, son.
Have some coffee.
- I just don't agree!
- Why not?
Look at her, son.
She's not listening to me.
- You must listen to Papa, mustn't you?
- Do you know what he's saying?
And this is between the two of us.
You aren't interfering.
You'll get a slap, Lali.
He's a guest...
is that how you talk to a guest?
What wrong have I said, son?
I'm looking for a groom for her
and she's refusing me.
When a girl keeps refusing to get
married, what does it mean?
It means there is someone else
she loves.
I'm not against that. All I want
is for you to have a nice wedding.
But how should the suitor be?
He must be just like this boy.
Clean-hearted, innocent eyes...
a handsome young man.
If there is someone you love,
tell me about it.
I'm not in love with anyone.
If you really don't love anyone,
you must obey your Papa.
- Papa, I'm willing to get married.
- Wow!
This is amazing!
I've been trying for so long
and she just wouldn't agree.
You spoke to her just once
and viola! She agreed!
Looks like we share the
same birth-sign, son.
I had a problem with the cabbie
and you solved.
And this problem of her marriage
you have solved too.
I'm happy to have achieved
what I set out to do.
Lali, I'm leaving by this
evening's train.
Do look after yourself, okay?
Come on... drop me on the way
Lali, I forgot to tell you
something very important.
There's a girl he knows
who stays here.
They have a fight going
between themselves.
- Never mind, Uncle. Please...
- Now wait a moment.
Won't I do anything for all the help
you've extended to me?
What will people say?
She's a very arrogant girl, Lali.
As he said, she's very stubborn too.
Not just stubborn, she's...
a bit mental, eko...
what word did you use?
- Never mind, Uncle. Forget it...
- Give me the word! What was it?
Yes! Ego!
She's possessed by ego!
Like spirits taking possession
of people's bodies...
this girl is possessed with ego!
Ask the girl not to
fight with him, dear.
He's a very nice boy. Even my Papa
believes he's a very nice boy.
Bring the two of them together.
Okay?
Will that be enough or do you want me
to stay over for your help, son?
No thank you, Uncle.
You've done so much!
That's all right...
See you.
She's a fool to get into a fight
with a nice boy like you.
It isn't her fault. It must be
her father who...
has really pampered
the arrogant girl.
What has come to be?
And why?
Don't think about it...
Think, how could that girl blow such
a little thing out of proportion?
I can't get this. This little part
of the female anatomy...
- Don't remind me, please!
- Everyone gets to look at it.
What went wrong if you looked at it?
In Mumbai, girls expose their legs.
This is just what
I can't understand!
Your friend Shibu has come all the
way from Kolkata to solve your problem.
And I'll solve it too.
Look at this. Once this goes in,
your woes will vanish.
No thanks. I don't drink.
I don't want it.
Drink it up... listen to me.
Just a little... come on.
Fun?
I'll now sing a hit song for you.
You'll find happiness.
Shut up! You make me sadder!
Drink some more. The more you drink,
the more your problems will vanish.
You didn't approve of the
Bengali song, did you?
I'll sing a song from Mumbai
for you.
♪ Everyone wants a slender waist ♪
♪ If only your heart
could win over the waist ♪
Fun, wasn't it?
The song's over, so is the booze.
You have a smoke...
I'll get lots of booze.
When you drop ash in this ashtray
you must know it's not the ashtray...
- but me it's falling on.
- Oh yes!
What are you staring at?
This way.
This way... look here.
What?
What are you staring at
with your big...
no, with your two small eyes.
What are you looking at?
All I did was to look
at this little waist.
Who do you think you are?
You're very beautiful?
Your face is like a chameleon's,
a pencil-thin nose...
and your body?
It's all right.
Your waist is the only thing
one can look at.
This little waist.
Draped in a black sari,
that little area...
is like a lemon.
No, lemons are yellow.
In reds and yellows, if it's shown up
in a romantic light...
naturally, I will look at it.
If you mind...
you mustn't show it at all.
Just as your face is a part
of your body, so is your waist.
I look at your face, you don't mind.
I see the waist, you mind. What for?
Tell me, darling. Speak.
Not just your body, I'm going to
take a look at your whole body now.
You have no right to
stand there before me!
You have no right to touch it!
I came here to discuss
something important with you.
But neither are you in the mood to
listen, nor am I in the mood to tell.
Khushi, I've done nothing.
It's my Bengali friend.
He forced me to drink.
If people smoke and drink,
why must I care?
It isn't necessary for me
to know why you had liquor.
Want some?
I came here because I thought
you were a nice human being.
But you're worse than
I could ever imagine.
If you'd listen...
♪ You're a performer... ♪
♪ you can't make me dance ♪
♪ When it's your turn... ♪
♪ you'll beat a hasty retreat ♪
- Master, that's Altaf Raja's tune.
- Altaf Raja? A foreigner?
He's a famous qawwal. This is
a tune from his famous album.
- How's that possible?
- It is.
You must've heard the tune
and pinched it
- But this is a three-year old tune.
- What a thief!
I composed the tune three days ago,
and he stole it three years back!
No more qawwali for me!
How did you know it's Priya
without even looking at her?
The fragrance! I can tell every
beautiful girl from her fragrance.
Where's this stink coming from?
Lay off!
You like my wig, don't you?
Here you are.
Remember, the cultural programme at
the college is fast approaching?
Join Karan immediately
and start your rehearsals.
- No, Master.
- Why?
- I can't participate in this function.
- Why not?
I've told you. I'm not participating.
Mukesh, make a team of Karan and Roma
and send them on the stage.
You have my blessings!
- Who's Roma?
- You don't know Roma? Roma!
A new student in the first year!
She's kicked up a storm in the college.
The students are crazy about her
and go around her like blind men.
What for?
Could you help me cross the road?
- You've crossed the road.
- Small road.
- What?
- You've helped a blind man.
Thank you so much.
You are large-hearted.
Slipped out of my hands! Damn it!
- What is the matter?
- Priya has sent a letter.
- You can give it to Vicky.
- It's not for him.
- Is it for me?
- No.
- It must be for you then.
- If not for me, you nor Vicky...
- It's for the two of us!
You read it.
I love Vicky so dearly...
I don't think anyone in
the world loves anyone as much.
You must think why every lover
in the world says that.
It's because they have
true love for each other.
And the suffering of separation
those truly in love go through...
only I know about.
I'm pining to meet Vicky.
Please bring us together.
Yours, Priya.
What are we to do now?
Priya has a friend called
Shehnaz, right?
- How are you, Rukhsana?
- I'm fine.
Be careful, Vicky.
The two of you chat,
I'm going to bed.
Who's this girl?
It's Shabana.
Shehnaz's friend.
Is she coming here
for the first time?
Yes.
I see. Go ahead and
chat with Rukhsana...
I'll take Shabana around the house.
- Come on, Shabana.
- Run away, Vicky!
Car number 906.
Is it yours?
- Yes.
- Karan?
Let me do it.
- How are you related to the girl?
- I...
- Help me with the injection.
- All right.
In the waist.
- Give it to her in the arm.
- This is meant for the waist.
- No, give it to her in the arm.
- The one for the arm...
is given in the arm, the one
for the waist is given in the waist.
You don't know anything
about this waist, doctor.
This waist has caused
a very big problem already.
If I go into details,
it'll take at least 2 hours.
Your duty hours will be over
and when the next doctor comes...
I'll have to explain to him!
Have mercy on me...
and give it to her in the arm.
That's all right!
You can give it wherever you wish.
Give it to anyone. To her,
the nurse or yourself...
I've seen nothing,
I will see nothing.
God, why did You make
this waist? Why?
♪ My heart, my love... ♪
♪ I've given to you ♪
♪ My love... ♪
♪ what have you done? ♪
♪ When our gaze met,
I realised... ♪
♪ I'm crazy about you ♪
♪ It's something my heart knows ♪
♪ You're the one
I've taken for my beloved ♪
♪ On your lips, is a smile.
Your eyes hold an intoxication ♪
♪ The sight of you
makes my heart sway ♪
♪ I love you all day and night.
I find peace only after meeting you ♪
♪ Your dark tressses
lend a fragrance to my being ♪
♪ All I wish to say is that
it's your arms I must stay in ♪
♪ Don't ever forget
this promise ♪
♪ Don't make me cry,
now that you make me smile ♪
♪ Don't make excuses... ♪
♪ don't ever hide
anything from me ♪
♪ My heart, my love... ♪
♪ I've given to you ♪
♪ My dream, my desire... ♪
♪ is to adorn your arms
with bridal bangles ♪
♪ These lovely meetings,
I love the way you talk... ♪
♪ Should you consent, my love... ♪
♪ I'd bring the bridal palanquin
to your house ♪
♪ I spend my nights pining.
I dream of marriage ♪
♪ My world of love,
you must embellish... ♪
♪ never leave me ever ♪
♪ Keep your promises ♪
♪ Always hold me in your arms ♪
♪ My heart, my love... ♪
♪ I've given to you ♪
♪ My love... ♪
♪ what have you done? ♪
What is it? What?
I tried several times to
meet you at your office.
But you staff wouldn't let me.
So...
My name is Karan.
Vicky's my friend, sir.
His past is nothing...
at present, he's a student
and he has a very bright future.
You don't know that,
but I do.
At my age, my father was
even worse off than Vicky is.
At this age, even you...
don't take offense.
You used to be a small-time thug.
But I tell you, at your age...
Vicky will be far ahead of you,
me and even my father.
Apart from all this,
he has a very kind heart.
When a boy falls in love
with a girl...
and he finds the girl
without any problem...
imagine how happy it'll make him.
Please don't separate them.
Please unite them.
Your two minutes are up.
Let's go, Gotya.
Did he have nothing to say?
Your two minutes are up, he said.
And left.
All right.
Even if he said nothing...
couldn't you guess
what was on his mind?
- What?
- I ask...
couldn't you guess
what was on his mind?
If one knew what's on everyone's mind,
there wouldn't be any problem at all.
We have these problems
because we don't know.
- What do you mean by these problems?
- These problems. Period.
All right. I must leave now.
Did you call?
Yes.
What for?
- To talk.
- That's what we've been doing.
No, there's something else
I want to talk about.
What is it about?
She knows... why must she
ask what it's about.
The arrogant one!
It's about what you think.
I'm thinking about nothing.
You wanted to talk to me.
So tell me what you want to.
- Is that what you called me to say?
- Yes.
Your intoxicating eyes...
your lips...
there's a huge list
I have of you.
Roma, can you fall in love with me?
Can you really like me?
However...
the possibility of me
falling in love with you...
- does exist.
- Thanks
I don't you well, you see.
Let's see each other for a few days...
and then I'll decide about it.
It'll take a bit of time, okay?
What's a bit... take all the time.
All my time is now yours.
I feel as if something is
stirred in my heart for you.
Your lovely tresses...
your rose-like lips...
and this lovely neck and...
I'm not calling you because
you have a girl in your arms.
Neither have I called you because
you're drawing pictures on her body.
I haven't called out
to disturb you.
We've got to be at Priya's place
at 7:30. You remember that?
- Karan, who's she? A friend?
- A friend? Oh no, no chance at all.
- Is she a lover then?
- Lover? How disgusting!
To be my lover,
a girl needs extra qualities.
So who's she?
She's Khushi. There's nothing else
I know about her.
Karan, just 15 minutes to go
for 7:30. May we leave now?
- When will you meet me again?
- Again?
- At lunch?
- Not lunch. At dinner.
At night. Candle-light.
Sunday 10, at my place.
Shall we?
Today's Sunday.
So?
It was you who said it...
Yes, I did, but...
Whoever you are with,
why must I care?
Sorry, I'm late.
- What happened?
- Last night... nothing.
- What did Priya have to say?
- She says forget it.
- Forget what?
- Love.
- Whose love?
- The love Vicky had for Priya.
Priya asks to forget it.
And what did you tell her?
When she herself isn't interested,
what can I do?
What is it with girls? Flirt when you
want to, dump the guy when you wish.
Have you girls ever considered
what it does to us guys?
You're acting like
a very decent guy?
Do you think I don't know
the truth about you?
Were you breathing heavily
last night, or weren't you?
What?
Were you breathing last night,
or weren't you?
Breathing? I was breathing last night
and the night before that too.
And I breathe every day...
and well at that.
It's good for the health.
Is it bad to breathe?
Maybe it's bad to look at this...
but why's it bad to breathe?
How will man live
if he doesn't breathe?
Am I the only one who breathes?
Everyone does. Every single day.
Your parents do, so do mine.
Because they breathe...
you are here, I am here...
so's the dog.
He breathes every day.
Nicely at that. Right puppy?
See? If you call that bad,
what can I do?
The breathing I spoke about is
different from the one you allude to.
It's all the same. If breathing
is wrong, everything is wrong.
I'll leave if you talk like this.
I know the suffering of one
truly in love.
Priya's words, weren't they?
So how can she ask us to forget it?
What does it mean?
We have to talk.
Today's the last day at college.
It's time to separate.
So come forth and take my blessings.
You been in a crowded train?
So many of them have
gone into coma for you.
I'm in a coma too. Embrace me
and revive me from the coma, Roma.
Priya's wedding has been fixed.
What are we to do?
Greetings.
Mr Zorawar Singh... over here.
Where are you going?
To fetch your daughter?
She's with us right now.
She's marrying the man she loves.
From the look of it, it appears
as if you want to give me a thrashing.
Don't even think of it.
Pray to God...
that I come to no harm.
If something happens to me...
you'll be the guilty one
in the eyes of the law.
I've made arrangements, you know.
You're picking up something
to throw at me.
Forget me...
you can't even touch my image.
Spend a month in Mahabaleshwar
before you return to Calcutta.
Dad has found a job for you
over there. Okay?
Spend your lives together.
Be happy.
There are problems between
you and Khushi, isn't it?
You know why man faces problems?
Because he hides his feelings.
If you speak your heart,
you face no problems.
But I don't know why man
doesn't understand that.
He loves someone,
but he pretends to hate her.
He hates someone and he pretends
to love her. What for?
Poor heart. Why do we burden
it with a thousand worries...
and make life unbearable for it?
If you love her...
tell her that you love her,
or tell her that you don't.
God has given you eyes to see,
ears to hear...
and a heart to love.
So forget about egoes
and fall in love.
Love each other.
I've told you how I feel.
You've been a great help in uniting
my friend with his beloved.
Thanks to you too. In uniting
my friend with her beloved...
you've been a great help.
Thank you.
This is Seema here.
- I'm leaving today.
- Okay.
- I'm leaving and you're just...
- I have another tension, Seema.
Sir, the taxi has arrived.
- Karan?
- He has left for VT Station.
- Which train is it?
- Howrah Mail at 7:15.
- Is Khushi there?
- She has left.
- Where to?
- Bombay Central.
- Which train?
- Golden Temple Express at 7:10.
- Karan?
- No one has arrived yet.
- Was there a girl called Khushi here?
- There's no one.
Maybe he has gone to
Mumbai Central to meet me.
Maybe she has gone to
VT Station to meet me.
And what if he hasn't?
Now?
A girl called Khushi will come here.
Please give her this letter.
A boy called Karan will come here.
Please give him this.
- Karan?
- Yes?
I've been wanting to tell you
something for a very long time.
You know?
I love you, Khushi.
When we were together,
this is what I wanted to say...
but I never could,
I don't know why.
And now that I want to speak,
you are not with me.
We said so much to each other
when we fought...
but we couldn't say one single word
to get together. I'm sorry, Khushi
When I freed my hand from yours
after thanking you...
I felt something strange
stir in my heart.
I don't know what it was.
But I need you, Karan.
I now realise that the fights
we had was all part of our love.
I need you, Khushi.
To love me, to fight with me.
You're a lucky girl to have
found a father like yours.
Ever since you agreed
to the wedding...
all he has done is to
look out for suitors.
He decided to have Lali married
the day she returned from the city.
Everything is ready.
The bridegroom, the garland...
step forward and be garlanded.
Lali! My child!
You're back! Welcome!
- Go and get ready quickly.
- But Papa...
Just don't worry, my little girl.
The boy I've chosen this time...
is neither running away
nor leaving behind letters...
and he's not in love with
another girl either
Why're you chanting Papa?
Go and get dressed quickly.
Coming!
Lali, take a look
at your bridegroom.
Take a look at him.
You left this note for him
in the train...
and he turned out to be
faster than you.
He halted the train and
took a flight to get here.
He has told me everything.
Karan's parents will also be
coming here for the wedding.
Are you happy now.
This is how two hearts met
and accepted each other.
They're celebrating their
ninth anniversary.
and they're still fighting
What is surprising is that.
they haven't one or two kids
they have 17 children in 8 years.
Twins every year But how
does it still add up to 17.
Confusing, isn't it.
They didn't fight for a year.
and they had triplets.
Khushi's expecting again.
Twins or triplets I don't know.
I'm just looking on
and praying for them.
May Karan keep giving Khushi
this happiness all her life.
Thanks Rohit for DVD English Subtitles
Subtitle re-synced and edited by -Haxxor-