'There are millions of clusters
of stars in the universe...'
'That are called galaxies.'
'The galaxy our world belongs to...'
'Is called the Milky Way.'
'My husband who was
a space scientist used to say...'
'There are innumerable galaxies
like the Milky Way...'
'And somewhere some planet
could possibly have life.'
'He had only one goal, to search
for life on other planets.'
'He'd made various
kinds of gadgets.'
'He used them to gather data.'
'He'd send sound signals to space.'
'He believed the voice never dies.'
'The message moves in space
in the form of waves.'
'He was convinced
that in some other world...'
'Somebody would someday
hear his sound signals.'
'And will respond to him.'
'One evening...'
'Sending'
'Receiving'
Sonia!
'Sending'
'Receiving'
Sonia!
- Coming.
What is the matter?
- Take a look at this.
They are responding.
But...
These sounds?
I made a pattern
using the word OM.
I converted this pattern
digitally on the computer...
And sent sound signals into space.
And somebody from
another planet is responding.
I've succeeded!
I've achieved a breakthrough!
We must inform the space centre.
So Dr Mehra, did they talk to you?
So did they say, hello?
And asked you how was
the weather on earth?
I'm sorry, sir.
But this isn't a joke.
Dr Mehra, do you see
this research centre?
We've been working on this for years.
And they contacted you?
How is that possible?
- Why not?
I too have spent my entire
life on this research.
I've sent varied sound waves.
Invented varied sound instruments.
After multiple experiments...
When I sent OM in diverse
notes and variations...
It is possible...
What is this OM
he's talking about?
OM is a Hindu religious word...
Which has all the
vibrations of the universe.
Oh! So they believe in
your religion as well!
Listen, Dr Mehra,
daydreaming is a very bad habit.
Believe me, Sir.
I can prove it to you.
You are wasting our time, Dr Mehra.
Please go home.
They say, daydreaming is
a bad habit. Go home and sleep.
Don't they know, every
discovery is initially a dream?
Sanjay, don't be discouraged.
The world rejects every new idea.
Then they accept it.
This will happen with us too.
Sanjay, is it possible...
Another world of this galaxy
which is millions of miles away...
Will ever contact us?
Why not? We went to the moon.
Sent out space shuttles.
Similarly they want
to know about us.
That is why UFOs are often sighted.
Why are the lights
switching on and off?
What is happening?
Sanjay, look at that.
UFO!
I can't believe it!
They didn't believe me
but they've come. Hey!
No!
In one moment, all my dreams
were shattered.
The man looking for other worlds
moved on to the next one.
After his death,
I had no support in Canada.
Rohit too was very young,
so I came back home here.
Mrs Mehra, I have understood
the entire case history.
These are the X-rays
of Rohit's brain.
Do you see these?
These white spots?
It's called gliosis.
It is formed when
the brain is hurt.
But nothing of that sort
ever happened with Rohit.
It did occur, Mrs Mehra,
when you met with the accident.
You fell on your belly and
the baby's brain was hurt.
He was in your womb and this
part of his head was damaged.
This is the reason that
his mental growth isn't normal.
And he is weak in studies.
He is 8 but has
the brain of a 2 year old.
I'm afraid, his mental age will
always lag behind his physical age.
But Doctor, there must be a cure.
There is a cure. Brain operation.
But...
- But what?
There are very few chances
of success in this case.
If the operation fails,
his body will be paralysed.
Or even death!
No, I've lost all I had.
I have nothing
but Rohit in my life.
I can't lose him.
'He is 8 but has
the brain of a 2 year old.'
'His mental age will always
lag behind his physical age.'
Rohit!
- Sorry, uncle Sukhwani.
You keep breaking my window panes
with your ball.
This is my last warning!
One more pane breaks and
I'll have you locked up!
Sorry, my foot! Shameless!
Rohit!
What did I ever do to you?
You broke my window pane again!
- I did but I also apologise.
Are you doing me
a favour by saying sorry?
I've been listening to
your apologies all these years!
This time I won't spare you!
I'm coming down!
Now what?
- Don't be scared.
Let him come.
Dear God, look at this state!
Broke the panes on top and bottom.
Sunlight and rain enter in.
Dust and dirt in and I'm out!
Don't worry, uncle.
When I grow up, I'll fix it up.
Great? How much more will you grow?
You're already as tall as a tree!
Will you grow as tall
as the Eiffel Tower?
Don't insult our friend.
We'll fix all your panes.
- Then do it!
First give me Rs 500.
- What? Rs 500?
Why? - To buy new glass.
Give us the cash.
Yes, pay up.
Asking me for cash!
Run or I'll beat you up!
Blackmailing me!
Rohit, hurry up.
You'll be late for school.
Today is an important day.
I'm going to a new class.
Seventh standard.
God, take care of me.
Please dear, God.
Did you never go to school?
You don't take old
books to a new class.
I'll get new books
in the seventh standard.
You're not going to the 7th.
- Why?
My friends are going.
You failed.
I failed again!
Yes.
I'll never go to school. Never!
The teacher is very bad.
I study so hard!
Yet he fails me.
He passed all the others.
I won't go! Why should I go?
I won't go!
Study harder this year.
You will pass.
No.
New boys will come to my class.
Once again they'll tease me.
They'll poke fun at me.
Call me tall bloke and names.
So I won't go to school.
I don't want the books!
How can you say that?
Promoting Rohit to
the 7th standard is impossible.
In fact, he shouldn't
be studying in this school.
There are special schools
for such children.
But there's no such
school in this city.
I'm trying to get a
transfer to Delhi.
Delhi has special schools
for children like Rohit.
The chairman of the bank
I work for has promised me.
Sir, it's a matter of a year.
Please?
Do me one last favour.
Teachers don't do
favours for children.
Promoting him in this way
won't help him at all.
Father, I know Rohit can never
become what I want him to...
Or what his dad wanted for him.
But for his happiness...
Please.
For his smile...
Okay, Mrs Mehra.
This is the last time.
Yes, boys?
If X = 12
and Y = 8,
How much is X + 3Y?
Solve it in your answer books.
Sir?
Yes, Rohit.
What is X + 3Y =?
Show me your answer.
Very good.
You are right.
- Really, sir?
But the next time, you should
be the first to raise your hand.
"When I see the flight of birds
flying high..."
"I dream of touching the sky."
"With our feet rooted,
our dreams will take us high."
Train!
"Tell me, how we will go there
without wings?"
"Anything is possible,
anything can happen."
"All you should do is
trust yourself."
"Tell me, how will we go
there without any wings?"
"Anything is possible.
Anything can happen."
"All you should do is
trust yourself."
"Believe me, one
day you will see..."
"Will only be my day."
"Everybody in the world
would want to be my friend."
"Believe me, one
day you will see..."
"Will only be your day."
"Everybody in the world
would want to be my friend."
"Your life will be
filled with all the happiness."
"One day, your life will change."
"The sky will be the limit
to your success."
"There'll be none like you here."
"When I see the flight of birds
flying high,"
"I dream of touching the sky."
"With our feet rooted,
our dreams will take us high."
"Our dreams will take us high."
Why are you shaking your head?
You're 6 feet tall and hanging out
with these little kids.
Have you no shame? Move aside.
We came here first.
- Yes.
We'll go first. Move your bikes.
Fool, our bikes don't
have reverse gears.
Shall we fit them?
You'll only be going in reverse.
He's started talking too much.
These dogs are barking too much.
Let's give them a shot today.
Formula number?
- 320.
Catch him!
Take this!
'STOP'
Move aside!
Good morning.
If you don't mind,
may I ask where you're rushing?
Driving in a No Entry road.
Are you crazy?
Sir, he threw down
our bikes and ran away.
That's no excuse
to break traffic rules.
Write them a receipt.
- Yes, sir.
Excuse me, sir?
You're probably
not aware of who I am.
You're the son of the
Collector Harbans Saxena.
Charge him with a double fine,
and print
this news in the local daily.
Everyone must know
when Inspector Khan is in charge...
Nobody can break the law.
Whether he's the collector's son
or the collector himself.
I hope you've got the message.
Good day.
Colonel, come out!
Harbans, you fool!
Never saw a bigger duffer than you!
You didn't come to
the station to receive me!
There can be no bigger idiot
than you in the world!
You sent a fax that you're coming.
But how and when?
Idiot, where to receive you?
- Show some consideration.
Guests aren't welcomed with abuse.
This guy is just too stupid.
Now he's standing still. Hug me.
My pal, nice to meet you.
He came here after retirement
to spend his life with his pal.
The friendship will be
celebrated for a whole year.
Starting with a grand party
at my house tonight.
Thank you, Harbans.
Take a seat.
- Yes.
Lost in catching up with you,
I forgot the most important thing.
What is it?
- Where is my little doll?
Your little doll has now grown up.
Is it?
But where is she?
Hello!
Hello! Hello!
Why are you late?
We'd have missed the bus.
I'm not late.
The bus will come after 5 minutes.
The film is 3 ½ hours long.
That long!
- Long films are in fashion.
The bus is here!
- Run!
Stop the Bus!
Run!
Run! Hurry!
Stop!
- Darn! We missed the bus!
Missed the bus and
film holiday ruined.
Excuse me?
- Yes, please?
I'm new to this city. Can you
tell me where Shanti Villa is?
Yes, it is...
- It's this way.
But Shanti Villa is...
- Empty jeep!
The girl seems naive,
she'll be of use to us.
Oh!
- Yes!
We'll take you there.
- Let's go.
Great.
Hurrah! Get in, everyone.
Hurrah!
- Hurry!
Come on, let's go.
- Thank you.
So sweet of you all.
- Very sweet.
My name is Nisha. What's yours?
Right.
- Right?
Turn Right!
- Go right!
What places are worth seeing here?
Many. - Sunset point,
China Beach, Chidiya Ghar.
Lal Bazaar.
- Tea Garden.
I mean the night life.
What do people do at night?
They sleep.
Good sense of humour.
Seriously.
Isn't there a night club or disco?
There is but kids aren't allowed.
Yes.
- Kids?
Go left!
- Left.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
- Stop!
We are there.
Get off!
- Hurry!
Hurry!
- Hey!
I don't see Shanti Villa.
- This is a cinema house.
Cinema?
But I want to go to...
- Yes, we know.
You want to go to Shanti Villa.
- Yes.
But we wanted to see the theatre.
Shanti Villa isn't far.
- First right then left...
Followed by right
and left and left.
There comes Shanti Villa.
So you wanted a lift.
Yes, aunty!
- Yes, aunty!
Aunty?
- Thank you, aunty.
You ought to be ashamed!
You fool people with these kids!
And you laugh!
- Not at you.
I'm laughing at your nose
which wobbles when you yell.
Like air rushing out of a balloon!
Let's go.
Bye!
- How dare you?
You shouldn't have done that.
You should help if somebody
asks for help, not fool them.
We'd have missed the film.
- I read the Gita to you.
What did I say? God always
helps those who help others.
Didn't I say that?
- Yes, you did.
I'd forgotten.
Promise, you'll apologise to
the girl when you see her next.
You'll say sorry.
- Okay.
Mother, what's this?
It's a computer your father made.
Dad made a computer!
- Yes.
Through the computer
and instruments he made...
He'd talk to people living
far away on the stars.
Do people live on the stars?
Yes.
Mother, I can't see them.
There are many things
that can't be seen.
But they exist.
What?
- Party.
Isn't that true?
Too good!
Amazing!
Even today, your jokes are funny.
Hasn't anything changed
in all these years?
It has. Look at Raj.
He was little and now he's so tall.
I'm sure somebody pulled his legs.
Hey! Look who is talking.
Even she used to be little and fat.
Always crying, mummy!
- Hey, what rubbish! Raj!
You've met after years
and are still fighting.
Come on, mom.
Fights bring us closer.
Right?
- Right.
Wow.
That is Rahul.
- Hey Rahul!
Hi.
- That's Monty.
Hello.
That's Kimi.
- Hi.
Girlfriend?
- No. Only a friend.
Man will sing praise of God
if he gets food on time.
Great. Pour some more.
Let's go.
It's the age to eat. I see chicken
but where's the 'papad'?
Excuse me?
- There's a queue.
I'll come back later.
- Take this.
Wow.
Is this mutton?
- Yes.
I eat it. Serve me more.
More. That's it.
- Give us some food.
You took a plate full.
- That's gone down.
Where?
- Here.
Good God.
What a belly.
- Serve this.
300 million in our country live
under the poverty line.
They don't get to see
a handful of rice.
And you eat 2 plates!
Does it pinch your pocket?
That is true.
- Serve some more.
Bittu, I want more.
- Hold on.
Holy smoke! Run! - I think
we should just let the boys drink.
I'm famished.
- Yes.
Bittu?
Pass some food!
You?
- Holy smoke!
Oh my God!
Somebody apprehend him!
Catch him!
Ah!
Stupid. Idiot.
What does he think of himself?
Ruined my hair!
Let me get my hands on him...
I won't spare him!
Hey! Rohit!
What are you doing?
What are you stealing?
No, I was saying sorry.
What?
- See how he says sorry.
Sticking gum to the seat.
No.
- Oh!
Sticking gum.
Raj? Raj!
He's the same boy.
He's the boy!
Scoundrel! Acting too smart!
First you mess with us.
Now you tease girls.
He's the boy who took me
to the movie hall instead of home.
He even threw food on my head!
That's nothing. Your hair
would be cut if he succeeded.
Look at the chewing gum!
My God! Such an innocent
face and so roguish!
He should be handed to the police!
No point handing him to
the police for a minor thing.
We'll let him go.
Raj, what do you say?
Run.
Go on.
Why are you letting him go?
He should be taught a lesson.
Don't beat me. I was telling the
truth. I only wanted to apologise.
Champion of the scooter?
Actually, Nisha,
that mad guy can't be blamed.
Anyone could lose
their sanity looking at you.
Really? Trying to flirt?
No but sometimes
the truth does slip out.
Now he won't mess up.
He's got punished severely.
Well, he deserves that.
No. He deserves to be amongst you.
He deserves to
be educated like you.
He deserves to be blessed
with an adult mind like you all.
But my son isn't like you.
Because God didn't
make him like you.
He is grown up
but has the mind of a child.
An innocent child.
Who doesn't know the difference
between good and bad.
You thrashed him black and blue.
You broke his scooter.
Assuming he's teasing a girl!
He'd come to apologise not
tease or trouble you.
Look at this.
He came to apologise to you!
Anyway, I can't complain to you.
Because you're new to the city.
But Raj knows everything.
Once he too was in Rohit's class.
He went ahead because he's normal.
But my son remained there.
But you know something?
I have no regrets about it.
No regrets at all.
If normal people are like you
then I am glad...
That my son Rohit is abnormal.
I am happy!
'Sorry, Rohit!'
Good morning, brother.
- Good morning.
Rohit?
What are you doing in
computer class?
Sir, he's taken computers
as the optional class.
Shut up.
Sit in your seat.
Sir, I too want to learn computers.
You need brains to
learn about computers.
You're so clever that
you're still in the 7th.
My dad was a great scientist.
He had a computer!
I want to be like dad.
- Then learn from your dad!
He's not in this world.
Then learn in the world he is!
Don't chew my brains! Get out!
Get out!
A1 cycle!
Mother!
Did you get this cycle for me?
- Yes.
Thank you, it's great. A1!
Thank you, mother.
Thank her. She got it for you.
I won't say thank you or sorry.
I don't want the cycle.
Rohit.
See that?
It's true that I was wrong.
But how was I to know you wanted
to apologise not make mischief?
Forget what happened.
Now let me apologise to you.
Sorry.
Not me alone but Raj, Monty
and the others too will say sorry.
Henceforth nobody will trouble you.
What if somebody does?
- We'll beat them up together.
Goodness! You too?
- Yes.
We're now friends.
- Really?
Truly!
Friend's!
Sorry.
It's okay.
All of you must apologise to Rohit.
So sweet.
- Sorry Rohit.
Sorry.
- Hi Rohit.
Hi.
- Sorry Rohit.
It's okay.
What did I tell you?
Now are you happy?
Hear me out, everyone.
Henceforth, no fights or mischief.
Only friendship.
Hey come, Nisha. Let's dance.
Be a moment, Rohit.
Rohit, let's go and dance.
I don't know how to dance.
- There's nothing to it.
Hold the body like
this and move to the music.
No, I'm scared.
There's nothing to fear.
I'll teach you.
I never learnt it.
- You're breaking in sweat.
Yes, a little.
Have a coke.
One coke.
Here, this will get rid of
the fear and the sweat.
Now I'm fine.
- Just a little.
It's horrid. Don't want it.
- It's nice. Have it.
Drink it. Then we'll dance.
What nonsense is this?
You're giving him alcohol!
- A little Bacardi won't hurt.
He's no kid.
- What did I tell you?
Don't trouble Rohit but you...
Shame on you guys!
Let's go.
Rohit?
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where am I
heading to."
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where am I
heading to."
"Oh, I tripped!"
"What have you done?"
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where am I
heading to."
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where am I going."
"Oh, I tripped!"
"Just like you did."
"Who has cast a spell on us?"
"Is that why we tripped
while walking?"
"What changed all of a sudden
while we were laughing?"
"Who has cast a spell on us?"
"Is this why we slipped?"
"What changed all of sudden
while we were laughing?"
"Why did we change?"
"We just did."
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where I'm going."
"Oh, I tripped!"
"What have you done?"
"Why are you so innocent?"
"You are saying that
because you're so nice."
"Why do you say that I'm nice?"
"Why do I tell you that?"
"Why are you so innocent?"
"You are saying that
because you're so nice."
"Tell me why am I nice."
"Why should I tell you?"
"Tell me something at least."
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where am I
heading to."
"Oh, I tripped!"
"Just like you did."
"I stagger when I go here and
I stagger when I go there."
"I don't know where I'm going."
"Oh, I tripped!"
"What have you done?"
"I tripped just like you did."
"I did too,
while walking with you."
Mr. Sukhwani.
- What is it?
Yes?
- What madness is this?
Your son is responsible for it.
I've got accustomed to living in
a house with broken panes.
Wind, water, I had everything.
Even sunlight.
Since I fixed the panes...
I feel suffocated.
But why do you have
to break the glass?
You could've opened the window.
The thought never struck me.
That's a good idea. Shame on me.
I'm the first Sindhi
who made a loss for himself.
Really?
- Yes, Nisha is your girlfriend.
How?
She gave you a cycle.
- Yes.
And took you to the disco.
- Yes and danced with me.
Then she took you home and said,
good night, Rohit.
Yes.
- Kissed you good night?
No.
- Then she's not his girlfriend.
Why?
They become a couple...
When they kiss!
Now what should he do?
My mom is right. All men are fools!
Don't you know you have
to be friends before kissing?
I want to meet your mother.
She thinks we're all fools!
Yes!
- Rohit, what you can do...
Is give her a present.
But I have no money.
Mother gives me only a buck.
I have an idea!
You can give her a flower.
Nisha?
Dear, you spoke about
a mentally challenged boy.
Yes.
- There's an article on the net.
I got a printout.
It says treat such guys with love.
That's their cure.
Rohit.
What are you doing?
Come on up.
Why are you hiding the flower?
- I'm not.
It's a present for you.
How sweet!
Thank you.
Why are you blushing?
My friends say,
if a girl kisses a boy...
They become a couple.
Your friends are right.
I am your girlfriend.
Really?
- Truly!
'Nisha!'
Yes, dad?
- I'll take your leave.
Come in. My parents
will be happy to meet you.
Dad? Mom? This is Rohit.
Hello, Rohit.
- Hello, sir.
Rohit, would you like
to drink some tea or coffee?
Bournvita.
- Bournvita?
Bournvita?
Bournvita is necessary
for energy and strength.
I'm in the seventh
but I am the tallest in class.
All because of Bournvita.
Sorry, Rohit. We don't have it.
- You don't?
You should have it
and drink it everyday.
Right, we'll get it today.
And we'll drink it too.
- Good.
Sir, call from the collector.
Tell him I'm coming.
Nisha, save this page.
I'll be back soon. - Okay.
Do you know anything
about computers. - Yes.
I also know that you
want to learn computers.
Will you teach me?
- Of course.
Let's go home.
My dad has a computer!
The stars...
- Dad was a great scientist.
He spoke to people
living on the stars.
Really?
- Of course.
Press enter to continue.
Enter.
What's this?
Don't know.
Must be your dad's project.
'Press key B'
See, 'Press B' is flashing.
Nothing is happening.
- There's B here too.
Let's connect this to that.
Okay.
Good.
Wow.
Press C.
Amazing.
Press F.
Press E.
How did you play this?
- I know this tune.
Mother taught me. Want to hear?
Fabulous!
Teach me too.
- It's easy. Give me your hand.
"My dreams and fantasies
have found a face in you."
"I have found meaning
to my existence."
"I have found him."
"I have found the one."
"Whom have you found?"
"I found someone special."
"Both of us have been meeting
each other everyday."
"But when I met you today,
I felt as though..."
"As if I have found her..."
"I have found the one."
"Whom have you found?"
"I found someone special."
"Tell me what you
feel when you meet me."
"Please tell me the truth."
"I'll whisper it to you.
So, come closer."
"Come close to me."
"I know what you're going to say."
"So, I won't come closer."
"No, please listen to me."
"We' like to talk to each other
everyday."
"But today that I feel as though..."
"As if I have found somebody."
"I have found somebody."
"Whom have you found?"
"I found somebody special."
"I feel your presence
even when you away."
"You are close
even when you are away."
"No other feeling is
as special as this one."
"This one is quite
a unique feeling."
"I don't know why
is this happening."
"I don't understand
what the heart wants to say."
"Try to understand
what your heart wants."
"My heart has been attracted
to many earlier."
"Why is it that today I feel..."
"As if I have found somebody."
"I have found him."
"Whom have you found?"
"I found someone special."
"My dreams and fantasies
have found a face in you."
"But today,
why did I feel as if..."
"I have found somebody."
"I found someone special."
Rohit!
Raj is a great player.
Kasauli Tigers is a strong team.
Blue Bulls is not less.
And he scores again!
Hurrah!
Minutes into the game
and the score is 60-58.
A player of Blue Bulls
passed the ball but...
Saxena of Kasauli
Tigers makes a move..
He crosses the half line...
Sorry. I'm sorry.
You...
- Raj!
Let's go. - What's going on?
Girl walks away with the boy.
The girl took the boy
and the player took the ball.
Which game should I comment on?
Anyway, Raj Saxena proceeds
with the ball and passes it.
He runs with ball and
the captain shows alertness.
Score is almost equal.
The match is getting exciting.
Last few seconds remain.
I see Kasauli Tigers have the ball.
He has the ball.
Tigers!
- Everyone is cheering the Tigers.
They bounce the ball...
Raj runs with the ball and scores!
Hurrah!
- Yes!
Kasauli Tigers are the winners
of this year's Hero Honda Cup!
Applause!
- Congratulations!
Hurrah!
What is going on, Rohit?
I too will play basketball
and be a champion.
Then people will clap for me too.
Oh!
Like Nisha was applauding me?
Yes.
How will you learn by yourself?
We'll teach you.
Will you teach me?
- Of course, we will.
Come on boys.
Let's teach Rohit basketball.
Take the ball.
Stand in the centre. Here...
Rohit, what are you doing?
Take the ball.
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
- It's okay.
The ball will come to me now.
I don't want to learn!
Get aside.
Huh?
How will Nisha applaud
unless you learn the game?
Next time watch your step
when you go to see Nisha!
Understand?
Mother says, sinners are
always punished.
But I haven't committed any sin.
Then why do I get punished?
Everyone makes fun of me.
Who will help me if You don't?
You have great powers.
Give me some of Your powers.
Please, dear God.
Please, God...
'Sending'
'Receiving'
'Upright!'
Rohit.
Rohit! What are you doing?
- What's wrong, mother?
Why did you touch it?
- What are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
- Why did you touch it?
It was playing on its own.
Why did you touch it?
- I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
It started on its own...
Mom!
What is happening?
What's happening?
- No lights in the city.
Darkness all around.
What's wrong with this?
It doesn't work on electricity.
Sir, I think a storm is brewing.
A terrible storm.
Sir! Take a look!
Good Lord!
'An Unidentified Flying Object
has been sighted in Kasauli.'
'Many world space organisations
find the incident hard to believe.'
'No radar station on earth
or satellite in space...'
'Have received UFO signals.'
'UFO stories are like ghost
stories.'
'Those who see them believe
in them, the others don't.'
'The UFO or saucer like
object sighted in Kasauli...'
'Was also seen in
Bangalore in May 2001.'
'Dad, did you see...'
- Not just in India, UFOs...
'People the world over
claim to have seen them.'
'There is no solid evidence
but believers believe in them.'
Captain, take the chopper down.
The burning grass and
3 depressions are evidence...
That the space craft that flew
over Kasauli last night...
Landed right here.
- You're absolutely correct.
It does seem as if the
space craft landed here.
This is terrific.
Amazing.
So out of the entire world
the aliens chose our city!
Imagine how popular our
little hill station will now be.
I declare 2 days' official
holiday to celebrate.
What is all this?
It's like a carnival.
People are dressed as aliens.
You also dress up.
- I'll take a moment.
Hey Rohit!
What are you doing?
Making eyes and a mouth on the pot.
Why? - I'm dressing as
an alien and going to the Mall.
Aliens...
You won't go anywhere.
- Why?
All my friends are going.
- They're different from us.
What difference?
- Don't argue.
But...
- I said, you won't go.
Holy smoke! Let's scoot.
Life from another planet.
Aliens.
Khan, what are you saying?
It's a fact that the
spaceship landed here.
So possibly somebody
may have come out of it.
That's exactly how it happened.
I inspected the entire area.
The footprints prove
that some creatures came out.
But...
- What?
But one of them hasn't gone back.
How can you say that?
I saw alien footprints
going towards the jungle.
But one set of footprints
didn't come back to the ship.
Suppose they are the
alien's footprints...
We'll nab him.
It will be an achievement bigger
than man going to the moon.
We can find out the
secrets of the universe.
But what if he's dangerous?
- We'll shoot him.
Whatever it is,
till this is proven beyond doubt...
It should remain between us.
The town is celebrating.
We don't want them to panic.
Okay, sir.
No excuse will work. Mother
won't let me go. Go away, Bittu.
Why are you whistling away?
I said I can't come!
Go away.
Rohit?
Do you know an alien got
left behind in the woods?
What's an alien?
Creatures living on other
planets are called aliens.
How does he look?
- Don't know.
He could be like an animal
or maybe like us.
Could he be like Bittu?
Bittu...
- Yes.
I was here last night and
I saw a child I thought was Bittu.
I got angry and broke this pot.
He ran back into the
woods but the pot is intact.
This must be another pot.
- No, it's the same.
I drew a face on it. See..
Oh my God!
Could it have been the alien?
Let's find him!
- One who can fix a broken pot...
Can do anything. I am frightened.
Why are you scared?
I am with you. Come on.
It must've been a child.
- Yes, let's go back.
Let's go.
Rohit!
Have you come from above?
He seems to have come from there.
We should help him.
God knows what
the police will do with him.
If he remains in the jungle,
wild animals will eat him up.
So what must we do?
We must keep him hidden.
Will you come with us?
Will you be our friend?
Long live India, sir.
- Long live India!
Good morning, sir.
Sukhwani.
Get these rolls developed
and printed. - Yes, sir.
Be quick.
Sir, you've done a great job!
It's the truth, the police job
can't be taken for granted.
And anything can happen
to an honest officer like you.
What nonsense!
- I'm praising you.
Your side business.
As long as there are weddings...
Your business will do well.
Sukhwani, do the job given to you.
Okay.
Indian Space Research Organization?
Dr Subramaniam?
Sir, Khan here.
According to your instructions,
I've photographed the footprints.
I'll send them to you very soon.
Sir, your opinion in this
matter is very important.
What's the matter? What is wrong?
What is wrong?
Open the door, Rohit.
I'm glad you came.
Why? Any problem?
Yes. He was screaming.
He's probably hungry.
I've given him many things
but he doesn't eat them.
He must eat something else.
What do you eat?
Glass?
Wood?
Wire mesh? Sun window?
No, Rohit.
He means something else.
Air?
Sun rays?
Sunlight?
- Sunlight.
Sunlight.
Holy smoke, he can speak!
He understands us.
This means he's very intelligent.
Yes.
But how can he eat sunlight?
It's not edible.
Our bodies get strength
from what we eat.
They possibly get strength
from the sun.
Look at his head.
- Rohit!
Hurry, hide!
What are you doing here
early in the morning?
Nothing Nothing.
When did you come, Nisha?
- A minute ago.
Join us for breakfast.
- You go ahead, we'll come.
I'm getting late, dear.
I have to go to office.
Why is the jug here? Bring it in.
Don't come out. We'll be back.
- Here you are.
Bye, Nisha.
- Bye, aunty.
Rohit, get up only
after finishing breakfast.
Holy smoke!
Bittu, found the ball?
- No, man.
The sixer sent the ball
out of the stadium.
No, it's in the outhouse. There.
Let's get it.
- Yes.
Where's the ball?
What are you doing here?
- Somebody is inside!
It's a ghost!
- No, it's a monkey.
Our ball is in his hand.
- Yes.
Why did you come out?
Told you to stay in the basket!
Ball.
Don't say a word.
You ruined everything!
Now everyone knows!
Who is he?
First all of you must promise,
you won't tell anyone about him.
Promise.
He's my friend. Like all of you.
Hi.
He came in the spaceship
that landed here.
The spaceship left but
this poor guy got left behind.
Holy smoke!
"I ate a 'dadd', and you ate two."
"Don't avert your eyes,
you are mad."
Holy smoke, magic!
- Yes, magic!
Magic!
"Magic... Yes, it's magic."
"Someone from the skies
is here on the earth."
"It is as if the wind is blowing
with us, not against us."
"Magic... Yes, it's magic."
"Magic...
- Yes, it's magic."
"Love needs no language.
Isn't that wonderful?"
"And now, there is no room
for unhappiness."
"Love needs no language.
Isn't that wonderful?"
"And now, there is no room
for unhappiness."
"There is no exchange of words
between us."
"Yet we can express
the feelings of our heart."
"Isn't this less than any miracle?"
"Magic... Yes, it's magic."
"Magic...
- Yes, it's magic."
"Magic... Yes, it's magic."
"Magic...
- Yes, it's magic."
"You live in our heart
and you are dear to us."
"No one will ever ask
anything in return."
"You live in our hearts
and you are dear to us."
"No one will ever ask
anything in return."
"You came here to meet us."
"You brought along
a lot of dreams."
"Promise to always be friends."
"Magic... Yes, it's magic."
Hey guys! What's up?
Why are you laughing hard?
New spaceship joke on the phone?
That's old hat.
We're laughing at the new joke.
Will Rohit and Nisha
have abnormal kids?
Rohit and Nisha's kids?
As if you don't know.
Nisha spends everyday with Rohit.
It's not too late. Do something.
Else that fool will steal
your girl away.
Any news of the alien?
- No, Colonel.
I think Inspector Khan was wrong.
Else we'd have found
something on him by now.
This is check and mate.
Congratulations, dad.
I have good news.
What is it?
Your son has decided
to get married.
Very good. Who is the lucky girl?
Nisha, uncle.
- Nisha?
This is fantastic.
That's great news.
Did you hear that?
Nisha and Raj want to get married.
Really?
What are you saying?
This is great news!
Isn't it, Indu?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What's up? - Do you know
Nisha is marrying Raj?
Holy smoke! How do you know?
My parents had gone to the
club last night. They told me.
But that's impossible.
Nisha is Rohit's girlfriend.
Let's go tell him.
- Yes.
Rohit!
Nisha!
Hi, Nisha.
Why did you lie?
I never said I'll marry you.
Neither did you refuse
and that's what our parents want.
It's not about them.
It's about lying.
There are no lies.
I like you and I know you like me.
Liking doesn't mean we get married.
It's vital to know
each other to get married.
Going by the present,
we'll never know each other.
What's happening?
- Oh come on, Nisha. I'm not blind.
Can't I see what's brewing
between you and Rohit?
What? An affair brewing
between me and Rohit!
Okay. Alright then.
Even if we're having it off,
it's none of your business.
I'll decide whom to meet.
You have no right to
interfere in my personal life!
Do you understand?
You insult me for that lunatic.
He's not a lunatic.
- You seem to know him well.
Yes, I know him well.
And I know you too.
What broke?
What's wrong, dear?
Rohit.
Nisha is getting married. To Raj.
Why does it annoy you?
Every girl gets married.
- But she is my girlfriend.
What? Nisha is your girlfriend!
Yes!
Talking to you doesn't
make her your girlfriend.
She said she's my girlfriend
and I'm her boyfriend.
She must have been kidding.
Nisha is an educated,
sensible girl.
She can make you her friend...
Not her life partner.
Why not?
Rohit.
You have grown up...
Yet you're still too immature.
You're not like boys your age.
Why not? Why am I not
like other boys my age?
I did nothing.
Then why is Nisha leaving me?
Rohit.
Everything would've been fine...
Had we not seen that evil spaceship.
Then your dad
would have been alive...
And you wouldn't be like this.
Spaceship?
Dad?
What had happened?
- We met with an accident.
I was carrying you then.
What are you doing here?
'Rohit.'
Take a quick bath.
I'll lay breakfast.
Don't smile. Go and hide.
Don't come out or you'll be caught.
Go.
Mother, I can't see.
Splash some cold water.
Then you'll be able to see.
Mother, I can see!
First he says, can't see.
Then he says, he can see!
Hurry up. You'll be late.
The computer bell
causes many problems.
Rohit, hide somewhere
or Rawat will scold you.
Why will he scold?
I'm now learning computers.
Where are your glasses?
Left them home?
I don't need them. I could see
everything clearly now.
What?
- Really.
Okay. Wait.
Read out what Mr Chaturvedi has
written on the blackboard.
If a turn-table rotates through
720 degrees in 1 second...
How many rotations
does it take in 1 minute?
Boys.
Write the answer to this.
120 rotations in 1 minute.
Who is that?
Who gave this answer?
You solved the Class 10 problem
without paper and pen, Rohit.
Yes.
- Come in.
Did you guess or...
Was it the right answer?
Absolutely right but
how did you solve it?
I don't know.
It just came to me when I read it.
Rohit? I can't believe it.
Neither can I believe it.
But it's the truth.
Where is Rohit?
How many times did I tell you,
you can't learn computers!
Learn carpentry or masonry!
You keep coming here and
I have to keep insulting you!
Mr Mathur.
Is this the way
to talk to a student?
This boy's IQ is 0.
He needs a doctor not a teacher.
See for yourself. Tell me.
Without opening a particular file...
How can you copy from one
drive of Windows to another?
You're asking a difficult
question to show him down.
First click in the program.
When the
Windows Explorer opens...
Take the cursor to
the file and right click.
Without leaving the button
take it to the other drive.
And your file will be copied.
It's right. It's absolutely right.
Holy smoke!
- How?
How do you know this?
You asked me to go
and learn from my dad.
I've learnt from my dad.
Sir, you're a teacher. You're
responsible for many children.
You should encourage
them to progress in life.
Computers didn't make man.
Man made computers.
Your computer can't do
what the human mind can.
Sir, never consider
anybody insignificant.
Because every small person
grows up someday in life.
That was fun.
How Mathur face fell!
Rohit, all of a sudden
how did you get so smart?
There's just one problem.
Now you'll forget us.
You'll have new adult pals.
- That's not true.
You're my friends and
you'll always be.
Rohit, pass the ball.
What will he pass? He still
hides behind his mother's skirt.
Why are you glaring?
Holy smoke!
Rohit, look at the ball!
Do you think you are
too strong now?
Show him.
What a punch, Rohit!
- Suddenly you're strong!
What muscles!
- Oh no!
Rippling muscles!
Take a good look!
What are you looking at? Come on!
Yes!
Come on!
You don't seem to have
had mother's milk.
Next time drink some,
so we can have a good fight.
Yes.
Why did you get me here?
Are you mad at me?
Yes.
Why?
- Because you're not my friend!
You're going with Raj!
I'm not going with Raj.
- You're not!
I turned him down.
- Good.
I don't like him.
- Neither do I.
We have similar likes.
- Yes.
We have similar tastes
and we understand each other.
Therefore I want to
explain something to you.
Every girl has to go someday.
She sets up her own home.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
What type of boy do you like?
I'll find him for you.
- You will!
Yes, we have the same likes.
You'll like the one I like.
So who is your choice?
I like Bunty, Bittu, Chottu.
Rohit, they are all kids.
- But I'm an adult.
That will be fun! We'll go
around and drink Bournvita!
Marriage doesn't mean
drink Bournvita together.
Marriage is a grave commitment.
There's only one responsibility
The husband should love his wife.
You can't live life only by love.
Every girl wants a man who
is physically and mentally strong.
Am I not physically strong?
Yes but...
But I'm mentally weak.
No. I...
Slow on the uptake.
I'll learn.
Just you watch.
I hit such a punch.
It was wonderful!
Nisha was very impressed.
And the ball I kicked it so hard,
it kept flying!
You did this, right?
Thank you, Jadoo.
Mother, don't be afraid.
He's Jadoo, my friend.
Stay away from him!
Don't go near him!
Stay away!
- Mother.
What on Earth is this?
Mother, don't scream.
- How did he get here?
Somebody might come.
Stay away!
- Mother...
- Mother, listen to me.
Sit down, Mother.
What is it?
- The spaceship that came.
He was on it.
- What?
I saved him in the woods.
He's with me since then.
He's very nice.
- Nice? Are you mad?
He can't stay here!
I'll call the police!
But listen to me.
How dare you hide him here!
Will you have the one
who did you a favour arrested?
What favour did he do me?
- Look at me.
Listen to me - I don't
want to hear or see anything!
Hello?
- Mrs Mehra?
Father Rodriguez here.
What have you done?
Rohit is a changed person.
The entire school is stunned
at his knowledge and intelligence.
We've decided to promote
him to the tenth class.
Are you on the line?
Mother, what's wrong? Who was that?
The Principal.
He's promoting you to the tenth.
That's because that's
their last class!
But how did this?
Jadoo performed this miracle.
I'm no longer that Rohit.
Your glasses?
I can see clearly.
I also understand everything.
I can explain to you
and show you things too.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Sir, this is Dr Steven.
- Hello.
This is Dr Subramaniam.
This is Dr Heinz.
- Hello.
And this is Dr Ferguson.
All are from space research
centre, sir. - I see.
Gentlemen, this is our
city collector, Mr Saxena.
Nice meeting you, sir.
The photographs sent
by Inspector Khan proved...
That these are
the footprints of an alien.
We've come here
for further research.
Khan, this implies that
your suspicions are true.
Tell me, doctor.
Is this alien dangerous?
Dangerous? I don't think so.
Had he been dangerous,
by now he'd have shown us.
But so far we've
received no reports.
The silence could also
mean that he is dead.
It is possible but even his
corpse will be priceless to us.
I'll have to search the area
to find him dead or alive.
We'll need extra force.
You have my permission.
'Sachin!'
Hey Jadoo.
How do I look?
What is wrong with you?
- I don't talk to kids.
It's my age to be dancing
not playing games.
Tell everyone.
What? Rohit dressed as a hero!
- Yes.
He said, it's his age to
be dancing not playing games.
Really?
Great.
- What are you doing?
Practice.
- Practice?
Take a look.
I'm a little slow.
Trying to become smarter.
Else all will laugh at you.
- On me? Why?
Because we're a couple,
so they'll laugh at you.
Rohit... - Ladies and gentlemen,
please give them a big hand.
What a vibe!
And our next participant
is Rohit Mehra.
You're taking part
in the dance competition!
Of course. Wish me luck.
Listen to what I'm saying.
- No, watch what I'm showing.
But...
Everyone is laughing.
Come on, let's go.
I'll be able to do it.
One more time. Music.
Move a little.
Holy smoke!
This is not child's play.
Let's go.
Very well. Then I'm leaving.
One last time.
Music.
"It's magic. It's magic."
"I've got the vibe that you need."
"Nothing is certain,
nor is anything fixed."
"What happens, is all a game."
"It's magic. It's magic."
"After the curtain rises
and before the curtain falls,"
"Anything can happen,
anything can change."
"Nothing is definite or sure."
"Whatever does,
is all a game of fate."
"Why do all the things which are
beyond our reach, look attractive?"
"Why don't we believe
in things that are near us?"
"The heart tries to make us see
reason, but we don't believe it."
"We don't pay heed. We never do."
"Nothing is certain or sure."
"What does, is all
a part of the game."
"See it for yourself
and give it a thought."
"Think about it well
and then second my words."
"Don't underestimate
the strength of a small thing."
"They give us an
important message."
"Yes, that is true.
Absolutely true."
"Nothing is certain or sure.
What does, is all a game."
"It's magic. It's magic."
"I've got the vibe you need."
"After the curtain rises
until the curtain falls,"
"You can expect the unexpected,
anything can change."
"Nothing is definite or sure."
"Everything that happens,
is a game."
"Are you ready to vibe?"
"Come on, everybody.
Vibe with me."
You were amazing.
- Thank you.
You were terrific. Good.
Am I ready?
You... I... This...
Rohit.
This is just the beginning.
Now watch the fun.
Rohit.
This isn't a child's toy.
Falls flat when exploded.
We'll see who falls flat.
Want to have a match?
Very confident.
- We'll know after the match.
Okay, you're on.
- What do we bet on?
Hero cup.
In addition to the Hero Cup,
Nisha will kiss the winner.
Alright?
Alright.
Nisha, be ready to kiss me.
Kiss?
- Yes.
We're playing a basketball match
and you will kiss the winner.
I'll never kiss Raj!
- But you'll kiss me!
Only if you win.
Dance and basketball are different.
`Accepted a match but have no team.
That's asking for trouble.
You are bound to lose
and Raj will beat you.
But you're my team.
- Us?
They're tall guys.
And we're little kids.
We can't even jump. Look.
Holy smoke!
Wow!
Today's match is quite strange.
Last year's winners Kasauli
Tigers have been challenged...
By Rohit Mehra and his team.
The team is called Pandavas.
Please welcome Pandavas,
ladies and gentlemen.
I don't believe my eyes.
Can this be a team? Kids?
Don't move.
The match begins with
the referee's whistle.
The ball is flung high and
Raj taking advantage of height...
Flings it towards
his team mate who passes it...
And proceeds towards half leg.
One more pass.
He throws it back towards Raj.
But I see,
Rohit running away with the ball!
He dribbles with it
and scores a basket!
Once again, the match begins
with the referee's whistle.
The ball is with Raj
who dribbles and advances.
Rohit grabs the ball and runs.
Rohit leaps high and
scores another basket!
He's being applauded
and the score board moving on.
Wow!
Raj's team, ball in hand,
passing to each other.
Ball gets to Raj Saxena.
He jumps and
Rohit throws the ball to his team.
Once again, the ball is with
Raj but Rohit snatches it back.
Once again he leaps up and basket!
Come here, guys.
Everyone surround Rohit.
Yes.
- Understand?
Okay. Give me 5.
- Yes.
The referee whistles
and match starts again.
Ball with Rohit but he
is surrounded by the Tigers.
Raj jumps over a little player.
And proceeds towards
the basket and scores!
Kasauli Tigers score.
Their supporters are happy.
The little kids begin the match.
Passing the ball but
Rohit Mehra can do nothing.
Little kids are helpless.
And Raj Saxena bounds
to score another basket!
Raj Saxena and his team is elated.
Kids are sad. - Yes!
Rohit still surrounded
by the Kasauli Tigers.
Raj Saxena runs with the ball.
Rohit tries to get ahead.
What do I see? Rohit Mehra falls.
He fell or perhaps got tripped.
But it has no effect on Raj.
He scores another basket!
Foul!
- Kids object to the foul...
But the referee isn't convinced.
- Foul!
Scores are equal.
Match begins.
A little player jumps and...
Flings the ball to Rohit
who dribbles and proceeds.
Once again Rohit passes
to another little player.
But I see the little player is
helpless compared to tall Tigers.
The Tigers score another basket!
What is happening?
Why aren't you flying?
We're trying but can't fly.
- Yes.
The match takes a turn.
The attack of the Tigers
gets more acerbic.
Raj Saxena lunges and
scores another basket!
Score board goes up.
They're scoring basket
on basket and here's another!
Looks like Raj and his friends
are playing with the kids.
The kids try to jump
and grab the ball.
But Raj scores again.
It feels as if the Tigers invited
the kids for practice.
And another basket!
Excitement amid the fans
of the Kasauli Tigers.
The referee whistles,
it's half time.
What is going on? Why can't we fly?
Sunshine.
- Sunshine?
Jadoo gets his powers from the sun.
He can do nothing till
the sun shines on him.
Jadoo can do nothing
till the sun comes out.
Now what do we do?
Dear Lord Kishen,
show us your glory.
The second half of the match
begins with the whistle.
Referee throws the ball
and Kasauli Tigers grab it.
They pass to each other.
Raj lunges to score and...
The basket is saved.
Rohit!
Rohit falls but the Tigers
run with the ball.
The kids try but are helpless
in front of tall men.
Tigers run with the ball
but Rohit tries to grab it...
And passes it to his little friend.
- Jump!
And his little friend...
The kid passed the ball in air,
another caught it and basket!
Something strange is going on but
whatever it is, it's amazing.
The spectators are staggered.
That's Jadoo.
Match is resumed.
The Tigers have the ball.
The Pandavas leaping in the air.
Rohit Mehra himself leaps
into the air and scores!
Hurrah!
All shout for the victory!
- Victory to the disciples!
The excitement is increasing.
- Hurrah!
Starting once again.
- Pass the ball.
The Tigers pass
the ball to each other...
I see them advancing and...
A little player leaps into the air,
grabs the ball and...
He passed the ball to Rohit Mehra.
I can't believe this!
I don't have to bend low to give
you an eye witness account...
Everything is happening
in front of my eyes.
The Tigers are falling and
the kids are flying in the air.
I don't understand anything.
Another basket!
The puny little kids
are teasing the tall men!
Hey!
I never thought the match
would take such a twist.
And the ball...
Sorry.
It's so exciting.
I think these kids
will defeat the Tigers.
Raj Saxena is exhausted
and the children keep scoring.
They're the best.
Scoring basket after basket!
The score board is increasing.
The last 25 seconds of the match
Pandavas at 48 and Tigers at 49.
Let's see which team
wins the Hero Cup.
Tigers!
Match continues.
Ball is with the Tigers.
Tight hold over the ball.
Carefully they pass it.
They're doing something
but won't leave the ball.
Raj, an experienced player
leaps with the ball...
But Rohit Mehra catches the ball.
Merely 10 seconds to go.
Rohit somersaults
and gets to the hoop.
Basket!
Final score 50 to 49.
Hurrah!
Thank you, Jadoo. We won!
The Kasauli Tigers stand
with heads bowed.
Little Pandavas stand proudly
and accept the cup.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
The cup is being presented.
Please applaud!
They also win
a Hero Honda motorbike.
Rohit.
Not now. Something remains.
Bring on Hero's Honda. Let's go.
I can't believe this.
How did the kids fly?
There is some secret.
Must find out from the kids.
What are you saying?
Whatever I'm saying is right.
My son is getting maligned
because of our friendship.
He's become a laughing
stock for everybody.
And your daughter
is the cause of it.
I understand.
I also tried to convince Nisha.
What do you mean?
Do you mean if Nisha
wants to marry Rohit...
In spite of knowing
that he is retarded...
Will you give your daughter
away to that lunatic?
Branding me a lunatic
won't solve the problem.
Simply branding a person mad
won't explain his madness.
What category of madness
does he fit into?
Schizophrenia is madness,
megalomania is madness.
Obsession, psychopathy
and mental imbalance is madness.
And lunacy is madness.
There's no limit to madness.
There are many names
for mad diseases.
Certain forms of madness
appear to be so...
But actually they're not mad
while some are actually mad...
But their madness isn't visible.
In short, this is a short
summary on madness.
Why are you standing?
Please sit down.
I'll have a Bournvita.
Thank you.
- Yes.
As I was saying there
are kinds of lunacy.
Shaking your legs nervously
is a form of madness.
And you think I'm mad.
Yes. I'm mad.
I'm madly in love
with your daughter.
Madly in love with Nisha.
Holy smoke!
"Holy smoke!"
"Oh my God!
- Something crazy happened."
- Your sensational touch!"
"Oh my God, I feel as if
I'm in a different world."
"What have I done unknowingly?"
"Oh my God, I felt as if
I'm in a different world."
"What have I done unknowingly?"
"Oh my God!
- Something crazy happened."
- Your sensational touch!"
"Holy smoke!
What is this desire in me?"
"What is this change in me?"
"Holy smoke!
What is this desire in me?"
"What is this change in me?"
"The touch was just an excuse..."
"To come close to you.
You have touched my heart."
"I have always loved you forever..."
"I only have confessed it to you."
"I have realised
what is in your heart."
"I have understood
the person that you are."
"And the truth is that
you are crazy."
"You have caught me.
- And your mischiefs too."
"Your arms are flawless.
- Why did you grab them?"
"You have set my pulse racing."
"Oh my God!
- Something crazy happened."
- Your sensational touch!"
"Oh my God, I feel as if
I'm in a different world."
"What have I done unknowingly?"
"Holy smoke!
It happened when you touched me."
"What is this desire evoked in me?"
"I feel as if I have
no control on my heart."
"I have no control over my heart."
"I tried to stop my heart."
"But it did not listen to me."
"What have you done to it?"
"Now, it only thinks about you."
"Who knows what I did?
Who knows what happened?"
"I can't stop smiling since then."
"Whether it is day...
- Or it is night."
"Let's sit together.
- And talk all the time."
"Love has conquered us."
"Holy smoke!
- Something crazy happened."
- Your sensational touch!"
"Holy smoke! What is this desire?"
"Why can't my heart
stop being so crazy?"
"Oh my God!
- Something crazy happened."
- Your sensational touch!"
"Oh my God! I feel as if
I'm in a different world.
"What have I done unknowingly?"
"I have no control over my heart."
Why did you stop? The other
day you were jumping a lot.
Jump over us today too.
Why are you looking down?
What's in that bag?
Run! The sun has set.
We must save Jadoo!
Jadoo!
Sir, I've seen it myself!
Rohit!
Stop firing. Follow me.
Jadoo.
Check the bag.
Come and check.
Hey!
Go home.
But how did you run?
Ran.
Got saved today.
- You were great.
What's wrong?
Is Jadoo here?
- He's inside.
Rohit.
What happened?
The way inspector Khan
looked at me.
He suspects us.
We must hide Jadoo elsewhere.
In my house.
My parents have gone out.
No. My house is best.
Nobody will imagine Jadoo
is with the collector's friend.
But how long will you hide him?
Someday he'll be caught.
- No!
I'll take Jadoo and
go to another city.
Once the police begin looking...
You can't hide Jadoo
anywhere in the world.
Then what do we do?
There's only one
way to save his life.
Send him back...
To where he's come from.
No, mother!
Nobody can take Jadoo away from me!
Nobody can touch him
as long as I am alive!
Rohit.
Aunt is right.
You can't fight the world.
Jadoo won't go.
Everyone will be sad
at being separated.
But you will safe
only in your world.
Jadoo won't go.
Or the powers will go.
What does he mean?
He means...
All the powers will leave with him.
That he has given me.
Jadoo.
You don't worry about me.
I was alright before you came...
I'll live the same way again.
Rohit.
Go, my son...
Lest it gets too late.
We'll miss you.
What's happening?
There's no answer.
'Rohit!'
We know the alien is with you.
Hand him over to us.
We've surrounded your house.
We'll count to 10.
If you don't hand him over...
We'll attack your house.
'Receiving'
One!
Two!
Perform some magic.
Sunlight.
Three!
Four!
They're responding.
'Receiving'
Five!
Six!
Rohit!
- Rohit!
Rohit! Hand him over to us.
Never!
- Don't compel us to use force.
Do as you please
but I won't hand him to you!
Snatch him.
Leave my child alone!
Leave him!
Rohit!
Jadoo!
Kasauli base, come in please.
- We have captured the alien.
Khan here. We'll soon be there
I won't leave him! Jadoo!
Rohit?
- Rohit?
I won't leave him!
Mother, where's Jadoo?
They took him away.
Where?
- I'll tell you.
Yes, me. I never saw
such love and friendship.
From Delhi, they're taking
your friend to America.
Rohit.
If you want to repay Jadoo
for his favours...
Go, this is the time.
Save him and prove...
That goodness still exists.
Rohit, go!
Jadoo!
Let's go.
You?
Jadoo?
Let's go.
Drive faster!
Fast!
You! Where's Rohit?
Inspector Khan! Keep searching.
Go, my friend.
They're waiting for you.
Thank you.
'Rohit Mehra remanded
to police custody.'
This is Priti Sompura reporting
for Zee News from Kasauli town.
'A Special court acquitted
Rohit Mehra on the basis...'
That he's mentally abnormal.
The town has gathered
to honour Rohit Mehra.
Rohit considered
the alien his friend...
By sending him back to his world...
He set a new example
of friendship and humanity.
Let's all welcome him.
Rohit once said,
he'd become a great man.
He's proved it.
Thank you.
Miss you, Jadoo.
I know what you're thinking.
Jadoo took back his powers.
But he hasn't taken my love.
You thought you were a hero.
What are you looking at?
The one on whose strength
you were flying, has left.
Now pass the ball.
Rohit, let's go.
Come on.
- Take him away...
And let him wear your bangles.
Rohit!
Rohit, the ball is flying!
I can't see!
There.
- I don't see...
I can see.
I see clearly.
Jadoo has returned your powers!
Look up there!
Thank you, Jadoo.