I'm not going to the circus with you.
Strange! Why vent your
anger against Mao, on me?
How can I help it if he refused
to climb the pole?
And the fish... instead of
coming into my hand...
They palmed off a can, a shoe and that...
Wow! Priya smile!
In India you caught the fish so easily!
Actually those fish knew me,
they stood by me.
But you're not standing by me!
I've come to stand by you for life, Priya.
For life? When my mother asks
you what you do?
What will you say?
I'll tell her what I do
Love you.
And... what else will you say?
I'll fulfill all your wishes, look after you.
And?
I'll never let a smile leave your face.
Whether times good or bad
we'll always be together.
just like eyelashes are with the eyes.
And?
You will dream and I'll fulfill them.
In the scorching heat of the sun,
I'll be your shade.
and in the cold, I'll give you warmth.
When the rains bother you, I'll change
the course of the clouds.
and when a storm blows...
I'll turn the winds away.
That's how I shall protect
you all my life...
from every danger.
from every trouble.
Now I hope your mother will agree?
ADLABS
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
"what have you ever done?"
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
"what have you ever done?"
"what have you done in this world?"
"If you've never fallen in love"
ADLABS
"you have set foot, On the moon"
"you've made an abode, in the seas"
"But have you taught those crying"
"how to laugh?"
"Even God will smile and ask you one day"
"heart"
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
"what have you ever done?"
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
"what have you ever done?"
"what have you done in this world?"
"If you've never fallen in love"
"Life's also a circus"
"straight now, upside down in a moment"
"Those who get love have things
straightened out"
"else, they keep hanging"
"It's the simple truth, believe it"
"Heart..."
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
"what have you ever done?"
"what have you done in this world?"
"If you've never fallen in love"
ADLABS
"One more time"
"If you haven't taken a heart"
"if you haven't given your heart"
Fire! Help!
Priya...
My daughter...
My daughter, she's trapped inside
please somebody save my daughter
Help! Help! Mummy papa Help!
Somebody save my sister's life!
Is anybody there? Help me!
I'll keep my strength, my abilities
and my talent... hidden
That's a promise, Grandma.
Help! Help!
Somebody help! Help me somebody!
Please help, help!
Help! Help!
Somebody help, Mummy Papa!
Look!
Mummy, Papa!
Our daughter is inside,
Please save our daughter, sir...
Please save my child!
I beg of you, sir. Please! save
our daughter sir.
Please!
Help! Help!
Somebody help!
Help!
Come!
Who... who are you?
Krrish
Friend
Priya!
Are you all right?
But how did you get here?
You had fainted.
I had gone to get some water for you...
God! What a blaze! Come,
let's go home.
The most sensational news in
Singapore right now
is the circus blaze at Marina Bay
which took place last night
and the daredevil masked man savior who, in a
flash, rescued many victims trapped in the fire
and has become every child's hero overnight but
his identity is still shrouded in mystery.
Till yesterday, we only had a description
and a picture of the masked man.
Today, we've got to know his name
and also got a piece of his mask.
Let's find out how.
He said his name is Krrish
and this piece of the mask broke
from his forehead.
So his name is Krrish!
KRRISH!
But his identity is still shrouded
in mystery.
Whoever Krrish is, a bravery award
and cash reward of 25000 dollars...
has been announced in appreciation
of his courage.
So how are we going to identify Krrish?
The one, whose mask this piece matches with,
will be considered to be Krrish.
And he'll be the one to be rewarded.
Krrish! Krrish! After all who is this Krrish?
Listen carefully, our priority
at the moment is Krrish.
Only Krrish! Get that?
Krrish's identity...
Our channel should be the
first to reveal him!
Do you get that?
Our channel must be the first one to
unmask this masked Krrish!
Get it? Stop nodding and leave!
Go, get him! Go, go!
Where are the two of you going?
To look for Krrish.
Ah, forget Krrish. And look for a new job.
New job?
You both are fired.
What?
You better go back to India...
and enjoy your Krishna's flute playing.
Don't waste your time, Go, go!
Out!
Thanks to Krishna we're jobless.
Now what do we do?
Honey, I think Krrish is none other
than our own Krishna.
What?
Yes, Honey!
At the circus, I saw Krrish from
such a close distance.
I have a strong feeling that Krishna is Krrish.
So why didn't you tell this to
boss at the meeting?
Because I wasn't sure, I need
to confirm it first.
Confirm? How?
Listen, I have an idea...
Honey, these guys?
Priya! I've hired some actors.
But I'm a bit late...
I'll be there soon.
What?
So who are these guys?
Oh my God! Help!
This is now mine... bye!
I'm so sorry, Krishna. I'm so sorry.
I thought you were Krrish and
planned my own kidnapping.
But then, real goons turned up
instead of the hired ones.
Real goons?
But why didn't you hit back?
Why did you quietly take their beating?
I wanted to see...
whether it hurts you to see me in pain.
It does.
Where's your ring?
Maybe they've...
Who's he? Why's he here?
I think he's the masked man.
Masked man?
Get him.
I'm sorry, sorry.
My friend Krrish!
I'll tell everyone, I'll tell my sister.
No, Kristian. Don't tell anyone.
Why? You become famous!
You'll get the reward.
Here, Kristian. You become Krrish.
Take it. Get the money for your sister.
Make her legs good again.
Take it!
No, it's yours. You are the hero.
Every human being who fights for a
good cause is a hero, Kristian.
You... are fighting for your sister.
You are a hero.
The biggest news of today!
Superhero Krrish has revealed his
identity to the media...
and the broken piece of the mask
fitting his mask
has confirmed his identity
Here today, Hero Honda is honoring
Krrish for his bravery
Well done young man.
Thank you
Not once did it occur to me that
Kristian could also be Krrish!
He was also there at the circus that night!
Had it struck me that night
I wouldn't have got a thrashing!
I've said sorry, haven't I?
What else do you want me to do?
Close your eyes...
again you...
Now open them.
How did you get it back?
Krrish, he's my friend.
Wouldn't he do this much for me?
Thank you, thank you
Take it
Won't you put it on my finger?
ADLABS
"where the rays of the sun come from"
"Where the moonlight dwells"
"comes news"
"there's no one like you"
"Where sleep hides"
"Where dreams are made"
"comes news"
"there's no one like you"
ADLABS
"Flower, butterflies, the buds..."
"they're all sulking"
"From them you have stolen..."
"their ability to evoke love"
"Where colors are created"
"and beauty is crafted"
"comes news"
"there's no one like you"
"You have stolen my heart"
"do you realize that"
"In you lies all the love in the world"
"In you it lies"
"Where people go crazy in love..."
"Where Lovers Are Born"
"comes news"
"there's no one like you"
ADLABS
Priya!
Move from there.
Priya, you're watching TV here and there boss has
ordered to vacate Krishna's apartment.
Hello! Are you listening?
I am & am not.
What's this?
Remember the explosion at the circus?
I had passed out, but I think the
camera was still on.
Now switch off the TV and think
about Krishna! Please!
Oh my god!
What happened?
I'll rewind and show you.
Krishna is Krrish!
What happened?
Why are you girls screaming?
Where are you both going?
Mom Office! I'll see you okay.
Office?
Come on Honey
To get our jobs back!
Ok bye!
Priya, your mobile.
Hello Priya?
No, I'm Priya's mother
Mother... hello.
When did you return from Hong Kong?
Hong Kong? I didn't go anywhere...
I've been right here
And who are you?
It's me, Krishna.
Krishna, who?
Priya has told you everything about me,
hasn't she?
No, Priya has said nothing about you.
You are Priya's mother aren't you?
Yes... I'm Priya's mother.
Where's Priya?
Priya left for office just now.
Office...
Right... Thank you
Priya, do you realize? Once this
footage is telecast...
Our Krishna will become a
world famous celebrity!
There's something about our Krishna!
He fooled us so convincingly.
In India, as Kalicharan, and here, as Krrish!
Didn't I tell you Honey, the truth
always comes out?
Look Priya, the truth about Krishna
the world is about to discover...
...is because you lied!
The lie that you love him brought him
here all the way from India.
And imagine! Now we're going to
create a big sensation!
You're right. A lie sometimes leads
to very big gains.
You didn't even tell me!
What could I say?
When his honesty turned my feigned
love into a genuine one...
I didn't even realize
I'm in love with Krishna, Honey
Krishna, Krishna
The culprit has been caught at last!
He did his best to hide his identity, you know
But I finally discovered who the real Krrish is!
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you keep me in the dark?
Where was the need to hide behind
a mask, even with me?
You're asking this Priya?
Someone who has never been honest with me
Someone who kept me in the dark till today
I have been unmasked Priya.
What about you?
What do you mean?
Why did you lie to me that you loved me?
I took your lies for the truth and came here.
to ask your mother for your hand in marriage
But you lied about her too!
yes, Priya
I've spoken to your mother
Krishna...
I'm sorry
I admit, I lied to you in the beginning
But now...
I really love you Krishna
Stop it, Priya! Stop it!
you may have more lies to tell me
But I don't have the strength to take
them for the truth anymore!
Listen to me, Krishna! I've done
all this only for you
I wanted to see you become
a very big man
and that's about to happen in
just a few hours
the whole world will get to know about
your extraordinary powers and talent
that's exactly what I didn't want
Why do you think I wore the mask?
because I had promised grandma that
I'd keep my identity hidden
that I would not let anyone know
about my powers
and you
grandma was right
people in the world only use each other
for their own selfish reasons
She tried to stop me, but I...
But why does your grandmother
want to stop you?
Why does she always want you
in front of her eyes?
Why doesn't she want the whole
world to know of your talent?
Is she not being selfish?
Priya!
You really want to know?
Then listen!
having lost her son, grandma
did not want to lose me
because I posses the same powers
but she still let me come here
for you
for my feelings, she gave in
But what do I tell her now?
Krishna, listen to me... Krishna!
Krishna...
Hello Honey
We've got to stop the telecast
of Krishna's tape
Why?
don't ask questions now, just
stop the telecast
but the tape is with boss
My god, where's boss?
I wish to thank all my investors
in Singapore
they are the ones who really
deserve this applause
for having had faith in my
various projects
I'm delighted to announce that
our company, Technotronics...
has made a profit of 400 million
dollars this year
I therefore announce 100% dividend
to all our shareholders
Any questions?
Yes?
Dr. Arya, congratulations on the phenomenal
success of your company
my question is
20 years ago, you tried to make a computer
that could see the future
What happened to that dream of yours?
20 years ago, you must have had
a lot of dreams too...
Did they all come true?
Pardon me?
some questions hurt
the media ought to understand
that dream died with the death of my
genius friend, Rohit Mehra
But from what I've read and
heard of you, Dr. Arya...
you don't ever accept defeat
I'd have tried to win...
had my genius friend been alive
Any further questions?
excuse me
sir, I need to speak to that lady
for just one minute
Please!
Krishna
Anything left to say?
Yes... This gentleman has
something to say
Who are you?
My name is Vikram Sinha
What do you want?
Don't go back the way you came.
What does that mean?
I mean, you came alone
don't go back alone.
Krishna, your father, Rohit Mehra,
is still alive.
What did you say?
This picture was taken when
your father worked for Dr. Arya
And I was the Senior Security
Officer at Technotronics.
He was younger to me in age,
and I was a junior in status.
And yet, we were very close friends.
not only because we were Indians
it was because of the sincerity in his smile
and the honesty in his eyes.
He was always smiling...
but someone cast an evil eye on him.
It's been so many years,
but that time...
seems to have frozen.
That day, he was working till morning...
because he had to complete his
project and go back to India.
Good morning, chief
Mr. Vikram? Welcome!
How are you this morning?
I'm doing fine, chief
but if you keep working round the clock like this,
you're going to get insomnia
I won't have to do it after today.
Once the computer is inaugurated today...
I'll hand it over to Dr. Arya and return
to my family in India.
Don't mind, chief...
but I still can't believe that we
can see the future.
Not believing does not change
the truth, Mr. Vikram.
You will believe it, when you see it?
What? You mean you're going to...
Of course!
Come see tomorrow, today
and tell me how it feels to see the future.
Please hold this.
Retina scan, an identification of my eyes
These 2 identifications of mine are
the password for this computer.
Without which, it won't start up.
But when you're not around, when
you've gone back to India?
I'll change the password before I leave
After that, only Dr. Arya will be able
to start the computer.
Tell me...
What would you like to see?
I... I don't want to see anything, chief!
But you said your wife is pregnant
Let's see whether I'm going to be an
uncle to a nephew or a niece?
Ok then... let's find out.
Nisha!
My darling baby...
Look, Nisha, your son looks just like Rohit.
Now go to your Mom. My son's
coming back to me.
Congratulations, chief! Your wife's
going to deliver a baby boy tomorrow!
But I'm going to distribute sweets
today! In fact, right now?
What did you say?
What happened to my Rohit?
What happened, Mom?
No! That's impossible!
My Rohit can't be dead!
My Rohit is alive!
No!
Which means, I...
Chief, the computer's malfunctioning!
Something's wrong with it!
Dr. Arya!
It's 6:40 there, it's 6:30 now!
This means, in just 10 minutes!
in this very room!
Look! Dr. Arya!
Have you heard of Shahjahan, Doctor Mathur?
Of course! He built the Taj Mahal.
Incomplete knowledge is always dangerous.
Shahjahan had the hands of workers
who built the Taj Mahal, chopped off!
so that there would never be another Taj Mahal.
Rohit Mehra is a worker for me
and I'm his Shahjehan.
You mean, you're also going to
cut off Rohit's hands?
No... his brain!
because Rohit's brain will create problems,
for himself as well as for me.
Actually, I'm going to feel very sorry about
it because Rohit is a very good boy.
Sincere, honest, intelligent...
They're coming here, chief. Please leave!
No, no! I'm won't let this computer
go into the wrong hands.
I'll destroy everything!
All right!
I'll try and stop them!
Hello!
Mom?
Rohit? I've brought Nisha to the hospital.
Congratulations! You're going to
become a father anytime.
Come home soon, son
I'm coming, Mom! I'm coming!
Rohit... What's the matter? You sound tense?
I've been exploited, the world is very selfish!
Don't worry, I'll be back, I'll be back soon.
Rohit!
What have you done?
I've destroyed your dream...
I've destroyed everything!
because I've got to know of your intentions
But those who know me also
know that I never accept defeat.
I'll rebuild this computer
using your research.
But I don't need you anymore.
Thank you so much for everything, Rohit
Good bye
Hold it, sir!
Don't kill him, sir
If you kill Rohit... then even if you
build the computer again
you'll never be able to start it
You need a password to start the computer
and the password is Rohit himself.
What?
Yes, sir
I've seen it with my own eyes.
Until scans of his retina and heartbeat
are fed into the computer...
the computer will not start.
This means, I'll have to keep you alive
till I don't build a new computer.
But die, you will.
For the world.
Breaking news.
Tragedy strikes!
Following a fire that broke out in
the lab of Technotronics...
The famous Indian genius Rohit Mehra
has met with a tragic death.
Let's observe a 2-minute silence,
so that Rohit Mehra's soul rests in peace.
Ever since, I had no choice but
to work for Dr. Arya.
I couldn't even go to the police...
because if Dr. Arya doubted me,
he would've killed me.
And I was the only man who could
get in touch with your family.
That's exactly why I've been looking for your
grandma and you for so many years.
And finally, I met you today, through Priya.
Dr. Arya
20 years...
for 20 years, he's kept a
mother away from her son
and a son away from his father
It's because of his lies that I lost my mother.
Where is my father?
Here in Singapore.
For 20 years Dr. Arya has used
machines to keep him in a state
that only his brain is alive,
his body almost dead.
Good evening, my friend Rohit Mehra
How are you feeling today?
Are these machines taking good care of you?
Yes?
Good!
Tomorrow's the glorious and historic day
when my, sorry, our computer
will be inaugurated.
Yes! Ours, because nothing
was possible without you
For so many years, you have
shown such patience and understanding
and cooperated with me.
When the computer starts tomorrow
your utility will come to an end,
and so will your pain.
See you tomorrow
Breaking news!
Dr. Arya has suddenly been
reminded of the poet Kabir.
Do today, what you must do tomorrow...
and do right now, what you must do today.
That's why, Dr. Arya has decided
to start the computer today itself.
and also end Rohit's life.
Is this where my father is kept?
Yes! But it's almost impossible
for a stranger to get there...
Dr. Arya has kept very tight security
everywhere on the island
So that now no one comes between
him and the computer
Krishna, if Dr. Arya starts the computer
how much havoc he can wreak and
the destruction he can cause, is unimaginable
mine... yours... ours, the worlds
destiny will come in his clutches.
That's why, Dr. Arya has to be
stopped at any cost.
Now you have to save not only your father
but the whole mankind, Krishna.
Hello.
Krishna?
Grandma!
Krishna, are you okay?
Yes, Grandma
I don't know why I'm feeling worried.
When are you coming back?
Come back soon
Your father's death anniversary is nearing,
you need to be here and fulfill the duties of a son.
I remember, Grandma. don't worry...
I'll fulfill all the duties of a son.
WELCOME TO THE FUTURE
Congratulations Sir!
See, Rohit I've won!
Now if you want you can end your life.
Or do you want me to help?
But what's the hurry? At least see how your
invention is going to make me God!
Rohit, we built this computer
so that we can see our future
and change it!
I will also change my future and show you
Today itself!
Dr. Arya's gone to look for the masked man
Masked man?
Kristian!
Krishna
Look Dr. Arya!
Come on, let's go!
What had Kristian done? Why kill him?
Dr. Arya has probably started the
computer and, he must've seen...
His future!
It will be just as Dr. Arya has seen.
I've changed my future!
I've changed my tomorrow!
There is no mask any longer...
Henceforth the new face of God is...
Dr. Siddhant Arya!
How is this possible?
I've killed him with my own hands.
Then... who's this?
Its 9:15 there and it's 9 here.
This means, he'll be here in
the next 15 minutes.
that means he is already on the island!
Stop!
To capture him we need
planning not power.
Dr. Arya has kept very tight security
everywhere on the island.
You're good! Very good.
But I'm better
Yes, I am better
Because I have seen the future.
But due to lack of time what I
couldn't see is what I want to know...
Why do you want to kill me?
And why do you want to rescue Rohit Mehra?
Who are you?
Come to me and give me the answer.
come!
I've told you, I have seen the future
And I know who is with me...
Hello!
and who is against me
So... please cooperate
Who are you?
We'll get to know right now.
Who... are you?
Your son... Krishna!
Mom.
Thank you, Jadoo.
Thank you