Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
What a mess!
Krishna. Krishna.
What am I going to do with this boy?
Krishna.
Yes, grandma?
Whose sketch book is this?
Mine, grandma.
And who made these sketches?
Grandma, why do grown ups
sometimes ask childish questions?
If it's my sketch book, obviously,
I've made the sketches.
Grown ups talk like children
when children act like grown ups.
Tell me something, how did
you make such beautiful sketches?
With this.
Like I've made your
sketch right now. See?
Wow! Let me see!
Rohit loved drawing too.
Papa made sketches too?
Yes.
When Rohit was your age and
he used to get tired studying,
he used to sketch.
I want to be like my Papa too.
You are like your Papa!
Mrs. Mehra, I've called
you here to tell you that...
we want to take Krishna's I.Q. test.
I.Q. test?
But why, Father?
Krishna's absolutely normal.
No, Mrs. Mehra.
He's not normal.
What are you saying, Father?
Are you telling me...
that Krishna is the same
as Rohit was in his childhood?
No, Father.
Krishna's a very bright child.
He scores very good marks,
he always gets A-plus grades.
He even does his homework
without any help.
And that of other children too.
What?
This is the notebook
of a Class Three student.
This is...
Krishna's handwriting.
Yes, Krishna has done
this child's math homework.
But, how's that possible, Father?
Krishna's still in Class One.
That's exactly why we wish
to take Krishna's I.Q. test,
so that we can ascertain just
how bright, sharp and ahead he is
of other children his age.
Krishna, how do you define amount?
Principle plus interest
is equal to amount, sir.
After what age does the
brain of a person stop growing?
After the age of 15, Father.
What happened, Mrs. Mehra?
The I.Q. test was going so well.
Krishna was answering
all of the questions right.
That's exactly why I brought him away.
But why?
You ought to be proud that
your grandson is so brilliant.
He's a genius, a miracle child.
Earlier it was a hunch, but now I'm sure.
The powers that Jadoo
had bestowed on Rohit,
have been inherited by Krishna.
You will see, Mrs. Mehra. Like his father,
Krishna will also achieve great success.
His name will appear in the Guinness Book,
and the whole world
will speak highly of him.
That's exactly what I don't want, Father.
What did Rohit gain, after all?
They gave him medals, applauded him,
but everybody only used him,
took advantage of him, Father.
And then...
I lost my son and my daughter-in-law.
I don't want to lose Krishna now.
I don't want to lose him.
I can understand your concern and fears.
But destiny cannot be changed.
And talent is a gift
which cannot be hidden.
I will hide it, Father.
I'll take Krishna far away...
very far.
Krishna. Krishna.
Coming, Grandma!
Toofan, let's see who gets home first.
Hey, what did you see?
As usual, I've seen nothing
and I won't say a word to anyone.
But as usual,
I'll take something from you.
Take this!
I hide all your secrets
and you always give me jaggery?
It won't work today.
Okay, okay, come home.
I'll give you Bournvita.
Bournvita?
-Yes. Don't you want to be like me?
-Yes!
So go, wear something below and come.
Krishna.
You've come?
Grandma, how do you know I've come?
I made no sound at all!
I can hear your heartbeats.
But how, Grandma?
Your eyes say that you've
been up to mischief again.
Mischief? Not at all, Grandma!
No mischief? Then why are
you hiding your face like a thief?
Not hiding,
just washing my face, Grandma.
Okay, lay the breakfast.
I've come!
I'm back.
What happened? What did you drop?
Chintu dropped a glass, Grandma.
Me?
Chintu! Up to mischief again?
Tell her the truth Krishna,
or else I shall.
Sure, go ahead.
I'll tell her since you've asked me to.
Grandma, Krishna was running
faster than Toofan today.
What? Faster than Toofan?
So? What's the big deal?
And how about that?
What?
You climbed the mountain
faster than the monkeys.
Grandma, you know that
tall mountain by the temple?
Krishna jumped from it into the river.
I thought it was all over.
But he came back!
Krishna, why do you do such things?
I've forbidden you time and again!
Why do you still do such things?
What do I do Grandma? You tell me!
How do I rid myself of loneliness?
Who do I make friends with?
Boys my age have gone away to the city,
to either study or earn a living.
And those that are here don't
want to be friends with me.
They say I'm not like them.
So, I've made friends
with animals and birds.
Keep myself busy with nature.
But even out here in the open,
I sometimes feel stifled.
I feel like running far away from here.
Will you leave me and go away?
It's because of you that I don't go!
Otherwise, I'd have left long ago.
Krishna has grown up, Rohit.
I'm not sure how long
I will be able to hide him.
Where is Sonia Mehra and
her grandson Krishna, Father?
It's the third time in so
many years that I've come to ask you.
And my answer is still the same.
I have no idea where Mrs. Mehra is.
I really don't know!
Why do you keep coming to
me again and again and waste my time?
Because you are the last
link to Rohit Mehra's family,
and you're the last person Sonia
Mehra met before she went missing.
You know where they are,
but you're lying.
-What?
-Yes.
You are lying, Father.
When I asked you whether Krishna
possessed the powers Rohit had,
you said he didn't.
But I was told that the
son was better than his father.
That he possesses all of
Rohit's powers. So tell me, Father,
I'll pay any price you ask.
How dare you!
Mr. Sinha, this is a school!
We don't indulge in business here!
Please, leave now!
You're making a mistake, Father.
A big mistake.
Krishna! Look!
What a huge kite!
But where's the string?
Must've snapped. Let's get it!
Catch!
Krishna, catch!
Krishna!
Don't scream! You needn't be afraid.
Close your eyes and hold me tightly? Okay?
Stop screaming!
Else, I'll drop you.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes, not widen them.
Close them! Close!
-Priya!
The glider came this way!
There it is!
-Where?
Sir. Up there!
Oh my God! Where's Priya?
There!
-What happened?
She's breathing.
She must've passed out.
-Thank God.
-Let's take her back to the camp.
Pick her up.
The glider was at such a height,
Priya Ma'am was down here...
and she's still breathing?
Where am I?
You're alive and you're with us.
Thank God you're alive.
Not God,
it's that boy we ought to thank.
That boy? Which boy?
The one who saved my life.
A boy saved you?
-Yes, sir.
-But there was no one there!
No sir! He must've been there!
We fell from the tree together.
Together?
But you went in the glider alone.
How did he come up the tree to rescue you?
Did he fall from the skies?
Yes sir. That's where he came from!
-But--
-She's right!
-Ghost!
-What happened?
Ghost!
Komal sir, ghost!
Ghost?
Run. Run. Run. Run. Run. Run!
What are you blabbering, Bahadur?
No blabber, sir.
It's a chant. To drive the ghost away.
What rubbish, Bahadur?
Ghost in broad daylight?
This is a jungle, sir!
Night and day are all the same here.
Priya ma'am, was he tall?
Yes.
Well built?
Yes!
-Fair-skinned?
-Yes!
-Kalicharan!
-Kalicharan?
-Yes, sir! Kalicharan's ghost!
He has been wandering in the mountains for
ages and hanging upside down on the trees.
A ghost in our times?
What happened?
Sir, it's either a sprain or a fracture.
Oh no!
We're here on a ten day adventure camp,
and you've already broken your foot!
Honey, take her into the
tent and give her first-aid.
Bahadur, go to your phone
booth and call for a car.
We need to send Priya
to the city for treatment.
I'll go at night, sir.
I feel scared by day.
-What?
-Yes! Kalicharan's ghost.
Scares people by day and sleeps at night.
Easy, easy Just relax.
You're always screaming!
Doesn't your throat hurt?
Your eyes are widening again!
You must never get scared--
Hey!
What happened, Priya?
Why were you screaming?
Honey, he was here!
In this room! He was here, Honey!
Who? Who was here?
The boy who saved me on the tree,
the one I told you about, sir!
God! What's happened to this girl?
Priya, it's just two seconds since I left.
Are you saying that in the meantime,
someone came and then went away?
You must've dozed off and had a dream.
I didn't dream, Honey.
Why doesn't someone believe me?
The moment I closed my eyes,
he entered the tent,
he twisted my ankle and the pain...
Hey! The pain in my ankle is gone! See!
The pain has disappeared!
Oh my God sir! My foot is all right!
Amazing.
Look at this, I can jump!
Oh my God. Look, I can jump!
My foot has healed!
Either this girl has really gone mad,
or she's conning us!
No, sir! I'm not conning you!
See, I can jump! Believe me!
I believe you!
Kalicharan has cured your foot.
Kalicharan?
So this ghost is also a doctor?
He isn't, but he was.
Kalicharan's father, Lalcharan.
Doctor Lalcharan.
There's no Kalicharan, there's no
Lalcharan. It's all a pack of lies!
It's some stupid local
boy playing a prank on me.
I'm going to find him today and
bring him before everybody,
and prove to them that
he's just another boy!
-Are you looking for someone?
-What?
You! I'm looking for you!
Where do you keep disappearing?
Why don't you appear before the
others as you appear before me?
And that stupid Bahadur keeps
telling them that you're Kalicharan!
You're not Kalicharan, are you?
You're human, aren't you?
Why are you kids giggling?
Who are you talking to, aunty?
Aunty? Firstly you call me aunty
and then you ask who I am speaking to?
I'm talking to this boy!
Which boy?
Can't you see this boy here?
That's a lamppost there, not a boy,
That's a boy.
-Lamppost.
-Boy!
-Lamppost!
-Shut up!
One moment. Please Listen.
What do you see there?
A boy? Or a lamppost?
Well, there's neither
a boy there nor a lamppost.
Look carefully..
What happened?
I'm feeling giddy.
You seem unwell.
My house is nearby,
come rest there for a while.
I'll get you a glass of water
Okay!
Why is his picture garlanded?
My son. He died 20 years ago.
But how's that possible? Moments ago, I...
It's a tragic tale...
Champa and Kalicharan.
Kalicharan and Champa.
Madly in love with each other
They were like one soul two bodies.
And then one day...
What happened?
Kalicharan was putting
some flowers in Champa's hair,
Lalcharan happened to see them.
He went red with rage!
And one day,
he deceived Champa into drinking
poison, in the name of medicine.
And poor Champa!
She screamed, "Kali, Kali!"
And then died. Just imagine!
Kalicharan just could not
bear the pain of Champa's death.
Over there! Look at that peak!
From that very peak, Kalicharan
screamed, "Champa, Champa!"
And jumped to his death!
Ever since, Kalicharan's spirit
has been looking for his Champa!
Why are you pointing towards me?
Because you are his Champa.
Me? Champa!
I mean, you look like Champa.
I'm feeling terribly scared.
We can't stay here anymore, please
Nobody goes anywhere!
Sir!
This silly Bahadur
talks a lot of nonsense,
and you start imagining?
Bahadur, you're not telling these
kids anymore stories. Understand?
And now get ready.
We're going mountain-climbing.
You will use ascenders to climb,
and then put descenders....
and you will come rappelling down.
Ghost!
Priya!
What on earth is that?
Kalicharan!
One hundred and four degrees.
I had told you, sir.
But you didn't listen.
We're not staying here any more.
Bahadur, go fast,
and make a call from your phone booth.
And arrange for our transportation. Go!
You've snatched my bread and butter.
I'm broke even before
I could make some money.
Why did you climb the mountain like that,
in front of them?
What could I do? She screamed so loudly.
I got scared.
And now they are so scared,
that they're all going back.
Now keep searching for
your Champa all your life!
What do we do, Bahadur?
How do I know? I did as you said.
You think of a way now.
-Idea!
-What?
Champa..
My name is Priya.
In this lifetime,
In your earlier six births
you were Kalicharan's Champa.
This is your seventh birth.
If you leave without meeting him,
he'll be very angry,
and he'll follow you wherever you go.
How will he follow her?
We're going back to Singapore.
He can reach Singapore too!
He doesn't need air tickets.
Bahadur, she's not meeting any ghost!
What if something happens to her?
This ghost is a gentleman, ma'am.
He hasn't harmed a soul.
Am I right?
Yes.
I leave the rest to you.
Wait, Bahadur!
-Honey.
-Yes?
You're going to meet him?
Yes. Only then will he find peace.
And you better not stop her.
If Kalicharan gets to know...
No! I wasn't stopping her!
I was only advising you, right?
Listen, you must meet the ghost.
He's such a gentleman!
I'm off to sleep. Bye, good night!
Honey!
Champa. Champa.
Hello! Kalicharan.
I am here...
to help you get peace.
Please, could you appear before me?
I am scared.
Do ghosts also feel scared nowadays?
I'm not a ghost.
You aren't a ghost?
Oh yes, I get it!
It offends you when someone
calls you a ghost, doesn't it?
And you're right!
You've ended your life for love.
And those who end their
lives for love aren't ghosts.
They are... they are...
They're lovers!
You're a lover, aren't you?
I'm Krishna.
Look, stay right there!
Don't come closer, okay?
You sent for me and here I am.
You'll get peace now.
-May I go now?
-All I want is friendship.
What? Friendship?
Hey, don't be afraid.
I'm as human as you are.
Touch me, if you can't believe that.
Touch you?
See? The color of my blood is red, too.
Are you convinced
now that I'm not a ghost?
If you're not a ghost, then that picture?
That's my father's photograph.
He's no more.
I look exactly like him.
I see.
But the other day,
how did you suddenly
get on that tree to save my life?
And yesterday! How did
you climb that mountain so fast?
Maybe because I've got used to it.
Right from my childhood,
I've grown up playing among
the trees and mountains
with the birds and the animals.
I spend most of my time here.
I guess that's why they're my friends.
-Would you like to meet my friends?
-What?
I still can't believe it!
I won't let you poke that pin again!
It hurts because I'm not Kalicharan.
See? He's not Kalicharan!
I've always been saying that!
That's what you're still saying.
Correct!
Kalicharan, you're so cute!
Krishna, you really got us scared.
But that was a nice prank.
Boys and girls, camping continues!
Krishna, you also join the group.
Catch!
Yes!
From where are you getting a flower
of a new color every time, Krishna?
From the rainbow.
The rainbow?
Yes.
Look.
Wow Krishna! It's such a beautiful sight.
Had I not come here,
I'd really have regretted it.
So would I.
I've never seen such a lovely place.
Krishna, you speak English?
And with such fluency?
Grandma taught me. She's my school,
my college and my university.
But you need talent
to learn anything, Krishna.
And you possess amazing talent.
You shouldn't be wasting
your talent in this remote village.
You ought to get out of here.
People in the world out there,
not just need talented people
like you, they appreciate them too.
But my grandma is my world.
I will never leave her.
You love your grandma very much?
More than very much.
Krishna, I want to meet your grandma.
♪Look even the breeze♪
♪Even the breeze now rises in a wave♪
♪having touched you♪
♪Secretly quietly♪
♪There's a joy♪
♪There's a joy that now sings♪
♪Having met you♪
♪Secretly quietly♪
♪It just doesn't seem as if you
have come from somewhere far♪
♪For yours has been
the face I have dreamt of♪
♪Your path is the
one I'd like to follow♪
♪It's the first ever journey
that's been so enjoyable♪
♪Changing colors and smiling♪
♪Are the desires of my heart♪
♪Secretly quietly♪
♪There are moments in life
that get etched in memory♪
♪And there are those wonderful
people who never leave your heart♪
♪Everybody understands
the language of the heart♪
♪It connects even with strangers♪
♪Dusk seems to be saying
something to you and me♪
♪Secretly quietly♪
Grandma, this is Priya.
Priya, she's my Grandma.
-Hello, Grandma.
-Bless you.
We've met before.
I remember. Tell me something..
Why did you go away, the other day?
I fled, grandma! Out of fright.
Krishna was playing a ghost to scare us.
Ghost?
And that well-built Komal
Sir was trembling in his boots!
He was down with 104 degrees fever!
-Yes.
-What? 104 degrees?
Is that true, Krishna?
You shouldn't play such
pranks on anyone, my son.
Why scare someone so much?
Did you apologize?
Yes, Grandma. To everybody.
Priya, tell me something about yourself.
I live in Singapore with my Mother.
My father is no more.
I'm here in India on
a vacation with my friend.
Her family lives in Chandigarh.
I see.
I'll go and wash my hands.
Priya, for how many
more days are you here?
Days? We're leaving today.
In fact, right now.
Oh my God! I must leave now.
Everyone must be waiting for me.
Honey, here's my phone number.
Whenever you want to come here again
please give me the opportunity
to serve you again.
Okay Bahadur.
-Where's Priya?
-There she is!
Hurry, we've got to leave.
Come on, everybody! Get in!
-Krishna, nice meeting you.
-Thank you.
We really enjoyed your company, Krishna.
We'd love to come back.
It was great fun, Krishna.
I had a wonderful time with you.
I didn't even realize
how ten days have passed by.
I'm going to miss this place.
And you, too.
Look after yourself, Kalicharan.
I have to go now.
May I?
May I go?
Krishna, how will she go,
if you don't let go of her hand?
Bye. Visit again.
Priya, see.
Crazy.
Priya, it looks like you're no
longer Priya. You've become Radha.
Krishna's Radha.
I seriously think Krishna
has fallen in love with you.
Honey, pray that the boss' mood is okay,
we're five days late.
We are saying hi to them,
why are they waving five fingers at us?
Stupid!
The five fingers stand for five days.
Oh my God! You mean boss too?
You took a leave of 15 days
and have come after 20 days.
So you girls are now fired!
Why just India? Go on a world tour! Go!
Stop, Priya.
Sorry boss, but you can't insult us.
Boss, you can't question our integrity.
Agreed that we were on
a leave of 15 days.
But on the 16th day we got to work.
What amazing work have you done?
We have found an Indian super-boy.
Honey! What are you saying?
Let me speak, please.
Boss, this boy scales high mountains
as if they were mere steps for him!
He runs faster than a horse!
And guess what?
He puts his hand in the
river and pulls out fish!
Just think about it, if a boy
as talented as him were to come here,
your rating's are going to soar!
No way, boss! You will believe it too,
when you see him doing
all those incredible things here!
See him here!
How? How's he going to come here?
I tried to stop you,
but you just wouldn't listen!
Please, Priya! There was
no other way of saving our job.
Besides, what's wrong
if Krishna comes here?
There you go again!
Relax! Sit down.
If Krishna's talents are
showcased on our channel
he'd be the one who'd gain.
Name, fame, money.
He'll have everything!
He'll be a big man!
I know you're right, Honey,
but Krishna will never leave
his grandma and come.
She is his world.
But now you are a part of his world too.
I know. Now do as I say.
Call for Krishna!
Phone.
Krishna, phone.
He's coming!
Who's coming?
A boy? Is he an Indian?
Does he live here in Singapore?
Have you finally chosen someone, Priya?
There you go again, Mom!
I haven't chosen anyone.
So choose one!
I will, please leave now,
we got to save our jobs.
-And when will you settle down?
-Tomorrow.
Call from Priya!
Priya?
-Hello, Krishna.
-Priya.
How are you?
I'm fine, but I don't like anything.
Me too.
I can't sleep.
I want to meet you.
Me too.
He's not saying anything
more than "Me too", so what do I do?
You continue reading, read from here!
Priya, why are you quiet?
Krishna, can't you come here
and meet my mother?
Your mother?
Yes, if you don't meet my mother,
she'll get me married to someone else.
Someone else?
No, I won't let that happen!
I'm coming there to meet
your mother, Priya!
But, how will I get there?
Yes, how will you get here?
Hello, Krishna! Don't worry.
Just give the phone to Bahadur?
Krishna! Aircraft! Singapore!
Priya ma'am!
How? When?
♪Come let me tell you a love story♪
♪There was a boy and there was a girl♪
♪She smiled♪
♪He smiled♪
♪Little did they know
what was happening♪
♪Come let me tell you a love story♪
♪There was a boy and there was a girl♪
♪What they couldn't say
till then they started saying♪
♪What they couldn't hear
till then they started hearing♪
♪What they couldn't say
till then they started saying♪
♪What they couldn't hear
till then they started hearing♪
♪It brings a smile to my
face to see us falling in love♪
♪We're lost in love♪
♪The world didn't matter
to them anymore♪
♪There was a boy
and there was a girl♪
♪She smiled he smiled♪
♪Little did they know
what was happening♪
♪Come let me tell you a love story♪
♪There was a boy and there was a girl♪
♪There was no yearning
there was no aching♪
♪They came together
their hearts skipped a beat♪
♪There was no yearning
there was no aching♪
♪They came together
their hearts skipped a beat♪
♪What was destined happened♪
♪They got lost in love♪
♪Oh how one heart ruled the other!♪
♪There was a boy and there was a girl♪
-Grandma!
-I am here.
Grandma!
-Grandma!
-Put me down.
Oh God.
What's the matter, Krishna?
-Grandma.
-You look very happy today.
Grandma, I got a call from Priya!
You told me that she'd forgotten me?
But it's not true, Grandma!
She misses me every moment.
She's always thinking of me!
And she keeps seeing me everywhere!
And I never told you
I've been in a similar state.
Ever since Priya has left,
I never liked anything.
But today after her call, I feel better.
Grandma, Priya has called me to Singapore.
She wants me to meet her mother.
-Her mother?
-Yes.
If I don't go and ask for her hand
her mother's going to get her
married to someone else.
I said, I wouldn't let that happen,
I'm coming.
I did the right thing, didn't I Grandma?
May I go, Grandma?
It's only a matter of a few days, Grandma.
I'll ask for Priya's hand in
marriage and bring her back with me.
May I go, Grandma?
You're not answering, Grandma.
When you've already decided to go...
then, why are you asking me?
Go on. Go.
You aren't happy, Grandma?
Don't you like Priya?
I like Priya...
but, I don't like the
idea of you going so far.
If Priya really loves you...
she can also come here with her mother.
But you're not going there!
Why not?
I said you're not going,
it means you're not going.
That's it!
But why can't I go?
What's going to happen?
I've been hearing
this since I was a child!
Don't go here, don't go there,
don't do this, don't do that.
Don't go to the city with your friends!
Forget the city, you don't even allow
me to go beyond the river. Why?
Now you've become so big that
I have to give an explanations?
You'll have to tell me today, Grandma!
Why do you keep stopping me?
Why can't I go anywhere?
Because I don't want to lose you
So, what do you want then?
Cut me off from the world and
keep looking at your face forever?
Bang my head on trees
and mountains all my life?
You want me to be alone all my life?
Is that what you want?
But I can't do I that, Grandma!
I have my own life too,
my own dreams. I too want
to achieve something!
I want an identity for myself!
You don't want to lose me,
even if I have to lose Priya.
You can't see me happy.
I have always obeyed you.
And you can't agree to my one request?
Today I realize, how selfish you are!
You only think of yourself! Only yourself!
You don't care for me!
Had my parents been alive,
they'd have understood my feelings!
They'd have let me go,
they wouldn't have stopped me!
I wish your parents were alive.
I wish!
I'm sorry, Grandma.
See these stars, Krishna.
With these infinite
twinkling stars in the sky...
you, your father, your grandfather
and I share a very deep relationship.
Your grandfather was a space scientist.
One night, he started receiving a reply
to a signal he had sent to outer space.
Suddenly, we saw a UFO in the sky.
The car swerved out of control.
And there was an accident.
I survived the accident.
But your grandfather...
No!
I was pregnant with Rohit at that time.
He had sustained a
head injury in the accident.
Because of which he was born abnormal.
Even when he grew up,
he had the I.Q. of a child.
One night, in our small town,
a huge spaceship descended.
Some aliens emerged from it,
but one could not go back.
And that is how Rohit met Jadoo.
Jadoo had supernatural powers,
which he passed on to Rohit.
Rohit changed completely.
Jadoo eventually went away...
but he did not take back
the powers he had given to Rohit.
And thereafter,
everything changed forever.
My son could do things that...
were impossible for
an ordinary human being.
It was around then that
Rohit married your mother.
And very soon,
his fame spread across the world.
The chairman of the world's largest
Information Technology Company,
invited Rohit abroad.
Mr. Rohit Mehra?
I was, this book--
Oh yes, that's the first
copy of my latest book.
Please read it and give your opinion.
It's a wonderful book, Sir.
You've done a lot of research.
How can you say that without reading it?
I've already read it, Sir.
Read it?
There are printing errors
on page 126, 244 and 354.
I've marked them.
You've read this 400
page book in just ten minutes?
I forgot who I was talking to.
Asking you such questions
is an insult to your talent.
I still can't believe,
that I'm standing face to face
with a great scientist
and innovator like you.
Your achievements in the
field of wireless communication,
is no less than a revolution, Sir.
You've invented the palmtop.
People can watch cricket matches
on their phones, thanks to you.
I have a new dream, Rohit. A new vision.
If this dream comes true,
it could change the destiny of the world.
And I need your help
to realize this dream.
I want to build a computer
that can see the future.
What would you like, tea or coffee?
I understand your dream, your vision, Sir.
You want to combine astrology,
astronomy and technology,
to build a computer
that can see the future.
Exactly! That's precisely
why I've called you here.
Because the people
I have here are trained...
not gifted like you.
What are you thinking, Rohit?
Sir, if we can really build a computer
that can see the future then--
Then, think of the good we
can do for this planet and mankind!
Earthquakes,
famines, floods, can be prevented.
Even if we can't prevent them,
we can at least be prepared for them.
You've already started
seeing the future, Rohit.
In the hope that this union of brilliance
and vision will become history.
Create history!
It took him two whole years...
but Rohit achieved the impossible.
He built a computer
that could see the future.
It was around the time
when you were going to be born.
-Hello, Rohit!
-Mom!
Rohit, I've brought
Nisha to the hospital.
That's where I'm calling from.
Congratulations! You're
going to become a father anytime.
Come back soon.
I'm coming, mom. I'm coming!
Rohit, what's the matter?
You sound tense.
I've been exploited.
The world is very selfish,
but don't worry! I'll be back soon!
But my son did not come back.
Moments after you were born,
we received word...
that a fire broke out in the lab...
and they couldn't save Rohit.
Your mother couldn't bear the shock...
and passed away in a few days.
When you were five years old...
I got to know that you too
were born with extraordinary powers.
that Rohit had. I got scared.
I didn't want the world to know about you.
And that's why I brought you here.
A place where nobody knew us.
I didn't want to lose
you at any cost, Krishna.
You no longer want to see my face...
but I'm living only for you, Krishna.
Yes, I'm selfish, very selfish.
Grandma? What are you doing?
I've taken out some
of your father's clothes.
You can't go to Singapore like this!
But Grandma?
I could shield you from the world..
But not your heart.
Go, bring Priya here.
Go.
Krishna...
stay carefully there.
Eat and sleep on time,
don't talk too much with anybody.
And don't get into any trouble.
Whatever you do, make sure
you behave like any other man.
Don't get carried away to
do things that make people realize...
Who I am? Right, grandma?
Yes, my son.
Don't worry, grandma.
I won't let anybody know about me.
I'll keep my strength,
my abilities and my talent hidden.
That's a promise, grandma.
Your welcome sounds
different and nicer today.
I've come a few days in advance.
But I couldn't help it.
I've waited so many years but
now that we're so close to success...
being patient is very difficult.
I must say, you and your
team deserve credit
for making my dream come true again.
Sir, the credit goes to Rohit Mehra.
If it wasn't for his notes and research,
it would have been impossible
to build that computer again.
The computer that Rohit made in two years,
Has taken us many years to make.
That's why I still miss him.
Till now people say,
"Who has seen the future?"
But in a few days, you and I...
will change many truths
and idioms forever.
Breaking news!
After years of struggle,
hard work, research and patience,
Dr. Siddhant Arya's most ambitious
project is about to be completed.
According to our correspondent,
in just a few days,
Dr. Arya will be able to predict
the future of individuals,
countries and the world!
He'll also be able to change
the course of their destinies.
And the truth is, one who
can see and change the future,
Is considered like God!
Wrong!
Not Like God...
he is God!
Now, no one can stop me.
Hurry up.
-Oh!
-What have you done?
We're already late and then
this is how you park the car?
I can't even open the door!
How am I going to get out?
But neither can I!
Great! Let's just sit in
the car and stare at each other!
You always mess things up!
Krishna's flight must have landed.
He must be looking for us.
Are you okay? I hope you're not hurt.
Krishna?
Krishna, you look so
good in these clothes.
They are my fathers.
O my God! You look so handsome!
You two have come alone?
How can two people come alone?
No! I mean,
hasn't your mother come with you?
Mother?
Is she also coming here?
It would've been nice if she were here.
I'd have asked for your hand
and gone back to India immediately.
Grandma's all alone, you see.
He's in a tearing hurry!
Has he brought a priest along
to solemnize the wedding?
-What happened?
-Well actually, mom, you know--
-Her mom's gone.
-Yeah she's gone.
Gone?
-To Hong Kong.
-Yes, Hong Kong!
Hong Kong?
She'll be back in 10-15 days, right?
Yes, she'll come.
Ten to fifteen days? But what will
I do here for so many days?
Why Krishna? Didn't you take us around
your village when we came there?
Now we'll show you our city.
This is your apartment.
This is your living room.
This is your bedroom.
And these clothes are for you
This is your cell phone.
It has all our numbers.
You can call us anytime.
But why can't I live
with you in your house, Priya?
Well...
-Because mom--
-Is not around!
Yes! Mom's not around. Very silly.
-It doesn't look good.
-Yes.
Hey! My phone is ringing!
It says 'Mama' how do I take the call?
Looks like I gave you my
cell phone by mistake. Excuse me.
-Hello!
-Priya, there's good news.
I've got a very good
marriage proposal for you.
I'm busy right now.
I'll call you later, mom.
It was your mom's call?
Let me say hello to her.
No, it wasn't mom.
It was my uncle.
I could've said hello to him.
-Does he live here too?
-Yes.
No! He lives in India.
I see, where in India?
Krishna, we've got to go to the office.
We'll give you her uncle's address later,
with pin code.
But we've got to leave now. Bye!
How many lies do we have
to speak to cover up one lie?
-The excuse of an uncle saved us today!
-Tomorrow it'll be an aunt!
There is no dearth of relatives. Relax!
Did you see his eyes?
They were full of love and trust.
Honey, I can't do this!
I can't hurt Krishna anymore.
Hurt? He's going to become
a celebrity thanks to you.
And we'll get a promotion.
And even if he gets to know,
a small lie is not going to hurt him.
What happened?
You? How did you get here from
the 20th floor so quickly?
-I took the stairs.
-Stairs?
Actually, Priya...
I've got something for you.
What?
-I'll go get the car, okay?
-Honey!
Close your eyes.
Priya, why do you widen your
eyes whenever I ask you to close them?
Open them now.
May I put it on your finger?
Give me your hand.
Looks nice?
Yes, now it looks nice.
What happened?
I'll tell you later, lets go!
Brother!
Ten days will go by in no time.
Tell me how are you finding it there?
Its very nice, grandma.
There are a lot of
high-rise buildings here.
And my apartment is on the 20th floor.
And I'm talking to you
from the balcony right now.
Okay, okay, take care of yourself.
And give my love
and blessings to Priya.
That's the name of our new show.
Can you imagine a human being
climbing a tree faster than a monkey? No?
Well, after watching our show today.
You won't just imagine,
but also believe that is possible.
Get set then! On one end is the
world famous orangutan Mao!
Who in a blink, will climb this pole.
And on the other side
is Indian super-boy Krishna!
-What's happening here, Priya?
-What happened?
You brought me here to watch a shoot!
Yes. But then I thought that if
you can watch the shooting
you can perform in it!
But how can I climb
the pole faster than Mao?
Like you climbed the mountain!
The zigzag manner. Remember?
But what if I lose to Mao?
I'm sure you won't.
But what if I do?
Well...
I'll marry Mao then.
No! I'll never let that happen.
So, do it please! It'll be great fun.
Fun it will be.
Priya, there's just a pole's
distance between us and our success!
Not a pole, it's just a moment, stupid!
I've straightened a
lot of these smart alecs.
Honey!
I'm not going to the circus with you.
Strange! Why vent your
anger against Mao, on me?
How can I help it if
he refused to climb the pole?
And the fish?
Instead of coming into my hand
they palmed off a can, a shoe and that...
Wow! Priya smile!
In India you caught the fish so easily!
Actually those fish knew me,
they stood by me.
But you're not standing by me!
I've come to stand by you for life, Priya.
If my mother asks you what you do,
what will you say?
I'll tell her what I do.
Love you.
What else will you say?
I'll fulfil all your wishes,
look after you.
And?
I'll never let a smile leave your face.
Whether times good or
bad we'll always be together.
Just like eyelashes are with the eyes.
And?
You will dream and I'll fulfil them.
In the scorching heat of the sun,
I'll be your shade.
And in the cold, I'll give you warmth.
When the rains bother you,
I'll change the course of the clouds.
And when a storm blows,
I'll turn the winds away.
That's how I shall
protect you all my life...
from every danger..
from every trouble.
Now, I hope your mother will agree?
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪What have you ever done?♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪What have you ever done?♪
♪What have you done in this world?♪
♪If you've never fallen in love♪
♪You have set foot on the moon♪
♪You've made an abode in the seas♪
♪But have you taught those crying♪
♪How to laugh?♪
♪Even God will smile
and ask you one day♪
♪Heart♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪What have you ever done?♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪What have you ever done?♪
♪What have you done in this world?♪
♪If you've never fallen in love♪
♪Life's also a circus♪
♪Straight now upside down in a moment♪
♪Those who get love have
things straightened out♪
♪Else they keep hanging♪
♪It's the simple truth believe it♪
♪Heart♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪Taken♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪Given♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪What have you ever done?♪
♪What have you done in this world?♪
♪If you've never fallen in love♪
♪One more time♪
♪If you haven't taken a heart♪
♪If you haven't given your heart♪
♪Heart love♪
Priya!
I'll keep my strength,
my Abilities and my talent.. hidden.
That's a promise, Grandma.
Krrish.
Priya!
Are you all right?
But how did you get here?
You had fainted.
I had gone to get some water for you.
Take it. What a blaze!
Till yesterday, we only had a description,
and a picture of the masked man.
Today, we've got to know his name,
And also got a piece of his mask.
Let's find out how.
-So his name is Krrish!
-Krrish!
But his identity is
still shrouded in mystery.
Whoever Krrish is, a bravery award
and cash reward of 25000 dollars,
has been announced in
appreciation of his courage.
So how are we going to identify Krrish?
The one, whose mask
this piece matches with,
will be considered to be Krrish.
And he'll be the one to be rewarded.
Krrish! Krrish!
After all who is this Krrish?
Listen carefully,
our priority at the moment is Krrish.
Only Krrish! Get that?
Krrish's identity.
Our channel should
be the first to reveal him!
Our channel must be the first
one to unmask this masked Krrish!
Where are the two of you going?
To look for Krrish.
Ah, forget Krrish.
And look for a new job.
New job?
You better go back to India,
and enjoy your Krishna's flute playing.
Thanks to Krishna we're jobless.
Now what do we do?
Honey, I think Krrish is
none other than our own Krishna.
-What?
-Yes, Honey!
At the circus, I saw Krrish
from such a close distance.
I have a strong feeling
that Krishna is Krrish.
So, why didn't you tell
this to boss at the meeting?
Because I wasn't sure,
I need to confirm it first.
Confirm? How?
Listen, I have an idea.
-Hello, Priya.
-Honey, these guys?
Priya! I've hired some actors.
But I'm a bit late.
-I'll be there soon.
-What?
-So who are these guys?
-Which guys?
Let go!
Krishna!
I thought you were Krrish
and planned my own kidnapping.
But then, real goons turned
up instead of the hired ones.
Real goons?
But why didn't you hit back?
Why did you quietly take their beating?
I wanted to see...
whether it hurts you to see me in pain.
It does.
Where's your ring?
Maybe they've...
Krrish! Krrish!
Not once did it occur to me
that Christian could also be Krrish!
He was also there
at the circus that night!
Had it struck me that night--
I wouldn't have got a thrashing!
I've said sorry, haven't I?
What else do you want me to do?
Close your eyes.
Again you...
Now open them.
How did you get it back?
Krrish, he's my friend.
Wouldn't he do this much for me?
Take it.
Won't you put it on my finger?
♪Where the rays of the sun come from?♪
♪Where the moonlight dwells♪
♪Comes news♪
♪There's no one like you♪
♪Where sleep hides?♪
♪Where dreams are made♪
♪Comes news♪
♪There's no one like you♪
♪Flower butterflies the buds♪
♪They're all sulking♪
♪From them you have stolen♪
♪Their ability to evoke love♪
♪Where colors are created?♪
♪and beauty is crafted♪
♪Comes news♪
♪There's no one like you♪
♪You have stolen my heart♪
♪Do you realize that?♪
♪In you lies all the love in the world♪
♪In you it lies♪
♪Where people go crazy in love♪
♪Where lovers are born♪
♪Comes news♪
♪There's no one like you♪
Wow! Krishna, look here.
Priya! Priya!
Move from there.
Priya, you're watching TV here,
and the boss has ordered us
to vacate Krishna's apartment.
Hello! Are you listening?
I am and am not.
What's this?
-Remember the explosion at the circus?
-Yes.
I had passed out,
but I think the camera was still on.
Now switch off the TV and
think about Krishna! Please!
What happened?
I'll rewind and show you.
Krishna is Krrish!
What happened?
-Let's go, Honey.
-Why are you girls screaming?
-Hurry up.
-Aunt.
-Where are you both going?
-Mom, office!
-Office?
-Come on Honey!
To get our jobs back! Okay bye!
Priya, your mobile.
Hello Priya?
No, I'm Priya's mother.
Mother? Hello.
When did you return from Hong Kong?
Hong Kong? I didn't go anywhere.
I've been right here.
Who are you?
It's me, Krishna.
Krishna who?
Priya has told you everything
about me, hasn't she?
No, Priya has said nothing about you.
You are Priya's mother, aren't you?
Yes, I'm Priya's mother.
Where's Priya?
Priya left for office just now.
Office?
Okay. Thank you.
Priya, do you realize?
Once this footage is telecast...
our Krishna will become
a world famous celebrity!
There's something about our Krishna!
He fooled us so convincingly.
In India, as Kalicharan,
and here, as Krrish!
Didn't I tell you Honey,
the truth always comes out?
Look Priya, the truth about Krishna
the world is about to discover,
is because you lied!
The lie that you love him brought
him here all the way from India.
A lie sometimes leads to very big gains.
You didn't even tell me!
What could I say?
When his honesty turned my
feigned love into a genuine one...
I didn't even realize.
Krishna, Krishna.
The culprit has been caught at last!
He did his best to hide his identity,
you know.
But I finally discovered
who the real Krrish is!
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you keep me in the dark?
Where was the need to hide
behind a mask, even with me?
You're asking this Priya?
Someone who has never
been honest with me.
Someone who kept me
in the dark till today.
I have been unmasked Priya.
What about you?
What do you mean?
Why did you lie to
me that you loved me?
I took your lies for
the truth and came here...
to ask your mother
for your hand in marriage.
But you lied about her too!
Yes, Priya.
I've spoken to your mother.
Krishna..
I admit, I lied to you in the beginning.
But now...
I really love you Krishna.
Stop it, Priya! Stop it!
You may have more lies to tell me.
But I don't have the strength
to take them for the truth anymore!
Listen to me, Krishna!
I've done all this only for you.
I wanted to see you
become a very big man,
and that's about to
happen in just a few hours.
The whole world will get to know
about your extraordinary
powers and talent.
That's exactly what I didn't want!
Why do you think I wore the mask?
Because I had promised grandma
that I'd keep my identity hidden.
That I would not let
anyone know about my powers.
And you...
Grandma was right.
People in the world only use each other
for their own selfish reasons.
She tried to stop me, but I--
But why does your
grandmother want to stop you?
Why does she always want
you in front of her eyes?
Why doesn't she want the
whole world to know of your talent?
-Is she not being selfish?
-Priya!
You really want to know?
Then listen!
Having lost her son,
grandma did not want to lose me
because I posses the same powers.
But she still let me come here...
for you...
For my feelings, she gave in.
But what do I tell her now?
Krishna, listen to me.
We've got to stop the
telecast of Krishna's tape.
Why?
Don't ask questions now,
just stop the telecast.
But the tape is with the boss.
Oh my God! Where's boss at the moment?
Twenty years ago,
you tried to make a computer
that could see the future.
What happened to that dream of yours?
Twenty years ago, you must
have had a lot of dreams too.
Did they all come true?
Pardon me?
Some questions hurt.
The media ought to understand.
That dream died with the death
of my genius friend, Rohit Mehra.
But from what I've read
and heard of you, Dr. Arya,
you don't ever accept defeat.
I'd have tried to win.
Had my genius friend been alive.
Krishna!
Krishna.
Anything left to say?
Yes, this gentleman
has something to say.
Who are you?
My name is Vikram Sinha.
What do you want?
Don't go back the way you came.
-What does that mean?
-I mean, you came alone...
don't go back alone.
Krishna, your father,
Rohit Mehra, is still alive.
What did you say?
This picture was taken when
your father worked for Dr. Arya.
And I was the Senior Security
Officer at Technotronics.
He was younger to me in age,
and I was a junior in status.
And yet, we were very close friends..
Not only because we were Indians.
It was because of
the sincerity in his smile.
And the honesty in his eyes.
He was always smiling.
But someone cast an evil eye on him.
It's been so many years...
but that time...
seems to have frozen.
That day, he was working till morning,
because he had to complete
his project and go back to India.
Mr. Vikram? Welcome!
I'm doing fine, chief,
but if you keep working
round the clock like this,
you're going to get insomnia.
I won't have to do it after today.
Once the computer is inaugurated today,
I'll hand it over to Dr. Arya
and return to my family in India.
I don't mind, chief..
but I still can't believe
that we can see the future.
Not believing does not
change the truth, Mr. Vikram.
You will believe it, when you see it?
What? You mean you're going to..
Of course!
Come see tomorrow, today...
and tell me how it
feels to see the future.
Please, hold this.
Retina scan, an identification of my eyes.
These two identifications of mine
are the password for this computer,
without which it won't start up.
But when you're not around,
when you've gone back to India?
I'll change the password before I leave.
After that, only Dr. Arya
will be able to start the computer.
Tell me...
what would you like to see?
I don't want to see anything, chief!
But you said your wife is pregnant.
Let's see whether I'm going
to be an uncle to a nephew or a niece?
Okay then. Let's find out.
Nisha!
My darling baby.
Look, Nisha,
your son looks just like Rohit.
Now go to your Mom.
My son's coming back to me.
Congratulations, chief!
Your wife's going to
deliver a baby boy tomorrow!
But I'm going to distribute
sweets today! In fact, right now?
What did you say?
What happened to my Rohit?
What happened, mom?
No! That's impossible!
My Rohit can't be dead!
My Rohit is alive!
No!
Which means, I...
Chief, the computer's malfunctioning!
Something's wrong with it!
Dr. Arya!
It's 6:40 there, it's 6:30 now!
This means, in just ten minutes!
In this very room!
Look! Dr. Arya!
Have you heard of Shahjahan,
Doctor Mathur?
Of course! He built the Taj Mahal.
Incomplete knowledge is always dangerous.
Shahjahan had the hands of workers
who built the Taj Mahal, chopped off,
so that there would
never be another Taj Mahal.
Rohit Mehra is a worker
for me and I'm his Shahjehan.
You mean, you're also
going to cut off Rohit's hands?
No, his brain!
Because Rohit's brain will create problems
for himself as well as for me.
Actually, I'm going to
feel very sorry about it,
because Rohit is a very good boy.
Sincere, honest, intelligent.
They're coming here, chief.
Please leave!
No, no! I'm won't let this
computer go into the wrong hands.
I'll destroy everything!
All right! I'll try and stop them!
-Hello!
-Mom?
Rohit? I've brought Nisha to the hospital.
Congratulations!
You're going to become a father soon.
Come home soon, son
I'm coming, mom! I'm coming!
Rohit, what's the matter?
You sound tense?
I've been exploited,
the world is very selfish!
Don't worry,
I'll be back, I'll be back soon.
Rohit!
What have you done?
I've destroyed your dream.
I've destroyed everything!
Because I've got
to know of your intentions.
But those who know me also
know that I never accept defeat.
I'll rebuild this compute,.
using your research.
But I don't need you anymore.
Hold it, sir!
Don't kill him, sir.
If you kill Rohit, then even
If you build the computer again...
you'll never be able to start it.
You need a password
to start the computer,
and the password is Rohit himself.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
If scans of his retina and
heartbeat aren't fed into the computer,
the computer will not start.
This means I'll have to keep you alive,
until I build a new computer.
But die, you will.
For the world.
Breaking news.
Tragedy strikes!
Following a fire that broke
out in the lab of Technotronics,.
the famous Indian genius Rohit
Mehra has met with a tragic death.
Let's observe a minute minute silence,
so that Rohit Mehra's soul rests in peace.
Ever since, I had no choice
but to work for Dr. Arya.
I couldn't even go to the police...
because if Dr. Arya doubted me,
he would've killed me.
And I was the only man who
could get in touch with your family.
That's exactly why I've been looking
for you and your grandma
for so many years.
And finally,
I met you today through Priya.
Dr. Arya.
Twenty years.
For 20 years,
he's kept a mother away from her son...
and a son away from his father.
It's because of his
lies that I lost my mother.
Where is my father?
Here in Singapore.
For 20 years Dr. Arya has used
machines to keep him in a state
that only his brain is alive,
his body almost dead.
How are you feeling today?
Are these machines
taking good care of you?
Tomorrow's the glorious and historic day,
when my, sorry,
our computer will be inaugurated.
Yes! Ours, because nothing
was possible without you.
For so many years, you have shown
such patience and understanding.
And cooperated with me.
When the computer starts tomorrow...
Your utility will come to an end,
and so will your pain.
Dr. Arya has suddenly been
reminded of the poet Kabir.
Do today, what you must do tomorrow,
and do right now, what you must do today.
That's why, Dr. Arya has decided
to start the computer today himself.
And also end Rohit's life.
Is this where my father is kept?
Yes! But it's almost impossible
for a stranger to get there.
Dr. Arya has kept very tight
security everywhere on the island.
So that now no one comes
between him and the computer.
Krishna, if Dr. Arya starts the computer,
how much havoc he can wreak,
and the destruction he
can cause is unimaginable.
Mine... yours... ours...
The worlds destiny
will come in his clutches.
That's why, Dr. Arya has
to be stopped at any cost.
Now you have to save
not only your father,
but the whole mankind, Krishna.
-Hello.
-Krishna!
Grandma!
Krishna, are you okay?
Yes, Grandma.
I don't know why I'm feeling worried.
When are you coming back?
Come back soon.
Your father's death
anniversary is nearing.
You need to be here and
fulfil the duties of a son.
I remember, grandma. Don't worry...
I'll fulfil all the duties of a son.
See, Rohit I've won!
Now if you want you can end your life.
Or do you want me to help?
But what's the hurry?
At least see...
how your invention
is going to make me God!
Rohit, we built this computer...
so that we can see
our future and change it!
I will also change my future
and show you today itself!
Dr. Arya's gone to
look for the masked man.
Christian! Christian! Christian!
Krishna!
Look Dr. Arya!
Christian!
What had Christian done? Why kill him?
Dr. Arya has probably started
the computer and, he must've seen--
His future!
It will be just as Dr. Arya has seen.
Krrish!
Justin!
I've changed my future!
I've changed my tomorrow!
There is no mask any longer.
Henceforth the new face of God is...
Dr. Siddhant Arya!
I've killed him with my own hands.
Its 9:15 there and it's 9 here.
This means, he'll be here
in the next 15 minutes.
To capture him we
need planning not power.
Dr. Arya has kept very tight
security everywhere on the island.
I have seen the future.
But due to lack of time, what I
couldn't see is what I want to know.
Why do you want to kill me?
And why do you want
to rescue Rohit Mehra?
Who are you?
Come to me and give me the answer.
I've told you, I have seen the future,
and I know who is with me.
Hello!
And who is against me.
So, please co-operate.
Who are you?
We'll get to know right now!
Your son Krishna!
Mom.
Rohit!
Translation: Rudolf D'sa