This tale began with the birth
of a mentally challenged boy, Rohit.
As years went by, his physical
growth continued unhindered...
but his mental age
remained that of a child.
The way he spoke,
his habits, everything...
But he had to pay a
price for his innocence.
Everyone makes fun of me.
lf you don't help me, then who will?
You are so powerful.
Please God, please can you
give me a little bit of your power?
And, one night,
a space-ship landed in Kasauli.
Rohit found Jaadu...
and his life turned into bliss.
Jaadu blessed Rohit
with amazing powers...
...and that transformed
him completely.
Rohit's fame spread far and wide.
One day he received
a special invitation...
...to visit Singapore
for some research.
The invitatioh was sent
by the fannmous Dr. rSidddhant Arya.
Mr. Rohit Mehra,
l'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Unfortunately Sonia
Mehra lost both her...
son Rohit and daughter-in-law
Nisha forever...
and her grandson Krishna
became her reason to live.
But, she was so scared by
Krishna's baffling super powers that
she took him away to
a remote and unknown location.
But Destiny chose the path of love...
Krishna followed his love,
Priya, to Singapore...
where he learnt the
shocking truth that...
his father Dr. Rohit Mehra was alive.
And was being held captive by Dr.
Siddhant Arya since many years.
Tinnme saw Krishna
create a hew history.
With a broken piece of a mask...
...that he donned in
the midst of a circus fire.
And, this led to the birth of...
a protector, a friend, a superhero
Krrish!
Kaal's experiment is a success.
Now, this virus...
will mark the beginning...
of the end of humanity.
Thahk you, Jaadu.
l have now understood your secret
of harnessing the power of sunlight.
lf this experiment is successful...
it will usher in a new beginning...
for this world, for all mankind.
Just 10 more minutes.
Papa? What happened?
ls everything alright?
Of course.
l am also fine!
And everything is also fine!
ln fact, l am so excited that...
Papa?
Oh , sorry for waking you up.
But, it's just 9 minutes to sunrise.
Come on,
you have to come up to the lab.
Come on! - Yes, papa.
C'mon!
lt should all work today!
l have tweaked the
formation to perfection.
My calculations should
not go wrong today.
Wow, papa!
What's all this?
My years of hardwork...
and endeavour.
Because life originates in light.
Light gives life.
And, l think l have finally...
managed to create the
perfect combination...
to multiply the energy of light...
by using mirrors to reflect it.
This nnmag.ical connmbination
is nnaturahhy ppresent in natureu.
But, unfortunately we cannot see it.
Hence, l have invented this pen...
which is actually
an electronic device.
Whenever it's in the presence
of such a combination...
it gets activated
and starts beeping...
And then,
it consolidates and multiplies...
all the light beams and
concentrates it on a subject.
And, manifests the life
giving properties of light.
You mean, the rays of the sun will...
revive this dead plant?
What?
But that's impossible!
What do you mean?
Of course it's possible!
lt will, l am certain.
Fingers crossed, cross them!
Papa, the sun...
The ppeh has been activated.
This means... the placement
of all the mirrors is correct.
The formation is absoluteehy right.
The power of the
energy is far too much.
l have to think of something.
l must do something.
Perhaps, we need to build a filter...
that passes just the
right amount of radiance...
and absorbs the rest of the energy.
You mean...
a filter with a brain, papa?
Correct. A filter with a brain!
Easy, l will build it.
And then you'll see.
This experiment will
change face of solar energy.
What are you staring at?
Don't you have work today?
Come on, time to go to office!
A filter with a brain.
Easy, l'll do it.
Krishna!
Ready, papa.
Hmm... smart you're looking.
Thahk you.
Did you fix the tyre that
someone punctured yesterday?
Yeah, no...
the thing is...
Where the hell is Priya?
Priya!
l am coming!
Ready, papa.
Sure.
Get dressed, first.
l am ready.
Are you sure?
l was only touching up...
l will finish it up in the car.
Puncture!
Look.
Yeah.
Wow!
Now you look perfectly ready!
l am also ready.
Okay, since we are all ready,
let's go paint the town red.
Red?
Don't you have to go
work at the TV channel today?
l have to.
But, after a quick
visit to the parlour.
Alright Krishna.
Your office is here.
Oh, actually my new
office is a little ahead.
lf you take the next right...
...then again the right
after the first left...
you will reach the security agency,
that's my new office.
Even the Air lndia job?
Hurry up! l am getting late!
Don't change the topic.
What happened this time?
l know what happened.
What?
When the clients must be
coming to book their air tickets...
he must have been in the air!
Hence, the airline
authorities must have...
permanently grounded him.
And told him to take off for good.
Correct?
Right, papa.
That is exactly what happened.
Very good.
l'm proud of you.
That's it. Right there. Stop.
This is my neww officee.
You work at SlS?
Oh husband, come here.
Yes, wife?
l am going to leave
the studio at 4:30 pm.
You have to meet me at 5:00 pm sharp.
l hope you haven't forgotten.
Yes.
lf you are late again, Mr. Mehra...
maybe you'll get fired
from being a husband too...
l know. Bye.
Bye.
Alright, papa.
Where should l drop you off?
What do you mean?
l haven't been sacked, yet.
Drop me off at the lab as always.
We shall overcome...
Krishna...
Kripal... you both have been fired.
Here's your termination letter...
and here's yours.
What's wrong?
Shrunk from a football
to a tennis ball?
Yesterday, when those four robbers
broke into the jewellery store...
you disappeared!
Are you really surprised
they fired you?
But, you also?
Well, even l ran.
But l ran away, so l could come back.
What do you mean?
l mean...
what are you all staring at?
We have been sacked...
but you still have jobs to do.
Get going. - Okay.
You don't understand.
Yesterday, after l ran off.
l mean, left...
who entered the store?
Who?
Who entered?
Krrish!
Correct!
Understood the secret?
What's my full name?
Kripal Sharma.
Yes, take the Kri of Kripal.
Kri.
And the Sh of Sharma.
Sh.
Put them together, what do you get?
Krrish.
You?
Not so loud.
lf anyone hears, a crowd will gather.
People will ask for autographs,
you know what l mean...
You still think l am wrong.
Right?
Height!
Krrish is quite tall.
And you are...
One has to adjust things, my friend.
Tall, when a fight is on.
But l like to be small on duty.
Never mind, you won't get it.
That's the style of us supermen.
And, you are a mere common man.
Go ahead and find a job
that you might be good at.
Correct?
Breaking news from Mumbai.
The front landing
gear of flight AKA 101...
coming in from Delhi
to Mumbai is jammed.
All the attempts of the pilot
to extend it have been futile.
Failure to lock down the landing
gear can cause a crash landing.
This can prove fatal
to all the passengers...
...and the crew present
in the aircraft.
See? Duty calls. l must go.
'And, we'll keep updating you about
it, time to time.' - Where did he go?
Mumbai Control. AKA 101...
waiting for instructions.
AKA 101...
we have cleared runway
2-7 for emergency landing...
you are cleared to land.
Best of Luck.
Sir, landing without an
extended nose landing gear...
can cause the plane to skid...
it can even explode.
We don't have any other option.
We have run out of fuel.
We have to take this chance.
Pay Attention, please keep
your seat belts fastened...
and take brace position for landing.
What did he say?
What's happening?
Looks like something is really wrong.
What's going on?
Mom, we are going to be fine?
God, Please help us. Please...
Bravo, Krrish.
Super job, Krrish.
We have safely landed.
Krrish!
Look mum, Krrish! - What? Where?
An eppiddemic of ah unknowh
virus has brokeun out ih lNamibia.
Disturbing images of
the virus outbreak have...
...just come in from
the city of Gobabis.
Our correspondent is currently
at the local office...
...of the lnternational
Health Council...
waiting for a statement from Dr.
Varun Shetty...
...Regional Director of the WHO.
On my return from
Namibia this morning...
l have immediately briefed
senior members of the lHC...
about the current
state of this outbreak.
This virus needs to be
contained as soon as possible.
Otherwise the consequences would be,
would be catastrophic.
lnfected samples of blood have
been dispatched to distinguished...
...scientists and doctors
in all parts of the world.
We need,
we need all the help possible...
...in coming out with an antidote.
lt is now quite clear that
the Namibia crisis is escalating.
Our channel has set
up a toll free emergency...
...help line for any
virus related information.
Hello, Yes, Dr. Shetty?
Dr. Mehra, l am sure you must have...
...heard about the
life threatening virus...
that is creating panic in Namibia.
Yes, we just saw it on TV...
Dr. Shetty, how long does it take for
the symptoms of this virus to show?
What is the incubation period?
People start exhibiting
the symptoms within...
...5 seconds to 5 minutes of contact.
This virus is sppreadihg
rappiddly through air ahd wwater.
We have sent the
blood samples of the...
...infected people
to several labs worldwide.
You will receive it too.
And, l am really hopeful that...
you will be successful
in coming up with a solution.
That's why,
you are my last hope, Dr. Mehra.
Please, do something.
l will give it my all, Dr Shetty.
l'll try my best.
Hello.
Hello, Dr. Shetty?
Yes, who's this?
Hello sir, this is Alok Sen.
Dr. Alok Sen.
Sir, l have to meet you right now.
lt's very urgent sir. Please, sir.
Regarding what?
Sir...
l have some shocking
information about...
the virus outbreak in
Namibia and its antidote.
What!
l will tell you everything
when we meet, sir.
That's why l am calling froom
a pay phohe, sir. Pleease, sir.
Okay... calm down, Dr. Sen.
l am heading to my office.
Why don't you come there?
The adddress is...
Yes, sir. l know where it is,
l'll be there soon.
Good evening, sir.
Good evening.
l am expecting someone.
Okay, sir. - Thanks.
Who are you?
Unique, Unusual, Unparalleled.
Because, l have no history...
no past.
Just the present.
Surprised?
Whoever you are, you have
clearly come to the wrong place.
The place is also right,
and so is the time.
The sameu cah't bee said
abboout my intenntions thoug.h...
What nonsense! Please leave!
At least get to know me first.
l am the answer
to all your questions.
- Look... - You look...
into my eyes...
to find yourself.
What the hell do
you think you are doing?
Sir, there is a Dr.
Sen here to see you...
Send him in.
Right, sir.
Dr. Shetty? l'm Dr. Sen.
Thank you for meeting me.
You said you wanted to tell
me something about the virus?
Yes, sir. Here...
This contains a sample of the virus,
and it's ahtiddote.
l work for Kaal Pharmaceuticals.
This company experiments
with the fusion of DNA...
of different species to
create antidotes for viruses.
But sir...
l recently discovered that...
before they can formulate
the antidote, they create the virus.
They have laboratories
all over the world.
Sir, l've collected
all evidence against them...
...and saved it in this pen drive.
You were assigned
charge of Lab no. 3.
Where you had to put together
the DNA of various species...
but instead you put
together these files?
How do you know?
l know!
You've made a grave
mistake by cheating him.
He can't stand traitors.
This is Kaya.
A miracle of science.
Created by the one,
who is creating...
his own, new and
extraordinary world on Earth.
This is Kaal.
He believes that he is the
master of his own life and destiny.
An enigma.
A scientific genius.
His research of many years
is now capable of changing the world.
But he began every experiment
with the aim of changing himself.
lt is rather ironic that...
a brain so sharp is housed in a body
that is paralyzed below the neck...
except for two of his fingers.
Unbelievable as it is,
but it is true...
that Kaal can conjure up the power
of his mind into these two fingers...
to lift things, make them fly, or
destroy them, through telekninesis.
Yet, he has been attempting
to obtain the bone marrow...
which would rejuvenate him.
But when Kaal,
with his unusual DNA...
could not find his
cure among humans...
he began experimenting on animals.
Fusing together his DNA and
blood with that of the animals'...
Kaal created creatures
as one creates test tube babies.
ln this process,
Kaal made such amazing creatures...
whose mind and soul were Kaal's.
human in appearance but
beastly in nature and strength.
Kaal has named them...
Manimals!
But despite all efforts Kaal
hasn't found the bone marrow yet.
His search still continues.
lnitiate!
Start Deliquidation!
Fusion is the future!
Begin the final test.
Kaal... - Let it learn
to survive in this environment...
and, continue your research.
l am sure you will
find that bone marrow.
And success will be yours soon.
l am successful even today.
You may have noticed the lethal
strike of my new manimal, Striker.
Success was Kaal's...
even when he made you.
Fusing my blood with
that of a chameleon's.
That's thee reasoh yoou
cah chahge your foorm ahd shape.
Wherever, whenever.
Let's find out how many lives
the virus has claimed in Namibia.
These reed doots indicateu
that moore thah...
40% of Namibia's population
has been infected by the virus.
This has thrown many genius
scientists off their keel.
Our scientists want to know
when we should send our antidote.
Let some more people die.
Let there be more fear.
lt's simple science, Kaya.
Our profit will rise
as people's hopes fall.
This virus is hot natural...
it was created.
But, sir...who would do such a thing?
A madman.
Dr. Mehra,
an antidote has been successfully...
...made for the virus
outbreak in Namibia.
This breakthrough was achievedd by a
connmppany called Kaal Pharmaceeuticals.
The antidote has reached Namibia
and the situation is under control.
Thahk Goddl
This antidoote has
pproveed yet agaih that...
there are more kind hearted
people than evil ones.
Krrish.
Al Sabah 13th floor, Millat Nagar.
Help! Help me!
Mummy!
Somebody, help!
Vicky!
Help! Help me!
Help me.
There's no need to be scared anymore,
you are safe now.
Okay?
ln fact, we're both safe.
But tell me something...
what were you doing up there?
l was doing my homework, when
l saw a pigeon stuck in the wires...
struggling to break free.
So l went up to the
roof to set it free.
Though l have small hands...
l managed to set the pigeon free.
But l got trapped.
Mother, help me. Mother.
But you saved me, Krrish.
Thahk you, hKrrish.
Thahk you...
Krrish.
Me?
You saved the pigeon's life.
Anyone who takes away tears
and spreads happiness is Krrish!
Wow, even l am Krrish!
Yes.
But, Krrish,
you have a mask, a suit...
and super powers.
What do l have?
You have an innocence which
has taught me a lesson today.
That, agee ddoesn't matter,
courag.ee does.
Here's a small gift,
from Krrish, to little Krrish.
This is now the symbol of
your honesty and righteousness.
Welcome to the team.
Team? l am a part
of your team, Krrish?
Yes, but you must promise me that...
you won't try to imitate me by...
...climbing,
jumping and leaping off buildings.
Promise? - l promise, Krrish.
Gone.
Sir... yes, sir?
Welcome!
How nice of you to make it on time!
Might as well have
come after we closed.
By the way,
may l ask you what took you so long?
l had to go, sir.
You had to go?
Yes, sir.
lt was more important than your job?
No.
The gueests wereu waiting
for Chiheese foodd...
and they left with a mouthful
of lndian abuses. - Breaking news!
Do you get it?
Eternal savior,
Krrish, rescued another kid and...
safely reunited him with his family.
Proving yet again, where
there's crisis, there is Krrish.
On one hand there's Krrish.
He flies like the wind,
winning over hopeless situations.
Yes. - And,
on the other, there's you.
You run like the wind
from situations which need you.
You could learn
something from Krrish.
Perhaps,
if you'd been more like him...
l wouldn't have to sack you.
You are fired!
Sir, please.
And, before we wind up,
another breaking news.
Our reliable sources
have confirmed that...
Krrish will be off duty,
starting 11 :30 tonight.
That's it for now.
This is Priya Mehra, Aaj Tak.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Krishna.
Happy birthday, husband!
This is the best surprise ever!
Well, l've also got
you the best gift ever!
What?
We're going to have a baby!
You...
''The preetttieest of ahl''
''So different from all''
''Look at her, that's my love''
''The worhd has manifeested
for theu sake of hoe''
''And my love has given
me a blessed gift''
''Raghupati Raghav''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''Non stop party''
''Tonight's party''
''Tonight's ceheubratioohs,
l dedicate to you''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''Non stop party''
''Tonight's party''
''Tonight's ceheubratioohs,
l dedicate to you''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''Raghupati Raghav''
''What a bbeautiful night''
''Unbelievable''
''My life''
''rShe is besidde me''
''l am so restless''
''Almost drunk''
''lntoxicated with my desires''
''A prayer once uttered by our lips''
''Has now been fulfilled by the Lord''
''My words are not enough to thank Him''
''Raghupati Raghav''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''Non stop party''
''Tonight's party''
''Tonight's ceheubratioohs,
l dedicate to you''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''What a groove''
''l want to move''
''Check it out''
''More colorful than colors''
''A moment so wonderful yet deep''
''This time wwihh hever connmee again''
''We might neer get this chahceu ag.ain''
''Newer dreams, light up my eyes''
''My thoughts go through a crazy riot''
''My desires have lost direction''
''My friends''
''My friends, salute to you all''
''Raghupati Raghav Raja Ram''
''Raghupati Raghav''
Today is a very happy day for us.
When kids grow up...
they start treating elders like kids.
l know it's Krishna's birthday today.
l've even got him a gift.
There's some other good news.
And Mr. Balgopal will
tell you what it is, himself.
Some other good news?
And, who is Mr. Balgopal?
l don't think l even
have any friends by this name.
Actually, l may just.
One can't even recall all
the names of his friends at this age.
Balgopal?
That's your hameu tooo!
You are going to be a grandpa.
Grandpa?
Really?
Yes, papa.
Every father wants
to see his kids grow up.
Wants to play with them,
fool around with them...
But that joy was taken away from me.
l could not see the number
of times you fell down...
the number of times you
got back up on your feet...
all the times you came
home covered in muck.
l still regret not being
able to witness all of that.
But, now, l have no regrets.
No complaints.
So what if l couldn't
be there as a father.
l will be there now, as a grandpa.
l will live up your childhood...
through your child.
Thahk you, Priya,
for coompheting our snnmahh family.
And yes.
Happy birthday, Krishna.
Here's a small gift for you...
for both of you.
Okay, papa.
And l will distribute these
sweets among my colleagues.
Everyone will be thrilled.
lt will be a fun day.
What are you doing, Kaal?
lf only l had the use
of all of my fingers...
my whole hand...
my entire body.
You have no idea what
l would be capable of.
l am still amazed...
how you manage to do, what you do.
How did you get these powers?
What is the secret behind it?
lnspite of being so powerful,
why is...
...your body still
wheelchair bound, Kaal?
Kaal, you are choking me.
lt hurts.
And it should.
Because, you have hurt me.
By asking me the question...
for which l don't have an answer.
And l am still searching for it.
What are you doing, son?
Don't misuse your powers.
Don't use your powers
for destruction.
How many times have l told you, Kaal?
And how many times
have l asked you, dad?
How did l get these powers?
Why am l like this?
l don't know that.
You have been lying all this while.
You are lying now too.
Trust me, l am telling you the truth.
Stop it, Kaal.
Kaal...
l didn't find an answer then.
Even after all this research,
all these experiments...
l still haven't found the answer.
But, l know science has the answer.
And, therein lies my cure.
My cure lies in that answer.
l have spent millions.
l will spend billions.
Doctors, how much have we earned
from the antidote sales in Namibia?
320 million dollars and counting.
A little fear and
320 million dollars.
And still counting!
The businneess of feuar...
is the best business.
But now millions are not enough,
we need to earn in billions.
lt is now time,
to plant the virus in a country...
that has a population of billions.
lndia? Or, China?
China's population surpasses
that of lndia, Kaal.
But a million Gods rule over lndia.
And people have
immense faith in them.
Let's find out if
any one of their Gods...
can save them from our virus.
Krishna, let's have ice cream?
lce cream?
But l heard, during pregnancy...
women like to have sour things.
But l am craving for sweet things.
- Really?
Because l want our baby
to turn out sweet, like you.
Okay.
Let's go and sit there.
Stop licking the ice cream like that!
You ate up my ice cream?
l thought you got it for me!
l couldn't eat my own!
How could l eat yours?
Let's get another one. - Let's go.
Kripal, what's up?
l am quite worked up.
l am trying to control my anger.
Because l was just accused
of being an ice cream thief.
We'd like to have same flavor again.
- Okay, sir.
So, what will you have?
So, you are handing
over empty cones to us!
Sir, l had filled it.
lf it was full, why is it empty now?
Sir, you can see while
l fill the scoop again.
Yes, do it in front of me.
Two choco blocks, please.
Sir, you saw it for yourself!
l had filled it!
Yeah, he filled
it and yet it's empty.
Mummy, my ice cream?
l just got you one.
Where's my ice cream gone?
Where is my ice cream?
Mummy, my ice cream?
Can you fill it once more please?
- Yes. sir.
What is it?
l'll be right back.
But...
Yes, Kaya.
Kaal, Mumbai's pulse
is about to change.
Nerve wracking reports coming
in from several parts of Mumbai.
This virus is sppreadihg
across Mumbbai cityy.
The wwhoohe oof Munnmbai has bbeeun eungulfedd
by a horrifying., unknownn disease.
First report came in
from 'CST Railway Station'
ln no time, a perilious
virus has taken over Mumbai.
On roads, offices and from
every where same reports are coming
Similar kind if reports
are started coming from..
..other parts of city as well.
As you can see...
fear and horror have
spread everywhere.
Every hospital is facing
a similar or worse situation.
Countless people are critical.
And, 117 people have lost their
lives to the rapidly spreading virus.
Someone call a crane
to move this truck.
Dad, get up!
Wake up, dad, please!
Krrish, please help.
My wife's in a bad condition.
Krrish... my dad...
Krrish, save my child
Krrish, my children...
Krrish, please save my wife...
Save my father.
Krrish, please help!
- Krrish, please help!
My fear has come true.
lt's the same virus that...
claimed thousands
of lives in Namibia.
Oh my God!
But there is an
antidote for this virus.
Contact Kaal
Pharmaceuticals immediately.
Kaal, after what
happened with Striker...
we should be wary of Krrish.
Our virus will test him too.
The lnddiah g.overnment has
wweakkeeneed due to this virus, hKaah.
They are contacting
our dealers repeatedly.
Kaal, the key component
of the antidote is ready.
We must start working on
the antidote as soon as possible.
How long will it take
for our scientists to make it?
10 days!
The cityy wwihl be dead in 10 days!
People are dying in front of me,
in my arms.
l can hear their screams...
and, l am helpless.
l am helpless, papa.
What is the point of me being Krrish?
There is a point.
There is.
lnspite of being around infected
people, you are not affected.
And neither is Priya,
as she is carrying your baby.
All my colleagues have
fallen prey to this virus.
All except me.
That means,
we are immune to this virus.
Perhaps, our blood
has something that is...
shiehding us, pprotecting us.
What are you doing?
lf l remain immune to this virus...
...even after it is
infused in my blood then...
my blood can be used to
make an antidote for this virus.
No, papa.
l won't let you do this.
Krishna, this is the only
way to find a cure for the virus.
Theh, ihjecct it in nnmy bblooodd.
No, that's too risky.
l could put you under risk...
but, not the people's hope.
Right now,
you are everyone's last hope, papa...
not me!
Test it on me.
But-
Please, papa.
Krishna.
Krishna!
l am okay.
This nnmeeahs, l cah makke
an antidote fronnm your bblooodd.
Now, we will be able to save people.
lt should take only a few hours...
But...
How can we provide the anitode
to so many in so little time?
How will we do that?
Kaal, there's a problem.
l don't know how...
but, the effect of our
virus is wearing off in Mumbai.
One of you has betrayed me.
You have cheated Kaal.
l warned you that the antidote should
not reach lndia until after 10 days.
How, then?
Who did it?
No one, Kaal.
We are still making our antidote!
Rumor has it, that a scientist from
a research institute in Mumbai...
has managed to create
the antidote to our virus.
What?
What nonsense?
How can a measly
scientist manage to...
find an antidote for Kaal's virus?
The antidoote cah
oohly bbe ppreepared froom...
my DNA...
my blood.
And how can anyone get it?
From where?
How?
How can my blood be coursing
through someone else's veins?
How?
Mumbai has once again proved...
to be unstoppable, unafraid, invincible
by vanquishing this virus.
l salute the courage of this city.
The spirit of its citizens...
and more importantly
the real hero of this victory.
A friend to the kids...
a hope for the grown-ups...
and, the support to the elders...
our very own, Krrish.
lf you are present here...
or wherever you are...
please know that words
aren't enough to thank you.
Yet, we have attempted in
our small way to felicitate you...
and, this shall be the
new identity of the city.
And, to present to you all,
this new identity...
l would like to call upon stage...
the man, without whom...
even Krrish's efforts
would have been futile...
Dr. Rohit Mehra.
Please come, sir.
Thahk you foor ahl your love.
Thahk you soo much.
But, l am sure if
you were in my place...
you would have done the same.
l was merely a medium.
Our effort has been successful...
...because of your
prayers and well wishes.
l would also like
to thank Krrish...
For making our nights safer and
gifting us a promise of a new day.
Sir, do you know Krrish?
l believe in Krrish.
l believe that...
we all have the essence
of Krrish in us.
Every person, who uses
their abilities to help others...
who extends a helping
hand selflessly...
who stands by those in need...
is, indeed Krrish.
We all have Krrish in us.
Even l am Krrish.
Krrish told me...
wwhen l saveed a pig.eon.
He also gave me this symbol.
Even l have one.
Me too.
l have one too!
''The nAlnnmightyy''
''Created man''
''Who has coome oh this eearth''
''To execute His plan''
''He is a friend's friend''
''A beust friendd''
''The evil ones fear his very name''
''The nAlnnmightyy''
''Created man''
''Till yeusterday he stoodd aloonnee''
''l have decided to walk on His path''
''Tog.ether weu nnmake this
wworhdd a beautiful place''
''We will brihg the dawh of hove''
''Tog.ether weu nnmake this
wworhdd a beautiful place''
''We will brihg the dawh of hove''
''He is a friend's friend''
''A beust friendd''
''The evil ones fear his very name''
''The nAlnnmightyy''
''Created man''
Looks like Krishna's here.
l'll check, papa.
What's the matter, Priya?
Who is it?
No one, papa.
Priya!
Priya.
What's her blood group?
O positive.
Any medical history, any allergies?
No.
But, Priya is pregnant.
Krishna, how is Priya?
l don't know anything yet, papa.
They have taken
her in for a check-up.
What's going on, papa?
Don't worry.
We'll soon find out.
Thahks to you oonee of the
attackers is in our ccustoddy.
l just hope... Mr. Mehra...
your wife is alright now.
But, l am sorry to say,
we couldn't save the baby.
Papa.
lt's going to be alright...
lt's going to be fine.
We don't need tears right now.
Because Priya needs you, Krishna.
You must make her smile again.
You must teach her
how to live again.
And, only you can do it.
Only you, Krishna.
Welcome, Mrs. Priya Mehra.
l hope you had a pleasant journey.
Who are you?
l know strange places
can be frightening.
You are in Kaal's world.
Here, l am trying to have
a conversation with you...
and you are trying
to run from me...
trying to attack me.
lt's not safe to be running
in your condition, for both of you.
So, please, sit down.
Sit!
Who is Krrish?
Who is he?
l... l don't know.
But you do know...
that the antidote for my virus...
was created by your father-in-law,
Rohit Mehra.
l'm sure you know how.
l don't know that.
But, l do know that...
only you have the answers
to all my questions.
Look, please...
my family...
my husband...
They must be searching for me...
And if they...
We search for things
that are missing.
But you are not missing, Priya.
You are here.
And there too!
Yes, two seats please.
Priya, all set!
First day, first show.
Shall we go?
Where are you lost?
l am right here.
ln front of you.
You are in front of me...
but not with me.
What?
lf you were really here...
you'd have sensed
that l have changed.
Yes, ma'am,
starting today, l'm all yours.
Just like your channel
entertains 24/7...
l am here at your service,
to entertain you.
48/14.
l have the list ready for each day.
From Sunday to Monday.
From shopping to cinema.
And, l won't ask for any leaves.
Nor any promotions.
l only want my salary.
Which would be...
A few thousand smiles.
A few million hugs.
A few billion kisses.
That's ahl l waht.
So, where do we start?
You've read my mind.
Where do we start?
We start by letting go of the past.
This is reeally strange.
His heart is beating
only once every two minutes.
This nnmeeahs, he is hibbernating.
ln this suspended state,
along with this heart rate...
he can stay alive
for as long as he wants.
But, human beings can't do that.
But some animals can.
They hibernate uhderground...
and resurface only when
the weather is favorable.
Perhaps,
he also has that very ability.
He is as much an animal,
as he is human.
l guess, he can be called a mutant.
Mutant?
Yes, Krishna.
Ancient mythology like Mahabharata
and Ramayana had such creatures.
Shurpnakha could
even change her form.
- Hello!
- Priya, are you okay?
- Yes, why?
- l will be late in coming home.
Because one of the attackers
is coming back to consciousness.
Once he is awake perhaps
he can help us and we can help him.
And, he can tell
us who it is that is...
trying to attempt such a dangerous
subversion of laws of nature.
Priya!
Priya, why did you come here?
l was getting scared.
No need to be afraid.
Krishna, l am afraid.
He will kill me.
He will kill us.
Do something, Krishna.
Get a sedative, immediately.
Papa, you have to kill him.
No, no, you have to kill him,
Krishna. lt'll be fine, Priya.
Priya. - Kill him!
Father.
That thing...
he tried to kill me.
You saw it, didn't you?
lf you weren't there to save me...
What did l ever do to them?
Who are these people?
What do they want from me... us?
Priya, l can imagine
you are disturbed.
But, please, calm down.
Perhaps we would
have got some answers...
if he had been alive for longer.
But, who are they?
And, why are they attacking us?
Attacking papa?
You think it could be because...
papa made an antidote
for the virus?
Yes, l think so too.
You are on the right track.
We can't be sure...
but, the attack seems to be linked
with the virus and the antidote.
lt seems very probable.
That means, they can come back.
They cah spreeadd the virus again.
We'd still be able to save people.
But, how?
They have burned the lab down.
Yes.
But we still have the antidote.
And if needed,
we can make more of it.
How?
How... papa?
Because, Priya, we have--
Papa, l think,
her questions won't stop until...
you make the antidote
in front of her eyes.
Because, she isn't Priya.
She is just a journalist right now.
Yes.
She is indeed interrogating
like a journalist.
Because she hasn't
been to work for so long...
the journalist in
her is trying to surface.
That's why, you shouldd
reusunnme workk fronnm tomorroww, Priya.
And right now,
you are going to bed.
- But, papa...
- Let's go.
Krishna, let papa tell us.
We should know this.
There's no teulling
wwhen wwe might heeud it.
Father.
Listen to me, Krishna.
lf we come to know how
papa makes the antidote...
we could help him.
This is very important.
Why don't you understand?
l love you.
Mr. Mehra,
here's your appointment letter.
You can join from tomorrow.
Thahk you, sir.
Ladiees andd g.eenthennman...
lt is now time to announce
the names of this week's...
...lucky draw winners,
at R City Mall.
Today's winner no.
3 who has won Rs. 50,000 is...
Mr. Sachin Gupta.
And our second place winner is Mr.
Pooja Mishra.
And today's jackpot winner, who
has won Rs. 100,000... - Thank you.
Mrs. Avi Shah.
Hey! That's me.
Help.
My baby!
My baby, my baby!
Thahk you.
My baby!
Thahk youl
This is from all of us.
What's this?
The symbbol of Korrish.
Anyone who steps up to help another
person, is rewarded with this.
Where can l meet Krrish?
l do not know that.
l just know that
he is always present...
...at the right place,
at the right time.
And, when he isn't...
kind people like you,
take his place.
But, what did l do?
You did.
You have done what
any kind person would do.
Your good human instincts
saved a child's life...
...and her mother's as well.
You don't understand, Krishna.
l love you.
''Oh heart''
''Tell meu''
''Where have you been hiding''
''Why, today, for the first time''
''Have l felt you beat inside''
''Oh heart''
''Tell meu''
''Where have you been hiding''
''Why, today, for the first time''
''Have l felt you beat inside''
''Yes''
''My heart''
''Has heard your''
''Heart's call''
''Oh heart''
''Tell meu''
''Where have you been hiding''
''Why, today, for the first time''
''Have l felt you beat inside''
''The worhd around
nnmee seeems to be a lie''
''On my dreams l now rely''
''Lost in your embrace''
''The world seems a better place''
''This love is''
''Like that gust of wind''
''Like that tidal wave''
''That sweeps away
everything in its path''
''l too have been swept away''
''And hae saidd''
''Everything l wanted to say''
''l too have been swept away''
''And hae saidd''
''Everything l wanted to say''
''My heart has heard
your heart's call''
''The sfky is within my reach''
''And Earth feels likkee paradise''
''Does this happen in love''
''To meu, noow eerythihg. feels hice''
''Oh heart''
''Tell meu''
''Where have you been hiding''
''Why, today, for the first time''
''Have l felt you beat inside''
''Yes''
''My heart''
''Has heard''
''Your heartt's call''
Who am l talking to?
Priya, or my Kaya?
l need some more time, Kaal.
l do not have time.
Bring me the information
by tomorrow or...
Kaal will obtain
it by his own means.
Doctor, are all
the parameters normal?
Parameters are normal.
The foetus is heualthy
and ih the right position.
Theh what is it still
doing in it's mother's wombb?
Get it out.
Right away.
But why, Kaal?
l want to try injecting my DNA
in its DNA at this foetal stage...
and see what generates.
Because, we have not yet conducted any
experiments with human foetuses.
That's right, Kaal.
But, it's too early.
Pulling the foetus
out right now is dangerous.
lt will die.
Until the foetus
is three months old...
we cannot take it out.
Nor, can we conduct
any experiments.
ln fact,
we cannot even do a DNA test.
How much longer?
At least a week, Kaal.
Only another seven days.
And your nine month long
ordeal will come to an end.
And perhaps get answers
to all my questions.
Krishna, where are you?
Some startling facts
have been revealed, Krishna.
At first, we discovered that...
the DNA of the antidote supplied
by Kaal Pharmaceuticals...
is a match to the DNA
of the mutant in our custody.
Even more alarming
truth is the fact that...
the DNA of the antidote
created by us...
is also more or less the same.
l did several tests to confirm.
Every single time,
l got the same result.
But, how is that possible?
Because we made
that antidote from...
- l guess Priya has woken up.
- Yes.
- About the antidote...
- How is she?
She is fine.
- The antidote... - Listen...
l am leaving for
Singapore tomorrow.
Take care of yourself and Priya.
You are going to Singapore?
Why?
Because...
Singapore, Dr.
Arya, and his cruel intentions...
are all an important
part of my past.
And, the facts that have surfaced
have raised many questions.
Perhaps, l can only find
the answers by revisiting my past.
- There you are.
- What happened?
Are you alright?
Yes, why?
l don't know.
l felt like you were calling
out to me from a distance.
l am right here with you.
Why would l call out to you?
True.
Papa had asked for some coffee.
He is still working.
But, it's quite late.
Let me go check on him.
No.
He said he is working
on some important research.
We shouldn't disturb
him until morning.
Come with me.
Come on.
Okay, let's go.
What's the matter?
No.
Now, l cannot break
Krishna's trust.
And...
what about Kaal's trust?
l will ask him to wait until
Rohit Mehra returns from Singapore.
Hello.
l have found all the answers
l was looking for, Krishna.
Coming to Singapore
was a good move.
Singapore?
You're in Singapore?
When did you leave?
Why didn't you tell me?
Of course, l did.
l told you last night...
when you came down to the lab.
Last night?
When?
And l was going to
share some more details...
but, Priya woke up.
Remember?
There you are.
What happened?
You're here with me.
But not really here.
Shurpnakha could
even change her form.
lf we find out how papa
made the antidote for the virus.
Krishna, you have to kill him.
She is indeed interrogating
like a journalist.
Krishna...
Who are you?
Priya.
l am Priya Mehra.
You are not Priya.
Yes, l am.
l am Priya... Krishna!
You aren't Priya.
lf you were...
you would know the truth
about Krishna and Krrish.
Tell me who you are!
Where's my Priya?
Your Priya?
Yes.
Krishna?
Yes, Krishna.
Your tears might influence Krishna.
But, they won't fool Krrish.
Where's my Priya?
She is in a safe place.
Priya and...
your child, too.
Believe me,
l am telling the truth...
to both Krishna and Krrish.
Where is she?
Welcome to the world of Kaal, Dr.
Rohit Mehra.
And, l am sorry...
l had to bring you
here without your consent.
You went to Singapore
looking for some answers.
Tell me, what did you find?
That man should
never try to be God.
Many years ago, Dr. Arya
had held me captive in Singapore.
And during that period...
he conducted a strange
experiment on me.
Dr. Mathur...
if this experiment is successful...
l will have created
a new Rohit Mehra.
From his own blood, his own DNA.
With all of Rohit's mental
and physical powers...
but, controlled entirely by me.
Dr. Arya did manage to
create a child using my DNA.
But the child turned
out to be handicapped.
Dr. Arya, instructed Dr.
Mathur to dispose of the baby.
But Dr. Mathur couldn't do so.
He left the baby
in an orphanage instead.
- And... - And then...
A rich man adopted
the handicapped child.
And raised him as his own.
That means, the one l
always regarded as my father...
was not really my father.
Because, that handicapped
child is none other than me.
And you... you are my father.
l like it.
Everything's going
to be alright now.
l found you and with you...
l found the answers
to all my questions.
Now l'll find a cure
for my condition as well.
l just need a little help from you.
What help?
l need your bone marrow.
Bone marrow?
You can have it.
l will help you.
You will have to put
an end to what you are doing.
You must destroy this
little universe you've created.
Dad...
can l call you dad?
Of course l can...
you are my dad indeed.
Dad...
no terms and conditions.
Doing that will cause you...
a lot of grief.
Because then...
l will be forced to take the DNA...
from the bone marrow
of the baby that...
Priya is carrying.
Your grandchild.
My grandchild?
But l thought...
- even before she could give--
- No...
the baby is alive.
Because, Priya is in my custody.
Do you want to see her?
But...
Priya is... there...
That is hot Priya.
She is one of my mutants.
Masquerading as Priya.
The real Priya is
here and she's safe.
Her baby is healthy.
And so is baby's bone marrow.
You may feel that we
are all alone right now.
And hence,
you may torture us all you want.
But, you don't know the
power of a father's tears.
That is why you
cahnoot seee him connming.
He is our strength.
And he is the end of you.
My real son...
Krrish!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Krishna...
Kaal is not in this facility.
Come in, dad.
Look, l have found my feet.
- Whereas you...
- How do you feel, Kaal?
l was talking to my dad.
This is just the beg.inhing.
A lot of blood is yet to be shed.
- Yes, Kaal?
- Kaya, thank you so much.
Because of you,
Rohit Mehra is with me.
Come back here,
from wherever you are.
Come to the facility
where l created you.
Aren't you glad to
be back in your world?
Kaya?
Kaal?!
Kaya, now you shall bear
witness to Kaal's powers.
l'm going to destroy humanity...
and create a race
of powerful creatures.
This world belongs to me now.
lt could have been ours...
but, you chose a different path.
By betraying me.
l knew you would bring Krrish here.
And that is exactly
what l wanted you to do.
Krrish!
You are going to need your tears.
Save them...
for your father.
Sorry, for our father.
Yes, we are brothers.
Two sons of the same father.
The only difference is that...
you are the child
born out of love...
and, l am the child born out of Dr.
Arya's insanity.
Ask him, if you don't believe me.
Papa?
l have only taken his bone marrow.
lf he survives...
the world will end, Krishna.
Dad, you are asking one
son to kill your other son?
l like it.
l will gladly fulfil your wish.
Krrish, my victory
will be marked by death.
Your and your child's death.
No member of your
family will survive.
Krishna!
Krishna.
Look dad,
l made your wish come true.
Now, l do not even
need to kill you.
Because the death
of your real son...
will finish you too, Rohit Mehra.
Krishna...
Krishna, get up.
Krishna!
Who are you?
Hey, did you get that?
The one that you
all pin your hopes on.
That you depehd oh.
Kaal has destroyed him.
l have killed Krrish!
What?!
Oh my God!
Yes, l have made Krrish a martyr.
Now, it's Priya Mehra's turn.
So bring her to me.
The longer she takes to reach me...
the more l will torture you all.
A filter with a brain.
Please God.
Krishna, never think you are alone.
Because no one ever really dies.
The souh... the ehergy...
it only gets transferred
from one body to another.
Old lives end but
return as new lives.
Look, Krishna...
l am coming back
to life within you.
Our powers are uniting.
We'll always be together.
l'll stay alive in you.
And in your memories.
And you will forever
be in my blessings.
What are you doing, Vicky?
Vicky, where are you going?
Vicky!
Emotional fools.
All you silly and helpless
people are like insects to me.
An inferior race.
One that l can crush anytime.
How will you save her?
We'll give our lives for her.
No!
We'll take his life.
l like it.
You have quite an attitude
for someone so small.
So what if l am small?
One's courage should be undettered.
Krrish said so.
Krrish...is no more!
This is the era of Kaal!
Krrish is the courage within us.
And cannot be killed by any Kaal.
Krrish will remain alive
until the last one of us is alive.
What's the matter, Kaal?
Scared?
Krishna!
Such a wonderful family reunion.
Who do l kill first?
Father?
Or son?
Look at yourself.
You are just an
ordinary human being.
An ordinary son.
A weak father.
Being human is not a weakness...
it is my strength.
Because l have the
blessing of every father...
and the love of every child.
Krishna...
Surprise!
Krishna, get up.
Krishna.
Only those who are born can die.
l was never born.
So, l can never die.
No matter how powerful evil is...
good will always triumph over it.
Krishna, never think you are alone.
Because no one ever really dies.
We'll always be together.
l'll stay alive in you.
And in your memories.
And you will forever
be in my blessings.
Mr. Krishna...
Mr. Krishna.
Congratulations.
lt's a boy.
You can go in now.
l wish papa were here.
He is right here.
l have named our son, Rohit.
Where did he...
He was right here...
''Whenever there
will be dense smoke.''
''Krrish will come
like a torch everytime.''
''Krrish Krrish''
''Whenever there
will be dense smoke.''
''Krrish will come
like a torch everytime.''
''Krrish Krrish''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He
has come with the wind''
is a shadow of you and me''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He
has brought love for you''
''He is Krrish''- ''He
has come with the wind''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He
is a shadow of you and me''
has brought love for you''
''Wheneveer theere
wwihh bbe a densee mist''
''Krrish will come
like a torch everytime''
''Krrish Krrish''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He
wakes up hopes in the heart''
increases the courage''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He solves the
problems He makes the fear go away''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He
wakes up hopes in the heart''
increases the courage''
''He is Krrish'' - ''He solves the
problems He makes the fear go away''
''Whenever there
will be dense smoke''
''Krrish will come
like a torch everytime''
''Krrish Krrish''
www.baiscopelk.com