What a mess!
Krishna...Krishna...Krishna...
What am l going to do with this boy...?
Krishna...
Yes, grandma?
Whose sketch book is this?
Mine, grandma.
And who made these sketches?
Grandma, why do grown ups sometimes
ask childish questions...?
lf it's my sketch book, obviously,
l've made the sketches.
Grown ups talk like children when
children act like grown ups.
Tell me something, how did you make
such beautiful sketches?
With this.
Like l've made your
sketch right now. See?
Wow!
Let me see!
Rohit loved drawing too.
Papa made sketches too?
Yes.
When Rohit was your age and
he used to get tired studying
he used to sketch.
l want to be like my Papa too.
You are like your Papa!
Mrs Mehra, l've called you here
to tell you that...
we want to take Krishna's l.Q. test.
l.Q. test...?
But why, Father?
Krishna's absolutely normal.
No, Mrs Mehra.
He's not normal.
What are you saying, Father?
Are you telling me...
that Krishna is the same as
Rohit was in his childhood?
No, Father.
Krishna's a very bright child.
He scores very good marks, he
always gets A-plus grades.
He even does his homework
without any help.
And that of other children too.
What?
This is the notebook of
a Class 3 student.
This is...
...Krishna's handwriting.
Yes, Krishna has done this
child's math homework.
But how's that possible, Father?
Krishna's still in Class 1.
That's exactly why we wish to
take Krishna's l.Q. test...
so that we can ascertain just how bright,
sharp and ahead he is...
of other children his age
Krishna, how do you define amount?
Principle plus interest is equal to amount, sir
After what age does the brain
of a person stop growing?
Afterthe age of 15, Father.
What happened, Mrs Mehra?
The l.Q. test was going so well, Krishna
was answering all questions right...
That's exactly why l brought him away.
But why?
You ought to be proud that
your grandson is so brilliant.
He's a genius, a miracle child.
Earlier it was a hunch
but now l'm sure.
The powers that Jadoo
had bestowed on Rohit...
...have been inherited by Krishna.
You will see, Mrs Mehra.
Like his father...
...Krishna will also achieve
great success.
His name will appear in
the Guinness Book ...
...and the whole world will
speak highly of him.
That's exactly what l don't want, Father.
What did Rohit gain, after all?
They gave him medals, applauded him...
but everybody only used him..
...took advantage of him, Father.
And then...
...l lost my son and my daughter-in-law.
l don't want to lose Krishna now.
l don't want to lose him.
l can understand your concern and fears.
But destiny cannot be changed.
And talent is a gift which cannot be hidden.
l will hide it.
l'll take Krishna far away...
... very far.
Krishna... Krishna...
Coming, Grandma!
Toofan, let's see who gets home first.
Hey... what did you see?
As usual, l've seen nothing and
l won't say a word to anyone.
But as usual, l'll take
something from you.
Take this!
l hide all your secrets and you
always give me jaggery?
lt won't work today.
Ok, ok, come home...
l'll give you Bournvita.
Bournvita?
Yes. Don't you want to be like me?
Yes!
So go, wear something below and come.
Krishna...
You've come?
Grandma, how do you know l've come?
l make no sound at all!
l can hearyour heartbeats.
But how, Grandma?
Your eyes say that you've been
upto mischief again.
Mischief? Not at all, Grandma!
No mischief? Then why're you hiding
yourface like a thief?
Not hiding, just washing my face, Grandma
Ok ok.. lay the breakfast.
l've come!
What happened?
Chintu dropped a glass, Grandma...
Me?
Chintu! Upto mischief again?
Tell herthe truth, Krishna, else l shall.
Sure, go ahead
l'll tell her since you've asked me to
Grandma, Krishna was running faster
than Toofan today
What? Fasterthan Toofan?
So? What's the big deal?
And how about that?
What?
You climbed the mountain faster
than the monkeys...
Grandma, you know that tall
mountain by the temple?
Krishna jumped from it
into the river.
l thought it was all over.
But he came back!
Krishna, why do you do such things?
l've forbidden you time and again!
Why do you still do such things?
What do l do Grandma?
You tell me!
How do l rid myself of loneliness?
Who do l make friends with?
Boys my age have gone away to the city,
to either study or earn a living
And those that are here don't
want be friends with me
They say... l'm not like them
So l've made friends with
animals and birds
Keep myself busy with nature.
But even out here in the open,
l sometimes feel stifled
l feel like running far away
from here.
Will you leave me and go away?
lt's because of you that l don't go!
Else, l'd have left long ago
Krishna has grown up, Rohit
l'm not sure how long l will be
able to hide him
Where is Sonia Mehra and her
grandson Krishna, Father?
lt's the third time in so many years
that l've come to ask you
And my answer is still the same.
l have no idea where Mrs Mehra is.
l really don't know!
Why do you keep coming to me again
and again and waste my time?
Because you are the last link to
Rohit Mehra's family...
and you're the last person Sonia Mehra
met before she went missing
You know where they are,
but you're lying.
What?
You are lying, Father.
When l asked you whether Krishna possessed
the powers Rohit had...
you said he didn't.
But l was told...that the son was
betterthan his father
That he possesses all of Rohit's powers.
So tell me, Father...
l'll pay any price you ask
How dare you! Mr Sinha,
this is a school!
We don't indulge
in business here!
Please leave now!
You're making a mistake, Father.
A big mistake.
Krishna! Look!
What a huge kite!
But where's the string?
Must've snapped. Let's get it!
Don't scream! You needn't be afraid
Close your eyes and hold on to me tightly
Stop screaming!
Else, l'll drop you.
Close your eyes
Close your eyes, not widen them.
Close them!
Close!
The glider came this way!
There it is!
Where...?
Up there!
Oh my God! Where's Priya?
There!
She's breathing. She must've passed out
Let's take her back to the camp
The glider was at such a height,
Priya Ma'am was down here...
...and she's still breathing?
Just imagine!
Just imagine.
lmagine!
Where am l...?
You're alive and you're with us
Thank God you're alive.
Not God, it's that boy
we ought to thank
That boy...? Which boy?
The one who saved my life
A boy saved you?
But there was no one there
No sir! He must've been there!
We fell from the tree together.
Together...? But you went
in the glider alone.
How did he come on
the tree to rescue you...?
Did he fall from the skies?
Yes sir. That's where he came from!
Priya, trust me, you were all alone. Right?
Ghost!
What happened?
G-H-O-S-T !
Komal sir, ghost!
Ghost?
What are you blabbering, Bahadur?
No blabber, sir. lt's a chant.
To drive the ghost away.
What rubbish, Bahadur?
Ghost in broad daylight?
This is a jungle, sir! Night
and day are all the same here
Priya Ma'am, was he tall?
Yes
Well built?
Yes!
Fair-skinned?
Kalicharan!
Kalicharan...?
Yes, sir! Kalicharan's ghost!
Been wandering in the mountains
for ages... upside down on trees
Just imagine!
What nonsense!
A ghost in ourtimes...?
l don't believe all this.
l also don't believe all this!
What happened?
Relax...
Sir, it's either a sprain or a fracture
Oh no!
We're here on a 10-day
adventure camp...
...and you've already broken yourfoot!
Honey, take her into the tent
and give herfirst-aid
Careful...
Bahadur, go to your phone booth
and call for a car
We need to send Priya to
the city fortreatment
l'll go at night, sir.
l feel scared by day.
What?
Yes! Kalicharan's ghost.
Scares people by day
and sleeps at night.
Just imagine!
Easy, easy
Just relax. l'll organise a painkiller
C'mon guys. Let's go
You're always screaming!
Doesn't yourthroat hurt?
Your eyes are widening again!
You must never get scared...
What happened, Priya?
Why were you screaming?
Honey, he was here! ln this room!
He was here, Honey!
Who...? Who was here?
The boy who saved me
on the tree...
the one l told you about, sir...
God! What's happened to this girl?
Priya, it's just 2 seconds since l left...
Are you saying that someone came
and even went away in the meantime...?
You must've dozed off and
probably had a dream.
l didn't dream! Why doesn't
someone believe me?
The moment l closed my eyes,
he entered the tent...
he twisted my ankle and the pain...
Hey! The pain in my ankle is gone! See!
The pain has disappeared!
Oh my God sir! My foot is all right!
Look at this... l can jump!
My foot has become all right
Eitherthis girl has really gone mad,
or she's conning us!
No, sir! l'm not conning you! See...
l can jump! Believe me!
l believe you! Kalicharan has
cured yourfoot
Just imagine!
Kalicharan...? So this ghost
is also a doctor?
Not is, was!
Kalicharan's father, Lalcharan.
Doctor Lalcharan.
There's no Kalicharan, there's
no Lalcharan... it's a pack of lies!
lt's some stupid local boy
playing a prank on me
l'm going to find him today,
bring him before everybody...
and prove to them that he's
just another boy!
Are you looking for someone?
What...?
You! l'm looking foryou!
Where do you keep disappearing?
Why don't you appear before others
as you appear before me?
And that stupid Bahadur keeps telling
them that you're a ghost!
You... you're not Kalicharan, are you?
You're human, aren't you?
Why are you kids giggling ?
Who are you talking to, aunty?
Aunty...? Firstly you call me aunty and
then you ask who l am speaking to?
l'm talking to this boy!
Which Boy?
Can't you see this boy here...?
That's a lamppost there, not a Boy,
That's a boy
Lamppost
Boy!
Lamppost!
Shut up!
One moment. Please Listen...
What do you see there?
A boy? Or a lamppost?
Well... there's neither a boy
there nor a lamppost.
Look carefully...
What happened...?
l'm feeling giddy.
You seem unwell
My house is nearby...
come rest there for a while
l'll get you a glass of water
Okay!
Why's his picture garlanded?
My son. He died 20 years ago
But how's that possible...?
Moments ago, l...
lt's a tragic tale that took place
20 years ago
Champa and Kalicharan
Kalicharan and Champa.
Madly in love with each other
They were like one soul two bodies.
And then one day...
What happened?
Kalicharan was putting some flowers
in Champa's hair...
Lalcharan happened to see them.
He went red with rage!
And one day, he deceived Champa into
drinking poison, in the name of medicine
And poor Champa! She screamed,
''Kali, Kali...''
... and died. Just imagine!
Kalicharan just could not bear
the pain of Champa's death
Overthere! Look at that peak!
From that very peak, Kalicharan
screamed, ''Champa, Champa...''
... and jumped to his death!
Ever since, Kalicharan's spirit has
been looking for his Champa!
Why're you pointing towards me?
Because you are his Champa
Me...? Champa!
l mean, you look like Champa
l'm feeling terribly scared. We can't
stay here anymore, please
Nobody goes anywhere!
This silly Bahadurtalks a lot of nonsense...
...and you start imagining?
Bahadur, you're not telling these kids
anymore stories. Understand?
And now get ready. We're going
mountain-climbing
You will use ascenders to climb...
...descenders to come down.
And you will come rappelling, down.
'right sir.ok sir'
Ghost!
Priya!
What... what on earth is that?
Kalicharan!
Just imagine
Can't imagine
Temperature. 104 degrees
We had told you sir.
But you didn't listen.
Sorry, sorry
We're not staying here any more
Bahadur, leave immediately.
And arrange for
ourtransportation. Go!
You've snatched my bread and butter.
l'm broke even before l could
make some money.
Just imagine!
Why did you climb the mountain
like that, in front of them?
What could l do? She screamed
so loudly...
..that l got scared
And now they are so scared,
that they're all going back.
Now keep searching foryour
Champa all your life!
What do we do, Bahadur?
How do l know? l did as you said
You think of a way now
ldea!
What?
Champa-ji...
My name is Priya.
ln this lifetime
ln your earlier six births you were
Kalicharan's Champa
This is your 7th birth.
lf you leave without meeting him,
he'll be very angry...
And he'll follow you
whereveryou go
Just imagine!
How will he follow her?
We're going back to Singapore
He can reach Singapore too!
He doesn't need airtickets
Bahadur, she's not meeting any ghost!
What if something happens to her?
This ghost is a gentleman, ma'am.
He hasn't harmed a soul
Am l right?
Yes
l leave the rest to you
Wait Bahadur!
Honey...
Yes?
l think he's right
You're going to meet him?
Yes. Only then will he find peace
And you better not stop her
if Kalicharan gets to know...
just imagine!
No! l wasn't stopping her!
l was only advising you, right...?
Listen, you must meet the ghost.
He's such a gentleman!
l'm off to sleep.
Bye, good night!
Champa... Champa...
Hello! Kalicharan ji...
Here l am...
... to help you get peace
Please... could you appear
before me?
''l feel scared''
Do ghosts also feel
scared nowadays?
''l'm not a ghost''
You aren't a ghost?
Oh yes, l get it...
it offends you when someone calls
you a ghost, isn't it?
And you're right! You've ended
your life for love
And those who end their lives
for love aren't ghosts...
They are... they are...
They're lovers! You're
a lover, aren't you?
l'm Krishna
Look... stay right there!
Don't come closer, okay?
You sent for me
and here l am.
You'll get peace now
May l go now?
All l want is friendship
Friendship...?
Hey... don't be afraid.
l'm as human as you are
Touch me if you can't
believe that.
Touch you?
l'm sorry
See? The colour of my blood
is red, too.
Are you convinced now
that l'm not a ghost?
lf you're not a ghost then
that picture?
That's my father's photograph.
He's no more
l look exactly like him.
l see
But the other day, how did you suddenly
get on that tree to save my life?
And yesterday! How did you climb
that mountain so fast?
Maybe because l've got used to it
Right from my childhood, l've grown up
playing among the trees and mountains...
...with the birds and the animals.
l spend most of my time here
l guess that's why they're my friends
Would you like to
meet my friends?
Wow! l still can't believe it!
l won't let you poke that pin again!
lt hurts because l'm not Kalicharan.
See? He's not Kalicharan!
l've always been saying that!
That's what you're still saying.
l'm Right!
Kalicharan! You're so cute!
Krishna, you really got us scared.
But that was a nice prank.
Boys and girls,
camping continues!
Krishna, you also join the group!
Just imagine!
C'mon! C'mon!
Come
From where are you getting a flower of
a new colour every time, Krishna?
From the rainbow.
The rainbow?
Yes
Look
Wow Krishna! lt's such
a beautiful sight
Had l not come here, l'd really
have regretted it
So would l
l've never seen such a lovely place.
lt's so beautiful. So pure,
so serene, so quiet
You should see this place in autumn.
lt's a riot of colours
When the sunrays touch the
fallen leaves, everything turns to gold
lt's so beautiful
Makes you realise what
a great artist God really is
Krishna, you speak English?
And with such fluency?
Grandma taught me. She's my
school, my college and my university
But you need talent to
learn anything, Krishna
And you possess amazing talent.
You're amazing!
You shouldn't be wasting your
talent in this remote village
You ought to get out of here.
People in the world out there...
...not just need talented people
like you, they appreciate them too
But my grandma is my world
l will never leave her.
You love your grandma
very much?
More than very much
Krishna, l want to meet
your grandma
ADLABS
''Look, even the breeze...''
''even the breeze now rises
in a wave...''
''having touched you...''
''secretly, quietly''
''There's a joy...''
''there's a joy that
now sings...''
''having met you...''
''secretly, quietly''
''lt just doesn't seem as if you have
come from somewhere far''
''Foryours has been the face
l have dreamt of''
''Your path is the one
l'd like to follow.''
''lt's the first ever journey
thats been so enjoyable''
''Changing colours and smiling...''
''are the desires of my heart...''
''secretly, quietly''
ADLABS
''There are moments in life that get
etched in memory''
''And there are those wonderful people
who never leave your heart''
''Everybody understands the
language of the heart''
''it connects even with strangers,''
''Dusk seems to be saying
something to you and me...''
''secretly, quietly''
ADLABS
Grandma... this is Priya.
Hello, Grandma
We've met before.
l remember. Tell me something...
Why did you go away, the other day?
l fled, grandma! Out of fright
Krishna was playing a ghost
to scare us
Ghost...?
And that well-built Komal Sir
was trembling in his boots!
He was down with 104 degrees fever!
What? 104 degrees?
ls that true, Krishna?
You shouldn't play such pranks
on anyone, my son
Why scare someone so much?
Did you apologise?
Yes, Grandma. To everybody
Priya ... tell me something about yourself
l live in Singapore with my Mother.
My father is no more
l'm here in lndia on a vacation
with my friend...
Herfamily lives in Chandigarh
l see
l'll go and wash my hands
Priya, for how many more days
are you here?
Days...? we're leaving today.
ln fact, right now
Oh my God! l must leave now.
Everyone must be waiting for me.
Here's my phone number.
Wheneveryou come here again...
...please give me the opportunity
to serve you again
Where's Priya?
There she is!
Hurry, we've got to leave.
C'mon, everybody! Get in!
Nice meeting you.
we really enjoyed your
company, Krishna.
We'd love to come back.
lt was great fun, Krishna.
Thanks, Krishna!
l had a wonderful time with you.
l didn't even realize how ten days
have passed by
Really!
l'm going to miss this place...
And you, too.
Look afteryourself, Kalicharan.
l have to go now.
May l?
May l go?
Krishna, how will she go,
if you don't leave her hand?
Bye, Krishna
Bye
Priya... See!
Looks like you're no longer Priya.
You've become Radha.
Krishna's Radha.
What?
l seriously think Krishna has
fallen in love with you.
l hope not...
Honey, pray that the boss' mood is ok,
we're five days late.
Hi! Honey. Hi! Priya
We are saying hi to them,
Why're they waving five fingers at us?
Stupid! The five fingers
stand forfive days.
Oh my God! You mean boss too...
You took a leave of 15 days...
...and have come after 20!
So you girls are now fired!
Why just lndia?
Go on a world tour! Go!
Stop, Priya.
Sorry boss, but you can't insult us.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Boss, you can't question
our integrity.
Agreed we were on a leave
of 15 days
But on the 16th day we got to work
What amazing work have you done?
We have found an lndian superboy.
Honey! What are you saying?
Let me speak, please.
Boss, this boy scales high mountains
as if they were mere steps for him!
He runs fasterthan a horse!
And guess what?
He puts his hand in the river
and pulls out fish!
Just think of it, if a boy as talented
as him were to come here...
...your rating's are going to soar!
Just imagine!
l hope you're not trying to make
a fool out of me?
No way, boss!
You will believe it too...
...when you see him doing all those
incredible things here!
See him here! How? How's he going
to come here?
l tried to stop you, but you just
wouldn't listen!
Please, Priya! There was no other way
of saving our job.
Besides, what's wrong if Krishna
comes here?
There you go again!
Relax! Sit down
lf Krishna's talents are
showcased on our channel...
...he'd be the one who'd gain.
Name, fame, money...
He'll have everything!
He'll be a big man!
Just think!
l know you're right, Honey...
...but Krishna will never leave
his grandma and come.
She is his world.
But now you are a part
of his world too.
l know. Now do as l say.
Call for Krishna!
Phone...
Krishna, phone
He's coming!
Who's coming?
A boy? ls he an lndian?
Does he live here in Singapore?
Have you finally chosen
someone, Priya?
There you go again, Mom!
l haven't chosen anyone
So choose one!
l will...
...please leave now,
we got to save our jobs.
And when will you settle down?
Tomorrow
Call from Priya!
Priya?
Hello, Krishna...
Priya...
How are you?
l'm fine, but l don't like anything
Me too
l can't sleep
l want to meet you
Me too
He's not saying anything more than
'' Me too '', so what do l do?
You continue reading,
read from here!
Priya, why are you quiet?
Krishna, can't you come here
and meet my mother?
Your mother?
Yes, if you don't meet my mother...
...she'll get me married to
someone else.
Someone else?
No, l won't let that happen!
l'm coming there, Priya!
But...how will l get there?
Yes... how will you get here?
Hello, Krishna! Don't worry.
Just give the phone to Bahadur?
Krishna! Aircraft! Singapore!
Priya Ma'am!
How? When?
Just imagine!
ADLABS
''Come, let me tell you
a love story''
''There was a boy and
there was a girl...''
''She smiled''
''He smiled''
''Little did they know what
was happening''
ADLABS
''What they couldn't say till then,
they started saying...''
''what they couldn't heartill then
they started hearing''
ADLABS
''lt brings a smile to my face to
see us falling in love...''
''We're lost in love''
''The world didn't matterto them
anymore''
''There was a boy
and there was a girl...''
''she smiled, he smiled...''
''little did they know what
was happening''
''Come, let me tell you a love story''
''There was a boy and there was a girl...''
''There was no yearning,
there was no aching...''
''they came together...
their hearts skipped a beat''
''There was no yearning,
there was no aching...''
''they came together... their hearts
skipped a beat''
''What was destined happened...''
''They got lost in love''
''Oh, how one heart ruled the other!''
''There was a boy and there was a girl...''
Grandma!
l am here
Put me down
What's the matter, Krishna?
You look very happy today.
Grandma, l got a call from Priya!
You told me that she'd forget me?
But it's not true, Grandma!
She misses me every moment.
She's always thinking of me!
And she keeps seeing me everywhere!
And l nevertold you...
...l've been in a similar state.
Ever since Priya has left,
l never liked anything.
But today with her call,
l feel better.
Grandma, Priya has called me
to Singapore
She wants me to meet her mother.
Her mother?
Yes
lf l don't go and ask for her hand...
...her mother's going to get her
married to someone else
l said l wouldn't let that happen,
l'm coming.
l did the right thing, didn't l Grandma?
May l go, Grandma?
lt's only a matter of a few days, grandma
l'll ask for Priya's hand in marriage
and bring her back with me
May l go, Grandma?
You're not answering, Grandma
When you've already decided to go...
...why ask me?
Go on. Go.
You aren't happy, Grandma?
Don't you like Priya?
l like Priya...
...but l don't like the idea
of you going so far.
lf Priya really loves you...
...she can also come here
with her mother
But you're not going there!
Why not?
l said you're not going,
it means you're not going
That's it!
But why can't l go?
What's going to happen?
l've been hearing this since l was a child!
Don't go here, don't go there,
don't do this, don't do that...
...don't go to the city with yourfriends!
Forget the city, you don't even
allow me to go beyond the river...
Why?
Now you've become so big that
l have to give explanations to you?
You'll have to tell today, Grandma!
Why do you keep stopping me?
Why can't l go anywhere?
Because l don't want to lose you
So what do you want then?
Cut me off from the world and
keep looking at yourface forever?
Bang my head on trees
and mountains all my life...?
You want me to be alone all my life?
ls that what you want?
But l can't do l that, Grandma!
l have my own life too...
...my own dreams. l too want to
achieve something!
l want an identity for myself!
You don't want to lose me,
even if l have to lose Priya
You can't see me happy
l have always obeyed you.
And you can't agree to my one request?
Today l realize, how selfish you are!
You only think of yourself!
Only yourself!
You don't care for me!
Had my parents been alive,
they'd have understood my feelings!
They'd have let me go,
they wouldn't have stopped me!
l wish your parents were alive.
l wish!
l'm sorry, Grandma.
See these stars, Krishna...
...with these infinite
twinkling stars in the sky...
...you, yourfather, your grandfather...
...and l share a very deep relationship.
Your grandfather was a space scientist
One night, he started receiving a reply
to a signal he had sent to outer space
Suddenly, we saw a flying saucer in the sky...
...the car swerved out of control
l survived the accident...
...but your grandfather.
l was pregnant with Rohit at that time...
...he had sustained a head injury
in the accident...
...because of which he was born abnormal.
...even when he grew up,
he had the l.Q. of a child.
One night, in our small town,
a huge spaceship descended.
Some Aliens emerged from it...
...but one could not go back.
And that is how Rohit met Jadoo.
Jadoo had supernatural powers...
...which he passed on to Rohit.
Rohit changed completely.
Jadoo eventually went away...
...but he did not take back the powers
he had given to Rohit.
And thereafter, everything changed forever.
My son could do things that were impossible
for an ordinary human being.
lt was around then that Rohit
married your mother.
And very soon, his fame spread
across the world.
The chairman of the world's largest
lnformation Technology Company...
...invited Rohit abroad.
Thank You.
Welcome to Technotronics.
Come with me, Sir
Dr Arya shall be here shortly
Mr. Rohit Mehra?
l'm sorry to keep you waiting
lt's all right, Sir.
l was, this book...
Oh yes, that's the first copy of
my latest book.
Please read it and give your opinion.
lt's a wonderful book, Sir.
You've done a lot of research.
How can you say that without reading it?
l've already read it, Sir.
Read it?
There are printing errors on
page 126, 244 and 354
l've marked them.
You've read this 400 page book
in just 10 minutes?
l forgot who l was talking to.
Asking you such questions is
an insult to yourtalent.
lt's an honourto meet you.
The honour is mine, Sir.
l still can't believe...
...that l'm standing face to face with a
great scientist and innovator like you.
Your achievements in the field of
wireless communication...
...is no less than a revolution, Sir.
You've invented the palmtop.
People can watch cricket matches
on their phones, thanks to you.
l have a new dream, Rohit. A new vision...
...lf this dream comes true, it could change
the destiny of the world.
And l need your help to realise this dream.
l want to build a computer
that can see the future.
That can see the future.
Future?
What would you like, tea or coffee?
l understand your dream, your vision, Sir.
You want to combine astrology,
astronomy and technology...
...to build a computerthat can see the future.
Exactly! That's precisely
why l've called you here.
Because the people l have here are trained...
...not gifted like you.
What are you thinking, Rohit?
Sir, if we can really build a computer
that can see the future then...
Then, think of the good we can do
forthis planet and mankind!
Wars can be prevented
Earthquakes, famines, floods,
can be prevented.
Even if we can't prevent them,
we can at least be prepared forthem.
You've already started
seeing the future, Rohit.
Welcome!
ln the hope that this union of brilliance
and vision will become history.
Create history!
lt took him two whole years...
...but Rohit achieved the impossible...
...he built a computer
that could see the future...
...lt was around the time
when you were going to be born.
Hello?- Mom?
Rohit, l've brought Nisha to the hospital.
That's where l'm calling from.
Congratulations! You're going to
become a father anytime.
Come back soon.
l'm coming, Mom...l'm coming!
Rohit? What's the matter?
You sound tense.
l've been exploited. The world is very selfish
But don't worry! l'll be back soon!
But my son did not come back.
Moments afteryou were born,
we received word
...that a fire broke out in the lab...
...and they couldn't save Rohit.
Your mother couldn't bearthe shock...
...and passed away in a few days.
When you were five years old...
...l got to know that you too were
born with extraordinary powers...
...that Rohit had. l got scared.
l didn't want the world to know about you.
And that's why l brought you here...
...a place where nobody knew us.
l didn't want to lose you at any cost, Krishna.
You no longer want to see my face...
...but l'm living only foryou, Krishna
Yes, l'm selfish, very selfish.
Grandma? What are you doing?
l've taken out some of
yourfather's clothes.
You can't go to Singapore like this!
But Grandma?
l could shield you from the world...
...but not your heart.
Go, bring Priya here.
Krishna...
...stay carefully there
Eat and sleep on time,
don't talk too much with anybody.
And don't get into any trouble...
...whateveryou do, make sure you
behave like any other man.
Don't get carried away to do things
that make people realise...
Who l am? Right, Grandma?
Yes, my son.
Don't worry, Grandma.
l won't let anybody know about me.
l'll keep my strength, my abilities
and my talent... hidden.
That's a promise, Grandma.
Welcome to Singapore, Sir.
- Thank you.
Your welcome sounds different...
and nicer, today.
Good afternoon, sir.
A very good afternoon, Dr. Mathur.
But sir...
-Yes, yes, l know...
l've come a few days in advance.
But l couldn't help it.
l've waited so many years...
...but now that we're so close to success...
...being patient is very difficult.
Must say you and yourteam deserve credit...
...for making my dream come true again.
Sir, the credit goes to Rohit Mehra...
lf it wasn't for his notes and research...
...it was impossible to build
that computer again.
Absolute genius!-You're right, sir
The computerthat Rohit made in 2 years...
...has taken us so many years to make.
That's why l still miss him.
Excuse me
People say ''Who has seen the future?''
But in a few days, you and l...
...will change this forever.
Breaking news!
Afteryears of struggle, hard work,
research and patience...
...Dr. Siddhant Arya's most ambitious project
is about to be completed.
According to our correspondent,
in just a few days...
...Dr Arya will be able to predict the future of
individuals, countries and the world!
He'll also be able to change the
course of their destinies.
And the truth is, one who can see
and change the future...
...is considered like God!
Wrong!
Not Like God...
He is God!
l will be God.
Now no one can stop me.
We're already late and then
this is how you park the car?
l can't even open the door!
How am l going to get out?
But neither can l!
Great! Let's just sit in the car
and stare at each other!
You always mess things up!
Krishna's flight must have landed...
...he must be looking for us.
l'm sorry, Sir!
You're not hurt, are you?
Krishna
Krishna, you're looking
is so good in these clothes.
They are my fathers.
Krishna, welcome to Singapore!
O my god! You look so handsome!
You two have come alone?
How can two people be 'alone'?
No! l mean, hasn't your mother
come with you?
Mother?
ls she also coming here?
lt would've been nice if she were here.
l'd have asked foryour hand and
gone back to lndia immediately.
Grandma's all alone, you see.
He's in a tearing hurry!
Has he brought a priest along to
solemnise the wedding?
Shut up!
What happened?
Well actually, Mom, you know...
Her mom's gone.
Yeah she's gone...
Gone?
To Hong Kong
Yes, Hong Kong!
Hong Kong?
She'll be back in 10-15 days
Yes, she'll come.
10-15 days? But what will l do here
for so many days?
Why Krishna? Didn't you take us around
your village when we came there?
Now we'll show you our city.
This is your apartment.
This is your living room.
This is your bedroom
And these clothes are foryou
This is your cell phone.
lt has all our numbers.
You can call us anytime.
But why can't l live with you
in your house, Priya?
Well...
Because mom...
- ...is not around
Yes! Mom's not around
wouldn't be proper
Hey! My phone is ringing!
lt says 'Mama' how do l take the call?
Looks like l gave you my cell phone
by mistake, Excuse me.
Hello Priya, l have good news!
l've found a boy foryou.
l'm busy right now.
l'll call you later, Mama.
lt was your mom's call?
Let me say hello to her.
No, it wasn't mom
lt was my uncle.
l could've said hello to him.
Does he live here too?
Yes...
No! He lives in lndia.
l see, where in lndia?
Krishna, we've got to go to office.
We'll give you her uncle's address later.
with pin code. But we've got to leave now. Bye!
Bye!- Bye
How many lies do we have
to speak to cover up one lie?
The excuse of an uncle saved us today!
- Tomorrow it'll be an aunt!
There is no dearth of relatives. Relax!
Did you see his eyes?
They were full of love and trust.
Honey, l can't do this!
l can't hurt Krishna anymore.
Hurt? He's going to become a
celebrity thanks to you.
And we'll get a promotion.
And even if he gets to know,
a small lie is not going to hurt him
What happened?
You? How did you get here from the 20th floor?
l took the stairs.
Stairs?
Actually, Priya, l've got something foryou...
What?
l'll go get the car ok?
Close your eyes.
Priya, why do you widen your eyes
whenever l ask you to close them?
Open them now
May l put it on yourfinger?
Give me your hand
Looks nice?
Yes, now it looks nice.
Okay bye.- Bye
What happened?
l'll tell you later, lets go!
No money- Okay
Brother!
Thank you.
You're welcome
Kristian Xuan Zhong Min Lee
What?
My name...too long
Short? Kris Lee, okay?
Oh, okay! Kris Lee.
Nice name.
My name is Krishna...Krishna Mehra.
Krishna? lndia?
Yes, lndia
l work here in the Great Bombay Circus
Must come, okay?
Okay.
Sunday, Okay?
Sunday, okay.
Ten days will go by in no time.
Tell me how are you finding it there?
lts very nice, Grandma.
There are a lot of high rise buildings here.
And my apartment is on the 20th floor...
And l'm talking to you from the balcony right now.
Ok, ok, take care of yourself.
And give my love and blessings to Priya.
Just imagine! That's the
name of our new show.
Can you imagine a human being
climbing a tree fasterthan a monkey?
No... isn't it? Well after watching
our show today.
You won't just imagine,
but also believe that is possible.
Get set then! On one end is the
world famous orangutan Mao...
....who in a blink, will climb this pole.
And on the other side is
lndian superboy Krishna!
What's happening here, Priya?
What happened?
You brought me here to watch a shoot!
True. But then l thought if you can watch a shoot,
you can even perform in it!
But how can l climb the pole fasterthan Mao?
Like you climbed the mountain!
The zigzag manner...remember?
But what if l lose to Mao?
l'm sure you won't.
But what if l do?
well...
l'll marry Mao then.
No! l'll never let that happen.
So do it please! lt'll be great fun.
Fun it will be.
Sir we're ready
Ready is it?
Chao, is Mao ready?
Ready
Krishna...Ready?
Priya, there's just a pole's distance
between us and our success!
Not a pole, it's just a moment. Stupid!
Taking
Roll camera
Action
Cut!
What the hell is this?
Boss, it's all about brotherhood
Shut up!
Sorry, Sir
Come on Mao, come on
Roll camera... Action
Cut!
You stupid ape! l've paid a lot
of money foryou, okay?
And l'm tired of you monkeying around
You don't get your act together;
you're out of my show. Okay?
l've straightened a lot of these smart alecs
Roll camera!
Action.
Where is the fish?
Cut!
Roll camera!
Action.
l'm not going to the circus with you.
Strange! Why vent your
anger against Mao, on me?
How can l help it if he refused
to climb the pole?
And the fish...instead of
coming into my hand...
They palmed off a can, a shoe and that...
Wow! Priya smile!
ln lndia you caught the fish so easily!
Actually those fish knew me,
they stood by me.
But you're not standing by me!
l've come to stand by you for life, Priya.
For life? When my mother asks
you what you do?
What will you say?
l'll tell her what l do
Love you.
And...what else will you say?
l'll fulfill all your wishes, look afteryou.
And...?
l'll never let a smile leave yourface.
And..?
Whethertimes good or bad
we'll always be together.
just like eyelashes are with the eyes.
And...?
You will dream and l'll fulfill them.
ln the scorching heat of the sun,
l'll be your shade.
and in the cold, l'll give you warmth.
When the rains botheryou, l'll change
the course of the clouds.
and when a storm blows...
l'll turn the winds away.
That's how l shall protect
you all my life...
from every danger.
from every trouble.
Now l hope your mother will agree?
ADLABS
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
''what have you ever done?''
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
''what have you ever done?''
''what have you done in this world?''
''lf you've neverfallen in love''
ADLABS
''you have set foot, On the moon''
''you've made an abode, in the seas''
''But have you taught those crying''
''how to laugh?''
''Even God will smile and ask you one day''
'' heart''
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
''what have you ever done?''
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
''what have you ever done?''
''what have you done in this world?''
''lf you've neverfallen in love''
''Life's also a circus''
''straight now, upside down in a moment''
''Those who get love have things
straightened out''
''else, they keep hanging ''
''lt's the simple truth, believe it''
''Heart...''
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
''what have you ever done?''
''what have you done in this world?''
''lf you've neverfallen in love''
ADLABS
''One more time''
''lf you haven't taken a heart''
''if you haven't given your heart''
Fire! Help!
Priya...
My daughter...
My daughter, she's trapped inside
please somebody save my daughter
Help! Help! Mummy papa Help!
Somebody save my sister's life!
ls anybody there? Help me!
l'll keep my strength, my abilities
and my talent... hidden
That's a promise, Grandma.
Help! Help!
Somebody help! Help me somebody!
Please help, help!
Help! Help!
Somebody help, Mummy Papa!
Look!
Mummy, Papa!
Our daughter is inside,
Please save our daughter, sir...
Please save my child!
l beg of you, sir. Please! save
our daughter sir.
Please!
Help! Help!
Somebody help!
Help!
Come!
Who...who are you?
Krrish
Friend
Priya!
Are you all right?
But how did you get here?
You had fainted.
l had gone to get some waterforyou...
God! What a blaze! Come,
let's go home.
The most sensational news in
Singapore right now
is the circus blaze at Marina Bay
which took place last night
and the daredevil masked man saviour who, in a
flash, rescued many victims trapped in the fire
and has become every child's hero overnight but
his identity is still shrouded in mystery.
Till yesterday, we only had a description
and a picture of the masked man.
Today, we've got to know his name
and also got a piece of his mask.
Let's find out how.
He said his name is Krrish
and this piece of the mask broke
from his forehead.
So his name is Krrish!
KRRlSH!
But his identity is still shrouded
in mystery.
Whoever Krrish is, a bravery award
and cash reward of 25000 dollars...
has been announced in appreciation
of his courage.
So how are we going to identify Krrish?
The one, whose mask this piece matches with,
will be considered to be Krrish.
And he'll be the one to be rewarded.
Krrish! Krrish! After all who is this Krrish?
Listen carefully, our priority
at the moment is Krrish.
Only Krrish! Get that?
Krrish's identity...
Our channel should be the
first to reveal him!
Do you get that?
Our channel must be the first one to
unmask this masked Krrish!
Get it? Stop nodding and leave!
Go, get him! Go, go!
Where are the two of you going?
To look for Krrish.
Ah, forget Krrish. And look for a new job.
New job...?
You both are fired.
What?
You better go back to lndia...
and enjoy your Krishna's flute playing.
Don't waste yourtime, Go, go!
Out!
Thanks to Krishna we're jobless.
Now what do we do?
Honey, l think Krrish is none other
than our own Krishna.
What?
Yes, Honey!
At the circus, l saw Krrish from
such a close distance.
l have a strong feeling that Krishna is Krrish.
So why didn't you tell this to
boss at the meeting?
Because l wasn't sure, l need
to confirm it first.
Confirm? How?
Listen, l have an idea...
Honey, these guys...?
Priya! l've hired some actors.
But l'm a bit late...
l'll be there soon.
What?
So who are these guys?
Oh my God! Help!
This is now mine...bye!
l'm so sorry, Krishna. l'm so sorry.
l thought you were Krrish and
planned my own kidnapping.
But then, real goons turned up
instead of the hired ones.
Real goons?
But why didn't you hit back?
Why did you quietly take their beating?
l wanted to see...
whether it hurts you to see me in pain.
lt does.
Where's your ring?
Maybe they've...
Who's he? Why's he here?
l think he's the masked man.
Masked man?
Get him.
l'm sorry, sorry.
My friend Krrish!
l'll tell everyone, l'll tell my sister.
No, Kristian. Don't tell anyone.
Why? You become famous!
You'll get the reward.
Here, Kristian. You become Krrish.
Take it. Get the money foryour sister.
Make her legs good again.
Take it!
No, it's yours. You are the hero.
Every human being who fights for a
good cause is a hero, Kristian.
You... are fighting foryour sister.
You are a hero.
The biggest news of today!
Superhero Krrish has revealed his
identity to the media...
and the broken piece of the mask
fitting his mask
has confirmed his identity
Here today, Hero Honda is honouring
Krrish for his bravery
Well done young man.
Thank you
Not once did it occurto me that
Kristian could also be Krrish!
He was also there at the circus that night!
Had it struck me that night
l wouldn't have got a thrashing!
l've said sorry, haven't l?
What else do you want me to do?
Close your eyes...
again you...
Now open them.
How did you get it back?
Krrish, he's my friend.
Wouldn't he do this much for me?
Thank you, thank you
Take it
Won't you put it on my finger?
ADLABS
''where the rays of the sun come from''
''Where the moonlight dwells''
''comes news''
''there's no one like you''
''Where sleep hides''
''Where dreams are made''
''comes news''
''there's no one like you''
ADLABS
''Flower, butterflies, the buds...''
''they're all sulking''
''From them you have stolen...''
''their ability to evoke love''
''Where colours are created''
''and beauty is crafted''
''comes news''
''there's no one like you''
''You have stolen my heart''
''do you realize that''
''ln you lies all the love in the world''
''ln you it lies''
''Where people go crazy in love...''
''Where Lovers Are Born''
''comes news''
''there's no one like you''
ADLABS
Priya!
Move from there.
Priya, you're watching TV here and there boss has
ordered to vacate Krishna's apartment.
Hello! Are you listening?
l am & am not.
What's this?
Rememberthe explosion at the circus?
l had passed out, but l think the
camera was still on.
Now switch off the TV and think
about Krishna! Please!
Oh my god!
What happened?
l'll rewind and show you.
Krishna is Krrish!
What happened?
Why are you girls screaming?
Where are you both going?
Mom Office! l'll see you okay.
Office?
Come on Honey
To get our jobs back!
Ok bye!
Priya, your mobile.
Hello Priya?
No, l'm Priya's mother
Mother...hello.
When did you return from Hong Kong?
Hong Kong? l didn't go anywhere...
l've been right here
And who are you?
lt's me, Krishna.
Krishna, who?
Priya has told you everything about me,
hasn't she?
No, Priya has said nothing about you.
You are Priya's mother aren't you?
Yes...l'm Priya's mother.
Where's Priya?
Priya left for office just now.
Office...
Right... Thank you
Priya, do you realise? Once this
footage is telecast....
Our Krishna will become a
world famous celebrity!
There's something about our Krishna!
He fooled us so convincingly.
ln lndia, as Kalicharan, and here, as Krrish!
Didn't l tell you Honey, the truth
always comes out?
Look Priya, the truth about Krishna
the world is about to discover...
...is because you lied!
The lie that you love him brought him
here all the way from lndia.
And imagine! Now we're going to
create a big sensation!
You're right. A lie sometimes leads
to very big gains.
You didn't even tell me!
What could l say?
When his honesty turned my feigned
love into a genuine one...
l didn't even realize
l'm in love with Krishna, Honey
Krishna, Krishna
The culprit has been caught at last!
He did his best to hide his identity, you know
But l finally discovered who the real Krrish is!
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you keep me in the dark?
Where was the need to hide behind
a mask, even with me?
You're asking this Priya?
Someone who has never been honest with me
Someone who kept me in the dark till today
l have been unmasked Priya.
What about you?
What do you mean?
Why did you lie to me that you loved me?
l took your lies forthe truth and came here.
to ask your motherforyour hand in marriage
But you lied about hertoo!
yes, Priya
l've spoken to your mother
Krishna...
l'm sorry
l admit, l lied to you in the beginning
But now...
l really love you Krishna
Stop it, Priya! Stop it!
you may have more lies to tell me
But l don't have the strength to take
them forthe truth anymore!
Listen to me, Krishna! l've done
all this only foryou
l wanted to see you become
a very big man
and that's about to happen in
just a few hours
the whole world will get to know about
your extraordinary powers and talent
that's exactly what l didn't want
Why do you think l wore the mask?
because l had promised grandma that
l'd keep my identity hidden
that l would not let anyone know
about my powers
and you
grandma was right
people in the world only use each other
fortheir own selfish reasons
She tried to stop me, but l...
But why does your grandmother
want to stop you?
Why does she always want you
in front of her eyes?
Why doesn't she want the whole
world to know of yourtalent?
ls she not being selfish?
Priya!
You really want to know?
Then listen!
having lost her son, grandma
did not want to lose me
because l posses the same powers
but she still let me come here
foryou
for my feelings, she gave in
But what do l tell her now?
Krishna, listen to me... Krishna!
Krishna...
Hello Honey
We've got to stop the telecast
of Krishna's tape
Why?
don't ask questions now, just
stop the telecast
but the tape is with boss
My god, where's boss?
l wish to thank all my investors
in Singapore
they are the ones who really
deserve this applause
for having had faith in my
various projects
l'm delighted to announce that
our company, Technotronics...
has made a profit of 400 million
dollars this year
l therefore announce100% dividend
to all our shareholders
Any questions?
Yes?
Dr. Arya, congratulations on the phenomenal
success of your company
my question is
20 years ago, you tried to make a computer
that could see the future
What happened to that dream of yours?
20 years ago, you must have had
a lot of dreams too...
Did they all come true?
Pardon me?
some questions hurt
the media ought to understand
that dream died with the death of my
genius friend, Rohit Mehra
But from what l've read and
heard of you, Dr. Arya...
you don't ever accept defeat
l'd have tried to win...
had my genius friend been alive
Any further questions?
excuse me
sir, l need to speak to that lady
for just one minute
Please!
Krishna
Anything left to say?
Yes...This gentleman has
something to say
Who are you?
My name is Vikram Sinha
What do you want?
Don't go back the way you came.
What does that mean?
l mean, you came alone
don't go back alone.
Krishna, yourfather, Rohit Mehra,
is still alive.
What did you say?
This picture was taken when
yourfather worked for Dr Arya
And l was the Senior Security
Officer at Technotronics.
He was youngerto me in age,
and l was a junior in status.
And yet, we were very close friends.
not only because we were lndians
it was because of the sincerity in his smile
and the honesty in his eyes.
He was always smiling...
but someone cast an evil eye on him.
lt's been so many years,
but that time...
seems to have frozen.
That day, he was working till morning...
because he had to complete his
project and go back to lndia.
Good morning, chief
Mr. Vikram? Welcome!
How are you this morning?
l'm doing fine, chief
but if you keep working round the clock like this,
you're going to get insomnia
l won't have to do it aftertoday.
Once the computer is inaugurated today...
l'll hand it overto Dr Arya and return
to my family in lndia.
Don't mind, chief...
but l still can't believe that we
can see the future.
Not believing does not change
the truth, Mr. Vikram.
You will believe it, when you see it?
What? You mean you're going to...
Of course!
Come see tomorrow, today
and tell me how it feels to see the future.
Please hold this.
Retina scan, an identification of my eyes
These 2 identifications of mine are
the password forthis computer.
Without which, it won't start up.
But when you're not around, when
you've gone back to lndia?
l'll change the password before l leave
Afterthat, only Dr Arya will be able
to start the computer.
Tell me...
What would you like to see?
l...l don't want to see anything, chief!
But you said your wife is pregnant
Let's see whether l'm going to be an
uncle to a nephew or a niece?
Ok then...let's find out.
Nisha!
My darling baby...
Look, Nisha, your son looks just like Rohit.
Now go to your Mom. My son's
coming back to me.
Congratulations, chief! Your wife's
going to deliver a baby boy tomorrow!
But l'm going to distribute sweets
today! ln fact, right now?
What did you say?
What happened to my Rohit?
What happened, Mom?
No! That's impossible!
My Rohit can't be dead!
My Rohit is alive!
No!
Which means, l...
Chief, the computer's malfunctioning!
Something's wrong with it!
Dr Arya!
lt's 6:40 there, it's 6:30 now!
This means, in just 10 minutes!
in this very room!
Look! Dr. Arya!
Have you heard of Shahjahan, Doctor Mathur?
Of course! He built the Taj Mahal.
lncomplete knowledge is always dangerous.
Shahjahan had the hands of workers
who built the Taj Mahal, chopped off!
so that there would never be another Taj Mahal.
Rohit Mehra is a workerfor me
and l'm his Shahjehan.
You mean, you're also going to
cut off Rohit's hands?
No...his brain!
because Rohit's brain will create problems,
for himself as well as for me.
Actually, l'm going to feel very sorry about
it because Rohit is a very good boy.
Sincere, honest, intelligent...
They're coming here, chief. Please leave!
No, no! l'm won't let this computer
go into the wrong hands.
l'll destroy everything!
All right!
l'll try and stop them!
Hello!
Mom?
Rohit? l've brought Nisha to the hospital.
Congratulations! You're going to
become a father anytime.
Come home soon, son
l'm coming, Mom! l'm coming!
Rohit...What's the matter? You sound tense?
l've been exploited, the world is very selfish!
Don't worry, l'll be back, l'll be back soon.
Rohit!
What have you done?
l've destroyed your dream...
l've destroyed everything!
because l've got to know of your intentions
But those who know me also
know that l never accept defeat.
l'll rebuild this computer
using your research.
But l don't need you anymore.
Thank you so much for everything, Rohit
Good bye
Hold it, sir!
Don't kill him, sir
lf you kill Rohit...then even if you
build the computer again
you'll never be able to start it
You need a password to start the computer
and the password is Rohit himself.
What?
Yes, sir
l've seen it with my own eyes.
Until scans of his retina and heartbeat
are fed into the computer...
the computer will not start.
This means, l'll have to keep you alive
till l don't build a new computer.
But die, you will.
Forthe world.
Breaking news.
Tragedy strikes!
Following a fire that broke out in
the lab of Technotronics...
The famous lndian genius Rohit Mehra
has met with a tragic death.
Let's observe a 2-minute silence,
so that Rohit Mehra's soul rests in peace.
Ever since, l had no choice but
to work for Dr Arya.
l couldn't even go to the police...
because if Dr Arya doubted me,
he would've killed me.
And l was the only man who could
get in touch with yourfamily.
That's exactly why l've been looking foryour
grandma and you for so many years.
And finally, l met you today, through Priya.
Dr Arya
20 years...
for 20 years, he's kept a
mother away from her son
and a son away from his father
lt's because of his lies that l lost my mother.
Where is my father?
Here in Singapore.
For 20 years Dr Arya has used
machines to keep him in a state
that only his brain is alive,
his body almost dead.
Good evening, my friend Rohit Mehra
How are you feeling today?
Are these machines taking good care of you?
Yes?
Good!
Tomorrow's the glorious and historic day
when my, sorry, our computer
will be inaugurated.
Yes! Ours, because nothing
was possible without you
For so many years, you have
shown such patience and understanding
and cooperated with me.
When the computer starts tomorrow
your utility will come to an end,
and so will your pain.
See you tomorrow
Breaking news!
Dr Arya has suddenly been
reminded of the poet Kabir.
Do today, what you must do tomorrow...
and do right now, what you must do today.
That's why, Dr Arya has decided
to start the computertoday itself.
and also end Rohit's life.
ls this where my father is kept?
Yes! But it's almost impossible
for a strangerto get there...
Dr. Arya has kept very tight security
everywhere on the island
So that now no one comes between
him and the computer
Krishna, if Dr. Arya starts the computer
how much havoc he can wreak and
the destruction he can cause, is unimaginable
mine... yours... ours, the worlds
destiny will come in his clutches.
That's why, Dr Arya has to be
stopped at any cost.
Now you have to save not only yourfather
but the whole mankind, Krishna.
Hello.
Krishna?
Grandma!
Krishna, are you okay?
Yes, Grandma
l don't know why l'm feeling worried.
When are you coming back?
Come back soon
Yourfather's death anniversary is nearing,
you need to be here and fulfill the duties of a son.
l remember, Grandma. don't worry...
l'll fulfill all the duties of a son.
WELCOME TO THE FUTURE
Congratulations Sir!
See, Rohit l've won!
Now if you want you can end your life.
Or do you want me to help?
But what's the hurry? At least see how your
invention is going to make me God!
Rohit, we built this computer
so that we can see ourfuture
and change it!
l will also change my future and show you
Today itself!
Dr Arya's gone to look forthe masked man
Masked man?
Kristian!
Krishna
Look Dr Arya!
Come on, let's go!
What had Kristian done? Why kill him?
Dr Arya has probably started the
computer and, he must've seen...
His future!
lt will be just as Dr Arya has seen.
l've changed my future!
l've changed my tomorrow!
There is no mask any longer...
Henceforth the new face of God is...
Dr Siddhant Arya!
How is this possible?
l've killed him with my own hands.
Then...who's this?
lts 9:15 there and it's 9 here.
This means, he'll be here in
the next 15 minutes.
that means he is already on the island!
Stop!
To capture him we need
planning not power.
Dr. Arya has kept very tight security
everywhere on the island.
You're good! Very good.
But l'm better
Yes, l am better
Because l have seen the future.
But due to lack of time what l
couldn't see is what l want to know...
Why do you want to kill me?
And why do you want to rescue Rohit Mehra?
Who are you?
Come to me and give me the answer.
come!
l've told you, l have seen the future
And l know who is with me...
Hello!
and who is against me
So...please cooperate
Who are you?
We'll get to know right now.
Who...are you?
Your son...Krishna!
Mom.
Thank you, Jadoo.
Thank you
Subs by Amay_MYS