Stairs!
I don't think I can...
Hey guys... just start without me.
I'll catch up.
Sweet!
Inner Peace. Inner Peace.
Itchy nose.
Finally, Inner Peace.
Now what?
"Kai" old friend!
Master Oogway.
Ah! Our battle ended
five hundred years ago.
Well, now I am ready for a rematch.
Took you long enough.
You've grown stronger.
500 years in the spirit realm,
you'll pick up a thing or two.
I have taken the Chi of every master here.
No.
- Yes.
And soon I'll have your power, too.
When will you realize,
"The more you take, the less you have"?
With your Chi, I'll finally be able
to return to the mortal world.
And this time, you won't
be there to stop me.
It was never my destiny to stop you.
I have set another on that path.
Then I will find him and take his Chi too.
Justice...is about to be served.
We'll have two Justice Platters, please.
- Umm... three.
- And a few tofu bun.
Oh, the spicy noodle soup for Tigress.
Did you want extra sauce with that?
She wants it on the side.
On the side.
- On the side.
Dragon you can do it.
Go Dragon Warrior.
- Defend the valley.
- Yeah defend the valley.
You guys aren't doing the
dramatic pose, are you?
Do we have to strike the
pose every time we land?
You guys never underestimate
the power of a dramatic entrance.
I've heard about some masters who could win
a fight just by throwing open a door.
Dramatic entrance?
Master Shifu.
The Dragon Warrior is great.
Really? I was just making...
yeah I mean yeah I am.
Before the battle of the fist
comes the battle of the mind.
Hence, the dramatic entrance.
Whoa, nice dramatic entrance.
- What's the occasion?
- Today will be my final class.
Your final...? wait
I didn't even know you were sick.
Although you have been looking a little...
- I'm not sick.
Healthy. A little healthy.
A lot actually.
My final class because from now on...
your training will be in the
hands of the Dragon Warrior.
What?
Me? Teach? I mean why not Tigress?
She's always telling everyone what to do.
Be quiet Po.
- See what I mean?
Tigress is not the Dragon Warrior.
You are.
Come on they're the five.
What can I teach them?
There is always something more to learn.
Even for a master.
For instance, let me show you another move.
The dramatic exit.
What's that?
Are you kidding me? That... what?
- Where'd he go?
- Master.
He's gone guys. It's cool.
- We are await your instruction master.
All you have to lose is our respect.
Seriously how bad could it be?
Leave me...
OK OK let's switch it up.
Monkey, immovable mountain stance.
Yes Master.
I mean... Tigress tornado back flip.
- Yes, master.
Oh no fire.
- Fire.
Sorry, my fault
Crane go high, I mean low.
Oh my claw thingy - Viper and
tigress, to... like a totem pole.
Poison, Technique.
You two, to... sworming insect bite
with yellow tail, yellow jacket...
Spicy... tuna.
Good job, Po.
Did you at least learn a little something?
- Yes, that you can't teach.
And tigress is flammable turns out.
That was a complete disaster.
I'm glad we're not Po right now.
- What a loser.
What was Shifu thinking?
- What was Oogway thinking?
I think he heard us.
- I didn't hear anything.
He said you're a loser.
Sorry Oogway.
Would you stop doing that?
- How was your first day teaching?
Humiliating.
- I heard.
Who told you?
Did Tigress tell you?
I heard from Monkey and
Crane and Mantis and
your dad and Mrs. Chau
from the gift shop.
And those ducks who just passed
and Tigress told me.
Yeah, well did she also tell you that
it'll never happen again cause I'm done?
Teaching, or being humiliated?
Both. I don't know why you ever thought
I could teach that class?
Oh I knew you couldn't.
- What?
You set me up to fail? Why?
If you only do what you can do
you'll never be more than you are now.
I don't wanna be more
I like who I am.
You don't even know who you are.
What do you...? Of course I do
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
And what exactly does
that mean Dragon Warrior?
It means... you know... just going around
and punching and kicking.
Defending the valley and stuff.
Punching and kicking?
You think that is what the great
master Oogway saw for you?
A five hundred year prophecy full-filled so
you can spend your days...
Kicking butt? And running through
town high-fiving bunnies?
Yes.
- No.
Oogway saw greatness in you Po
against my better judgment.
More than you can see in yourself.
Incredible power awaits you.
Power beyond anything you can imagine.
What was that?
- That was chi.
What's chi?
The energy that flows
through all living things.
So you're saying if I,
so you're saying if I
teach, I'll be able to
do cool stuff like that?
No I'm saying if you teach, I'll be
able to do cool stuff like that.
Mastery of chi requires mastery of self.
Oogway sat alone in a cave for
thirty years asking one question...
Who am I?
I'm lucky if I get five
minutes before you interrupt.
So now I have to sit alone
in a cave for thirty years?
Eventually.
After you master teaching.
Teaching? There's no way
I'm ever gonna be like you.
I'm not trying to turn you into me.
I'm trying to turn you into you.
Turn me into me?
Wait a second. That makes no...(sense)
Almost there shifu, just a little more
confusing and you'll be the next Oogway.
Sorry, no offense master Oogway
I just...
I'll let you get back
to your eternal peace.
What is this place?
- Aaah... my brother's farm.
If I stepped on you, would you die?
Yes.
The mortal realm.
You hear that Oogway?
I'm back.
Kai has returned.
Who?
- Kai. General Kai.
Supreme warlord of all China.
I don't know.
- The jade slayer, master of pain.
You may know me as the beast of vengeance.
Maker of widows?
OK I used to work with Oogway.
Oh master Oogway, he was a great warrior.
We've heard of master oogway... Wise and...
OK... Silence.
Find Oogway's students
and bring them to me.
By the time I am done with them Oogway...
There will be no one left who
will even remember your name.
Kai is coming.
I am ready...
to teach you a lesson.
- Teach me?
Oh no he's the Dragon teacher.
- Yeah he's so handsome.
Thank you for the compliment.
No, please don't teach me to death.
Po?
Oh hey dad What's up?
I like just ...stopping
by for a little soak.
OK, What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing? I come home and find you
taking a bath with your dolls.
Action figures. - And instead of
adding bath-salt to the water...
You just added Szechuan peppercorns.
- Szechuan what?
My tenders.
OK yes, something's wrong - There there
son, you tell your daddy all about it.
Lift your arm.
Shifu says I don't know what it
means to be the Dragon Warrior.
And now I have to be a teacher.
I thought I finally knew who I was. If I'm
not the Dragon Warrior, then who am I?
A teacher? Teaching kung fu?
That's a promotion. Take the job, son.
And someday, when you're
in charge of the whole.
Jade palace, I can sell
noodles in the lobby.
Why are you still here taking a bath like
a baby? Get out. Get out. Go, go, go.
Franchise expansion awaits us.
What about the Dragon Warrior
look alike contest?
Mrs. Chau always wins that.
- Skadoosh.
And the Dragon Warrior
dumpling eating contest?
I have to defend my title.
No one's gonna beat your
dumpling eating record.
Someone's about to beat your
Go. Go. Go.
Who's eating my dumplings?
- And who's paying for them?
101, 102.
Li: 103.
Is that a new record?
Who are you?
I'm Li Shan.
- What?
I'm Li shan.
I'm looking for my son.
You lost your son?
- Yes, many years ago.
I lost my father.
- Very sorry.
Thank you.
Well, good luck to you.
- You too.
I hope you find your son.
And I hope you find your father.
Son? Oh my gosh, it is you.
Well don't just stand there
give your old man a hug.
I can't believe you're alive.
I thought I'd lost you forever
little Lotus.
This is very embarrassing, but
I think you've got me confused
with a panda named Lotus.
My name is Po.
Oh right, you wouldn't... OK.
See, the little Lotus was the name
you were given at birth.
Really?
- Really.
I can't believe it. After all these
years and you're really here?
This is amazing.
Oh dad. Come say hi to...
I don't know what
I'm supposed to call you.
I'm pretty sure
he said his name is Li.
You... come here.
Thank you, thank you for taking
such good care of my son.
Your son?
Now hold on just a minute.
How do we know this stranger is
even related to you?
Look at that.
Our bellies could be brothers.
Hey son, let me teach you how to
belly gong. All right, belly gong.
It's like looking in a fat mirror.
I can't believe we're
taking a picture together.
But I still don't understand.
I thought Po was the only panda left.
No, there's a whole bunch of us.
- Where?
Here, a secret panda village in the
mountains - A secret panda...
But how did you know where I was?
- I received a message that led me here.
How could you receive a message
if no one could find you?
Sounds suspicious to me.
No, wait wait.
It was a message from the universe.
Rats.
Now what's all this about a Dragon Warrior?
How'd you know I was the Dragon Warrior?
Did the universe tell you that, too?
No, the poster did and the gift shop
I bought a tiny cup.
Oh right, of course...
You gotta... you have no idea there's
so much to show you.
You're gonna be so awesomely proud.
Come on, come on.
I'm already awesomely proud.
Couple more steps.
- Oh.
Feeling the burn.
Do you have panda asthma, too?
Does that run in the family?
Dad, you're gonna love this.
It's like the coolest thing ever.
This is the hall of heroes.
Home of the most priceless
kung fu artifacts in all of China.
This place is...
Awesome?
You were going to say awesome, right?
Because it totally is.
- Totally.
But be super careful,
everything is very fragile here.
Like the Urn of Whispering warriors.
Someone broke that once.
Who?
- Some idiot.
This is master flying Rhino's battle armor.
- I wonder if I could fit in that.
Get out of my head, dad.
I've wondered the same thing.
If I could fit in it?
- If you could? No, if I could fit in it.
Dad, check it out.
Master Ram's crossbow
The infinite gates smasher.
Dad, look at this. The battle helmets of
master Rat's army. They're so tiny.
Master Dolphin's water proof armor.
This is my favorite.
Check it out. It's the legendary
battle rickshaw of emperor Hawk.
Sweet ride.
Dad, what are you doing?
We're not supposed to touch anything.
- Oh sorry sorry. Should I put it back?
Yeah you probably should.
You look so cool, though.
How does it feel? Do the hinges hinge?
Does it smell like rhino?
Does it feel like you're impenetrable?
Does it feel like you can take
on a thousand warriors?
And emerge unscathed?
Yes, it's pretty cool.
Wonder what this does?
I should pull it.
I think I just peed a little.
Anything else we should try in here, son?
Charge.
Faster, faster, faster.
Thumb war.
- Reinforcements.
This is so much fun.
Here we go.
- Awesome.
There, there.
- I'm fine I'm fine.
There you go.
Dolphin style attack.
You got me.
- Dolphin style retreat.
Go long son.
I wasn't ready.
Coming back at you.
- I got it.
Throw high.
- Yeah, C'mon.
I'm coming for you.
- Bring it on master Rhino.
Here I come.
I'm gonna get you.
Who's gonna get you?
Master Rhino.
- Why, what's wrong?
Guys guys, you're never gonna
guess who just showed up.
Not in a million years.
You can't... you just try.
- Your father.
Wow, how did you just guess that?
Oh, wait a second. Yeah of course.
We look exactly the same.
Say hi to my friends, Mantis
Tigress, Monkey, Crane, and Viper.
Oh Viper, was it?
- Monkey, sir.
They're kind of my best friends.
And this... this is master Shifu.
Legend.
It is an honor to meet you, master Panda.
Perhaps your father would care to join us
in the training hall?
Your son will be teaching the class
I'm sure he's tired.
I'm sure you're tired.
He's tired. I'm gonna show him
the chrysanthemums suite.
What? Tired? No, I'm fine.
I would love to watch you teach.
Trust me.
It would be more fun to watch me.
Fight.
What is that?
- The valley is under attack.
Son? Under attack?
- This is perfect.
Now you can see what being
the Dragon Warrior is all about.
Follow me.
Enemies of justice.
Prepare for... whoa.
Are you kidding me?
What's the deal with the green guys?
Some kind of jade zombies.
- Jade zombies?
Zombies, Jinx.
Lotus be careful.
- It's OK dad. I do this every...
Whoa. I recognize this guys.
The master Badger twins.
With their crushing double gong
technique.
Yeah that's the one.
That guys is... no.
Master Porcupine.
I thought he died hundred
hundred years ago.
These guys are legends.
Get a quick sketch of us.
Did you get it?
Aw, I blinked.
Can we get another one?
I'm being choked by master Porcupine.
This is so cool.
Look. It's you.
- Po, focus.
Message from universe? I'll give you
one message from the universe...
Stay away from my son.
Sorry dad. I'll clean it up later. - Whoa,
whoa, not my good pan. Take this one.
Lotus, watch out.
Dad, check out my dumplings of doom.
Gotcha.
I see you.
Your chi will soon be mine.
Is he talking to me?
- Which one? They're all talking.
Whoa, you're right.
That's so scary.
We should try that, too.
Maybe it'd be scary back at them.
OK but we gotta plan
what we're gonna say first
otherwise it won't be scary,
it'll be just stupid.
It's not them talking. Idiots.
It's me talking through them, Kai.
Who?
- OK OK, enough.
Did you see that? Did you see?
- Whoa, what just happened?
The green smoke just poof... and then poof
Shifu, what wast that?
Kai? Kai? Kai.
Nope. Never heard of him.
Kai, where is it?
There's so much wisdom in here,
I can't find anything.
Yes.
Behold.
All the answers will be found within.
What? It's blank?
Are you kidding me?
Not again.
Wait, wait. Hold on. Sorry
Oh OK, here we go.
It is written in Oogway's hand.
Long ago, I had a brother.
- Oogway had a brother?
In arms. In arms, sorry.
He said brother in arms.
- Can you just unroll it all at once?
I was an ambitious young warrior
leading a great army.
And fighting by my side was Kai.
My closest friend.
One day we were ambushed.
I was badly wounded.
My friend carried me for days
looking for help.
Until we came to a secret
village, high in the mountains.
An ancient place of healing.
A village of pandas.
Pandas?
- Yes, pandas.
Pandas who used the power
of chi to heal me.
They taught me how to give chi.
But Kai wanted the power all to himself.
He saw that what could be given
could also be taken.
I had to stop him.
Our battle shook the Earth.
Until, finally, I banished Kai to
the spirit realm.
Should he ever return to the mortal realm
he can only be stopped
by a true master of chi.
True master of chi?
Like you.
Me? I can barely make a flower bloom.
I'd need at least thirty
more years, and a cave.
Viper: We need a chi master.
Shifu: He will continue stealing the chi
of masters until he has consumed it all.
Viper: We have to make a way to stop him.
Crane: Oh get more more powerful
with every master he defeats.
Tigress: There is no choice. We fight.
I can teach you, son.
You can do this?
- Of course, I'm a panda.
That must be why the universe
sent you here.
OK, so what do I have to do?
You have to come home with me.
To the secret village?
- Yes, son.
You must rediscover what
it is to be a panda.
You have to learn how to live like a panda.
Sleep like a panda.
Eat like a panda.
Those 103 dumplings?
Hmm... I was just warming up.
I've always felt like I wasn't
eating up to my full potential.
You can't take Po away from me. No, no
I want a second opinion.
Shifu, open another scroll or something.
I think he should go.
- Fine. A third opinion.
Monkey? Viper? Tigress? - Dad you
heard what Shifu said Oogway said.
This guy can only be stopped
by a master of chi.
And I can only master chi by knowing
who I really am.
Well, I'm a panda.
I'll pack your lunch for the road.
Do you really think Po can master chi
in time? - Doesn't matter what I think.
It only matters what the universe think.
- So, that's a No?
Master, what are we going to do?
- You are going to find out where Kai is.
Follow the trail of those jade creatures
but do not engage.
For with every foe he faces
Kai becomes stronger.
Why me? Is it because I asked.
- No, it is because you can fly.
Go.
- Should be kept your beak shut.
And take Mantis.
- What? Oh man, is it because I ...?
Yes.
Lunch break?
- You don't need to ask me twice.
Dad?
- Yes.
What are you doing here?
- What am I doing? Getting a backache.
Did you have to step on every rock?
No, I mean why are you here?
- What was I supposed to do, huh?
What if the pandas don't
have food you like?
You're never gonna be able to save
the world on an empty stomach.
I consider my presence mission critical.
Oh yes about that. We can't share
the location of the village with others.
So... - Well, you think I
can't keep a secret, huh?
I raised Po for twenty years before
I finally told him he was adopted.
Seriously?
- Yeah.
OK, I guess it would be cruel
to make you fly back.
You can fly?
- I'm a bird, Po.
We're here.
Sure looks like a long ways up there.
And my son hates stairs.
So let's go home.
We're pandas.
We don't do stairs.
I've waited my whole life
to hear those words.
Rats.
Whoa.
This is the secret panda village?
No wonder you keep it a secret.
If I lived here,
I wouldn't tell anyone either.
Now you can whoa.
- Whoa.
Li?
Everyone, Li is back.
They're both back.
- He found his son.
He made it.
- They're back.
Li?
- He found his son.
Everyone, Li is back.
Hang on, we're coming.
He made it.
Why are we running?
- Li shan is back.
Everyone, everyone gather around.
This is my son.
Triplets.
- Hi, I'm Ku Ku
I'm Meng Meng.
- I'm Shuai Shuai, he smells like cookies.
He's so handsome. Just like his father.
- Thank you.
Son, these are your cousins.
Dim and Sum.
I have cousins.
- Welcome.
Whoa, buns on a string.
- We call it a snacklace.
That's right.
We'll make you another one.
It's you.
Oh, that's nice to see you. Hi.
- I don't know who you are.
Oh, stripy baby. So beautiful.
OK, careful with that.
That's my action figure. Can I keep her?
No... problem. Of course,
yeah that's why I brought her.
Take good care of her.
Yes, stripy baby.
You look just like me
but a baby.
You're like me but old.
You're like me but fatter.
You're like me but...
with a hat.
You all look like me.
Let's feast in my son's honor.
What the...?
- Pandas don't walk. We roll.
How you ever seen anyone
look so ridiculous?
Po, what are you doing? Po?
You're right.
That is better than walking.
What kind of panda doesn't know
how to roll?
Well, I'm kinda new at this whole
being a panda thing.
And what kind of panda are you?
You have a funny neck.
I'm not a panda at all.
What's that?
- My hat, My beak, My wing, My dumplings.
No more questions.
Go away, kid.
Here, son, I packed your chopsticks.
- Thanks, dad.
What?
- What are those for?
These? These are chopsticks
They're for picking up dumplings.
You mean you only eat one at a time?
I knew I wasn't eating
up to my potential.
I am Mei Mei.
Wow, she's amazing.
She's so beautiful.
That's sweet, Po but
please try to save all
other compliments until
after the performance.
Me? No, I didn't say...
Shut it.
After the performance.
Has it started yet?
Best ribbon dancer in the world.
At least that's what she says.
- Look away, look away.
No, you can't. Can you?
Dad, why does she keep staring at
me like that? - Try to keep up.
I don't really know how to dance.
- Of course you do.
All pandas dance.
I know what you're thinking.
You do?
How can one panda be so beautiful?
For me?
Help me, dads.
- Yeah, no. You're on your own.
You're doing great, son.
Your turn.
Don't worry, you'll get the hang of it.
I have so much to learn.
Wings of surveillance.
Why do you do that?
- Do what?
Just because you say "Wings of..."
before something it doesn't mean
that you're doing a special move.
It's like me saying,
"Antenna of power" or...
" Thorax of making sandwiches".
Wings of disagreement.
- Whoa, there.
Master Bear, master Chicken, Master Croc,
what are you doing out here?
Jade creatures attacked our villages.
We've tracked them here. Stop.
They must be in there.
Master Shifu strongly advised us...
not to engage.
- Gotta get in there.
But master Shifu said...
- You're seriously afraid?
Even master Chicken's going in there
and he's a chicken.
That's it, I'm going in.
- Mantis, we have orders not to...
They need our help. Come on.
I'll go high, you go low.
No, wait.
Fear the bug.
Alright, you little...
Hold on, buddy. I'm coming.
- "Antenna of power".
Ah, it didn't work.
- Mantis.
Mantis?
Your chi is strong
just like your friend, the bug.
Mantis.
Don't worry, little birdie.
I'll put your chi to good use.
Destroying the Jade palace
and everyone in it.
No.
Wings of... regret.
Oh yeah, first day of panda training.
Alright flower, I'm gonna make you bloom.
Dad, dad.
What? What? What is it? - I'm ready
for my first day of panda training.
What?
You know, learn to be a panda,
master chi, save the world.
Pandas sleep till past noon.
So lesson number one is
go back to bed.
Of course.
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
Did I oversleep?
- You sure did.
Yes.
Yeah show him kids.
- Can you do this? Can you do that?
How about this? How about that?
Am I doing it? Is this good?
I got it.
Grandma panda, heads up.
- We better roll.
Po, lunchtime.
You gotta let the hill tell you
where to roll.
Rookie mistake. - Dim, Sum, let's
show him how we go uphill.
That's beautiful.
- Snack time.
Po, you can fly?
- I'm coming in hot.
Get them while they're cold.
What are you doing there?
That food is for Po.
Throw it in.
There, there, that's it.
Feeling relaxed?
- Yeah, really.
Just let yourself fall into it.
- Got it.
I'm fine. I just...
There we go.
Just let it all out.
That's my boy.
Get out of there.
My noodles. Leave my noodles alone.
Subtle, Po. Very subtle.
- Let me get some of that.
Leave my hat alone.
We love noodles.
- Oh, just like my Po.
What are you guys looking at?
That's how we roll.
Cannonball.
Yeah.
Mom, look it.
How was that?
Whoa.
Now you try again but don't try so hard.
- OK, OK.
Much better.
Thanks, dad.
- For what?
You know, just for you know,
showing me what it feels like...
to be a panda.
So when do you think I'll be ready?
Ready?
You know, learn how to master chi.
Soon, real soon.
Come on.
I wanna show you something else. C'mon.
Sorry about the mess,
I don't usually get visitors.
Is this my mom?
I had this done on your
one hundredth day.
Your mama couldn't hold you still.
You nearly eat the paper.
It's true.
- What was she like?
She was the total package.
Smart, beautiful.
Tremendous appetite.
She was the love of my life.
And then, just when I thought
I couldn't get any luckier.
Along you came, my little Lotus.
I really had it all.
Until that one moment...
When I...
lost everything.
Dad, you don't have to worry about
losing me ever again, OK?
Let me get some of that.
It's from the eastern province.
Master Lizard, master Ox, master Eagle,
all of them.
In every village from the sea to here.
Every master in china...
has vanished.
- Maybe they are all at a party?
Monkey.
- I didn't get invited either.
Kai has taken their chi.
We are all that stand between him and
the knowledge Oogway left
in our care.
The villagers, evacuated?
- Done, master.
Crane? Mantis?
- Still nothing.
Wait, it's them.
Kai.
Nice, very tacky.
How dare you set foot on these grounds.
Look at your pathetic fools.
Groveling at the feet of
Oogway the magnificent.
You are not fit to speak his name.
I am not fit, little kitten?
I fought by his side. I loved
him like a brother.
And he betrayed me.
Well now I will destroy
everything he has created.
Go.
How's that for a little kitten?
I will not let you destroy
Oogway's memory.
Why not?
He destroyed mine.
Mantis, it is me, your bestie.
Sorry Tigress.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Shifu.
- Bring them to me.
No, you must warn Po.
- Master please.
I will show you the true
power of chi, brother.
No.
Oogway, forgive me.
Hmm, what do you say Oogway?
Do you forgive him?
You may have destroyed the Jade palace
but you will never succeed.
There will always be someone to stop you.
Who? The panda?
His chi is strong but
it won't be enough.
He will meet the same fate as you.
- No.
And so will every panda in that village.
Yes.
Po, I hope you're ready.
Dance Lotus, dance.
He's so handsome.
Hi.
- That's a panda hug.
Hey.
Po.
Tigress?
Who's she?
Baby stripy baby.
- What are you doing here?
Kai attacked the valley.
He's taken every master in china
including Shifu and the others.
It's... it's all gone, Po.
Everything, everyone.
- Everyone?
Everyone.
- How's my restaurant?
We'll talk later.
- And now he's on his way here.
He's after you, Po.
He's after all pandas.
How long do we have?
- Not long.
Please tell me you've mastered chi.
- Here, take the baby. OK,
who belongs to this one?
You need to teach me
the secret chi technique now.
I'm afraid you need more time.
Everyone, go get your things.
Let me hand you that. - I don't have
more time. I need to learn it now.
Sorry, you're not ready.
OK, pack everything.
- I am ready.
Not quite.
- What are you talking about?
I've done everything you've asked.
I mastered napping,
sleeping in hammocks, hot tubs.
I am totally involved
with my panda parts.
Now why won't you show me?
- Because I don't know it.
You what?
I don't know it, OK?
No one does.
Maybe we used to but...
But not anymore.
- You lied?
No, I...
Yes.
- Why?
To save your life.
I find out some blade-swinging
maniac is coming for you.
What am I supposed to do?
Just let that happen?
- Yes, I'm the Dragon Warrior.
Facing maniacs, that's my job.
But because of you
I left the valley unprotected.
I left my friends unprotected.
And now they're all...
they're all...
And you would have been, too.
I lost you once.
I am not going to lose you again.
I can't.
You just did.
Mom, pick me.
Po, I'm so worried for you that I can't
even enjoy being right about everything.
Now run, run, run, as fast as
those chubby legs can go.
Run? There's nowhere to run.
- What are you going to do?
I'm gonna stay and
fight that monster.
Po, he may be a monster
but he's still your father.
Not him, Kai.
- No.
Hungry?
- No, I... Not really.
Well, maybe just one.
You know, you weren't the only one
who was lying.
I didn't really come along because
I was worried Po would go hungry.
I was worried about you.
- Worried that I'd go hungry?
No, I was worried you'd steal Po from me.
- I'd what?
I know. That was crazy.
But I realized having you in Po's life
doesn't mean less for me.
It means more for Po.
Well I'm not in his life.
Not any more.
- Your son got mad at you.
Welcome to parenthood.
- You don't understand
I lied to him.
He'll never forgive me.
I lied to him for twenty years.
He still thinks he came from an egg.
Sometimes we do the wrong things
for the right reasons.
Look, he's hurt.
He's confused
and he still has to save the world.
He needs the both his dads.
This isn't going to work.
- It has to.
You 're not thinking straight.
- I am.
You're not.
No Yes, I am.
I've seen Kai.
I've seen what he can do.
But he hasn't seen what
I can do.
The Wuxi finger hold?
- That's my best move.
I just have to get to Kai,
grab his finger, and then Skadoosh.
Back to the spirit realm.
He has an army of jade warriors.
Everything they see he sees
so there's no sneaking up on him.
You will never get close enough.
- It's gonna work.
He can only be stopped by a master of chi.
Oh, you sound just like Shifu with the chi.
Chi this. Chi that. Chi chi.
I'm not a master of chi. OK?
I don't know if I'm the Dragon Warrior.
I don't even know if I'm a panda.
I don't know who I am.
You're right. There's no way
I can stop him and his army.
Unless you had an army of your own.
You?
- Not just me.
Us.
- All of us.
I finally found my son
after all these years.
It's gonna take a lot more than
the end of the world to keep us apart.
But you don't even know kung fu.
- Then you will teach us.
What? I can't teach you kung fu.
I couldn't even teach Tigress.
And she already knows kung fu.
Po, I know I'm the last guy
you wanna trust right now.
But you gotta believe me.
We can do this.
We can learn kung fu.
We can be just like you.
What did you just say?
- We can do this?
No.
We can learn kung fu?
- After that.
We can be just like you?
Yes.
- We can?
No, you can't.
But you don't have to be.
That's what Shifu meant.
I don't have to turn you into me.
I have to turn you into you.
- That doesn't make any sense.
I know.
Thanks, dads.
- You're welcome?
I'm gonna do something I never thought
I'd be able to do.
I'm gonna teach kung fu.
You guys, your real strength comes
from being the best you you can be.
So who are you?
What are you good at?
What do you love?
What makes you you?
Yes, good.
Good, again.
Good, good, good, again.
Huh?
- Stripy baby, stripy baby.
Faster, faster.
Roll those ribbons.
Hug that log you, hug that log
like it's the last time
you're ever gonna hug it.
Goodbye forever.
Higher, and a little more to the
left this time. You can do it.
I don't wanna see any of these
hit the ground.
Wait, wait, stripy baby.
Good, try it with this.
Now try it with these.
Good, now try it with these.
They are ready.
What?
OK pay attention cause I might gonna
go over this ten more times.
The only entrance to the village is here.
The dumpling squadron
will take position here
while the cookie squadron
will take position here.
Now, on my signal,
the two squadrons will...
Alright OK.
The noodle squadron will...
anyway, the important thing to remember
is that this is the spot where...
OK, I saw that coming.
If you only remember one thing,
it's just distract the zombies until
I get close enough to put the.
Wuxi finger hold on Kai. Got it?
Pandas on three. One, two, three
panda, you guys...
Never mind.
I'll teach you that later.
I wish I could have thought
you this, son.
It's OK, dad. I'm...
He's here.
That's what I call a dramatic entrance.
Haha, you must be the Dragon Warrior.
And you must be Kai.
Beast of vengeance, maker of widows.
Yes, finally.
Thank you, almost makes me wanna spare
your life. - Oh, you wanna spare me?
How about you spare me the chitchat?
Let's do this.
I'm going to take your chi then the chi
of every panda in the...
Oh, chitchat.
- In the...
Chitty chitty chat chat chat chat chat
in the...
- Chitchat.
Oh, you pudgy little...
Round them all up.
Oh no, it's true.
You guys have all been turned green.
Except for you, Mantis,
you were already green.
Now?
- Wait for the signal.
Here we go.
Dumpling squad.
Ready?
- Go time.
Belly.
- Gong.
Seriously?
- We did it.
Sorry, Crane.
Spring roll squad
Time for some takeout.
Over here, Mr. zombie.
I don't know who you are either.
Noodle squad.
Get ready to dance with danger.
Sweet.
Stripy baby.
Do it.
- You're mean.
Fire.
Fire in the hole.
Yes.
All right kids.
You got it guys.
Oh no, master Shifu.
I can't hit Shifu.
I can.
- And so can I.
Double dad defense.
Left, dad.
- Right, dad.
Thanks dad.
Back at you then.
We've got this, son.
- Go, dads.
We got 'em now.
- Stop, stop, enough.
Let's finish this.
That's our boy.
Sorry, buddy. Gotta send you back to
the spirit realm. Skadoosh.
OK, that didn't work.
Let me try one more time. Skadoosh.
Skadoosh, skadoosh, skadoosh.
What the?
Hold on, wait. It's working.
No, no.
No, it's not. Did Oogway
teach you that little trick?
Too bad. It only works on mortals.
And I am a spirit warrior.
Come.
Son.
- Po.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
Run, run.
So Oogway, this was the one
destined to stop me?
I will have his chi
and then all of theirs.
And you...
You really thought you can
send me back to the spirit realm?
You are just a stupid mortal.
It only works on mortals.
You're right.
I can't send you there.
But I can take you there.
What's that?
What?
Po.
- Son.
Skadoosh.
Son.
No.
What happened?
Where is Po?
He took Kai away.
He saved us.
No.
He saved us
but who's saving him?
Whoa, the spirit realm.
It worked.
Get off me, you...
You brought me back?
Don't blame me. I tried to finish this
in the regular realm.
And we'll finish it here.
Come on, son.
Fight.
We have to help him.
Everyone gather around.
That's it. Come in close.
Come on.
We can do this.
Po, you taught us who
we were meant to be.
A father.
A friend.
- A dumpling kicker.
A lethal fighting machine.
- A huger.
A nunchuck chick.
Stripy baby.
A family.
Sweet.
Who are you?
- I've been asking the same question.
Am I the son of a panda?
The son of a goose?
A student?
A teacher?
Turns out, I'm all of them.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
Get it?
See the giant dragon?
Get ready to feel the thunder.
This is awesome.
Belly gong.
Butt slap.
Perhaps a bit of lunch
cause I'm starving.
Let's do this.
Heads up.
It took me five hundred years
to take Oogway's chi.
I will have yours if it takes me
five hundred more.
Chtity chitty chat chat, chitchat.
You want my chi so bad?
Then take it.
Yes, the power is mine.
Wait, no. It's too much.
That's too much. No.
No.
Where'd he go?
We're back.
- Bestie.
I'm still green. It didn't work.
Oh wait, that's my normal green.
Stripy baby.
- Not a baby, not a baby.
What about Po?
Have you seen Po?
- No, he's not here?
Po... Po.
Why isn't he back?
Dragon warrior.
- Oogway?
I can't believe it.
Whoa, you're extra shiny.
- As are you.
I know, right?
It's like the best cape ever.
When I run with it,
then it looks really cool.
It suits you.
You've grown.
Yeah, I gotta lay off the panda buffet.
- Grown up.
As I hoped you would when
I sent the message to your father.
You sent the universe mail? Whoa.
Yes because the universe needed you.
You finally became the panda
you were always meant to be.
But how'd you know I could?
- On the first day we met...
I saw the future of kung fu.
And the past.
I saw the panda
who could unite them both.
That is why I chose you, Po.
Both sides of the Yin and Yang.
And my true successor.
Me? I can't take that.
- Yes, take it.
I have a bigger one.
I mean, you're enlightening everything
I'm just...
Really?
- Yes.
Now what we do?
Hmm, you tell me.
- No Oogway, don't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I live here.
Oh right.
It's you who must decide
whether to stay or go.
Wait, I can go back?
- Who knows?
I've never tried.
Po.
- You can fly.
Dad, dad, dads.
- Son.
Don't you go disappearing
in petals ever again.
We thought we lost you.
No, you saved me.
You all did.
Now come on over here.
Hugs.
Master Shifu.
- The student has truly become the tea...
Wait, where did you get that?
Oh this. Oogway gave it to me
in the spirit realm.
Of course he did.
- I think I mastered chi.
Of course you did.
Can you teach me?
Ready.
Monkey, help me.
- Greeny baby.
Get off me.
Hello.
Skadoosh.
Panda asthma.