[female voice]
Long ago, in ancient China,
the Peacocks ruled
over Gongmen City.
They brought great joy
and prosperity to the city,
for they had
invented fireworks.
[pops, whistling]
But their son, Lord Shen,
saw darker power
in the fireworks.
What had brought
color and joy,
could also bring darkness
and destruction.
Shen's troubled parents
consulted a soothsayer.
She foretold that if Shen
continued down this dark path
he would be defeated by
a warrior of black and white.
The young lord
set out to change his fate.
But what he did next...
...only sealed it.
Shen returned to his parents,
full of pride.
But in their faces,
he saw only horror.
He was banished
from the city forever.
But Shen swore revenge.
Someday he would return,
and all of China
would bow at his feet.
[chains clanking]
[grunts]
It's almost done, Lord Shen,
but we've run out of metal.
Search the farthest villages!
Find more metal!
China will be mine.
And then the Dragon Warrior
joined the Furious Five!
And they became the most
awesomest kung fu team ever!
Enough talk. Let's fight!
- Yah!
- Hi-yah!
Listen, listen.
You can hear the Dragon Warrior
training right now!
- [Viper] 33.
- [Mantis] Stop him!
- It's too dangerous!
- [Tigress] 35.
- Stay focused!
- [Viper] 36, 37!
How is he doing that
with his face?
[strains]
[muffled] 38 bean buns!
Yes! New record!
You monster!
- Keep going! Hit 40!
- He'll never hit 40.
[muffled] You guys wait,
we'll get to 40!
Do it.
No problem!
Yeah!
Yeah!!
[grunts]
[muffled] Give me a minute.
- [laughing]
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- He did it!
Well done, Po!
- [laughter]
- Your training has paid off.
- [distant gong]
- Oh, Master Shifu!
- Gotta go. See you later!
- Ooh, yeah!
You'll save those for me, right?
[Po grunting]
[grunting]
[water dripping]
[exhaling, inhaling]
Inner peace.
[exhales]
- Inner peace.
- [approaching footsteps]
- [splashing]
- [Po grunting]
[Shifu groaning] Inner peace.
Master Shifu.
Master Shifu,
what do we got?
Pirates?
Vandals of Volcano Mountain?
Whatever it is, I will take them
down, 'cause I am in a mood.
I need to get something done,
you know what I mean?
Uh, what are you doing?
One of Master Oogway's
final teachings.
[gasps] Whoa!
[chuckles] Awesome!
How did you do that?
Inner peace.
Inner piece. That's cool.
Inner piece of what?
It is the next phase
of your training.
Every master
must find his path
to inner peace.
Some choose to meditate
for 50 years in a cave
just like this...
...without the slightest taste
of food or water.
[stomach grumbles]
Or?
Some find it through pain
and suffering as I did.
Po, the day you were chosen
as Dragon Warrior
was the worst day of my life.
By far.
Nothing else came close.
It was the worst,
most painful,
mind-destroying,
horrible moment...
- OK.
- ...I have ever experienced.
[shivers]
But once I realized the problem
was not you, but within me,
I found inner peace,
and was able to harness
the flow of the universe.
So that's it?
I just need inner peace?
My innards are already
super, super peaceful,
so all I need to do
is just get this thing going.
Inner peace,
you're going down.
Now show me what you were
doing there with your feet.
I saw you do sort of
a fancy foot...
Po! Bandits!
Approaching
the musicians' village.
Danger.
Tell those musicians
to start playing
some action music,
because it is on.
Don't worry, Shifu,
I'll master inner peace
as soon as I get back.
- No snack stops this time.
- [laughing]
Snack stops.
[blows raspberry]
Wait, are you serious?
[bell gongs]
[shouting]
- [yelling]
- [growling]
Get all the metal
you can find!
Grab the metal!
[shouting]
- [sobbing]
- Help, help, help, help!
[shrieks]
That's everything!
Let's get out of here.
OK.
- Oh, no.
- [grunts]
[high-pitched cry]
Wings of Justice!
[yelling]
[screaming]
Po!
Yee-hah!
- [all] Hah!
- Hmm?
Ha-ha!
- [cheering]
- The Dragon Warrior!
The panda?
That's impossible.
My fist hungers for justice.
[grumbling]
- That was my... fist.
- [groans]
Get 'em!
- Come on!
- Yeah!
[all] Ooh!
- [clanging]
- [all] Yay!
[groans]
[plays stringed instrument]
Take that!
[clattering]
Po! Incoming!
Thanks, Mantis!
[growling]
[groans]
[plays stringed instrument]
[yelps]
[growling]
[growling and snarling]
Tigress, Double Death Strike!
[Po] Ye-aargh!
- Feet of Fury!
- Aaargh!
[all cry out]
Tigress!
Monkey!
Viper! Mantis!
- Bunny! What?
- [continues playing]
Oh, sorry.
[howls]
(screams) Help!
- Crane, go!
- I'm on it!
Ahh!
Hoo!
Whoa!
[straining]
Is everyone OK?
- [cheering]
- Awesome!
I got this.
[crying]
Po!
Oof!
[all cry out]
Chew on that, tubby!
Ha-ha, ha-ha-ha!
[grunts and groans]
- Are you OK?
- What happened?
I think I saw...
I think... I gotta go.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming
to Dragon Warrior Noodles
and Tofu.
- More tea? Lemon sauce?
- No.
If you need anything, just ask.
- Thank you.
- Feet of Fury!
Ah, the Dragon Warrior's mop.
He mopped these very floors!
Uh, uh... No touching!
You'll get the mop dirty.
- He once waited on me.
- Awesome!
Yeah,
I have the stain to prove it.
Hey, where is
the Dragon Warrior?
He doesn't work here anymore.
He's busy out there
protecting the Valley.
- [gasps] The Dragon Warrior!
- There he is.
- Po!
- Wow!
Uh... Uh, here.
- [giggling]
- OK, OK.
You should have
told me you were coming.
Hi, Dad.
I would have saved you some
stinky tofu.
Uh... Uh...
- Dad, can I talk to you?
- Of course, son.
In honor of my son,
free tofu dessert for everybody!
- [cheering]
- With purchases.
[all groan]
Oh, it's so good
to see you, Po.
Have you lost weight? I can
almost put my wings around you.
Ah, well, maybe a little.
Poor you, you must feel weak.
- Let me get you some soup.
- No, that's OK, Dad.
- I'm not hungry.
- Not hungry?
Po, are you all right?
Yeah. No, I'm fine.
I just...
Earlier today,
I was fighting these bandits.
- Uh-huh.
- Nothing too dangerous.
- They were just, you know...
- Yeah.
And then the strangest thing
happened.
I had this crazy vision.
I think I saw my mom
and me... as a baby.
What? Huh?
Mom? A baby?
- Um, Dad?
- What are you talking about?
- What...?
- How do I say this?
[whimpers]
Where did I come from?
Well, you see, uh, son, baby
geese come from a little egg.
Don't ask me
where the egg comes from.
Dad, that's not what I meant.
I know it's not.
I think it's time I told you
something I should have told you
a long time ago.
OK.
You might have been kind of...
...a... a... a...
...adopted.
- I knew it.
- You knew?
- Well, who told you?
- No one. I mean, come on, Dad.
But if you knew, why didn't you
ever say anything?
Why didn't you say anything?
How did I get here, Dad?
Where did I come from?
Actually, you came from this.
It was just another day
at the restaurant.
Time to make the noodles.
I went out to the back
where my vegetables
had just been delivered.
There were cabbages,
turnips, radishes.
Only there were no radishes...
...just a very hungry
baby panda.
Whee!
There was no note.
Of course,
you could have eaten it.
I waited for someone to come
looking for you but no one did.
[Po gurgles]
[crying]
[gurgles]
[Ping] I brought you inside.
Fed you.
Gave you a bath.
And fed you again.
And again.
[playful whine]
And tried to
put some pants on you.
[sobs and whimpers]
And then I made a decision that
would change my life forever.
To make my soup
without radishes...
...and to raise you
as my own son.
Xiao Po, my little panda.
And from that moment on,
both my soup and my life
have been that much sweeter.
And, little Po,
that's the end of the story.
Ha! Look at me.
No, don't look at me.
That's it? That can't be it.
There's gotta be more, Dad!
Well, there was the time
you ate all my bamboo furniture.
It was imported, too.
One dumpling, please,
Dragon Warrior size.
[grunts]
Oh, Po, your story may not have
such a happy beginning,
but look how it turned out.
You got me. You got kung fu.
And you got noodles.
I know. I just have
so many questions.
Like, how did I ever fit
in this tiny basket?
Why didn't I like pants?
And who am I?
[grunting]
[male voice] Good.
Watch your form.
Good.
Better. Elbow.
Straighten it out!
[all grunting, shouting]
[all cry out in pain]
Shen?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Now we've got the
pleasantries out of the way,
please leave my house.
- Your house?
- Yes.
Didn't you see the peacock
on the front door?
Ah, there you are, Soothsayer.
It seems your fortune-telling
skills are not as good
as you thought.
- We shall see, Shen.
- No, you shall see, old goat.
- Where were we?
- What do you want, Shen?
What is rightfully mine.
Gongmen City!
Gongmen is under the stewardship
of the Masters' Council
and we will protect it.
Even from you.
[chuckles] I'm so glad
you feel that way.
Otherwise, I'd have dragged
that here for nothing.
What's in the box, Shen?
You want to see? It's a gift.
It's your parting gift.
In that it will part you.
Part of you here,
part of you there
and part of you way over there,
staining the wall!
You insolent fool!
[grunts]
Show-off.
That is a warning.
You are no match
for our kung fu.
I agree.
But this is.
[metallic snarl]
Are you familiar with
the Master of Gongmen City?
- Master Thundering Rhino?
- Yes.
- Son of Legendary Flying Rhino?
And Slayer of the Ten Thousand
Serpents in the Valley of Woe?
- He's dead.
- Whoa.
[Crane] That's impossible.
Rhino's Horn Defense
is impervious to any technique.
It was no technique.
Lord Shen has created a weapon.
One that breathes fire
and spits metal.
Unless he is stopped,
this could be
the end of kung fu.
- But I just got kung fu!
- And now you must save it.
Go! Destroy this weapon
and bring Lord Shen to justice!
OK, here we go!
Here we go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second.
How can I do this?
I mean,
how can kung fu
stop something
that stops kung fu?
Remember, Dragon Warrior,
anything is possible
when you have inner peace.
[cheering]
Inner peace. Inner peace.
Inner peace.
[exhales] Peace on.
- [Ping] Oh, Po?
- Peace!
Oh, Po, I got you
a travel pack.
I packed you food for weeks.
Cookies, buns, vegetables.
I even packed all your
action figures. See?
[guffaws]
Oh, uh... Hey,
I don't know what those are.
Never seen them before
in my life.
Dad, you got scratches
on my Tigress.
I also packed your paintings
of our best time together,
just in case you get lonely.
That's me and you
making noodles.
And that's me and you
eating noodles.
And that's me giving
you a piggyback ride.
Isn't that cute?
On second thought,
I'll hang on to this one.
Hey, uh...
they're waiting for me.
Of course, of course.
You have a job to do...
...far from home,
in a strange city,
filled with strange people,
and strange noodles,
facing horrible danger
from which you
might never return!
Don't go, Po.
I gotta go.
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
It's kind of my job
to save kung fu.
And if I don't...
what am I?
You're my son.
Right?
- [Tigress] Po, it's time.
- Um, goodbye.
Don't worry, Mr. Ping.
He'll be back
before you can say "noodles".
Noodles.
Come on, guys, let's go!
Yeah!
[panting and groaning]
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah...
[Po] Oh!
[Po grunting]
[Po howling]
[grunts] Ooh.
[exhales and strains]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Mama?
Mom? Dad?
Is that you?
Mom! Dad!
Oh, hi. Hey, son.
You're back.
Huh?
Honey, what are you
doing here?
But I thought...
We've replaced you, dear,
with this lovely radish.
Radish?
It's quiet, polite,
and frankly,
does better kung fu.
- [squeaks]
- No. No, no, no.
Wait! [grunting]
- [groans]
- [squeaks]
- Hi-yah!
- No!
[cries out]
Radish, radish, radish.
[growls] Yah!
Inner pea... [grunts]
Pea... [clears throat]
P...
Inner peace.
[dripping]
Aaah!
[yells]
[prolonged yell]
Inner peace! Inner peace!
Inner peace! Inner peace,
inner peace...!
[Tigress clears throat]
Oh. Uh, I'm, uh, training.
The mast is not
a worthy opponent.
- I am ready.
- OK.
So serious.
[impact echoes]
Ha-ha-ow!
- I think I prefer the mast.
- Apologies.
I used to punch the ironwood
trees by the palace to train.
Now I feel nothing.
That's severely cool.
Again!
Hah!
So, uh, this
punching ironwood trees,
how long did you
have to do that?
- Twenty years.
- Oh. Twenty...
Twenty years? [groans]
Is there any, uh,
you know, faster way?
You know, until you, uh,
you know... don't feel anything?
No.
- Besides...
- [shouts]
I don't think hard style
is your thing.
Oh.
Po, why are you
really out here?
I just found out that my dad...
isn't really my dad.
Your dad? The goose.
That must have been
quite a shock.
Yeah.
- And this bothers you?
- Are you kidding me?
We're warriors, right?
Nerves of steel.
Souls of platinum.
Like you.
So hardcore you
don't feel anything.
[chuckles] Yeargh!
Yo. Wow.
- I was...
- [Mantis] So, what are
you guys talking about?
Nothing. Nothing.
Po's having daddy issues.
I'm so lucky. I don't have
any problems with my dad.
Maybe it's because Mom ate
his head before I was born.
- I don't know.
- Mantis, this isn't about you.
Po is the one freaking out.
- I'm not freaking out.
- Po.
- I'm freaking in.
- Po!
- What?
- We're here.
Gongmen City.
[growls]
[Shen] My father's throne.
He used to let me play here
beside him,
promising someday
that this throne would be mine.
A little to the left.
Oh, but it's so heavy, master!
Thirty years I've waited
for this moment.
Everything must be exactly
how I envisioned it.
And I envisioned it
a little to the left.
- [gorillas grunt]
- Perfect!
With the weapon by my si...
A little bit more.
With the weapon
by my side,
all of China
will bow before me.
We move out in three days,
when the moon is full
and the tide is high.
[chuckles]
Now, you old goat,
why don't you tell me my...
Fortune?
F... Future.
I was going to say future.
Look into your bowl
and tell me what glory awaits.
If you continue on your
current path... [gasps]
...you will find yourself...
at the bottom of the stairs.
Oh.
I see...
I see pain.
- Ow!
- And anger.
How dare you?
That is the finest silk
in the province!
- Followed by denial.
- This is not fortune-telling.
- You're just saying
what's happening...
- Now?
- [sighs]
- The most important
time is now.
But if you really want
to see the future...
Oh, what do you see?
[Soothsayer] A peacock...
...is defeated by a warrior
of black and white.
Nothing has changed.
[Shen chuckles]
That's impossible,
and you know it.
It is not impossible,
and he knows it.
- Who?
- Lord Shen! I saw a panda!
- A panda?
- [grunts]
A kung fu warrior.
It fought like a demon!
Big and furry.
Soft and squishy. Ugh.
Kind of plush and cuddly.
There are no more pandas.
[Soothsayer] Even with his poor
eyesight, he can see the truth.
Why is it that you cannot?
Find this panda
and bring him to me!
Yes, sir!
One panda lives.
That does not make you right.
You're right.
Being right makes me right.
Then I will kill him
and make you wrong.
[crunch]
Will you stop that!
[Po grunts]
[Po scatting] Oh!
That must be Shen's palace
on the other side of the city.
Great. We'll march into
the tower and proclaim,
"We are the Dragon Warrior
and the Furious Five,
and we are here to
bring you to justice!"
[grunting]
What are you doing?
This place is
crawling with wolves.
[chatter]
Hey, isn't that the guy
who hammered you in the face?
Oh!
I do not like that guy.
We need to get to that tower
without being spotted
by those wolves.
Got it. Stealth mode.
- Ow!
- [clattering]
- [snickers]
- [chatter continues]
- [Wolf] Ah, get out of the way!
- [Po] Foiled again.
Hmm. Where did those noodles go?
Ooh.
Oh! [giggles]
[girlish voice] Hello.
I couldn't help but...
Yeah, OK.
Anyway, where was I?
- Where's Po?
- How can we lose
a guy that big?
Ooh. OK.
[screams]
[fireworks fizz and whistle]
Guys! Guys?
- Hey, Po.
- What? Sorry.
So that was stealth mode, huh?
To be honest,
not one of my stronger modes.
...gold in there, come on!
- [gasps]
- [Wolf] This rice is raw!
You stole all my metal pots
for Lord Shen!
- Either you cook my rice,
or I cook you!
- My apologies.
Po, do something.
How am I supposed to help her
cook rice without getting
caught?
- Wait, I have a better idea.
- [Wolf] ...two...
One.
- Hey.
[Wolf] Ooh! Aargh! [groans]
- Aaargh!
- [blows thud]
Ooh. Ah.
Yuck!
We're here to liberate the city
and bring Shen to justice.
- You will need help.
- Thank you, brave sheep,
but it's too dangerous.
I can't let you.
Oh, no, not me.
It's not safe to speak here.
Right.
Ooh.
[screams]
I'm talking about Masters Ox
and Croc.
They're in Gongmen Jail
on Black Dragon Alley.
What? They're still alive?
They must be in that jail
gathering intelligence,
hatching a plot
to use their awesomeness
to defeat the weapon!
OK, let's go!
Thanks, sheep.
Hey! Stop that costume!
- Hold it right there!
- Get them!
- Ooh, sorry!
Take... that!
- Keep going!
- Faster!
Hey!
[wolf soldiers cry out]
Ha-ha.
[shouting]
Surround him.
- [Wolf Leader] Now!
- [Others] Yeargh!
Gotcha!
Huh?
Huh? Where'd he go?
Spread out!
Search everywhere!
- [Wolf] What about over there?
- [Wolf Leader] Is there
a part of everywhere?
- I... I guess.
- Then search there!
They must be close.
I can feel a kung fu chill
riding up my spine.
Sorry, Po. It's just me.
Look. Gongmen Jail.
Aw, it's cute.
Cute, huh? [shouting]
- Yah!
- Pi-yah!
- Ohh!
- Nice work, Po.
At the first sign of trouble,
I'll give you a signal.
Ga-gah, gi-gee!
- You mean like Crane does?
- Yeah.
Excuse me, when have I
ever made that noise?
Master Ox! Master!
[gasps]
The ferocious Master Croc!
And Master Storming Ox.
[chuckles]
I can't believe we're rescuing
actual legends of kung fu.
We're gonna free you from those
bonds of injustice. No problem.
Gotta be a key around here.
No, they wouldn't
leave a key around here.
Yah!
Oh, good! You found it.
Come on, you guys! Yeah!
We're coming for you, Shen!
Wah-how!
Wah-hah-hoo-hoo!
Whoo...
Guys, are we going or not?
Do you want to
meet us there later?
You do want to take
back your city, right?
Of course we do.
But if we stand up to Shen,
he will turn the weapon
on the city.
Listen to yourself.
You're protecting Gongmen City
by not protecting Gongmen City?
- If we all fight together...
- Then the weapon would kill
everyone.
Oh, would it?
Then we use... a sneak attack!
- We get inside and then...
- And then you will be
stopped...
...by the unstoppable weapon.
Nothing's unstoppable
except for me
when I'm stopping you from
telling me something's
unstoppable!
Master Ox, I'm not letting you
stay in this cell.
I'd like to see you get me out!
Hah!
You guys see that?
It's called being awesome.
Come on! Whatever
happened to being heroes?
The only hero in this town
is a dead one!
Aaargh!
Like I said, you are not
getting me out of this cell!
[Master Ox] Oh...
Yes! Ha-ha! Whoo!
All right, let's go!
I get the top bunk.
It's time to surrender, panda.
Kung fu is dead.
I... Ooh...
[stammers] You, you...
Kung fu is dead? Fine!
You stay in your prison of fear
with bars made of hopelessness.
And all you get are three
square meals a day of shame!
With despair for dessert.
We'll take on Shen
and prove to all those
who are hungry for justice
and honor
that kung fu still lives!
Yeah!
[growling]
Monkey!
Ka-kaaa!
You! You're mine!
I'll tell you
what's gonna be yours!
My fist in your plush,
cuddly, super-soft face!
[both] Yah-ho!
Uh-oh.
Get him!
- Get me out of here!
- Yes, sir!
[Mantis] Stop him! Ya!
Faster!
Go, go!
- Lose him!
- Yes, sir!
- Viper!
- Hang on!
Oooh-waaah!
Whoo-hah!
[whimpering]
What?
Watch out!
Whoa! Waargh!
Uncool, very uncool!
Ah! Try this! [laughs]
Guys, guys, guys!
Ha-ha-ha!
Maybe something smaller!
No, no! Oh, no, no.
[bunnies laugh]
Ha, ha-ha, ha-ha, ha!
Cute bunnies off the face!
Excuse me! OK, pardon me!
Aaaargh!
[Bunnies] Fire! Fire!
We've lost them.
Ah!
[Bunnies] Whoa!
[Bunnies] Again, again!
Hah!
Crane, catch!
Wheee!
- Gotcha!
- Yay!
Whoa! Ow!
Ha-ha!
Guys, guys, guys,
give me a shove!
Mantis, now!
[Tigress] Heh-yah!
[howling]
[cries out]
Is that all you've got?
'Cause it feels like
I'm fighting a big,
old, fluffy cloud!
Well, this cloud is
about to bring the thunder!
- [clanging]
- Ooh! Ow! Ow!
- Your turn!
- Huh? Ah! Ooh!
Ha-ha-ha!
- Why are there...
so many signs?
- [clanging]
[howls]
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow, ow!
[both cry out]
Come here!
Alakasquasho!
Yes! Taste the defeat!
Let me tell you something.
Next time you mess with a panda,
you better bring a whole...
[snarling]
I guess nobody told you,
if you mess with the wolf,
you get the fangs.
- Ooh!
- I've hit you twice.
What are you going to do now?
We surrender!
Ha!
You can chain my body,
but you'll never chain my...
...warrior spirit.
Hey, don't forget
the little guy.
Did you just call...?
Po, what are you doing?
Trust me. I got a pl...
Aargh! Ow!
No way. Eight-point
acupressure cuffs?
Just like the ones
that held Tai Lung.
The more you move,
the tighter they get. [howls]
These are the best cuffs!
[grunts]
Greetings, panda.
At last we meet!
No, no.
No, no, no.
We meet at last!
Yes, that's it.
Greetings, panda.
We meet at... [gasps]
- You are afraid for a reason.
- I am not afraid.
He is coming to me in chains.
- If anyone should
be afraid, it's...
- You.
Don't even think about it.
I hope this turns out
better than your plan
to cook rice in your stomach,
by eating it raw
and then drinking boiling water.
This plan is
nothing like that plan.
- How?
- This one's going to work.
[chuckles]
Keep moving.
Ah, my old enemy.
Stairs.
[thudding steps]
- [thudding]
- [grunting]
[Po groans]
Thanks for carrying me
those last few flights. OK.
I threw up a little bit
on the third floor.
Someone might
want to clean that up.
Is there some sort of
evil janitor or something?
Greetings, panda.
- We meet at...
- Hey, how you doing?
Hey.
You've grown up
bigger than I thought.
Hey. Enough with
the poking around.
Strong, hmm? Healthy.
Look, I don't know who you are,
but please stand aside, sir.
- [whispers] That's a lady.
- Oh! Sorry.
The beard threw me.
It's kind of misleading.
- False advertising.
- Enough of this nonsense!
Bring the prisoners to me.
Sorry, ma'am.
Get ready, guys.
Keep your eyes peeled
for the... weapon!
Yeargh! Hah! Yah!
Sparrow kick! Wyy-yah!
We did it!
I just kung fu-ed it!
Did you guys see that?
I was all like...
Waaargh...!
Oh!
[Shen laughs]
Do you actually believe
this is the warrior
destined to defeat me?
I do not.
I know he is.
[laughs] Oh, look at him.
A lifetime to plot his revenge
and he comes to me on his knees.
What? A lifetime?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I did not have a lifetime.
We only heard about
Master Rhino a few days ago,
and we came
to avenge him!
You've come to avenge
nothing else?
Well, yeah. All the pots
and pans that you stole.
- I'm gonna want those back.
- Nothing else?
You probably did some other
evil stuff along the way,
I don't know.
- What else did you do?
- You don't know?
- Know what?
- [laughter]
What's so funny?
The very thing that
you clearly do not know!
OK, enough of these riddles!
Would you guys spill the beans?
First we come in and the weapon
is tiny. Surprise, it's big.
Then the lady over here,
I think it's a guy.
'Cause he's got... Whoa!
The only reason
you are still alive
is that I find your stupidity
mildly amusing.
Well, thank you. But I find your
evilness extremely annoying.
Who do you think you are, panda?
Who do you think I am, peacock?
[both laugh]
Why are we laughing?
[sighs]
Take aim.
Fire. [laughs]
Huh?
Well, light the thing!
I did!
Fear the bug!
Ha-ha!
[Po] Get the weapon!
Tigress!
[screams]
[continues screaming]
[cheering]
[crying]
You... you were there.
Yes. Yes, I was.
You just let Shen get away!
At least we destroyed
the weapon.
Fire!
Oh, no, he's got way more.
Aargh, aargh!
- My wing!
- Help, Po!
Coming! Aaargh!
- Watch out!
- Po!
Whoa. Wow!
- Help me up!
- No. Get him down.
Use the ropes.
Waaargh!
Run, run, little panda!
Whoa! [screams]
[screeches]
[panting]
Po, come on.
We need you to focus!
- I got it, I got it!
- Bring it down!
- We're trapped!
- This way!
[rumbling]
[laughing] Goodbye!
Yah!
Fire!
Get back!
Hah! Hah!
- The only way out is up.
- Aaargh!
[all] What? [screaming]
Yee-hah!
Whoo-hoo!
Follow me! Come on!
- Where are they going?
- To the top!
Come on! Keep going!
Here we go!
Whoa-aahh!
You idiot!
Ow! My nose!
Call in the wolves! All of them.
I want them ready to move!
The Year of the Peacock
begins now!
Right now?
'Cause it's the middle
of the year,
so you'd only get,
like, a half of the
Year of the Peacock.
And this is the Year,
of course, of the Peacock.
Happy New Year, sir.
Get the wolves ready.
We're loading the ships now.
Now!
Now, now, now, now!
Move! Move, move, move, move!
[howls]
[Tigress] This way.
- [howling]
- Let's go.
[grunting]
Oh, you! What did you do?
It's chaos up there.
What happened to stopping Shen?
Yeah.
Guys, come on.
Give me a little credit.
I meant for him to get away
because, uh...
...it was a trick.
It was a plot.
I was thinking...
I'll figure out his plot more.
That makes no sense.
- What do you mean?
Sure it does.
- Po, the truth.
- You had Shen. What happened?
- What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking
about. I... Yeah...
OK, he caught me off guard.
The truth.
Fine. They will keep you
far from danger.
- Real far.
- What?
You're staying here.
W... Wait!
I have to go ba...
You're staying here!
I'm going.
And you can't stop me.
Whoa!
OK. I wasn't ready that time.
Guys? Don't.
Ready.
Look!
[screams]
- Aaaah!
- [thudding]
Stay down.
- I have to get to him.
- Then tell me why!
He was there! OK?
The peacock was there
the last time I saw my parents.
He knows what happened.
Where I came from.
Who I am.
Look, I'm going.
I have to know.
- The hardcore can't understand.
- Tigress, no!
The hardcore do understand.
But I can't watch
my friend be killed.
- We're going.
- Maybe you can't
watch me be killed?
- Stop being a wimp.
- And she's back.
- No.
- Don't worry, kid.
You're better off here.
[Shen] You were wrong,
Soothsayer.
We sail to victory tonight.
Your magic panda
is clearly a fool.
Are you certain
it is the panda who is a fool?
You just destroyed
your ancestral home, Shen.
A trivial sacrifice
when all of China is my reward.
Then will you finally
be satisfied?
Will the subjugation
of the whole world
finally make you
feel better?
Mmm, it's a start.
I might also convert
the basement into a dungeon.
The cup you choose to fill
has no bottom.
It is time to stop
this madness.
Why on earth
would I do that?
So your parents
can rest in peace.
My parents hated me.
Do you understand?
They wronged me.
And... I will make it right.
They loved you.
They loved you so much
that having to send you
away killed them.
The dead exist in the past...
...and I must tend
to the future.
Set the Soothsayer free.
She's no use to me.
Goodbye, Shen.
I wish you happiness.
Happiness must be taken...
...and I will take mine.
Huh?
[Wolf Soldier] Hurry it up!
If all of those weapons
leave the building,
China will fall.
- We bring down the building!
- Hey, guys.
How about this?
Oh! This will work!
- All right, let's go.
- I can't feel my face.
[gasps]
Aargh!
[groaning]
[mumbling] Did you hear him
call it Year of the Peacock?
- [scoffs]
- Hey.
Hey.
OK. Keep it cool.
Keep it cool.
[Guard] You!
Where are you going?
On your feet!
And wipe those stupid grins
off your faces.
[wolf howling]
[Shen] Move, you dogs!
Faster, faster.
Load them all.
[Shen laughs]
Greetings, panda.
[gasps]
Tell me what happened
that night.
What night?
- That night.
- Ah, that night.
Yes. We're talking
about the same night, right?
Yes, I was there.
Yes. I watched
as your parents abandoned you.
It's a terrible thing.
I believe it went
something like this.
Waah!
Aaaah!
[grunts]
Here's your New Year's gift.
Hope you like it
'cause you can't return it.
- [chuckles]
- [Po] Aargh!
Po? What's he doing here?
Return it! Return it!
Yah! Hah!
[shrieks]
[chuckling] Are you willing
to die to find the truth?
You bet I am.
Although I'd prefer not to.
Yow!
Waargh!
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[Mantis] We got them. Go!
Wah!
Yah!
- [roars]
- [snarls]
[Tigress grunts]
Whoa! Oh!
[screaming]
[Po] You looking for me?
Um...
I said that too soon,
didn't I?
Kee-ya! Ahhh!
Po!
Po, get away from him.
I'll get up.
Here we go.
No more running, Shen.
So it seems.
Now... answers.
Oh, you want to know so badly.
[breathing heavily]
You think knowing
will heal you, huh?
Fill some crater
in your soul?
Well, here's your answer.
Your parents
didn't love you.
But here,
let me heal you!
[gasps]
[metallic snarl]
- Ah!
- No!
Oh!
[thunderclap]
[thuds]
[thunder rumbling]
[gasps] Ohh!
Yeah, like you could
make me drink that.
Aaahh! Aaah...
[groans]
If I wanted you dead,
I would have left you
in that river.
Well, why save me?
So you can fulfill
your destiny.
What are you talking about?
Where am I?
[Po] What is this place?
I'm surprised you
remember so little.
But you were so little
when it happened.
- [muffled uproar]
- Aah!
Perhaps you do remember.
What? It's just
a stupid nightmare.
Nightmare or memory?
[gurgling]
[laughter]
This was a thriving village.
Young Shen was in line
to rule Gongmen City.
But he wanted more.
I foretold that someone
would stand in his way.
A panda.
But I never could have foretold
what came next.
[baby crying]
[cries out]
[whimpers]
Get them all!
Take our son and run away.
Go!
[crying]
[gasps]
Stop fighting.
Let it flow.
[gasping]
[snarling]
[gurgles and mews]
[crying]
Shh. Shh!
Mmm-ma.
[gurgling]
[crying]
[snarling]
[wailing]
[sighs heavily]
Your story may not have
such a happy beginning
but that doesn't
make you who you are.
It is the rest of your story.
Who you choose to be.
So, who are you, panda?
I am Po.
And I'm gonna need a hat.
Such sad, sad faces.
But now is a time
only for joy.
You are going to be part
of something beautiful.
[growls]
Once we reach the harbor,
in front of all the world,
you and your precious
kung fu will die.
[laughs]
Then China will know
to bow before me.
Set sail!
- Aargh!
- [clang]
[laughter]
[all gasp]
What is that?
Honestly, guys,
I never thought
I'd die like this.
I always thought I'd meet
a nice girl and settle down
and then she'd eat my head.
- So sad.
- We cannot give up hope.
Po would want us
to remain strong.
Hardcore.
Right, Tigress?
Lord Shen,
what about the bridge?
Nothing stands in my way.
[Shen] Fire!
[shouts of panic]
You coward!
Po?
[all] Po!
Huh?
How many times
do I have to kill
the same stinking panda?
Shen!
A panda stands
between you and your...
[distant] ...destiny.
What?
Prepare yourself for a hot...
[distant] ...serving of justice.
Your reign of terror
comes to an end.
- What?
- And now, free the Five!
Disc of Destruction!
[Wolf Soldiers grunt]
[groans]
OK.
Take aim!
- Ready?
- Oh!
[grunts]
Ohh! Aargh! Ow!
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
[grunting]
This way and that way.
That way and this way.
You can't follow me.
Just get him!
[chuckles nervously]
Oh!
- Yeah, huh. Here we go.
- Come on!
[gasps]
Ya-ha!
- No, no, no, don't shoot!
- Don't shoot!
No, don't shoot!
- Don't shoot.
- Don't shoot!
I won't shoot
if you won't shoot.
Don't shoot!
Woo-woo! Hah!
Don't shoot! Crossfire!
Attack!
Hi-yah! Yah!
Catch of Freedom!
Monkey!
Impressive, Dragon Warrior.
What's your plan?
Step one: Free the Five.
What's step two?
Honestly, I didn't think
I'd make it this far.
- Po!
- Uh, stop Shen
before he gets to the harbor.
Woo-hoo! Nice.
Viper, Puppet of Death!
Tigress!
[Master Ox shouts]
Huh!
[gasps] Master Ox!
- Cham-pah!
- [Po] And Croc!
Vengeance is served.
- Why did you...?
- Your friend there
is very persuasive.
Hi-yah!
Yoo-ha! Wah!
Master Shifu!
Quickly. Use their boats
to block the way.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Crane!
Wings of Justice!
Ka-kaaa!
Woo-hoo-hoo! Yeah!
Yee-haw!
What?
[slow motion] I love you guys.
Why aren't we firing?
They're taking out our gunners,
sir. They're getting close.
Fire! Fire!
F-F-Fire at them!
But, sir, we'll kill our own.
I said, fire at them!
Fire!
No.
[groans]
Po!
[coughing]
Tigress?
[groans]
[laughs]
As you wish.
Let's finish this.
Fire!
[Po] Inner peace.
Inner peace. Inner peace.
Aaieee!
Ho, ho, ho!
Cha, cha, cha!
Again!
Whoa, whoa!
[gasps]
Yeah! [grunts]
Kill him! Somebody kill him!
Aah... oh!
Ha, ha!
Yai!
- [cheering]
- What?
[Shen] No!
Keep firing!
Aaahh!
Skadoosh!
[coughs]
How did you...?
How did you do it?
You know, you just
keep your elbows up
and keep the shoulders loose.
[Shen] Not that.
How did you find peace?
I took away your parents.
Everything.
I scarred you for life.
See, that's the thing, Shen.
Scars heal.
No, they don't.
Wounds heal.
Oh, yeah.
What do scars do?
- They fade, I guess.
- I don't care what scars do.
You should, Shen.
You gotta let go
of that stuff from the past
'cause it just doesn't matter.
The only thing that matters
is what you choose to be now.
You're right.
Then I choose... this!
Aargh!
Whoa!
Ohh! Aargh!
[gasps]
[cheering]
[sighs]
That was pretty hardcore.
- Po, come here! Yeah!
- Don't ever do that
again, please.
It seems you have
found inner peace.
And at such a young age.
Well, I had a
pretty good teacher.
Oh!
[fireworks pop and whistle]
[cheering]
[female voice] What do you mean,
he's not here?
It's my son's birthday.
All he wanted was
to meet the Dragon Warrior.
How about some tofu
birthday cake instead, huh?
You know, I think we'll just try
again another time.
When do you think
he'll be back?
I don't know.
OK, I don't know.
Maybe never.
I mean, I worry, OK?
But that's my job.
I'm his dad.
At least, I was his dad.
Why did he have
to go and save China?
I know why.
But why?
He's just one little panda.
[giggles]
Aaah!
So, how did it go?
Did you save China?
Yep.
Well, I knew you would.
That's why I had
new signs made.
"My son saved China.
You, too, can save.
Buy one dumpling,
get one free."
Hey, that's a pretty good deal.
- Would you like to try one?
- Maybe later.
[sighs]
There's something
I should tell you.
[gulps]
While I was gone,
I found the village
where I was born.
I found out how I ended up
in that radish basket.
You did?
I know who I am.
You do?
I'm your son.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too, son.
Ah. Delicious, fat radishes!
You're probably hungry.
Let me make you
something to eat.
What are you talking about?
I'll cook.
- No, no, I'll cook.
- Dad!
It's the least I can do.
You saved China.
No, it's the least I can do.
You raised me.
- Po.
- Dad.
- Po!
- OK.
Let's both cook.
- Together.
- Together?
No, I'll cook.
[both chuckle]
My son is alive!
[up-tempo music]