KUNGFU PANDA 3 (TELKAH CINE BETINYU) :D
Banda Aceh, 11 February 2016 with Google Translate
Subbed By Rizdar Wien Argum Gayo
I have two "justice saucers"?
Three. - And what tofu sandwiches.
The spicy noodle soup for Tiger. With extra sauce?
Apart.
- Apart.
You can do it.
Turn it on, Dragon Warrior. - Defend the valley.
Nobody does the dramatic pose, either?
Should we pose at each landing?
Never underestimate the power of a dramatic entrance.
I've heard some masters win a fight by throwing a door.
Dramatic entrance?
The Dragon Warrior is right.
Really? I was just ... Yeah, that's right.
At the stroke of the fist, comes the battle of the mind.
Therefore, the dramatic entrance.
What a great dramatic entrance.
What's the occasion? - Today is my last day of classes.
You last? I did not even know you were sick?
Although you looked pretty ... - I'm not sick.
healthy, one bit. Very well actually.
It's my last day of class, because as of now ...
you are trained by the Dragon Warrior.
What?
I teach? Why not Tiger? She tells everybody what to do.
Be still, Po. - See?
Tiger is not the Dragon Warrior. That's you.
These are the fiery five. What can I learn from them?
There is always something to learn. Even for a master.
For example, these sets.
The dramatic departure.
What is that?
Is this a joke?
Where did he go? - Master.
He is gone. It is well. - We are waiting for your instructions, Master.
You only have to lose our respect.
How bad can it be?
Let's swap. Monkey, 'Unwavering Mountain Shock.
I mean, Tiger, 'Tornado backflip. - Yes, Master.
Oh nee. Vuur.
Sorry. My mistake. Crane go up, I mean down.
My claw thingy. - Adder and Tiger as a "Totem Pole ...
technique. Julie two a swarm insect bites with a yellow jacket "...
spicy tuna ...
Well done, Po.
Have you learned anything? - Yes, you can not teach.
And Tiger is obviously flammable.
That was an absolute disaster.
Glad I do not have Po. - What a loser.
How do Shifu. - What about Oogway did.
I think he heard us. - No, it is not.
He said you're a loser.
I'm sorry, Oogway.
Want to do more? - How was your first day?
Humiliating. - I've heard it.
Whose? Tiger.
I've heard of Monkey, Crane, Mantis your father, and Mrs. Chow souvenir shop ...
and those ducks we saw before, and I heard it from Tiger.
She has also said that it does not happen anymore, because I quit.
Teaching, or humiliated?
Both of them. I do not know why you thought I could learn some class.
I knew you could not. - What?
Why did you fail me?
If you do only what you can do you will never be more than you are now.
I do not want anymore. I am happy with myself.
You do not even know who you are.
Of course it is. I am the Dragon Warrior.
What does that mean exactly? Dragon Warrior.
It means kicking and hitting.
And defend the valley.
Kicking and hitting?
Do you think Master Oogway it had in mind for you?
completed a five hundred year old prophecy, so you can spend your days ...
to fall on him? And high fivend can run through the village?
Oogway saw something in you. Against all knowledge.
More than you can see in yourself.
There awaits a stunning effect.
It surpasses your wildest imagination.
What was that? - That was Chi.
Wat is Chi?
The energy that flows through all living beings.
So when I teach, I can too?
No, if you are a teacher, I can do it.
It requires self-control to control Chi.
Oogway was 30 years in one cave. With the question...
'Who am I?'
I'm lucky if I get five minutes before you interrupt.
So I have now for 30 years alone in one cave?
Finally. After teaching controlled.
Teaching? I can never be like you.
I'm not trying to change me.
I'm trying to change yourself.
I change myself? Wait? Is that true ...
You're almost there, Shifu. Even more confusing and you will be the next Oogway.
Sorry, no offense, Master Oogway, it is ....
I'll let you go back to your eternal peace.
What is this place? - The farm of my brother.
If I were you, would you die?
And?
The mortal realm.
Did you hear that, Oogway? I am back again.
Kai is back.
Wie; - Kai. Generaal Kai.
The highest warlord China.
No. No idea. - The Jade Butcher. Master of pain.
You know me I think as' The Beast of Vengeance. "
The Widow Maker.
I once worked for Oogway.
Oh Oogway. A great warrior. - Yeah, we know ...
Enough. Silence.
Search Oogways students and bring them to me.
By the time I've destroyed them ...
none remains about which name you will remember.
Kai is coming.
I'm ready...
to teach you a lesson. - Learning?
No. It's the Dragon Master. - He is so handsome.
Thanks for the compliment.
Teach me do not die.
Hello, Dad. How is it going?
I just stopped by for a bath.
Good. What's wrong? - Nothing.
Nothing? I come home and you sit in the bath with your dolls.
Action Figures. - Instead of using bath salts ...
take peppercorns. - What?
My Gems.
There is indeed something wrong. - Tell your father just about everything.
Put your arm.
According Shifu I do not know what it means to be a Dragon Warrior.
And now I must teach.
I thought I knew who I was. If I'm not the Dragon Warrior, who am I?
A teacher who teaches kung fu?
That's a promotion. Take it to work.
If you take over the palace one day, then I sell my noodles in the lobby.
Why are you still in the bath as a baby? Out. Rise.
Company Expansion waiting. - And the Dragon Warrior look-alike contest?
Mrs. Chow who always wins.
En de Drakenkrijger dumplingwedstrijd?
I have to defend my title. - No one will break your dumpling record.
Someone is about to break your record.
Those who eat my dumplings? - And who pays for it?
101, 102 ...
103.
Is that a new record?
Who are you?
Ik ben Li Shang.
I'm looking for my son.
You lost your son? - Yes. Many years ago.
I lost my father. - Sorry.
Thanks.
I wish you the best. - You too.
I hope you will find your son.
And I hope you will find your father.
Son? You're right.
Do not stand there. Give your father a hug.
I can not believe you're here now.
I thought I had lost you forever. Little Lotus.
This is quite embarrassing, but you confuse me with one panda named Lotus. I am Po.
Of course. You can never ...
Little Lotus was the name that you got when you were born.
Really? - Really.
I can not believe you're here now. This is amazing.
Dad? Say hello to ...
I do not know what to call you. - He just said his name is Lee.
Come here you.
Thank you properly care for my son.
Your son? Wait. How do we know that this stranger or one akin?
Look. Our bellies are like brothers.
Let me teach belly dancing.
Like looking in a mirror dikmaak.
I can not believe we're in the picture.
I get it still does not. Po was still the only surviving panda?
No. There are many more. - True?
A hidden panda village in the mountains. - A hidden Panda ...
How did you know where I was? - Because the message I received.
How could you receive something if nobody could find?
That sounds suspicious.
It was a message from the universe.
Why are you a Dragon Warrior?
How did you know I was that? Through the universe?
No. The courier and the souvenir shop. I bought this little cup.
Of course.
You have no idea. I have so much to show you. You will be very proud.
I'm not terribly proud.
Yet to enter a few.
Do you have property asthma? Is this a family thing?
Dad, are you going to find this amazing.
It's the coolest place ever.
Hero Gallery.
All Kung Fu priceless artifacts from China.
This place is really ... - Great! Did you say that?
Because that's it. - Really.
Be careful. Everything is fragile here. Like the urn whispered Warriors.
Someone broke once.
Who? - A fool.
Master Rhinos armor. - Do you think it fits me?
Unbelievable. I also asked myself.
Whether it suits me? - No, if I can handle it.
Dad, you have to look.
Master Rams crossbow. The 'Infinite Gates Breaker.
Pap. Look. Helmets master Rats army. They are so small.
Master Dolfijns waterproof armor. It's my favorite.
Look, the legendary fighter rickshaw.
How cool.
What are you doing? We are allowed to touch anything. - Sorry. Will I recover?
Yes please. But it is you.
How does it feel? Itches? Smells of rhino?
Feels impenetrable? Can you give a thousand warriors?
And remain unscathed?
Yeah, it's pretty cool this.
Where was this for? I pull it on.
I think I just peed.
Anything else we can try?
Search.
Master...
Thumb War. - I got reinforcement.
It is so nice ...
Here we go. - Cool.
Calm down. - All is well with me.
Dolphin attack.
You've got me. - Dolphin attackers retreat.
Catch.
I was not ready yet.
I give him back. - I've got it. Higher.
I'll get you. - Come on, Master Rhino.
Here I come over.
I'll take you to graze.
Who do you graze?
Master Rhino. - What is it?
Boys. You'll never guess who just showed up.
Try it. - Your father.
How did you know? Of course. We look like each other.
Pap. Say goodbye to my friends. Mantis, Tigress, Monkey, Crane. Viper.
Viper right? - Monkey, sir.
They're my best friends.
This is Master Shifu. A legend.
It's an honor to meet you.
Maybe you want father to accompany us to the training room. Your son teaches.
He is tired. You are tired. He is tired. I bring him to the chrysanthemums suite.
Tired? I feel fine. It seems to me only to see teaching you.
It is better to see me fight.
What is that? - Our valley is attacked.
We are being attacked? - This is perfect.
Now you see what it's like to be the Dragon Warrior.
Follow me.
Enemies of justice. Get ready for war ...
Is this a joke?
Who are those green guys?
Jade Zombies.
Zombies?
Lotus. Be careful. - It is well. I do this every day.
I recognize these guys. Master Das twins.
The "Crashing double gong technique.
Yes that's them. And that guy is ...
Meester Stekelvarken.
he died a century ago?
These are legends.
Make a quick sketch of us.
Is it successful?
I blinked. we do another one?
I am strangled by Master Porcupine. This is really fat.
This is you. - Po, concentrate.
Notice of the universe? I will give you a message.
Stay away from my son.
Sorry, Dad. I'll clean it up later. - Not my good pan. Take this.
Lotus, pas op.
Dad, look at my calamity dumplings again.
Got it.
I see you.
Your Chi will soon be mine.
Is he talking to me. - Who? They all talk.
You're right. That's so scary.
Let's try. Maybe they find that scary.
First let's make a plan. Otherwise it's not scary. But stupid.
They do not talk. Idiots.
I'm talking. Kai.
Who? - Enough.
Did you see that?
Green smoke disappeared. Shifu what was that?
Kai;
No, never heard of.
Where is it? There is so much wisdom here that I can not find anything.
Behold.
All the answers are here.
What? Nothing?
Is this a joke? Not again.
Wait a second. Sorry. Good. Here we go.
It was written by Oogway.
I once had a brother. - Oogway had a brother?
Brother weapon.
He says a brother in arms. - Can you roll it all the way?
I was an ambitious young warrior. And led a large army.
Kai fought by my side.
My best friend.
One day we were attacked. I was badly injured.
My friend has carried me for days. Looking for help.
Until we saw a secret village. High in the mountains.
An ancient healing place spot.
A panda village.
Panda's? - Yeah, panda's.
Pandas used their chi to heal me.
They taught me to give Chi.
Kai wanted that power only for themselves.
He saw what you could give, it can be taken away too.
I had to stop him.
Our struggle has made the earth shake.
Until I left Kai banished to the spirit realm.
Should he return to the mortal realm ...
he can only be stopped by one full Chi Master.
A true Chi Master? Just like you.
I can barely make a flower bloom.
I need at least another 30 years, and a cave.
I can teach you.
You can do that? - Of course, I'm a panda.
That must be the reason why the universe sent you here.
What should I do?
You should come home with me.
To the secret village?
You must rediscover what it means to be a panda.
You have to learn to live like a panda. Sleep like a panda.
Eating like a panda.
The 103 dumplings that was just the beginning.
I found all that I ate too little.
Po You can not take away from me. I want a second opinion.
Shifu? Make another roll open.
I think he should go. - Fine. A third opinion?
Monkey? Viper? Tiger? - You heard Shifu and Oogway.
It can only be stopped by someone who has mastered Chi.
And I can only control Chi, if I know who I am now really.
I'm a panda.
I'll pack your lunch on the go.
Do you think Chi Po in time to control it? - It does not matter what I think.
But what about the universe. - Is that a no?
What do we do? - You're going to find out where Kai is.
Follow the trail of the Jade beings, but they do not fall to ...
as with any enemy he is facing, Kai becomes stronger.
Why me? Because I asked? - No, because you can fly.
Go ahead. - You should have said nothing.
And take Mantis. - What? Because I...
Lunch break. - You do not ask me twice.
Papa -? Ja.
What are you doing here? - What I do? getting back pain.
Did you really get up every stone?
No. Why are you here? - What could I do?
If the store does not have your favorite food?
You can not save the world on an empty stomach.
I consider my presence mission critical.
We may not share the location of the village with others.
So ... - You think I can not keep a secret?
Po I have for 20 years been brought up before I told him he was adopted.
Really? - Yes.
Well then. It would be cruel to let you back now fly.
You can fly? - I am a bird, Po.
We are here.
It seems extremely high.
My son hates stairs. Let's go home.
We are pandas. We do not kick in.
I am waiting my whole life for those words.
Is this the secret panda village? No wonder you can 't hide.
If I could live here, I would tell no one.
Now you may say WoW. - WoW.
Li is back.
They are back both. - He found his son.
They made it. - He found his son.
Moment. We komen.
He made it.
Why do we run?
He made it. - Li Shang's back.
come all standing around us. This is my son.
Triplets. - I'm Ku Ku.
And I Shuai Shuai. - My name is Meng Meng. He smells like cookies.
He is as handsome as his father. - Thanks.
These are your cousins. And Dim Sum.
I have nephews. - Welcome.
Bread on a chain. - We call it Snack Less.
We make another one.
It's you.
What good to see you. - I have no idea who you are.
Striped baby. So beautiful.
Careful. That is my action figure. - Can I keep her?
Problem. That's why I brought her. Take good care of her.
Striped baby.
She looks like me, but as a baby.
You look like me, but old. And you're also like me, but thicker.
Do you also like me, but ...
with a hat.
You all look like me.
Let's celebrate in honor of my son.
Pandas do not run, we roll.
Have you ever seen someone who looked so ridiculous?
What are you doing?
You're right. That's better than walking.
Which panda now do not know how he should roll?
I did not know that pandas did.
What pandas are you? You have a weird neck.
I'm not a panda. What is that?
My hat. My wings. My dumplings.
No more questions. Go away, kid.
I packed your chopsticks. Thanks, dad.
What? - What are those for?
Here you can eat dumplings with it.
Do you eat only one at a time?
I knew I was not much ate as I could.
I'm Mei Mei.
She is amazing. She is so beautiful.
That's sweet, Po. Keep all compliments until after the performance.
I? I said...
Mouth closed. After the performance.
It has already begun?
Best ribbon dancer in the world.
That says said. - Do not look.
You can not, do you?
Why she keeps staring at me? - Try to follow it.
I can not dance. - Of course it is.
Pandas can dance.
I know what you're thinking. How a panda can now be so beautiful.
For me?
Help me, Daddy's. - You're doing great, son.
Your turn.
It's gonna be fine.
I have so much to learn.
Wings monitoring.
How do you do that? You say wings ...
something. That does not mean it is something special.
I say, "antenna effect". Whether...
"Create brisket sandwiches.
Wings of disagreement.
Master Bear, Chicken Master, Master Crow, what are you doing here?
Green creatures have attacked our village. We followed them.
They are there to worry.
Master Shifu had advised us ...
not to engage in the struggle ... - We have to go into it.
Master Shifu said ... - Are you really scared now?
Even Master chicken goes into it. And he's a chicken.
I'm going in there. - Mantis, we have orders to ...
They need our help. I go by air, you over the ground.
No, wait. - Here comes the bug.
Well, you little ...
Hold on, buddy. I'm coming. - Aerial of power.
That worked. - Mantis.
Mantis?
Your Chi is strong. Like that of your friend, the beetle.
Mantis.
Do not worry, little bird. I'm going to use your good Chi.
To destroy the Jade Palace, and everyone who is in it.
No.
Wings up.
First day panda training. I'm going to bloom, flower.
What is it? - I'm ready for the panda training.
Learning to be a panda. Chi master. save the world.
Pandas sleep until after midnight.
Lesson number one. Go back to bed.
Of course.
No one said this would be easy.
I overslept? - Yes, definitely.
Show him, children. - Can you do this and do that?
Is this good?
I understood.
Panda, Vangen. - Ga maar ROLLEN.
Po lunchtime.
Let the hill tell you where you need to roll over.
Beginners error. - Dim Sum, lets see how we do it.
It's beautiful. - Snack Time.
Can you fly? - I am coming...
Pick them when they are cold.
What are you doing there? That food is for Po.
Do you feel relaxed? - Totally.
Let yourself fall into it. - Got it.
It's okay ...
Go ahead. Pour it out.
Well done, son.
Go out.
Let my noodles alone.
Very subtle, Po. - Give me some.
Let my ...
We love noodles. - Like my Po.
What are you looking at?
How we roll. Canyon ball.
How is that?
Try again. But do not mind your best.
Much better.
Thanks, dad. - What?
Just. Because you show me how it feels.
To be a panda.
If you think I'm ready? To become a Chi Master.
Very soon.
Come on. I want to show you something else.
Sorry about the mess. I do not often visit.
Is this my mummy?
I made this on your hundredth day.
Your mom could not keep you quiet.
You ate almost the paper.
It's true. - How was she?
She had it all.
Smart, beautiful.
A great appetite.
She was the love of my life.
And just when I thought I could not be happier ...
you came. My little Lotus.
I had it all really.
Until that one moment ...
when I...
all lost.
Dad, do not worry. You will never lose me again.
there Give me some of it.
This is from the eastern provinces.
That's the lizard.
Master Ox, Master Eagle. All.
In each village from the sea up here every Master in China ...
disappeared. - Maybe they're all at a party.
Monkey. - I'm not invited.
Kai has taken away their Chi.
We are the only ones still standing between him and the remaining knowledge ...
in our care.
Evacuur the villagers. - Done, Master.
Crane, Mantis. - Still nothing.
Wait, there they are.
Kai.
Beautiful, very awkward.
How dare you come here.
Look at you pathetic idiots sometimes.
Crawling at the feet of the great Oogway.
You are not worthy to speak his name.
I'm not worthy, little kitten?
I fought at his side, and loved him as a brother.
And he betrayed me.
Now I will destroy everything he has created.
Hurry up.
What do you say to a little kitten?
I will not let you destroy Oogways memory by you.
Why not? He who has destroyed me.
Mantis, it's me. You monkey.
Sorry, Tiger.
Shivu. - Bring them to me.
No, warn Po. - Master, please.
I'll show you the true power of Chi, brother.
No.
Oogway, forgive me.
Do you forgive him, Oogway?
You can then have destroyed the Jade Palace ...
but you'll never succeed.
There will always be someone who holds you back.
Who? Panda? He has a strong Chi, but ...
it will not be enough.
He will suffer the same fate as you.
And every panda in that village too.
He is so handsome.
A handsome panda hug.
Tiger?
Who is she?
Large Skazy Dazy. - What are you doing here?
Kai has attacked the valley. He took each master in China.
Shifu and others. It's all gone, Po.
Everything, everyone. - Everybody?
Everybody. - How's my restaurant?
We'll talk later. - Now he comes over here.
He's after you, Po. Behind all the pandas.
How long do we have? - Not long.
Please tell me that you are the Chi master.
Take the baby. Who belongs to this.
Teaching me the secret Chi technique. - No.
You need more time. Grab your stuff.
I have to learn it now. - Sorry, you're not ready yet.
Pack everything. - I'm ready for it.
Not quite. - I've done everything you asked.
I have a nap under the knee, sleep, hammocks, hot tubs.
I share one with my panda.
Why do you want me to learn? - I do not know it.
I do not know it.
Nobody can do it. Maybe used to be.
Not any more. - You lied?
No.
Yes. - Why?
To save your life. I find out that one with knife-wielding idiot ...
coming to get you. What should I do?
It just happen? - Yes, I am the Dragon Warrior.
Idiots to face is my job.
Because of you I have unprotected left the valley.
And my friends.
And now they're all ...
This had happened to you also.
I've already lost, that does not happen to me again.
I can not do that.
You've just done.
I'm so worried about you. I can not even enjoy my right.
Run as fast as you plump legs can carry you.
I can not go anywhere racing. - What are you going to do?
I'll stay and fight that monster. - He's otherwise still your father.
He did not, but Kai. - No.
Hungry? - Not really.
One then.
You lied alone.
I have not gone because I thought Po hunger would get.
I was worried about you. - I'd get hungry?
No, you would take away from me Po. - I would do what?
That was idiotic.
I now know that if you Po have in your life, I can not do less far.
It means more to Po.
I'm not in his life.
Not anymore. - Your son was mad at you.
Welcome to parenthood. - You do not understand.
I lied to him. He never forgive me.
I have long been lying to him for 20 years. He still thinks he came out of an egg.
Sometimes we do the wrong things for the right reasons.
Look, he is in pain.
He is confused, and should still save the world.
He needs both fathers.
This does not work. - It has to.
You're not thinking clearly. - Welwaar.
Nietus. - Welus.
I saw Kai, and seen what he can do.
But he has not seen what I can do.
You hold my finger? - That's my best grip.
I have to go to Kai, grab his finger and then back to the spirit realm.
He has an army Jade Warriors.
Everything they see, he sees too. You can not sneak up on him.
You'll never get close enough. - It'll work.
He can only be restrained by a Chi Master.
You sound just like Shifu. Chi this and Chi it.
I'm not a Chi Master. I'm not sure I'm a Dragon Warrior.
I do not even know if I'm a panda. I do not know who I am.
You're right. I can not stop him and his army.
Unless you yourself have an army.
Do you? - I'm not alone.
Us. - All of us.
I finally found my son. After all those years.
There is much more than the end of the world to pick us apart.
You do not know Kung Fu. - Then you learn us.
I can not teach you Kung Fu. I could not learn Kung Fu Tiger.
And they already know Kung Fu.
Po, I'm the last person you want to trust now.
But, believe me. We can do this.
We can learn Kung Fu. We can just as you are.
What did you just say? - We can do this.
We can learn Kung Fu. - Thereafter.
We can just as you are? - No, you can not.
But you do not.
That meant Shifu. I do not have to change in me ...
I have to turn you into yours. - That makes no sense.
I know that.
Thanks, Dad's. - You're welcome?
I'm going to do something I thought I could never do that.
I'm going to teach Kung Fu.
Your strength lies in getting the best from yourself up.
Who are you? What are you good at?
Where do you like? What makes you, you.
Yeah, fine. Again.
Good. Again.
Faster. Turning with ribbons.
Hug stump like it's the last time you smooch. Goodbye forever.
Higher and more to the left this time. You can do it.
They may not touch the ground.
Try it with this.
Well done. With this.
Good. Try it now with this.
They are ready.
What?
Note that I do this, but ten times over.
Here is the only entrance to the village.
The Dumpling Unit is here, and the Biscuits Unit is here.
When I say it, the two units will ...
Good. The Dumpling Unit will ...
Remember that this is the point that ...
Remember one thing ...
infer the Jombies until I'm so close I finger grip Wuxi ...
can do when Kai. Got it?
Pandas, on three.
Forget it. I teach you later.
I wish I had you learned this, son.
That's okay, Dad ...
He is here.
That's what I call a dramatic entrance.
You must be the Dragon Warrior.
And you must be Kai.
The Beast of Revenge. The Widow Maker.
Yes finally.
Thanks. I almost want to save your life. - Really?
Save me just chitchat. But come on.
I grab your Chi occasionally those of all other pandas.
Terrible chitchat.
In ... - chitchat.
You puffy, small ...
Make them all off.
It's true. You have all become green.
Except for you, Mantis. You were already green.
Now? - Wait for the sign.
Here we go.
Dumpling Unity, ready? Just go.
Belly.
Really? - You did it.
Sorry, Crane.
Spring rolls Unity, we'll take some.
Yesterday, Mr Jombie.
I do not know who you are.
Noodle Unit.
Get ready to dance with danger.
Beautiful.
Scar Daza.
Do it. - You're mean.
Fire.
Here it comes.
Well done, guys.
No, Master Shifu.
I can not hit Shifu.
I can do that. - And I.
Duplicate Dad defense.
Goed zo, papa. - Bedankt, papa.
We manage it, son. - Go for it, Dad's.
Now we have him. - Stop. Enough.
Let's finish this.
Well done, son.
Sorry, buddy. I must return you to the spirit realm.
That did not work. Just try.
Wait. It works.
No.
No, it does not work. Oogway has taught you that trick?
Pity. It only works with mortals.
And I'm a Ghost Warrior.
Come on.
Son. - Po.
I was wrong. Sorry. Racing.
It was therefore destined to stop me, Oogway?
I will tackle Chi, and that of all of them.
And you...
Do you really thought you could send me back to the spirit realm?
You're just a silly mortal.
It only works with mortals.
You're right. I can send you not go there.
But I can with it to increase. What is that?
Po. - Son.
Son.
No.
What happened? Where is Po?
He took Kai. He saved us.
No.
He saved us, but who saves him?
The spirit realm. It worked.
You've brought me back?
Do not blame me. I tried to end it in the real realm.
Then we end it here.
Come on, son. Fight.
We have to help him.
all come closer.
Come on. This we will succeed.
Po, you taught us what we needed to be.
A father.
A friend. - A dumpling chopper.
A little fighting machine. - A cuddly.
A nunchuckmeisje.
Striped baby.
A family.
Beautiful.
Who are you? - I have asked the same question.
I am the son of a panda?
The son of a goose? A student?
A teacher?
It turns out that I am all.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
Do you understand? See that big dragon?
Get ready to feel the thunder.
This is fantastic.
Buikstoot.
Kick ass.
Maybe have lunch. I'm starving.
We're going to do this.
Beware.
It took me 500 years to take away Oogways Chi.
I'll take yours too, if it takes me another 500 years.
Chitchat.
You want my love to Chi? Grab it.
Yes, the power is mine.
No, that's too much.
No.
Where is he?
We are back. - I'm still green. It did not work.
So I'm usually out too.
Green baby. - No baby.
En Po and?
Have you seen Po? - No. Is not he here?
Why is not he back?
Dragon warrior. - Oogway?
I can not believe it.
You shine all. - You too.
What a great cape. If I run it is completely fantastic.
He looks good. You have grown.
I must leave the panda buffet. - Become adult.
Just as I had hoped, when I sent the message to your father.
You sent the universe post?
Because the universe needed you.
You finally got the panda to which you were assigned.
But how did you know I could do that? - On the first day we met ...
I saw Kung Fu future.
And the past.
I saw the panda who could unite them both.
That is why I chose you, Po.
Kanten Beide van de Ying en Yang.
And my true successor.
I? I can not accept. - Yes, take it.
I have a bigger one.
You are enlightened and so. I'm just ...
Really? - Yes.
What are we going to do now?
You tell me. - No. Oogway. Do not go away.
I'm not going anywhere. I live here.
Right. - You must decide whether you stay or leave.
Can I go back? - Who knows.
I've never tried it.
Po. - You can really fly.
Daddies. - Son.
Disappearing never again. - We thought we'd lost you.
No, you saved me. You all.
Come here.
Hugs.
Master Shifu. - The student is really ...
Where did you get that? - From Oogway in the Spirit World.
Of course. - I think I've Chi master.
Of course.
Can you teach me?
Ready.
Monkey, help me. - Green baby.
Get him off me.
Hello.
Bohemian.
Panda asthma.
Thanks For Watching And Sorry for Bad Sub and Translating with Google :D