[panting]
Whoa.
[breathing heavily]
[out of breath]
Stairs...
I don't think I can... [grunts]
You guys, just start without me.
I'll... I'll catch up.
[wheezes]
[panting]
[grunts]
[chuckles, sighs]
Sweet.
Ah.
Inner peace. Inner peace.
Itchy nose.
[blows]
[sneezes]
Finally, inner peace.
Now, what?
[clangs]
Kai, old friend.
Master Oogway.
-Our battle ended 500 years ago!
-Well, now, I'm ready for a rematch.
Took you long enough.
[laughs]
[growls, grunts]
[yells]
[grunts]
You've grown stronger.
Five hundred years in the Spirit Realm,
you pick up a thing or two.
I have taken the chi
of every master here.
[gasps]
No.
Yes. And soon I will have your power, too.
When will you realize?
The more you take, the less you have.
[grunts]
[grunting]
With your chi, I will finally be able
to return to the mortal world.
And this time,
you won't be there to stop me.
[sighs]
It was never my destiny to stop you.
I have set another on that path.
Then I will find him
and take his chi, too.
[Hans Zimmer's "Hungry for Lunch" playing]
Hai!
Justice is about to be served!
[yells]
Whoo-hoo!
[growls]
Yee-haw!
[yells, laughs]
[whimpers]
[yells]
[grunts]
Ya-hoo!
We'll have two Justice Platters, please.
-Um... Three.
-Three.
-And a few tofu buns.
-Oh, the spicy noodle soup for Tigress.
-Did you want extra sauce with that?
-She wants it on the side.
-On the side.
[all cheering]
-Go, Dragon Warrior!
-Defend the Valley!
[crowd cheering]
-Go, Dragon Warrior!
-Yeah! Defend the Valley!
Yee-haw!
You guys aren't doing
the dramatic pose, are you?
Do we have to strike a pose
every time we land?
You guys, never underestimate
the power of a dramatic entrance.
I've heard about some masters who can
win a fight just by throwing open a door.
[shouts]
Oh!
Dramatic entrance?
-Master Shifu.
-The Dragon Warrior is correct.
Really? I was just making--
Uh, yeah. I mean, yeah, I am.
Before the battle of the fist
comes the battle of the mind.
Hence, the dramatic entrance.
Oh! Nice dramatic entrance.
-What's the occasion?
-Today will be my final class.
Your final-- Wait.
I didn't even know you were sick!
-Although you have been looking a little--
-I'm not sick!
...healthy, a little healthy.
A lot, actually.
[sighs]
My final class because, from now on,
your training will be in the hands
of the Dragon Warrior.
What?!
Me? Teach? I mean, why not Tigress?
She's always telling everyone what to do.
-Be quiet, Po.
-You see what I mean?
Tigress is not the Dragon Warrior.
You are.
Come on, they're the Five.
What could I teach them?
[scoffs] There is always something
more to learn, even for a master.
For instance,
let me show you another move.
The dramatic exit.
What's that?
Whoa! Are you kidding me?
That-- What--? Where'd he go?
-[all] Master.
-[chuckles]
He's gone, guys. It's cool.
-We await your instructions, Master.
-All you have to lose is our respect.
-[gulps]
-Seriously, how bad can it be?
Very bad! [groans]
Very, very bad!
Okay, okay. Let's switch it up.
Monkey! Immovable mountain stance!
Yes, Master.
[groans]
[sighs]
Tigress, tornado back flip!
Yes, Master.
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-Oh, no! Fire!
-Fire!
-[whimpers]
Sorry, my fault. Crane, go high.
I mean, low! Oh!
[laughs, groans]
Ah, my claw thingy!
Uh, Viper and Tigress,
do, like, a totem pole poison technique?
Uh, you two! Do a swarming insect bite
with a yellow tail,
yellow jacket, uh, spicy tuna...
-[crashes]
-I'm sorry.
[Tigress grunting]
Good job, Po.
Ah!
Did you at least learn a little something?
Yes. That you can't teach.
And Tigress is flammable, turns out.
[gasps]
[male goose]
That was a complete disaster.
[female goose]
Uh, I'm glad we're not Po right now.
-What a loser!
-What was Shifu thinking?
[male goose]
What was Oogway thinking? [laughing]
-[whispering] I think he heard us.
-I didn't hear anything.
Uh, he said you're a loser.
Sorry, Oogway.
[gasps]
Would you stop doing that?
-How was your first day teaching?
-Humiliating.
-I heard.
-Who told you? Did Tigress tell you?
I heard from Monkey and Crane
and Mantis and your dad
and Mrs. Chow from the gift shop
and those ducks you just passed and...
Tigress told me.
Yeah, well, did she also tell you that
it'll never happen again? 'Cause I'm done.
Teaching? Or being humiliated?
Both! I don't know why you ever thought
I could teach that class.
-Oh, I knew you couldn't.
-What? You set me up to fail? Why?
If you only do what you can do,
you will never be more than you are now.
I don't want to be more. I like who I am.
You don't even know who you are.
What are you--? Of course I do.
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
And what exactly does that mean,
Dragon Warrior?
Hmm.
It means, you know, just going around
and punching and kicking.
Defending the Valley and stuff.
Punching and kicking?
You think that is what
the great Master Oogway saw for you?
A 500-year prophecy fulfilled,
so you could spend your days
kicking butt
and running through town
high-fiving bunnies?
-Yes?
-No!
[sighs]
Oogway saw greatness in you, Po.
Against my better judgment.
More than you can see in yourself.
Incredible power awaits you.
Power beyond anything you can imagine.
-Whoa! What was that?
-That was chi.
Whoa! What's chi?
The energy that flows
through all living things.
So, you're saying, if I--
So, you're saying, if I teach,
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that?
No, I'm saying, if you teach,
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that.
-Oh.
-Mastering chi requires mastery of self.
Oogway sat alone in a cave for 30 years
asking one question.
"Who am I? Who am I?"
I'm lucky if I get five minutes
before you interrupt--
[groans] So, now, I have to sit alone
in a cave for 30 years?
Eventually. After you master teaching.
Teaching? There's no way
I'm ever gonna be like you.
I'm not trying to turn you into me.
I'm trying to turn you into you.
Turn me into me? Wait a second,
that makes no-- Almost there, Shifu!
Just a little more confusing
and you'll be the next Oogway!
Hmm. Oh! Ah. Sorry, no offense,
Master Oogway. I just...
I'll let you get back
to your eternal peace.
[rumbling]
[loud rumbling]
[Zimmer's "The Arrival of Kai" playing]
[grunts]
[snorting]
[both scream]
[both whimper]
-What is this place?
-Uh, my brother's farm?
Ah. If I stepped on you, would you die?
Yes?
The mortal realm.
You hear that, Oogway? I'm back.
Kai has returned!
-[both] Who?
-Kai, General Kai.
Supreme Warlord of all China.
-Huh?
-I don't know.
The Jade Slayer. Master of Pain.
You may know me
as the Beast of Vengeance.
Uh... Maker of Widows?
Eh?
Okay, I used to work with Oogway.
[both]
Oh, Master Oogway!
-He was a great warrior.
-We've heard of Master Oogway.
Okay, okay, enough. Silence!
[both scream]
Find Oogway's students
and bring them to me.
[both yelp]
By the time I am done with them, Oogway,
there will be no one left
who will even remember your name.
[laughs]
Kai is coming!
I am ready.
Wa-tai! To teach you a lesson!
"Teach me?
Oh, no, it's the Dragon Teacher!"
"Yeah, he's so handsome."
Thank you for the compliment.
Wa-tah!
"Oh, no! Please don't teach me to death!"
-[blows raspberry]
-Po?
Oh, hey, Dad. What's up?
I was just, uh...
stopping by for a little soak.
-Okay, what's wrong?
-Nothing.
Nothing? I come home to find you
taking a bath with your dolls.
Action figures.
And instead of adding bath salts
to the water,
you just added Szechuan peppercorns.
Szechuan--?
Oh, oh, oh! Oh, my tenders!
[groans]
[sighs]
Okay, yes, something's wrong.
There, there, son.
You tell your daddy all about it.
Lift your arm.
Shifu says I don't know what it means
to be the Dragon Warrior.
Now, I have to be a teacher?
I thought I finally knew who I was.
If I'm not the Dragon Warrior,
then who am I?
A teacher? Teaching kung fu?
[gasps]
Po, that's a promotion. Take the job, son!
And someday, when you're in charge
of the whole Jade Palace,
I can sell noodles in the lobby!
[exclaims]
Why are you still here
taking a bath like a baby?
Get out, get up. Go, go, go!
Franchise expansion awaits us!
But what about the Dragon Warrior
look-a-like contest?
Oh, Mrs. Chow always wins that.
Skadoosh.
And the Dragon Warrior
dumpling eating contest?
I have to defend my title!
No one's gonna beat
your dumpling-eating record.
Someone's about to beat
your dumpling-eating record!
[all]
Go! Go! Go!
-Who's eating my dumplings?
-And who's paying for them?
[all]
...100, 101, 102!
[all gasp]
[all cheering]
[muffled]
One hundred and three!
[laughs]
[mumbling]
Yay! Is that a new record?
Who are you?
-[mumbling] I'm Li Shan.
-What?
I'm Li Shan. I'm looking for my son.
[all gasp]
-[gasps]
-You lost your son?
-Yes. Many years ago.
I lost my father.
-I'm very sorry.
-Thank you.
Well, good luck to you.
You too. I hope you find your son.
And I hope you find your father.
[all groan]
-Son?
-[gasps]
Oh, my gosh, it is you!
[wheezes]
Well, don't just stand there!
Give your old man a hug.
-I can't believe you're alive.
-[all cheering]
Oh, I thought I lost you forever,
Little Lotus.
Uh... okay.
Uh, this is very embarrassing,
but I think you've got me confused
with a panda named Lotus?
My name is Po.
Oh, right, you wouldn't know--
Okay, see, Little Lotus was the name
you were given at birth.
-Really?
-Really! [laughs]
I can't believe it. After all these years.
And you're really here? This is amazing!
Oh, Dad! Come say hi to, um--
I don't know-- [chuckles] I don't know
what I'm supposed to call you.
-I'm pretty sure he said his name is Li.
-You. Come here!
-[honks]
-Ah...
Thank you. Thank you
for taking such good care of my son.
Your son? Now, hold on just a minute.
How do we know this... stranger
is even related to you?
-Look at that.
-[both laugh]
-Our bellies could be brothers!
-That is so cool.
Hey, son, let me teach you
how to belly gong.
-Boing!
-Belly gong!
-[Po] They jiggle the same!
-[Li laughs]
[Li]
Why, it's like looking in a fat mirror.
I can't believe
we're taking a picture together!
-[Li laughs]
-[Po] Huh?
But I still don't understand.
I thought Po was the only panda left.
-Oh, no, there's a whole bunch of us.
-Where?
[whispers]
A secret panda village in the mountains.
-A secret panda--
-Shh!
Whoa!
-But how did you know where I was?
-I received a message that led me here.
How could you receive a message
if no one could find you?
-Sounds suspicious to me.
-[all] Hmm...
-No, it was a message from the universe.
-[all] Whoa!
-Whoa!
-Rats.
[chuckles] Now, what's all this
about a Dragon Warrior?
How did you know
I was the Dragon Warrior?
[gasps]
Did the universe tell you that, too?
-[all gasp]
-No, the poster did.
And the gift shop. I bought a tiny cup.
Oh, right! Of course!
[chuckles]
[stammering] You have no idea.
There's so much to show you!
You're gonna be so awesomely proud!
Come on! Come on!
I'm already awesomely proud.
[both grunting]
-[Po] Couple more steps.
-[Li] Okay.
[Po]
Feeling the burn.
Do you have panda asthma, too?
Does that run in the family?
Dad, you're gonna love this.
It's like the coolest thing ever.
-This is the Hall of Heroes.
-[gasps]
Home of the most priceless
kung fu artifacts in all of China.
-Whoa! This place is--
-Awesome?
Were you gonna say--? You were gonna say
"awesome," right? 'Cause it totally is!
-Totally!
-But be super careful.
Everything is very fragile here.
Like the Urn of Whispering Warriors.
Someone broke that once.
-Who?
-Some idiot.
Wow!
This is Master Flying Rhino's
battle armor.
I wonder if I could fit in that.
Get out of my head, Dad.
I've wondered the same thing!
-If I could fit in it?
-If you could--? No, if I could fit.
-Oh.
-Dad, check it out!
Master Ram's crossbow,
the infamous Gate Smasher!
Dad, look at this! The battle helmets
of Master Rat's army! They're so tiny.
Master Dolphin's water proof armor!
This is my favorite.
Check it out. It's the legendary
battle rickshaw of Emperor Hawk!
-Sweet ride.
-[gasps]
Dad, what are you doing?
We're not supposed to touch anything!
-Oh, sorry, sorry! Should I put it back?
-Yeah, you probably should.
You look so cool though.
[laughs] How does it feel?
Do the hinges hinge?
Does it smell like rhino?
Does it feel like you're impenetrable?
Does it feel like you could take on
a thousand warriors and emerge unscathed?
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Ooh! I wonder what this does.
I should pull it.
[clinking]
I think I just peed a little.
Anything else we should try in here, son?
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Charge!
[laughs]
Faster, faster, faster!
Thumb war!
-Reinforcements!
-Ooh! Ooh!
No fair, no fair!
[laughs]
-[both laugh]
-Yeah!
-[groans]
-This is so much fu--
[clanging]
Whoo!
-[Li] Here we go! Go, go, go.
-Awesome.
[retching]
-There, there.
-I'm fine, I'm fine.
-[vomits]
-There you go.
Dolphin-style attack!
-Twing!
-You got me.
Dolphin-style retreat!
[imitates dolphin sounds]
Go long, son!
Whoa!
I wasn't ready!
[laughs]
-Coming back at ya!
-I got it!
-Going high!
-Yeah, come on, throw it!
-[laughs]
-I'm coming for you!
-Bring it on, Master Rhino!
-Here I come!
[laughing]
Oh.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Li] I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna get you, I'm gonna get you,
I'm gonna get you...
-Psst. Psst. Psst.
-I'm gonna get you.
Who's got you? Who's got you?
Who's gonna get you?
Yeah, who's gonna get you? [chuckles]
-[whistles]
-[laughs]
[blows raspberry]
Master Rhino!
What? What's wrong?
[clears throat]
[grunts]
-[crashes]
-[Whispering Warriors moan]
Hello.
Guys, guys! You're never gonna guess
who just showed up.
Not in a million years.
[stammering] You guys, you just try--
[all]
Your father!
Whoa! How did you just guess that?
Oh, wait a second.
Yeah, of course. We look exactly the same.
Dad, say hi to my friends.
Mantis, Tigress, Monkey, Crane, and Viper.
-Oh, Viper, was it?
-Monkey, sir.
They're kind of my best friends.
And this... this is Master Shifu. Legend.
Uh, it is an honor to meet you,
Master Panda.
Perhaps your father would care to join us
in the training hall?
-Your son will be teaching the class.
-[all groan]
-Oh, ho, ho!
-I'm sure he's tired.
I'm sure you're tired.
He's tired. I'm gonna show him
to the Chrysanthemum Suite.
What? Tired? No, I'm fine.
I would love to watch you teach.
-Trust me, it'll be more fun to watch me--
-[gong ringing]
Fight!
-What is that?
-The Valley's under attack!
-Son? Under attack?
-This is perfect!
Now, you can see what being
the Dragon Warrior is all about!
Follow me!
[all yelling]
[Po]
Enemies of justice! Prepare for war!
Are you kidding me? Whoa!
-[crashes]
-Ow!
[all grunting, yelling]
What's the deal with the green guys?
-[grunts] Some kind of jade zombies.
-Jade zombies?
[both]
Jombies! Jinx!
Ow!
-[gasps] Lotus, be careful!
-It's okay, Dad. I do this every day!
[groans]
Whoa! I recognize these guys!
The Master Badger Twins,
with their Crushing Double Gong technique!
-[gong chimes]
-Ow! Yeah! That's the one.
And that guy is-- [gasps]
No! Master Porcupine!
-I thought he died a hundred years ago.
-These guys are legend!
Get a quick sketch of us!
Did you get it? Did you get it?
Oh, I blinked!
Can we get another one?
[grunts]
[choking]
I'm being choked by Master Porcupine!
This is so cool.
-Oh, oh, look! It's you.
-Po, focus!
"Message from the universe."
I'll give you a message from the universe!
Stay away from my son! Ah!
-Sorry, Dad, I'll clean up later!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! Not my good pan!
Uh, take this one!
[grunting]
-Lotus! Watch out!
-[grunts]
Whoa!
-[screams]
-[grunts]
Dad, check out my Dumplings of Doom.
-[all grunt]
-Gotcha!
[Kai laughing]
I see you.
Your chi will soon be mine.
-Is he talking to me?
-Which one? They're all talking.
Whoa! You're right. That's so scary.
We should try that, too.
Maybe it'd would be scary back at them.
Okay, but we gotta plan
what we're gonna say first.
Otherwise, it won't be scary,
it'll just be stupid.
It's not them talking, you idiots!
It's me talking through them! Kai!
-Who?
-Okay, okay, okay. Enough.
-Did you see that?
-Whoa, what just happened?
This green smoke-- just poof.
And then, poof. Shifu, what was that?
Kai... Kai... Kai!
Nope, never heard of him.
[Shifu]
Kai... Kai... Where is it?
There's so much wisdom in here,
I can't find anything! Yes!
Behold.
All the answers will be found within.
What? It's blank?
Are you kidding me? Not again!
-[all groan]
-Wait, wait, hold on. Sorry.
Oh, okay. Here we go.
It is written in Oogway's hand.
"Long ago, I had a brother."
-Oogway had a brother?
-"In arms. In arms." Sorry.
-He says, "Brother in arms."
-Maybe you should unroll it all at once?
-"I was an ambitious young warrior..."
-[Oogway] ...leading a great army.
And fighting by my side was Kai,
my closest friend.
One day, we were ambushed.
I was badly wounded.
My friend carried me for days,
looking for help,
until we came to a secret village,
high in the mountains.
An ancient place of healing.
A village of pandas.
-[all gasp]
-Pandas?
[Oogway]
Yes, pandas!
Pandas who used
the power of chi to heal me.
They taught me how to give chi.
Oh, but Kai wanted the power
all to himself.
He saw that what could be given
could also be taken.
I had to stop him.
[growls]
[Kai yells]
Our battle shook the earth,
until, finally, I banished Kai
to the Spirit Realm.
Should he ever return to the mortal realm,
-he can only be stopped...
-[Shifu] "...by a true master of chi."
True master of chi?
-Like you!
-Me? I can barely make a flower bloom.
I'd need at least 30 more years
and a cave!
[Viper]
We need a chi master!
[Shifu] He will continue stealing the chi
of masters until he has consumed it all!
[Viper] We have to think of a way
to stop him.
[Crane] He'll get more and more powerful
with every master he defeats!
[Tigress]
There is no choice. We fight.
-I can teach you, son.
-[gasps]
-You can do this?
-Of course. I'm a panda.
That must be why
the universe sent you here!
Okay, so what do I have to do?
-You have to come home with me.
-What?
-To the secret village?
-Yes, son.
You must rediscover
what it is to be a panda.
You have to learn to live like a panda,
sleep like a panda, eat like a panda.
Those 103 dumplings? [scoffs]
I was just warming up.
I've always felt like I wasn't eating up
to my full potential.
No, you can't take Po away from me!
No, no, I want a second opinion.
-Shifu, open another scroll or something!
-I think he should go.
Fine, a third opinion.
Monkey? Viper? Tigress?
Dad, you heard what Shifu said
Oogway said.
This guy can only be stopped
by a master of chi,
and I can only master chi
by knowing who I really am.
Well, I'm a panda.
I'll pack your lunch for the road.
Do you really think
Po can master chi in time?
It doesn't matter what I think.
It only matters what the universe thinks.
So, that's a "no"?
-Master, what are we going to do?
-You are going to find out where Kai is.
Follow the trail of those jade creatures,
but do not engage,
for, with every foe he faces,
Kai becomes stronger.
-Why me? Is it because I asked?
-No, it is because you can fly. Go!
-Should've kept your beak shut. [laughs]
-[Shifu] And take Mantis.
-What? Oh, man! Is it because I--?
-Yes.
[sighs]
[panting]
[stomach rumbles]
-Oh, lunch break?
-Oh!
-You don't need to ask me twice.
-[Mr. Ping groans]
-Dad?
-Yes?
-What are you doing here?
-What am I doing? Getting a backache!
-Did you have to step on every rock?
-No, I mean, why are you here?
What was I supposed to do, huh?
What if the pandas
don't have food you like?
You're never gonna be able
to save the world on an empty stomach.
I consider my presence mission critical.
Oh, yes, about that, we can't share
the location of the village
with others, so...
Well, you think
I can't keep a secret, huh?
I raised Po for 20 years
before I finally told him he was adopted.
Seriously? Yeah?
Okay. I guess it would be cruel
to make you fly back.
[gasps]
You can fly?
I'm a bird, Po.
[both grunting]
-[chuckles, blows raspberry]
-[both grunting]
We're here.
Sure looks like a long ways up there.
[chuckles]
And my son hates stairs.
So, let's go home.
We're pandas. We don't do stairs.
I've waited my whole life
to hear those words.
[bell rings]
Rats.
Whoa-- Huh?
[Mr. Ping] This is the secret
panda village? [chuckles]
No wonder you keep it a secret.
If I lived here,
I wouldn't tell anyone either.
[Li chuckles]
-Now, you can "Whoa."
-Whoa!
-[cub 1] Let's go!
-[cub 2] Over here! Come on!
[cub 3]
Yeah!
[pandas chattering, indistinct]
[cubs laughing]
[all gasp]
[chuckles]
Oh.
[chuckling]
Li? Everyone, Li's back!
-They're both back!
-He found his son!
-He made it!
-They're back!
-Li?
-He found his son!
Everyone, Li's back!
Hang on, we're coming!
[grunts]
-He made it!
-[cub] Whoo-hoo! They made it.
Why are we running?
-Li Shan is back!
-[pandas chattering, indistinct]
[all panting]
[panda]
Whew!
Everyone! Everyone, gather around!
This is my son.
-Hello. Hi.
-He's here.
[chuckles]
Triplets!
-Hi, I'm Ku Ku!
-I'm Meng Meng!
-I'm Shui Shui.
-Your fur is soft.
He smells like cookies.
-He's so handsome, just like his father.
-Thank you!
Son, these are your cousins.
Dim and Sum.
[laughs]
I have cousins!
-Welcome!
-Whoa. Buns on a string.
-We call it a snacklace.
That's right!
-Uh... we'll make you another one.
-Oh! It's you!
-Oh, that's nice. Yeah. Hi.
-[bones cracking]
I don't know who you are.
Oh, Stripy Baby! So beautiful!
-[Lei Lei giggling]
-Oh, okay, careful with that.
That's my action fig--
-Can I keep her? Can I?
-No...
[sobs]
...problem. Of course.
Yeah, that's why I brought her.
-Take good care of her.
-Yes! Stripy Baby! [giggles]
You look just like me but a baby.
[giggles]
[gasps]
You're like me but old.
-You're like me but fatter!
-Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
-You're like me but...
-[laughs]
[whimpers]
With a hat!
-[laughter]
-He does wear a hat!
-You all look like me.
-[laughter]
Let's feast in my son's honor!
[all cheer]
-[Po] What the--?
-Pandas don't walk, we roll!
Have you ever seen anyone
look so ridiculous? [laughs]
[stammers]
Po, what are you doing? Po!
[grunts]
Ow!
You're right. That is better than walking.
[laughter]
[all]
Mmm!
-[panda 1] Yeah, that's good stuff.
-[panda 2] Have some dumplings.
What kind of panda
doesn't know how to roll?
Well, I'm kind of new
at this whole "being a panda" thing.
Hey, what kind of panda are you?
-You have a funny neck.
-I'm not a panda at all.
-What's that? What's that?
-My hat. My beak.
-My wing. My dumplings!
No more questions! Go away, kid!
Here, son, I packed your chopsticks!
-Thanks, Dad!
-[panda 1] Wow!
-[all] Whoa!
-[female panda] Oh, my!
What?
-What are those for?
-These? These are chopsticks.
-They're for picking up dumplings.
-You mean, you only eat one at a time?
-Mmm. Yum.
-Yeah, yummy.
[gasps]
I knew I wasn't eating up to my potential!
[gong ringing]
[all cheer]
Huh?
I... am Mei Mei.
[mimicking Po's voice]
"Wow, she's amazing. She's so beautiful."
[in normal voice]
That's sweet, Po.
But please try to save all other
compliments until after the performance.
-Me? No, I didn't say--
-Shh, shh, shh! Shut it!
-After the performance.
-Huh! Has it started yet?
Best ribbon dancer in the world!
[chuckles]
At least, that's what she said.
Look away! Look away!
No, you can't, can you?
Dad, why does she keep
staring at me like... that!
-Try to keep up.
-[gasps]
Uh, I don't really know how to dance.
Of course you do! All pandas dance!
-I know what you're thinking.
-You do?
-"How can one panda be so beautiful?"
-[chuckles]
Oh, for me? Oh!
Ooh, ooh, ooh! Oh...
-Help me, Dads!
-Yeah, no, you're on your own.
You're doing great, son!
Your turn!
[groans]
-[grunts]
-[all laugh]
-Huh?
-[all cheer]
Yay, Po!
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
Don't worry, you'll get the hang of it.
[laughs]
I have so much to learn.
[all cheering]
Wings of Surveillance!
-Why do you do that?
-Do what?
Just 'cause you say "Wings of"
before something,
it doesn't mean
that you're doing a special move.
It's like me saying "Antenna of Power"
or "Thorax of Making Sandwiches."
-Wings of Disagreement.
-Whoa! There!
[Crane] Master Bear! Master Chicken!
Master Croc! What are you doing out here?
[clucks]
Jade Creatures attacked our villages!
-[clucks] We've tracked them here.
-Stop!
They must be in there.
-Master Shifu strongly advised us...
-[roars]
-[yells]
-...not to engage.
-We've got to get in there.
-But Master Shifu said--
You're seriously afraid?
Even Master Chicken is going in there!
And he's a chicken!
-[clucks]
-[blades clink]
[clucks loudly]
[gasps]
That's it! I'm going in.
-Mantis! We have orders not to--
-They need our help. Come on!
-I'll go high, you go low.
-No, wait!
Fear the bug!
All right, you little... Uh-oh.
-Hold on, buddy, I'm coming!
-Antenna of Power! Ah, it didn't work!
Mantis!
Mantis?
[whispers]
[gasps]
[whistles]
[grunting]
-[snorts]
-[grunts]
Your chi is strong.
Just like your friend, the bug.
[gasps]
Mantis!
Whoa!
[breathing heavily]
Don't worry, little birdie.
I'll put your chi to good use...
destroying the Jade Palace
and everyone in it.
No!
-Wings of... Regret!
-[laughing]
Hm! Oh, yeah. First day of panda training.
All right, flower...
I'm gonna make you bloom.
Whoo-hoo!
-Dad, Dad!
-What? What? What is it?
I'm ready for my first day
of panda training!
-What?
-You know, learn to be a panda.
Master chi, save the world!
Pandas sleep till past noon.
[yawns] Lesson number one
is go back to bed!
Oh! Of course!
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
[snoring]
-[yawns] Did I oversleep?
-[laughs] You sure did!
Yes!
-Yeah! Show him, kids!
-Can you do this?
-Can you do that?
-Hey!
-How about this? How about that?
-Am I doing it? Is this good?
Whoa.
-I got it!
-[cubs cheer]
-Uh, Grandma Panda, heads up!
-Hello! Oh!
-Oh!
-We'd better roll.
Po, lunchtime!
[yelps]
[grunts]
-Po?
-[grunts]
You gotta let the hill
tell you where to roll.
[sighs]
Rookie mistake.
Dim, Sum, let's show him
how we go up hill.
[both shouting]
It's beautiful.
Snack time! Po!
-Whoo-hoo!
-You can fly?
-I'm coming in hot!
-[groans]
Get them while they're cold. Hmm.
[cubs laughing]
Ah! What are you doing there?
That food is for Po!
-[blows]
-Throw it in!
Ah!
-[bones cracking]
-There, there.
-[exhales]
-That's it.
-Feeling relaxed?
-Totally.
-Just let yourself fall into it.
-Got it.
[grunting]
-I'm fine, I just-- [retches]
-There we go. Just let it all out.
-[retches]
-That's my boy.
-Oh, oh, oh...
-[cubs laugh]
[Mr. Ping]
Get out of there!
-No!
-[cubs giggle]
Ah, my noodles!
Leave my noodles alone!
[grunting]
-Subtle, Po. Very subtle.
-Let me get some of that.
[bones cracking]
Hey, leave my hat alone!
[groans]
[all]
We love noodles! More noodles!
Just like my Po.
[screams]
[grunting]
-What are you guys looking at?
-[Po screams]
-That's how we roll! Cannonball!
-[all cheer]
[cheers]
Yeah!
[cubs laughing]
[female panda]
Here, bring it up here.
-Mom, lookit!
-Whoa!
[breathes deeply]
How was that?
Whoa!
Now, you try again,
but don't try so hard.
Okay, okay.
[breathes deeply]
Much better.
-[chuckles]
-[grunting]
[sighs]
-Thanks, Dad.
-For what?
You know, just for, you know,
showing me what it feels like.
To be a panda.
-So, when do you think I'll be ready?
-Ready?
-You know, to learn how to master chi.
-Soon. Real soon.
Come on, I want to show you
something else. Come on.
Sorry about the mess.
I don't usually get visitors.
Is this... my mom?
I had this done on your 100th day.
Hmm. Your momma couldn't hold you still.
-You nearly ate the paper.
-[both chuckle]
-It's true.
-What was she like?
[sighs]
She was the total package.
Smart, beautiful.
-Tremendous appetite.
-[chuckles]
She was the love of my life.
And then, just when I thought
I couldn't get any luckier,
along you came, my Little Lotus.
[chuckles]
I really had it all.
Until that... one moment...
when I lost everything.
[wolf howling]
[babbles]
[crying]
[wolves growling]
Dad...
You don't have to worry
about losing me ever again. Okay?
Let me get some of that!
[laughs]
[bones cracking]
It's from the Eastern Province!
Master Lizard, Master Ox,
Master Eagle. All of them.
In every village from the sea to here,
every master in China has vanished.
-Maybe they are all at the party?
-Monkey!
-I didn't get invited either.
-Kai has taken their chi.
We are all that stand between him
and the knowledge Oogway left in our care.
-The villagers, evacuated?
-Done, Master.
-[Shifu] Crane, Mantis?
-[Tigress] Still nothing.
[gasps]
Wait! It's them!
No!
[Tigress growls]
Kai...
Nice. Very tacky.
How dare you set foot on these grounds!
Look at you pathetic fools.
Groveling at the feet
of Oogway the Magnificent.
You are not fit to speak his name.
I am not fit, little kitten?
[Tigress growls]
I fought by his side.
I loved him like a brother.
And he betrayed me.
Well...
Now, I will destroy
everything he has created!
Go!
[yells]
[all grunting]
Huh?
[groans]
-How's that for a little kitten?
-[snorts]
[yells]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Yah!
[grunts] I will not let you destroy
Oogway's memory!
Why not? He destroyed mine.
Mantis! It is me, your bestie!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Sorry, Tigress! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
[grunts]
Sorry!
[grunting]
-Shifu!
-Bring them to me!
[screams]
[laughing]
-No! You must warn, Po.
-Master, please!
[groans]
I will show you
the true power of chi, brother.
-[grunts]
-No!
[panting]
-Oogway, forgive me.
-[laughs]
Hmm. What do you say, Oogway?
Do you forgive him?
You may have destroyed the Jade Palace,
but you will never succeed.
There will always be someone to stop you.
Who, the panda?
His chi is strong, but it won't be enough.
He will meet the same fate as you.
-No...
-And so will every panda in that village.
[pants]
Yes.
[sighs]
Po, I hope you're ready.
-[festive music playing]
-[pandas chattering, indistinct]
-Dance, Lotus, dance!
-[laughs]
-He's so handsome!
-[chuckles]
-Hi!
-Now, that's a panda hug.
-Hey!
-[chuckles]
Oh! Oh! Oh! [giggles] Po.
[pandas chatter, indistinct]
[breathes deeply]
[gasps]
Tigress?
-Who is she?
-[female panda] Who is that?
-[gasps] Big Stripy Baby!
-Hmm.
-What are you doing here?
-Kai attacked the Valley.
He's taken every master in China,
including Shifu and the others.
It's... It's all gone, Po.
Everything. Everyone.
-Everyone?
-Everyone.
How's my restaurant?
We'll talk later.
And, now, he's on his way here.
He's after you, Po.
-He's after all pandas.
-[pandas gasp]
-How long do we have?
-Not long.
Please tell me you've mastered chi.
-[Li] Here, take the baby.
-Dad! Dad!
Okay, who belongs to this one?
You need to teach me
the secret chi technique now.
No, no. I'm afraid you need more time.
Everyone, go get your things!
Let me hand you that--
I don't have more time.
I need to learn it now.
Sorry. You're not ready.
Pack everything!
-I am ready.
-Not quite.
What are you talking about?
I've done everything you've asked.
I've mastered napping, sleeping in,
hammocks, hot tubs.
I am totally at one with my panda parts.
Why won't you show me?
Because I don't know it!
-You what?
-I don't know it, okay?
No one does! Maybe we used to,
but... but not anymore.
-You lied?
-No, I...
[sighs]
Yes.
-Wh... Why?
-To save your life.
I find out some blade-swinging maniac
is coming for you.
What am I supposed to do?
Just-Just let that happen?
Yes! I'm the Dragon Warrior.
Facing maniacs-- that's my job.
But, because of you,
I left the Valley unprotected.
I left my friends unprotected.
And, now, they're all... they're all...
And you would have been, too!
I lost you once.
I am not going to lose you again.
I can't.
You just did.
[panda cubs crying]
Mom! Pick me!
-Oh.
Po, I'm so worried for you
that I can't even enjoy
being right about everything.
Now, run, run, run as fast
as those chubby legs can go!
-Run? There's nowhere to run.
-What are you going to do?
I'm gonna stay and fight that monster.
Po, he may be a monster,
but he's still your father.
-Not him. Kai!
-[gasps] No!
[grunts]
[snorting]
[grunting]
-Hungry?
-No, I... Not really.
Well, maybe just one.
You know, you weren't the only one
who was lying.
Oh?
I didn't really come along
because I was worried Po would go hungry.
[chuckles]
I was worried about you.
-Worried that I'd go hungry?
-No.
I was worried you'd steal Po from me.
-I'd what?
-I know. That was crazy. [chuckles]
But I realize having you in Po's life
doesn't mean less for me.
It means more for Po.
Oh. Well...
I'm not in his life, not anymore.
[scoffs] Your son got mad at you.
Welcome to parenthood.
It-- You don't understand.
I lied to him. He'll never forgive me.
I lied to him for 20 years.
He still thinks he came from an egg.
Sometimes, we do the wrong things
for the right reasons.
Look... he's hurt. He's confused.
And he still has to save the world.
He needs both his dads.
[grunting]
[panting]
-[yells]
-[grunts]
-This isn't going to work.
-It has to.
-You're not thinking straight.
-I am!
-You're not.
-No. No.
-Yes, I am!
-[grunts]
-I've seen Kai.
-I've seen what he can do.
-But he hasn't seen what I can do.
The Wuxi Finger Hold?
It's my best move.
I just have to get to Kai,
grab his finger, and then skadoosh!
Back to the Spirit Realm.
[groans]
-He has an army of jade warriors.
-Ooh!
Everything they see, he sees,
so there's no sneaking up on him.
-You will never get close enough.
-It's gonna work!
He can only be stopped
by a master of chi.
Oh, you sound just like Shifu,
with the, "Chi chi chi!
"Chi this! Chi that! Chi chi chi chi chi!"
I'm not a master of chi, okay?
I don't know if I'm the Dragon Warrior.
I don't even know if I'm a panda.
I don't know who I am! [sighs]
You're right. There's no way
I can stop him and his army.
[sighs]
[Li]
Unless you had an army of your own.
-You?
-Not just me.
-Us.
-All of us.
I finally found my son
after all these years.
It's gonna take a lot more than the end
of the world to keep us apart.
-But you don't even know kung fu.
-Then you will teach us.
What? I can't teach you kung fu.
I couldn't even teach Tigress.
And she already knows kung fu!
Po, I know I'm the last guy
you want to trust right now.
But you gotta believe me,
we can do this.
We can learn kung fu.
We can be just like you!
-What did you just say?
-Uh... "We can do this"?
-No!
-"We can learn kung fu"?
-After that!
-Uh... "We can be just like you"?
-Yes!
-We can?
No! You can't!
[laughs]
But you don't have to be.
That's what Shifu meant.
I don't have to turn you into me.
I have to turn you into you!
That doesn't make any sense.
I know! Thanks, Dads.
[both]
You're welcome?
I'm gonna do something
I never thought I'd be able to do.
I'm gonna teach kung fu.
You guys, your real strength comes
from being the best you, you can be.
So, who are you?
What are you good at?
What do you love?
-What makes you, you?
-[yells]
-[all grunting]
-Yes. Good, good. Again!
Good. Again!
Good, good, good. Again!
-Huh?
-Stripy Baby! Stripy Baby!
Faster, faster! Twirl those ribbons!
Hug that log, you!
Hug that log like it's the last time
you're ever gonna hug it good-bye forever.
Higher! And a little more to the left
this time. You can do it!
-Whoo-hoo!
-[both] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I don't want to see any of these
hit the ground!
[yells]
[all grunting]
Wait, wait! Stripy Baby.
[grunts]
-Good! Try it with this!
-[chuckles]
-[cubs grunting]
-[Po whistles]
Now, try it with these!
Good! Now, try it with these!
-Oh. Oh!
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[chuckles]
[groans]
[grunting]
-[both] Whoo!
-[both grunt]
They are ready.
-[Lei babbling]
-What?
Okay, pay attention, 'cause I'm only
gonna go over this ten more times.
The only entrance to the village is here.
The dumpling squadron
will take position here,
while the cookie squadron
will take position here.
Now, on my signal,
the two squadrons will...
-Right, okay.
-[all laugh]
-The noodle squadron will...
-[slurps]
-[all laugh]
-All right. Okay, anyway,
the important thing to remember
is that this is the spot where-- [gasps]
-Okay, I saw that coming.
-[all laugh]
If you only remember one thing,
it's distract the jombies
until I get close enough
to put a Wuxi Finger Hold on Kai.
-Got it?
-[all] Yeah!
Pandas on three!
One, two, three, pan--
You guys, never mind.
I'll teach you that later.
I... I wish I could have
taught you this, son.
-It's okay, Dad. I'm--
-[clinking]
[all gasp]
He's here.
[snorting]
[grunts]
[yells]
Wow! That's what I call
a dramatic entrance!
Ha-ha! You must be the Dragon Warrior.
And you must be Kai!
Beast of Vengeance, Maker of Widows.
Yes! Finally! Thank you!
-Almost makes me want to spare your life.
-Oh, you want to spare me?
How about you spare me the chitchat?
All right? Let's do this.
I'm going to take your chi,
then the chi of every panda in the--
-Oh, chitchat!
-In th--
-Chitty-chitty chat-chat. Chat-chat-chat.
-In the--
-Chitchat.
Ah, you pudgy little...
[growls]
Round them all up.
[gasps] Oh, no, it's true.
You guys have all been turned green!
Except for you, Mantis.
You were already green.
-Now?
-Wait for the signal.
-[yells]
-Here we go!
[snorts]
Dumpling Squad!
-Ready?
-Go time!
-Belly!
-Gong!
[both]
Whoo!
Seriously?
We did it! Whoo-hoo!
-Yeah!
-Sorry, Crane!
[clucks]
[snorts]
-[grunts]
-[yelps]
Spring Roll Squad!
Time for some take out!
[all grunt]
[clucks]
[all cheer]
Yoo-hoo! Over here, Mr. Jombie!
[laughs] Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know who you are, either.
Noodle Squad!
Get ready to dance... with danger!
[yells]
Oh, sweet!
[groans]
-Hey, Stripy Baby!
-[gasps] Oh!
-Wee!
-[grunts]
[Lei Lei giggling]
-Do it.
-You're mean!
-Hi-ya!
-[Lei Lei giggles]
Oh.
[cub]
Fire!
[all yelling]
[groans]
Fire in the hole!
-Oh!
-Yes!
All right, kids!
You've got it, guys!
[clucks]
Oh, no! Master Shifu!
I can't hit Shifu!
-I can!
-And so can I!
[both]
Double Dad Defense!
-Left Dad!
-Right Dad!
-Thanks, Dad!
-Back at ya, Dad!
We've got this, son!
[laughs]
Go, Dads!
[Li]
Yeah!
Yeah! [laughs]
We got him now.
[groans]
Stop! Stop! Enough! Enough!
-[laughs]
-[gasps]
Let's finish this.
[both]
That's our boy!
[grunts]
Sorry, buddy. Gotta send you back
to the Spirit Realm. Skadoosh.
Okay, that didn't work.
Let me try one more time.
Skadoosh! Skadoosh, skadoosh.
Shadoo-- What the--?
Hold on. Wait! It's working. No. No!
[choking]
[laughs]
No, it's not.
Did Oogway teach you
that little trick? Too bad.
It only works on mortals
and I am a Spirit Warrior.
Come!
[grunts]
-[snorts]
-[yelps]
[both grunting]
Whoa!
[grunts]
[groans]
[all gasp]
-Son! [gasps]
-Po!
[pandas murmuring]
I was wrong. I'm sorry. Run, run!
[pandas gasp]
[laughing]
So, Oogway, this was the one
destined to stop me?
I will have his chi,
and then all of theirs!
[all screaming]
[Lei Lei crying]
And you... [laughs]
You really thought you could send me
back to the Spirit Realm?
[laughs]
You are just a stupid mortal.
It only works on mortals.
You're right. I can't send you there.
But I can take you there.
-What's that?
-[pandas gasp]
Ow! What?
-Po?
-Son!
Skadoosh.
[both]
Son!
No!
[all gasp]
Wha... What happened? Where's Po?
He took Kai away. He saved us.
No.
He saved us, but who's saving him?
Whoa! The Spirit Realm! It worked!
-[whimpers, screams]
-Get off me, you--
-You brought me back?
-[grunts]
Don't blame me. I tried to finish this
in the regular realm.
Then we'll finish it here!
[gasps]
-Whoa!
-[grunts]
[gasps]
Come on, son. Fight!
We have to help him.
We have to help him!
Okay, everyone, gather around!
That's it. Come in close.
Come on, we can do this!
[Li]
Po...
You taught us who we are meant to be.
A father.
A friend.
-A dumpling kicker.
-A lethal fighting machine.
A hugger.
-A nunchuck chick.
-Stripy Baby.
A family.
Sweet!
[Kai groans]
[snorting]
[groans]
Whoa!
-Who are you?
-I've been asking the same question.
Am I the son of a panda?
The son of a goose?
A student? A teacher?
Turns out... I'm all of them.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
Get it? See the giant dragon?
[laughs]
Get ready to feel the thunder.
This is awesome! [laughs]
[barks]
Whoo-hoo!
Hmm.
Uh-oh!
-[growls]
-[yelling]
Belly gong!
-Butt slap!
-[grunts]
Perhaps a bit of lunch
'cause I'm starving.
[inhales]
Mmm.
[grunting]
-Let's do this!
-No!
Heads up!
[screaming, groaning]
[groans]
[snorts]
It took me five hundred years
to take Oogway's chi.
I will have yours
if it takes me five hundred more!
Chitty-chitty chat-chat! Chit. Chat.
[growling, grunting]
You want my chi so bad? Then take it.
Yes! The power is mine!
Wait. No. It's too much.
It's too much!
No!
[screaming]
[Kai]
No!
[all murmuring]
-[grunting] Where'd he go?
-[clucks]
[snarls]
-We're back!
-Bestie!
I'm still green! It didn't work!
Oh, wait, that's my normal green.
-Greeny Baby!
-Not a baby! Not a baby! Antenna of fear!
-What about Po?
-Have you seen Po?
No. He's not here?
Po? Po? Why isn't he back?
-Dragon Warrior.
-Oogway?
Whoa! Oh! [grunts]
Yeah! [gasps] I can't believe it.
-[chuckles]
-Whoa!
-You are extra shiny.
-As are you.
I know, right?
It's like the best cape ever!
When I run with it,
then it looks really cool.
-It suits you. You've grown.
-Yeah, I gotta lay off the panda buffet.
Grown up.
[chuckles]
As I hoped you would
when I sent the message to your father.
[gasps]
You sent the universe mail! Whoa!
Yes. Because the universe needed you.
-Me?
-[chuckles]
You finally became the panda
you were always meant to be.
But how'd you know I could?
On the first day we met,
I saw the future of kung fu...
...and the past.
I saw the panda
who could unite them both.
That is why I chose you, Po.
Both sides of the Yin and Yang.
And my true successor.
Me? I can't take that.
Just take it. I have a bigger one.
I mean, you're enlightened
and everything. I'm just...
[gasps]
Oh... Really?
Yes.
[chuckles]
-Now, what do we do?
-Hmm. You tell me.
No, Oogway, don't go!
I'm not going anywhere. I live here.
Oh, right.
It's you who must decide
whether to stay or go.
-Wait. I can go back?
-Who knows? I've never tried.
Wow!
[all cheer]
-Po!
-Oh! You can fly!
-[screams]
-[all laugh]
Dad! Dad! Dads!
[both]
Son!
[Li laughs]
Don't you go disappearing
in petals ever again!
We thought we lost you.
No, you saved me. You all did.
-[laughs]
-Now, come on over here!
-[all cheer]
-Hugs!
[laughter]
Master Shifu!
The student has truly become the tea--
Wait, where did you get that?
Oh, this? Oogway gave it to me
in the Spirit Realm.
[sighs]
Of course he did.
I think I mastered chi.
[sighs]
Of course you did.
Can you teach me?
Ready!
[all grunt]
[Shanghai Roxi Musical Choirs
"Kung Fu Fighting" playing]
-Yah!
-[all grunting]
-Whoa!
-[groans]
Ow!
[all cheer]
-Monkey! Help me!
-[laughs]
-Greeny Baby!
-Get them off me!
-[grunts]
-[giggles]
[grunting]
[laughs]
Mmm. Hello.
Ya-hoo!
-Ya!
[clucking]
Skadoosh.
[wheezing]
Panda asthma.
[chuckles]