Sync & Corrections by aHruaia
(From Aorion's)
Stairs...
I don't think I can...
Hey, guys,
just start without me.
I'll catch up.
Sweet.
Inner peace.
Itchy nose.
Ah-choo!
Finally, inner peace.
Now, what?
Kai, old friend.
Master Oogway.
Our battle ended 500 years ago.
Well, now I'm ready for a rematch.
Took you long enough.
Ha ha ha ha...
Yaaa!
You've grown stronger.
(Chi)
500 years in the Spirit Realm,
you pick up a thing or two.
I have taken the Chi
of every Master here.
- No!
- Yes.
And soon I will have your power too.
When will you realize,
the more you take, the less you have.
With your Chi, I will finally
be able to return to the mortal world,
And this time,
you won't be there to stop me.
Ah, it was never
my destiny to stop you.
I have set another on that path.
Then I will find him,
and take his Chi too.
Justice, is about to be served.
KUNG FU PANDA
Sync & Corrections by:
aHruaia
We'll have two justice platters , please
- umm...three
- Three.
- And a few tofu buns.
Oh , the spicy noodle soup for Tigress.
Did you want extra sauce with that?
She wants it on the side
- On the side
-On the side
Dragon, you can do it.
- Go, Dragon Warrior.
- Defend the valley.
Go Dragon Warrior
- Yeah, defend the valley
Yee-ha!
You guys aren't doing
the dramatic pose , are you?
Do we have to strike a pose
every time we land?
You guys, never underestimate
the power of a dramatic entrance.
I've heard about some Masters who could win
a fight just by throwing open a door
Shuh-sha!
Dramatic entrance?
Master Shifu
The Dragon Warrior is correct.
Really? I was just making....
yeah, I mean, yeah, I am.
Before the battle of the fist
comes the battle of the mind.
Hence... the dramatic entrance.
Whoa ,nice dramatic entrance.
-What's the occasion?
-Today will be my final class.
Your final...? Wait.
I didn't even know you were sick
Although you have been looking a little....
-I'm not sick.
healthy. A little healthy.
A lot actually
My final class because from now on...
your training will be in the
hands of the Dragon Warrior.
What?
Me? teach?I mean why not Tigress?
She's always telling everyone what to do.
- Be quiet Po.
-See what I mean?
Tigress is not the Dragon Warrior.
You are.
Come on they're theFfive.
What can I teach them?
There is always something more to learn.
Even for a Master.
For instance ,
let me show you another move.
The dramatic exit.
What's that?
Whoa!
Are you kidding me?
That....what?
- Where'd he go?
- Master.
He's gone guys. It's cool.
- We await your instruction, Master.
All you have to lose is our respect.
Seriously, how bad could it be?
Very bad!
Very, very bad!
Okay. Okay, let's switch it up.
Monkey, Immovable Mountain Stance.
Yes, Master.
I mean.... Tigress, Tornado back flip
- Yes, Master
- Oh no, fire.
- Fire
Sorry, my fault
Crane go high, I mean low
Oh, my claw thingy
Uh, Viper and tigress , to...
like a totem pole
Poison , Technique.
You two, to...
Sworming insect bite with yellow tail , Yellow jacket...
Spicy....tuna
Good job, Po.
Ah.
Did you at least learn
a little something?
Yes , that you can't teach.
And tigress is flammable, turns out.
That was a complete disaster.
I'm glad we're not Po right now.
-What a loser
- What was Shifu thinking?
- What was Oogway thinking?
- I think he heard us.
- I didn't hear anything.
He said you're a loser
Sorry, Oogway.
- Would you stop doing that?
- How was your fisrt day teaching?
- Humiliating.
- I heard.
Who told you?
Did Tigress tell you?
I heard from Monkey and Crane and Mantis and
your dad and Mrs. Chau from the gift shop
And those ducks who just passed
and Tigress told me.
Yeah, well did she also tell you that it'll never
happen again cause I'm done?
Teaching , or being humiliated?
Both. I don't know why you ever thought
I could teach that class?
Oh, I knew you couldn't.
What? You set me up to fail?
Why?
If you only do what you can do
you'll never be more than you are now.
I don't wanna be more
I like who I am.
You don't even know who you are.
What do you....? Of course I do
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
And what exactly does
that mean Dragon Warrior?
It means...you know... just going around
and punching and kicking
Defending the valley and stuff.
Punching and kicking?
You think that is what the
great Master Oogway saw for you?
A five hundred year prophecy full-filled so
you can spend your days...
Kicking butt?
And running through town high-fiving bunnies?
- Yes.
- No!
Oogway saw greatness in you, Po,
against my better judgement.
More than you can see in yourself.
Incredible power awaits you
Power beyond anything you can imagine.
Whoa!
What was that?
-That was chi.
Whoa!
What's chi?
The energy that flows
through all living things.
So you're saying if I, so you're saying if I teach,
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that?
No I'm saying if you teach,
I'll be able to do cool stuff like that.
- Oh.
- Mastery of chi requires Mastery of self
Oogway sat alone in a cave
for thirty years asking one question....
Who am I?
I'm lucky if I get 5 minutes
before you interrupt .
So now I have to sit alone
in a cave for thirty years?
Eventually.
After you Master teaching
Teaching? There's no way
I'm ever gonna be like you.
I'm not trying to turn you into me.
I'm trying to turn you into you.
Turn me into me?
Wait a second. That makes no....(sense)
Almost there Shifu , just a little more confusing
and you'll be the next Oogway.
Oh.
Ah.
Sorry, no offense Master Oogway
I just....
I'll let you get back
to your eternal peace.
- What is this place?
-Aaah...my brother's farm?
Ah.
If I stepped on you, would you die?
Yes.
The mortal realm.
You hear that Oogway?
I'm back.
Kai has returned.
- Who?
- Kai. General Kai.
Supreme warlord of all China
I don't know.
The jade slayer,
Master of pain
You may know me
as the beast of vengeance
Maker of widows?
Ok, I used to work with Oogway.
Oh, Master Oogway, he
was a great warrior.
- We've heard of Master Oogway. Wise and...
- Ok, ok, enough.
Silence!
Find Oogway's students
and bring them to me.
By the time I am done
with them, Oogway...
There will be no one left to
who will even remember your name.
Ha ha ha!
Kai is coming!
I am ready...
- to teach you a lesson.
-Teach me?
- Oh no, ite's the Dragon teacher
- Yeah he's so handsome.
Thank you for the compliment.
No, please don't teach me to death
Po?
Oh, hey dad
What's up?
I like just ....
stopping by for a little soak.
- Okay , What's wrong?
- Nothing
Nothing? I come home to find you taking a
bath with your dolls...
- Action figures.
-And instead of adding bath-salt to the water.
- You just added szechuan peppercorns.
- Szechuan, what?
Oh, oh, oh... my tenders.
Okay, yes, something's wrong
There, there, son , you tell
your daddy all about it
Lift your arm
Shifu says I don't know what
it means to be the Dragon Warrior.
And now I have to be a teacher?
I thought I finally knew who I was.
If I'm not the dragon Warrior,
then who am I?
A teacher?
Teaching kung fu?
Po, that's a promotion.
Take the job, son
And someday, when you're in charge of the whole
Jade palace, I can sell noodles in the lobby. Yoohoo.
Why are you still here taking a bath like a baby?
Get out. Get up. Go, go, go.
- Franchise expansion awaits us!
- What about the Dragon Warrior look alike contest?
- Mrs. Chau always wins that.
- Skadoosh
And the Dragon Warrior dumpling eating contest?
I have to defend my title
No one's gonna beat your
dumpling eating record.
Someone's about to beat your
Go. Go. Go.
- Who's eating my dumplings?
- And who's paying for them?
101, 102
Li : 103.
Yeah!
Is that a new record?
Who are you?
- I'm Li Shan
- What?
I'm Li shan.
I'm looking for my son.
- You lost your son?
- Yes, many years ago.
- I lost my father
- Very sorry
Thank you.
Well , good luck to you.
You too.
I hope you find your son.
And I hope you find your father
- Son?
- Huh?
Oh my gosh, it is you.
Well, don't just stand there!
Give your old man a hug!
I can't believe you're alive.
- Yeah!
I thought I'd lost you forever,
Little Lotus.
Oh, Okay.
This is very embarrassing,
but I think you've got me confused with
a panda named Lotus. My name is Po.
Oh right, you wouldn't... Okay
See, Little Lotus was the name
you were given at birth.
- Really?
-Really.
I can't believe it. After all these
years and you're really here?
This is amazing.
Oh, Dad.
Come say hi to...
Um. I don't know- I don't know
what I'm supposed to call you.
I'm pretty sure he
said his name is Li.
You...come here
Thank you, thank you for taking
such good care of my son.
Your son?
Now hold on just a minute.
How do we know this stranger
is even related to you?
Look at that.
Our bellies could be brothers.
Hey son, let me teach you how to Belly Gong.
All right, belly gong
That's so cool.
They jiggle the same.
It's like looking in a fat mirror.
I can't believe we're taking
a picture together.
But I still don't understand.
I thought Po was the only panda left.
- No, there's a whole bunch of us.
- Where?
- Here, a secret panda village in the mountains
- A secret panda....
Whoa.
But how did you
know where I was?
I received a message
that led me here.
How could you receive a message
if no one could find you?
Sounds suspicious to me.
No, wait, wait.
It was a message from the universe
- Ooooooh!
- Whoa!
- Whoa.
- Rats.
Now, what's all this about
a Dragon Warrior?
How'd you know I was the Dragon Warrior?
Did the universe tell you that, too?
No, the poster did, and the gift shop.
I bought a tiny cup.
Oh right, of course...
You gotta... you have no idea
there's so much to show you.
You're gonna be so
awesomely proud!
Come on!
I'm already awesomely proud.
- Oh. Couple more steps.
- Oh
Feeling the burn.
Do you have panda asthma, too?
Does that run in the family?
Dad, you're gonna love this
It's like the coolest thing ever.
This is the hall of heroes
Home of the most priceless kung fu artifacts
in all of China.
Whoa.
This place is ....
Awesome? You were going-you were going
to say awesome, right?
- Because it totally is!
- Totally!
But be super careful, everything
is very fragile here.
Like the Urn of Whispering warriors.
Someone broke that once.
- Who?
- Some idiot.
Wow!
- This is Master flying Rhino's battle armor.
- I wonder if I could fit in that
Get out of my head, dad.
I've wondered the same thing.
If I could fit in it?
-If you could? No, if I could fit in it.
- Oh.
- Dad, check it out.
Master Ram's crossbow
The infinite gates smasher.
Dad, look at this.
The battle helmets of Master Rat's army.
They're so tiny.
Master Dolphin's water proof armor.
This is my favorite.
Check it out. It's the legendary
battle rickshaw of emperor Hawk
Sweet ride.
Dad, what are you doing?
We're not supposed to touch anything.
Oh. Sorry, sorry.
Should I put it back?
Yeah, you probably should.
You look so cool, though.
How does it feel? Do the hinges hinge?
Does it smell like rhino?
Does it feel like
you're impenetrable?
Does it feel like you can
take on a thousand warriors
and emerge unscathed?
Yes, it's pretty cool.
Wonder what this does?
I should pull it.
I think I just peed a little.
Anything else we should try in here, son?
Hmm?
Charge!
Faster, faster, faster!
- Thumb war!
- Reinforcements!
Yeah!
This is so much fun...
- Here we go.
- Awesome!
- There, there
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
There you go.
Dolphin style attack!
Tweee.
- You got me.
- Dolphin style retreat!
Go long son.
Whoa!
I wasn't ready.
- Coming back at you.
- I got it.
- Throw it high!
- Here you go. Yeah, C'mon.
- I'm coming for you.
- Bring it on Master Rhino.
Here I come!
Oh.
I'm gonna get you.
Shh, stop.
Who's gonna get you?
- Master Rhino.
- Why, what's wrong?
Hello.
Guys guys, you're never gonna
guess who just showed up.
Not in a million years. You can't....
you just try.
- Your father!
Wow, how did you
just guess that?
Oh, wait a second. Yeah of course.
We look exactly the same.
Dad. Say hi to my friends, Mantis
Tigress, Monkey, Crane, and Viper.
- Oh, Viper, was it?
- Monkey, sir.
They're kind of my best friends.
And this... this is Master Shifu.
Legend.
It is an honor to meet you, Master Panda.
Perhaps your father would care
to join us in the training hall?
Your son will be teaching the class.
Ho-ho.
I'm sure he's tired.
I'm sure you're tired.
He's tired. I'm gonna show him
the chrysanthemums suite.
What?Tired? No, I'm fine.
I would love to watch you teach.
Trust me.
It would be more fun to watch me...
- Fight!
- What is that?
The valley is under attack.
- Son? Under attack?
-This is perfect!
Now you can see what being the dragon
warrior is all about.
Follow me!
Enemies of justice.
Prepare for.... whoa
Are you kidding me?
Whoa!
Ow!
What's the deal with the green guys?
- Some kind of jade zombies.
- Jade zombies?
- Jombies, Jinx.
Oh!
- Lotus, be careful!
- It's Okay, Dad. I do this everyday....!
Whoa. I recognize this guys.
The Master Badger twins.
With their crushing double gong technique.
Ow!
Yeah, that's the one.
That guys is.... no
Master Porcupine.
I thought he died hundred years ago?
These guys are legends.
Get a quick sketch of us.
Did you get it?
Aw, I blinked.
Can we get another one?
I'm being choked by Master Porcupine.
This is so cool.
- Look. It's you.
- Po, focus!
Message from the universe.
I'll give you one message from the universe...
Stay away from my son.
Sorry dad. I'll
clean it up later.
Whoa, whoa, not my good pan.
Take this one.
Lotus, watch out!
Dad, check out my dumplings of doom.
Gotcha!
Ahahahaha...
I see you.
Your chi will soon be mine.
- Is he talking to me?
- Which one? They're all talking.
Whoa, you're right.
That's so scary.
We should try that, too.
Maybe it'd be scary back at them.
Okay, but we gotta plan
what we're gonna say first,
otherwise it won't be scary,
it'll be just stupid.
It's not them talking, you idiots!
It's me talking through them, Kai!
- Who?
- Okay, okay, enough.
- Did you see that? Did you see?
- Whoa, what just happened?
The green smoke just poof....
and then poof.
Shifu, what wast that?
Kai? Kai?
Kai?
Nope. Never heard of him.
Kai... Kai...
Where is it?
There's so much wisdom in here,
I can't find anything.
Yes!
Behold.
All the answers will be found within.
What?
It's blank?
Are you kidding me?
Not again.
Wait, wait. Hold on. Sorry
Oh, okay, here we go.
It is written in Oogway's hand.
- Long ago, I had a brother.
- Oogway had a brother?
In arms.
In arms, sorry.
He says brother in arms.
- Can't you just unroll it all at once?
I was an ambitious young warrior
leading a great army.
And fighting by my side was Kai.
My closest friend.
One day we were ambushed.
I was badly wounded.
My friend carried me for days
looking for help.
Until we came to a secret village,
high in the mountains.
An ancient place of healing.
A village of pandas.
- Pandas?
- Yes, pandas.
Pandas who used the
power of chi to heal me.
They taught me how to give chi.
But Kai, wanted the power all to himself.
He saw that what could be given
could also be taken.
I had to stop him.
Our battle shook the Earth.
Until, finally, I banished Kai to
the Spirit Realm.
Should he ever return
to the mortal realm,
he can only be stopped
by a true Master of chi.
True Master of chi?
Like you.
Me?
I can barely make a flower bloom!
I'd need at least thirty more years, and a cave.
Viper: We need a chi Master.
Shifu: He will continue stealing the chi
of Masters until he has consumed it all.
Viper: We have to make a way to stop him.
Crane: He gets more more powerful
with every Master he defeats.
Tigress: There is no choice.
We fight.
I can teach you, son.
- You can do this?
- Of course, I'm a panda.
That must be why the universe
sent you here.
Okay, so what do I have to do?
- You have to come home with me.
- What?
- To the secret village?
- Yes, son.
You must rediscover
what it is to be a panda.
You have to learn how to live like a panda.
Sleep like a panda.
Eat like a panda.
Those 103 dumplings?
Hmm... I was just warming up.
I've always felt like
I wasn't eating up to my full potential.
You can't take Po away from me. No, no
I want a second opinion.
Shifu, open another scroll or something.
- I think he should go.
- Fine. A third opinion.
Monkey? Viper?
Tigress?
Dad, you heard what
Shifu said, Oogway said.
This guy can only be stopped
by a Master of chi.
And I can only Master chi by knowing
who I really am.
Well, I'm a panda.
I'll pack your lunch for the road.
Do you really think Po
can Master chi in time?
Doesn't matter what I think.
- It only matters what the universe thinks.
- So, that's a "No"?
- Master, what are we going to do?
- You are going to find out where Kai is.
Follow the trail of those jade creatures
but do not engage.
For with every foe he faces
Kai becomes stronger.
- Why me? Is it because I asked.
- No, it is because you can fly.
- Go!
- Should have kept your beak shut.
- And take Mantis.
- What? Oh man, is it because I ...?
Yes.
Hmun dang zawng aia tlawma
Air Tickets la duh tan
D&L TRAVELS #9612136045 ah
biak mai tur a ni e.
- Oh, lunch break?
- Ha.
- You don't need to ask me twice.
- Ow.
- Dad?
- Yes?
- What are you doing here?
- What am I doing? Getting a backache.
Did you have to step on every rock?
- No, I mean why are you here?
- What was I supposed to do, huh?
What if the pandas
don't have food you like?
You're never gonna be able to save the world
on an empty stomach.
I consider my presence mission critical.
Oh yes about that. We can't share
the location of the village with others.
- So...
- Well, you think I can't keep a secret, huh?
I raised Po for 20 years before
I finally told him he was adopted.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Okay, I guess it would be cruel
to make you fly back.
- You can fly?
- I'm a bird, Po.
We're here.
Sure looks like a long ways up there.
And my son hates stairs.
So, let's go home.
We're pandas.
We don't do stairs.
I've waited my whole life
to hear those words.
Rats.
Whoa... huh?
This is the secret panda village?
No wonder you keep it a secret.
If I lived here,
I wouldn't tell anyone either.
- Now you can whoa.
- Whoa...!
Oh.
Li?
Everyone, Li is back.
- They're both back.
- He found his son.
- He made it.
- They're back.
- Li?
- He found his son.
Everyone, Li is back.
Hang on, we're coming.
- He made it.
- Yoo-hoo!
- He made it!
- Why are we running?
- He made it.
- Li shan is back.
Everyone, everyone gather around.
This is my son.
- Hello. Hi.
- Cute.
- Triplets!
- Hi, I'm Ku Ku.
- I'm Meng Meng.
- I'm Shuai Shuai, he smells like cookies.
- He's so handsome. Just like his father.
- Thank you.
Son, these are your cousins.
Dim and Sum.
- I have cousins.
- Welcome.
- Whoa, buns on a string.
- We call it a snacklace.
That's right.
Yum yum yum yum yum.
We'll make you another one.
Ooooh.
It's you.
- So, that's nice to see you. Hi.
- I don't know who you are.
Oh, stripey baby
So beautiful.
Oh, Okay, careful with that.
That's my action figure.
Can I keep her?
- Noooo...
- Can I?
No....problem. Of course, yeah
that's why I brought her.
- Take good care of her.
- Yes, stripey baby
You look just like me
but a baby.
You're like me but old.
You're like me but fatter.
- You're like me but.....
- Ha ha.
Wooooo... with a hat.
He does wear a hat.
You all look like me.
Let's feast in my son's honor.
- Yeh.
- Yeah.
- What the.....?
- Pandas don't walk! We roll!
How you ever seen anyone
look so ridiculous?
Po, what are you doing?
Po?
Ow.
Oh.
You're right.
That is better than walking.
- Yeah.
- That's nice stuff.
Yeah, have some dumplings.
What kind of panda doesn't know
how to roll?
Well, I'm kinda new at this whole
being a panda thing.
Hey, what kind of panda are you?
You have a funny neck.
I'm not a panda at all.
- What's that? What's that? What's that?
-My hat , My beak , My wing , My dumplings.
No more questions.
Go away, kid.
Here, son, I packed your chopsticks.
- Thanks, dad.
- What?
- What are those for?
These? These are chopsticks
They're for picking up dumplings.
You mean you only eat
one at a time?
Yum yum yum.
I knew I wasn't eating
up to my potential.
Huh?
I am Mei Mei.
Wow, she's amazing.
She's so beautiful.
That's sweet, Po,
but please try to save all
other compliments until
after the performance.
- Me? No, I didn't say....
- Shhh. Shhh. Shh...
Shut it.
After the performance.
Ha.
Has it started yet?
- Whoa.
- Best ribbon dancer in the world.
- At least that's what she says.
- Look away, look away.
No, you can't.
Can you?
Dad, why does she keep
staring at me like that?
Try to keep up.
- I don't really know how to dance.
- Of course you do.
All pandas dance.
- I know what you're thinking.
- You do?
How can one panda be so beautiful?
- Whoa!
- For me? Fine.
Ooo.
Oh.
- Help me, dads.
-Yeah, no. You're on your own.
You're doing great, son.
Your turn.
Bring it home!
Don't worry, you'll get the hang of it.
I have so much to learn.
Wings of surveillance.
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
Just because you say "Wings of......" before something
it doesn't mean that you're doing a special move.
It's like me saying,
"Antenna of power" or....
" Thorax of making sandwiches"
- Wings of disagreement.
- Whoa, there.
Master Bear, Master Chicken, Master Croc,
what are you doing out here?
Jade creatures attacked our villages.
We've tracked them here.
Stop.
They must be in there.
Master Shifu strongly advised us.....
- ...not to engage.
- We got to get in there.
- But Master Shifu said...
- You're seriously afraid?
Even Master Chicken's going in there
and he's a chicken.
- That's it, I'm going in.
- Mantis, we have orders not to....
They need our help. Come on.
I'll go high, you go low.
No, wait.
Fear the bug.
Alright, you little...!
Oh oh.
- Hold on, buddy. I'm coming.
- "Antenna of power"
- Ah, it didn't work!
- Mantis!
Mantis?
Your chi is strong,
just like your friend, the bug.
Huh?
Mantis.
Whoooooa.
Don't worry, little birdie.
I'll put your chi to good use.
Destroying the Jade palace
and everyone in it.
No.
Wings of...regret.
Oh yeah, first day
of panda training.
Alright flower,
I'm gonna make you bloom.
Hoo-hoo!
Dad, dad .
- What? What? What is it?
-I'm ready for my first day of panda training.
What?
You know, learn to be a panda,
Master chi, save the world.
Pandas sleep till past noon.
So lesson number one is
go back to bed.
Of course.
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
- Did I oversleep?
- Ha, ha! You sure did.
Yes!
Yeah, show him kids.
Can you do this?
Can you do that?
- How about this? How about that?
- Hey?
- Am I doing it? Is this good?
- Whoa.
Here we go.
I got it!
- Whoa.
- Grandma panda, heads up.
- Ow.
- Oh.
- We better roll.
Po, lunchtime.
Po. You gotta let the hill
tell you where to roll.
- Rookie mistake.
- Dim, Sum, let's show him how we go uphill.
- It's beautiful.
- Snack time. Oh.
- Po, you can fly?
- I'm coming in hot!
Get them while they're cold.
What are you doing there?
That food is for Po.
Throw it in.
There, there, that's it.
- Feeling relaxed?
- Yeah, really.
- Just let yourself fall into it.
- Got it.
I'm fine.
I just.....
There we go.
Just let it all out.
That's my boy.
Get out of there!
My noodles.
Leave my noodles alone.
- Subtle, Po. Very subtle.
- Let me get some of that.
And leave my hat alone.
- We love noodles!
- Oh, just like my Po.
What are you guys looking at?
That's how we roll.
Cannonball.
Hoo-hoo.
Yeah!
- Mom, look it.
- Whoa.
How was that?
Whoa
- Now you try again but don't try so hard.
- Okay, Okay.
Much better.
Thanks, dad.
- For what?
You know, just for you know,
showing me what it feels like...
to be a panda.
- So when do you think I'll be ready?
- Ready?
You know, to learn how to master chi.
Soon, real soon.
Come on.
I wanna show you something else. C'mon
Sorry about the mess,
I don't usually get visitors.
Is this my mom?
I had this done on your
one hundredth day.
Your mama couldn't hold you still.
You nearly eat the paper.
- It's true.
- What was she like?
She was the total package.
Smart, beautiful.
Tremendous appetite.
She was the love of my life.
And then, just when I thought
I couldn't get any luckier.
Along you came, my Little Lotus.
I really had it all.
Until that one moment...
When I ...
lost everything.
Hmun dang zawng aia tlawma
Air Tickets la duh tan
D&L TRAVELS #9612136045 ah
biak mai tur a ni e
In/Office lamah pawh a thlawnin
tickets kan dahsak thei.
Dad, you don't have to worry about
losing me ever again, Okay?
Let me get some of that.
It's from the eastern province.
Master Lizard, Master Ox,
Master Eagle, all of them.
In every village from the sea to here.
Every Master in china...
- ... has vanished.
- Maybe they are all at a party?
- Monkey.
- I didn't get invited either.
Kai has taken their chi.
We are all that stand between him
and the knowledge Oogway left
in our care.
- The villagers, evacuated?
- Done, Master.
- Crane? Mantis?
- Still nothing.
Huh!
Wait, it's them!
No!
Kai
Nice, very tacky.
How dare you set foot
on these grounds!
Look at your pathetic fools.
Groveling at the feet of
Oogway the magnificent.
You are not fit to speak his name.
I am not fit, little kitten?
I fought by his side.
I loved him like a brother.
And he betrayed me.
Well, now I will destroy
everything he has created.
Go!
How's that for a little kitten?
Huh!
Ya!
I will not let you destroy
Oogway's memory.
Why not?
He destroyed mine.
Mantis, it is me, your bestie.
Whoooaaa!
Sorry Tigress.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
- Shifu.
- Bring them to me.
Heh ha ha ha...
- No! You must warn Po.
- Master please.
I will show you
the true power of chi, brother.
No.
Oogway, forgive me.
Hmm, what do you say Oogway?
Do you forgive him?
You may have destroyed
the Jade palace.
but you will never succeed.
There will always be someone to stop you.
Who? The panda?
His chi is strong but
it won't be enough.
- He will meet the same fate as you.
- No.
And so will every panda in that village.
Yes!
Po, I hope you're ready.
Dance Lotus, dance.
He's so handsome.
- Hi
-That's a panda hug.
Hey
Oh! Ooo.
Eh, ha ha.
Po.
Huh!
Tigress?
Who's she?
Who is that?
- Baby stripey baby
- What are you doing here?
Kai attacked the valley.
He's taken every Master in china
including Shifu and the others.
It's....it's all gone, Po.
- Everything, everyone.
- Everyone?
- Everyone.
- How's my restaurant?
- We'll talk later.
- And now he's on his way here.
He's after you, Po.
He's after all pandas.
- How long do we have?
- Not long.
Please tell me you've mastered chi.
- Here, take the baby.
- Dad, dad.
Okay, who belongs to this one?
You need to teach me the
secret chi technique now.
No, no.
I'm afraid you need more time.
Everyone, go get your things.
- Let me hand you that.
- I don't have more time. I need to learn it now.
Sorry, you're not ready.
- Okay, pack everything.
- I am ready!
Not quite.
What are you talking about?
I've done everything you've asked.
I Mastered napping, sleeping in hammocks,
the hot tubs.
I am totally in one
with my panda parts
- Now, why won't you show me?
- Because I don't know it!
You what?
I don't know it, Okay?
No one does.
Maybe we used to but...
- But not anymore.
- You lied?
No, I ...
Yes.
Why?
To save your life.
I find out some blade-swinging
maniac is coming for you.
What am I supposed to do?
- Just let that happen?
- Yes, I'm the Dragon Warrior!
Facing maniacs, that's my job.
But because of you,
I left the valley unprotected.
I left my friends unprotected.
And now they're all...
they're all...
And you would have been, too.
I lost you once.
I am not going to lose you again.
I can't.
You just did.
Mom, pick me.
Po, I'm so worried for you that
I can't even enjoy being right
about everything.
Now run, run, run, as fast as
those chubby legs can go.
- Run? There's nowhere to run.
- What are you going to do?
I'm gonna stay and
fight that monster.
Po, he may be a monster but
he's still your father.
- Not him, Kai.
- Huh! No.
- Hungry?
- No, I..... not really.
Well, maybe just one.
You know, you weren't the only one
who was lying.
I didn't really come along because I was worried
Po would go hungry.
- I was worried about you.
- Worried that I'd go hungry?
- No, I was worried you'd steal Po from me.
- I'd what?
I know.
That was crazy.
But I realized having you in Po's life
doesn't mean less for me.
It means more for Po.
Oh.
Well.
I'm not in his life.
- Not any more.
- Your son got mad at you.
- Welcome to parenthood.
- You don't understand.
I lied to him.
He'll never forgive me.
I lied to him for 20 years.
He still thinks he came from an egg.
Sometimes we do the wrong things
for the right reasons.
Look, he's hurt.
He's confused
and he still has to save the world.
He needs the both his dads.
- This isn't going to work.
- It has to.
- You 're not thinking straight.
- I am.
- You're not.
- No.
- Yes, I am.
I've seen Kai.
I've seen what he can do.
But he hasn't seen what
I can do.
The Wuxi finger hold?
That's my best move.
I just have to get to
Kai, grab his finger,
and then, Skadoosh.
Back to the Spirit Realm.
He has an army of jade warriors.
Everything they see he sees
so there's no sneaking up on him.
You will never get close enough.
- It's gonna work.
He can only be stopped
by a Master of chi.
Oh, you sound just like Shifu with the chi chi chi.
Chi this. Chi that. Chi chi chi chi.
I'm not a Master of chi. Okay?
I don't know if I'm the Dragon Warrior.
I don't even know if I'm a panda.
I don't know who I am.
You're right.
There's no way I can
stop him and his army.
Unless you had an army of your own.
- You?
- Not just me.
- Us.
- All of us.
I finally found my son
after all these years.
It's gonna take a lot more than
the end of the world to keep us apart.
- But you don't even know kung fu.
- Then you will teach us.
What? I can't teach you kung fu.
I couldn't even teach Tigress.
And she already knows kung fu!
Po, I know I'm the last guy
you wanna trust right now.
But you gotta believe me.
We can do this.
We can learn kung fu.
We can be just like you.
What did you just say?
- Uh... We can do this?
- No.
- We can learn kung fu?
- After that.
Uh... I...
We can be just like you?
- Yes!
- We can?
No, you can't!
But you don't have to be.
That's what Shifu meant.
I don't have to turn you into me.
I have to turn you into you!
That doesn't make any sense.
I know!
- Thanks, dads.
- You're welcome?
I'm gonna do something I never thought
I'd be able to do.
I'm gonna teach kung fu.
You guys, your real strength comes
from being the best you you can be.
So, who are you?
What are you good at?
What do you love?
What makes you you?
Yes, good.
Good, again.
Good, good, good, again.
- Huh?
- Stripey baby, stripey baby
Faster, faster.
Roll those ribbons!
Hug that log, you.
Hug that log
like it's the last time you're ever
gonna hug it. Goodbye forever.
Higher, and a little more to the
left this time. You can do it.
I don't wanna see any of these
hit the ground.
Wait, wait, save Stripy Baby some.
Good, try it with this.
Now try it with these.
Good, now try it with these.
Oh.
- Ow.
- Oooh.
Hmun dang zawng aia tlawma
Air Tickets la duh tan
D&L TRAVELS #9612136045 ah
biak mai tur a ni e
In/Office lamah pawh a thlawnin
tickets kan dahsak thei.
They are ready.
Baby, he he he.
What?
Okay pay attention cause I might gonna
go over this ten more times.
The only entrance to the village is here.
The dumpling squadron will take position here
while the cookie squadron will take position here.
Now, on my signal,
the two squadrons will...
Alright, Okay.
The noodle squadron will...
Alright. Okay, anyway,the
important thing to
remember is that this
is the spot where...
Okay, I saw that coming.
If you only remember one thing,
it's just distract the jombies until
I get close enough to put a
Wuxi finger hold on Kai.
You got it?
- Yeah!
Pandas on three. One, two, three
panda, you guys...
Never mind.
I'll teach you that later.
I... I wish I could have taught
you this, son.
It's okay, dad.
I'm....
He's here.
Whhhhooooaaa!
That's what I call a dramatic entrance.
Haha, you must be the Dragon Warrior.
And you must be Kai.
Beast of vengeance, maker of widows.
Yes, finally.
Thank you, almost makes
me wanna spare your life.
Oh, you wanna spare me?
How about you spare me the chitchat, alright?
Let's do this.
I'm going to take your chi then the chi
of every panda in the...
- Oh, chitchat.
- in this...
- Chitty chitty chat chat chat chat chat
- in...
- in the....
- Chitchat.
Oh, you pudgy little...
Round them all up.
Oh no, it's true.
You guys have all been turned green.
Except for you, Mantis,
you were already green.
- Now?
- Wait for the signal.
HAA!
Here we go!
Ooo.
Dumpling squad!
- Ready?
- Go time.
- Belly...
- Gong...
Seriously?
- Yeah!
- We did it!
- Woo hoo hoo.
- Yeah!
Sorry, Crane.
Spring roll squad.
Time for some takeout.
Yoo hoo.
Over here, Mr. jombie.
I don't know who you are either.
Noodle squad.
Get ready to dance with danger.
Waaaaa!
Oooh.
Sweet.
- Stripey baby
- Huh!
Weee!
- Do it.
- You're mean.
Fire.
Fire in the hole.
Aww!
Yes
All right, kids!
You got it, guys.
Oh no, Master Shifu.
I can't hit Shifu.
- I can.
- And, so can I.
- Double dad defense.
- Left, dad.
- Right, dad.
Thanks dad.
Back at you, dad.
We've got this, son.
Ho ho.
Go, dads!
Yeah.
Yeah!
Ha ha!
- We got 'em now.
- Stop, stop, enough.
Stop.
- Ha ha ha ha ha.
- Eee!
Let's finish this.
- That's our boy!
Sorry, buddy. Gotta send
you back to the Spirit Realm.
Skadoosh!
Okay, that didn't work.
Let me try one more time.
Skadoosh.
Skadoosh, skadoosh, skadoosh.
What the?
Hold on, wait.
It's working.
No.
Nooo!
No, it's not.
Did Oogway teach you
that little trick?
Too bad.
It only works on mortals.
And I am a spirit warrior.
Come!
Ooof.
Oh.
Aw!
Whoa!
Son!
Po!
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
Run. Run!
So, Oogway, this was the one
destined to stop me?
I will have his chi
and then all of theirs.
And you...
Hehahahaha.
You really thought you can
send me back to the Spirit Realm?
You are just a stupid mortal.
It only works on mortals.
You're right.
I can't send you there.
But I can take you there.
What's that?
Oh.
What?
- Po.
- Son!
Skadoosh.
No!
- Aw!
What... What happened?
Where is Po?
He took Kai away.
He saved us.
No.
He saved us
but who's saving him?
Whoa, the Spirit Realm!
It worked!
Get off me, you...
You brought me back?
Don't blame me. I tried to finish this
in the regular realm.
And we'll finish it here.
Hmun dang zawng aia tlawma
Air Tickets la duh tan
D&L TRAVELS #9612136045 ah
biak mai tur a ni e
In/Office lamah pawh a thlawnin
tickets kan dahsak thei.
Come on, son.
Fight.
We have to help him.
Okay, everyone gather around.
That's it. Come in close.
Come on.
We can do this.
Po, you taught us
who we were meant to be.
A father.
- A friend.
- A dumpling kicker.
- A lethal fighting machine.
- A hugger.
A nunchuck chick.
Stripey baby.
A family
Sweet.
Ah!
Who are you?
I've been asking
the same question.
Am I the son of a panda?
The son of a goose?
A student?
A teacher?
Turns out,
I'm all of them.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
Get it?
See the giant dragon?
Ha ha ha!
Get ready to feel the thunder.
This is awesome!
Ho ho ho ho.
Ha ha!
Waa hoo!
Oh oh.
Belly gong.
Butt slap.
Perhaps a bit of lunch
cause I'm starving.
Mmm.
Let's do this!
Heads up.
It took me 500 years
to take Oogway's chi.
I will have yours if it
takes me 500 more.
Chtity chitty chat chat, chitchat.
You want my chi so bad?
Then take it.
Yes, the power is mine.
Wait, no.
It's too much.
That's too much.
No.
Noooo!
Where'd he go?
- We're back.
- Bestie.
I'm still green.
It didn't work!
Oh wait, that's my normal green.
- Stripey baby
- Not a baby, not a baby!
Antenna of Fear.
What about Po?
- Have you seen Po?
- No, he's not here?
Po?
Why isn't he back?
- Dragon warrior.
- Oogway? Whoaaa.
I can't believe it.
- Whoa, you're extra shiny.
- As are you.
I know, right? It's like
the best cape ever.
When I run with it,
then it looks really cool.
It suits you.
You've grown.
- Yeah, I gotta lay off the panda buffet.
- Grown up.
As I hoped you would
when I sent the message to your father.
Huh.
You sent the universe mail?
Whoa!
Yes, because the universe needed you.
Me?
You finally became the panda
you were always meant to be.
But how'd you know I could?
On the first day we met...
I saw the future of kung fu.
And the past.
I saw the panda
who could unite them both.
That is why I chose you, Po.
Both sides of the Yin and Yang.
And my true successor.
Me?
I can't-I can't take that.
Just take it.
I have a bigger one.
I mean, you're enlightening
and everything. I'm just....
Huh.
Ooooh.
- Really?
- Yes.
Now, what do we do?
Hmm, you tell me.
No, Oogway, don't go!
I'm not going anywhere.
I live here.
Oh right.
It's you who must decide
whether to stay or go.
- Wait, I can go back?
- Who knows?
I've never tried.
Wow!
Po.
Ohhh.
You can fly.
Dad, Dad, Dads!
- Son.
Don't you go disappearing
in petals ever again.
We thought we lost you.
No, you saved me.
You all did.
Now come on over here.
Hugs
Master Shifu!
The student has truly
become the tea...
Wait, where did you get that?
Oh this. Oogway gave it
to me in the Spirit Realm.
- Oh. Of course he did.
- I think I mastered chi.
Oh.
Of course you did.
Can you teach me?
Ready!
Monkey, help me.
Greeny baby.
Get her off me!
Mmm.
Hello.
Skadoosh.
Panda asthma.
2016 D&L Infotainment