Legend tells of a legendary warrior,...
...whose kung fu skills
were the stuff of legend.
He travelled the land
in search of worthy foes.
I see you like to chew.
Maybe you should on my fist!
The warrior said nothing
for his mouth was full.
Then he swallowed.
And then he spoke.
Enough talk. Let's fight!
He was so deadly in fact,
that his enemies will go blind,...
...from over exposure to pure
awesomeness.
- My eyes!
- He's too awesome!
- And attractive.
- How can we re-pay you?
There is no charge for awesomeness.
Or attractiveness.
It mattered not how many foes he faced.
They were no match for his bodacity.
Never before had a panda
been so feared and so loved.
Even the most heroic heroes
in all of China,...
...The Furious Five, bowed in respect
to this great master.
We should hang out.
Agreed.
But hanging out
would have to wait.
Cause when you're facing the ten
thousand demons of demon mountain.
There is only one thing
that matters and that’s...
- Po! Get up!
- You'll be late for work.
What?
Po, get up!
Hey, Po.
What are you doing up there?
Ah, nothing.
Monkey, Mantis, Crane,
Viper, Tigress!
Po, let's go.
You're late for work.
Coming!
Sorry dad.
Sorry, doesn't make the noodles.
What were you doing up there?
All that noise?
Oh, nothing.
Just had a crazy dream.
About what?
What were you dreaming about?
What was I...
...I was dreaming about a...
Noodles.
Noodles?
You were really dreaming about noodles?
Yeah, what else would I be
dreaming about?
Oh, careful.
That soup is... sharp!
Oh, happy day. My son finally
having the noodle dream.
You don't know how long
I have been waiting for this moment.
This is a sign, Po.
A sign of what?
You are almost ready to be
entrusted with the secret ingredient,...
...of my secret ingredient soup.
And then you will fulfill your destiny
and take over the restaurant.
Just as I took over from my father
who took over from his father...
...who won it from a friend
over a game of mahjong.
Dad, dad, dad.
It was just a dream.
No, it was "the dream".
We're noodle folk.
Broth runs through our veins.
But dad, didn't you ever... I don't know,
wanted to do something else?
Something beside noodles.
Actually, when I was
young and crazy.
I thought of running away
and learning how to make Toe Foo.
So why didn't you?
Oh, because it was
a stupid dream.
Can you imagine me making Toe Foo?
Toe Foo.
No, we all have our place
in this world.
- Mine is here and yours is...
- I know, is here.
No, it’s tables 2, 5, 7 and 12.
Service with a smile.
Well done, students...
...if you were trying
to disappoint me.
Tigress, you need more ferocity.
Monkey greater speed.
Crane, height.
Viper, subtlety. Mantis...
- Master Shifu...
- What?
It's... it's Master Oogway,
he wants to see you.
Master Oogway, you summoned me?
Is something wrong?
Why must something be wrong
for me to want to see my old friend?
- So, nothing is wrong?
- Well, I didn't say that.
You were saying?
I have had a vision.
Tai Lung will return.
That is impossible.
He's in prison.
Nothing is impossible.
Zeng, fly to Chor Ghom Prison.
And tell them to double the guards,...
...double the weapons.
Double everything.
Tai Lung does not leave
that prison.
Yes, Master Shifu.
One often meets his destiny
on the road he takes to avoid it.
We have to do something. We can't
just have him march in the valley.
And take his revenge.
He'll, he'll...
Your mind is like this water
my friend. When it is agitated...
...it becomes difficult to see.
But if you allow it to settle,
the answer becomes clear.
The Dragon Scroll.
- It is time.
- But who?
Who is worthy to be trusted
with the secret to limitless power...
...to become the Dragon Warrior?
I don't know.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Sorry.
- Oh, sorry.
- Hey, watch it Po.
Sorry.
Sorry, a thousand pardon.
What?
Master Oogway is choosing
the Dragon Warrior, today.
Everyone, everyone, go!
Get to the Jade Palace!
One of the five is going
to get the Dragon's Scroll.
We've been waiting a thousand
years for this. Just take the bowl!
This is the greatest day in Kung Fu
history! Don't worry about it. Just go!
Po! Where are you going?
To the Jade Palace.
But you're forgetting your noodle cart.
The whole valley will be there and
you will sell noodle to all of them.
Selling noodles?
But Dad. You know I was kind
of thinking, maybe I...
- Yeah?
- I was kind of thinking, maybe I...
Could also sell the bean buns.
They're... They're about to go bad.
That's my boy!
I told you that dream was a sign.
Yeah...
I'm glad I had it.
- I'm a kung fu warrior!
- Me too!
Almost there.
What? No!
Oh, no!
- Sorry, Po.
- We'll bring you back a souvenir.
No, I'll bring you back a souvenir.
It's a historic day.
Isn't it Master Oogway?
Yes. The one I feared
I would not live to see.
- Are your students ready?
- Yes, Master Oogway.
Now know this old friend...
...whomever I chose will not only bring
peace to the valley, but also to you.
Let the tournament begin!
No, no, no, wait!
I'm coming.
Hey! Open the door.
Let me in!
Citizens of the Valley of Peace!
It is my great honour
to present to you,...
...Tigress, Viper, Crane,
Monkey, Mantis.
The Furious Five!
They're The Furious Five!
Warriors prepare!
- Where's... Hah! A peeky hole.
- Ready for battle.
The thousand tons of fire!
- Wow, look at that!
- Hey! Get out of the way!
And finally, Master Tigress.
Believe me citizens,
you have not seen anything yet.
I know!
Master Tigress faces Iron Arms
and it's "Blades of Death".
I sense the Dragon Warrior
is among us.
Citizens of the Valley of Peace,...
...Master Oogway will now choose
the Dragon Warrior.
Ha? But I...
No, no, no wait!
Yeah.
Po! What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
Stop! Stop! I'm going to see
the Dragon Warrior.
But I don't understand,
you finally have the noodle dream.
I lied. I don't dream
about noodles, dad.
I love Kung Fu!
Oh, come on, son.
Let's get back to work.
Okay.
Po! Come back!
Oh. What's going on?
Where...?
Why are you pointing...?
Oh. Okay. Sorry. I just wanted
to see who the Dragon Warrior was?
How interesting?
Master, are you pointing at me?
- Him.
- Who?
- You.
- Me?
The universe has brought us
the Dragon Warrior.
- What?
Stop wait.
Who told you to...
Master Oogway, wait.
That flabby panda can't possibly
be the answer to our problem.
You were about to appoint the Tigress
and that thing fell in front of her.
- That was just an accident.
- There are no accidents.
Forgive us, Master.
We have failed you.
No. If the panda has not quit by morning,
then I would have failed you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I bring a message from Master Shifu.
What? Double the guard?
Extra precautions?
Your prison may not be adequate?
You doubt my prison security?
Absolutely not!
Shifu does.
I'm just the messenger.
I'll give you a message
for your Master Shifu.
Escape from Chor Ghom prison
is impossible.
Impressive, isn't it?
Yes, very impressive.
It's... It's very impressive.
One way in, one way out.
One thousand guards
and one prisoner.
Yes, except that prisoner is Tai Lung.
Take us down.
Oh, my!
Behold Tai Lung.
I'll... Uhm...
I'll just wait right here.
It's nothing to worry about.
It's perfectly safe.
- War posts! At the ready.
- War posts?
Hey, tough guy.
Did you hear?
Oogway is finally going to give
someone the Dragon Scroll...
...and it's not going to be you.
What are you doing?
Don't get him mad.
What is he going to do about it?
I've got him completely immobilised.
Oh, did I step on
the woolly kiddy's tail?
I'm gonna... I've seen enough.
I'm gonna tell Shifu,
he has nothing to worry about.
- No, he doesn't.
- Okay I'll tell him that.
Can we please go now?
Oh. Wait a second.
I think there has been
a slight mistake.
Everyone seems
to think I'm, err...
The sacred Hall of Warriors.
No way!
Look at this place.
Master Flying-Rhino's armour.
With authentic battle damage!
Wow! The Sword of Heroes.
Said to be so sharp, you can cut
yourself just by looking...
The invisible "Trident of Destiny".
I've only seen paintings
of that painting.
No!
The legendary "Urn of
Whispering Warriors".
Said to contain souls of the
entire Tenshu army.
- Hello?
- Have you finished sightseeing?
Sorry. I should have
come to see you first.
- My patience is running thin.
- Ohh?
Well. I mean, it's not like
you are going anywhere.
- You turn around.
- Sure.
Hey, how is it going?
How do you get 500... Master Shifu!
Someone broke that.
But I'm going to fix it... I'll... I'll...
Do you have some glue?
I've a splinter.
So you are the legendary
Dragon Warrior?
- Ahh, I guess so?
- Wrong!
You are not the Dragon Warrior.
You will never be the Dragon Warrior...
...until you've learned the secret
of the Dragon scroll.
Wow. So... Uhm...
How does this work?
Do you have a ladder?
A trampoline or...?
You think it is that easy?
That I'm just going to hand you
the secret to limitless power?
No! I...
One must first master the highest
level of Kung Fu...
...and that is clearly impossible
if that one is someone like you.
- Someone like me?
- Yes!
Look at you!
This fat butt, flabby arms.
Those are sensitive
in the flabby parts.
And this ridiculous belly.
- And utter disregard for personal hygiene.
- Now wait a minute.
- That's a little uncalled for... - Don't stand
that close. I can smell your breath.
Listen, Oogway said that I was the...
Uh... the Wuxi Finger Hold.
No, Wuxi Finger Hold.
You know this hold?
Developed by Master Wuxi
in the 3rd dynasty. Yes.
Then you must know what happens
when I flex my pinky.
No, no, no.
You know the hardest part of this?...
The hardest part is cleaning up afterwards.
Okay. Okay, take it easy.
Now listen closely, Panda.
Oogway may have picked you,
but when I'm through with you,...
...I promise you,
you're going to wish he hadn't.
Are we clear?
Yes, we're clear, we're clear.
We are so clear.
Good. I can't wait to get started.
Let's begin.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
- Now?
- Yes, now.
Unless you think that the great Oogway was
wrong and you are not the Dragon Warrior.
Okay. Well, I don't know
if I can do all of those moves.
Well, if we don't try,
we will never know, will we?
Yeah, it's just, maybe we can find
something more suited to my level.
- And what level is that?
- Well, you know...
I'm not a master, but
let's just start at zero.
- Level zero.
- No, there is no such thing as level zero.
Hey, maybe I can start with that.
That? We use that for training children
and for popping the door open when it is hot.
But if you insist.
Wow! The Furious Five.
You're so much bigger
than your action figures.
Except for you, Mantis.
You're about the same.
Go ahead, Panda.
Show us what you can do.
Are they going to watch? Or should I just
wait until they get back to work or something?
- Hit it.
- Okay, I mean, I just ate...
...and so I'm still digesting, so my
Kung Fu may not be as good as later on.
Just hit it.
Alright.
What'd you got?
You've got nothing cos' I got it right here.
You picking on my friends?
Get ready to fell the thunder.
Come on, crazy feet.
What're you going to do about crazy feet?
Come on. I'm a blur. I'm a blur.
You've never seen Bear style.
You've only seen Praying Mantis.
Or Monkey style.
Or imagine snake-kiddy Snake.
Would you hit it?
Alright. Alright.
Why don't you try it again?
A little harder.
How's that?...
Oh, that hurts!
This will be easier than I thought.
Feeling a little nausea.
My tenders.
How did I do?
There is now a level zero.
- There is no words.
- Don't denying that.
I don't understand
what Master Oogway was thinking.
- Poor guy is going to get himself killed.
- He is so mighty.
The Dragon Warrior fell out
of the sky in a ball of fire.
When he walks,
the very ground shakes.
One would think that Master Oogway would
choose someone who actually knew Kung Fu.
- Yeah or could at least touch his toes.
- Or even see his toes.
Okay.
Great.
Oh, hey. Hi.
You're up?
- Am now.
- I was just... er... someday... huh?
The Kung Fu stuff is hard work, right?
Your biceps sore.
I've had a long day and rather
disappointing day, so... er...
Yeah... I should probably
get to sleep now.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
- Okay. Thanks.
It's just, I'm...
I'm such a big fan...
You guys were so totally amazing
at the battle of the Weeping River.
Outnumbered a thousand to one.
But, you didn't stop. You just,...
Oh. Sorry about that.
Ahh... Look you don't belong here.
I know, I know.
You're right.
I don't have it.
It's just, my whole life, I dreamed of...
No, no, no. I meant you don't
belong here, I mean in this room.
But this is my room.
Property of Crane.
Oh, okay. Right, right.
So...
Yeah, you want to get to sleep.
I'm keeping you up.
We've got big things tomorrow.
Alright. You are awesome. The last thing
I'm going to say. Okay, bye-bye.
- What was that?
- I didn't say anything.
Okay. Alright. Good night.
Sleep well.
Seem a little bit awkward.
Master Tigress, didn't mean
to wake you. Just a...
- You don't belong here.
- Ah, yeah. Yeah, of course.
- This is your room... - I mean you don't
belong in the Jade Palace.
You're a disgrace to Kung Fu and if
you have any respect of who we are...
...and what we do,
you will be gone by morning.
Big fan.
I see you've found the Sacred
Peach Tree of Heavenly Wisdom.
Is that what this is? I'm so sorry.
I thought it was just a regular peach tree.
I understand.
You eat when you are upset.
Upset? I'm not upset. Why? Why?
What makes you think that I'm upset?
So, why are you upset?
I probably sucked more today
than anyone in the history of Kung Fu.
In the history of China.
In the history of sucking.
Probably.
And the Five... Man, you should have
seen them, they totally hate me.
Totally.
How's Shifu ever going to turn me
into the Dragon Warrior?
I mean, I'm not like the Five.
I've got no claws.
No wings, no venom.
Even Mantis got those thingies.
May be I should just quit
and go back to making noodles.
Quit. Don't quit.
Noodles. Don't noodles.
You are too concerned with
what was and what will be.
There's a saying.
Yesterday is history,
Tomorrow is a mystery,
But today is a gift.
That is why it is called the "present".
- Oh, no!
- What's happening?
To your battle stations!
Go! Go! Go!
- Fire Cross-Bow!
- Fire!
Fire!
Tai Lung's free. I must warn Shifu.
You are not going anywhere.
Neither is he!
- Let go of me.
- Bring it up!
- Wait!
- Bring it back!
- He's going this way.
- He won't get far.
Archers!
We're dead.
So very, very dead.
Not yet, we're not.
Now!
- Can we run now?
- Yes.
I'm glad Shifu sent you.
I was beginning to think
I've been forgotten.
Fly back there and tell them, the real
Dragon Warrior is coming home.
Good Morning, Master.
Panda!
Panda! Wake up!
He's quitted.
What do we do now Master
with the Panda gone?
Who will be the Dragon Warrior?
All we can do is resume your
training and trust that in time...
...the true Dragon Warrior
will be revealed.
What are you doing here?
Hey. Good morning, Master.
I thought I'll warm up a little.
- You're stuck.
- Stuck?...No...What?...Stuck?
No... This is one of the...
Yeah... I'm stuck.
- Help him.
- Oh, dear.
Lift me on three.
One, two,...
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- No, really. I appreciate it...
- Ever.
You actually thought you could
learn to do a full split in one night?
It takes years to develop
ones flexibility.
And years longer
to apply it in combat.
Put that down!
The only souvenirs we collect here
are bloody knuckles and broken bones.
Yeah! Excellent!
Let's get started.
- Are you ready?
- I was born ready...Oww!
I'm sorry brother.
I thought you said you're ready.
That was awesome!
Let's go again!
I've been taking it easy on you Panda
but no more. Your next opponent...
...will be me.
- Alright. Yeah, let's go!
Step forth!
The true path to victory is to find
your opponent's weakness.
And make him suffer for it.
Oh yeah. To take his strength
and use it against him.
Until he finally falls or quits.
But a real warrior never quits.
Don't worry Master, I'll never quit.
If he is smart he won't
come back those steps.
- But he will.
- He's not going to quit, is he?
He's not going to quit bouncing.
I'll tell you that.
I thought you said accupuncture
will make me feel better.
Trust me it will. It's just not easy
finding right nerve points...
...under all this...
- Fat? - Fur!
- I was going to say fur.
- Sure you were.
Who am I to judge a warrior
based on his size?
I mean, look at me.
I'm over here.
Maybe you should take
a look at this again.
Okay.
Ouch!
Stop it! Stop it!
I know Master Shifu is trying
to inspire me and all.
But if I didn't know any better
I'd say he's trying to get rid of me.
I know he can seem like heartless.
But you know he wasn't
always like that.
According to legend there was once a time
when Master Shifu actually used to smile.
- No... - Yes.
- But that was before...
- Before what?
- Before Tai Lung.
Aah... Yeah. We are not really
suppose to talk about him.
Well, if he is going to stay here
he should now.
Guys, guys,
I know about Tai Lung.
He was a student. The first to ever
master the 1000 scrolls of Kung Fu.
And then he turned bad
and now he's in jail.
He wasn't just a student.
Shifu found him as a cub.
And he raised him as his son.
And when the boy showed
talent in Kung Fu...
...Shifu trained him.
He believed in him. He told him
he was destined for greatness.
It was never enough for Tai Lung.
He wanted the Dragon Scroll.
But Oogway saw darkness
in his heart and refused.
Outraged, Tai Lung
laid waste to the Valley.
He tried to take the Scroll by force.
And Shifu had to destroy
what he had created.
But how could he?
Shifu loved Tai Lung like
he had never love anyone before.
Or since.
And now he has a chance
to make things right.
To train the true Dragon Warrior.
And he is stuck with you.
A big fat Panda
who treats it like a joke.
- Ohh... That's it!
- Wait! My fault!
I accidentally tweaked
his facial nerves.
And may have also stopped his heart.
Inner peace.
Inner...in...in...in
inner peace.
Look, whoever is making that
flapping sound, quiet down.
Inner...
Oh, Zeng. Excellent.
I could use some good news right now.
Master. Master.
I... I... have... It's a...
It's a very bad news.
Aah, Shifu. There's just news.
There's no good or bad.
Master, your vision...
Your vision was right.
Tai Lung has broken out of prison.
He's on his way.
That is bad news...
...if you do not believe that
the Dragon Warrior can stop him.
Panda? Master, that Panda
is not the Dragon Warrior.
He wasn't even meant to be here.
It was an accident.
There are no accidents.
Yes, I know.
You said that already.
- Twice.
- Well, that was no accident either.
- Thrice.
- My old friend.
The Panda will never fulfill
his destiny, nor you, yours.
Until you let go of the
illusion of control.
- Illusion?
- Yes.
Look at this tree, Shifu.
I cannot make it blossom
when it suits me.
Nor make it bear
fruit before it's time.
But there are things
we can control.
I can control when
the fruit will fall.
And I can control...
...where to plant the seed.
That is no illusion, Master.
Ah yes, but no matter what you do,
that seed will grow to be a peach tree.
You may wish for
an apple or an orange.
- But you will get a peach.
- But a peach cannot defeat Tai Lung.
Maybe it can, if you are willing
to guide it, to nurture it.
To believe in it.
But how? How?
I need your help, Master.
No, you just need to believe.
Promise me, Shifu.
Promise me, you will believe.
- I... I will try.
- Good.
My time has come.
You must continue your journey
without me.
What?...what?...what are you...
Wait!
Master.
You can't leave me.
You must believe.
Master!
- I'm not scared.
- Yeah. Sound like fun. He maybe a wolf.
You may be the scariest bandit
in Harjin Province.
- But you're a lousy tipper.
- Really.
So, how did you
get out of there alive?
I mean, I didn't actually said that,
but I thought it, in my mind.
If he could read my mind
he would have been like...what?
Order up!
You like it?
This is really good.
Now, come on. You should try
my dad's secret ingredient soup.
He actually knows the secret ingredient.
What are you talking about?
This is amazing.
- Wow, you are really a good cook.
- I wish my mouth was bigger.
Tigress, you got to try
Hmm...
It is said that the Dragon Warrior can
survive for months at a time on nothing...
...but the dew of a single Gingko leaf
and the energy of the universe.
I guess my body doesn't know
it's the Dragon Warrior yet.
I need lot more than dew
and the universe juice.
- What?
- Oh, nothing, Master Shifu.
You will never be the Dragon Warrior
unless you lose 500 pounds...
...and brush your teeth.
What is the noise you're making?
Laughter?
I have never heard of it.
Work hard Panda and maybe someday
you'll have ears like mine.
That's good.
Oh...oh, yup.
Ears?
It's not working for you.
- I thought they're pretty good.
- It's Shifu!
Of course it's Shifu.
What do you think I'm doing?
Master Shifu.
You think this is funny!
Tai Lung has escaped from prison!
- And you all are acting like children!
- What?
He's coming for the Dragon Scroll and
you're the only one who can stop him.
And here I am saying you've
got no a sense of humour.
I am gonna... step down.
What? You're serious?
And I have to... I... No...
Master Oogway will stop him.
- He did it before. He'll do it again.
- Oogway can not!
- Not anymore.
- Ha?
Our only hope is the Dragon Warrior.
- The Panda?
- Yes, the Panda!
Master please, let us stop Tai Lung?
This is what you train us for!
No! It is not your destiny
to defeat Tai Lung! It is his!
Where did he go?
You cannot leave!
A real warrior never quits!
Watch me!
Come on! How am I suppose
to beat Tai Lung?
I can't even beat you to the stairs.
You will beat him because
you are the Dragon Warrior.
You don't believe that!
You never believed that.
From the first moment I got here,
you've been trying to get rid of me.
Yes, I was!
But now I ask you to trust in your Master
as I have come to trust in mine.
You are not my Master.
And I am not the Dragon Warrior.
Then why didn't you quit?
You knew I was trying to get rid of you.
- Yet you stayed.
- Ya. I stayed.
I stayed because every time
you threw a brick at my head...
...or said I smelled, it hurt!
But it could never hurt more than
it did everyday in my life just being me.
I stayed because I thought
if anyone could change me,...
...could make me, not me...
...it was you. The greatest
Kung Fu teacher of all of China.
But I can change you! I can turn
you into the Dragon Warrior. And I will!
Come on, Tai Lung is
on his way right now.
And even if it takes him
a hundred years to get here.
How are you gonna to change this
into the Dragon Warrior?
Hah?
How?
- How?
- I don't know!
I don't know.
That's what I thought.
This is what you trained me for.
Tigress!
Don't try to stop me.
- We are not trying to stop you.
- What?
We are coming with you.
What?
I eat when I am upset, okay!
Oh! No need to explain.
I just thought you might be monkey.
He hides his almond cookies in the top-shelf.
Don't tell Monkey.
Look at you.
- Yeah, I know. I disgust you.
- No, I mean, how did you get up there?
I don't know,... I just...
I don't know. Just get the cookies.
And yet you are 10 feet off the ground
and have done a perfect split.
No, this?
This is just an accident!
There are no accidents.
Come with me.
I know you are trying to be
all mystical and Kung Fu-ey.
But could you least tell me
where we are going?
You drag me all the way
out here for a bath?
Panda, we do not wash our pits
in the pool of sacred tears.
Uuh?...The pool of...
This is where Oogway unraveled
the mysteries of harmony and focus.
This is the birth place of Kung Fu.
- Do you want to learn Kung Fu?
- Yeah.
- Then I am your Master.
- Okay!
- Don't cry.
- Okay.
When you focus on Kung Fu,
when you concentrate, you stink.
But perhaps that is my fault. I cannot
train you the way I've trained the Five.
I now see that the way to get
through to you is with this.
Great, cause I am hungry.
Good, when you have been trained
you may eat.
Let's begin.
After you, Panda.
Just like that?
No setups? No, ten-mile hike?
I vowed to train you and you've been
trained. You are free to eat.
Enjoy.
- Hey!
- I said you are free to eat.
Have a dumpling.
- You are free to eat.
- Am I?
Are you?
I am not hungry.
Master.
Cut it!
- Where is the Dragon Warrior?
- How do you know you are not looking at her?
You think I'm a fool.
I know you are not the Dragon Warrior.
None of you!
I heard how he fell out of the sky
on a ball of fire.
But he's a warrior unlike anything
in the world has ever seen.
- Po?
- So that is his name.
Po!
Finally, a worthy opponent.
Our battle will be legendary.
We got this, help her.
- Monkey!
- Go!
Mantis!
Now!
Shifu, taught you well.
But he didn't teach you everything.
- You have done well, Panda.
- Done well?
Done well!
I have done awesome!
The mark of a true hero is humility.
But yes,
you have done, awesome.
Guys? Guys!
They're dead.
No, they are breathing.
They're asleep?
No, their eyes are open.
We were no match
for his nerve attack.
He has gotten stronger.
Who? Tai Lung?
Stronger?
He's too fast.
Sorry, Po.
- I thought we could stop him.
- He could have kill you.
- Why didn't he?
- So you can come back here...
...and strike fear into our hearts.
But it won't work.
It might. I mean a little.
- I'm pretty scared.
- You can defeat him, Panda.
Are you kidding?
If they can't... They're Five Masters.
I'm just one me.
But you have the one thing
that no one else does.
You really believe I'm ready?
You are, Po.
Behold, the Dragon Scroll.
- It is yours.
- Wait.
- What happens when I read it?
- No one knows.
But legend says you will be able
to hear a butterfly's wings beat.
- Wow! Really? That's cool.
- Yes!
And see light in the deepest cave.
You will feel the universe in motion around you.
Wow! Can I punch through walls?
Can I do a quadruple back flip?
- Focus. Focus. Focus!
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Read it Po,
and fulfill your destiny.
Read it and become the Dragon Warrior.
It's impossible to open.
Come on! Come on, now!
Thank you.
Probably, loosen it up for you.
Okay, here goes.
- It's blank.
- What?
- Here, look.
- No, I am forbidden to look upon...
Blank! I don't...
I don't understand.
Okay. So like Oogway was
just a crazy old turtle after all.
No. Oogway was wiser than us all.
Oh, come on.
Face it. He picked me by accident.
Of course, I'm not Dragon Warrior.
Who am I kidding?
- But who will stop Tai Lung?
- He will destroy everything.
- And everyone.
- No.
Evacuate the Valley.
You must protect the villagers...
...from Tai Lung's rage.
What about you, Master?
- I will fight him.
- What?
I can hold him off long enough
for everyone to escape.
But Shifu, he'll kill you.
Then I would have finally
paid for my mistake.
Listen to me, all of you.
It's time for you to continue
your journey without me.
I am very proud to have
been your master.
We got to get them out safely.
Come little one,
let's find your Mama.
Viper, gather the southern farmers.
Mantis, the north.
Crane, light the way.
Look, it's the Dragon Warrior.
Hey Dad.
Po!
It's good to have you back son.
- Good to be back.
- Let's go, Po.
For our next shop, it's time to face it.
The future of noodles is diced cut vegetables.
No longer slices.
Also, I was thinking...
...maybe this time we'll have
a kitchen you can stand up in.
You like that?
Po, I'm sorry things didn't work out.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Po, forget everything else.
Your destiny still awaits.
We are noodle folk.
Broth runs deep through our veins.
I don't know dad. Honestly, sometimes
I can't believe I'm actually your son.
Po, I think it's time I told you
something I should have told you...
...a long time ago.
Okay.
The secret ingredient of
my secret ingredient soup.
Come near me.
The secret ingredient is...
- Nothing!
- Hah?
You heard me.
Nothing!
There is no secret ingredient.
Wait, wait.
It's just plain old noodle soup?
You don't add some kind
of special sauce or something.
Don't have to.
To make something special...
...you just have to believe
it's special.
There is no secret ingredient.
I have come home, Master.
This is no longer your home
and I am no longer your master.
Yes, you have a new favourite.
So where is this Po?
- Did I scare him off?
- This battle is between you and me.
- So that's how it's going to be.
- That is how it must be.
I rotted in jail for 20 years...
...because of your weakness!
- Obeying your master is not weakness!
You knew I was the Dragon Warrior!
You always knew.
But when Oogway said otherwise...
...what did you do?
What did you do?
- Nothing! - You were not meant
to be the Dragon Warrior.
- That was not my fault!
- Not your fault?
Who filled my head with dreams?
Who drove me to train
until my bones cracked?
Who denied me and my destiny?
It was never my decision to make!
It is now.
- Give me the Scroll.
- I would rather die!
What I ever did,
I did to make you proud!
Tell me how proud you are Shifu!
Tell me!
I...I have always
been proud of you.
From the first moment,
I have been proud of you.
And it was my pride
that blinded me.
I love you too much to see
what you were becoming.
What I was turning you into.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't want your apology.
I want my Scroll.
What?
Where is it?
Dragon Warrior has taken Scroll
half way across China by now.
You will never see
that Scroll, Tai Lung!
Never!
Hey!
Stairs.
Who are you?
Buddy, I am the Dragon Warrior.
You?
Him? He's a Panda.
You're a Panda.
What are you going to do, big guy?
Sit on me.
Don't tempt me.
Now, I'm going to use this.
You want it. Come get it.
Finally.
That Scroll is mine!
The Scroll has given him power.
No!
Finally.
Oh, yes.
The power of the Dragon Scroll
is mine!
It's nothing!
It's okay. I didn't get
it the first time either.
- What?
- There is no secret ingredient.
It's just you.
Stop it! Ho, ho, ho.
I'm going to pee.
Don't! No, don't.
You can't defeat me.
You...
You're just a big
fat Panda!
I'm not a big fat Panda.
I'm the Big Fat Panda!
The Wuxi finger hold?
Oh, you know this hold.
You're bluffing. You're bluffing!
Shifu didn't teach you that!
Nope. I figured it out.
Skadoosh!
Look!
The Dragon Warrior.
That's my boy! The big lovely
Kung Fu warrior is my son!
Yes.
Thanks Dad.
Hey guys.
- Master.
Master?
Master Shifu?
Master!
Shifu! Shifu! Are you okay?
Po.
You are alive.
Or we are both dead.
No Master, I didn't die.
- I defeated Tai Lung.
- You did?
Wow!
It is as Oogway foretold.
You are the Dragon Warrior.
You have brought peace
to this valley.
And to me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Po.
Thank you. Thank you...
No, Master...
No, no, no!
Don't die Shifu, please!
I'm not dying, you idiot!
Aah... Dragon Warrior.
I'm simply at peace.
Finally.
So I should stop talking.
If you can.
Do you want to get
something to eat?
Yes.
Edited by: LittleKea