Po you must take your
next step on your journey
incredible power awaits you
(hayyyyyy)
justice is about to be served
we will have two splatter tigress
did you want extra sauce with that
she wants it on this side
on this side on this side
if you only do what you can do you
will never be more then you are now
I like who I am you
don’t even know who you are?
i am looking for my son?
dad?
give your old
man a hug ahhhh
how do we even know that
he's even related to you?
look at that its like
looking in a fat mirror
come home with me
hi I'm Mei Mei
you must rediscover
what it is to be a panda
yeah
hear we go awesome
(ouuuuuuuuuuu)
there there I'm fine I'm fine there you go
Kai has returned
who?
The master of pain the beast of vengeance
okay I used to work with Oogway
ohhhhh master Oogway silence
you must save the the world
there is no way I can stop him unless you
have an army of your own you don’t even
know kung fu then you will teach us
haiiiii
no one said this was gonna be easy
I'm gonna turn you into kung
fu masters uuuuuu my dendus
the dumpling squadron will take
position hear on my signal
the noodle squadron will
this is the spot where ahhhhhh
OK like saw that coming
this was the one destined to stop me How
about you spare me the chitchat. I'm
going to take your chitchat in the
chitty chitty chat chat in the Chitchat
this is master flying
rhino’s battle armor do
you know what this does?
I should pull it
oooouuuhhhhhhh
I think I just peed a little.
Made By : Madmax 12
Hey Guys Plz Rate