[peaceful music playing]
[narrator] Legend tells
of a legendary warrior...
whose kung fu skills
were the stuff of legend.
He traveled the land
in search of worthy foes.
[laughter, indistinct chattering]
[whimpering]
I see you like to chew.
Maybe you should chew on my fist!
[thud]
[narrator] The warrior said nothing,
for his mouth was full.
Then he swallowed. And then he spoke.
Enough talk. Let's fight!
Shashabooey!
[energetic music playing]
[narrator] He was so deadly in fact,
that his enemies would go blind
from overexposure to pure awesomeness.
-My eyes!
-He's too awesome!
-And attractive.
-How can we repay you?
There is no charge for awesomeness.
-Or attractiveness.
-[girl giggling]
[warrior] Kablooey!
[narrator] It mattered not
how many foes he faced.
They were no match for his bodacity!
[energetic music continues]
[warrior grunts]
[narrator]
Never before had a panda been so feared!
And so loved.
Even the most heroic heroes
in all of China,
the Furious Five,
bowed in respect to this great master.
-We should hang out.
-Agreed.
[all] Yiii!
[narrator]
But hanging out would have to wait.
'Cause when you're facing
the 10,000 demons of Demon Mountain,
there's only one thing
that matters and that's--
Po! Get up!
You'll be late for work!
What? [screams]
-[grunts]
-[thumping]
[yawns]
[Dad] Po! Get up!
[sighs]
[grunting]
[Dad] Hey, Po.
What are you doing up there?
Uh... nothing.
[grunting]
[yells]
Monkey! Mantis! Crane! Viper! Tigress!
[roars]
Uh...
[Dad] Po! Let's go! You're late for work.
Coming!
-[grunting]
-[thumping]
-Sorry, Dad.
-Sorry doesn't make the noodles.
What were you doing up there?
All that noise.
Oh, nothing. Just, uh, had a crazy dream.
-About what?
-Huh?
What were you dreaming about?
What was I...? Uh...
I was dreaming about uh...
uh...
-noodles.
-Noodles?
You were really dreaming about noodles?
Uh... yeah. What else
would I be dreaming about?
Oh! Careful! That soup is sharp.
Oh, happy day! My son, finally
having the noodle dream!
[sobbing]
You don't know how long
I've been waiting for this moment.
-This is a sign, Po.
-Uh, a sign of what?
You are almost ready to be entrusted
with the secret ingredient
of my Secret Ingredient Soup.
And then you will fulfil your destiny
and take over the restaurant!
Just as I took it over from my father,
who took it over from his father,
who won it from a friend
in a game of mahjong.
Dad, Dad, Dad,
it was just a dream. [chuckles]
No, it was the dream.
We are noodle folk.
Broth runs through our veins.
But Dad, didn't you ever,
I don't know, want to do something else?
Something besides noodles?
Actually, when I was young and crazy,
I thought about running away
and learning how to make tofu.
-So why didn't you?
-Oh, because it was a stupid dream.
[scoffs] Can you imagine me making tofu?
[laughing] Tofu.
No! We all have our place in this world.
Mine is here, and yours is--
I know, is here.
No, it's at table two, five, seven
and 12.
Service with a smile.
[gong sounding]
-[Po sighing]
-[flute playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
Well done, students...
if you were trying to disappoint me.
Tigress, you need more ferocity!
Monkey, greater speed.
Crane, height.
Viper, subtlety. Mantis--
-Master Shifu. [gasps]
-[Shifu] What?!
[Zeng] It-- It's Master Oogway.
He wants to see you.
[pants, exhales slowly]
Master Oogway, you summoned me?
Is something wrong?
Why must something be wrong for
me to want to see my old friend?
So, nothing's wrong?
Well, I didn't say that.
[continues blowing out candles]
You were saying?
I have had a vision.
Tai Lung will return.
-[growling]
-[menacing music playing]
That is impossible! He is in prison.
Nothing is impossible.
Zeng! Fly to Chorh-Gom Prison
and tell them to double the guards,
double their weapons, double everything!
Tai Lung does not leave that prison!
Yes, Master Shifu! [squawks]
One often meets his destiny
on the road he takes to avoid it.
We have to do something!
We can't let him march on the valley
and take his revenge!
-He'll-- He'll--
-Your mind is like this water, my friend.
When it is agitated,
it becomes difficult to see.
But if you allow it to settle...
[whispers] ...the answer becomes clear.
[peaceful music playing]
[Shifu] The Dragon Scroll.
It is time.
But who? Who is worthy to be trusted
with the secret to limitless power?
To become the Dragon Warrior?
I don't know.
[Po] Excuse me. Pardon me. Sorry.
-Oh! Oh! Sorry. Sorry.
-Hey, watch it, Po!
-Suck it up!
-[babies crying]
Ooh. Sorry. A thousand pardons.
-[gong sounding]
-What?
Master Oogway's choosing
the Dragon Warrior! Today!
Everyone! Everyone! Go!
Get to the Jade Palace!
One of the Five is gonna
get the Dragon Scroll!
We've been waiting 1,000 years for this!
Just take the bowl!
This is the greatest day
in kung fu history!
-Don't worry about it, just go!
-[Dad] Po! Where are you going?
To the Jade Palace.
But you're forgetting your noodle cart.
The whole valley will be there,
and you'll sell noodles to all of them.
Selling noodles?
But Dad, you know, I was kinda thinking,
-maybe I--
-Yeah?
-I was kinda thinking maybe I...
-Uh-huh?
...could also sell the bean buns.
They're-- They're about to go bad.
That's my boy!
I told you that dream was a sign.
Yeah... [chuckles] Glad I had it.
[up-tempo music plays]
-[bunny] Yippee! Me too!
-I'm a kung fu warrior!
-There's spots at the top.
-Let's go.
[gulps, grunts]
[wheels squeaking]
[grunting, panting]
Come on. Come on!
Almost there.
What?
No! Oh, no! [groans]
-Sorry, Po.
-We'll bring you back a souvenir.
[firework whizzes, bangs]
No. I'll bring me back a souvenir.
[energetic music playing]
It is an historic day.
Isn't it, Master Oogway?
Yes, and one I feared
I would not live to see.
Are your students ready?
Yes, Master Oogway.
Now, know this, old friend.
Whomever I choose
will not only bring peace to the valley,
but also to you.
-[announcer] Let the tournament begin!
-[cheering]
[Po grunting]
[groans]
Yeah. [chuckles]
-[door creaking]
-Oh, no! No, no, no, wait!
I'm coming! Wait, wait! Yes!
-Ow!
-[crowd cheering]
Hey! Open the door!
[energetic music plays]
Let me in!
[Shifu] Citizens of the Valley of Peace...
[Po] Come on.
-...it is my great honor...
-[Po] Okay.
...to present to you, Tigress!
Viper! Crane! Monkey! Mantis!
-The Furious Five!
-[chortles]
Yeah, the Furious Five!
[grunts]
[Shifu] Warriors, prepare!
What? No. Oh, peeky-hole.
-[Shifu] Ready for battle!
-[Po] Yeah. Whoo!
The Thousand Tongues of Fire. [chuckles]
-[fan] Whoa! Look at that.
-Hey, get out of the way!
Oh! [laughs]
[screams]
[grunts]
[moaning]
-[upbeat music playing]
-[crowd cheers]
[grunts] Ow!
Oh...
Oh! [groans]
[crowd cheering]
[Shifu] And finally, Master Tigress!
Believe me, citizens,
you have not seen anything yet.
I know!
[Shifu] Master Tigress,
face Iron Ox and his Blades of Death.
[Po laughing]
[groans]
[crowd gasps]
I sense the Dragon Warrior is among us.
Citizens of the Valley of Peace,
Master Oogway will now choose
the Dragon Warrior!
Huh? Oh, no! No, no, no, wait!
Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
[laughing]
-[match sparks]
-[chuckles]
Oh, Po! What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing? Stop!
Stop! I'm going to see the Dragon Warrior!
But I don't understand.
You finally had the noodle dream!
I lied. I don't dream about noodles, Dad.
I love kung fu!
[groans]
[sniffles]
Oh, come on, son. Let's get back to work.
[sighs deeply] Okay.
-[fireworks whooshing]
-[screams]
-Po!
-[chuckles]
Oh! Come back!
[screaming]
[all] Oooh. Ahh.
[screams ]
Uh-oh.
[Po groans] What's going on?
Where, uh...?
What are you pointing...?
Oh! Okay, Sorry.
I just wanted to see
who the Dragon Warrior was.
How interesting.
Master, are-- are you pointing at me?
-[Oogway] Him.
-Who?
-You.
-Me?
The universe has brought us
the Dragon Warrior!
-What?
-[both] What?
[up-tempo music plays]
[crowd chanting]
Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
-Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
-Stop, wait! Who told you to...
[crowd] Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
[straining]
Master Oogway, wait.
That flabby panda can't possibly
be the answer to our problem.
You were about to point at Tigress,
and that thing fell in front of her!
That was just an accident!
There are no accidents.
[grunting]
[straining]
Forgive us, Master.
-We have failed you.
-[Shifu] No.
If the panda has not quit by morning,
then I will have failed you.
[Zeng grunting]
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I bring a message...
from Master Shifu.
What? "Double the guard.
"Extra precautions."
"Your prison may not be adequate."
[chuckling nervously]
You doubt my prison security?
Absolutely not.
Shifu does. I'm just the messenger.
I'll give you a message
for your Master Shifu.
Escape from Chorh-Gom Prison
is impossible!
-Oh! Oooh!
-[laughs]
Impressive, isn't it?
It's very impressive.
It's-- It's very impressive.
One way in, one way out.
One thousand guards and one prisoner.
Yes, except that prisoner is Tai Lung.
Take us down.
-[Zeng] What are you doing?
-[laughing]
Oh, my...
-[chains clanking]
-[Zeng chuckling nervously]
[commander] Behold Tai Lung.
I'll, um...
I'm just gonna wait right here.
It's nothing to worry about.
It's perfectly safe.
-Crossbows! At the ready!
-[Zeng] Crossbows?
Hey, tough guy, did you hear?
Oogway's finally gonna
give someone the Dragon Scroll,
and it's not gonna be you.
What are you doing? Don't get him mad!
What's he gonna do about it?
I've got him completely immobilized.
[laughs] Aw!
Did I step on the witty kitty's tail? Aw.
I'm good. I've seen enough.
I'm gonna tell Shifu
he's got nothing to worry about.
-No, he doesn't.
-Okay, I'll tell him that.
Can we please go now?
[crowd chanting] Dragon Warrior!
Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
[groans] Wait a second!
[chuckles]
I think there's been a slight mistake.
Everyone seems to think that I'm, uh...
Ooh! The Sacred Hall of Warriors! No way!
Look at this place. [gasps]
Master Flying Rhino's armor,
with authentic battle damage!
Whoa!
The Sword of Heroes!
Said to be so sharp
you can cut yourself just by looking. Ow!
[gasps] The Invisible Trident of Destiny!
I've only seen paintings of that painting.
[giddy laughter]
[gasps] No!
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho!
The legendary Urn of Whispering Warriors.
Said to contain the souls
of the entire Tenshu Army.
Hello.
[Shifu] Have you finished sight-seeing?
Sorry, I should have
come to see you first.
-[Shifu] My patience is wearing thin.
-Oh.
Well, I mean,
it's not like you were going anywhere.
-[Shifu] Would you turn around?
-Sure.
Hey. How's it going? How do you get five--
Master Shifu!
-Oh!
-[moaning emanating from urn]
Someone broke that.
But I'm gonna fix it. I'll-- I'll--
Do you have some...
-...glue?
-[moaning emanating from urn]
[Po] Ow! Ow. Oh, I have a splinter.
So, you're the legendary
Dragon Warrior, hmm?
-Uh, I guess so.
-Wrong!
You are not the Dragon Warrior.
You will never be the Dragon Warrior
until you have learned
the secret of the Dragon Scroll.
Whoa.
So, um, how does this work?
Do you have a ladder,
or a trampoline, or...
[chuckles] You think it's that easy?
That I'm just gonna hand you the secret
-to limitless power?
-No, I--
One must first master
the highest level of kung fu.
And that is clearly impossible
if that one is someone like you.
-Someone like me?
-Yes, look at you!
-This fat butt! Flabby arms!
-Ouch!
Those are sensitive in the flabby parts.
-And this ridiculous belly.
-Hey!
And utter disregard for personal hygiene.
Now, wait a minute. That's uncalled for.
Don't stand that close.
I can smell your breath.
Listen, Oogway said I was the--
The Wuxi Finger Hold.
Not the Wuxi Finger Hold!
Oh, you know this hold?
Developed by Master Wuxi
in the Third Dynasty. Yes.
Oh. Then you know what happens
when I flex my pinky.
-[gasping] No, no, no!
-You know the hardest part of this?
The hardest part
is cleaning up afterwards. [chuckles]
Okay, okay, take it easy.
Now listen closely, panda.
Oogway may have picked you,
but when I'm through with you,
I promise you,
you're going to wish he hadn't!
Are we clear?
Yeah, we're clear.
We're clear. We're so clear.
Good. [chuckles]
I can't wait to get started.
[Furious Five grunting]
[grunting continues]
[grunting]
[grunts]
Ow! Ooh! Ow!
-Let's begin.
-Wait, wait, wait.
W-- What?
-Now?
-Yes, now.
Unless you think
the great Oogway was wrong,
and you are not the Dragon Warrior.
Oh, okay, well...
I-- I don't know if I can--
I can do all of those moves.
Well, if we don't try,
we'll never know, will we?
Yeah, it's just,
maybe we can find something
-more suited to my level.
-And what level is that?
Well, you know,
I... I'm not a master, but, uh,
let's just start at zero. Level zero.
[chuckles] No.
There is no such thing as level zero.
-Hey, maybe I can start with that.
-That?
We use that for training children.
And for propping the door open
when it's hot.
But if you insist...
[Po] Whoa. The Furious Five!
You're so much bigger
than your action figures.
Except for you, Mantis.
You're about the same.
Go ahead, panda.
Show us what you can do.
Are they gonna watch? Or should I wait
till they get back to work?
-Hit it.
-Okay, yeah. I mean, I just ate.
Um... So I'm still digesting.
So my kung fu might not
be as good as... later on.
Just hit it.
All right. What you got?
You got nothing,
'cause I got it right here.
You picking on my friends?
Get ready to feel the thunder.
I'm coming out with crazy feet.
What you gonna do about crazy feet?
Come on. I'm a blur.
You've never seen bear style.
You've only seen praying mantis.
Or monkey style. [screeching]
Or I could come at you snickety-snake.
-Would you hit it!
-All right. All right.
Why don't you try again? A little harder.
How's that--
Whoa!
-[all gasp]
-[moaning]
Ow, that hurts!
[screams in slow-motion]
This will be easier than I thought.
I'm feeling a little nauseous!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Oh. Ow, those are hard!
[moans]
My tenders.
[groans]
Uh-oh. [yells]
[groaning]
How did I do?
There is now a level zero.
-[Mantis] There's no words.
-[Crane] No denying that.
[Viper] I don't understand
What was Master Oogway thinking?
The poor guy's
just gonna get himself killed.
[mocking] He is so mighty!
The Dragon Warrior
fell out of the sky on a ball of fire!
-When he walks, the very ground shakes!
-[all laugh]
One would think that Master Oogway
would choose someone
who actually knew kung fu.
Yeah, or could at least touch his toes.
-Or even see his toes.
-[laughter]
[straining]
[Po] Ow!
-Okay.
-[floor squeaking]
Great.
[wood breaking]
-Oh, hey. Hi. You're up?
-Am now.
I was just, uh...
Someday, huh?
That kung fu stuff is hard work, right?
-Are your biceps sore?
-Um...
I've had a long, a--
and rather disappointing day, so, uh...
Yeah, I should probably get to sleep now.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course.
-OK, thanks.
It's just...
Man, I'm such a big fan!
You guys were amazing
at the Battle of Weeping River.
Outnumbered a thousand to one,
but you didn't stop. You just--
-[grunts]
-[wall rips]
Oh. Sorry about that.
Look, you don't belong here.
I know. I know. You're right.
I don't have-- I just...
My whole life I dreamed of...
No, no, no.
I-- I meant you don't belong here.
I mean, in this room. This is my room.
Property of Crane.
Oh. Okay. Right, right.
[clears throat] So, yeah,
you want to get to sleep.
-Yeah.
-I'm keeping you up.
We got big things tomorrow.
All right. You're awesome.
Last thing I'm gonna say. Okay, Bye-bye.
[sighs]
What was that?
I didn't say anything.
Okay, all right. Good night. Sleep well.
That seemed a little bit awkward.
Master Tigress!
Didn't mean to wake you. Just--
-You don't belong here.
-Yeah, yeah. Of course, this is your room.
I mean, you don't belong
in the Jade Palace.
You're a disgrace to kung fu,
and if you have any respect for who we are
and what we do,
you will be gone by morning.
Big fan!
I see you have found
the Sacred Peach Tree of Heavenly Wisdom.
Oh!
Is that what this is? I am so sorry.
I thought it was just
a regular peach tree.
I understand. You eat when you are upset.
Upset? I'm not upset.
W-- W-- What makes you think I'm upset?
So, why are you so upset?
[exhales] I probably sucked more today
than anyone in the history of kung fu.
In the history of China.
In the history of sucking!
-Probably.
-And the Five!
Man, you should've seen them!
They totally hate me.
Totally.
How is Shifu ever going
to turn me into the Dragon Warrior?
I mean, I'm not like the Five.
I've got no claws, no wings, no venom.
Even Mantis has those... thingies.
Maybe I should just quit
and go back to making noodles.
Quit, don't quit.
Noodles, don't noodles.
You are too concerned
with what was and what will be.
There's a saying...
"Yesterday is history,
tomorrow is a mystery,
but today is a gift."
"That is why it is called the present."
[breathing deeply]
[grunting]
-Oh, no!
-What's happening?
[man] To your battle stations! Go! Go! Go!
[snarling]
Fire crossbows! Fire!
Fire!
Tai Lung is free! I must warn Shifu.
You're not going anywhere
and neither is he!
-Let go of me!
-Bring it up!
Wait! Bring it back!
[neck cracking]
-He's coming this way!
-He won't get far. Archers!
[both laughing]
-[indistinct shouting]
-[snarling]
[snarling]
[both growling]
[shrieks]
We're dead. So very, very dead.
[laughs] Not yet we're not. Now!
-[roars]
-[all gasp]
[laughing]
-Can we run now?
-Yes.
[all screaming]
[groans]
[gulps]
[exhales deeply] I'm glad Shifu sent you.
I was beginning to think
I'd been forgotten.
Fly back there and tell them...
the real Dragon Warrior is coming home.
[shuddering, panting]
[all] Good morning, Master!
Panda! Panda!
Wake up!
[chortling] He's quit.
What do we do now, Master,
with the panda gone?
Who will be the Dragon Warrior?
All we can do is resume our
training and trust that in time,
the true Dragon Warrior will be revealed.
What are you doing here?
Hi! Good morning, Master!
I thought I'd warm up a little.
[straining]
You're stuck.
Stuck? Nah. What? Stuck?
[scoffs] Nah.
This is one of my-- Yeah, I'm stuck.
-Help him.
-Oh, dear.
[Po] Yeah, maybe on three. One, two...
three.
-Thank you.
-Don't mention it.
-No, really, I appreciate--
-Ever.
You actually thought you could learn
to do a full split in one night?
It takes years
to develop one's flexibility!
And years longer to apply it in combat!
Ooh...
Put that down!
The only souvenirs we collect here
are bloody knuckles and broken bones.
Yeah! [chuckling] Excellent.
Let's get started.
-[Viper] Are you ready?
-I was born re--
Ow! [grunts]
I'm sorry, brother.
I thought you said you were ready.
That was awesome! Let's go again!
Ow! Oh!
[shrieks]
[groans]
[grunting] Ow!
[Shifu chuckles]
I've been taking it easy on you, panda.
But no more.
Your next opponent will be me.
All right! Yeah, let's go!
Step forth.
The true path to victory
is to find your opponent's weakness
and make him suffer for it.
Oh, yeah!
To take his strength
and use it against him...
until he finally falls...
-or quits.
-[nasally] But a real warrior never quits.
Don't worry, Master. I will never quit!
[screams]
Ow! Ow!
If he's smart,
he won't come back up those steps.
But he will.
-He's not gonna quit, is he?
-[Po grunting]
He's not going to quit bouncing,
I'll tell you that.
[laughs]
[Po] Oh! Ooh! Ah! Ooh!
[exclaiming]
Ow! I thought you said acupuncture
would make me feel better.
Trust me, it will. It's just not easy
finding the right nerve points
-under all this, um--
-Fat?
Fur. I was going to say fur.
-Sure you were.
-Who am I to judge a warrior
based on his size? I mean, look at me.
-I'm over here.
-Ah-ha!
Maybe you should look at this again.
Oh, okay.
[Po] Ow! [laughing]
Stop it. Stop!
-Ow!
-[gasps]
I know Master Shifu
is trying to inspire me and all,
but if I didn't know any better,
I'd say he was trying to get rid of me.
[laughing]
I know he can seem kind of heartless...
but, you know, he wasn't always like that.
According to legend, there was once a time
when Master Shifu actually used to smile.
-[Po] No!
-[Mantis] Yes.
[Viper] But that was before.
Before what?
Before Tai Lung.
[Crane] Yeah, we're not really supposed
to talk about him.
Well, if he's going to stay here,
he should know.
Guys, guys, I know about Tai Lung.
He was a student.
The first ever to master
the Thousand Scrolls of kung fu.
And then he turned bad,
and now he's in jail and...
He wasn't just a student.
Shifu found him as a cub...
...and he raised him as his son.
And when the boy showed talent in
kung fu...
Shifu trained him.
He believed in him.
He told him he was destined for greatness.
It was never enough for Tai Lung.
He wanted the Dragon Scroll.
But Oogway saw darkness
in his heart and refused.
Outraged, Tai Lung
laid waste to the valley.
He tried to take the scroll by force.
And Shifu had to destroy
what he had created.
But how could he?
[panting]
[Tigress] Shifu loved Tai Lung
like he had never loved anyone before.
Or since.
And now he has a chance
to make things right.
To train the true Dragon Warrior.
And he's stuck with you.
A big fat panda who treats it like a joke.
-Oh, that is it!
-Wait! My fault!
I accidentally tweaked his facial nerve.
And may have also stopped his heart.
[Shifu] Inner peace.
Inner peace.
Inner-- In-- In...
In-- In-- Inner peace.
Would whoever is making
that flapping sound quiet down?
Inner--
-[squawks]
-Hmm...
Oh, Zeng.
Excellent.
I could use some good news right now.
Uh...
-Master! Master!
-[Oogway] Hmm?
I-- I-- I have-- It's--
It's very bad news.
Ah, Shifu.
There is just news.
There is no good or bad.
Master, your vision.
Your vision was right.
Tai Lung has broken out of prison.
He's on his way.
That is bad news...
if you do not believe
that the Dragon Warrior can stop him.
The panda? Master, that panda
is not the Dragon Warrior.
He wasn't meant to be here!
It was an accident.
There are no accidents.
[sighing heavily] Yes, I know.
You've said that already.
-Twice.
-Well, that was no accident, either.
-Thrice.
-My old friend,
the panda will never fulfill
his destiny, nor you yours,
until you let go
of the illusion of control.
Illusion?
Yes. Look at this tree, Shifu.
I cannot make it blossom when it suits me,
nor make it bear fruit before its time.
But there are things we can control.
I can control
when the fruit will fall. [grunts]
[chuckles]
And I can control...
[grunts]
...where to plant the seed.
That is no illusion, Master.
Ah, yes.
But no matter what you do
that seed will grow to be a peach tree.
You may wish for an apple or an orange,
but you will get a peach.
But a peach cannot defeat Tai Lung!
Maybe it can.
If you are willing to guide it.
To nurture it.
To believe in it.
But how? How?
I need your help, Master.
No, you just need to believe.
Promise me, Shifu.
Promise me you will believe.
I... I will try.
Good.
My time has come.
You must continue your journey without me.
What-- What-- What-- What are you-- Wait!
Master!
You can't leave me!
You must believe.
Master!
[Po] Yeah, so I'm like,
"Fine, you may be a wolf,
you may be the scariest bandit
in Haijin Province...
-but you're a lousy tipper."
-Really?
So, how did you get out of there alive?
I mean-- I mean,
I didn't actually say that...
but I thought it, in-- in my mind.
If he could read my mind,
he'd have been, like, "What?"
Order up! Hope you like it.
This is really good!
No, come on. You should try
my dad's Secret Ingredient Soup.
He actually knows the secret ingredient.
What do you talking about?
This is amazing!
[Crane] Wow, you're a good cook.
-[Mantis] I wish my mouth was bigger.
-Tigress, you've got to try this.
It is said that the Dragon Warrior
can survive for months at a time,
on nothing but the dew
of a single ginkgo leaf
and the energy of the universe.
I guess my body doesn't know
it's the Dragon Warrior yet.
I'm gonna need a lot more than dew
and, uh, universe juice.
[all laughing]
-What?
-Oh, nothing... Master Shifu.
[all laughing]
[imitating Shifu] You'll never be the
Dragon Warrior unless you lose 500 pounds
-and brush your teeth!
-[laughter]
What is that noise you're making?
Laughter? I never heard of it!
Work hard, panda, and maybe someday...
you will have ears like mine.
-That's good.
-[laughter stops]
Ears. It's not working for you?
I thought they were pretty good.
It's Shifu!
Of course it's Shifu.
What do you think I'm doing?
Ooh! Master Shifu!
[laughter]
[Shifu] You think this is funny?
Tai Lung has escaped,
and you're acting like children!
-What?
-He is coming for the Dragon Scroll,
and you are the only one who can stop him.
[laughs] And here I am,
saying you got no sense of humor.
I'm gonna... stop Tai Lung.
What? You're serious? And I have to...
M-- Master Oogway will stop him!
He-- He did before.
-He'll do it again.
-Oogway cannot!
-Not anymore.
-[all gasping]
Our only hope is the Dragon Warrior.
-The panda?
-Yes, the panda!
Master, please! Let us stop Tai Lung.
This is what you've trained us for.
No! It is not your destiny
to defeat Tai Lung.
It is his!
Where'd he go?
[screaming]
You cannot leave!
A real warrior never quits.
Watch me.
Come on.
How am I supposed to beat Tai Lung?
I can't even beat you to the stairs.
You will beat him
because you are the Dragon Warrior.
Ow! You don't believe that.
Oh! You never believed that.
From the first moment I got here,
you've been trying to get rid of me.
Yes! I was.
But now I ask you to trust in your master
as I have come to trust in mine.
[grunts] You're not my master.
And I'm not the Dragon Warrior.
Then why didn't you quit?
You knew I was trying to get rid of you,
yet you stayed.
Yeah, I stayed.
I stayed because every time
you threw a brick at my head
or said I smelled, it hurt...
but it could never hurt more
than it did every day
of my life just being me.
I stayed because I thought,
if anyone could change me...
could make me, not me...
it was you!
The greatest kung fu teacher
in all of China!
But I can change you!
I can turn you into the Dragon Warrior!
-And I will!
-Come on.
Tai Lung is on his way here right now.
And even if it takes him
a hundred years to get here,
how are you gonna change this
into the Dragon Warrior, huh?
How?
-How?!
-I don't know!
I don't know.
[dramatic music playing]
That's what I thought.
This is what you trained me for.
[Viper] Tigress!
Don't try and stop me.
[Viper] We're not trying to stop you.
-What?
-We're coming with you!
[dramatic music concludes]
[peaceful music playing]
[Po yelling]
[yelling continues]
[Po burps]
What? I eat when I'm upset, okay?
Oh. No need to explain.
I just thought you might be Monkey.
He hides his almond cookies
on the top shelf.
[gasps]
[dishes clattering]
Don't tell Monkey.
-Look at you.
-Yeah, I know, I disgust you.
No, no! I mean, how did you get up there?
I don't know, I...
I guess... I don't know.
I was getting a cookie.
And yet you are ten feet off the ground.
And have done a perfect spilt.
No, this? This is just a...
accident.
-[exclaims]
-[crashing]
There are no accidents.
Come with me.
[Po panting heavily]
I know you're trying to be
all mystical and kung fuey...
but could you at least
tell me where we're going?
[panting heavily]
You dragged me...
all the way out here...
for a bath?
Panda, we do not wash our pits
in the Pool of Sacred Tears.
Huh? The Pool of...
This is where Oogway
unraveled the mysteries
of harmony and focus.
This is the birthplace...
of kung fu.
[gasps]
-Do you want to learn kung fu?
-Yeah!
Then I am your master!
Okay! [sniffs]
-Don't cry.
-Okay. [sniffles]
When you focus on kung fu,
when you concentrate... you stink.
But, perhaps, that is my fault.
I cannot train you
the way I have trained the Five.
I now see that the way
to get through to you...
is with this.
Oh, great, 'cause I am hungry.
[chuckles] Good.
When you have been trained, you may eat.
Let us begin.
[Po grunting]
Whoa! Oh... [yells]
[exclaims]
[grunts]
Ow!
Yah!
-[Shifu] After you, panda.
-Just like that?
No sit-ups? No-- No-- No--
No ten-mile hike?
I vowed to train you,
and you have been trained.
You are free to eat.
Enjoy.
-Hey!
-[munching]
I said you are free to eat.
Have a dumpling.
Hey!
You are free to eat.
-Am I?
-Are you?
[exclaims]
[laughs]
[Po] Whoo!
Ow! Ow!
[both grunting]
[panting]
[chortles]
I'm not hungry.
Master.
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[growls]
Cut it!
Where's the Dragon Warrior?
How do you know you're not looking at her?
[laughs] You think I'm a fool?
I know you're not the Dragon Warrior.
None of you!
I heard how he fell out
of the sky on a ball of fire.
That he's a warrior
unlike anything the world has ever seen.
-Po?
-So that is his name. Po.
Finally, a worthy opponent.
-Our battle will be legendary!
-[snarling]
-[grunts]
-[shouts]
We've got this. Help her.
-Monkey!
-Go!
What was I thinking?
[groans]
Mantis!
Now!
-[screams]
-[grunts]
[crashing]
-[all gasping]
-Shifu taught you well.
But he didn't teach you everything.
[Shifu] You have done well, panda.
Done well? Done well?
I've done awesome!
The mark of a true hero is humility.
-But, yes, you have done...
-Ow!
...awesome.
[both laughing]
-[footsteps approaching]
-Huh?
Guys? Guys! They're dead!
No, they're breathing.
They're asleep? No, their eyes are open.
We were no match for his nerve attack.
He has gotten stronger.
Who? Tai Lung? Stronger?
-Ow!
-He's too fast! Sorry, Po.
-I thought we could stop him.
-He could have killed you.
Why didn't he?
So you could come back here
and strike fear into our hearts.
-But it won't work.
-Uh, it might. I mean, a little.
I'm-- I'm pretty scared.
You can defeat him, panda!
Are you kidding? If they can't--
They're five masters. I'm just one me.
But you will have the one thing
that no one else does.
You really believe I'm ready?
You are.
Po.
Behold, the Dragon Scroll.
It is yours.
Wait. What happens when I read it?
No one knows.
But legend says you will be able
to hear a butterfly's wing beat.
Whoa. Really? That's cool.
Yes. And see light in the deepest cave.
You will feel the universe
in motion around you.
Wow! Can I punch through walls?
Can I-- Can I--
Can I do a quadruple back flip?
-Focus. Focus.
-Will I have invisibility--
-Focus.
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
Read it, Po, and fulfill your destiny.
Read it and become...
the Dragon Warrior.
Whoa!
[straining]
It's impossible to open.
Okay. Come on, baby. Come on now.
-[top pops]
-Thank you.
I probably loosened it up for you though.
[clears throat] Okay, here goes.
-[screaming]
-[all gasp]
-It's blank.
-What?
-Here, look.
-No!
I am forbidden to look upon...
Blank. I don't...
I don't understand.
Okay. So, like,
Oogway was just
a crazy old turtle after all.
No. Oogway was wiser than us all.
Oh, come on! Face it,
he picked me by accident.
Of course I'm not the Dragon Warrior.
Who am I kidding?
[Tigress] But who will stop Tai Lung?
[Crane] He'll destroy
everything and everyone.
No.
Evacuate the valley.
You must protect the villagers
from Tai Lung's rage.
-What about you, Master?
-I will fight him.
-What?
-I can hold him off long enough
-for everyone to escape.
-But Shifu, he'll kill you.
Then I will finally have paid
for my mistake.
Listen to me, all of you.
It is time for you
to continue your journey without me.
I am very proud to have been your master.
We've got to get them out safely.
Come, little one. Let's find your mama.
Viper, gather the southern farmers.
Mantis, the north. Crane, light the way.
[mocking] Look, it's the Dragon Warrior.
[exhales deeply]
Hey, Dad.
Po!
Good to have you back, son.
Good to be back.
Let's go, Po.
So for our next shop, it's time to face it
the future of noodles
is dice-cut vegetables,
no longer slices.
Also, I was thinking, maybe this time
we'll have a kitchen
you can actually stand up in.
You like that?
Po, I-- I-- I'm sorry
if things didn't work out.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Po, forget everything else.
Your destiny still awaits.
We are noodle folk.
Broth runs deep through our veins.
I don't know, Dad.
Honestly, sometimes I can't
believe I'm actually your son.
[chuckles] Po...
I think it's time I told you something
I should have told you...
a long time ago.
Okay.
The secret ingredient
of my Secret Ingredient Soup.
Oh.
Come-- come here.
The secret ingredient is...
-nothing.
-Huh?
You heard me. Nothing!
There is no secret ingredient!
Wait, wait.
It's just plain old noodle soup?
You don't add some kind of
special sauce or something?
Don't have to.
To make something special,
you just have to believe it's special.
There is no secret ingredient.
[thunderclap]
[thunder rumbling]
I have come home, Master.
This is no longer your home.
And I am no longer your master.
Oh, yes. You have a new favorite.
So, where is this Po?
[chuckles] Did I scare him off?
This battle is between you and me.
So, that is how it's going to be.
That is how it must be.
[growling]
[shouting]
I rotted in jail for 20 years
because of your weakness!
Obeying your master is not weakness!
You knew I was the Dragon Warrior.
You always knew.
But when Oogway said otherwise,
what did you do?
What did you do?
Nothing!
You were not meant
to be the Dragon Warrior!
That was not my fault!
Not your fault?
Who filled my head with dreams?
Who drove me to train
until my bones cracked?!
Who denied me my destiny?
-It was never my decision to make!
-[snarls]
It is now.
Give me the scroll!
I would rather die.
[straining, grunts]
[both shouting]
[snarls]
All I ever did, I did to make you proud!
Tell me how proud you are, Shifu!
-Tell me!
-[grunting]
Tell me!
I have-- I have always been proud of you.
From the first moment,
I've been... proud of you.
And it was my pride...
that blinded me.
I loved you too much
to see what you were becoming.
What I...
was turning you into.
I'm s...
I'm sorry.
[snarling]
I don't want your apology.
I want my scroll!
What? Where is it?
Dragon Warrior has taken scroll
halfway across China by now.
You will never see that scroll, Tai Lung.
Never.
[straining] Never.
[Po] Hey!
[breathing heavily]
Stairs.
Who are you?
Buddy, I am the Dragon Warrior.
[pants]
You? [chuckles]
Him? He's a panda.
You're a panda. What are you
gonna do, big guy? Sit on me?
Don't tempt me. No.
I'm gonna use this.
You want it? Come and get it.
-Oh!
-Finally!
[chuckles]
Yaaa! Whoo!
-[growling]
-Ooh... [screams]
-[snarls]
-[chuckles]
That scroll is mine!
[both grunting]
Oh!
[screaming]
[crashing]
Whoa!
Lightning! Whoo!
Aah! [chortling]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[Tai Lung] The scroll has given him power!
No!
-Oh!
-[growls]
[panting]
Finally! Oh, yes.
The power of the Dragon Scroll is mine!
It's nothing!
It's okay.
I didn't get it the first time, either.
What?
There is no secret ingredient.
It's just you.
-[roars]
-[screams]
[laughs]
Stop it!
I'm gonna pee.
[laughing] Don't.
-Don't! Don't!
-[grunts]
[meows]
[roars]
Oh!
[roaring]
[screaming]
You...
can't defeat me.
you're just a big...
fat...
panda!
I'm not a big fat panda.
I'm the big fat panda.
The Wuxi Finger Hold!
Oh, you know this hold?
You're bluffing. You're bluffing.
Shifu didn't teach you that.
[Po] Nope.
I figured it out. Skadoosh!
-[all gasping]
-[wind howling]
[chattering indistinctly]
Oh, look!
The Dragon Warrior.
[coughs]
[all cheering]
[crowd chanting] Dragon Warrior!
Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
That's my boy! That big lovely
kung fu warrior is my son!
Yes!
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, guys.
Master.
[all] Master.
Master?
Master Shifu!
[Po panting]
Master!
Shifu, Shifu? Are you okay?
[grunts] Po.
You're alive.
-Or we're both dead.
-No, Master, I didn't die.
-I defeated Tai Lung.
-You did?
Wow.
It is as Oogway foretold.
You are the Dragon Warrior.
You have brought peace...
to this valley...
and...
and to me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Po.
Thank you. Thank you.
No! Master!
No, no, no,
don't die, Shifu, please!
I'm not dying, you idiot!
Uh, Dragon Warrior.
I am simply at peace.
Finally.
Oh! So, um, I should stop talking?
If you can.
You want to get something to eat?
[sighing deeply]
Yeah.
["Kung Fu Fighting" playing]
♪ Everybody is kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Your mind becomes fast as lightning ♪
♪ Although the future
Is a little bit frightening ♪
♪ A little bit frightening ♪
♪ It's the book of your life
That you're writing ♪
[Po] Look out! Skadoosh!
♪ Everybody is kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Your mind becomes fast as lightning ♪
♪ Although the future
Is a little bit frightening ♪
♪ A little bit frightening ♪
♪ It's the book of your life
That you're writing ♪
♪ Life that you're writing ♪
♪ You are a natural ♪
♪ Why is it so hard to see? ♪
♪ Maybe it's just because
You keep on looking at me ♪
♪ The journey's a lonely one
So much more than we know ♪
♪ But sometimes you've got to go ♪
♪ Go on and be your own hero ♪
♪ Everybody is kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Your mind becomes fast as lightning ♪
♪ Although the future
Is a little bit frightening ♪
♪ A little bit frightening ♪
♪ It's the book of your life
That you're writing ♪
♪ Life that you're writing ♪
♪ You're a diamond in the rough
A brilliant ball of clay ♪
♪ You could be a work of art
If you just go all the way ♪
♪ Now what would it take to break? ♪
♪ I believe that you can bend ♪
♪ Not only do you have to fight ♪
♪ But you have got to win ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody is kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Your mind becomes fast as lightning ♪
♪ Although the future
Is a little bit frightening ♪
♪ A little bit frightening ♪
♪ It's the book of your life
That you're writing ♪
♪ Life that you're writing ♪
♪ You're a diamond in the rough ♪
♪ A brilliant ball of clay ♪
♪ You could be a work of art ♪
♪ If you just go all the way ♪
♪ Now what would it take to break? ♪
♪ I believe that you can bend ♪
♪ Not only do you have to fight
But you have got to win ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody is kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Kung fu fighting ♪
♪ Your mind becomes fast as lightning ♪
♪ Although the future
Is a little bit frightening ♪
♪ A little bit frightening ♪
♪ It's the book of your life
That you're writing ♪
[peaceful music playing]