Master Shifu?
Good time?
Bad Time?
Time is an illusion, there is only the now.
So now is a, good time?!
You must take the next step of your journey,
from warrior to teacher.
But I'm no good at it.
It's the dragon teacher, he's so handsome.
Po?!
Oh, hey dad whats up!
You're terrible at it.
Who are you?
I'm looking for my son.
Dad?!
Give your old man a hug!
How do we know he's even related to you?
Look at that!
Come with me, there's a secret Panda village in the mountains.
Welcome home son!
You look just like me but a baby!
You're like me but old!
Oh, he's adorable!
I'm good!
I have returned!
Who?!
The master of pain, beast of vengeace, maker of widows.
I dont know.
Ok, I used to work with Oogway...
Oh, master Oogway.
Silence!
Kai attacked the valey, it's all gone.
Now he's coming for the Pandas!
You must teach them to fight.
I am ready!
I'm gonna turn you into Kung Fu masters.
Nobody said this was gonna be easy.
Get ready to dance with Fang Ja!
Enemies of justice prepare for... what, are you kidding me?
You must be the dragon  warrior!
How about you spare me the chitchat.
I'm going to take your...
Oh, chitchat
in the...
chitty chitty chat chat.
in ....
Chat chat chat.
in the...
Chitchat.
We've gotta get in there.
But master Shifu said...
You seriously afraid?!
Even master Chicken is going in there!
And he's a chicken!