Dear students…
on this event
of World Science Day celebrations,
may we cordially invite
the most knowledgeable professor
and a very popular atheist,
Dr. Lenin Satyam.
And may I now request him
to please say a few words.
Hi.
Thank you.
Faculty members and my dear students…
we seek an auspicious time
when we enter our new home.
We look for an auspicious moment
to step outside our homes.
We seek an auspicious time
for marriage and death.
when we send rockets into space as well.
And the worst part is…
some doctors deliver the child by
cutting the womb at an auspicious time.
Is it science or dogma?
Is this all science?
We put lemons in front
of our cars to avert danger.
And tie talismans around
the neck when our kid gets a fever.
From dawn to dusk,
our world revolves around astrology,
horoscopes, discourses,
and reincarnation theories.
Believe in science,
and search for the truth.
As an atheist, as a professor
who believes in science, I am telling you,
that if faith is suppressing the truth,
that faith is buried by blind faith.
Rachalakshmi!
Don't do it.
Praise the Lord.
Hey Lord, please bless us.
Bless us, Lord.
Praise the Lord.
Take blessings.
Won't you listen to me?
What if Dad learns about it?
You will directly go
to hell if you don't bother
about good and evil.
Mom, we are atheists.
It doesn't affect us.
It doesn't bother you but it bothers me.
You went to study in London and
came back with this white-skinned girl.
She knows zilch
about our customs and traditions.
Rajalakshmi! I have
such a beautiful name.
She mispronounces that as well.
Yes, Rachalakshmi!
Come here! You can eat that later.
Do you know what he did yesterday?
I sent him to buy lemons.
He brought the ones thrown on the road.
I had no clue
so I used it to make lemon-rice.
I kept fearing day and night
if those lemons were used for black magic.
What if our whole family gets cursed?!
What's my fault in this?
It's not your fault but mine.
-Grandpa…
-Yeah.
See, what she is doing.
What?!
You…
Here I spread the word that have
more faith in yourself than in God
and you keep visiting temples.
What will happen to me
if someone spots you here?
My image will be ruined.
Don't worry about that.
No one knows me there.
I wear a double mask
so that no one sees me.
Have you lost your mind?
Mom.
Please calm down.
What is it, Mom?
-Interview?
-I am leaving.
-All the best.
-Thanks, Dad.
Why don't you join an MNC company?
Why are you taking up a government job?
Because who wants to work?
Bye, Mom.
Bye.
Mr. Viplav!
May I come in, madam?
You are very lucky.
You're the only one
to get posted in Mumbai.
-Really lucky…
-How am I lucky?
I am bored with Mumbai.
It's the same Marine Drive,
the same Gateway,
the same vada pav,
the tolls, and the same potholes.
Please select something
more exotic, madam.
Do you think it's a government office
or a tourism company?
Sorry!
Please don't misunderstand me, madam.
I am still young and haven't seen enough.
-Raju…
-Yes, madam.
-Send that new groom in.
-Okay, madam.
Excuse me, madam.
He's newly married
and got posted in Kashmir.
-If you both agree mutually…
-I'll gladly go to Kashmir.
I even have a sweater.
Thank you, sir.
-You can leave.
-Okay, madam.
Why are you laughing?
He should have gone to Kashmir
and enjoyed his honeymoon.
What's there in Mumbai?
Do you think you can enjoy your stay
over there with this kind of salary?
You don't need money to enjoy.
You just need the vibe.
The experience of listening
to A. R. Rahman's music,
eating hot noodles
in the snow-clad mountains,
and plucking fresh red apples
from the trees.
I will call you
and share the experience
and see how happy or jealous you feel.
Forget about my feelings.
I hope you are clear.
I am clear about it, madam.
-I am approving it.
-Go ahead.
I told you, Sweetie.
No officer from South Mumbai
will accept the posting to Kashmir.
-Really?
-Yes.
I'll close the telephone exchange quickly.
And leave for Patna immediately.
Sweetie, the train is here.
Stay on the line.
Is he here?
I can't see him.
He is not here!
Didn't I tell you?
He will not come here.
I will come to Patna.
What will I eat in the garden?
We will have rasgulla.
-What shall we eat?
-We'll eat apples.
Sweetie, here he is.
You can have rasgulla
and I will again have an apple.
Pitobash?
I couldn't notice you, sir.
I took the seat next
to the driver for a better view.
Is that so?
Please come.
Pitobash!
Can we engage in some off-roading?
These terrains are too dangerous
to try such things.
Really?
How far is the telephone exchange
from here?
We'll reach by evening.
No problem. Go slowly.
The terrain dictates the speed here, sir.
Wow! It's so beautiful!
Looks just like a frame
out of the film Roja.
It's the same snow! The same feel!
All I need is a heroine!
Nice.
I swear in the name
of the Himalayas, Pito.
I am madly in love with Kashmir!
Oh, sir! Oh God!
Sir, let go of me!
Control yourself, sir.
Hey, RK, look how beautiful Kashmir is!
It's so beautiful.
Yes.
Stop the vehicle by the side
and have two pegs.
You already have ice with you.
Come here. Let's have it together!
If you fall from here,
you'll end up in Pakistan.
-Hey, Viplav.
-Hello? RK?
To heck with the signal!
Hey, lift it.
These mountains…
this beautiful sky…
where are we, Pitobash?
Praise the Lord!
-Praise the Lord.
-Where are we, Pitobash?
A war just broke out, sir!
Don't you get it?
Are you blind?
Pakistan is on the
other side of this hill.
Pakistan?
Yes, of course. What did you expect?
This is very common here.
Both sides keep hurling
bombs at each other, sir.
What do you mean, Pitobash?
Why did you come here, sir?
Who will take care of my Sweetie
if something happens to me?
Sweetie!
Oh, Lord!
-Hey, who are you?
-Sir.
-Sir…
-What are you doing here?
Sir, we are BSNL employees.
J.T.O., Kashmir posting, sir.
Why Kashmir?
Sir, the location is beautiful here.
I've come to enjoy the scenery here.
What?
I've come to enjoy here, sir.
Enjoy?
We are risking our lives
to protect the country
and you have come here for enjoyment.
-Just get out of here. Quick.
-Go! Go!
-Hail Mother India!
This is our exchange office, sir.
Can't we exchange it?
You can sleep in your car if you wish.
Sorry, sir.
-Bring my luggage inside.
-Yes.
-Greetings, brother.
-What's up?
Oh, shit!
-Pitobash.
-What happened, sir?
The bathroom is stinking.
It's a government office.
That's how things will be, sir.
Why don't you go in the open?
What? Are you joking?
-Hey, get up.
-What?
I am sorry, Pito.
I can't pee in the open.
Let's find something more comfortable
nearby like a hotel or a restaurant.
Comfortable?
This beautiful night…
Come and embrace me
-Come and embrace me
-Who knows whether or not
-This beautiful night will ever
-Hey, Pito!
-Come again
Your song
doesn't match the situation.
-It's very distracting. Please!
-In this life…
You need a fag to freshen up.
I need a song to perk up.
You are my boss in the office
and not over here.
The locals will be here anytime soon.
They may even shoot us
mistaking us for bears.
Wrap it up fast.
-Come and embrace me
-Me…
-This beautiful night…
-Will ever come again
-My Sweetie loves this song.
Poor Sweetie.
In this life…
Hey!
What's that?
You worry too much!
Everyone's got their talent.
-I am hungry, Pitobash.
-So am I, sir.
Let's eat something.
Pito…
why are all the shops shut?
It's wartime, right?
So, there will be a curfew for a week.
-What next?
-There will be a war again.
What about our meal now?
We will have to beg for food.
I hope we find some kind people.
-Or else?
-They will abuse us.
-What are you staring at?
-Hello, sir.
It's curfew time. Just leave!
-Yes, we are moving.
-Move.
-We are going. Okay.
-Pito.
-Yes, sir…
How do we ask in their language?
Ma'am, could you please
give me some food?
You have to beg for it
and not demand for it.
Ma'am, could you please
give me some food?
Okay. All the best.
Ma'am, could you please
give me some food?
Ma'am…
Ma'am, could you please
give me some food?
Ma'am…
Ma'am, could you please
give me some food?
I don't want an apple.
Stop, guys.
I don't want this!
Bloody apples!
-Kids, have these apples.
-Yes.
-I don't want.
Ma'am, could you…
please give me some food?
Eat this.
Hey, do you think I am crazy?
What's wrong?
Why is everyone giving me an apple?
-Don't you have anything else?
-Really?
-Don't you eat anything else?
-I am not your chef! Get out of here!
-Vada pav or pav bhaji.
-What are you saying?
-You can get anything in Mumbai.
-Get the hell out of here.
-Everyone is giving me an apple.
-I will show you!
-What happened?
-Get out!
Ma'am, what's wrong?!
-I am leaving!
-Don't bake my brains in the morning.
Don't you dare come back here!
Uncle, eat this.
-Madam.
-Viplav, how are you?
Madam…
I came to the market to buy
apples at 250 rupees per kilogram.
And that's when I thought of calling you.
You must be plucking fresh
apples from the orchard there.
Madam, this is a different Kashmir.
There's biting cold on one side
and insatiable hunger on the other.
There's war and curfew everywhere
with nothing else but apples to eat.
I will come back to Mumbai.
Post me there.
How can I do that?
We have to fend for
each other as BSNL employees.
-Viplav, I can't hear you!
-Madam, I know you can hear me.
I can't hear you, Viplav.
Madam, don't disconnect!
I don't want to live here. I…
Ma'am!
She's at work now.
Will you have an apple?
But they won't pay you money!
This little heart of mine
And its little desires
Stop singing, Pito.
Why, sir?
I need to meet Mani Ratnam
and A.R. Rahman.
-Why, sir?
-They took us for a ride.
How can they be inspired by Kashmir?
But there's nothing here
except snow and apples!
Then why don't you leave, sir?
I will get some relief.
Aara… flowers
Brother, can you come here?
Pito, I found the inspiration.
Inspiration for what?
Rahman's background score.
Don't stare at them.
This is Kashmir, not Mumbai.
The heart doesn't understand geography.
-Deepu…
-Yes.
Someone's following us on that boat.
-Where?
-Look over there.
Look at how he is staring at us.
He is just gazing at us, dear.
He is ogling at us. Can't you see?
Give that paddle to me.
For what?
-Give it to me!
-Give that! Here you go.
-He is following us!
-Pito, I am the Captain now!
I am coming, Begum.
-Sir… No, he's not!
-I am coming.
What are you doing, sir?
Please.
Look at how he's breaking
the paddle and rushing to us.
He will get closer if he figures out
that we are from Pune.
Have you forgotten why we are here?
I will somehow avoid him.
You stay quiet.
Brother, go fast.
Fast. Fast.
-Hey, Pito!
-Sir…
-She's leaving. Push!
-The paddle is with you, sir.
-Why don't you push with your hands, Pito?
-What a torture!
The thing you are making me do!
Now I am liking Kashmir.
-Begum.
-Stop, sir!
-Listen to me.
-Catch!
-Oh God!
-Wait a second.
-Hey! What do you want?
-Sir.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
-Can we speak to the Begum once?
-Please let them go, sir.
Which Begum?
Do you know where we are from?
I don't know about you.
-But Begum is straight from heaven!
-Sir!
We are from Pakistan.
What the hell is she saying?!
We're here in search of her brother,
Feroze who is eight years old.
She's come all the way
from Pakistan to Kashmir
in search of her eight-year-old brother,
Feroze who's gone missing.
Her relatives are all training
in different terrorist camps.
Why are you so keen to die?
-If you even look at her…
-Look at me, sir. I am harmless.
-They will kill you with an AK-47 gun.
-Oh, my God!
They have an AK-47!
-They will gun us down!
-Let's go.
-It's not worth it.
-Excuse me.
-This is suicide.
-Would you mind…
-If I fall in love before I die?
-Hey!
Hey!
Sir, she will kill us all!
She's a terrorist!
They are very dangerous!
You will be blown to bits.
So, what if they are terrorists, Pitobash?
They are still humans and have feelings.
Feelings are unpredictable.
Here's my ID card.
It has my number.
-Hey!
-No.
Keep it, Begum.
Think again.
Feel my love.
And do call me.
Yes, of course.
Let's go.
He's a bit too much!
He even gave us his number!
Who does that?
Men will always be men.
To hell with him. Ignore him.
Joy is when I spot you
Joy is when you are with me
My sweetheart
She casts a spell full of warmth
She tantalizes me like a cute dream
Her eyes sparkle all over like moonshine
Your presence is as magical as twilight
You and I together
You are my only love
Look at the shower of love in my heart
Joy is when I spot you
Joy is when I am mesmerized by you
Joy is when you are with me
My love for you has made me intoxicated!
Walking in the air in a trance of you
I am getting lost in this love
I carry my heart on my sleeve
My life hangs by the thread that you hold
The heartbeat goes on
And every beat reverbs your name
A storm in my heart
But the storm feels harmonious
My sweetheart
She casts a spell full of warmth
She tantalizes me like a cute dream
You and I together…
We are a match made in heaven
Look at the shower of love in my heart
Joy is when I spot you
Joy is when I get mesmerized by you
Joy is when you and I are together
Dear, did you change
Chintu's diapers on time?
I haven't come here to relax.
Look at how he is making us work.
Good morning, madam.
I heard it.
I told you on day one of your joining.
If you are working under me,
forget about your family and the world.
I was fine with work-from-home,
but this work-from-vacation
is a bit too much.
-Where is Aaradhya?
-No idea, sir.
-Sir…
-Where are you, Aaradhya?
Sir, I am…
The client is driving me mad
about the presentation.
Chatur sir…
Aara is embarking on a prayer
trip to Mamuleswar temple
for relief to her
grandmother from knee pains.
She needs to break coconuts
as part of her prayer.
Break them on my head.
Where are they now?
The Anantnag road is blocked, sir.
We are traveling via Pulwama now.
That place had a blast recently.
That place is infested with infiltrators!
At least send me the presentation.
We have the perfect disguise.
If Aaradhya is not back
in the resort in the next hour,
I am going to fire her
-Hello!
-after reaching Mumbai. Hello!
-I can't hear you.
-Brother…
-Need a vehicle to go
-Hello!
to Mamuleswar temple.
-Mamuleswar?
-Yes.
Will tonga be fine?
It's fine.
Salim…
Yes, bro.
Okay. Come over.
Please go.
Brother…
two girls are here
who are wearing a burqa.
They are inquiring about the way
to Mamuleswar temple.
She looks like an Indian Officer
on a secret mission, bro.
Nobody shall leave this place!
I was wondering,
what must be in Begum's red bag?
What else can it be, Pitobash?
If a girl is holding onto the bag,
it must be lipstick
and other accessories.
She's a Muslim, right?
So she must be carrying surma, etc.
Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Thank God.
-I worried that it carried explosives.
-Pito…
Begum!
Brother, how much will it cost a trip?
-Ma'am, 6,500 rupees.
-Sixteen, seventeen…
Begum.
Why are you here?
We… are…
You're here for Feroze, right?
-Yes, for Feroze.
I know you're frantically
searching for Feroze.
Give me a chance.
Let me try as well.
Instead of looking around everywhere,
I will make an announcement for Feroze.
No! No!
Begum.
I am here for you.
Brothers and sisters…
this is Aara Begum.
Her younger brother,
Feroze has gone missing.
If anyone knows about his
whereabouts, please inform me.
Who is Feroze amongst you?
Come forward. Don't be shy.
I am Feroze!
-I am Feroze!
See brothers…
all of you look like wild bears.
That boy Feroze is a cute,
young boy, like my Begum.
Pitobash, translate this in Kashmiri.
Pito…
Okay, tell me now. Who is Feroze?
I am Feroze.
Kill him.
Hey. But why?
Why kill me?
Let's sit and talk.
Begum, these are your brothers, right?
Please talk and sort it out.
No…
-Hey!
Don't come near me!
I will smash your heads, bloody fellows.
I will break your heads,
I am warning you.
Praise the Lord. I am Feroze!
Begum, come with me.
-Sir…
-Get lost!
-Pito.
-Sir, come here.
Hey, stop!
Oh, God! Go back!
Praise the Lord.
Begum, don't get scared.
I am used to these kinds
of chases in Kurla.
You are safe.
Praise the Lord!
-Hold me, Begum.
-No.
They will chop our heads off!
-What happened?
-Begum, two more to go.
Let's finish them.
Sir…
Do not go into the water.
If you want something,
you have to give up something.
But what do you want?
Someone's heart.
Praise the Lord!
Sir, come fast!
Hail Lord Bholenath!
Begum?
You are a Muslim, right?
Why are you visiting a Hindu temple?
Aara can do anything for Feroze.
She prays to every God.
-Aren't all Gods created equally?
-Yes, all Gods are equal.
-Yes, all are the same.
-All are the same.
Yes, we'll go.
Hey, stop.
She wants to pray in solitude inside.
Can you wait here?
-We will go inside. Okay?
-Okay, please carry on.
-Pito…
-Sir…
A Pakistani girl.
Look how broad-minded she is!
My family will love her.
Hurry up.
He may barge in anytime.
Hail Lord Shiva!
-Guruji.
-Hey, don't touch!
You look familiar, Guruji.
Have you ever been to a temple?
I never even put a tilak on my forehead.
You will pray to God in the future
with folded hands.
Hail Lord Shiva!
You will wear the tilak…
and break the coconuts as well.
Hail, Lord Shiva! Please relieve
my Grandma from knee pain.
You will also wear a talisman.
God, bless me with a happy life
without the hassles of marriage!
You will beg God to spare you
from the agony of hell!
You have a long journey ahead, son.
God, bless me for the on-site job.
-What? Highly unlikely!
-Hail Lord Shiva!
The girl is from Pakistan.
It is not possible.
-Okay.
-Tell him, dude.
Yes, sir. His lover is from Pakistan.
Oh, my dear love
She is from Pakistan!
-Oh, my dear love!
-Hey, shut up.
Stop all this nonsense.
Before you get ready
to get trapped for life,
take this fruit.
It is good for your health.
-Guruji, what about me?
-You won't need it. He needs it.
Convey my regards to Sweetie.
-Sweetie?
-Hail Lord Shiva!
Hail Lord Shiva!
He is very powerful, sir.
There is some connection
between this fruit and that girl, sir.
Nonsense!
Look at the way he is
standing like a tower.
I'll manage him.
Thank you for everything.
-We are leaving.
-Please! Don't leave, Begum.
Please come to my exchange tonight
and enjoy our hospitality and dinner.
Both of you sleep with me.
What?!
Don't you have manners?!
Is this how you talk to girls?
What did I say, Pitobash?
Why is she upset?
Of course,
she is upset when you talk so vulgarly.
No.
Oh, no, that's not what I meant.
What I meant was that
both of you can come to my place.
You can take some rest there.
And we will step out in search
of Feroze in the morning.
Those goons can be back anytime, Aara.
We can stay with him.
But we know nothing about him.
I'll take care of it.
It's okay.
Okay. We will come.
-Please come, Begum.
-Please come.
Come.
Keep walking.
Don't worry.
Hope you had a good veneration.
Everything is fine, sir.
Aara and I will
reach the resort in the morning.
Just tell me your location.
I will pick you both.
The place seems like a hill station…
Telephone Exchange…
Hello…
Hello!
Hello, Chatur sir.
Will they leave without us?
No way. You have the presentation.
He needs it to present to the client.
Don't worry about him.
He will come to you.
Just wait and watch.
-Are you sure?
-Begum…
-Oh, no!
-He is back.
Begum…
Here's a special meal for you from afar.
What is it?
Your favorite dish.
Mutton biryani.
-Begum?
-Duffer!
-Aara!
-I have had enough!
How dare he offer me that?
I am a Brahman! A vegetarian!
I am feeling dizzy.
He will pay in hell for this misdeed.
I feel like throwing up, Deepu!
You didn't like it?
Since you are from Pakistan,
I thought you'll love it.
This bloody idiot…
Do you think only India has vegetarians?
We have vegetarians even in Pakistan.
Aara is a pure vegetarian
Pakistani Muslim.
Pakistani… vegetarian Muslim?
Oh, God!
Where the hell should
I fetch rice and lentils from?
Thank you, Lord!
Such tasty food after a long time!
I will devour it.
Pito.
Yes, sir.
Do you know the meaning of selflessness?
To be concerned more with the needs
of others than with one's own.
-Why don't you practice it?
-What do you mean, sir?
-Sir, I am a vegetarian.
-Leave the meat aside and have the rice!
Begum…
This is my home
but consider it as your own.
Don't be shy.
Promise?
Hey, Pito…
Are you sleeping here?
Of course! Like I do every day.
You idiot!
These girls are all alone.
Their parents are not here.
It will be awkward for them
to sleep next to the two of us.
What is awkward about it, sir?
I think of her as my sister.
Don't you?
Hey…
She's your sister-in-law.
Begum!
You sleep here.
Please.
We will keep vigil outside.
-I can't bear the chill outside. No, sir!
-Hey, let's go.
How do they say "good night" in Pakistan?
Shabba khair.
Shabba khair, Begum.
Hopefully, we'll meet tomorrow.
Begum.
I'm parched.
If you don't mind, may I have some water?
Thank you.
Begum…
It is very cold out here.
If you don't mind,
can I have some warm water?
Thank you.
Deepu.
He was here.
-Inside?
-Yes.
-Twice.
-Did he misbehave?
He is trying his best to flirt with me.
If I am not careful, I will become
easy prey to him in this snowy weather.
I have an idea.
Tell me.
Love with Aara
Has cost my heart to me
From a star
I turned into dust
Love with Aara
Has cost my heart to me
-I have gone crazy in your love, baby
-Hey, come here.
You are my Roja
You are my love
Since I found you…
Life's been a joyous journey!
You are my Roja
You are my love
Since I found you…
Life's been a joyous journey!
He is her younger brother.
No, I didn't see anyone.
Did you see a small boy named Feroze?
Go and search there.
-Did you see a small boy?
-No.
-He looks just like him
Thank you.
Sorry, Begum.
In the ocean waves
You are my silent melody
In your divine torrent
A fight started
You are my partner
I am your commander
You are my friend I am your leader
I will accept whatever decision you make
Okay, sweetheart
You are my Roja
You are my love
Since I found you…
Pito…
Oh, God.
Let's get every orphan boy named Feroze
in Kashmir and present him to Begum.
-Get up. Get the car ready!
-Psycho.
-Feroze.
-No.
-Haleem.
Haleem?
Nice name.
I used to eat it on Mohammad Ali Road.
Are you Feroze? Damn it!
I am Feroze!
Useless fellow, Feroze!
You don't know how to do this.
Don't know how the world works.
Hey, Feroze, where are
you taking the flock to?
Hey, Feroze…
Praise the Lord.
Feroze?
Come here.
Where's your mom and dad?
Not there?
Do you want ice cream?
Chocolate flavor?
Come with me.
Hey, Mustak. Come here.
-Someone has kidnapped Feroze.
-Make some space for him.
-Who are you all? Someone stop them.
-Sit. Let's go!
-Feroze! Stop!
-Drive! Let's go!
Brother, give me two cups of tea.
Make it fast!
Hey, Feroze.
If I slap you once,
you will come to your senses.
Did you see his cat eyes, sir?
He can not be Aara's brother.
Let Begum confirm that, not you.
-Ready. One, two, three!
-Praise the Lord!
-Chatur sir, listen to me.
-Yes, tell me.
-Listen to me.
-I am listening.
-We are on a hill station called Pampur.
-Pampur?
-Yes! That's what…
-Hello.
-Come on, boys. Come inside.
-Hello!
Begum…
all of them are named Feroze.
Come here.
Who is your Feroze here?
No one.
Begum, just look at them once.
Look at him. He looks just like you.
No.
Drop them back, Pitobash.
Come on. Let's go.
No, we won't leave.
Why won't you go?
We can't feed you food. Let's go.
If we go back, we will all get beaten up.
Yes, brother. They will beat us all.
It's all because of you.
He is roaming with us just
because you made up a story.
-Let me tell the truth.
-Hey!
Just stay silent for a day.
We shall leave tomorrow.
Chatur sir is on his way.
Karim, these are all the boys
who lost their way.
Please check the register
and call for any of their kith and kin.
-What's the name?
-Feroze.
A boy called Feroze has gone missing.
If there's anyone amongst you
who is their parent, please come here.
A boy called Feroze has gone missing.
Feroze…
Feroze!
Mom.
My son!
Mom!
Where did you go?
Begum…
I did all this to impress you…
but looking at the joy on her face,
I promise you we will find your
Feroze before you go to Pakistan.
I am the poetry
And you are the first line of this poetry
To your heartbeat
I can become the echo
When our eyes meet mine
I dreamt of many dreams
I want to be in your footsteps in
Your Journey and be in your shadow
I will agree to whatever you say
Okay, sweetheart
Love with Aara
Has cost my heart to me
From a star, I turned into dust
You are my Roja
You are my love
Hello.
Chatur sir, where are you now?
I am near Pampur.
Something is wrong over here.
Please come fast.
Love with Aara
Has cost my heart to me
From a star, I turned into dust
You are my Roja
You are my love
Since I found you…
Life's been a joyous journey!
You are my Roja
You are my love
Since I found you…
Life's been a joyous journey!
Deepu…
I want to tell the truth to Viplav.
Begum.
What happened?
Aren't you able to sleep?
Please come, Begum. Please sit.
Please sit. Two minutes.
It's cold, right?
Even I couldn't sleep.
I just had a dream, Begum.
I got married.
And my wife and I lived in this house…
with two kids.
I feel as if we just served
them dinner, put them to bed,
and are now merrily chatting
on the balcony like this.
The one I will fall in love with…
will be the only one I will ever love.
Dreams are just dreams.
I know!
Uncle, one special tea
with double cashew nuts!
You won't drink?
I will have it with Begum.
Really?
Just like Begum warmed up to tea,
she will take a liking
to me too in the future.
I hope you will come
to visit me in Pakistan!
I will if you are alive.
Thank you, brother.
-Write in my account.
-Okay.
What's the point of
walking so far just to get tea?
My legs are hurting.
This tea can be had…
Begum is sleeping.
-Be quiet.
-Okay.
Begum…
Aara Begum!
Sir…
have a look.
Begum has fled.
Keep munching cashew nuts now.
You were talking about going
to Pakistan.
These days there's
no guarantee for lovers.
Whereas yours is from Pakistan.
WE HAVE FOUND FEROZE.
WE ARE LEAVING FOR PAKISTAN.
She found her younger brother
and hence she left.
No problem. Let's go and sleep inside.
-It is biting cold outside.
-Begum still loves me.
I have felt it.
Didn't you?
-Ours is an inter-nation marriage.
-Oh, man.
Maybe she was skeptical
about it, and hence she left.
If necessary,
we'll initiate a surgical strike
to reach out to her family
and persuade them for our marriage.
Sir, the Begum would have
taken the Amritsar Express by now
to cross the Wagah border.
-Come, let's go to Pakistan.
-Pa--
JAMMU TAWI - AMRITSAR
Brother, did you see two Muslim girls
along with a young boy?
Pitobash!
JAMMU TAWI - PUNE - HYDERABAD
Michael, the presentation--
-Why are you blocking the way?
-Hey, you fool.
You left me?
You were the one in my dream.
You didn't get that?
Oh, man! When will she understand me?
Say something, Pitobash.
Madam, please. Please go there.
Sit here. Thank you.
Begum…
I already told you, I am
with you till death do us part.
I know you have the same feelings for me.
Don't get scared. Let's go to Pakistan.
We need to get on the train
to Pakistan, Begum.
-Not this one. This one goes to Hyderabad.
-Yes, that's right.
Let's leave now. I am coming with you.
Give me your luggage.
Begum, where's Feroze?
-Feroze! The kid…
-Feroze? Tell me, Begum.
I am not Begum.
Brahmin.
Pitobash…
did she just speak in Marathi?
She also said she's a Brahmin.
-Br… Brahmin?
-Yes.
My name is Aaradhya.
From Kothrud.
-Kothrud?!
-Kothrud is in Pune!
What about Feroze?
And Pakistan?
We just made it up to
avoid getting followed by you.
But who lies about being from Pakistan?
Forget all that.
Do you love me?
I believe in God and destiny.
After passing all the hurdles,
I held your hand
and felt blessed after having
visited Mamuleshwar Temple.
Those days spent with you at the Exchange
and the pains you took to search for a
Feroze who didn't exist melted my heart.
I fought hard to hide
my feelings towards you.
Without knowing anything
about me or my antecedents, you
were prepared to spend
the rest of your life with me.
That very moment I fell in love with you.
That's enough.
I will never leave your hand.
Hey, saint.
I am discussing the most
important matter of my life.
Can we stop that nonsense for a while?
-Nonsense! Don't talk like that.
-Hey!
-You can't call that nonsense, dear.
-Hey, it's all a nuisance.
It's a holy discourse.
Seek his pardon.
Do it, sir.
The discourse is by my dad himself.
-Who is it?
-Don't you know him?
The famous preacher from Pune.
Don't you know
Mr. Sakharam Maharaj Wadekar himself?
Our religion is an eternal one.
It outlasted various invasions
and attacks from atheists.
The path of devotion.
Don't you see the "Bhakti" channel?
Do you know my dad?
Who?
He is the president of the
State Atheists Association.
Lenin Satyam.
Are you his son?
Yes.
Well, then both our dads hate each other
and are diametrically opposite.
Do you think this will work out?
I didn't give up when it was Pakistan.
I won't give up now
even if it's Pune.
We won't give up.
In two weeks, we'll witness
a complete lunar eclipse.
While the atheists are describing
it as a celestial spectacle,
the priests are apprehending
it will bring in more doom.
We'll soon find out the truth.
Let's welcome our two seasoned speakers,
famous atheist, Mr. Satyam Lenin
and noted Hindu preceptor,
Mr. Sakharam Maharaj Wadekar
who will debate this out.
-Welcome, Mr. Sakharam.
-Greetings.
Can we see the moon on new moon day?
The lunar eclipse happens
because of Rahu.
This lunar eclipse happens
because Rahu is swallowing the moon.
Is the moon chocolate…
to be swallowed by Rahu?
Where is Rahu to be found
in our solar system?
It's just a shadow of
the earth on the moon.
You are unnecessarily scaring the public.
Look here.
Our saints have determined the planetary
movements without the help of a telescope.
What do you have to say to that?
They spew all kinds of nonsense.
If they were true, then we wouldn't
have scientists working at ISRO.
We cannot suffer their stupid
views corrupting the public.
You please share your views
and the list of do's and don'ts that day.
Nothing dramatic.
You shouldn't have any food
or take a bath during the eclipse.
Can we take nature's calls?
Or do we need permission
for that as well?
Don't you go to the doctor
if you get a heart attack?
Nonsense!
We should be ashamed of why we are
organizing such debates such as this.
This is ridiculous.
-I will not talk to this brainless fellow.
-Sir…
-What is saying? This is ridiculous.
-Mind your tongue!
Pathetic!
-Why is he talking without decorum?
-One minute. Please stop.
-He talks only baloney.
-Sir…
-How can he command any respect?
-We are live right now.
-Please calm down
-Why are you barking like a dog?
Start wearing a silver ring with a pearl
to control your anger.
Father-in-law, let's leave now.
We have to catch the train.
They are conveniently evading
us and running away from here.
We are not scared.
You are safe because
this is not Pune.
Come to our city to see
who is more powerful.
-Calm down. He's a fool.
-Shut up and get out.
-Don't waste your energy on him.
-He's testing my patience.
-He needs to meditate.
-Let him go.
Mr. Jaffer…
Don't call me for a debate
with this fellow ever again.
It's over.
Sir, Viplav requested an immediate
transfer from Kashmir to Mumbai.
His mother… has asthma.
His father has back pain issues.
He has to take care of his parents.
Okay, sir. Thank you so much.
What a breezy love story in just a week
of seeing each other! And now marriage.
Is she so good-looking?
She is as beautiful
as an angel, madam.
My granddaughter prayed for me
at Mamuleshwar temple.
I got fully cured after that.
Mr. Sakharam.
This is our contribution
to your discourse.
Oh, no! I don't take money
for giving discourses.
It's all in the service of God.
Mr. Shankar,
did you watch TV last night?
He gave a proper comeuppance
to that stupid atheist Satyam.
I saw that.
He is the perfect antidote to such folks.
She's all grown up.
Are you looking for a groom for her?
Yes.
We should be ashamed of why
we are organizing such debates!
Why are you barking like a dog?
Start wearing a silver ring with a pearl
to control your anger.
Jaffer!
On the next new moon day,
all of us are going to watch
the lunar eclipse and
have chicken biryani.
If we don't get harmed,
ask if Mr. Sakharam
can keep quiet after that.
Call him for a debate.
I will not spare him.
Arrange a discussion in Pune
if possible. I'll come.
During Sita's groom-selection ceremony,
Lord Ram broke the bow of Lord Shiva
and married Sita. And after that…
Oh, no, it's you!
I dreaded if it was your dad.
Mr. Sakharam Maharaj's
discourses are engrossing.
Mom!
Do you know Mr. Sakharam's
daughter is even better?
Who are you talking about?
Your daughter-in-law.
She is so beautiful.
She is Mr. Sakharam's daughter.
Her name is Aaradhya.
We met in Kashmir and fell in love.
Only you can get us married.
I will try my best. Do not worry.
At least, she will address
me as "Mother-in-law"
instead of mispronouncing
my name like your sister-in-law.
-Am I right?
-Shall I call her?
-Right now?
-I will call her.
Viplav!
-Baby!
Talk to my mom.
Here you go.
-Hello!
-Auntie.
Can you call me mother-in-law?
Mother-in-law!
One more time!
What a blessing!
Hey, who's this "Mother-in-law"?
In Kashmir…
In Kashmir?
I fell in love with this boy.
Who's this boy?
-Did you take your tablets?
-Yes.
Son of Mr. Lenin Satyam.
Oh, my God!
Be quiet!
He is coming here
tomorrow to talk to Dad.
You must take care of the rest.
-No, I can't…
-Grandma, please!
To Pune?
-To Pune?
-Yes.
Dad will censure us if hears this!
Let's do it before he comes to know.
-Don't involve me in this.
-Mom…
She will call you mother-in-law.
The final chapter of today's sermon.
Tulsidas wrote this brilliant
line in Hanuman Chalisa.
It describes how Lord Hanuman
leaped into the sky seeing a glowing sun…
mistaking it for a fruit, and traveled
thousands of miles to kiss the Sun.
That's how powerful Hanuman is.
Hail Hanuman!
-Son, this is enough for my life.
-Forget about the devotion,
-focus on the main job, Mom.
-What happened?
-He is behind you. Talk to him.
-Behind me?
-Salutations, sir.
-Enough.
Blessings to you.
-I am your big fan, sir.
-God is kind.
-Both of us are deeply religious.
-It is quite self-evident. Be blessed.
But my husband is an atheist.
He doesn't even bow before God, Guruji.
-And…
-And chastises anyone who does it.
He even beats them.
Everyone is different in a family.
Don't you feel angry
about such people, Guruji?
Why should I get angry with your husband?
Then…
will you give consent to your
daughter Aaradhya to marry my son?
What?
-Marriage?
-I am Mr. Lenin Satyam's son, Guruji.
Aaradhya and I love each other.
We would like to get married.
With just a twist of logic, look how
they trapped our daughter.
And the alliance is the
son of the noted atheist.
At least Aaradhya should
have had some sense.
-Oh, Guruji is leaving.
-Mom, do something.
Guruji!
How did you fall in
love with Satyam's son?
I didn't know that Viplav
was Mr. Satyam's son.
Mr. Satyam, it seems!
He is an educated fool.
He undermines the faith of people and
keeps hurting their religious sentiments.
We should have some discretion.
Love knows no discretion.
At least you should have
had some sense.
Why are you defending her?
Well, haven't you seen the boy
and his mother in the temple?
They were so good and
the boy looked handsome.
We have seen many folks like him.
-You please stop.
-You wait.
Both, the boy and
the girl love each other.
Let's go as per our tradition.
We will wait for
Satyam's consent as well.
-What do you think?
-Why should we even talk to them?
Do we want to push our
daughter into that dungeon?
-Father-in-law…
-We'll send her off. Who am I?
He is coming here because of his son.
He needs it now.
We will settle scores
with him right here.
Dear son, look at her face.
Father-in-law, please agree.
She is very keen on him.
He is a good boy.
-Accept this. It's a great chance.
-Think about it.
Okay, let's talk.
Neither I will go to his house,
nor he will come here.
Let's talk.
Dad, Aaradhya is not like her dad.
She is very practical
and logical like us.
Mom, tell him.
She is quite modern, dear.
Would you like some curry?
Have some.
After marriage, Sakharam will change
your name from Viplav to Vipranarayan.
He is a fool who injects ignorance
and dogma into people's minds.
And you fell in love with his daughter.
Dad, I want to marry Aaradhya,
not her father.
Anyway, they are visiting us
tomorrow to discuss the alliance.
Is he coming?
Let him come.
But let's meet them somewhere
outside and not in our house.
Okay, Dad.
Look…
It's not the appropriate time
to talk about marriage.
What?
Tell me.
Let me come straight to the point.
My son is in love with your daughter.
Don't stop this marriage. That's it!
That's it.
Can you give a good reason why my daughter
deserves to step into your household?
We are not fussy about caste,
creed, and religion.
We are not ritualistic.
We don't pick auspicious
moments for doing anything.
All we care about is they are in love.
That's all.
You may think that's enough.
But we need to match
their horoscopes as well.
Right?
Horoscopes?
We don't believe in them.
We are done here. Come.
-Viplav, let's leave.
-Wait.
-What planet are they from?
-Dad.
-Let's leave.
-First, why should we get down?
It will look bad. Let them get down.
Uncle, we look bad.
Let's not do it then.
Sit down, Dad.
Is this why you planned this in the metro?
-Keep quiet. Sit down.
-You're a genius!
We don't want to check
the horoscope. What next?
Well, for whatever good,
I did cast Viplav's horoscope
when he was born.
-Here.
-Give it.
What are doing?!
Why did you tear it?
Uncle!
It's the original.
The girl's star is Uttarashada.
The boy's star is Rohini.
It is going to be opposites
like a snake and a mongoose.
They will fight to the death.
-It's a big defect!
-What?
If they marry, they will invite
untold misery and mayhem…
and problems galore from
misunderstandings to miscarriage.
If they marry, they will have all the
mayhem that a marriage shouldn't bring.
What's the remedy, Guruji?
Both father and son should
do a remedial oblation.
An oblation?!
The boy should anoint a copper plate
with sacred mantras on the entrance,
chant the hymn Mahamrutyunjaya mantra,
donate clothes, food, and a cow to
Brahmin priests and the cow dung…
And plaster the cow dung
on the wall, right?
I don't care about you, but I
am not approving of this marriage.
Let's leave.
-Even we want that.
-Dad…
Let's go, Father-in-law.
Don't mind, Guruji.
I am leaving, dear.
-What are you staring at? Come.
-We made a total mess of it.
Do you see their stupidity?
Do you still want to marry the girl?
Even if he had agreed,
I would have never approved it.
Dad…
we need no permission from anybody.
I am going to marry Aaradhya…
tomorrow.
So, you have made up your mind?
You stop.
Look, my dear Aaradhya.
I am speaking to you not as a dad…
but as Sakharam Wadekar,
who's well-versed in scriptures.
He has a snag in his horoscope
because of which, your
future happiness is bleak.
Convince him for an oblation ceremony.
Or else, you will see hell in marriage.
I can't force this on him, Dad.
Viplav is a good boy.
He will take good care of me.
-Without him…
-You can't live, right?
-But you can live without us.
-No, Dad.
-So, you can be without us.
-Dad, I didn't…
So, it is fine.
Did you hear that?
-Dad, I didn't mean that.
-That's what you said. It's okay.
Dear, get her suitcase.
-Get it now. She will go.
-Father-in-law…
How can we let go like that?
-Let her go.
-You wait, dear.
We can explain things to others.
But some things must
be experienced first-hand.
She will come back in six months.
Write it down.
But…
Come, child. Go.
Give that to her!
Here. Take this!
-Dad…
-Take that also.
-Here is your suitcase.
-Listen to me.
-You can leave as well.
-No.
Son, listen to me…
-Start your new life.
-Listen to me.
Go.
Is that how a father behaves?
Why is he cursing his daughter?
Why is he slamming the door in the face?
If someone slams the door on me,
I don't bother about them.
-I don't want my family.
-Okay.
Then I don't want them either.
-Let's not take any sides, okay?
-Okay.
Okay. Let's not take sides.
Let's prove to the world
what an ideal couple we are.
-Yes, we'll show it to them.
-We'll show it to them.
We will.
We will prove it to them.
We will show it to all who
believe in horoscopes.
And to your dad.
And to those disbelievers.
We'll show it to everybody.
-Let's show the world.
-World?!
Viplav!
What happened?
A black cat.
So, what?
It's a bad omen.
So?
We shouldn't leave immediately, Viplav.
Shall we stop for two minutes and go?
Okay?
Everybody, clap!
-Who are the witnesses?
-I am.
I hope you'll take good care of her.
Madam? Do you doubt me?
I know he will take care of me.
Look at how she's relying on you.
Now that you're married,
what will you call our boy?
Hello, husband!
Oh, no. It is not the 1960s anymore.
That's so boring.
Viplav!
-That's what I call him.
-Yes!
Anything else?
-Cutie.
-Oh.
Did you eat anything, cutie?
Hey, the wedding is over.
What about the party, Pushpa?
Nobody should be seen around
for the next three days!
The most improbable marriage between
the son of noted atheist Mr. Lenin Satyam…
and the daughter of a famous Hindu
speaker Mr. Sakharam Maharaj Wadekar
happened at the registrar's office today…
-Let's hear from the couple.
-Viplav!
Do your parents know about your marriage?
Or did you alienate your
parents for this marriage?
We didn't alienate them.
Okay, but what if both of you
spar in the future like your parents?
-We won't let that happen.
-Then how will you manage?
With love.
Do you see any remorse
on her face, Father-in-law?
You better keep your mouth shut.
Son, if you keep these aspersions aside,
they're a really cute couple!
Sure! Why not garland them
for their deeds?!
Father-in-law has said
that this marriage won't last long.
The defect is in the boy's horoscope.
Both the fathers will forget all
their differences to cradle the babies…
Thomas' chicken biryani is just…
But nobody knows the secret recipe.
Hey, don't tell them my secret.
Just enjoy the biryani.
Viplavam?
-Viplav.
-Sorry, Viplav.
Viplav.
I planned to delight Zoya on our wedding
day with a lovingly cooked biryani.
My bad! Because after that day,
she stopped stepping foot in the kitchen.
Oh, come on!
-Can you cook, Aaradhya?
-What are you talking about, madam?
-Aaradhya makes amazing halwa.
-Hey!
You must have heard
about the famous halwa from Pune.
It's her recipe.
Wow.
Aaradhya, you can learn
culinary skills from Thomas.
And then, he won't be making fun of you,
he'll literally be eating out
of your hands.
Is it just the two of you?
We have a daughter, Lissy.
She stays in Alleppey, our native place.
She loves nature and silence.
We go there to meet her
on her birthday every year.
Have it…
Serve them some biryani!
What are you doing?
Are you done?
Did you like it?
Take it home.
-Aaradhya, shall we leave?
-Yes.
Viplav, why do you
go to that old quarters?
It smells of fresh paint.
Why don't you stay back?
We don't want to disturb you.
We will manage. Come.
The mosquitoes won't let you sleep!
Please give us the mosquito coil, madam!
We will adjust.
Why do you have to suffer?
Madam, just spare us a pillow
and a quilt. We'll manage it.
Hey, let them go.
Okay.
Hey, why did you say no?
Do you think we are going
to sleep tonight?
Whichever leg we use
to step inside the house
it's going to
offend one of our dads.
What should we do?
I won't allow you to keep
your leg on the floor at all!
You are my sunshine
You are my moonlight
You are the stars in the sky
Come with me now
You have my desire
Come along
Just the way you are Aaradhya
Waltzing towards you
The gait is yours
The body draped itself
Take hold of it
You plundered my heart
My heart proclaims…
Take your name softly
Amidst all the cacophony
Amidst all the raucousness
Our love will strive through
Aaradhya… Aaradhya…
I seek nothing else but you
Let me be the words
And you be the rhyme
Let our song of love echo forever
Let your poetry and poems
Always adorn me!
A beautiful…
Tune…
In the heart…
We sing the song of our love
Aaradhya… Aaradhya…
I seek nothing else but you
Yearning to say something
And listen to your words
I crave for a lover like you
In every birth of mine
The lights…
Calls us
You come…
And make my heart dance on your tune
You plundered my heart
My heart proclaims…
Your name softly amidst all the cacophony
Amidst all the raucousness
Our love will strive through
Aaradhya… Aaradhya…
I seek nothing else but you
Your lover
-Aaradhya…
-Your one and only lover…
You are everything to me
My life…
Aaradhya…
Hey, RK.
You're going to be an uncle.
Good news, brother.
Get sweets and come to the hospital.
-Okay, brother.
-Right.
Are you fine?
I need a baby Aaradhya.
With the same features.
No, not with my nose. I like your nose.
She should resemble you…
She should be as tall as me
and should be brainy like me.
If she's as tall as you, it's difficult
to get a boy for marriage.
Boys? Boys are bad!
I won't let any of them get near her.
Look who's talking!
She'll always be with us.
Hi.
Doctor, how's the baby?
Does she bear the same
features as Aaradhya?
We can't say that now.
Why are you whispering, doctor?
Say it aloud! Everyone in Pune
should also come to know about it.
Baby.
Dear, such things are common
in a seven-week pregnancy.
What's common, doctor?
Don't make me tense.
Just tell me what's wrong.
It's a miscarriage.
Baby's heart is not beating.
Is there a history of
miscarriage in your family?
But the pregnancy kit
shows that she is pregnant.
The pregnancy kit claims it,
but the scan shows the actual report.
-Is your scanning machine working?
-Of course!
Hey, Aaradhya.
Don't cry.
We can still go to better hospitals.
We'll get another opinion
from better doctors.
-Excuse me.
-Please don't cry.
You'll get the same reports everywhere.
We have to go for an MTP.
-What is MTP?
-It's a cleaning procedure.
It's a good time to sign the documents.
You will be settled for life.
Hello, who is this?
Mr. Shankar.
You're going to become an uncle
to Viplav's soon-to-be-born child.
So, tell your father-in-law
to junk the horoscopes.
Okay? Bless you.
Daddy!
-In one year…
-RK!
What happened, dude?
Why are you so dull, sister?
RK, do we need kids so soon?
It's been only a year.
We have so much more to do in life.
Don't we both need our personal space?
Luckily, the doctor said that she
was not pregnant.
What? She's not pregnant?
What about the sweets?
Distribute to everyone.
Does he want me to distribute it?
Viplav, all this happened because
we didn't do that oblation.
Aaradhya, didn't the doctor
say this is quite normal?
That's not a problem.
Shall I tell you something?
This is the time to be strong.
Everything will be fine. Okay?
-Ramaya.
-Rambhadraya.
-Ramchandraya.
Father-in-law…
-Vedhase.
Raghunathaya.
-Raghunathaya
-Aaradhya is pregnant.
Did you hear the news?
Aaradhya is pregnant.
Didn't you tell us that the defect in
their horoscope will not get her pregnant?
In less than a year, they
proved your shastras wrong.
How do we face that Satyam now?
I was shocked when I heard about
Aaradhya's pregnancy!
Just shut up.
There's no end to your horrible talk.
Shame on you to wish
ill for your niece like that.
The horoscope cannot dictate the
destiny that can be altered by the self.
Aaradhya is lucky.
Let's go see her once.
If her mother were alive, she
would have rushed immediately.
Son, let's go.
What's the matter?
I can't stop thinking about it.
My feet trembled when
the doctor broke the news.
I blanked out.
Zoya and I didn't want
to have kids for two years.
Later, Lissy was born.
But those two years were
the best time of our lives!
Put it.
You are still recently married.
You must enjoy every
moment of your life.
Otherwise, Viplav will keep
devouring that lemon rice, etc.
That fish.
It smells, right?
One piece of fish.
Give it to me.
Cutie.
Father? Is everything fine?
How are you, dear?
I can smell fish curry here!
You must be careful now, dear.
You always thought I didn't do enough.
Well, I convinced your dad to come here!
Father-in-law, look around!
There's no photo of any deity
or even a basil plant.
Oh, God!
Look there. They put liquor bottles in the
most auspicious direction of the house.
He has done it.
He has converted Aaradhya like him.
They have started
eating fish curry as well.
What a blasphemy!
Oh, no, Dad. Our neighbors
are from Kerala.
They cook meat day and night.
Did you see how she covered it up?
He saw it.
Why don't you freshen up, Dad?
Where's the marriage photo?
My dear!
Everything will be alright.
-Hey, RK, what are you doing here?
-Your dad is here.
-My dad?
-Yes.
Why?
He wants to congratulate you
on the verge of becoming a dad.
How did he come to know?
I couldn't hold the
news and told everyone.
You can't even hold urine for long, man.
Forget that, dude.
Even your dad is unable
to contain himself here.
Watch the spectacle!
-What is this?
-You know your dad better.
-Hey, Viplav. Is this true?
-What is all this, Mom?
Have some sweets.
My dear son!
You made a grandpa!
Well done, Viplav.
Sakharam will hang himself
if he comes to know about this news.
My cute son! I can't believe
you're going to be a dad.
He can't believe it either.
Look, Viplav.
That Wadekar family
is capable of rubbing all their
orthodoxy on the unborn child too.
Stay away from all that.
Don't worry about that, Dad.
Aaradhya is a good girl.
She has even learned to cook
fish curry for me.
A fish curry by Sakharam's daughter!
He's my son!
Really?
Auntie, you can't believe, right?
Hey, call Aaradhya right now
and put it on the speaker.
Son, please call your
daughter-in-law once.
-Viplav!
-Aaradhya!
My mom and dad are coming home,
can you cook fish curry for all of them?
That's not possible!
Even my dad and mom are here.
I feel numb and can't think
of anything. Where are you?
Aaradhya…
I am coming, Dad.
Aaradhya!
Got him!
Son…
we're fortunate that Aaradhya
is starting a family.
Why don't you talk to her?
What are you thinking?
Talk to her.
-Hello, Mr. Sakharam.
-Greetings.
-A great man said…
-How are you?
that you must do
oblations to beget children
and some nonsense about cow dung, etc.
Now, Viplav and Aaradhya are soon
going to be parents
without any of these rituals.
Mr. Sakharam,
there is a science behind
an apple falling from the tree.
It's called the law of gravity!
There is a science
behind a woman conceiving.
It's called the reproductive science.
To understand this,
you need to understand science.
Admit defeat if you
have any iota of shame,
and stay away from the to-be-born child.
-Sir, he is just joking--
-Shut up!
Otherwise, wipe that
sacred ash and be like us.
-Father-in-law…
-Let me finish.
-I am not pregnant!
-Aara…
It was a miscarriage.
What? Oh, no!
What, dear?
What are you saying?
The fetus couldn't survive, Grandma!
-My dear! Oh, my dear!
-It didn't survive!
It's okay, dear.
Mr. Satyam…
You said something a while ago.
Science, my foot!
That there's a science
behind an apple falling…
and that there's a science
behind a healthy baby's birth.
But nothing happens without
the five elements of nature.
Science is born out of creation.
Creation is not born out of science.
-Look, Mr. Sakharam--
-Folks like you won't get it. Leave it.
You will only conceive if
an oblation is performed.
I am saying this as your well-wisher dad…
and not as Sakharam Maharaj.
Let me console him.
Come with me.
Take care of her.
Baby…
Why did you rush to tell them the truth?
You could have withheld for a day.
-Are you angry with me?
-Not that, Aaradhya.
Use your brains, sometimes.
You can't get emotional all the time.
Baby, just listen to me--
Did you notice?
Yesterday was the first night we slept
without kissing each other.
You're looking fresh.
What do you mean?
I've been crying the whole night, Viplav.
What happened, dear?
Why did you slam the door on me?
I didn't slam the door on you.
I let it slide slowly.
I was…
-You deliberately did it.
-Why would I?
Why didn't you utter a word when
your dad verbally abused my dad?
Well, didn't we decide
not to take any sides?
Being silent is also
tantamount to taking sides.
-You were sleeping like a log.
-What?
What if I had taken an extreme step?
Aaradhya, why are you getting worked up?
You don't know what happened, madam.
Madam, we want to stay
away from both sides.
How can I scold my dad
in front of her dad?
I didn't ask you to scold him.
I said you could've stopped.
Well, you stopped it
all by telling the truth.
As if you never lied to anyone.
What did I lie about?
Forget it now.
It's okay, Viplav, tell me.
When did I lie to you?
Pakistan.
Feroze.
Terrorist camp.
She has lied to me as well, madam.
I was large-hearted
enough to forgive her.
Stop it, Viplav.
Let's discuss this later.
It's getting late for the office.
Yes, I told all lies.
I should have also lied that I didn't love
you. It would have saved all this labor.
I deserve this for
leaving everything for you.
Why are you behaving like a kid?
Is it right for you to intrude when wife
and husband are arguing?
Hey…
why are you venting out on her?
You calm down.
Apologize to her.
Why should she say sorry to me?
Don't bother, dear.
Let's go to the office now.
Apologize to her, Aaradhya.
Sorry, madam.
Viplav…
Aaradhya is a girl with self-esteem.
She is hurt for sure.
Let it be, madam.
Nothing will happen.
She said she erred in trusting you.
That's an uneasy
feeling for any girl to get.
Madam, we should
keep them within their limits.
Hey, stop.
What happened, madam?
Get down.
What did you say?
We should keep them within their limits.
That applies to all the women, right?
That coconut seller, Aaradhya,
myself, everyone, right?
What is the connection with
that coconut seller, madam?
Well, didn't you just say it?
Why do you paint every
woman with the same brush?
You're just like any other male.
Do one thing.
Walk to the office.
Madam.
Yes, just think about what you said.
Don't leave me here, madam.
Why is Aaradhya doing this?
The moment I stepped in…
she said I slammed the door on her,
and she felt like committing suicide.
Even I am outside that door now.
What if I also commit suicide?
Marriage itself means
writing our own obituary.
You are a dead meat. RIP…
Sir, shall I squeeze a lemon?
Who asked you to barge in like this?
We were bitching about our wives!
Get the hell out of here.
Keep the munchies here.
You should always be kept
within your limits.
You…
Have you got any shame?
Why do you talk like a male chauvinist?
How do we treat women then?
You should think highly of them.
Oh. Okay.
Sister. Sorry. Please don't mind.
Please squeeze a lemon.
Squeeze one for him first.
Sister! Hey!
-Sister, wait!
-How many glasses will you break?
Why are you scared so much?
Relax. Come.
What do you think about me?
People may have their opinions about me.
But I am a feminist at heart.
Please sit. Sit.
Sit down.
Clean yourself.
Wow!
Poor Aaradhya. I can empathize
with how she must be feeling.
I just wanted to draw her
closer, hug her, and say sorry.
You can still do that.
Just imagine our maid Lakshmi
to be Aaradhya for a moment.
You can hug her
-Dirty fellow!
-and show your emotions.
Aaradhya is the only woman
I have in my life.
Nobody else.
Okay, sir.
I can't stand these night shifts.
What are you wearing
for tomorrow's success party?
I am not in the mood for it.
Hey, there's your husband!
Look, there.
Aaradhya!
Baby.
Look at your eyes.
They are restless.
You should stop these night shifts.
Hold this.
Have this coffee.
I made it.
Baby! Hey!
Baby, have it. Please.
Dear, do you know him?
-Yes.
-No.
-Baby…
-Don't you have any other work?
Auntie, no.
She's kidding.
Move out. Go and stand over there.
-Baby, tell her.
-Move.
-Take this as well.
Baby, say something.
-Today's match was excellent!
-It was great!
-He batted so well!
-He could have been dismissed.
We bowled really well as well.
He took three wickets.
If not for him,
we would have lost the match.
-The match went till the last ball!
-Exactly.
It was fun.
-Shall I play? I'll teach you.
-No.
-Let me teach you. Leave it!
-Hey!
-Please!
-Let me play.
Say it…
-I am yours!
-Hey!
Hey, give it back.
Do you want me to call the police?
Hey, the teacher is upset.
Guys, it's finals tomorrow.
Let's be serious about it.
Hey, listen!
She's the girl from our colony.
Remember the one at the medical shop?
She's trying hard for a kid
for over a year now.
Baby…
You're tender like a baby.
Do you still need babies?
Hi.
Dilip!
Why don't you give me a chance?
-I will fulfill your wish.
-Hey.
I've helped many aunties get pregnant.
I can assist you as well.
You can trust me.
Just give me a chance.
Please! Just give me a chance. Please!
Dilip!
Hey!
Never tease a lady
if she is wearing a nuptial chain.
Especially when her husband is with her.
That's me.
Hey, if I hit, it will be a six for sure!
-Got it?
-Hey!
-Go and hit it then!
Hey, I am the best player
from Ghatkopar! Don't mess with me!
-Get lost!
-Teacher!
Say it…
I wrecked you!
We are sorry, sir.
Out!
-He smashed us!
-Let's get out of here!
Let's go!
Baby!
Baby, sorry.
We didn't talk for two days.
I won't leave you until you talk to me.
Baby.
I feel these rifts are because
of the defects my dad pointed out.
What are you saying?
I don't think so.
What about the miscarriage?
That's a medical condition.
Didn't the doctor say that
it is quite common?
What about the fight on the terrace?
Oh, that's not a fight.
It's a miscommunication.
We're the best couple in the colony.
Nothing will crop up between us.
Don't you believe me?
Okay.
The world will see how good
a husband I am for the next 24 hours.
Baby!
Let's both get tested.
If there's some issue, we will fix it.
Else, as my dad said…
Why talk about your dad?
You want to get tested, right?
I will do…
as you say.
Fix it!
Love you, baby.
Isn't the doctor here?
Hello, brother.
My friend, Viplav is a fresher.
Five years seniority.
You…
Why are you calling me out by name?
I will leave if you do all this.
Hey, just sit down, dude.
We're meeting Dappu Subhani,
the best sexologist in Kurla.
Don't call him a sexologist.
It is a fertility clinic.
There are deadly stories about him, dude!
But why are you embarrassing me, dude?
Please keep quiet.
I don't doubt my abilities.
I came here because of Aaradhya.
Calm down, man.
Love you too, nurse.
-Idiot!
-Let's go.
Hi, Subhani sir.
-Come sit.
-Greetings.
He's my friend, sir.
Works like a bull, but to no avail!
His wife wants a child.
Please help him out, sir.
What's the hurry?
Let them take the test.
If the test is successful,
will they beget children?
What's the hurry?
Let them take the test.
What if there's a problem?
What's the hurry?
Let them take the test.
-Sir, you must make him manly again.
-Hey!
What's the hurry?
-Let them take the test.
-Come.
-Go! Get it done.
-Okay, sir.
Viplav, be blessed with kids.
Fill it to the brim.
Is it the Niagara Falls?
Come, let's go.
Hey!
What happened?
Look at the rush!
-This doctor is very famous!
-I am not staying here!
Hey, stop! Let me handle it!
Come. Uncle, move aside, please.
Move aside!
We are from the department.
So what?
How can you jump the queue?
Uncle, my friend is from BSNL.
This test is very important for him.
Don't tell them about me.
Our phones have not been working
for the past two months. Go, fix it.
It has been fixed. Go and check it.
We all have the same problem.
Please try to understand.
-What's there to understand?
-What are you talking?
Listen to me for a minute.
-Listen to me. Try to understand.
-Don't we have anything else to do?
Hey! Shut up!
My name is Viplav.
A BSNL employee.
Just wait for two minutes.
I will fill the container and come out.
-What nonsense is this?
-How can you let him go inside?
I have sent you a link on WhatsApp.
For ten years of our company.
-Cheers.
And Michael,
as I promised, your project
was completed on time.
Thanks to my dedication,
devotion, and hard work.
Not yours.
It's Aaradhya's hard work.
Of course, but she's on my team.
Can you leave us for some time?
Now?
Aaradhya.
I am so impressed with your work.
You are a big support for me.
Thank you, Michael.
Hey, listen to me.
Whatever happens in life,
never miss a party, dude.
Okay? Just chill.
-Aaradhya.
-Wow! Hey!
Are you married?
Yes, I am.
That's bad news for me.
Otherwise, I would've married you.
He's into you.
Anyone can easily fall in love with you.
Hey, what happened?
That white fellow says
he will date her if she is single.
She should have slapped him!
But she's laughing with him.
-I don't want to stay here. Let's go home.
-Hey, wait.
The drinks are free.
Let's have some and then leave.
I promise. Just two drinks.
-One drink for you, two for me.
-Excuse me.
-Hey, no. Let's go.
-Please…
Viplav…
-Hi.
-Let me introduce my client.
No need.
-Are you okay?
-Go.
What happened to the test?
He must have failed the test.
He's surely down now.
Guys are very sensitive on these matters.
Don't ask him now, Aaradhya.
You can discuss it at home.
Come.
Pour me some more.
Perfect. Yes.
Here. Drink it.
Everything will be fine after two drinks.
Drink. Come on!
Come on. Drink.
Cheers.
Hey!
Who are you? who invited you?
I am his friend, sir.
Aaradhya told us about Viplav.
Where did he come from?
What is this?
What are you drinking?
-It is a foreign brand.
-Glenfiddich.
-Repeat after me.
-Fridge.
It's beyond your status, man!
It is for premium people like me.
You can't buy this one
with even your monthly salary.
Go to the other counter.
We've kept cheap liquor
for freeloaders like you.
Go.
Idiot. What's wrong with you?
Give me a tissue.
Even my dad has never
humiliated me like this.
At home, she is always depressed.
Look how happy she is with her colleagues.
I throw a party for many friends
every day at my penthouse.
Now he's talking about my status!
She won't even talk to me
just because I said no?
She should come here and talk to me.
Dude, you're always obsessed
with your wife. Don't you value me?
I've helped you so much! Got you married!
Took you to the doctor.
Your pain is mine,
but my pain isn't yours!
You didn't even say anything to that jerk
after he humiliated me!
You look nice.
-Come with me.
-Why?
Now Glen-fridge won't work.
Only cheap liquor will soothe your pain.
Do you understand?
Mustafa, Mustafa!
-Don't worry, Mustafa!
-I am sorry.
Viplav, remember me?
I am Ratna.
From Wilson High School?
-Oh…
-Ratna!
-Tenth class, C-section.
-You were so small.
-How you've grown!
-I proposed to you thrice then.
-Me?
-But you rejected me every time.
-Oh, shit!
Are you mad? Who rejects a girl?
-I was a kid. I made a mistake.
-How could you?
Apologize. Apologize to her.
Sorry, Ratna.
But bad luck. I am married now.
I am happy that you got married.
-Why?
-Because now I have three beautiful kids.
I feel sorry for your plight.
So sad!
My plight?
Hey!
Why is Ratna feeling sad for me, brother?
What happened to me?
Aaradhya, my uncle is a
famous doctor in Australia.
He has treated men
aged over 50 for infertility.
Let's consult him for Viplav.
I know a saint from Solapur.
Let's take Viplav there.
How do all of them know about it?
Did you tell them?
Why will I tell them?
I thought he was a powerhouse.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to kill myself.
-Don't worry.
-I'm going to die.
Why is she telling everybody
about my personal issues?
These wives can't
keep anything to themselves.
Hey, stop it. Are you crazy?
Get on the stage!
Announce it! Go!
Greetings to everyone.
A humble request to all the folks here
who are agog with discussions
about my virulence and manliness.
I just got the lab test results.
I've got the certificate
for my virulence.
But my wife is spreading
fake stories to defame me.
Let me now share a story about my--
Sorry.
I mean, wives in general.
Just listen to me.
Hey!
For the first time
I saw her in Kashmir
Without thinking anything
I started loving her
Without listening to my mother
I came out for her
Got married married to her
And made a blunder!
Then the struggle began
She has changed day by day
My dear wife
You have become like a hot chili
Please stop dear
I am struggling like a hen
Before the butcher kills it
Listen everybody
Let me tell you something
Don't even dream to get married
Wife is powerful than gun
She will get you pissed
Listen every body
Let me tell you something
Don't even dream to get married
Wife is powerful than gun
She will get you pissed
They won't open the door
When we go home late
If we drink with friends
They will peel off the skin with words
They always keeps eye on ex-girlfriend
They can track their husbands
Like a drone
They pamper you with nicknames
They will treat you like God
On special occasions
If we speak one word against them
Just do as you have been instructed
Wife became a knife
Life has become arid
With her entry
My fate has burnt to ashes
Wives are ghosts
Ghosts are wives
Wives… you are not good wives
Ghosts… you are all ghosts
My dear wife
You have become like a hot chili
Please stop
Please stop dear
I am struggling like a hen
Before the butcher kills it
Listen, everybody
Let me tell you something
Don't even dream to get married
Wife is powerful than gun
She will get you pissed
Listen, everybody
Let me tell you something
Don't even dream to get married
Wife is powerful than gun
She will get you pissed
We've a fight in less than 24 hours.
Who said couples don't fight?
This is very common.
If both of us don't have a problem,
then where's the problem?
You tell me about it.
As my dad foretold, the problem
lies in that horoscope defect.
All this is because you
haven't done that oblation yet.
Aaradhya…
my dad has an image
to live up to in society.
I can't make him do all these rituals.
Please give me some time.
Everything will get sorted.
Nothing will change for years, Viplav.
Do you remember that one day
we were talking about miscarriage
at a traffic signal,
and a saint threw holy ash
and said the same thing?
So?
Everyone is trying to
nudge us to do the oblation.
Hey!
Have you gone mad?
Are you possessed?
So, you trust the devil but can't
seem to believe in God!
Oh, Aaradhya. Just leave me alone.
So, do you want me to walk out?
No, I am asking you
to leave me now!
Let me go to sleep.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Viplav.
Who were you thinking about
during the test?
When I was young,
I saw the movie Titanic.
So whenever I am in a bad mood,
I talk to that heroine.
Why?
Did you think
I was thinking about you?
Have something.
Did you guys fight again?
It's Lissy's birthday in two days.
Thomas and I are going to Alleppey.
It's a beautiful place.
You and Aaradhya need a change.
Both of you can come with us.
Oh, madam.
Why us?
We don't want to play
spoilsport in your party.
Don't make excuses, Viplav.
It's my daughter's birthday.
Please listen to me…
Come with her,
or I'll send you back to Kashmir.
Okay?
Zoya and her
husband left for Alleppey.
I just dropped them off at the airport.
It's Lissy's birthday.
They also invited us.
It will be nice to go to Kerala.
Look, Aaradhya…
Zoya ma'am has helped us
a lot since day one.
So, drop your ego…
I mean,
let's drop our egos and go there.
They will be happy to have us.
Let us not be childish…
and act more mature.
Sir, Kunjappan's boat is the
best boat available in Alleppey.
If you are in love, you will tie the
knot when you get onto this boat.
If you are married,
you will have kids here.
How many kids do you have?
How many kids?
Tell me.
You drive it.
Go forward.
Give me some water.
Aaradhya.
It's not what you think.
I am in my monthly cycle.
We would have canceled
the program in that case.
Now, you say that.
But if I said this earlier…
you would have been angry at me
and called me a liar. That's why I didn't.
Please don't start arguing with me.
-Am I arguing?
-Obviously!
All I am saying is that…
you should have told me before
we started. What's wrong with that?
Did you really ask me
if I was alright or not?
Why do you girls turn out like
this after marriage?
Always fussing about it.
If you didn't want to spend time with me,
you could've stayed back at home.
I came here for Zoya madam.
Superb! Thank you.
Just stay patient for two days for the
sake of Zoya madam without fighting!
Later, you can do what you feel like.
You can decide if you want to stay with me
or go to your house.
Let's stay away from
each other for two days.
You are driving me crazy!
The moment
When my heart dissolves
In your nearness
Praising your name
With all my heart
Is all I want
Oh Lord
Who saves this world
With boundless love
In your world
My child's life is
Sweeter than the elixir
Let's celebrate Lissy's birthday.
Happy birthday, Lissy.
Happy birthday.
Okay. Thank you, Father.
Come on, let's enjoy.
-Everybody, please enjoy!
-Enjoy your food and drinks.
-Viplav! Welcome.
-Hi, Viplav. Aaradhya.
Hey, why are you looking sad, Viplav?
Don't you know it is
Lissy's birthday today?
Come, let's enjoy.
Lissy doesn't like gloomy faces.
It is Lissy's birthday, Viplav.
You must have a drink.
Right?
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers, Aaradhya.
No!
What happened to Lissy, madam?
Lissy… Her time's up.
She's gone.
I still remember the
day I delivered Lissy.
She was a premature baby…
with most features unformed yet.
When I picked her up,
the doctors warned that…
she was extremely fragile
and may break her bones.
My heart sank…
that very moment.
All the relatives who saw her
left without saying a word.
Doctors gave her just six months.
That was when Thomas held my hand…
and said…
he would do everything in
his power to save her life.
The confidence he gave me…
helped us save Lissy for five years.
After that, we didn't want any kids.
We don't want to…
trouble another life.
We just became kids to each other.
With or without Lissy…
Thomas stood like a
rock of support for me.
Thomas is my courage.
Hey.
Why talk melancholic
-when the mood is so upbeat?
-Correct.
Yes, Viplav.
Backwaters…
romantic mood…
Enjoy.
-Right?
-Yes.
Enjoy.
Aaradhya.
Kunjappan!
Yes, brother?
Did you see Aaradhya?
Who?
Aaradhya? My wife?
Hey, Johnson!
What?
Did you see his wife
traveling in a boat?
Yes, she left a while ago.
Sir, she left. Is there a problem?
Kunjappan, take the boat out!
It's difficult to catch up in a boat.
Let's go on the bike.
There she is, sir.
Aaradhya.
Where are you going?
As you wanted, I came for Zoya madam.
Now I am leaving.
Where are you going, Aaradhya?
Pune.
To Alleppey Railway Station.
Okay then, let me also join you.
Why do you want to come when
you wish to part ways, Viplav?
What are you saying, Aaradhya?
You don't get what I want.
When I tell you, you get irritated.
I am scared to even talk to you, Viplav.
All this while, I thought
you had a problem only with
my family and our orthodox ways.
Ma'am, will you come or not?
But you have a problem with me.
Aara…
Dear heart
Biding goodbye to us
Amidst nostalgic thoughts
I hope you are happy
The heart is wounded
Wishing to end life
Your eyes wound me
Like a thorn
Heart is lost in anxiety
While silent pauses go up
We go on our separate paths
Our lives don't walk along now
You stood by me
All these days like a loyal shadow
But now you desire to
Desert me for few days only
Every thought
In remembrance of you
Is meditation in love
But even a moment of forgetting me
Makes me pine for you
The heart is wounded
Wishing to end life
We go on our separate paths
Our lives don't walk along now
Hello!
Aaradhya!
Hello, Mr. Shankar.
It's common to see fights
between a wife and a husband.
My friend is pining for Aaradhya, sir.
Please ask her to talk to him once.
What's there to talk about now?
There is no relationship between them.
Aaradhya herself says it's all over.
It seems there's nothing between the
both of you. Aaradhya herself said it.
Let's leave.
It's getting late.
I can't stay without her, dude.
Like a kite that burns in fire
I burn in love
Even in my wildest dreams
I cannot imagine forgetting you
Pierce me with as many arrows as you want
My love
Won't reduce a bit
You can test me
The heart is wounded
Wishing to end life
Your eyes wound me
Like a thorn
Heart is lost in anxiety
While silent pauses go up
We go on our separate paths
Our lives don't walk along now
Dear heart
Biding goodbye to us
Amidst nostalgic thoughts
I hope you are happy
The auspicious time needs to be changed.
I will consult my father-in-law
and revert.
Call me after reaching Kothrud.
Father-in-law!
I will do the sacred oblation, sir.
What about your father?
Both of you need
to perform the oblation together.
My father-in-law made this very clear.
I still reiterate the same.
Is the hard-core atheist
Mr. Lenin Satyam coming to the temple?
Aaradhya.
We will talk about it only
after the oblation.
Oh, it's you, son! Come inside.
Why don't you call him in?
Does he really want to come inside our
home amid the cows and the rituals we do?
Carry on. We'll notify you later.
Do you want to do the oblation?
This is their plan
to make me appear like a clown in public.
You can go for it
but don't drag me into it.
I am warning you again. You can't stand
their nonsense for even ten minutes.
I am done with this discussion.
Forget Aaradhya.
Dad, aren't you and Mom
now married for 30 years?
Of course.
Mom never believed in your philosophies.
She still believes in God.
How did you stand her
for all these years?
Why didn't you desert mom?
She is my wife…
and I…
love her too much.
If your love for your wife
can stand for 30 years…
can't I stand my wife for three hours to
sit for the oblation and oblige her?
The oblation is in Pune tomorrow.
It starts with me,
but it will be completed
only with your presence.
I am leaving.
Wear this dhoti and circumambulate
101 times around the temple.
Then you must sit for the oblation.
Is your dad here?
If this Satyam fellow doesn't turn up,
the whole ceremony will be a waste!
-Are we ready for the oblation, priest?
-Yes, we are ready.
Dear, can you help me tie up?
You're such a grown-up!
Don't you know how to wear a dhoti?
Turn around.
Hey, the boy is here.
Talk to him.
Aaradhya…
I need to speak to you once.
Aaradhya.
Hey, Viplav.
Did she speak to you?
What's this attire?
Can't you make out if the
damn thing is coming off?
Hey, we need a holy cow.
What cow?
We need to gift one cow after the ritual.
Get one.
A cow?
-It's only been a minute since he set foot
-Mom, where's dad?
in a temple,
and my friend has already changed.
You wished for too much
to expect your dad to turn up.
For him, it is principles
before anything else.
Let me sit on his behalf.
I will convince her dad.
Mom, he won't allow it.
The ritual will be completed
only if Dad comes.
But he won't!
He sees God and these
temples as mere stones.
But in reality,
he himself is made out of stone!
How did you think
he would mend ways
and come for the oblation
only for his son? Is this possible?
But I will do anything for you, my son.
Even if it means,
falling at their feet. Yes.
Tell me…
what do I need to do, Son?
You don't worry…
Father-in-law, Lenin Satyam has arrived!
Put kumkum on the forehead.
Put it on your forehead.
Pray to God.
Sir, hold your nose with
your hands and say, "mama."
"Mama."
Pray to God to grant your wish.
Make a wish.
Like this.
Dear, can I bring water for you?
Dad, are you okay?
I am fine.
If you place that in the sacred fire,
then the ritual will be done.
Get up.
Let's go.
Bring your dad inside.
Fast.
Dear, come inside.
Viplav, bring your dad inside.
Ask him to come in.
Come inside.
Oh, God! Why did it have to rain?
It's okay.
I'll participate in the ritual
however long it takes.
I am fine if I lose,
and you win.
But my son…
is going to prosper.
That's enough for me.
Mr. Satyam…
when Viplav relented and
came home to commit to this ritual,
I didn't think I won.
We saw the depth of love
your son had for my daughter.
Even today, when you stooped down to
perform this oblation for your son's sake,
I didn't see that as my victory.
I only saw your love for your son.
While fighting for my
shastras or your philosophy,
we are forgetting humanity.
I know that even if I seem like a winner
by making you bend your
way to sit through the ritual,
I have lost it as a human being.
What's the point?
Before I called it off,
God intervened and called it off.
He will take care of both the kids now.
You can leave with my
daughter after the rain stops.
Aaradhya, I will do any
number of rigorous rituals…
or do as many tests as you want.
But please stay with me.
If this oblation can settle our love,
I would have agreed to it long back.
I wanted both of us to overcome all
of this and prove that we are strong.
What does strong mean, Viplav?
Is it called being strong
to separate over a disagreement?
Will you fight the world alone?
I will ensure we will never
fight again, Aaradhya.
Fights will happen, Viplav.
Fights will happen.
But if we stay united despite that,
we can say we are stronger.
Perhaps these arguments
may seem irritating to you,
but for me, I see it as love.
We are women, Viplav.
There are things we confess to God…
that we wouldn't dare share
even with our dad or husband.
And I left that…
God to be with you.
Where should I go if you ask me to leave?
I am still learning, Aaradhya.
I am still learning.
I can see the pain you went through.
And I can see the affection
behind your desire to do the ritual.
But when I was alone for ten days…
It felt like
my life had become a living hell!
The way Thomas stood like a rock for Zoya…
That's true love.
I promise to stand by you too.
Each and every day,
for the rest of our lives!
Let's complete this ritual
and get back home, Aaradhya.
I don't want any more
of these rituals, Viplav.
All I need is your love.
Whether we beget kids or not,
or whether we spend our
last days in an old-age home,
but we must be together.
Our kids?
Before they send us to an old-age home,
I will send them to a hostel.
Let us demonstrate to the world
that we are meant for each other.
Let's prove it.
Hello, grandfathers…
as I told you, Aaradhya and Viplav are
happily married, and have a baby girl now.
How do you both feel now?
Hello, what's the matter?
Why did you call me
when you wanted to talk to each other?
What's happening?
What's wrong with you?
You call the famous Brahma Tiwari
from Kanpur here
to get the baby girl's ears pierced
and then ignore him?
-Where is the baby? Call her.
-I will call her.
Aaradhya, get the baby.
Wait! Are you going to
pierce her ear with that?
You are scared as if I am holding a sword.
It will be over in no time.
It will prick like an ant bite, Viplav.
Just give her to your mom.
-Be careful!
It's okay, dear.
You'll be fine.
-Be careful!
I understand that you
really care about the baby.
Do we stop taking a vaccine
just because it causes momentary pain?
Okay, I have an idea.
-Be careful!
-I think I should just retire.
Sir, just be a bit careful.
With soft hands.
How? Show me.
Just be careful. Please.
Please be careful.
We are just asking you to be careful.
Why don't you come and do this yourself?
Everyone is instructing me.
Not now. We'll do it
after the girl grows up.
How will you get it done?
Will she listen to you after she grows up?
Better do it after she reaches her age.
You can call me then.
I will do the needful. Strange people.
-Oh, no. Guruji, please don't go.
-What is this nonsense?
Sit down.
-Viplav, just get it done!
-No, Mom.
-Why?
-Just look at me.
-Yes.
-Look into my eyes.
-Come here, dear.
-Look here. It's fine.
-Please carry on, Guruji.
-Don't look there.
Dear God, let it happen this time.
Do not worry. Stay calm.
Look at me.
It's over.
Look at how cute she is.
All that drama
just to get an ear pierced!
I got tired of hearing "Be careful."
By the way, what did you name her?