Helsinki, get out of there.
Take shelter in the museum.
I'm making a trench!
Helsinki, do you copy?
Helsinki, are you there?
Fatty!
I'm alive.
Get out of there now!
Leg trapped.
Open wound.
Blood.
Lots of blood.
Don't fall asleep. We're almost there.
I promise you, once we get out of here,
I'm going to show you,
three nights in a row,
why Argentinian meat
is the best in the world.
And then what?
You'll take me to the movies?
Yes, but only if you don't fall asleep.
Promise me you'll stay awake.
I'm awake.
Squadrons three and nine, now!
Move! Come on!
They're here.
We don't know what just happened.
It looks like a terrible explosion.
There are hundreds of people
here at the Bank of Spain…
LIVE
HEIST AT THE BANK OF SPAIN
This is the Professor.
The stormwater tank is safe.
I request an assessment
of the situation. Palermo!
They blew up the roof! Bogotá,
Rio and I are going to the top floor.
Helsinki's trapped.
Lisbon, location.
Second floor, with Stockholm.
Tokyo, location.
About to go out onto the roof.
We'll attack them from behind.
-No, don't open that door!
-What?
-And Helsinki?
-They'll kill you.
They're coming down!
Cover the flanks and stay together.
If you don't go, they'll kill Helsinki.
Go!
Should we go out or not?
There are 100 snipers aiming
at the roof, and they're soldiers.
They won't let you attack
from behind. They'll blow your heads off.
Professor, you're sacrificing a man!
The only way to save him
is to attack on two flanks.
We'll use the hole in the roof.
But you have to get out there
without getting killed, and I know how.
Go get the hostages.
Maintain your position!
Fire at three o'clock!
Come on!
Gandía!
Take cover! Quick!
Now!
Everyone take cover!
We'd often thought we were at war.
But that was simply because
we didn't know what war actually was.
Frederiksborg Castle.
It has tight security measures.
Just to get in or out, you must go through
two arches with metal detectors
and armed security guards.
All that's before you reach the party.
It'll be the perfect soiree.
Fancy cars, tuxedos,
cocktails, classical music
and 12 kilos of gold.
Tatiana's fingers will work their magic.
And all we have to do is enjoy the party.
Why? By then, the trickiest part
of the job will have been taken care of.
In fact, you'll have done it
the day before.
-Me?
-Yes, you.
You're the only one among us
with the plain, inconspicuous appearance
of a piano tuner.
What's this?
Well,
it's a magnetic stripe card reader,
a skimmer for cloning cards.
Exactly!
This will be concealed, right?
This is normally used to steal
card information at ATMs and all that.
Tatiana will suddenly feel indisposed.
Nerves, the concert…
I need some air.
So you'll be left on your own
with a magnificent grand piano.
You'll need help.
This type of magnetic stripe card cloner
requires you to be within ten centimeters
of the card you want to clone
for 30 seconds, obviously.
That's easy,
they'll be hanging from their necks.
Nothing a stubborn B-flat can't fix.
Then your tool cart comes into play.
That's where we'll hide the fake pieces.
It's coated with barium sulfate,
so an X-ray machine won't detect anything.
They'll escort you to the safe place
where the pieces will be kept.
From then on,
Hans will be the only problem.
-Hans?
-The security guard at the gold room.
He's always by the door.
He never leaves.
This man has no wife,
no dog, no kids,
and his father is senile.
What's his weak spot?
I don't know. A second-degree relative?
Why resort to a second-degree relative?
His father is senile.
His father.
His father's senile.
He's in a sanitarium.
He doesn't recognize anyone anymore.
-Bring in Cristoff.
-Copy that.
Rafael.
The briefcase.
Thank you.
We're in.
Set Cristoff free.
Walk towards the music, Cristoff.
Towards the music.
Cristoff is on the move.
-Cameras?
-I'm accessing the system.
Music.
I got it.
It's on a loop.
Music.
Picture Hans's astonishment.
He thinks his father is in a sanitarium,
in slippers, watching Wheel of Fortune,
and all of a sudden…
Music.
This is Bear 3. Emergency in Room 1.
I need an immediate replacement in Room 1.
Copy that, Bear 3.
On my way.
Rock and roll.
There's something I haven't told you.
I have absolutely no idea
what's in there.
Music.
You never know
what you'll find in a secret vault.
It's beautiful.
Let's do it.
They're encrypted safe-deposit boxes.
Excuse me.
And that is the key
that opens all the doors.
Good. Which box contains the gold?
The information is in here.
It's a matter of coding. I can hack it.
This box is attached to a beam.
It's a fixed structure.
Because the walls move.
This is the most fascinating
security system I've ever seen.
He just found his father.
Don't grow too fond of it, son.
You've got one minute to blow it up.
I can't do this in one minute, Dad.
Jakov, it's an emergency.
We need three minutes.
-I can't do it in three minutes either.
-It's okay, don't worry.
You'll have plenty of time
to figure it out in jail.
Excuse me.
I'm a doctor.
I think this gentleman doesn't feel well.
He's disoriented.
It's nothing serious. Thanks.
Come on, Dad.
-Come on!
-I found the gold. I'm breaking the code.
-How much longer?
-I don't know.
Jakov.
Two minutes.
Got it!
Excuse me.
Out there…
One minute, Jakov.
He crossed the line with some ladies.
What?
The president of the foundation
almost called the police.
What did he do?
He said
inappropriate things.
What things?
About…
genitals.
Did you see if he was with someone
or how he got here?
Move aside.
Come on, Dad.
Andrés, Hans is suspicious.
They're headed your way.
Excuse me.
Jakov, it's done.
We're out.
The adrenaline,
the endorphins…
You feel powerful. Don't you, son?
It's amazing.
The most important lesson comes now.
That's it.
What are you doing? No.
Dad?
Dad!
-Why?
-I'm teaching you a lesson!
A lesson? I can't believe this.
You just threw away 12 kilos of gold.
That's 15 million euros.
Teach me a lesson, my ass.
Look at you.
Only a thief can feel
that something they don't own is theirs.
Now you know you're one of us.
So, next time,
leave that arrogance
and moral superiority behind
and don't you ever
call your father a cynic again.
Now it's time to enjoy ourselves.
I came here to listen to Tatiana play.
Bravo!
The dream of any thief is
to leave the place of the heist
surrounded by applause,
people taking pictures, smiling,
calm, determined
and in love.
And, above all,
free of any suspicion.
We'll leave the country undetected,
in a beautiful, small boat,
celebrating Tatiana's success,
headed to Malmö, Sweden.
What's wrong with him?
A tantrum.
I never know
whether he's tired, hungry or gassy.
My love, are you ready?
Of course.
Let's have a look!
You expected us
to walk out the door with it?
I never took you to play tennis.
We never cycled up
a mountain pass together or went rowing.
You wouldn't have learned anything new
from doing that with your father.
But here, you will.
If you really want something in life,
you have to steal it from whomever has it.
That's how the world works, my son.
Now!
We're here, Fatty. Don't worry.
Stay calm, Fatty. I'm here.
Arteche.
Arteche!
I can't hear anything. Tosco's injured.
His pulse is very weak.
It hit the femoral artery.
We gotta make a fucking tourniquet.
Breathe, Fatty.
We'll get you out of here, you hear me?
Put it higher. Higher. Come on.
Sagasta, do you copy?
-What the hell is going on?
-It was a hostile rocket.
I want a damage report now!
Shut your fucking mouth, Colonel.
I have wounded men in here.
Canalejas, we have to make
a trench to secure the perimeter--
Hey, look at me.
This is going to hurt. Ready?
Three, two, one.
Get the bomb disposal robot.
Any second now, we'll go in from below.
We're going up!
It's your lucky day.
We're running a drill, like in school.
So keep quiet and get in line.
You're the infantry now.
Matías, the backpacks with the equipment.
We're going to the roof.
Copy that.
Come on, move!
Palermo, cut my fucking leg off.
Cut it off.
Look at me.
I won't cut your leg off,
you hear me? I won't.
Palermo,
my femur, tibia and knee are shattered.
Everything.
They'll cut it off in the hospital.
You know damn well, Palermo.
This will make you feel better.
We'll get you out. Stop being stupid.
Fatty, stay calm. I'm here with you.
Look at me, Mirko.
Hey, look at me.
He's right.
It's a marble column.
It weighs at least two tons.
We can't move it, Palermo.
I'll cut it off.
No, let's find a fucking lever
and move the statue!
We need something strong.
Back stairs.
The snipers have to think you're hostages.
Have half of them remove their masks.
You've got one minute to get up there.
You're going to play
the role of your lives!
I want an Oscar-winning performance!
Is that clear? Come on!
That's it.
Come on!
Ms. Tokyo, wait. I have a stitch.
Come on, we're almost there.
Pass me a bandage, Bogotá.
-Don't fall asleep.
-Hang in there.
-Stay calm, Fatty.
It looks much better.
Fatty, hey.
You're with me, right?
-Palermo.
-Open your eyes.
Keep your eyes open, Fatty.
Helsinki. Look at me, Fatty, please.
Look at me. Come on, Fatty!
Fatty, look at me, for fuck's sake!
Don't go. Look at me.
Palermo, would that beam work?
Cover us.
Thank you.
Lisbon, hurry up. We need covering fire.
We're going out. Everybody ready?
-They're going to kill us!
-Nobody's going to kill you.
I might kill you
for being so annoying, but they won't.
They won't kill any of you
'cause half of you will remove
your masks. Is that clear?
Make sure they can see you're hostages.
You'll remove your mask.
You too. You and you too, darling.
Okay, good.
Masks.
Professor.
Bomb squad. They're preparing
to enter at the ground floor.
Let's go!
They're preparing a second attack.
Why'd you release the governor?
Tell me there's a plan.
We hid a microphone in the handcuffs.
I thought we'd have a chance
if the handcuffs were removed
before they were searched
with the radio frequency detector.
We're getting him out.
And I'll tell you why.
And?
We've got Tamayo by the balls.
Contact Pakistan.
You're the sexiest woman in the world,
but I love you for your mind.
I'm a little busy with a war here.
Let's talk dirty later.
Sounds good.
Benjamín, call your men.
Let's prepare the foundry.
Alicia.
Marseille, go out and buy pacifiers,
diapers, a crib. Anything that's needed.
Are you breast- or bottle-feeding?
Breast and bottle, okay? Let's do it all.
And bring something for his foot.
He didn't notice that I shot him.
By the way, I think you should give
your cartridge clip to Marseille.
For everyone's safety.
Thank you.
Professor, we're on the roof.
Good. Tokyo, it's important
that they don't see you're armed.
Keep the equipment inside the weapon bag.
Tie one end of a rope to the bag
and the other end to one of you.
You'll get to the hole in the roof
by hiding among the hostages.
Matías, we need your help.
As soon as I say "stampede,"
shoot to distract the snipers.
Then pull the rope
and retrieve the bag. Understood?
Palermo. Stockholm and I are in position.
Lisbon, smoke in five,
four,
three,
two, one.
Good luck.
Now!
Smoke!
Covering fire!
I have no visual!
Come on, Rio.
Tokyo, now.
Don't shoot!
I'm Miguel Fernández Talanilla
from Totana, Murcia.
They're on the roof
and are removing their masks.
If anyone goes near the hole, open fire.
Copy that.
The robot. Enter through the door now.
They can't handle the commando
and hostages at the same time.
-Now's the time.
-You got it.
Don't shoot!
Exit achieved, Professor.
Come on!
Bandage, now!
We're running out of smoke. Hurry!
Come on, Rio! We have to get out of here!
-Come on!
Bogotá! Are you okay?
Hang in there!
I'm waiting for the green light.
Palermo, give the order.
Give the order now!
Hold on up there. We're freeing Helsinki.
We don't have much time.
Once we get him out, we'll be the bait
to lure them out of the trench.
Chuikov!
Don't get close
to the hole until I tell you to.
Don't shoot!
-Get ready to intervene.
-Copy that.
Let's go!
In position, sir.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Sir, we're ready.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
You're connected.
Don't raise your tiny hand
because you don't want anyone
to overhear this conversation.
Tell me, do you do yoga
or something like that?
Capoeira.
That's why you're so flexible.
You're so flexible that you can dodge
problems, resignations, responsibilities.
With such flexibility,
you must be an excellent lover.
I am, but this conversation
is starting to disgust me a bit.
Tell me what the fuck you want.
Proceed.
They didn't revive anyone,
and they killed him in cold blood.
It would be best if he died
in the next ten minutes.
This is a gift, and I'll use it
to finish them off. No law, no rights!
We'll shoot them in the back
even if they surrender!
And that's why
I need everyone
to think they're fucking murderers.
What are you after?
-I want a just war.
-That doesn't exist.
Tamayo, you sent
eight elite soldiers into the bank.
I have ten thieves inside.
I think it's quite balanced.
I don't want to see any more movements.
You think that recording will stop me?
Colonel, you started a war
to save yourself without qualms or ethics.
I'm only asking that you continue.
Either you stop the second attack,
or I'll prove it was you who fabricated
evidence against Alicia Sierra,
that it was you who ordered
payment from the reserve funds,
and I'll transfer ten million to a company
in the Dutch Antilles, in your name.
And, believe me, that operation
will link you directly to me.
Postpone the intervention.
That's not the order I expected.
You don't get calls from the president
or report to the government, do you?
Then go munch on some fucking cookies
and let me give the orders.
-Help!
-Tokyo!
Don't shoot!
Don't shoot! We're hostages!
What's wrong?
-I'm fine.
-What happened?
-Nothing.
All this might be
just a bit too much for me,
but I'm fine, really.
I used to rob gas stations, man.
And now the Army is out there.
It's okay. You're not alone.
It's okay.
I'm not alone. Everything's fine.
Let's go.
Relax.
It's okay.
Look at me.
Don't close your eyes, okay? Look at me.
-Tell me a story.
-What?
Whatever you want.
How did you end up here?
Well, the other heist went so well.
But this one, not so much.
And I wanted
to spend time with this weirdo.
But from the time I got to the monastery,
I knew this wasn't going to go well.
Why is that?
Because you were there
with your wife, with a child, like…
You looked like a picture-perfect family.
And I felt so stupid…
Stupid? Why?
Because I've been in love
with him all my life.
Stop fooling around.
It's no time for jokes.
It's not a joke, sweetie.
It's not a joke. But since we might die,
because this is getting ugly,
I'm saying it.
No, I'm saying it to get it off my chest.
No, okay? Listen to me.
Nobody's going to die. You hear me?
-Say it.
-Nobody's going to die.
-Good. Okay?
-Okay.
Life goes on, right?
-Life goes on.
-That's right.
Pull him as if you were an ox!
Professor, Helsinki's out.
Matías, get ready to shoot on my command.
Yes, Professor.
Tokyo, Manila, Denver, get ready.
Let's get ready.
Follow me, okay?
Matías, stampede.
By the door! Shoot!
Fire!
They're approaching the hole.
I request permission to shoot.
You can't shoot. They're hostages!
I have a visual, sir.
Visibility is reducing.
I request permission to shoot.
They're civilians running
from the line of fire. Permission denied.
Bogotá, Rio, let them advance.
They're backing off.
Full-court press, now!
Tokyo.
They left their nest. Wait for my signal.
Not yet.
-Now!
Fire at six o'clock!
Let's go!
Fuck, girl.
We get an hour to rest and they all fuck.
What is this? A camp for teenagers?
If Rio were here,
what do you think you'd be doing?
There are a ton of saints
and Jesuses in here.
They're my boyfriends. And my bodyguards.
They protect me and Helsinki.
Shit.
This one should stay behind.
Sorry to say, but I don't know if I want
them all showing up the day I die.
I see.
What do you think happens?
When we get shot in the head?
Do you believe in heaven?
Actually…
no.
Really?
Nothing.
That's what you believe?
That everything's over?
Not everything.
Your memory lives on.
How would you like to be remembered?
I don't know. I guess…
I'd like people to say
they felt things with me.
But real things.
I don't know,
like friendship, for example.
You know those people who say,
"I have tons of friends"?
So?
You don't need to have them.
You need to feel them.
Don't you think Helsinki will remember me
every fucking Christmas?
I'll remember you saying…
"I'll go."
I'll go where?
Into the lion's den
to rescue my boyfriend.
Come on.
Babe…
I do think there's something.
Actually,
I think…
that you keep living
in the last thought you have before dying.
That's why, when things get crazy,
I think of when I was happy.
And in those memories,
I'll stay and live forever.
That's a great plan.
-What? Who's next door?
-Come on. Who do you think?
-No.
-Of course!
Yeah, Aikido, Professor!
Aikido all the way, man!
Shut up!
Who's in charge here?
Major Sagasta.
Sagasta, you're surrounded.
Throw your weapons
into the middle of the room, now.
Come and get them, pillow-biter!
Sagasta, update.
Send in the second detachment.
The whole gang is here.
Even the postman and his mom
could walk in the main door right now.
Sagasta, you have to resist.
There won't be a second detachment.
They snuck in right under your nose
and now you leave us high and dry.
Over and out.
Arteche, what do you think?
We're between two fronts.
We need to get rid of one.
Sagasta, you've got ten seconds.
Gandía, can you activate
the museum's security lock?
Affirmative.
There's a fingerprint reader in the room.
Seven seconds!
Okay, four corners. Wait for my order.
Five seconds!
Four!
Three!
Two!
All right! We'll drop our weapons.
Hands on your heads!
Get down on the ground, damn it!
Okay.
We're going to drop our weapons.
I don't like this one bit.
Now!
Grenade!
Get back!
Fuck!
-What's happening, Lisbon?
-Grenades!
-We've retreated to the museum.
-Don't lose sight of Tokyo's group.
Tokyo, keep going!
Impossible.
I have no visual.
They're lowering the doors.
There's a security lock.
A security lock?
That's impossible. It's not in the plans.
They must have installed them afterwards
'cause three doors are closing, Professor.
Come on!
Go to the kitchen.
Tokyo!
A little bird just told me Nairobi
is saving you a place in heaven.
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick