MADRID
FIVE DAYS SINCE D-DAY
Oh, Alicia…
Now the only way out is to take the blame.
And who's going to do that?
For the CNI, Prieto.
For the police, you.
Package delivered, Professor.
I'll be out in two minutes.
You’re going to take the rap anyway.
Be strong. We’re with you.
Lisbon!
Welcome to the Bank of Spain.
The government gave the orders.
The National Center of Intelligence,
police commanders,
and the Ministry of the Interior.
Absolutely everyone knew about it.
Where's the helicopter going?
Court proceedings
have been initiated against Alicia Sierra…
and a warrant issued for her arrest.
-Yes!
-Come on!
Professor. Lisbon is with us.
Listen to me.
This war…
we're going to win.
For Nairobi.
For Nairobi!
Checkmate, son of a bitch.
Don't make me shoot you
because I'm dying to kill you.
I'm the wife of a dead man.
I'm a disgraced police officer.
I'm a torturer for those who love me.
All thanks to you.
I'm not putting a bullet in your brain
because there's someone who
needs me for the next 18 years.
But it's a fine line.
If you make me cross it, I'll do it
with a smile on my face.
You live here.
This is your hideout.
In the most disgusting hole
in Madrid, of course.
You're living where
a rat like you is supposed to live.
What are you going to do to me?
I'm going to get your plan out of you…
and turn you in.
I'll make sure
you're charged with terrorism,
sentenced to life in prison,
and don't ever get to see
the light of day again.
Listen to me closely.
Your condemnation
is our salvation.
-Look at how civic-minded they are.
-Yes.
They're such beautiful people.
And you and me, here, father and son.
How nice.
Our father-son relationship
hasn't exactly been ideal, Dad.
But I've forgiven you.
Forgiven me for what?
For being born.
I had an excellent… and exquisite
relationship with your mother.
And you stood
in the way of our happiness.
All I wanted was
to take her out to dinner, travel…
make love
in beautiful places around the world,
and then you arrived and took it all away.
You were like a nuclear warhead
that blasted away that dream.
I don't know, Dad.
Everyone has kids and they adapt.
Look at those lobsters!
Let's eat here. Waiter!
Two aquavits and the menu please.
Rafael.
Rafael…
We're here to start over again.
Not to get wrapped up in our resentment.
No, you're right, Dad.
The past is the past
and there's no point in giving it…
too much thought. That's it.
Come on.
I'm happy
that we're here and together again.
Really.
Tatiana.
You brought your girlfriend?
It's a family honeymoon
for the three of us.
I'm going to the restroom.
Is he okay?
He's slightly annoyed.
He didn't know you were coming.
Have you told him he's here for a heist?
My love,
the really important things in life
are always unexpected.
What's next?
After the Paris Plan?
The Rome Plan will begin immediately.
No.
-Rome? Seriously?
-Yes.
That's great!
That's grea…?
Hey, what's up with you?
Huh? Iceman?
Are you letting romance take the wheel?
Of course not.
And what's after Rome? The Venice Plan?
I mean burnt-to-a-crisp Rome,
the Rome destroyed by Nero.
Nero?
I don't like the sound of that. Continue.
If we release
the only person they've arrested
and put them inside the bank,
right under their noses,
it'll be so humiliating they'll want
to destroy us as quickly as possible.
They'll use their best weapon.
The army.
Let's intervene immediately.
We need to talk.
-We can brainstorm later.
-I need backup.
I need officers
from Catalonia and the Basque Country.
-I need them here!
-Good idea.
Sure, take them to Puerta del Sol.
Rumor has it, Pikachu is picking pockets!
Only the army can fix this.
This is a civil matter
that concerns the police.
It's a matter of national security.
I'm bringing soldiers in,
ones that either conquer or die.
Martínez, get me Major Sagasta.
A battalion, maybe two. I don't know.
They'll break in at full force,
because killing hostages
will become a lesser evil.
And then what?
-How's it going downstairs?
-We have melted 59.
Plug the pump in. Let's start to extract.
There are 31 tons left.
The plan is to melt them.
My presence changes everything.
Extraction is the priority now.
Our only chance is to take the gold
we've managed to melt up until then.
Fuck…
The whole Rome thing turned me on.
-How much time do we have?
-Three, four hours.
Many lines of investigation are open
and there's a helicopter in the air.
Where's that helicopter?
It's heading southwest from Guadalajara.
We're 11 minutes behind it.
I can order an F18 from the base
in Torrejón to shoot it down.
No. We need the pilot alive.
That helicopter will eventually land
and we'll be there.
Yes, Colonel.
Bear 21, this is Bravo Three.
You must land immediately.
I repeat, land immediately.
Don't touch me!
The wound is next to the femoral artery.
Stitch him up and make him zip it.
Come on, hero.
I'll only allow a surgeon
in a hospital to touch me.
What the fuck did you do?
You came here under one condition:
never reveal your identity.
You were to be a hostage among hostages.
There was a guy holding an M16.
Arturo with an M16 is useless.
Arturo with a bazooka is useless!
We have a protocol.
I may have saved your life.
You should be
at least a tiny bit thankful.
You said you'd keep Cincinnati
if they catch us.
That was the deal.
You had your alibi.
You blew it.
And now my son has no plan B anymore.
-Manila did what she had to do.
-No.
We trusted her to raise our child
and she doesn't give a shit.
Arturo can do no wrong.
It doesn't matter what he does.
Whether he has an M16,
rubs up on you with a hard-on
or assaults a hostage,
it's always someone else's fault!
Look…
if we lose Cincinnati,
it's our fault.
We came here because we wanted to.
So stop talking shit.
This isn't over yet.
Attention!
We're changing stages.
I repeat, changing stages!
Get the remaining ingots
and plug in the extractor pump.
Now! Let's go!
Come on!
What are you looking at? Let's go!
Another eight hours
at full blast and it'll all melt.
Melting comes second now.
I want to prioritize extraction.
We needed to melt 90 tons
to get out alive and now 60 is enough?
Lisbon is inside the bank.
That will speed up an intervention
we can't counteract.
Either we take the gold out now
or we have no chance. Do you understand?
Did you know that rescuing Lisbon
would jeopardize our meticulous plan?
I didn't know shit!
Of course you didn't, damn it!
We never would've agreed.
If getting someone out of jail
puts the plan at risk,
they stay in jail, period.
That goes for everyone.
I'm not giving the orders.
You were before, damn it.
What are you now? The errand boy?
Man,
we're starting to improvise,
and that's how people
in heists get killed.
Lisbon to Professor. Do you copy?
How long did they
interrogate you in the tent?
Thirty hours.
Why? Is that too long
to keep my mouth shut?
Not for me.
For you, I don't know.
Maybe you saw a badge and felt nostalgic.
And then confessed
how we're going to get the gold out…
At least I didn't shake my ass
at all the clubs in Panama.
Professor, this is Lisbon. Answer.
What is Raquel doing there?
He must be covering Marseille outside.
We have a check-up call in 20 minutes.
If we have 20 minutes, I need a shower.
And a red jumpsuit.
At your service, Ms. Professor.
How did Raquel get in the bank?
How are your pals getting out?
And the gold?
Okay, speak now…
or I'll shoot you.
I've been threatened
at gunpoint many times.
I won't threaten you then.
Fuck, you have great self-control.
Let's talk now…
to prevent any further deep wounds, okay?
You're melting the gold.
What for?
We're turning it to grit…
into…
two-millimeter nuggets to get it out.
I knew it.
How will you get it out?
The only possible way.
The sewage system.
It'll come out all mushed up,
mixed into the water.
You think I'm stupid, right?
The sewers are brimming
with underground police.
Tell me the truth.
The grit will go right past them,
covered in mud. They won't see it.
So…
if you're getting it out
through the sewers…
why are you here?
What the fuck are you doing here?
Let's go!
Major Sagasta, Colonel Tamayo speaking,
from the Bank of Spain operation.
-This is Sagasta. Is something wrong?
-I want you to lead an attack on the bank.
Negative. I'm on leave.
Sagasta, this is not the time
to break my balls with your cold hands.
-You're familiar with my background.
-Every inch. That's why I'm calling.
Afghanistan, Yemen,
the pirates in the Horn of Africa,
Boko Haram…
Do you know
what all those missions have in common?
What? Mosquitoes?
They're undercover operations abroad.
No witnesses.
Why would I meddle in a civil matter,
with Spanish civilians
and the attorney general as spectators?
First, because it's an order.
Second, for your country.
Isn't that enough?
They're attacking us
and you pledged allegiance to the flag!
Let me tell you
a couple of things, Colonel.
Well, three things.
First, I couldn't find the right time
during this conversation
to tell you that I'm pooing.
And I guess it's too late now.
Second, I'll be there in 40 minutes.
And third,
I'll go in with my trusted team.
The ones from Afghanistan, Yemen and Mali.
I want them all.
What does this look like?
This.
Turn me in to the police.
Nope.
If I take you to the police
or to prison, you'll escape.
No matter where I take you,
you've got a plan and you'll escape.
Answer my question.
How are you getting the gold out?
If you push me,
you'll never clear your name.
How will you do it?
What will you give them?
A smashed up corpse full of bullets?
-The gold.
-You'll look crazy.
Okay. Let's fly then.
Do you understand
the situation better now?
You don't understand.
I'll never…
turn my gang in. Do you get it? Never!
Listen to me. The plan is devised
to survive against any setback,
even my death.
So, let's do this…
Throw me into the void!
Even better, shoot me!
Empty the chamber!
Come on, I can't wait! Do it!
Do it!
I wish.
When they find out about Murillo,
and they will,
the shit's going to hit the fan
and someone will have to take the rap.
We can share it
and each of us can take part of the blame.
-Or we can make someone else take it.
-Who? A fellow officer?
No, Pope Francis. Get out of here.
Yes, a fellow officer. A former officer.
A traitor, Alicia Sierra. It's obvious
she's working for the Professor.
-How do we know that?
-I don't know, nor do I need to.
There was probably a mole
and it had to be her.
But there's no evidence.
Evidence? What evidence?
Evidence can be fabricated if needed.
What are we, newbies?
Martínez, get Sierra's emails.
We need to prove
she leaked Prieto's conversations
with Osman and everything about Algeria.
Track her phone.
I want her near the National Court.
Irrefutable evidence
she was working with Murillo.
I'll need the operators to cooperate.
The operators will do
whatever the CNI tells them to.
Antoñanzas, go to forensics
and stop Nairobi's autopsy.
Put an army doctor on the report instead.
Only one bullet hole should be listed…
Gandía's.
We'll say that,
when Sierra ordered to shoot,
Nairobi was wearing a vest.
That it was all a farce, in short.
With all this, I think we're covered.
Colonel, we're breaking the law.
More than they are.
And I believe in the law.
So I'm leaving.
Where do you think you're going,
Pooh Bear?
If I stay,
I'll report anyone participating in this.
Who are you going to report?
You're the only fraud here!
You found the Professor's hangar.
You could have stopped him from escaping.
So don't play Mahatma Gandhi now!
Don't mess with me, Tamayo!
I was coming out of a coma!
I have recordings from your phone.
You're totally drunk…
Your phone calls to Murillo.
After 15 years with you,
at your side, like a fucking fool.
She was arrested in front of you
and you wouldn't cooperate with Prieto
because you were drooling
like a lovesick puppy, weren't you?
Answer me, Angelito.
I'm not answering any of that.
Then start negotiating
or you'll go to prison before Rio,
Tokyo and Albuquirky.
Fine, you're getting promoted
to inspector negotiator. How's that?
You may even become commissioner later.
If I'm the negotiator, we'll do it my way.
I won't do anything illegal, Tamayo.
"I won't do anything illegal, Tamayo."
Your job is to negotiate.
We'll do the dirty work.
Colonel.
The helicopter is slowing down.
The ground tracing units
are seven minutes away.
Tell them to hurry.
I want a full road blockade.
The air deployment continues.
What's up, Maserati?
Your jumpsuit,
a towel and…
a pair of Helsinki's panties.
I'm just kidding. Fuck.
Thank you.
Sorry I was so out of line before.
I needed to see your reaction.
And?
Did I react well?
You don't seem stressed.
I know they'll crush us.
And I can't help but think
this situation is somewhat romantic.
Really?
How so?
He dug a 12-meter tunnel
to get me out of the National Court.
He took me for a ride
all around Madrid in an attack helicopter.
Then, he got me
into the Bank of Spain reserve
in front of 3,000 police officers.
That's beautiful.
It is.
Love grows exponentially during a heist.
Does it?
How so?
Because…
every second could be your last.
The adrenaline makes you
live life to the fullest.
You don't want to leave
anything for later.
It's definitely more romantic
than going grocery shopping on Fridays.
I've known this since the first time
I kissed someone before a hold-up.
Your heart's pounding.
-Ready?
-Ready.
You walk in…
Nobody move, motherfuckers!
Hands up! This is a hold-up!
-Do it! Come on!
-Your wallets!
Hands up!
Let's go!
…and wreak havoc.
You're a goddess!
Open the fucking cash register!
Come on, open it! Now!
Get out of here! Now!
And in the middle of the turmoil…
Come on! Move!
…you look him in the eye
and realize you're so fucking happy.
Wallets out!
Come on! Faster!
Come on!
You leave with a backpack full of dough,
scream on the motorcycle…
You feel…
indestructible, powerful.
You cling tightly to him
at 110 miles per hour.
You cross the border into Portugal.
And you stop somewhere random…
because you can't resist
your desire for him any longer.
You want to devour time
before it slips away.
And that…
makes every moment so magical…
You're not talking about Rio, are you?
It was before him.
He was killed during a hold-up.
I was there.
I knew I'd never find
a love like that again.
He was the love of my life.
Mozart is your favorite composer?
Well, I'd actually choose,
because I'm a huge fan of his,
Robert Schumann.
Wait until you hear me play Schubert.
I'll have to see it… I mean, listen to it.
Why didn't you tell me
your son loves Schumann?
He's so charming.
I'm going to the restroom.
Can you order more champagne?
Of course, my love.
Are you making eyes at my wife?
Seriously, Dad?
You've been making passes
at her all afternoon.
I'm just being polite.
You're flirting!
Maybe you misinterpreted
something I did or--
Look me in the eye.
Is she attractive?
-That's irrelevant.
-Yes or no, Rafael?
Well, I think she's… pretty.
Would you make love to my wife?
I'm your father.
I'll know if you're lying.
If the situation were… different
and you didn't have
a formal relationship with her…
It's flattering that a young man like you
wants to butter my wife's bun.
You realize that, right?
See how confusing life can be sometimes?
Paradoxical.
For example,
I'd look like a good dad
if I wanted to work with my son, but…
if that job were a robbery,
some prude would probably be against it.
I'll never steal with you, Dad!
-I'm an engineer.
-I know.
An electronic engineer.
With a graduate degree in cybersecurity.
From MIT in Massachusetts.
I paid for it.
Why do you think I did that?
You…
You are…
despicable…
and selfish.
Do you want a dull life
defined by schedules, meetings, emails?
An endless rat race
that uses up all your energy?
Where one month of vacation a year
gives you only a glimpse of freedom?
You'll get your glimpse of freedom
when you go to jail!
At my job,
you don't go to prison or get killed.
Death is a word that, a priori,
refers to everything that doesn't exist.
And, once you're dead,
you won't remember you were alive.
So that's why you wanted to meet, is it?
That's why? And you say you love me?
You don't love me.
You don't care if I die.
I don't want you to die
before you've lived!
I'm giving you…
a path to freedom.
We thieves are the real liberators.
And if we ever have to pay
for what we've done…
then so be it.
Madrid isn't the Bermuda Triangle.
We can't make
an 11-ton helicopter disappear.
They'll be watching Marseille
with their radars, satellites,
even NATO's ballistic missile defense.
So, as soon as Marseille drops Lisbon…
he won't stand a chance.
The helicopter is descending!
-In what area?
-In the countryside.
In Guadalajara.
It looks like a cattle farm.
-It's landing!
-Launching.
The coordinates, fast.
Forty degrees,
33 minutes, 47 seconds, north.
Three degrees,
12 minutes, 34 seconds, west.
To get your lady out of trouble,
you put Marseille in a tight spot.
That'd be the case, Benjamín, except…
our magic trick continues.
Police!
Hold your positions!
Two to the helicopter, quick!
On the ground!
I'm the farm owner!
Get down! I said get down!
Hands on your head!
On the ground, now!
Clear!
-Clear!
No guilty party would ever claim damages
in such an angry, obsessive…
They killed my lambs.
Shut up!
…and annoying way.
Stand up!
Who will pay for the lambs
your colleague killed? Who?
He's not one of us. Shut up!
-Who the fuck is that?
-He sounds like a victim.
He landed on my flock
at insane speeds. He's nuts!
-Was there just one man?
-In the helicopter? Yes, just one.
In the car…
Boris, how many people were in the car?
Two, right?
No, just one. They both left,
but there was only one man waiting.
Vehicle model?
It was like… a funeral car.
At that point,
they'll only have one clue. The red Volvo.
The cameras at the National Court
will record it when we get Lisbon out.
And that is precisely
what you'll tell them.
Ask him if it was
a red Volvo from the '90s.
Was it a Volvo?
A red station wagon.
I don't know the make.
Volvo, yes.
They drove in the direction of Albolleque.
This will be the peak of our magic trick,
because from then on…
everything will change.
We've got them. It's them!
Calling all units,
the suspects are in a Volvo Polar 240,
plate number 15318 Victor, Charlie, Mike.
Captain.
Yes, Colonel?
-Take the same route. And hurry.
-Copy.
Miranda, you stay here.
Everyone, we're leaving now!
Open communication.
Squad, situation report.
The vehicle is 1.2 miles away.
We have to stop that car.
Attention, suspect vehicle
approaching at one mile.
Come on!
Suspect vehicle approaching at 0.6 miles.
Listen up. It's the Professor.
He might come out with a smoke bomb.
He's Houdini.
Vehicle approaching
very quickly at 0.3 miles.
We have visual. Ready to fire.
Stop the car! Stop the fucking car!
Shoot the fucking wheels!
Fire!
Get out of the car!
Get out of the fucking car!
There's a bomb!
On the ground!
What's going on?
They've got my wife!
-Is it the Professor?
-We were kidnapped
when we left the hairdresser.
A woman was kidnapped
as she left the hairdresser.
We should file a report
or the lambs won't be covered.
Shut the fuck up. And get back to work.
And then, pretending we're going back
to work on the farm…
Come on, let's feed the cattle.
…we'll flee.
We've been duped, Colonel.
MUSEUM OF GOLD
Why aren't we melting all this gold?
This gold was already stolen once.
It can't be stolen twice.
This gold belongs to the Quimbayas,
the Incas, the Quechuas…
If anything,
we should give it back to them.
It's a treasure.
I wouldn't call it a treasure.
My two-year-old son
could make this statue if he wanted to.
-Just saying.
-Let's go.
Lisbon to Professor.
Hurry up…
or they'll stress out.
Check-up call for the Professor.
Professor speaking.
Hello, Sergio.
The Paris Plan was a success.
We're launching the Rome Plan.
We'll start extraction in one hour.
There will be no extraction.
This may be the last time
I speak to any of you.
They know about the stormwater tank.
What if someone finds out
about the stormwater tank?
That'd be the end.
Hi, Lisbon.
Hi, Tokyo, Helsinki…
Well, hi,
to all the cities you'll remember
but never be able to visit again.
Who's that?
Inspector Sierra.
-She's leading the investigation.
-Something like that.
How are you, Raquel?
You're on an emotional roller coaster,
aren't you?
First… you were detained in the tent.
Then, you flew around
like a little, free bird.
And suddenly, boom!
Everything's over.
But we both knew
this came with a price tag.
Okay then.
Now it's time to pay.
The price could be really high, Dad.
Because when it's time to pay,
you won't be here,
in a luxury restaurant, eating lobster.
You'll be in a police van. And your life,
everything you've built, will just…
disappear.
Or worse, you'll be in the middle
of a puddle of blood, dead…
like my grandfather.
The things that matter most
in life are expensive.
Rebellion.
Freedom.
Ideals.
Any last words, Professor?
I'm sorry, Raquel.
I'm so sorry, Rio.
I'm sorry, Palermo.
I'm so sorry, Helsinki.
I'm sorry, Manila.
I'm sorry, Bogotá.
I'm so sorry, Stockholm.
I'm sorry, Denver.
I'm so sorry, Tokyo.
-I'm so sorry.
-That's enough.
That's enough.
Professor…
don't cry on me.
There are no big battles
without big opponents.
And well, guys,
I'd love to do therapy with you for hours
and comment on your best plays,
like the ferret in the sewer.
Hilarious. But we have
a lot to talk about here.
Okay? Over and out, sweeties.
There's got to be a plan B…
The Professor always has a plan B.
Not this time.
There's no plan B.
Is he that self-centered? He has a plan
for everything except if he fails?
-I can't believe it.
-What would you suggest?
There's only one way to get the gold out.
There's no plan B
because only plan A is viable.
We may be trapped…
but we aren't dead yet.
The army!
Soldiers.
A lot of soldiers.
This is when you hit a wall
at 90 miles per hour.
It's the end of the road.
It happens to us all
at some point in our lives.
One day your brother
is diagnosed with a terminal illness.
One day you realize
that you won't ever see your child again.
That you won't ever
see your friends again.
Or the lover you never had.
Dad.
And that all you have left
is your father's last embrace.
Another day,
you leave a bank with your boyfriend
and a shot ends it all
in a matter of seconds.
That your family…
won't ever get together again.
That everything we lived through,
dressed in red,
ended here.
This was the end of our journey together.
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick