When you've been locked up for 100 hours,
chained, about to be killed,
and you've lost your best friend,
those 100 hours feel like 100 years.
And going outside…
the biggest freedom in the world.
Who cares if soldiers are aiming at you?
Unarmed,
barefoot,
with the sun on your face
and surrounded by silence…
you feel free.
We were sending a message of hope.
Lisbon was there with us,
walking out of the bank,
not at the National Court
or in prison like everyone thought.
Colonel Tamayo!
White flag!
We were telling them that
if we could do that…
we could do anything.
And people started to believe in miracles.
I want your team ready
in one minute, Suárez!
I want a clean operation!
Top priority is those three bitches,
then the hostages.
I want them here!
I don't care how you do it.
You heard him! I want everyone ready.
We can't do that, Tamayo.
She pissed on our faces.
I'm going to wipe her out, no matter what.
-30 seconds!
-They're waving a white flag.
It's been a symbol of peace
since the Punic wars.
Even the Nazis respected it.
Are we going to dismiss it
with the whole world watching?
We're ready!
-We're awaiting your orders.
-I heard you! I'm thinking.
-If we negotiate, we're shitheads.
-No.
This battle is to show who the good
and bad guys are in this war.
If they have a corridor, so do we.
We have to project a friendly image.
No tie.
No jacket. Sleeves rolled up
and no bullet-proof vest.
I'll look like a wimp.
You'll look solid as a rock, Tamayo.
You have to be tough.
You'll give them an ultimatum.
In two minutes, we go in.
We need to cause panic in there.
Let them know they're fucked.
You're giving me a hard-on.
Set up a security corridor
so I can negotiate with them.
-Go get them, Colonel!
-Go, Colonel!
Governor.
What's the army doing here?
This isn't a civil conflict anymore.
Two battalions, assault troops…
They're going in.
It's about time.
That's not good news.
To the police, we're hostages.
To the army, we're collateral damage.
Leaving the security perimeter.
And what's that supposed to mean?
They'll shoot anyone
that's wearing a mask.
Their priority is to kill them,
not rescue us.
The Three Graces have come to put
a friendly face to the heist's name.
We've come out with our faces uncovered
so everyone can see
I'm not at the National Court,
I'm not being interrogated in the tent
and I'm not in prison.
-What the fuck do you want?
-Gandía's injured.
I have to show you something.
Raise your hand,
everyone knows what that means.
Palermo.
Let's see, you slimy snake.
Come on.
There's shrapnel
between his cervical vertebrae.
One wrong move
and he'll never move his arm…
or his lungs, again.
It's called the phrenic nerve.
He urgently needs a neurosurgeon.
One from the army, if you want.
You've got a few.
What are we waiting for?
Let's run to the tent. Now!
They won't shoot us.
We can't go back in the bank.
Of course we can.
Our fellow hostages have no idea.
They'll find out eventually.
It's every man for himself out here.
We have the moral obligation
to do something.
You came in here to be a hero, right?
Well, now's the time.
If I send a doctor in,
I'll have to wait 3 or 4 hours
to get the army in,
which you know I'll do.
That's why you're using
the only card you have. Gandía's injury.
Will you let a man you used be paralyzed?
-Let him go. I'll treat him.
-I get nothing out of that.
You do.
I'll tell you why.
If you don't let him go,
I go in right now.
But if you do, until he tells me
what you're up to in there,
I may as well wait an hour.
It's up to you.
Give us a minute to discuss it.
Of course.
It looks like
I'm getting out before you, Sandokan.
What the fuck are you doing, Bogotá?
At that moment…
We need to release Gandía.
We need that hour.
…Lisbon was the only one
who noticed a tiny detail…
Lisbon?
…that would radically
change the rules of the game.
They don't have the Professor.
-What?
He gave us an ultimatum
and didn't use his trump card.
If you can checkmate
in one move and don't…
it's because you don't know you can.
Exactly.
Sierra's a lone ranger.
I'm starting to like that nutcase.
Get Gandía ready.
I'm going to fight this piece of shit.
Bogotá, stop!
I may be destroyed,
but I'm still going to beat your ass.
Shit, Bogotá! We're letting him go.
We can't give them scraps.
He'll be carried out feet first.
Hurry up, the minister is waiting
for me with a medal.
Shut up, asshole!
Every time you punch him,
you're punching us.
Your pride's going to fuck us all.
We're already fucked.
This won't change a thing.
Dignity is all we have left.
That's revenge.
-Revenge is a selfish act, you know that.
-It's respect.
Respect for us
and respect for our executed colleague.
-That's what this is.
-I'm with him!
Are you all morons or what?
Lisbon has agreed to release him.
She's buying time.
I don't know Lisbon, but I knew Nairobi.
We're destroying him
before they fuck us over.
Oh, now you're going to kill him?
You're the asshole who says
"Kill him," from behind,
because you couldn't do it
when you had the chance!
You didn't have the balls to do it.
You stopped in your tracks.
So stop being stupid!
You're going to beat each other up, too.
Are you really coming after me?
He's the perpetrator,
he pulled the trigger.
And the mastermind is that bastard.
So stop busting my balls, okay?
Do you want me
to take some flowers to forensics?
Your friend must still be warm.
And even firm.
What would you do if Stockholm were dead?
You hit Arturo when he teased you.
This motherfucker killed one of us.
What's reason enough for you
doesn't apply to us?
Do whatever the fuck you want.
Is it that important to you?
Brother…
We need this
so we can look each other in the eye.
He's all yours.
Let's enjoy recess
before the girls come back.
-Let's go.
-Let's do this.
We'll let Gandía go.
But before we do,
I need to check with the Professor.
Ask him whatever you want.
You've got four minutes.
What do you suggest we do?
Organize an escape.
With 10, 15 or 20 hostages.
Deal.
Take them to a safe area.
-You know there are no safe areas inside.
-Of course there are.
Come on…
Any of the four vaults
that open with my fingerprint.
Hit me.
I said hit me.
Hit me!
-Do you know why I'm going to kill you?
-Because I groped your girlfriend's ass.
No…
Because you're a fascist.
As soon as you lift a gun
to defend your country,
some asshole calls you a fascist.
Open the door!
You're fascist for saying "mutt."
"Gypsy."
What the hell?
Close the doors! Get in line!
Back off! Now!
-I said back off!
-"Redneck!"
-Against the wall! Hands up!
-Stop it!
For calling Palermo a "one-eyed queer…"
Right now!
-Leave them alone!
-Stop it!
…and a "wetback!"
-What are you doing?
-You're racist!
We're trying to make miracles happen
and you set up a fight.
You're sexist!
-Stop them!
-No!
You're homophobic!
And this is for Nairobi.
Bogotá.
-He killed Nairobi.
-The police don't have the Professor.
Nairobi wouldn't want this.
Tamayo doesn't know anything
about the Professor. It's not checkmate.
We stand a chance.
-He killed her.
-Let him go.
Let him go.
Do I still turn you on?
Tokyo…
You missed it.
Boom.
Come on, recess is over!
-Stitch him up.
-I'll kill you, asshole!
She knocked me out, fucking Sandokan!
Not you!
On the ground, you terrorists!
Fuck!
-This way, come on!
-Get them out of here!
-Denver!
Fucking hell.
It's okay, keep calm.
Let me see the wound.
-Stay calm. It's okay.
-There's an exit wound.
I need the surgical kit.
-Now!
-Coming.
Get the kit. Your gun, let's go!
Helsinki, Manila, the hostages have fled.
They hit Denver and some of their own.
They've got weapons!
Copy that.
Let's go!
You stay here. Don't let anyone move.
Let me see.
That son of a bitch.
Denver.
Fix Gandía, he's top priority!
Denver!
Fuck!
I need a medical unit by the door!
The bank's head of security is about
to come out with a severe prognosis.
You're the next to move.
You're in charge of the intervention.
-With what men?
-Special Forces III.
You know most of them. They're the best.
-Cañizo!
-At your command, sir!
Get your men ready immediately.
Yes, sir.
-How's the recording?
-It sounds like a shooting.
I told you I'd go in with my team.
I want them.
The guys you requested
are out of the question.
Colonel, it's going to be a massacre.
I need men who won't ask who's behind
the mask when they have to shoot.
And Special Forces will,
because somewhere in their brains
lies the notion of rescuing hostages.
I need people who will go in there
to conquer territory, not to save lives.
What percentage of civilian casualties
are we talking about?
Well, don't count on more than…
thirty percent surviving.
Either I go in with my team…
or I don't go in.
Your team?
Mateo Canalejas,
arrested for playing Russian roulette
with his service weapon
in a joint in Tbilisi.
Arantxa Arteche organizes
illegal monkey fights in Gibraltar.
What a fucking joke.
Salvador Torrecilla
pretended Boko Haram kidnapped him
after spending six days copulating
with the chancellor's daughter in Mali.
Shall I continue?
Ramiro Vázquez, your trusted bomb expert,
is in the Mondragón mental hospital.
I'm aware of all that.
They're all outside, waiting.
I called them
when the Professor started throwing bills.
Should I get them…
Colonel?
Sagasta.
Don't fuck with me.
Go to the right!
Palermo! Come out to play, motherfucker!
Fuck!
-Shoot the vests!
-Shoot the ceiling!
Get down.
-Helsinki, they're headed your way.
-Get down!
Do you copy, fatty?
Help!
We're right here!
Cover me!
Lisbon!
We're trapped! There's no way out!
I don't want to die!
We won't make it to the vaults,
but we can get them out
through the loading dock.
-How?
-Through the next door. Cover us!
Come on!
-For fuck's sake!
-Fuck!
-They're heading to the loading docks.
-Follow them!
Palermo, with me.
We'll use the other door.
Helsinki! Go to the top floor.
Report any troop movement.
Weapons, ammunition, men, anything.
I want to know if they're coming.
Let's go.
Let's go! Matías,
take five of your hostages.
Let's go!
To the library, now!
Come on!
Inspector.
It's confirmed, shots were fired.
Through this hallway. Run!
Let's go. Down this hallway.
-Run!
-This way!
Run!
They're coming!
Fuck!
Get down.
Okay, let's go.
Back off!
Shoot the vests.
Watch out!
Come on!
Shit.
We're fucked.
Let's go, guys. This way!
-They've blocked the exit with steel…
-Shit.
…and explosives.
They're the ones who are fucked, Governor.
All their weapons are here.
My name is Alicia Sierra.
I'm an inspector with the National Police…
They've issued a warrant for my arrest.
I'm recording this video
in case the police or the CNI
try to hide, distort
or misrepresent the real facts.
But I won't fall apart on you all
because today calls for celebration.
Here we are. Look who's here with me.
Let's see. Here we are, in the hideout…
of this smart little animal.
The Professor.
Wave to the camera, Mr. Marquina.
Mr. Marquina?
-This isn't necessary.
-Of course it is.
Tell us, Mr. Professor, who arrested you?
-You did.
-You, who?
Do your part.
I've been arrested
by inspector Alicia Sierra.
Exactly!
Cross my heart and hope to die.
I, Alicia Sierra,
at 9:50 a.m. on April 8th,
located the abandoned stormwater tank
at kilometer 21 on the road--
Can I tell the truth?
I'd like to tell the truth.
Go ahead.
I recruited one of your officers.
He was part of the Paris Plan.
We recruited Mr. Benito Antoñanzas.
Antoñanzas jumped
into his gated community's swimming pool
from his home,
specifically from his bathroom window.
And that's when I began to leave a trail.
In your colleague's defense, we made
him fear for his and his family's life--
Shut the fuck up.
What did you have for lunch, a parrot?
He won't stop chatting.
I'm trying to set the facts straight
and tell the truth.
You've been lying the whole time.
You didn't even tell
your brother the truth.
-What's going on?
-That's why now's the time…
Fuck you. Keep your fucking mouth shut!
Marseille!
I'll blow your fucking head off.
Shut your mouth.
Marseille! Code red!
Marseille! Benjamín!
Marseille!
Shit!
Hell yeah.
Marseille! Police!
I'm not a police officer anymore,
four-eyes.
Marse…
Marseille…
Mars…
-You need a tourniquet.
-I'm okay.
Come on, Amanda, Miguel, grab some guns.
You can do it.
Let's go, you two!
The windows.
You two, cover from the windows.
-Do you know what you're doing?
-Of course. What has to be done.
I don't think you do.
The windows!
Get back! Get out of here!
Stop this. You got two people injured.
Yes, but I saved four
and we've got their weapons.
Look at me!
They both have families.
It wasn't my fault.
It was the damn recoil.
Collateral damage.
This is war! Can't you see?
Churchill would see it as a victory.
Ammunition?
-Two clips.
-What?
We can't cover the hallway with two clips.
God damn it.
We need to blow it up.
If the weapons in there explode,
the entire building will collapse.
-We have no other choice.
-We need grenades.
Where the hell do we get those?
I know where there are grenades.
And much more.
Distract them. They won't suspect
we went to get explosives. Lisbon…
Good luck, Tokyo!
We heard shots in the building.
Something serious is going on.
It's the same as always.
The Valencia or Beijing Plan. It's a show.
They're blowing stuff up
so we change our road map.
They're assault rifles.
There are civilians in there.
-Suárez, please.
-Colonel.
Are you organizing
an operation behind my back?
-Would it be an issue if I were?
-This is a civil conflict.
-I demand to be part of any intervention.
-You demand? Who do you think you are?
I'm the inspector in charge
of the special operations group.
No matter how hard you try to ignore us,
let me remind you we killed Berlin
while fighting against his Browning.
Sagasta!
Sagasta, go in with your team. Right now!
Okay.
Rio! Come with me.
-Motherfucker!
-Don't move!
You're a son of a bitch, Denver.
What?
You kicked me out of the previous heist,
the good one.
But you call me for this one,
which is a fucking mousetrap.
I'm doing this because I'm a good person,
but I should be doing this to your balls!
Back off!
Denver!
Listen. You're bleeding
like a stuck pig, come back.
Okay. Your arm will go numb,
but it'll be fine, okay?
You can go now.
-What are you going to do with that?
-Make them dance.
Didn't you say we should be heroes?
That's exactly what I'm doing.
The hostages are in the armory
and we have two fucking clips left.
I'm not going anywhere.
We can't attack rashly.
We have their weapons.
It's a matter of time
until the army attacks.
Honey. Dani, sweetie, please come back.
I'm fine, okay? I'm great.
You're not fine.
It's our job to defend
this position intelligently.
Defend? An Italian defense? Huh?
With little Messi on our team?
And Neymar?
And Cristiano Ronaldo?
No, we're not playing defense here.
We're playing tiki-taka!
Come on, go get some cover.
Your turn.
-Grenade!
Are you okay?
How are you?
Bad!
Arturo!
I'm going to rip your balls off!
They're right here, you bastard!
Come pay me a visit!
Fucking hell!
-Are you okay?
-No!
They've got enough ammo for four wars!
We're fucked!
-What is this?
-Put it down, it's a flamethrower.
A flamethrower, huh?
Everything in here
is flammable and explosive!
Don't worry, Governor.
The barbecue will be out there.
…is for all of you who see this mask
as a symbol of the resistance.
We need you.
The State has declared war on us.
A filthy war.
Professor?
And we've decided to face them.
The police have detained
one of us in a foreign country.
Aníbal Cortés.
It's been almost two months
since his arrest.
They haven't filed
formal charges against him.
Professor?
They haven't requested extradition.
Marseille. The bathroom.
-They haven't provided him with a lawyer.
-Go check it out.
He's being held captive…
Hello?
Anyone in there?
…somewhere unknown, and in all likelihood…
they're torturing him.
So we demand
that this illegal detention
be brought to an end immediately
and that he be brought to justice in a way
that respects legal standards.
-The State started this war…
-Benjamín.
…and we will not hide.
He's sleeping.
We will fight,
blow…
for blow.
And this time…
it will be an even bigger heist.
Well done, Professor.
The next shots
will clear out the whole toilet,
so throw your gun under the door
and come out behind it.
Very well.
Three, two…
one.
Who the fuck are you?
-Logroño?
-I…
don't have a…
city name.
Shit! The tank is running out of oxygen.
It's refilling. It'll take a minute.
In the bathtub,
I told you to break up with me.
But I didn't say my last words.
You're not leaving here without me.
You know that, right?
You'd have to kidnap me.
That's a bad way to start over.
But it'd be hot.
I've learned
a few tricks about kidnappings.
How to tie people up… and all that.
Are you cutting steel or hitting on me?
I can do two things at once.
And I could do a third one.
You three,
get in the first vehicle! Move!
It's Helsinki.
There's movement outside.
The army's special ops.
They're loaded with every kind of weapon.
A C-90 rocket-launcher,
grenade launchers, machine guns,
shotguns, rifles.
Come on, let's go!
They're getting in two LMVs.
Shit, immediate intervention!
Bogotá, Lisbon speaking.
Let Gandía go immediately.
He'll tell them
we're chasing the hostages.
If we don't, they'll break in now!
We don't have any weapons.
The hostages have taken the armory.
Hey! Cover me! All of you!
Fuck!
God!
Denver!
I am Cincinnati's dad!
You fucking dick.
Come give me a kiss!
-Who's the father? I don't get it.
-Shut up or I'll staple your mouth shut.
Come here!
-Area secured.
-All clear.
-Get ready to intervene.
-Clear, Colonel.
Green light. We can proceed.
Now!
He's ready.
Come on.
Son of a bitch!
Arturito!
Do you believe in reincarnation?
If not, then you better negotiate, right?
Can you hold your breath?
For as long as it would take me
to fuck your mother up the ass.
Is that enough?
It's fentanyl.
The doors are opening.
Let's see if this doesn't
knock you out either.
The hostages!
-What the fuck is that?
-The hostages are…
The hostages…
Abort the intervention!
The hostages are…
Confirmed, Colonel.
It's Gandía, Colonel. It's Gandía!
Sagasta, abort operation
until further notice.
The hostages…
Denver.
I know you're listening.
Do you think she loves you?
Denver?
No.
You're not man enough for her.
She used to tell me
I taught her what love is.
Did she ever
say anything like that to you? No.
Do you know why?
Because you lack the intelligence
to get where I got.
Your personal vendetta
is putting us all at risk!
Shut up!
I know that kid as if he were my own son.
I know where to scratch to rile him up.
And that's what I'm going to do.
When he comes out, I'll scorch him.
With me…
she never wondered,
"What am I doing with this guy?"
Never.
And I was married.
And she knew.
But she couldn't leave my side
for a second.
Sparks flew between us
every time we ran into each other
by the coffee maker.
Give me your gun.
We were doing it all the time.
In every corner.
One year…
after another.
We made love everywhere, Denver.
It didn't matter
if we were under the printer,
in the cafeteria bathroom,
or in my office.
Or on the coin display cabinet.
It didn't matter.
And every night…
Every night, as soon as she got home,
she wrote me these beautiful texts,
sent me photos
and told me and promised me
she had never felt like that before
and couldn't live without me.
Denver,
has she ever told you anything like that?
I bet she hasn't.
-Give me the walkie-talkie.
-No.
Why didn't you have another child?
Your own child!
You stole her from me, you bastard!
You had to kidnap her!
And before she knew it,
she was in the middle of nowhere,
doomed to share her life with a bumpkin!
No, man, don't!
Come on!
Keep a cool head,
for fuck's sake!
Tokyo will be here
with the weapons any second now.
Keep your cool.
I'm sorry.
Weapons!
They have more weapons.
Fuck!
Change of plans!
You two, get those shields
and set up the Browning
on the forklift. Now!
There's no military logic
to abandoning our position.
Out there you have no chance.
Listen to me closely,
because I won't say this twice.
They're attacking us. And you heard them,
they have more weapons.
As soon as they bring them here,
this will become a rat trap
and they'll finish us off!
I told you, we need to strike!
Now!
Let's go.
They stopped covering the windows.
We can't wait any longer.
Attack quickly! Now!
-What the fuck is that?
-Back off!
Open!
Close!
Last clip!
Open!
Shit!
We're out of ammo!
Arturo!
Mónica…
Calm down.
Move and I'll shoot him!
On your knees!
Come on, get down.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
Put the gun down, please.
But you won't shoot…
right?
You'd never shoot your son's dad.
Do you know how I know?
I'll be the only one left to look after
that child when this is all over.
-The only one he won't be embarrassed by.
-Get down!
Don't you understand?
Don't you get it?
Don't pretend to be someone you're not.
You'll never be one of them.
You'll always be a secret--
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick