René!
No!
Three people were killed
after an attempted bank robbery.
According to early reports,
at least one of the robbers
was able to escape.
The suspect is a woman
between 25 and 30 years of age.
According to witnesses…
Sergio, come look at this!
…despite the large police presence.
Two of the deceased
were security guards at the bank.
The third was one of the robbers,
an unidentified 30-year-old male.
The police are looking for a young female
of average height,
brown hair, and thin build.
The state security and police forces
have set up roadblocks
on all roads leaving Madrid.
They warn that the suspect
is armed and dangerous.
We must find her.
She's got the talent we need.
Our battering ram.
She's the most wanted person
by the police.
We shouldn't involve
someone so high profile.
Four armed people. Three die, one doesn't.
What more do you need to know?
That woman is a survivor.
And now she's a killer, too.
That heist was a botched job.
She clung to the ceiling like Spider-Man.
Who does that?
Instead of tying up
the officers in the parking lot,
she took them in the patrol car
and passed all the roadblocks
with the sirens on.
She escaped like a queen,
with the police's blessings.
That's art, isn't it?
There's no information about the operation
set up by the authorities
in pursuit of the woman.
Look, Sergio.
I just got out of prison,
and I can assure you
I only met dumbasses in there.
Brain-dead people. People with no talent.
Not everyone has
what we just saw.
It's not easy to find.
That may be.
She may be talented. She is talented.
But that girl is a lost cause.
That's exactly why.
And she's got nothing to lose.
That's exactly what we need.
ROBBERY SUSPECT AT LARGE
THREE CASUALTIES
If they haven't found her in 72 hours,
we'll start looking for her.
-I'm going to the library.
-Okay.
Get some pastries from San Onofre!
Silene Oliveira.
That was my name when this story began.
When I was convinced
you could outrun pain,
just like the police.
Run,
close your eyes,
and resist.
But inevitably, at some point, you stop.
And all that pain runs through you.
And you feel like there's nothing
you can do to escape it again.
I spent ten days in hiding.
Playing the images of my life with René
over and over again in my head.
Thinking about how he never liked banks.
And when we decided to rob one.
And just like that,
my pain got worse.
And so did my sense of guilt.
For leaving him there, all alone.
Lying on the wet ground, under the rain,
as if René could still feel it.
And then I thought
I had to run faster than before.
So that grief wouldn't catch up with me.
And I didn't stop.
Not even when I arrived at that dead end,
where an army commando
was determined to kill us.
At this point in my life,
I was miles away from standing down
and making it easy for them.
Take cover!
Fire!
This is a fucking rat trap.
We have to block the door!
How the fuck do we do that?
The stove top!
Tokyo, cover us!
Fire!
Arteche, destroy that door!
Hurry up!
Fucking hell!
We have to lift the stove top.
Three.
-Two.
One. Now!
Tokyo!
Wait!
Grenade!
Up!
Hey, chefs!
Put it inside a piece of cheese next time!
LISBON, PORTUGAL
FOUR YEARS UNTIL D-DAY
When I was little
and summer vacation ended, I thought,
"When I grow up, I won't have
to go back to school anymore."
Now I don't go back to school.
I go back to something worse.
Why do we have to give this up?
Because vacation always ends, baby.
But I also smile when I see you
in our neighborhood.
And I'm happy when we stroll around
the streets of Madrid
and have a beer in the square.
We live like royalty.
We spend our days trying to make a living,
wondering if we can afford
to turn the heat on.
You spend all day breaking your back
with those gas bottles.
I don't care.
And I spend all day
looking for another shitty job.
I want to be with you all the time.
So we need to rob bigger things.
Because you don't want
to have money to buy things.
You want it to be free,
and that's very expensive.
That's what I want.
To be free.
Why do we need to settle?
If we don't steal,
our life is stolen from us.
What do you think?
I want to travel the world with you.
I want to see you on a desert island,
in the middle of nowhere,
with a mojito in each hand
and think, "Fuck, I'm so lucky."
So if we're that lucky,
we should make the most of it.
Name a city.
Very far away.
I promise to take you there.
Tokyo.
Get ready, Japan.
The first time I chose Tokyo
was to travel with René
to the farthest city in the world.
I'd learned that loving him
in different cities made me happy.
Saint Anthony.
You beautiful thing!
The second time I chose Tokyo
was to change one life for another.
They're using the stove top as cover.
They've got a good shooting angle.
And aim.
Cañizo, Sagasta speaking.
They're in the kitchen.
Find a shooting angle from the outside.
Sniper unit in position.
Let's throw grenades,
blow up their fortification and go in.
Screw it.
Anyone who gets close to that corridor
is a dead man.
We won't accomplish anything
with a grenade.
That stove top is made with cast iron
and I'm sure they fortified it.
And what do you suggest?
Sit here and see if they come out
to use the bathroom?
We're going to drill through the wall.
We'll drill a hole
and attack from the pantry.
It'll take us at least ten minutes,
and time is the only thing on our side.
We need to go in now,
before they come from the museum.
Negative.
Push harder.
Get it in there, damn it!
I got it!
Done.
Rio, can you hack this shit?
I can. It's cracking the codes.
It'll take at least 30 minutes.
Realistically, one hour.
One hour?
What? No, there's no time.
We need the foundry workers up here now.
Come on.
First-aid kit.
Bogotá. How long would it take
to cut through the door?
At least 11 minutes,
if there's enough gas.
We need to decide.
When we cut, the system will block,
and I won't be able to do anything.
Bogotá, go with the foundry workers.
Copy.
-You good alone?
-Of course.
Come on, Helsinki. You can do it.
God.
Tokyo, how long can you resist?
As long as it takes.
Start drilling. Canalejas, help him out.
Major, you've got no fucking clue
what you're doing.
Captain, do you know
what we're going to do?
Exactly what I say.
And you're going to zip it.
What's going on?
They're arguing, Professor.
The boss wants to drill the wall
and come in through the pantry.
Gandía wants to attack
through the corridor.
Gandía is questioning orders.
Tokyo, that's his weak point.
-You know him. Can you do something?
-Of course.
Then do it.
Hello, Gandía.
How are you, sweetie?
Did you miss me?
Only at night.
But you didn't come back for me, did you?
You're back
because you felt like a traitor.
You were an ally to the robbers
through a walkie-talkie.
You lied to the CNI,
and thanks to that, Lisbon got in.
That's why you're back.
Because you don't have the balls
to go home
and look your wife
and your son Juanito in the eyes.
Shut up, you little rat.
I'll come in
and wash your mouth out with soap
if you talk about my family.
No.
They saw you come out alive on TV.
I'm sure they cried, hugged each other,
and thought you'd be home for dinner.
But nope.
You didn't even call them, did you?
Of course not.
What would you say?
"I killed a defenseless woman,
and then betrayed myself and my people
because I'm a coward"?
Gandía, calm down.
"Hi, Juanito. Do you know what, son?"
"Daddy's a piece of shit."
"Why? Because I'd rather get myself killed
than stay with you and read you a story."
What are you doing?
Don't, Captain.
Captain, did you hear me?
"And tell Mom…"
That's an order, Captain!
"…I was always late
because I didn't want to fuck her."
I'm talking to you. Captain!
Gandía!
Grenade!
Take cover!
What was that?
-Rio.
-Rio!
-Come back!
-Where are you going?
Bogotá, we need you here now!
We'll be there in two minutes, Lisbon.
Move, fuck!
Everyone against the wall!
Come with me, move!
Hang in there.
It's okay.
I've got it.
Stockholm, status? Do you copy?
I'm trying!
I'm fucking trying!
-Ramiro, are you okay?
-Yes, sir.
Hernando?
Canalejas?
Torrecilla and Tosco, injured, Major.
You got him killed.
You got him killed!
One casualty, Professor.
It was an accident.
These things happen.
-Not here.
-Arteche.
-What's going on?
-They're fighting.
That buys us a few minutes,
but not much more.
Arteche, calm down.
Cañizo speaking.
We can shoot one of the kitchen windows.
Visibility isn't good,
but one of the pantries is within range.
-Stay in position.
-Roger that.
Arteche.
I got him, didn't I?
-Did I get him or not?
-You got his vest.
Congrats.
Arteche! Two members of your team
have been wounded.
Go look after them.
Arteche! That's an order.
You're doing great.
Maybe the same thing
will happen to you two.
Shut your little mouth.
Because of what happened earlier,
on the rooftop.
I understand that people say things
they don't mean under pressure.
No worries.
Not really. I was being honest.
Well, I think now is not the time to talk
about these things.
I decided to start being honest
a long time ago.
What's gotten into you?
Nothing. It's how I feel.
I want to be clear, Dani.
Let me be clear, Manila.
This is a fucking war.
I'm with Stockholm.
I can't be clearer than that.
Are you in love with her?
I'll cover you.
Disobey me again and I'll put you
on your knees and shoot you in the head.
-You're not answering me.
-I'm madly in love.
-Come on.
-"Come on" what?
We know each other.
I know who you are, what you like.
I know your dreams.
The huge, three-floor techno nightclub
you wanted to open.
You've got more than enough dough now.
Listen, the thing is, Spanish-style clubs
aren't popular in Indonesia,
but I can tell you
I've danced a ton with Stockholm.
We even danced in a vault.
Okay, what about the martial-arts gym?
That's popular in Indonesia,
you can't say it isn't…
But I can't spend my life kicking asses.
I wanted to grow up.
Tell me something.
You've been in Indonesia
for two fucking years.
In all that time,
have you ever had any doubts?
Never.
I get up in the morning,
and I see Stockholm asleep,
rays of sunlight
coming through the window and…
my life looks like a fucking commercial.
A commercial for cologne.
That's not you.
That's not your life.
It's a different life, but it's his
just as much as the previous one was.
One life can be made up of several.
There's no need for this.
Shut it.
Keep walking.
Is anyone here?
No.
Are you living with grandma?
Well, it's just a safe place.
Who are they?
People in same situation as you.
Potential members for our gang.
You're the first recruit.
Good.
I'll stop you
from making a fool of yourself.
If you want to steal 2.4 billion euros,
you'll get shot in the head.
So stop talking about it.
You get shot when you don't think.
When you go into a bank barefaced
and act without thinking.
But this plan is many years in the making.
How many years?
Twenty years.
I'm offering you freedom.
I'm already free.
I can go out that door right now
and vanish.
Why don't you?
Because out there,
nothing, no-one, is waiting for you.
Your life ended in the last robbery.
I can bring you back to life.
A second life.
Or you can just linger on the memories
of the first one.
What do you know about me and my life?
Or how much I've given up to be free?
All I need to know,
and I'm going to find out right now, is…
whether you're brave enough
to be born again.
To live again, find love again, a family.
It's a yes-or-no question.
Today is the day to decide.
Now.
Wouldn't he want you to be happy again?
Who are you?
Welcome.
Come on!
Hurry up!
Three lives are at stake. Let's go!
The foundry workers are in the museum.
We're cutting.
Good.
Come on! Now!
I need the jackhammer.
Where's the jackhammer?
Stockholm! Where's the jackhammer?
Over there.
Morphine.
Give me morphine. Please.
I know that look.
First dead.
Always stays in head. Turning and turning.
It'll pass. It's the shock.
Morphine. Please.
Get ready, Tokyo, freshen up.
I'm on my way.
People think true love
only happens once in a lifetime.
What people don't know
is that you can live several lives.
Rio, right?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Stargazing.
What is it?
That doesn't seem like you.
You don't know me.
Look, that's the Big Dipper.
That's the Ursa Major
and that's the Ursa Polaris.
Hacker and astronomer. How about that?
The Professor has it all covered.
Some people can read
the future in the stars.
Do you know how?
Well, I mean, kind of.
Tell me my future.
Really?
Okay.
Okay, so, from the star alignment…
it looks like you're going to meet a guy.
Is he cute?
We'll have to check
with Andromeda's angle.
Look. There it is.
-What?
-The constellation.
Where?
Look. Right there.
Oh, yeah.
What is it?
He's a normal guy.
A bit of a loner too.
An average guy,
but a good guy.
I don't know how I'll meet him
locked up in here,
attending Professor's classes.
I bet Cassiopeia knows.
Let's ask her.
-Wow, that's weird.
-What?
Cassiopeia says you'll meet him dancing.
Can I have this dance?
It's okay. We've lost one of the lances.
How much time do we have?
No less than six minutes.
Professor, what was that?
I've got to tell you something.
There's one more of us
in the stormwater tank.
Inspector Alicia Sierra
gave birth to a baby,
a beautiful girl
weighing around three and a half kilos,
and she's in great health.
Congratulations.
A baby is always a joy and…
there's no surplus of joy
around here lately.
What's her name?
Well…
I was thinking of Germán,
after her father.
But since she's a girl, I've gone blank.
What about Danica?
In my country it means "morning star."
You're a true poet, Marseille.
If you're accepting ideas,
I've always liked Lucía for a girl.
I don't know if she looks like a Lucía.
She looks more like a Victoria.
Victoria.
I'm going to name her Victoria.
That's beautiful.
That's it, Victoria.
Because she's going to be
as strong as a bombshell, and so will I.
And so will I.
Take her.
Victoria.
Everything you bought is pink.
Pink, because she's a girl.
And? First of all,
there are no colors for girls or for boys.
And second, you're conditioning her.
You don't know if she'll feel like a girl,
a boy, or God knows what.
She's not even a day old,
and you're already traumatizing her.
Even the rattle you bought is pink.
Give me the baby.
No. She gave me the baby.
You've lost your mind.
Cover the door.
The lance is out!
We've got two lances left.
Come on, hurry up!
Cañizo, they're in the pantry.
Tokyo, run!
Fire!
Tokyo!
Tokyo, no!
The day I killed Gandía,
the odds were against me.
I was like a puppet riddled with bullets.
And with five bullets in my body,
I thought about my samurai.
Open it. Don't worry, it's not a ring.
It's a Japanese samurai.
I found it in a shop window.
It's a sign.
I know what you're thinking.
You can read my mind with a snow globe?
You don't want to live the high life
and leave your mom behind.
I already thought about that.
We're going to give her a gift.
A male stripper to spice up her life?
We'll pay off her mortgage.
If we go to Polynesia, she can go to Rome,
or Paris or wherever she wants,
so she can enjoy life.
She deserves it too.
And you need it.
Where will we get all that cash?
Ask it. Rub it a little
and see what it has to say.
Let's see.
It says that…
It says you've already thought
about how we'll do it.
Banks.
We've already pulled off 15 clean heists.
We understand each other.
-We're good.
-The best.
Let's go after the banks.
You know it's higher risk, don't you?
Hang in there.
Tokyo is injured, Professor.
She took bullets in her arms and legs.
Fuck! The lance is out.
Enough. Guys, go down to the foundry.
Hang in there.
Professor, we're out of gas.
Help me, Lisbon.
Denver, listen.
We need more time to open the museum.
Set up a defensive position
to cover any possible entry.
As long as you're covered,
you stand a chance.
We'll resist.
Ready.
Now.
Fuck!
You're not going in,
you're benched. Follow me.
You lot, set up the explosives.
Shoot anyone who comes through that door.
Everyone else, take cover.
Can you shoot?
Until my arms fall apart.
Manila, come on. Let's go!
Professor, we're behind the trench,
and there's no fucking way out.
There's no way out.
Denver?
Denver, the hole.
Denver, there's a hole.
The dumbwaiter.
The dumbwaiter from the office, Denver.
Denver, the dumbwaiter…
from the office, Denver.
It's right here.
What?
It's at least six floors.
Fucking hell!
Come on. Go down.
-What?
-You have to go.
Both of you, come on.
Go down now.
-What about you?
-I'm staying.
-What?
-I can't go down.
Manila, listen to me. Manila!
I can't hold on to the ropes, okay?
I need you to go down really fucking fast,
and put cushions, curtains,
cardboard boxes, anything, at the bottom.
Anything, you hear me?
Okay? And I'll jump.
-Manila.
-No.
Go! Now!
Manila, go down! Come on! Go down!
I won't leave you.
You're coming with me.
I'm not leaving you here.
-No, Denver!
-Let's go.
-Leave me here. You're hurting me.
-Tokyo.
Listen to me, please.
My dad died in a heist.
I won't let my sister die.
I won't.
Sweetie,
I need you to save my life.
-Everything's going to be fine.
-Okay.
Okay?
Go.
I'm okay.
-Explosives ready.
-Connect the detonator.
Tokyo!
Detonators ready.
Tokyo.
Tokyo. I'm here with you.
I'm here.
Ramiro?
Hold on. I'm going to get you out, okay?
-You're good at construction too?
-I'm full of surprises.
Take cover!
Tokyo, what is it?
What's going on?
Rio, they're here.
We're going in!
Manila, hurry up!
-I'll open the gap.
-Rio.
There's no time.
Don't say that, and don't smile like that.
It's because I'm happy you're here.
No.
Tokyo.
Come on.
Do you know what I'm thinking about?
Our first night in Toledo.
When we danced together.
Now!
Professor, we're downstairs.
Tokyo, they're downstairs.
Resist 30 seconds.
Mónica!
Mónica! Fuck!
Come on! Hurry up!
Fire!
Tokyo.
Rio.
Don't be sad.
-Something is ending today.
-No.
But it's the first day of your next life.
You've got a lot of lives to live.
-No.
-Lots of them.
Advance!
You need to leave…
because it's party time.
No!
Tokyo!
Fire, Arteche!
No!
Canalejas!
Fucking shit!
Fire, Gandía!
Tokyo, jump!
Tokyo!
Can you hear me?
Tokyo, there's no time. Jump now.
Tokyo!
You're out of time. Jump now.
It's going to be hard.
How will you manage without me?
I won't, Tokyo. Jump now!
You've always been my guardian angel.
Now it's my turn to be yours.
No!
I'm not the type to rot in prison.
I'm more of the runaway type.
And if my body can't run away,
at least my soul can.
Get back!
Tokyo!
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick