One, two, three, four.
I need help!
Paddles! First aid kit!
We have to stop the bleeding!
He’s got no pulse.
-Hurry! Come on!
-On your knees, bastards!
Hang in there, please.
-Hurry!
-Coming!
Pass me the scissors.
Come on.
Jesus.
-Jesus.
-Here.
Grab the paddles. Come on, Arturo.
Three, four.
-Clear!
-Stand back!
Stop, you’re searing a corpse.
-Stockholm.
-Get the epinephrine. Now.
I've got it.
You killed him. Accept it.
What are we doing?
The army's going to destroy us.
Stand back!
He has a pulse.
Yes, he does.
He has…
a pulse.
He's got a bullet in his heart.
He won't survive.
We need to take him to the hospital.
We need to get him out now!
He was dead a minute ago,
and he’ll be dead again
when you stop blowing air into his lungs.
If we get him out, we’ll become murderers.
-No.
-Yes.
They're going to storm in.
They’ll kill the hostages… and us.
We can't let him die.
Listen. That fucking crazy
son of a bitch was asking for it.
You shot him twice.
You did well. Now you feel guilty.
You want to get rid of your guilt
by tossing a bucket of shit on us all.
You can have a clean conscience.
Mine is already dirty. I’ll kill him.
-No!
-I'm going to shoot him!
-For fuck's sake, stop!
Relax!
Listen.
We’re taking him out,
and I’ll tell you why.
We need a doctor!
As Stockholm watched Arturo
hang between life and death,
she felt completely empty.
She knew she had taken the last safety net
that could protect her son from the world.
Arturo was her child's biological father.
And Stockholm was beginning to realize
that neither she nor Denver
would ever see Cincinnati again.
She wasn't the only one thinking
that parenthood is the largest source
of anxiety in the world.
We were expecting the heist men
to make a move.
You're watching live…
Our lives depended on three guys
whose hands were tied,
and who had a gun in their faces.
Under any other circumstances,
they'd have given up,
but Benjamín had
a daughter inside the bank.
And the Professor had ten.
He's in a critical condition.
I'll be there as soon as possible.
Frisk these men in my office.
I need to start the interrogation.
Run the electromagnetic detector
over them.
They could have mics in their teeth.
-No radio waves.
-Bring them some clothes.
Colonel, they're clean.
There are ten heist men.
There's always one with the hostages,
here, in the library.
What happened to Arturo Román?
We tried to bring some hostages to safety…
but he lost it.
He was obsessed with the weapons…
He attacked them with a flamethrower.
Mounted a machine gun on a forklift.
He put us in danger.
They had to take him down.
He had no pulse for minutes,
but they revived him.
They didn't revive anyone,
and they killed him in cold blood.
It would be best if he died
in the next ten minutes.
This is a gift, and I'll use it
to finish them off. No law, no rights!
We'll shoot them in the back
even if they surrender!
And that's why
I need everyone
to think they're fucking murderers.
Understood?
Is anyone else injured?
Two hostages.
Román injured them.
Absolutely not. It was them.
I've been summoned
to the Ministry of the Interior.
Do not intervene until I get back.
Martínez, the documentation!
Martínez!
He would've killed you.
What am I doing here?
What am I doing here, throwing lead,
while my child's with some monks?
When he grows up…
and finds out about everything,
and asks about his mom…
I don't want anyone to tell him who I was.
I've ruined my son's life.
My father also thinks he ruined my life,
but I love him madly.
A miner with a trans daughter in the '90s…
He made a lot of mistakes.
When I was five,
I went straight to my dad,
and told him, "Daddy, I'm a girl."
And he looked at me
with his serious miner face,
and said, "Juan, you're a man.
Men are not girls."
There was this makeup case that I loved…
I don't know how many times
I asked him to buy it for me.
And in the end,
I got a case, but it was full of tools.
You end up understanding
that anything your dad deems girly
is bad, so you hide it.
But you couldn't tell anyone?
There weren't any transgender people
in my town.
There were a lot of pickpockets, burglars…
there were tons of junkies,
but there weren't any trans people.
In those days,
when a man dressed like a woman on TV,
it was to fool around,
for people to laugh.
My father was the first to crack up.
But I forgave him,
because I didn't have any role models,
but neither did he.
I think confusion is
a parent's natural state.
At the end of the day,
your parents don't have to be perfect,
they just have to love you.
Do you like your present?
Are these gentlemen my present?
They're the best teachers.
Authentic graduate professors.
A tip-top squadron for your first flight.
And we've chosen, especially for you,
a zero-risk robbery.
Basically, it's just for fun.
So tell me, Dad,
what's a zero-risk robbery?
One that goes unnoticed when you rob them.
But they'll find out at some point.
Well, not now.
Not in one, two, or three months…
Not even in ten.
They'll find out in 15,
when the Viking gold museum opens.
But by then, who will connect the dots?
Viking gold?
These are exact brass replicas
of all the pieces
of the biggest Viking treasure
discovered to date.
It was found at an archaeological site
eight months ago,
and is now being held in
a Danish national heritage security room.
The real treasure is in there, well kept,
in limbo, awaiting its destiny.
Do you know where that security room is?
At Frederiksborg Castle.
Exactly the same venue
where I'm playing a concert in three days.
It'll be the perfect soiree.
Fancy cars, tuxedos, cocktails…
classical music…
and 12 kilos of gold.
What are you laughing at?
First, these are Viking grave goods,
not treasure.
That's the term used by archaeologists.
And second, I think you're a cynic.
Dad, you pretend to be in love with art.
You restore monasteries.
I'm sorry, but these items
should be in a museum.
Wait a minute. Do you call this art?
Of course I do.
These objects
are more than 1,000 years old.
They're hand carved,
and have Nordic symbols on them.
-This is pure art!
-It's the work of a blacksmith.
Of uncouth barbarians!
These people pillaged iconic,
extraordinary pieces,
Latin, Greek, Phoenician,
and melted them down
to make wine goblets, plates, charms!
We're giving the gold its dignity back.
Oh, please.
We're the ones who are going to make art.
It'll be an unforgettable heist.
Imminent press conference
at the Ministry of the Interior.
Tamayo, the colonel in charge
of the operation, is going to speak soon.
What's Arturo Román's condition?
You almost kill
the only hostage people know.
And you release the governor
of the Bank of Spain.
Hello? Anyone running the show in there?
This is the situation.
The army is going in.
They're waiting for Tamayo to destroy you.
And he will, for two reasons.
First, he's a coward and a bastard.
Second, you've made it easy for him.
Unanswered questions.
Are hostages being killed?
Is the army preparing an intervention?
You're shooting hostages.
Your fans are going to worship him.
Your girlfriend,
the trashy Power Ranger,
the teddy bear from the Balkans,
the kid from the grave…
The people you're willing to die for.
Your people…
are dead.
Only I can prevent it.
Give me the information.
I'll make a call, and nobody dies.
Move over, please. Thank you.
Good morning.
We're holding
this additional press conference
to inform you of the latest
regarding the disappearance
of Alicia Sierra.
Former Inspector Alicia Sierra
has betrayed
the police force she represents,
and is now working
for the Professor's gang.
Since she escaped,
her whereabouts are unknown.
We're using
all the means at our disposal
to bring her to justice.
This is her current appearance.
This is a CCTV image
from a store close to her home.
Son of a bitch.
We lost the trail on her cell phone
two blocks from the National Court.
We've located a safe house in the area
where she may have coordinated
Murillo's extraction.
All of this is under investigation.
The forensic analysis
on the equipment found at her house
suggests that she leaked the emails
about the torture procedures in Algeria.
She falsified testimonies,
and broadcast Anibal Cortés' fake burial.
We've found traces of encrypted
communication with opaque servers.
Alicia Sierra used them to leak
sensitive information to the Professor.
In the last few hours, we have learned
that she received eight million euros
in companies in her name
in Panama, Belize, and Delaware.
What did you expect?
You've got no way out.
There's always a way out.
Now, if you have any questions…
-Colonel, please!
-You.
What's Arturo Román's condition?
He's in a critical condition, very severe.
It's too late now.
The police, the CNI, the government…
They've all fabricated the evidence.
If you turn us in, they'll say that,
after betraying them, you betrayed us.
Shut up.
Do you really think they'll admit
to fabricating evidence?
The CNI never backs down or apologizes.
You know that.
Shut up.
-Colonel.
-I have a question.
-Are you planning an intervention?
-Things have changed drastically.
What was once a heist with hostages
is now a kidnapping with executions.
-The protocols are completely different.
-Is that why the army has been mobilized?
As the operation is ongoing,
I cannot provide further details.
-Please!
-Colonel! Here!
That's the green light.
It's going to be a massacre.
They're going to go in.
They kicked me out of the game.
I don't even know
how they're getting the gold out.
The gold.
-It doesn't matter anymore.
-Of course it does.
You don't get it.
The gold doesn't matter anymore.
-Shut up.
-You've been condemned.
You've been charged
with the same crimes as us, or even worse.
-Quiet.
-Yours include disobedience.
-Shut up.
-You're a traitor now.
-For the police, government, colleagues…
-Shut up.
-No one will bail you out of jail.
Shut up! I need to think!
No.
Her water broke.
Not now.
Be reasonable.
You can't raise a child in prison.
Kids can be raised just fine in prison.
It's called a "prison nursery."
Godfather…
Thanks for including me in this.
I needed it.
If you needed money,
all you had to do was call.
I needed someone to believe in me.
She's talking about her father, Dad.
I know she's talking about her father.
He thinks I can't do heists anymore,
but I can do them even better than before.
But you have to study for this one.
We're going to print 2.4 billion euros.
Like this: chug, chug, chug.
You told your father you're here, right?
He doesn't know, nor will he.
Okay.
Well, we're going to bed.
Tomorrow we have shooting practice
and… whatnot. Let's go.
-Good night.
Dani.
Son!
-Wake up!
-Dude! What's wrong?
I think we misunderstood something.
What did we misunderstand, Dad?
It's five in the morning, Dad!
What did we misunderstand?
Maybe we didn't understand
how Benjamín wanted us
to look after Julia,
and we're screwing it up.
We're not screwing anything up.
Julia wants to be here.
Julia's a grown, adult woman.
She's got her own life, she's independent.
I don't care what she wants.
I need to tell Benjamín
that I might have messed
the "right track" thing up.
And maybe my idea of the right track
isn't the same right or wrong track
Benjamín has in mind.
We need to clean this mess up
before the bullets start flying.
Dad, Benjamín is in prison,
and there's nothing we can do
because we don't have a phone.
We have to soldier on. So good night.
Come on, get up! I have to call him.
You want to call him in prison right now?
What do you mean by "right now"?
We have to walk for three or four hours
until we find a phone.
-I'm not going anywhere.
-You're not what?
-God.
-Come on.
-I can't go back to sleep now.
-Get up.
The C4 goes behind steel sheets.
We don't want a sympathetic detonation.
Our defense began
by moving the weapons to a safe place.
Grab seven more.
Rio, grenades?
-Six.
-Take as many as you can.
We felt like we were building
our own grave, not a bunker.
We got this.
Without the Professor outside,
we felt like orphans.
This is the last fight. Stay strong!
No father, no plan, and no hope.
Forgive me for the soccer reference,
but it's all I've got.
Sometimes, during the World Cup finals,
you can tell who will lose.
You can smell a team's fear
as they sing their anthem.
And I can smell the fear here today.
But we're going to change that.
A game is 11 against 11.
We're playing ten against 10,000,
and have no coach.
Calling the heist team
at the Bank of Spain.
Breaking news from the stormwater tank.
Sierra's not wearing
her police armband anymore.
Tamayo ousted her. He let her go.
Sierra's flying solo.
Do you know what that means?
Can you guess?
Tokyo? Rio, do you know?
The Professor is not finished.
He's playing his own game, and he can win.
He's playing against a nutcase.
No. She's much more than that.
She's a raging nutcase
who's been betrayed by her own people,
They threw her to the wolves.
She probably already knows the Professor
isn't her biggest enemy anymore.
-Breathe with your diaphragm.
-What?
Breathe with your diaphragm
to control the contractions.
Are you a midwife now?
We can't win this war.
The Balkan bear got the strategy wrong.
We don't need to win this war.
We're going to lose it…
but very slowly.
And you…
my boys and girls in red…
We, who have been cast off by society,
a team made up
of the biggest losers in history,
trans, criminals, scum, gays…
Balkans, Latinos…
What can they teach us about losing?
We know how much it hurts
to lose this slowly.
We know.
And we can lose one more day.
Why would we want to lose another day?
To melt the gold,
and get it all out of the vault.
We're back.
It sounds fucking good to me.
But you've got a plan to lose,
and you're not filling us in.
Of course I do.
I may be an engineer,
but being an infantry general
is my true calling.
I need to dilate.
Oxytocin… would work really well.
Unfortunately, we don't have any.
-I need something for the pain.
-No, that would put the baby at risk.
Are you fucking kidding me?
In an open field,
we wouldn't stand a chance.
But with rooms, their advantage wanes.
We'll crawl through every corner,
every fucking heap of rubble.
We'll throw a grenade, then another,
followed by machine gun fire.
This isn't a fucking Vietnam War movie.
Exactly. It's worse.
This is the defense of Stalingrad.
This strategy was devised
by General Chuikov.
We'll blast music so loudly
they won't hear the grenades, the gunfire,
and even better…
they won't even hear their own radio.
Alicia, listen.
You can't go to a hospital.
And you can't do it on your own.
Release us. You need help.
-Let us help.
-I'm going to give birth…
on my own.
Like my grandmother did,
and like hundreds
of women throughout history have done.
Like this!
Welcome to the spectacle of life.
I need three volunteers.
This mission won't be easy.
These three will have to take the rear.
Our only chance
is to attack them on both fronts.
We'll need to move fast
through the elevator shaft, the air ducts,
or wherever we can, but fast.
Logroño.
You seem to know more than him.
How dilated am I?
I couldn't tell you…
Dilation is measured by touch.
Let's see.
What part of the plan is this?
The birth plan!
I need three volunteers and, listen up…
these three will be the most exposed.
Good. Let's do it.
Come on!
Denver,
say goodbye to her.
We've a long night ahead. This might
be the last time you see each other.
Are we seriously going to walk?
How else can we get there at 5:00 a.m.?
Shit, we could steal a car.
There you go again. Is stealing always
the first thing you think of?
As soon as something gets tough,
boom, a theft.
Says the one who brought me here
to rob the Royal Mint.
So you can learn to do it intelligently,
like the Professor.
He steals as one should,
in one big go, not small amounts,
and screwing other people over.
It's 5:00 a.m. If we leave now,
we won't be back until 11:00.
If the Professor sees us,
what will you tell him?
See? You're thinking with your head,
and being sensible.
We'll steal a car,
but from someone
who won't report it stolen.
-Coming.
-Come on.
What can I say, Benjamín,
that you don't already know?
There's a risk.
The job is huge,
but every detail
has been thought out, I swear.
If something goes wrong,
Julia will be taken to a men's prison.
I can't even imagine that.
Yeah, but if she asked
to be transferred to a women's prison,
they'd probably do it.
It's taken Julia a long time
to get where she is now.
She's…
just starting to live her life.
She's happy.
I'd never seen my daughter happy…
in 30 years.
Her body was a prison.
Don't make her go back.
If the job is as big as you say,
won't you look after her?
Of course. As if she were my own daughter.
Benjamín, listen,
I've stood by Julia my whole life,
and I'll stand by her until the day I die.
Thanks, Dani.
Don't… mention it.
I have to go.
Bye.
You overdid it a bit.
I did? How?
Let's get out of here.
-Bye.
-See you.
Coming.
That phone call is irreversible.
Think about it for a second, please.
That call will condemn you and your child.
You can hate me as much as you want.
You can wish me dead, or whatever,
but, sadly, right now,
to save your and your kid's life,
you need to save mine.
Right now,
we're in the same place, we're equals.
You and I aren't equals,
you piece of shit.
Your job is to break the law.
I work to stop that.
God.
And that's what I'm doing.
You're condemning your own child.
They'll destroy you
because they don't owe you anything.
My life.
They owe me my life.
I became the queen bitch for them.
And they can't let bitches like me down.
I won't let you down.
Shut up.
Don't talk to me
as if I were one of your people.
I won't spend the rest of my life
on the run.
I don't run away.
I don't hide.
I don't go to the Philippines.
I liked my life.
I like Madrid. And lamb tripe.
And the Puerta del Sol. And corruption.
I'm not losing my country because of you!
Tamayo betrayed you, not me.
I hate you.
Fine. But we're running out of time,
and your hate for me doesn't entitle you
to put your baby's life at risk.
This kid…
adores risk, you son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Follow me.
Tamayo's here,
and soldiers are going in with him.
Did the Professor call?
If he had, I'd have informed you.
Everyone out!
We're going to plan
a military intervention here!
Move it!
Police officers are leaving the tent.
They're organizing something.
Copy. We've got a few minutes.
When you shoot someone,
you feel like shit.
You hate yourself.
I shot you.
Something bad could've happened to you.
I could've been a murderer…
You think the only option
is prison or be killed.
But no.
It's not how it works.
I treated your wounds.
I danced for you.
And ever since then
we've been fucking happy, Mónica.
Just because things worked out once
doesn't mean they will twice.
In fact…
we may be pushing our luck too far.
I'd like to talk when you get back.
What if I don't come back?
Then I'd like to kiss you.
A first kiss.
A first kiss is only the first time.
That's why it's called a first kiss.
But I don't want to give you a last kiss…
I want to give you a second first kiss.
Like a kiss couples give each other
when they make up.
That's the one I want.
The building is blast resistant.
That leaves us few options to break in.
The main entrance,
the loading docks… or the windows.
But they'll be expecting us
to come in through precisely those places,
so none of them is an option.
But there's another option.
You know Captain Gandía.
He was a green beret.
I'm honored to have served by his side,
and some of you have too.
He's proposing an alternative plan.
The rooftop is marked
as "blast resistant" in the plans,
but part of it isn't
due to a load-bearing issue.
It's confidential information.
They ignore it.
There's a hole
in the Bank of Spain's blast protection?
No. It's fully protected.
But it starts at the museum,
and ends with steel doors
like the ones on the ground floor.
So we'll climb up there,
blow the roof off,
and go straight into the dining hall.
That coffered ceiling goes back
to the 18th century… During the Civil War,
it was brought here from a palace in Jaén
to protect it from the bombings.
Do you think someone in Bosnia said,
"Don't blow up the Mostar Bridge,
it's old"?
No, and there it is, rebuilt.
Or the Sarajevo Library.
During the World War, Berlin burned,
and nobody said, "Don't bomb
this neighborhood, it's pretty."
There are Goya paintings
and Quimbaya gold in there…
We have Amnesty International on our ass.
Are we going to confront UNESCO as well?
You couldn't care less
about Quimbaya gold.
You're looking at me as if I'm a dog.
Tell me what the fuck you're thinking!
You condemned an innocent person.
You slandered her. She'll go to prison.
Angelito, a country's security
is above any individual's honor,
it's above all else!
The National Reserve
is a country's backbone.
Is Sierra's dignity more important
than the safety of 47 million people?
For fuck's sake, Tamayo!
You condemned her to save yourself,
not to save 47 million people.
We'll get in by blowing up
that coffered ceiling!
Come on, baby!
A little bit more, and you'll be out!
Fuck!
It won't come out!
Why won't it come out?
Because that's not the head.
What?
It's breech.
What do I do?
You need to insert your hand,
place the baby on your arm,
as if it were horseback riding,
hold its mouth with your index and thumb,
bring its head close to the breastbone…
and pull it out.
There's no other way,
and you need to do it now.
You have to release me.
A convoy is leaving the tent.
Copy. Everyone in position.
Lisbon?
We're ready.
-Tokyo?
-I'm in.
Matías, code red.
Okay, no one moves!
Put your head between your legs,
and brace yourself. Like in an airplane!
It's going to be bumpy.
Change of plans!
Whatever happens up there,
no matter what you hear,
no matter what shakes, don't stop melting!
Don't stop even if Jesus appears,
and dances reggaeton in front of you.
-Bogotá?
-I'm heading up.
If anyone's thinking
of taking a bit of gold
to make earrings for their grandma…
don't.
Ask Daddy for the gold when we're outside,
understood, children?
Get to work!
Come on! Let's go!
-Let's do it!
-Start melting!
They're heading southwest.
God.
No!
Marseille, grab sheets.
Benjamín, clean water.
Move! Everyone out!
Quickly!
Everyone out!
Come on! Out!
They're in a blind spot.
If they're in a blind spot,
it's because they're climbing.
They're going to blow the roof!
Tokyo, Denver, Manila, go to the stairs!
Ready!
Now!
God.
Listen to me.
Start taking deep breaths.
That's it.
You can't push now. That's very important.
I'm going to put my hand in.
-Okay?
-Okay.
It'll be okay.
Let's do it.
-Location, Tokyo.
-We're on the second floor.
Third floor.
Go to the roof,
and catch them from behind. Helsinki?
I'm building a trench!
Retreat to the museum. Wait for me.
-I can't.
-No, for God's sake.
Please!
Come on.
A little bit more.
The breastbone. I've got it.
Please…
Almost there.
I'm pulling it out.
A little more.
Helsinki, get out.
Take shelter in the museum.
Negative!
Let's do this.
Let's do it.
Take cover.
…a terrible explosion…
LIVE
EXPLOSION AT THE BANK OF SPAIN
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick