LA SECRÉTAIRE
Six mois plus tôt
J'ai quitté le centre le jour du mariage de ma sœur.
J'avais commencé à m'y habituer.
8 h : petit-déjeuner, 14 h : cours,
I got out of the institution on the day of my sister's wedding.
16 h : séance de thérapie, 22 h : au lit.
Tu peux m'appeler à tout moment, Lee.
I had started to get used to the place.
Je serai toujours prêt à t'aider.
Breakfast at 8:00, classes at 2:00,
Au centre, la vie était simple.
therapy at 4:00 and asleep by 10:00.
Merci, docteur Twardon.
You can call me any time, Lee.
C'est pourquoi je m'en allais à reculons.
I will always try to be of help to you.
Inside, life was simple.
Thank you, Dr. Twardon.
For that reason, I was reluctant to go.
Bon voyage.
Bonjour, Peter.
Peter, oui. Tu as presque réussi à oublier.
Mais non.
Contente d'être rentrée ?
Hi, Peter. Peter, yeah, who you almost successfully forgot.
Vraiment contente d'être rentrée ?
Je ne sais pas.
- No, I did not. - Come on, everybody! Are you happy to be home?
Je comprends.
I mean, are you happy to be home?
I don't know.
I know what you mean.
Tu es superbe.
Merci, papa.
Here's a little something for the lovebirds.
Tu n'avais pas arrêté ?
Boy!
You look so beautiful.
Tu nous as manqué, ma puce.
Thanks, Dad.
Vous m'avez manqué aussi.
I thought you stopped.
Dis...
Do you know how much we missed you, pumpkin?
Je ne me sens pas très bien.
Well, I missed you, too.
Asseyez-vous.
You know what?
I don't feel too good.
Let's go sit down.
- Bye! - Goodbye!
- Have fun! - Goodbye! Take care!
Arrête de me parler comme à un enfant !
- Je sais ce que je fais. - Tu agis en enfant !
Tu t'es fait virer !
What are you talking about?
You want to treat me like I'm a child. You want to talk to me like a child. - Huh? You think I'm a child? - You...
Je suis content qu'on m'ait viré. Je détestais ce boulot !
You think I don't know what I'm doing? You act like a child!
Je m'en fiche. Tu es ivre !
Yeah, right. You don't act like a man. You've been fired!
Je ne suis pas ivre ! Arrête...
Pourquoi tu dis toujours ça ?
Well, I'm glad I'm fired!
Fiche-moi la paix !
I'm glad I'm fired! Boy, I hated that job!
I don't care that you hated it! You're drunk!
I'm not drunk! Why do you... Why do you... I'm not drunk!
- Why do you always say that? - Get off my back!
Regarde-moi ça...
Watch this. You watch this.
Évitez, en posant les doigts,
de regarder le clavier.
Vos doigts doivent rebondir sur chaque touche.
Chaque frappe doit être pensée.
Avoid the temptation of placing your fingers on the home keys by sight.
N'envisagez pas un instant de jeter un œil sur votre feuille.
Strike each key so that your fingers bounce with each stroke.
"Mes fleurs, de désespoir, venaient d'expirer,
Do not strike without thinking.
"d'où, exception faite des plantes du fleuriste,
Do not even attempt to steal a glance at your paper.
"un printemps sans fleurs, le premier depuis des années."
Terminé !
"My flowers had just about given up in despair, "so with the exception of a few potted plants from the florist,
Je suis fière de toi, chérie.
C'est courageux de sortir.
"we're flowerless for the first spring in years."
And time!
Au moment de mon accident,
I'm so proud of you, honey.
on était dans la cuisine, je lui tournais le dos.
Getting out in the world like this.
À l'étage, papa s'apprêtait à partir travailler chez Havis.
When my accident happened, we were in the kitchen and my back was to her.
Dans ma hâte de profiter de son inattention...
Upstairs, my dad was just leaving for work
j'y ai été trop fort.
at Havis department store.
Comment ai-je pu être si maladroite ?
Because there was a limited amount of time that my mom's back was turned...
Je le faisais depuis la cinquième.
- Lee! - I slipped and cut too deep.
I'm not sure how I could have misjudged.
I've been doing it since seventh grade.
Simple précaution.
Just a precaution.
"Devenez dirigeant."
"Be a leader."
Je n'ai encore jamais travaillé.
Mais soyez sûr que cette offre me motive extrêmement.
Merci.
I have never had a job before,
Je n'ai pas encore de références,
but I can assure you that I am very excited about this opportunity.
mais je crois que le centre municipal des impôts
Thank you.
serait un lieu parfait
Well, I don't have any references yet.
pour débuter
ma carrière.
But I think that the municipal tax office
would be a wonderful place to begin
my career.
Secrétaire.
"Secretary."
RECHERCHE SECRETAIRE
Bonjour, je...
Attendez...
Hello. I...
Wait! I...
Par ici !
Hello?
Bonjour.
In here.
C'est vous, l'avocat ?
Hi.
Pardon. Je repasserai.
Are you the lawyer?
Non, restez.
Oh. Uh...
Yes.
I'm sorry. I'll just come back later.
No.
No, stay.
Vous cherchez une secrétaire ?
C'est exact.
It said "secretary."
Êtes-vous enceinte ?
That's right.
Envisagez-vous une grossesse ?
Are you pregnant?
No.
- Vivez-vous dans un appartement ? - Une maison.
Do you plan on getting pregnant?
Seule ?
Avec mes parents.
Frères et sœurs ?
Ma sœur
No. - Are you living in an apartment? - A house.
va habiter avec son mari dans le bungalow de la piscine.
- Alone? - With my parents.
Êtes-vous mariée ?
Siblings?
Well, my sister is going to live in the backyard
Avez-vous déjà gagné un prix ?
with her husband in the pool house.
C'était pour quoi ?
Are you married?
Dactylographie.
No.
Have you ever won an award?
C'est votre CV ?
Yes.
What did you win the award in?
Typing.
Lee...
Holloway.
Are those your scores?
Yes.
"Lee Holloway."
Vous m'apportez un café sucré ?
Could you get me a cup of coffee with sugar?
Vous voulez vraiment être secrétaire ?
Do you really want to be a secretary, Lee?
Vos notes sont les meilleures que j'aie vues.
Yes, I do.
Vous êtes bien trop qualifiée pour ce poste.
Vous vous y ennuieriez.
Je veux m'ennuyer.
You scored higher than anyone I've ever interviewed.
You're really over-qualified for the job. - You'd be bored to death. - I want to be bored.
J'ai une assistante juridique à mi-temps.
Je n'ai besoin que d'une dactylo.
I have a part-time paralegal.
Quelqu'un qui arrive à l'heure et réponde au téléphone.
Je peux le faire.
All I need is a typist
Ici, on tape à la machine. Pas d'ordinateurs.
Ça me va.
who can get to work on time and answer the phone.
C'est un travail très monotone.
I can do that.
J'aime les tâches monotones.
We only use typewriters here, not computers.
That's fine.
It's very dull work.
Vous avez quelque chose de...
I like dull work.
There's something about you.
Vous êtes totalement renfermée.
Un mur.
You're...
Je sais.
You're closed up tight.
Vous vous ouvrez, parfois ?
A wall.
Je ne sais pas.
I know.
Je ne suis pas là.
Do you ever loosen up?
I don't know.
I'm not here.
Moins sucré, le café.
Less sugar in the coffee.
Comment ça s'est passé ?
Je suis prise.
How'd it go?
I got it.
Je savais que tu pouvais y arriver !
NE PAS DÉRANGER
I knew you could do it!
Bonjour.
Hello.
Ici le bureau de monsieur E. Edward Grey.
Laissez votre message en précisant l'heure de l'appel,
Hello. You have reached the office of Mr. E. Edward Grey.
ainsi que votre numéro de téléphone
et l'heure à laquelle on peut vous joindre.
Please leave your message and the time you called,
Nous nous efforcerons
along with your phone number and the best time to reach you,
de vous recontacter dans les meilleurs délais.
Nous...
and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
Secrétaire.
We.
Secretary.
Envoyez 4 exemplaires de ce courrier à O'Malley et Barret.
Tout de suite, monsieur.
Type up this letter and send four copies to O'Malley and Barrett.
Right away, sir.
C'est bien. C'est bien.
C'est vous, la nouvelle secrétaire ?
That's good. That's good.
Excusez-moi,
So, you're the new secretary.
quel est le rôle d'une assistante juridique ?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
À plus.
What exactly is a paralegal?
See you.
L'œil de l'expert.
Oh, um...
Et voilà...
on agrandit le regard.
Okay.
Up at the sides. Wide-eyed.
Je vous ai apporté ça.
I brought you these.
Par mégarde, j'ai dû jeter mes notes sur l'affaire Feldman.
Pourriez-vous...
Fouiller les poubelles ?
I think I accidentally threw out my notes on the Feldman case.
Oui. Merci.
Maybe you could...
Go through the garbage?
Yes, Lee. Thank you.
Qu'est-ce que tu fais là ?
Je t'attends, chérie.
J'en ai encore pour 5 heures !
Je sais.
Why are you here?
I'm just waiting for you, honey.
But I'm here for five more hours.
I know.
Excusez-moi, monsieur.
C'est bon, j'en ai un autre.
Il me faut plus de sucre.
Excuse me, sir.
Et ceci en 6 exemplaires.
It's okay. I found another set.
Rechargez ce piège et posez-en un autre.
This needs more sugar.
- Sugar? - And six copies of these.
Freshen up that trap, Lee.
And put out one more.
Les souris se faufilent derrière les fauteuils.
En dépit des obstacles, ne négliger aucune possibilité.
Mice like to go behind the chairs, too, Lee.
Just because it's hard to reach
Donnez-moi ça.
does not mean that we don't take care of every possibility.
Here. Give me that.
Merci.
Thank you.
Bureau de M. Grey, j'écoute.
Les services d'AT&T nous conviennent, merci.
Il est là ?
Un petit instant.
E. Edward Grey's office. May I help you?
C'est intéressant, mais...
J'y vais.
We're very happy with AT&T. Thanks, though.
Un instant, je vous prie !
Is he in? Could you just wait one moment?
Je comprends...
Soumise.
You're right. That is a very good offer. I'm going back now.
Pardon ?
Could you just wait one minute, please?
Edward !
Yes, I do understand that.
J'ignore totalement si notre facture dépasse les 40 dollars
Submissive.
en longue distance vers Chattanooga !
Excuse me?
Edward!
Listen, I have no idea if we make over $40
Annoncez Tricia O'Connor.
Monsieur Grey ?
worth of long distance calls to Chattanooga each month.
Tell him it's Tricia O'Connor.
Mr. Grey?
Miss Holloway.
Hello?
Mr. Grey?
Ms. Holloway.
Je ne suis pas là.
Mr. Grey?
I'm not here.
J'ai peur qu'il ne soit plus là.
Ah, vraiment ?
Okay.
I'm afraid he's gone.
Bureau de M. Grey.
C'est toi, ma chérie ?
Is that right?
Papa ?
C'est bon de t'entendre.
Papa... où es-tu ?
E. Edward Grey's office.
En ville. Quelque part.
Is that you, honey? It's me. Daddy?
Ne quitte pas, s'il te plaît.
It's so good to hear your voice. Dad.
Y a-t-il un message ?
Where are you?
I'm downtown, somewhere.
Could you please hold?
Do you have a message, Ms. O'Connor?
Dites-lui de signer l'accord.
Tell him to sign the settlement.
Papa ?
Hello?
Hello, Dad?
Ça a été, au travail ?
Très bien.
Comment est M. Grey ?
Peter a appelé.
How's work?
Fine.
How's Mr. Grey?
He's fine. Well, Peter called.
Y en a qui lavent des fringues à peine portées.
Une demi-journée, et au sale.
D'autres, plus relax, lavent leur linge quand il est sale.
T'es de quel genre ?
Some people, right, have to wash something as soon as they've worn it,
Du genre qui a envie
- you know, for, like, half a day. - Yes. And then you got your more laid-back folk who just,
de se marier et d'avoir un gosse.
you know, maybe they'll wash their stuff when it's dirty. Which kind are you?
Je ne le lave que lorsqu'il est sale.
I'm the type of guy
Moi aussi.
who wants to get married and have a kid.
C'est ça l'important dans une relation : la compatibilité.
I wash my clothes just when they're dirty.
Dans une relation ?
Me, too, and... And that is what counts in a relationship.
Compatibility.
In a relationship?
- Ln a relationship. - Relationship.
Je t'en ressers une larme ?
Pourquoi pas.
May I interest you in a little more?
Tu n'es plus le même qu'au lycée.
- Just a little more? - Why not? Okay.
Effectivement. J'ai changé.
- Pourquoi ? - J'ai fait une dépression nerveuse.
Moi aussi.
You're different than you were in high school, Peter.
En quelque sorte.
I... I changed.
What happened?
I had a nervous breakdown.
Me, too.
Peter...
Sort of.
J'ai lu que ce genre de sous-vêtements
Two items. This and these.
te compresse...
les machins.
- Peter? - Yes, Lee? I've read that if you wear that kind of underwear,
Les couilles.
that it squeezes
- Les bonbons. - Les bonbons.
Les testicules.
your things.
- Balls. - Yes. Balls?
Alors, tu ne peux plus avoir d'enfants.
My grapes.
Mais tu veux en avoir.
Your grapes? My...
Voilà, je l'ai dit.
Your testicles.
Bébés !
Your sperm gets squozen, and then you can't have babies, and I thought that you said that you wanted to have babies.
Couches-culottes !
Fesses irritées.
There you go. I said it.
Allaitement et pleurs.
To babies!
To diapers.
To diaper rash.
To breast-feeding. And to crying.
Regardez !
Vous voyez ?
Quoi ?
3 bévues dont une faute d'orthographe.
Look at it!
Je suis désolée.
Do you see that? What?
Les fois précédentes, je n'avais rien dit,
This letter has three typing errors in it,
mais ça ne peut plus durer.
one of which is, I believe, a spelling error.
Imaginez l'image que cela donne de moi !
I'm... I'm sorry.
Je suis désolée...
This isn't the first time, either. There've been others that I let go because it was in the first few weeks.
Retapez-moi ça. Et correctement, cette fois.
This cannot go on.
Do you know what this makes me look like to the people who receive these letters?
I... I'm sorry. I'm...
Type it again and get it right.
Vous me faites perdre mon temps.
You're wasting my time.
"Un morceau de moi. Un petit sacrifice. Pour M. Grey."
Au revoir.
Bye.
Facturez 500 dollars à cette femme.
Vous ne vérifiez pas la lettre ?
Go type up a bill for that woman for $500.
Aren't you going to proofread the letter?
Lee.
Aux yeux de ceux qui entrent dans ce bureau, vous me représentez.
Et votre style vestimentaire est à vomir.
When people come into this office,
Je suis désolée.
you are a visual representation of my business.
Vous piétinez sans arrêt
et vous touchez vos cheveux.
And the way you dress is disgusting.
Portez un filet ou cessez de vous toucher les cheveux.
I'm sorry. You're tapping your toe all the time and playing with your hair.
Autre chose :
You're either going to have to wear a hairnet
Savez-vous que vous passez votre temps à renifler ?
or stop playing with your hair.
Je renifle ?
Et ce jeu avec votre langue,
And another thing,
quand vous tapez.
do you realize that you are always sniffling?
Pardon, j'ignorais que je reniflais.
I... I'm sniffling? And what is with your tongue
C'est pourtant le cas.
when you're typing?
I'm sorry. I didn't know I sniffled.
Monsieur Grey,
Well, you do.
merci mille fois
pour vos conseils avisés.
Mr. Grey,
Parce que je m'efforce de devenir
thank you so much for your helpful suggestions.
la meilleure secrétaire possible
pour vous.
Because I am trying to be
Je l'entends ainsi : "En l'absence de l'appui approprié
"d'une source bien informée,
the very best secretary that I can be.
"ma cliente n'aurait jamais
For you.
"décidé cela de son propre chef."
Point final !
The sentence should read,
Je vous ai répété...
"Without proper guidance from a knowledgeable source,
"my client would never have made
"these material decisions on her own." Period!
I have repeated the sentence twice.
Why don't you listen, think and then respond.
Pas de vin, vraiment ?
Okay?
C'est un vin maison. Hein, Stewart ?
Goûtez, il est bon.
Une goutte, Lee ?
Non, merci. Pas pour l'instant, Sylvia.
Are you sure you wouldn't like some wine?
Peter parle de vous sans arrêt.
We make it homemade, don't we, Stewart?
Il prétend avoir trouvé l'âme sœur.
Try it. It's good.
Would you like some, Lee?
Tu as dit ça ?
No, thank you.
Not right now, Sylvia.
Oui.
You know, Peter talks about you all the time.
Sa sœur, Lindsey,
He says he's found his soul mate.
va se marier l'hiver prochain à Las Vegas.
Did you say that?
Peter a un très bon poste. Ils lui paient même un mobile.
I did. Peter's sister, Lindsey,
Ce sera peut-être un double mariage.
is getting married this coming winter in Vegas.
Did you know Peter has a very stable job at JC Penney?
They even gave him a cell phone.
Perhaps it'll be a double wedding?
Mom.
Miss Holloway ! Venez dans la bibliothèque.
Immédiatement.
Ms. Holloway, come into the library.
Immediately.
... des remarques faites par écrit.
En résumé des débats sur le cas Berkowitz. Veuillez agréer, etc.
"Refer only to slanderous remarks made in print. "In summation of the events
Le téléphone sonne.
"in regard to the Rubin Berkowitz libel. Yours sincerely, etc."
Répondez.
Okay.
The phone is ringing.
Je suis désolée...
Answer it.
I'm sorry...
Bonjour. Bureau de...
Vous êtes assez grande
Oh.
pour faire sortir des sons plus forts de votre gorge frêle.
Frêle.
Hello? This is the office of...
Miss Holloway,
Listen.
vous m'aviez affirmé avoir l'habitude
You're a big girl. You can get a much bigger voice out of that tiny throat of yours.
de répondre au téléphone.
J'ai l'habitude.
Tiny.
Avez-vous bien dormi, cette nuit ?
Ms. Holloway.
Ça sonne !
You told me when I hired you
that you were used to answering phones.
I am. Did you get enough sleep last night?
Bureau de M. E. Edward Grey.
Vous voyez ?
- I... - The phone is ringing!
Là, ça pulse ! Ce n'est pas une morgue, ici.
Hello.
This is the office of Mr. E. Edward Grey.
You see? You see? You see? You see?
That's showing a little spunk.
After all, I'm not running a mortuary.
No.
Approchez.
Lee.
Mr. Grey.
Come here.
Êtes-vous sortie avec un homme, récemment ?
Qui était-ce ?
Did you have a date recently?
Peter.
Vous avez fait l'amour ?
Yes.
With whom did you have a date?
Je ne sais pas.
- Peter. - Peter?
Did you have sex?
Vous êtes timide ?
No?
Moi, je le suis.
I don't know.
Vous n'êtes pas timide. Vous êtes avocat.
Are you shy?
Si, je suis timide.
I'm shy.
Je cache ma timidité
You're not shy. You're a lawyer.
pour que les choses avancent.
I'm shy.
Je ne vous crois pas timide.
I overcome my shyness to...
Ln order to get things done.
Je vais être honnête avec vous.
I don't think you're shy.
Je sais, je suis votre employeur,
notre relation est donc déterminée.
Lee, I want to be frank with you.
Mais...
Now, I know I'm your employer, and we have
vous devriez vraiment vous sentir libre
a prescribed relationship.
de me parler de vos problèmes.
But you really should feel free
to discuss your problems with me.
Qu'est-ce que c'est que cette trousse ?
Oh.
What's going on with the sewing kit and the Band-Aids?
Je me sens...
timide.
Lee?
Un chocolat chaud ?
I feel...
- Shy. - Shy.
Do you want some hot chocolate?
Okay.
Pourquoi vous mutilez-vous ?
Je ne sais pas.
Why do you cut yourself, Lee?
Est-ce pour faire sortir la douleur,
pour la voir matérialisée
et comprendre que vous êtes là ?
Puis, la cicatrisation,
I don't know.
cela vous réconforte, non ?
Is it that sometimes the pain inside has to come to the surface,
and when you see evidence of the pain inside,
you finally know you are really here?
Then, when you watch the wound heal, it's comforting. Isn't it?
On peut le voir comme ça.
Êtes-vous prête à m'écouter ?
I...
Vous écoutez ?
That's a way to put it.
I'm going to tell you something, Lee. Are you ready to listen?
Plus jamais à l'avenir
vous ne vous mutilerez.
Yes. Are you listening?
C'est compris ?
Me suis-je clairement fait comprendre ?
You will never,
Tout ça, c'est terminé.
ever cut yourself again.
C'est du passé.
Do you understand?
Have I made that perfectly clear?
You're over that now.
It's in the past.
Plus jamais.
Yes.
Vous savez ce que j'aimerais ?
Never again.
Quittez le bureau plus tôt.
Okay. Now, you know what I want you to do?
Vous êtes adulte, votre mère n'a pas à vous récupérer chaque jour.
I want you to leave work early.
Rentrez à pied, prenez un bon bol d'air.
Ça vous fera du bien.
You're a big girl, a grown woman. Your mother doesn't need to pick you up every day.
Vous ne ferez plus jamais ça,
n'est-ce pas ?
I want you to take a nice walk home, in the fresh air.
Non, monsieur.
Because you require relief.
Bon.
Because you won't be doing that anymore.
Will you?
No, sir.
Good.
Il est bien tôt.
Maman,
je rentrerai à pied, désormais.
Look who's early.
J'ai coupé à travers Hawkins Park.
Mom,
C'était comme si je me promenais seule pour la première fois.
I'm going to walk home from now on.
En y réfléchissant, je me suis aperçu que c'était le cas.
I took a shortcut through Hawkins Park, and it was as if I'd never taken a walk by myself before.
Parce qu'il m'avait autorisée à le faire,
parce qu'il m'y avait poussée,
And when I thought about it, I realized I probably never had taken a walk alone.
je me sentais soutenue par lui, tout en marchant seule.
But because he had given me the permission to do this,
Je le sentais avec moi.
because he'd insisted I do it,
Parallèlement,
I felt held by him as I walked along.
je sentais quelque chose croître en M. Grey.
Un filament intime
I felt he was with me.
échappé de l'un de ses plus sombres recoins,
At the same time, I was feeling something growing in Mr. Grey,
né du sentiment
d'avoir découvert quelque chose chez moi.
an intimate tendril creeping from one of his darker areas,
Le lendemain, je suis venue sans mes petits ciseaux.
nursed on the feeling that he had discovered something about me.
Mais j'ai refait une faute de frappe.
Ces choses simples ne le sont-elles pas assez ?
The next day, I didn't even bring my cuticle scissors and my iodine.
- Le courrier et le téléphone ? - Pardon.
Manifestement !
But I did make another typing mistake.
- Pardon. - Assez d'excuses !
What is wrong with you? That is all you have to do.
Qu'est-ce qui se passe dans votre tête ?
Type and answer the phones. Is that beyond you?
- I'm sorry. - Well, it certainly seems to be.
- I'm sorry. - Don't apologize to me!
What goes on inside that head of yours?
Venez dans mon bureau avec la lettre.
Come into my office and bring that letter.
Posez-la sur mon bureau.
Put the letter on my desk.
À présent, penchez-vous de façon à l'avoir bien en face.
Approchez votre visage de la lettre et lisez-la tout haut.
Now, I want you to bend over the desk, so you're looking directly at it.
Je ne comprends pas.
Il n'y a rien à comprendre.
Get your face very close to the letter, and read the letter aloud.
Posez les coudes sur le bureau, penchez-vous,
I don't understand.
approchez votre visage de la lettre et lisez-la tout haut.
There's nothing to understand.
Put your elbows on the desk, bend over,
get your face close to the letter and read it aloud.
"Cher M. Garvey,
"je vous suis reconnaissant de m'avoir..."
"Dear Mr. Garvey,
"I'm grateful to you for referring..."
Poursuivez.
Miss Holloway, lisez.
Continue.
Um...
Ms. Holloway, read.
"... de m'avoir soumis votre dossier.
"La captivité des animaux est un sujet qui me tient à cour
"For referring me to your case.
"et ma secrétaire a rassemblé divers documents
"qui ne manqueront pas de vous éclairer.
"The subject of animal captivity has been of interest to me for quite a while.
"Merci
"And my secretary has prepared research material
"de m'envoyer ce courrier du 5 juin que nous avons évoqué,
"that I think you'll find illuminating.
"afin que nous puissions l'examiner sans délai.
"If you would be so kind "as to send me the June 5th letter of which we spoke,
"N'hésitez pas à me contacter dès qu'il vous siéra.
"Sincères salutations,
"my associates and I will review it immediately."
"E. Edward Grey."
"Please feel free to call me at your earliest convenience.
"Yours sincerely, E. Edward Grey."
Relisez-la.
"Cher M. Garvey,
Read it again.
"je vous suis reconnaissant
"de m'avoir soumis votre dossier.
"Dear Mr. Garvey,
"La captivité des animaux est un sujet
"qui me tient à cour...
"I am grateful to you
"for referring me to your case.
"The subject of animal captivity has been of interest to me
"Et ma secrétaire a rassemblé divers documents...
"for quite a while.
"qui ne manqueront pas de vous éclairer."
"And my secretary has prepared research material
"that I think you'll find illuminating."
Relevez-vous et retapez-la.
Now straighten yourself up and go type it again.
Miss Holloway,
très bon courrier.
Ms. Holloway. Good letter.
Maman...
tu peux déverrouiller le buffet, à présent.
Mom?
The lock can come off the cabinet now.
Ma chérie...
Honey.
- Oh!
Remplacez les ampoules du couloir qui mène au bureau.
120 watts.
M. Garvey. Vous vous rappelez ma secrétaire, Miss Holloway ?
Replace the light bulb in the hallway to my office.
Excusez mes fautes de frappe.
120 watts.
- Mr. Grey. - Good to see you again, Mr. Garvey.
You remember my secretary, Ms. Holloway. I'm sorry about the typo.
Il y a du steak,
de l'écrasée de pommes de terre... enfin de la purée,
des petits pois,
du thé glacé et de la glace.
Une cuillerée de purée,
It's porterhouse steak, mashed, no, creamed potatoes,
une noisette de beurre
quatre petits pois
green peas, iced tea and ice cream.
et...
autant de glace que vous voudrez.
Okay. Just a scoop of creamed potatoes,
and a slice of butter, four peas
and as much ice cream as you'd like to eat, doll.
Cosmo vous conseille, afin d'obtenir de votre homme
des confidences d'ordre intime,
de miser d'abord sur un humour léger.
Évitez absolument
Cosmo's advice for getting your man to share his feelings more intimately
de vous lancer illico dans des discussions de couple.
is to first try some breezy humor.
Whatever you do, don't jump too quickly into relationship talk.
Je suis votre secrétaire.
Votre secrétaire.
Juste une cuillerée de purée,
une noisette de beurre
I'm your secretary.
et...
quatre petits pois.
Just one scoop of creamed potatoes,
one slice of butter,
and four peas.
Aviez-vous éteint la chaudière avant de descendre ?
How many inches away...
Had you turned off the furnace before you went down to the basement?
Peut-être n'avez-vous pas appuyé assez...
Okay.
Maybe you didn't squeeze it hard enough.
Well, there's always concern about it bursting.
No! God, no. I haven't had time to get to that.
Où était-elle quand vous vous êtes glissée en dessous ?
I'm doing as much as I possibly can.
Et le coffre, vous l'avez recouvert ?
À l'étage ?
Where was she when you crawled under the house?
Je ne comprends pas.
And the lockbox? Did you cover it with dirt before you left?
Votre fils obèse ou votre neveu de Baltimore ?
Mud upstairs?
Sur la rambarde.
No, I'm confused by that.
But...
All right. This was the overweight child, or your nephew from Baltimore?
Je dois travailler.
On the banister.
Laissez-moi une semaine.
Je suis navré, le bureau a été...
I have to work.
pris d'assaut.
Okay. Give me a week and I'll have something for you.
M. Grey, je rentre chez moi.
I'm sorry, the office has been
Si vous avez encore
des courriers à taper,
overwhelmed.
je reviendrai plus tard.
Mr. Grey, I'm going to go home now. If you need any more typing done, I could come back later.
Merci, Miss Holloway. Bonsoir.
Ce sera tout.
Thank you, Ms. Holloway, good night.
Un exemple :
That'll be all.
l'autre soir, il m'a invitée à aller prendre un verre.
Et il voulait savoir si je portais des collants ventre plat.
Des normaux ne serviraient à rien.
Here's just one example.
Ton patron ?
He asked me out to Red Lobster the other night for a nightcap.
Poursuis-le pour harcèlement.
- Right. - Yeah. And yesterday, he asked if my hose were control-top,
C'est une idée séduisante.
and if they were, I certainly didn't need it.
Mon avocat défend une femme qui l'a fait.
- Your boss? - Yeah.
C'est un bon avocat ?
You should sue him for sexual harassment.
Le meilleur !
- I like that idea. - Hello.
My lawyer's representing a woman who's suing her boss for sexual harassment.
Pour combien de temps ?
Is he a good lawyer?
He's the best.
C'était qui ?
"He's the best." How long will he be there?
Il est venu de lui-même à l'hôpital.
Who was that?
He checked himself into the hospital.
Lee?
Yes? Lee?
Je voulais juste...
Hi.
J'avais besoin que vous...
I...
Je voulais que vous...
I just wanted...
Vous aviez besoin de quoi ?
I needed you...
I wanted you to...
You need me to what?
Je voulais vous rappeler de consulter le dossier Lynch.
Je l'avais en tête.
Tant mieux.
I just wanted you not to forget to go over the Lynch papers for tomorrow.
Merci, Lee.
No. I haven't.
That's good.
Thank you, Lee.
Après m'avoir fermé sa porte, il m'a renvoyée à mes occupations
et il a arrêté de le faire.
Il a jeté tous ses stylos rouges.
After he turned me away from his house, he put me back at my old desk,
J'ai continué les bourdes,
and he just stopped doing it.
mais il me traitait comme une vieille secrétaire ordinaire.
Ça vient ?
He threw out all his red pens. I kept making typos, but he just treated me like a regular old secretary.
Alors, je me suis demandé si je ne l'étais pas vraiment.
Aucun chèque de M. Garvey ?
Aucun, monsieur.
Are you coming?
After a while, I began to wonder if that was all I was.
Classez ça.
Have we received any checks from Mr. Garvey?
No, sir.
Jolie cravate.
File these.
Mais vous n'allez pas jouer au golf.
Quoi ?
Votre cravate.
Il y a des golfeurs, dessus.
That's a pretty tie. But I guess you won't be golfing today. What?
Eh oui.
Your tie.
It has golfers on it.
C'est pas vrai !
Right.
Damn it.
N'aie pas peur.
Je n'ai pas peur.
Don't be scared.
I'm not. I'm...
Je ne pensais pas à ça.
Excuse-moi.
Regarde.
That's not what I meant.
D'accord, mais je garde mes vêtements
I'm sorry, I just... Look here.
et on éteint toutes les lumières.
I'm sorry.
Okay, but my clothes get to stay completely on
and I want the lights out.
Je t'ai pas fait mal ?
Lee, Lee, Lee.
I didn't hurt you, did I?
No.
Miss Holloway.
Oui, M. Grey ?
Venez dans mon bureau.
Ms. Holloway.
Mais, M. Marvel attend.
Yes, Mr. Grey?
Miss Holloway, venez dans mon bureau.
Come into my office.
Oui, monsieur.
But Mr. Marvel is waiting.
Enfin !
Ms. Holloway, come into my office.
Yes, sir.
Finally.
Laissez.
Ignore it.
Relevez votre jupe.
Pourquoi ?
Aucun risque que je vous baise.
Now, pull up your skirt.
Ça ne m'intéresse pas le moins du monde.
Relevez votre jupe.
Why?
You're not worried that I'm going to fuck you, are you?
I'm not interested in that, not in the least.
Now, pull up your skirt.
J'ai dit : relevez votre jupe.
Lee, Lee, Lee, Lee
Lee?
Peter !
Je ne pourrai pas venir dîner, d'accord ?
I said, pull up your skirt.
Peter. I'm not going to be able to come to the diner today, okay?
D'accord... c'est pas grave.
Okay.
That's okay. Because... That's all right.
Baissez vos collants et votre culotte.
Je vous l'ai dit, je ne vous baiserai pas.
Pull down your panty hose and underwear.
I told you I'm not going to fuck you.
Faites remplir ces formulaires,
puis vous pourrez aller déjeuner.
Apportez-moi mon sandwich, je ne sors pas.
Et...
Get these forms filled out, and then you can take your lunch break.
Prenez le même que d'habitude.
Bring me my sandwich, I'm eating in.
Sans mayonnaise, cette fois.
Et puis,
And you'll have the usual.
faites entrer monsieur...
No mayonnaise this time.
And send in what's his name.
Okay?
Monsieur Grey...
Mr. Grey.
Bite.
Mettez votre queue dans ma bouche.
Sautez-moi.
Cock. Place your prick in my mouth.
Screw me.
Mayonnaise. Orchidée.
Shit. Fuck.
Mayonnaise. Orchid.
Mr. Grey.
Edward.
La plupart des gens considèrent plus vivable de fuir la douleur.
Mais il est bien plus appréciable d'explorer
le panel entier des émotions.
Most people think that the best way to live is to run from pain.
En faisant l'expérience de la douleur comme celle du plaisir,
But a much more joyful life embraces the entire spectrum
on peut donner à sa vie plus de profondeur et de sens.
DOMINANT / DOMINÉ
of human feeling.
If we can fully experience pain, as well as pleasure,
we can live a much deeper and more meaningful life.
"Chère Lee,
"c'est dégoûtant. Pardon. J'ignore pourquoi je fais ça."
Miss Holloway.
Apportez-moi votre CV.
- Ms. Holloway.
Yes, sir?
- Bring your typing scores. - Okay.
Que s'est-il passé ?
Êtes-vous enceinte ?
What happened?
Envisagez-vous une grossesse ?
Are you pregnant?
No.
Vivez-vous dans un appartement ?
Une maison.
- Do you plan on getting pregnant? - Could I...
Seule ?
Do you plan on getting pregnant?
Avec mes parents.
No.
Êtes-vous mariée ?
Are you living in an apartment?
A house.
Alone?
With my parents.
Are you married?
No.
C'est votre CV ?
Are those your scores?
Vous voulez vraiment être ma secrétaire ?
Yes.
Do you really want to be my secretary?
Il ne s'agit pas de simple dactylographie, n'est-ce pas ?
Non, monsieur.
Yes, I do.
Quoi ?
Non, monsieur.
This isn't just about typos, tape, staples and pencils, is it, Lee? - No, sir. - What?
Je vous aime bien, mais je ne vais pas vous embaucher.
No, sir.
Pourquoi ?
À cause de votre attitude.
I like you, Lee, but I don't think I'm going to offer you the job.
Comment ça ?
Elle est répréhensible.
Why?
It's your behavior.
Je suis désolé. Rassemblez vos affaires.
What about my behavior?
On arrête !
It's very bad.
Vous êtes virée.
- Vous êtes viré ! - Vous !
À présent, sortez !
I'm sorry. You can collect your things.
- Time-out! - Time-out? - You're fired. - You're fired! You're fired. Now, Lee, get out!
Vous avez souillé de colle les documents Ramsey.
Je réparais votre broyeuse, vous m'avez vue.
Vous ôtez vos chaussures sous le bureau.
Je sens vos pieds.
Why did you get glue smear all over the Ramsey papers?
Changez-vous de collants ?
Tous les jours.
Because I was fixing your shredder. You saw me.
Quand vous gommez, vous en mettez plein votre bureau.
Are you aware you kick your shoes off under your desk?
Je vous ai dit de rapporter ce walkman chez vous.
I can smell your feet. Do you ever change your panty hose? Every day.
Je refuse que vous puissiez écouter de la musique
Every time you erase, there are little shavings all over your desk.
au lieu de travailler.
I told you to take that Walkman home.
J'ai vérifié vos tiroirs, je sais qu'il y est.
J'y remédierai.
I don't want the possibility of your listening to music
when you're supposed to be working for me.
I saw it in your desk. I know it's there.
I'll move it.
Il faut partir, ou je n'arrêterai pas.
N'arrêtez pas.
Je ne peux plus faire ça.
You have to go, or I won't stop.
Mais je veux vous connaître.
Don't.
I cannot do this anymore.
But I want to know you.
Je suis désolé de ce qui s'est passé entre nous.
Je me rends compte de l'erreur effroyable
que j'ai commise avec vous.
I'm so sorry for what happened between us.
Et je ne peux qu'espérer que vous comprenez.
I've realized what a terrible mistake I made with you.
Je vous fournirai d'excellentes références.
And I can only hope that you understand.
Sortez.
Be assured you can count on me for excellent references.
Qu'est-ce que...
Sortez !
Get out.
- What are you doing... - Get out!
J'ai ouvert l'enveloppe en arrivant.
C'était un chèque de 680 dollars.
Plus que ce qu'il me devait.
J'ai pensé déchirer le chèque, mais je ne l'ai pas fait.
I opened the envelope the second I got home.
J'avais l'impression de faire ce qu'il fallait
It was a check for $680. More than he actually owed me.
et je n'ai rien dit à personne.
It occurred to me to tear up the check, but I didn't.
Je suis partie au matin comme d'habitude
I felt like I was doing the right thing.
et je me suis postée sur le trottoir d'en face.
And I didn't tell anybody about any of it.
Il avait embauché une nouvelle et fait changer les serrures.
I pretended to go to work as usual, and watched his office from across the street.
Je ne pouvais rien y faire du tout.
He hired a new girl and changed the locks on the doors.
There was just nothing for me to do about it.
Le docteur, au centre, m'avait dit :
"Il n'y a que le premier pas qui coûte."
Alors, j'ai décidé de rencontrer quelqu'un.
My doctor at the institution once said, "Every journey begins with the first step."
Celui-là essayait déjà de me pincer les seins
avant même qu'on soit dans sa voiture.
So I decided it was time to meet someone new.
Un autre m'a demandé d'uriner sur son patio
et comme je refusais...
There was one who tried to grab and pinch my nipples
Tu te disais masochiste.
before we even made it to his car.
Puis il y a eu l'accro des cuisinières,
Hi.
brûleurs tous azimuts.
Another guy kept ordering me to pee on his patio,
Je lui lançais des tomates.
Merci.
and when I refused, he said... I thought you were a masochist.
Puis, j'ai abandonné. Je suis restée à la maison.
Then there was the one who liked being tied to a gas stove
J'aidais papa à lutter pour rester sobre.
while the burners were on full blast, and I had to throw tomatoes at him.
Mais un jour,
sans crier gare,
Thank you. For a while I just stopped trying and stayed at home,
Peter m'a demandée en mariage au sous-sol de son travail.
helping Dad adjust to his new sobriety.
J'ai dû dire oui par désarroi.
Until one day, out of the blue, Peter proposed marriage to me
J'étais sans doute plus mince que vous, à l'époque.
in the basement of JC Penney's.
I think I said yes because I didn't know what else to do.
Il faudra retenir votre respiration.
Restez-là, j'appelle Stewart.
Well, I guess I was a little lighter than you in those days.
Vous êtes jolie. Vraiment trop jolie.
Okay.
Now, if you hold your breath through the wedding, you'll make it.
Don't move. I'm going to get Stewart.
You're beautiful. You're just too beautiful.
Je ne dois pas te voir avant !
Lee?
No! I'm not supposed to see you before the wedding!
Where are you going?
J'ai quelque chose à vous dire.
Je vous aime.
Il ne faut pas venir ici.
- I have something to say to you. - Lee.
I love you.
Lee, you should not be here.
Je suis désolé, mais je pense que c'est faux.
C'est vrai. Je vous assure.
I'm sorry, but I don't believe that to be true.
Cette affaire s'est réglée par des indemnités de licenciement.
Well, it is true. Lt is.
Je vous aime.
This matter was resolved
On ne peut pas faire ça 24 heures sur 24.
when I received your canceled severance check.
Pourquoi ?
I love you.
We can't do this 24 hours a day, seven days a week.
Why not?
Posez les mains sur le bureau.
Put both your hands on the desk. Palms down.
Je veux faire l'amour.
Ne décollez pas les pieds du sol avant mon retour.
I want to make love.
Keep both your feet on the floor until I come back.
Je vous informe que votre fiancée est à mon bureau.
Hello?
In case you're wondering, your fiancée is at my office.
Lee, je vous aime beaucoup moi aussi.
Ah, c'est toi.
Lee, I'm very fond of you as well.
Oh, it's you.
Qu'est-ce que tu fais, Lee ?
Je ne comprends pas ce...
Je regrette, tu dois partir.
What are you... What are you doing?
Je suis ton fiancé, Lee !
Lee, I don't... I don't know what the deal is with...
Tu outrepasses les limites.
I'm sorry, I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
Tu fais une incursion injustifiée,
tu t'introduis subrepticement
dans une sphère individuelle.
I'm your fiancée, Lee!
You are trespassing.
You are making an unwarranted incursion, a gradual or stealthy entrance into the sphere of another.
Ce que tu fais là...
c'est sexuel ?
Ça en à l'air, à ton avis ?
Okay, Lee, Lee, are you doing something sexual right now?
Je ne sais pas, Lee !
Pourquoi tu ne bouges pas ?
Does this look sexual to you?
Parce que je n'en ai pas envie.
I don't know, Lee!
Why don't you move your hands?
Because I don't want to.
No!
Je ne veux pas de toi.
Va-t'en.
Peter, I don't want you.
Va-t'en !
Now, get out.
Get out.
Get out!
Je t'ai apporté des petits pois.
- Here you go. - Great.
Aucune loi ne peut réglementer les relations entre hommes et femmes.
I brought you some peas.
Il y a d'autres moyens d'exprimer ses sentiments. Plus normaux.
There are no statutes capable of controlling the relations between men and women.
J'exige de récupérer cette robe dans un état irréprochable.
Je vous laisse consulter ces livres.
There are other ways to show your feelings, Lee. More conventional ways.
Commencez donc par la lutte des femmes.
I expect that dress back, dry-cleaned, in perfect condition.
I'm just going to leave you with this literature.
Why don't you read about women's struggle first?
Cela nous fait remonter très loin dans l'histoire du catholicisme.
Les moines portaient des couronnes d'épines
et les nonnes en cousaient dans leurs vêtements.
You know, Lee, there's a long history of this in Catholicism.
Il y a 2 ans, on a dû admettre que ça ne marchait pas.
The monks used to wear thorns on their temples.
Il m'a filé entre les doigts.
Tu te joins à une grande tradition.
And the nuns, they wore them sewn inside their clothing.
Je vous admire.
Two years ago, when it didn't work out between us, that was it.
Il est de loin l'homme le plus seul que j'aie jamais vu.
Le ver de terre : stupéfiant !
I let him slip through my fingers. You are part of a great tradition.
Qui a dit que l'amour devait être doux et affectueux ?
I admire you, Ms. Holloway. Without question, he is the most isolated man I have ever known.
"Tu es l'enfant du saint présent divin qu'est la vie.
The worm. Amazing. Who's to say that love needs to be soft and gentle?
"Tu viens de moi, mais tu n'es pas moi.
"You are the child of God's holy gift of life.
"Ton âme et ton corps t'appartiennent,
"à toi d'en disposer à ta guise."
"You come from me, but you are not me.
Merci, papa.
"Your soul and your body are your own, and yours to do with as you wish."
Thank you, Daddy.
Les boissons !
Chacun prend ce qu'il a demandé, pas le verre d'un autre.
57...
Drinks.
bières sur le mur.
Take what you ordered. Now don't take anybody else's drink. What you ordered.
57 bouteilles de bière.
Fifty-seven bottles of beer on the wall
Retirez-en une...
Fifty-seven bottles of beer
Take one down...
C'est le troisième jour de ce qu'on nommera
la grève de la faim de Lee Holloway.
Vous savez peut-être que certains ici
doutent de sa volonté de se laisser mourir de faim.
We're here on day three of what has come to be known
as the Lee Holloway hunger strike. Now, you may have heard that there are those in the community
D'une façon ou d'une autre, j'ai toujours souffert.
who wonder if Ms. Holloway is even willing to starve herself to death.
Je ne sais pas trop pourquoi.
Mais je sais que je n'ai plus peur de souffrir, à présent.
In one way or another, I've always suffered.
Je ressens plus que jamais,
I don't know why, exactly.
et j'ai trouvé quelqu'un avec qui ressentir,
But I do know that I'm not so scared of suffering now.
avec qui jouer,
quelqu'un à aimer.
I feel more than I've ever felt,
Sur un mode qui me convient.
and I've found someone to feel with, to play with, to love
J'espère qu'il sait que je vois sa souffrance
et que je veux l'aimer.
in a way that feels right for me.
I hope he knows that I can see that he suffers, too.
And that I want to love him.
À chaque coupure, chaque cicatrice, chaque brûlure
correspond une humeur, une période différentes.
Je lui ai parlé de la première,
Each cut, each scar, each burn, a different mood or time.
je lui ai dit d'où venait la seconde.
Je me les rappelais toutes.
Et pour la première fois de ma vie,
I told him what the first one was.
je me suis sentie belle.
I told him where the second one came from.
J'appartenais enfin à ce monde.
I remembered them all.
Je touchais la terre
And for the first time in my life,
et il m'aimait en retour.
I felt beautiful.
Finally part of the earth.
I touched the soil, and he loved me back.
Quel lycée as-tu fréquenté ?
Comment était ta mère ?
Comment s'appelait-elle ?
Where did you go to high school?
Quel commentaire
What was your mother like?
accompagnait ta photo sur le palmarès de ton école ?
What was her name?
Qui était ton premier amour ?
What did it say under your senior yearbook picture?
Quand as-tu eu le cour brisé
pour la première fois ?
Who was your first love?
When did your heart first get broken?
Où es-tu né ?
Where were you born?
Des Moines, dans l'Iowa.
Des Moines, Iowa.
Toutes nos activités
devinrent une sorte de train-train,
jusqu'à ce qu'on ressemble à tous les couples.
Rabats-le.
All our activities melted into an everyday sort of life
Bien tendu.
Ces oreillers
until we looked like any other couple you'd see.
bien empilés...
Turn that over, yes. Just pull it tight.
Du plus grand au plus petit.
On s'est mariés en juin.
Now, these pillows like to be stacked.
Seuls devant l'officier civil.
Largest to smallest.
Puis, la lune de miel dans la montagne.
We had a June wedding,
Juste un week-end : Edward devait retourner travailler.
by ourselves at the justice of the peace.
Then, we honeymooned in the mountains.
We only had the weekend because Edward had to get back to work.
Adaptation : Sylvie André
Sous-titrage : C.M.C. - Paris
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412