[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
But I just killed you.
It's a delicious little mystery for you
to turn over in that pretty little head,
- isn't it, Sara Lance?
- No, you're dead.
You're not the only one
who's flirted with death.
How?
♪ You'll never guess
in a billion years ♪
You're a clone.
Okay, yes. You got it.
- Just like the AVAs.
- No.
No, not like the AVAs. Different.
There's only one of me.
One at a time.
We're all just coding, Sara.
DNA can be mapped and cloned,
and each and every data point
in our brain can be mapped and cloned.
You can recreate yourself,
body and mind?
The mind is just impulses,
synapses, and memory.
No different from any computer.
Look, science has evolved quite a bit
beyond your comprehension.
You're like a caveman to
me... or like a monkey.
Or like a cave monkey.
Imagine what you could've done
if you used that knowledge
for good instead of this.
I am using it for good.
I am restarting the doomed human race,
and you will see that eventually.
[WEAPON WHIRS]
You will see it my way in time.
♪ And you've got nothing but time ♪
♪ Because no one's coming to save you ♪
♪ ♪
[HEROIC MUSIC]
You drank all the booze.
Not my fault you couldn't keep up.
I can only hold two glasses
at a time unlike you
who can hold eight with your...
tentacle things.
Or you're just a lightweight.
Oxygen mask.
Atmosphere's Earth-like.
Bishop's terraforming the place.
As long as you don't go past
his electrostatic barrier,
you'll be fine.
What if Sara's past the barrier?
Then she's already dead.
Air out there would kill most creatures,
and you don't want to
meet the native ones
who could survive it.
You seem scared.
I'm not scared. I'm smart.
Let's go find my ship.
Then we find Sara.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[LOW GROWL]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
[QUIRKY STRING MUSIC]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, what the?
- That's-a me-a.
- Oh, oh.
Hello there, 12 pizzas for
a Ber... oh, Bernard, uh...
12 pizzas, really?
No fabricator. Gotta plan ahead, right?
[DELIVER MAN STAMMERING]
Really don't think
Gideon's gonna appreciate
being installed on a cathode-ray tube
from 1974, John.
Well, TV rots your brains...
oh, cripes, I'm hungover.
At least you can track down
aliens so we can do our job
until Rory returns with Sara.
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
- Ow!
Um, is anything in this room
by chance flammable?
I need some bloody tea.
♪ ♪
What the hell is this, eh?
The anti-alien security system.
You know those greenies are gonna try
to make a move on us here.
We'll be ready.
Oh, that's who took my tea then, is it?
Zari said they make a good
skincare treatment.
No, I got these roadside
caffeine pills though.
[SIGHS, SNORTS]
Stay off the black tiles!
Unless you like
pumiliotoxin-tipped darts.
Great.
♪ ♪
Zari!
See, names and nomenclature
imply we aren't all the same organism,
living and breathing as one.
So I'm also Behrad Tarazi?
Everyone is, and they aren't.
Oh, bruv.
- [GUITAR CHORD]
- Johnny!
This guitar is sick.
Can I pluck a little "Stairway"?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure, mate.
Yeah, you and your Legend
cohorts can do anything
you like here apparently.
- Ah, thanks, gorg.
- [PLAYING GUITAR]
Grant me the flame of knowledge.
Ooh!
Making progress.
That's great, love. That's really great.
You carry on. Go on.
[GROANS] My head.
- Oh, John-John.
- Oh!
They've turned this place
into a bloody insane asylum.
I know, let's go out and
find you some breakfast.
Black pudding, baked beans,
and bubble and squeak?
- Oh, I love bubble and squeak.
- I know.
♪ ♪
[TRACKER BEEPING]
[SIGHS] The thing's in rough shape,
and it needs a whole new fuel cell.
Damn it.
My mother got me that ship
for my 300th rotation.
Where's Sara?
Judging by the presence of that trooper,
she's already captured.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Time for a chat. Here.
♪ ♪
- [WEAPON WHIRS]
- Drop it!
Where's Sara?
I need backup.
Ava?
Clones.
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
Little help here!
Scared, huh?
Not scared, smart.
[SHIP WHIRS]
Hey! I was gonna steal that.
[ELECTRICITY WARBLES]
Thank you, Captain Sharpe.
It's good to be back.
- [ELECTRIC GUITAR FEEDBACK]
- What is that noise?
Just the sound of everybody
trying to get comfortable here.
So any time anomalies?
What do you got for me, Gideon?
[ELECTRIC STATIC, WARBLING]
Yes, it seems there was
a massacre by a patient
of the alien variety
at Endless Meadows Asylum in 1956.
Perfect.
Anything to keep my mind
off Sara's rescue mission.
Um...
"Um"? What's "um"?
Gideon, you don't "um".
When admitted to the hospital,
the patient gave the name Sara Lance.
[GUITAR CRASHES]
I'm okay!
Don't tell John!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
According to records, the patient flew
into a manic episode during a procedure,
causing the massacre.
Victims were found with sting
marks and exploded hearts.
We never meet the chill aliens.
No. Okay.
So we need to find out what it knows
and why it's using Sara's name.
We should probably also make sure
this thing doesn't kill
a bunch of people.
Right.
You could... and please believe me,
I am not trying to get
you all massacred...
bring it back here.
Mm, speaking purely as a house guest,
is bringing a rampaging
alien back to John's house
something we should run by him first?
No. Definitely not.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You know, sanitariums,
not really my thing.
[SIGHS] Keep that
antenna going, Spooner.
Let me know if you get any weird vibes.
Oh, I got weird vibes.
♪ ♪
Welcome! Checking in your wife?
Hysteria or the blues?
Oh, no, we're here to pick up my sister.
Yes, she used the name Sara Lance.
Oh, yes, of course.
She was in a frenzy when she
arrived and had to be sedated.
But don't worry, she's scheduled
for a very effective electric
shock treatment later today.
Fantastic.
That must be what set her off to kill.
Yeah, I'm getting some weird
alien vibes behind those doors.
♪ ♪
We are just glad we have someone here
who can give us the real story.
She said that she flew
here in a spaceship.
Could you imagine? [CHUCKLES]
Sara! Your brother is here.
Don't be alarmed.
Sometimes she goes by
different names in the moment.
Mary Pickford, Marion Davies.
Her favorite though is Amelia Earhart.
Yes?
♪ ♪
Are we going somewhere?
Could you imagine if
it was the real Amelia?
She'd be 60 by now. What's
her secret, am I right?
Yeah, what is her secret?
♪ ♪
Oh, nice one, love.
You know, I thought I was gonna
go batty in this mad house.
What in the bloody blazes
has happened now?
Astra!
- [GRUNTS]
- Shh!
Who's that woman on my telly?
Is that Amelia Earhart?
It's an alien shaped like Amelia Earhart
that also uses the name Sara Lance,
and she's also totally knocked out
on some pretty gnarly '50s 'ludes.
So we're waiting to see
if she's gonna freak out
and try to murder us when she detoxes.
Did you guys eat all the
gluten-free mushroom?
For the record, Captain,
this plan is stupid.
Look, I say we go right
in there and talk to it.
Yeah, that's right, turned a new leaf.
Maybe I'm not a shoot first,
ask questions kinda gal.
- Huh.
- Nice.
That's great, Spooner.
You're working on yourself.
- I am impressed.
- Yeah.
Why just splat them
when you can find out
their deepest fears
and exploit them?
Hm, Spooner, now I'm impressed.
That was dark.
B, why don't you and Spooner go
and play a little bad cop, Behrad cop,
and see if we get this
Amelia talking, hm?
I like your style, chief.
- What?
- It's gonna be fine.
- Trust me.
- Well, I'm off.
Something about watching
a prisoner interrogated
makes me nostalgic for the
good old days back in Hell.
[SIGHS]
Please, just... please,
please tell us where Sara is.
Are you spying on me?
[SIGHS] There, finally alone.
What the...
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS, GROANING]
[PANTING]
I finally found you!
I searched through every
sewage pipe in the facility.
Wh... oh, eugh.
- You were in the pipes?
- Yeah.
You ever seen an octopus
squeeze through a hole?
My body's like that.
Necrians take great pride
in our scrunching.
Too bad you can't ride the pipes with me
because I discovered where
the fuel cells are kept.
We could fly Kayla's ship out of here.
Gary, get back in that toilet
and get the fuel cell to the ship.
I'll find my own way out.
Can I count on you?
I'm your man.
Alien man.
♪ ♪
Happy trails.
[FLESH SQUELCHING]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Rise and shine, Mia.
Baby steps.
Maybe we can get you
those easy-wake lamps.
- For now, there's tea.
- Tea?
We're taking this nice and easy.
- Where am I?
- You're at Shady Acres.
It's the chillest sanitarium there is.
Okay, Spooner, are you picking up
any alien brainwaves?
No.
I mean, there's something going
on, but it's still too quiet.
I'm thinking she's still
feeling the Quaaludes.
♪ ♪
Oh, don't mind her.
We're just here to ask
you a few questions.
- What kind of questions?
- Easy ones.
Do you ever get the urge to
freak out and attack people?
What she meant to ask is,
why do you use the name Sara Lance?
Sara Lance.
Doesn't ring a bell.
I don't think I like you very much.
♪ ♪
You're not very nice.
May I have some more?
Say, how did you end up
at Endless Meadows?
Wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember I was
soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator Fred
almost done our flight
around the globe.
That does sound like something
the actual Amelia Earhart would say.
Or she's just a very good shapeshifter.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [SNIFFS]
Well, the important thing is,
you're back in one piece, right?
Don't know if I can say
that about my plane back.
She's gotta be talking about the pod.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, find out where its pod is.
Do you remember where you landed it?
Landed it right by my old house,
37 Locust St, Rye, New York.
I love when aliens give exact addresses.
Yeah, okay, keep it calm and friendly.
We're gonna go check out the pod.
All right, there are the cells.
Now all I need is a distraction.
[SPLASHING SOUNDS]
[CHUCKLES] Idiot.
Biggest in the galaxy.
[SNEAKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Intruder by the cells!
[GRUNTS]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Oh!
Hey, stay where you are.
Hey, you're the freak that ate D Squad.
- Put it back.
- I have regrets about that.
I just need one little battery,
and then I'll be...
[LAUGHS]
Damn, those clones are handy.
♪ ♪
We're getting a radiation reading,
but I don't see a crash site.
- It's gotta be around here somewhere.
- _
If it can help us get Amelia to talk,
then maybe we can get an idea
of when Rory and Sara
are coming back, right?
Then do I hear wedding bells?
[WALL GONGS]
- No...
- [VEHICLE BEEPS]
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Amelia Earhart was talking
about the Waverider?
That's impossible.
Sara, are you there?
Rory?
Sara?
Hey, Bishop!
[CLEARS THROAT] Yoo-hoo!
♪ Hey, man, whatcha doing out there? ♪
♪ Wanna come chat, if you dare? ♪
I love it!
Oh, it thrills me to see
you're in a good mood.
I am, and you know what?
I have been thinking.
Uh-oh. About what?
You.
I can't deny the fact that
what you've done here,
- it is astonishing.
- Oh.
And I didn't want to admit it at first,
but it's true.
You are humanity's best hope.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Can I just say, thank you?
For seeing me.
I do, and I want to be a part of it.
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS]
So I'm hoping that we could
just put the past behind us.
Put the past behind us.
I am listening. I am interested.
Well, I can forget about the fact
that you imprisoned me,
if you forget about me
snapping your neck?
- Bygones?
- Bygones!
I couldn't have said it better myself.
I love this new turn of events.
♪ I love it, too ♪
BOTH: ♪ Ooh, hoo, hoo, hoo ♪
[LAUGHS] Tonight.
We'll make a fresh start.
Dinner at 8:00?
Choose something groovy
from the wardrobe.
Of course. Oh!
But it might be kind of hard
to get dressed with these.
Oh.
Yeah, of course. [LAUGHS]
Aw. [LAUGHS]
Oh.
- Oh!
- Whoa... oh!
[LAUGHING]
Oh, you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Me and my navigator Fred
almost done our flight around the globe.
I thought the tea was herbal.
I may have snuck a few
caffeine pills in there.
At least she's not freaking out, right?
I can try to read her mind
more when she settles down.
I blacked out.
Strangest plane I've
ever seen, and then...
You can never know what
a person is really thinking,
even if you open up their brain.
That is technically true, Amelia, yes.
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
Just keep her calm, right?
She's under no threat.
You!
Drop the pretense and start talking.
Whoa, I thought we weren't
supposed to rile up
the residents.
She stole the Waverider!
She's from the planet
where Rory took the ship.
I wouldn't do that.
She's pretty awake now.
[WHIRRING]
[GRUNTS] She's definitely awake.
How the hell did you get our ship?
Tell me where Rory and Sara are, huh?
Where the hell is Sara?
[GROWLS]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
Get tranq'd, greenie.
Weird, she looks like a human again.
I mean, it feels like a human, too.
Like, I know that's an alien,
but I just can't sense it.
Well, she knows where
Mick and Sarah are,
and we don't, so we
need to get it talking.
There is a spell I used on
an uncooperative person
to rip a memory they
didn't wish to share.
I've only done it on humans though.
Okay, fine, but we'll do it
back at the Waverider,
where Gideon can help us
if anything goes wrong.
[BANGS ON TV]
Splendid.
But first, I would like
to enlist the services
of my new apprentice.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[CLEARS THROAT]
What?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
This cannoli...
would make God himself weep.
It is perfection.
Oh, I'm so happy to
hear you say that, sir.
Here you go... oh! Sorry.
- I owe you everything.
- Mmm, sugary carbs.
One of the true pleasures
of having replacement bodies
to spare.
Uh-oh.
Sir, AVA troops from sector 12
have apprehended an intruder.
His name's Mick Rory? He
seems to know Sara Lance.
Apparently, he's very belligerent
and maybe intoxicated.
Terrific.
It's a rescue attempt.
He doesn't know Sara has joined us.
We're gonna have to
take down the barrier.
♪ ♪
- Sir?
- Just for an hour.
That'll let in enough toxic atmosphere
to kill anything living out there...
♪ And we'll be safe and sound in here ♪
But sir, there... sorry.
The troopers are still out in the field.
They've already apprehended
the intruder, so we can just...
How do you know he's alone?
I don't.
I'm not risking it.
Don't worry.
Your clone sisters are well-trained.
They'll survive.
Or, you know, be replaced.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Lower the barrier.
♪ ♪
[BARRIER POWERS DOWN]
Good girl.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Keep moving.
[GROWLS]
Huh? Are they lowering the barrier?
Is this a drill?
No, it's real.
[COUGHS]
Have fun choking to death.
♪ ♪
Now?
Mm-mm.
I am not dying on this planet!
When you mine the depths
of another psyche,
you need to move
swiftly and deliberately.
A little space, John.
If your concentration
wanders, distracted
by some fleeting memory
of an ancient alien world,
then you'll do irreparable
damage to her mind and yours.
The only person distracting
me right now is you.
Apologies, love. Yeah.
I can do this.
Got the greatest magic
tutor in the world.
Seems like a big deal.
Why don't you just
handle it yourself, John?
Yeah, no offense, Astra,
but if this can go badly,
I'd rather the expert do it. John?
No, no danger, none at all.
How else is Astra gonna learn, anyway?
All right, showtime.
Tortured mind with secrets hidden,
show me that which is forbidden.
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
Feels like a real Amelia Earhart memory.
She's setting off on a journey
around the world.
The thrill of defying the odds.
I'm confused.
It's an alien, ain't it?
Well then, shouldn't its memory
be about its home planet?
In the clouds, she's perfectly free.
Then a bright light, unconsciousness.
[GROANING]
She's on an operating
table against her will.
They're experimenting,
altering her.
She's escaped.
She's ostracized. She doesn't know.
She's alone, intensely alone.
She does what she can to survive.
[GRUNTS]
Where's Sara?
Astra, we need to know
if she's seen her.
Listen, this creature,
Amelia, she's exhausted,
- and we should end this right now.
- John, we need to know.
She has a visitor.
Sara Lance.
Did you say Sara?
Is she okay? What is she doing?
- [GROANS]
- I'm trying...
there's some sort of
divide in her memories...
a firewall I can't cross.
Push through, Astra.
Please, we need more.
[GROANS]
I'm trying to push past.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS] Fighting.
Slashing, anger.
Bound, breaking free, anger, hunting.
Hunting!
[GROWLS]
Sever the link. Sever the link!
[SCREAMS AND GROWLS]
♪ ♪
[SHRIEKS]
[SHOUTS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
♪ ♪
Seal it off! Seal it off!
[GROWLS]
[ALIEN GROWLING, OBJECTS CRASHING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Word to the wise:
Gideon's Mezcal is
high grade toilet water.
I never drink it. Mezcal, I mean.
Or toilet water.
You seem down, bad cop. You wanna talk?
Look, you don't wanna
be friends with me.
It'd make killing me that much harder.
So you've figured out my secret plan
to murder all the Legends?
No.
That thing started out human.
Something took it out, and now...
Hey, Spoon, you're
not like Amelia, okay?
We did the scans.
I spoke its language today.
I've never done that before.
My powers have been growing
ever since I joined y'all.
What are you gonna do
if I don't just talk
like them anymore?
What if I start to fight like them?
Sting like them?
Let me tell you a secret.
It's the only way I survive in this job.
Don't think about your past,
and don't think about your future.
You have to live in the now.
I know it seems crazy
to say in a time machine,
but the past and the
future don't really exist.
There's only right here and right now.
Thanks, B.
Oh, and word to the wise:
Gideon's blueberry Kush is...
[GROWLS]
Spooner...
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[ROPE CREAKING]
[GRUNTS]
Suckers.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[GASPS]
[GROWLS AND CHITTERS]
Wait a minute.
You're that thing that ate D squad.
Let's get him!
Stop! He's a hero.
He saved my life.
I'm so sorry about D squad.
No matter how delicious they were.
But I never would have
knowingly eaten an Ava.
You're the most remarkable
women I've ever met.
The Ava I know, she's a great leader,
has amazing hair just like you,
and still has time for her
one true pairing, Sara.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
AVAs lead?
No, AVAs serve.
You don't have to. I served her.
[GASPS]
Oh, she must be a great leader
to have a great servant like you.
Well, I wouldn't say
I'm the best assistant,
but... yeah.
[SIGHS]
Is Astra okay?
Seemed like a lot for a beginner.
She'll recover.
What about you? Are you okay?
John, you know you can talk to me.
[SIGHS] I'm sorry, love.
It's just that, you know, they
nearly destroyed my house.
There's dart holes all over the plaster.
Nate rendered my guitar
practically unplayable.
I'm sure that it's afflicted
by some tone-deaf banshee.
Okay, enough.
I know you wouldn't have
put Astra in that position
if you could've done it yourself.
I may not know magic,
but I do know people.
That's just not even remotely true.
You know, I am in complete
command of all of my power...
Oh, give it up, John. She knows.
Oh, you're not gonna
tell her? Fine, I will.
John owed me, and I was tired
of playing second fiddle,
so I took the lead.
Right.
So everything is perfectly
normal with you?
Everything is perfectly normal with me.
[MURMURING]
See?
And what good would John Constantine be
without magic, eh?
You know, I'd still find use for you.
Well, that is good.
That is more than good.
That is great.
[SIGHS]
Nice one.
Can't have everyone
in this world and below
knowing that I'm disarmed.
Yeah, well, now you really owe me.
[SIGHS]
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[COUGHS AND GASPS]
[GASPING]
[LAUGHS] Sucker.
[MASK WHOOSHES]
[PANTING]
Why?
It's heavy.
A battery missing?
Why are you telling me
and not the inventory AVA?
Everything okay?
♪ Everything is perfect ♪
Oh, wow.
[CHUCKLING] Oh.
I am so glad we can finally
get together like this.
Yeah, me, too.
My AVA assistant has
prepared something truly...
transcendent for us.
Ava, bring on the appies.
She's probably just putting
the final touches on the appies.
Appies, I can't wait.
♪ To you, to you ♪
When I heard about the great Sara Lance,
I thought...
♪ She's gonna be a
tough cookie to crack ♪
But after our little chat today,
I think we're finally on the same page.
The same page.
- Wonderful.
- [GLASSES CLINK]
To new beginnings.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
That's some storm.
Oh, well, your friend Rory arrived.
I had to drop the artificial atmosphere,
killing every humanoid creature
outside of this compound.
Rory's here?
Here on this planet? Yes.
Here in the sense of being
alive and breathing, no.
Honestly, I don't see why it matters.
We're putting our pasts behind us.
Fresh start.
I meant, let's get to know each other,
not let's kill each other's friends.
Oh, well...
look, there seems to have been
some miscommunication on this.
He's dead.
Best thing now is if we don't
let this ruin the appies.
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Why are you fighting me?
You know struggling
against me is useless.
Oh, kill me all you want, Sara Lance.
I'll be back, unlike your friend.
[LAUGHS]
You said you'd help me rescue Sara.
I got you here, didn't I?
Where'd you run off to?
Steal the Waverider.
Always gotta have a backup plan.
Someone got there first.
Backup plan, smart.
Here.
[GRUNTS] Necrians have to be smart.
You humans are stupid.
It was inevitable you'd be the authors
of your own extinction.
What, you don't defend your species?
[THUNDER BOOMS]
No.
They're cowards, liars, cheats, frauds.
They betray you, lock you up.
Sara's different.
That's why I have to find her.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[LOW GROWLING]
[WHIRRING]
Spoons, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Everyone's being weird today.
Spooner.
Spooner...
Come to me.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We could have at least
gone to the entrees
before you desecrated my face.
Why don't you feel more pain?
I modified my pain receptors.
I wasn't born yesterday, you know.
Whoa... actually, technically
I was born yesterday,
but you get my meaning.
So what's your hopeless plan?
I am gonna put an end to you.
For good this time.
[CHUCKLING] Oh, exciting.
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
All this violence
when I was planning on showing
you all this for dessert.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What do you think?
[ZAGURONS GROWLING]
Zagurons. They hide from the light.
They hunt at night.
Come on.
[ZAGURONS GROWLING]
[ZAGURON SCREECHES]
Door's open!
[GRUNTS] It's stuck.
[GRUNTS, COUGHS]
- They outnumber us.
- Then we fight!
Foolish humans and your heroics.
[SCREECHES]
[ZAGURONS SCREECHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[LOCK HISSES]
BOTH: [PANTING]
You're shaking.
I know I've always said
"I'm not scared, I'm smart".
I was definitely scared back there.
Maybe now we should
do something not smart.
Well, no one's ever accused
me of being smart.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Yeah!
- [TENTACLE SQUEAKS]
- Ow, ow, ow!
[SCREECHING]
[GROWLING]
[OBJECTS CRASH]
Welcome, Spooner.
Who are you?
- [WEAPON WHIRS]
- Where do you come from?
Look, if you help us, we can help you.
[SHRIEKS]
Drop your weapon.
Come inside.
[CLICKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GROWLS]
[HISSES IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Are you Amelia Earhart?
I was fused with this human,
but she just made me weak.
[GROWLS]
♪ ♪
You fought Amelia from inside her?
There is a struggle inside you as well.
That is your fear.
[HISSES IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Fear can be a gift.
Sara Lance did not fear me.
Sara L...
[HISSING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Humans are weak.
You killed Sara?
Yes.
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROWLS]
[BOTH HISSING]
[SHRIEKS]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Sara?
What did it tell you?
I'm so sorry.
It killed her.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SNIFFLES]
[EXHALES]
- [GRUNTING]
- [BUTTON CHIRPS]
AVAs!
Still holding on to all that anger.
Not healthy.
How are we gonna start fresh?
I don't start fresh.
Now see, this is what
you got wrong about me.
Every scar on my body is a memory,
a lesson that I learned in blood.
And it's what makes me who I am.
And I don't forget any of it.
Now, we've both faced death.
We've both died before.
The difference is I learned
from my scars, and you?
You've just forgotten yours.
But, Sara,
I don't see any scars on you.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
Oh, there are those scars
on the dead body of the real Sara Lance.
♪ ♪
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -