Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
- I plan on asking Nora to marry me.
- Yes.
You don't understand how
dangerous that Loom is.
Come on, Charlie. We'll
use the Loom to help Astra,
and then I will help you
destroy it forever. Deal?
Someone's trashing
Rebecca Silver online.
Cute, you have a troll.
- This your kid?
- She's your kid too.
Nora belongs in the real world.
I need you to support her.
And she can't do it
on that ship of yours.
Do the right thing, son.
[LIGHT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
- ♪♪
- _
Morning, babe.
Hey.
You okay?
Actually, I was thinking about your dad.
That's romantic.
Thinking about something he said to me.
When I committed my
life to you, I meant it.
So I've been thinking
maybe our life together
isn't on the ship.
Maybe it's time for us to move on
and move out.
Together.
Whoa, hey.
Listen, I wanna build a life
with you wherever we are.
I know, but...
you can't really do
your job on a timeship.
What about the Legends?
They've become my family,
but we can't begin our life together
when I literally have
one foot in the past.
So I think I'll do one
last mission with the team
and say good-bye.
Wow.
We're doing this.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Okay. [LAUGHS]
Mmm.
Yeah, but maybe after
we brush our teeth.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
[GROANS]
Come on! Is she still in there?
Zari, there's a line!
I'm doing my hair.
You can't stop the glam
routine mid-process.
Come on, we talked about this!
Ooh, let me guess. Zari?
- Huh?
- Hey.
What happened to the
sign-up sheet I made?
Oh, Mick burned it in frustration
after Zari's last Korean sheet mask day.
Well, um, I guess now
is as good a time as any
to tell you two that
Nora and I have some big news...
We talking big news?
'Cause, guys, I got a whopper.
I told John we'd help
him find the Loom of Fate.
Nuh-uh. You know the rules.
No MacGuffin talk until
after I've finished my coffee.
Yeah, and besides,
you guys were about to
- make a big announcement?
- Yes.
[GROANS] Is it time for
morning announcements?
'Cause I need you all to
know, I have to go so badly.
If my sister ever leaves the bathroom!
- Oh, B!
- Come on.
Hey, bro,
let's not pretend like
you don't take this long
- with your hair.
- Get in line.
Bathroom's are also for other things.
And in other announcements...
She still in there?
I would be too if I
had all that damn hair.
Okay, well, uh, this
is the perfect time,
now that we're all here,
to let you know that Nora and I...
- You're moving out.
- Hmm?
- How'd you know that?
- Well, you got married.
Next logical step in a relationship...
and by the way,
I heard you two going at it
like jackrabbits last night.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, at least someone's getting it.
Oh, my God.
Look, after one final mission,
Nora and I will be leaving.
- Aw, I'm gonna miss you, man.
- Wait, for real?
- Seriously?
- Congrats!
I mean, we always knew
this day would come,
but I never thought it would be so soon.
How are you gonna tell Nate?
- Tell Nate what?
- What?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Hmm?
- Uh...
- [WHEEZES]
The wait for the bathroom
is upwards of 30 minutes.
- Can you believe it?
- Hey, take it easy.
At least I get to wait in
line with the happy new couple.
Nora, welcome to your
new morning routine.
- Uptown!
- [CHUCKLES]
- [MECHANICAL DOOR OPENS]
- Thank God.
Good morning, good
morning, good morning.
Damn, she looks good.
Glam complete. [GIGGLES]
You guys could really
work on your hygiene.
It's 7:15.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Mick!
There you are.
Mona.
- Consent to hug you?
- [GRUNTS]
I'll take that as a no.
So what's new?
Any torrid affairs,
flourishing romances,
lovers left behind?
Rebecca Silver could always
use fresh inspiration.
- No.
- Anyway,
had to be here for
Nora's first book club
as a married woman.
And speaking of books,
I could use your advice.
Rebecca Silver has been
besieged by a troll.
Forget about her... I mean... him.
Whoever.
Well, I tried that and it didn't stop.
- I was thinking of reaching out.
- Don't.
It's just gonna make you feel worse.
Well, I think it's a cry for help.
Maybe someone just
needs to show them love.
But it's got nothing to do with love!
♪♪
[SPUTTERING PERCUSSIVELY]
Hey.
I was packing up my stuff in the lab,
and I noticed that
Marie Antoinette is gone,
and the jars of Rasputin are empty.
Astra must have recalled
their souls to Hell.
Damien said something
about eternal torture.
So, um, packing huh?
- You talked to Nate yet?
- Ha.
When I saw his face back there,
I-I just couldn't.
He was so excited about
us living together.
[SIGHS] I just have to wait for
the perfect moment, you know?
Look, I say just get it over with,
and then you guys can enjoy
your last hoorah together.
Yeah.
Saying good-bye to Nate's
my biggest mission yet.
- Mm-hmm.
- [CHUCKLES]
I did go to the moon
once, so second biggest.
[CLEARS THROAT]
The Loom of Fate.
Eons ago, I tossed it
through space and time
because it was too dangerous,
but now for all my sins,
we're gonna piece it
back together again.
And finally put an end
to our encore problem.
By rewriting Astra's life and
setting her on the right path.
Yes, speaking of life changes...
[TENSE MUSIC]
Must be a life-changing
experience for you, Charlie,
to know that the Loom
is back on our Earth.
Huh? Charlie?
Yeah, it is.
But there's only one piece
who's spot I'm sure of.
I gave it to a close mate
of mine for safekeeping.
All right, so we go back to
right after you dropped it off.
- That's our move.
- And, uh, speaking of moves...
♪♪
Let's get a move on it!
[CHUCKLES BREATHLESSLY]
Where are we headed, Charlie?
Well, the last place I
left it was in London 1594.
- Gideon, set a course.
- Affirmative, Captain.
And speaking of setting a new course...
Of course, she means, Sara,
please give us one of those
terrific period-specific send-offs.
Fine.
[BAD ENGLISH ACCENT]
Enjoy the jolly old London,
ya blokes!
♪♪
That was... that was bad.
And frankly offensive.
- [EXCITING MUSIC]
- _
[JAUNTY TUNE PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, it warms my cockles
to know that Londoners
haven't changed a bit.
Let's find this bloody
Loom piece, shall we?
Well, I disguised the pieces as rings.
And this one I gave to
a close mate of mine,
and if I know him, he'll be here.
Wasn't a day he didn't
stop by for a pint.
Why stop at one pint?
Hmm, well, I found our guy.
Will the Quill.
You didn't tell me you were friends
with the real William Shakespeare.
Well, I didn't wanna name drop.
Pardon the intrusion, squire.
We have the knowledge that
you came into possession
of a particular ring
some several days past.
I know not of what you
speak, good constables.
And why should anyone hand me a ring?
Do I appear as a jeweler to thine eyes?
[ENGLISH ACCENT] It's a pity!
[ACCENT FADING] Because
that ring was stolen
from the Duke...
And he wants it back!
And if it were to be discovered
that someone had lied
about its whereabouts...
Let's just say heads would roll.
Y-yes, the ring!
The ring, now I remember it well.
Would that I could yield it for you,
but I just sold that very
ring of which you speak.
What? You sold it
already, you lousy git?
It was by necessity.
See, a stubborn case of writer's block
is preventing me from finding the ending
to my new play, "Romeo and Juliet".
Sounds like an instant classic.
My producer, Philip Henslowe,
has threatened to remove me
of hands by way of
sword if I can't finish.
Thus I gave him the ring
in exchange for more time.
If I can't bring my story to a close,
my career is over.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So much for quick and easy.
♪♪
Discussing "Romeo and Juliet"
- in Elizabethan England.
- Mm.
Eva, you needed me?
Sorry, is this an intervention?
No, no, no, no, no.
So since you're a member of the team,
we wanted to invite you to book club!
- [CHEERING]
- Oh, that is very sweet,
but I actually have a
lot on my plate right now,
so I don't really have
time to talk about books.
The thing about book club is, uh,
we don't really talk about books.
- Mm-mm.
- Because book club is magic.
What she means is, book club is a place
where you can hang out with your friends
and talk about your problems.
- And eat tiny crackers.
- And drink.
Well, according to the
iron monger at the bar,
for 20 shillings I can get
a bottle of wine and a strumpet.
Also, Henslowe and
his goons just arrived
and they're right over there.
Yeah, I can see the ring on his hand.
I doubt he's gonna give it up so easily.
Bah, it's simple.
You distract the goons,
and I'll punch the producer in the face.
Anyone got 20 shillings?
Wh-whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This mission has to be epic. Okay?
By which I mean, extremely well
and elaborately coordinated.
Ray's right.
♪♪
And I have the perfect plan.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
We have the element of
surprise on our side,
so I say aerial attack.
I'll rappel down while
he's totally distracted.
Love it, and then I'll
rappel next to Nate.
And then we'll high-five
mid-air, and it will be epic.
And then...
wait, Ray, are you crying?
It's just that, I love this plan.
Oh, yeah... hey, man, I get it.
I'm a little choked
up. It's a great plan.
And then we'll land behind Henslowe
to his total surprise!
- [LAUGHS]
- [GRUNTING]
We'll subdue him, and
I'll grab the ring.
Ah, got it!
Then, Behrad will air
blast Henslowe's thugs
with a killer gust of wind!
[APPLAUSE]
Dude, I don't dance like that.
And then Constantine will
emerge from the shadows,
- per uzh...
- Oh, yambo bambo mumbo jumbo!
Spout some nonsense and cast
a spell on any troublemakers
to make them think that they're animals.
[INDISTINCT ANIMAL NOISES]
And then we go to Star
City, we pick up Wild Dog,
- and we...
- Oy!
Story time's over. I got it.
- How the hell did you do that?
- Well, I just nicked it off
his hand while you
lot were prattling on.
Does that mean the mission is over?
Which is why we should, uh,
get moving, find that
next Loom piece, yeah?
It's time for you to go, Haircut.
Wait, where are you going?
♪♪
On... on my honeymoon.
Nora and I are going
to Bermuda... Bahamas.
Shut up!
You're doing the whole Kokomo package?
Bro, you're gonna be gone for weeks.
I didn't even throw you
a proper bachelor party.
The mission isn't officially over
until we bring the ring
back to the ship, right?
Which is where we should
be going right now.
- Come on, let's go.
- Ray!
You're not going anywhere.
Grab your doublet and your ruffs,
because this bachelor party is gonna be
an Elizabethan extravaganza!
You know the other
thing about book club is,
it can help you figure out
where your true path
is supposed to be...
- Oh, so this is a cult.
- No. No, no, no.
We don't... we don't
use certain C-words.
- Cult, clone...
- I would know,
because book club helped me move forward
after my time in a real cult.
Look, I get your reservations.
The last "club" I joined
programmed me to be an assassin.
But book club is helping
me be a real person.
And I killed a federal agent.
I meant to lead with,
"I'm a Kaupe... it's
like a Hawaiian Werewolf".
Book club helped me cope with that.
That's also a lot. Okay.
So what do you think, Zari?
Can book club help you?
♪♪
You know what? Enough about me.
This is Nora's last book club.
Shouldn't we be throwing her
a belated bachelorette bash?
- [GASPS]
- Yes!
- That's what I'm saying!
Right?
Captain, I have an
incoming transmission.
- Let's get firemen.
- It's the boys!
- Shh!
- What?
Hey, Sara, sorry the
mission's taking so long.
It's just a dog took the ring,
and it turned out to be the,
um, you know, the Queen's dog.
But we got it covered. We're good.
Well, great. Then, uh, keep us posted
- and be safe.
- Copy that.
Fill 'em up! She bought it.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
All right, the boys
are gonna be a while,
so pop that champagne and fill her up!
- [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- Whoo!
I notice John Constantine
is walking topside.
Plans changed. I needed leverage.
John is working for me now.
He promised me something.
What exactly is John
Constantine doing for you,
Astra?
He said something about
some powerful artifact.
Whatever it is, that
can bring my mom back.
[EERIE MUSIC]
I'd have a family again.
♪♪
So...
John makes this grand promise
to bring your family back,
and you quickly forget that
I am the one who found you
roaming the streets as a child.
I'm the one who pulled
you from the gutter.
- I raised you...
- No, no, I...
- I haven't forgotten.
- Then did it occur to you
if John brings your mother back,
I will no longer be in your life?
You know I don't want that.
You are my family.
If there's a way to
discover what he's after
maybe you could get it for yourself.
♪♪
I know a way we can find out.
This is an exspiravit ritual.
It will allow you to see the other side.
You'll be among those on Earth
able to spy on John like a ghost.
You sure you're ready?
♪♪
Fill it up.
Go on, Ray, say a few words.
- Speech, speech!
- Speech, speech.
Um, I just wanna say,
thank you for this, uh, bachelor party
you're the best friend a guy could have.
No, no.
- Because you are!
- Ah!
- You are!
Is there anything else
you'd like to say, Ray?
Mm-mm.
Anyone have any big life
changes that they wanna reveal?
♪♪
- I got a kid.
- Wha...
Been trying to ignore her, but I...
can't stop thinking about her.
Aw. It's a good thing, Mick.
It's called love.
Wow, let's keep this share-fest going.
All right? Who's next?
[UPBEAT MUSIC, INDISTINCT CHEERING]
- Whoo!
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
♪ First base, second
base, all the way home ♪
♪ I can't go kissing alone ♪
♪ First base, second
base, all the way home ♪
♪ I can't go kissing alone ♪
♪ First base, second
base, all the way home ♪
♪ I can't go kissing alone ♪
♪♪
Hey, we're a regular old,
uh, Fellowship of the Ring.
Here's again to the first
piece of the Loom of Destiny!
Here. Yeah, the Spear of Fate.
Do you remember the totems?
- Mmm.
- The totems?
I met Elvis.
I mean, it's the Loom of Fate.
All right, once we
piece it all together,
we'll rewrite Astra's life.
And I'm telling you all,
this is gonna be worth it.
[EERIE WHOOSHING]
Who's there?
♪♪
Charge thee, speak.
[EERIE WHOOSHING]
Hey!
Watch it, you pigeon-livered worm!
[CHUCKLES] Piss off.
- You want some?
- [EXCITING MUSIC]
Hey, leave him alone!
Hey! [GRUNTING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
What the devil?
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
Ack! Ugh!
- Oh!
- Yes, B!
That was it!
Speak to me!
What plane of Hell did you surface?
Well, whoever you are,
I'm afraid I must do my duty
and send you back.
Fuge!
[EERIE DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Astra!
Astra?
Astra? Oh, no.
♪♪
- [LAUGHTER]
- Yeah, buddy!
Ah, time for the Atom-eth,
to save-eth the day-eth.
[BEEPING]
♪♪
- Deactivate suit!
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- Sorry!
- Watch out!
Ow!
[GRUNTS]
Code X-94. X-94!
Doctor Palmer, voice authenticated.
- [METAL CLANGS]
- [GROANS]
- Yes!
- [LAUGHS]
♪♪
[SHRIEKS]
Party's over!
Yeah, Jocko's right about that one.
Zounds!
Yeah, we better mind-wipe that dude.
I got it. [CLEARS THROAT]
♪ Doot doot doodly, doot doot doot ♪
Wait, no, no, it's
pointing the wrong way.
- I got it.
- [THUNDEROUS ZAP]
Well, another Legends mission perfect.
Let's head back to the ship.
♪♪
- [CLATTERING]
- Sorry.
- No, you!
- I can't, I can't...
- I can't, I can't.
- Yes!
[UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC]
Hey!
- Turn off the music!
- [POWERING DOWN]
Look at this. Take a look at that.
What is that?
Did something go wrong with the mission?
- Is that Mick?
- What's "Romeo v. Juliet?"
Shakespeare is writing superhero plays?
Oh, that's gonna be a problem.
♪♪
I cannot believe you guys!
I put you in charge of the
mission, and you lied to me.
- You... you lied to me.
- Ow.
So why... so why, you could just...
you could go party?
That's what we should've done.
We should've waited for
Ray and Nora to come back
from their honeymoon
and throw one big party.
- My bad, buddy.
- Yeah, and guess what?
We're well on our way
to assembling the Loom.
Uh, but you're right, Sara.
I really should've insisted
that we come back to the ship sooner.
- Yeah.
- "Tybalt draws his sword
on Mercutio, but
Mercutio turns to steel!"
- What?
- Well, thanks to you guys
and your stupid party,
this mission's not over.
"With another swing,
Tybalt stabs Mercutio.
'I am hurt.'"
Why didn't he just steel up again?
Stupid Mercutio.
This is the least of our worries.
We need to get out
there and fix hiss-ory.
- What's that?
- His-story.
History... time! We gotta fix time.
- Une question, Le Capitaine.
- What?
- Are you sloshed?
- [LAUGHS]
Follow up question: why is
there glitter on your face?
Uh, looks like your tachyon
scrubber needs to be replaced.
[SCOFFS] Whatever that means.
It's uh...
just see this fine
gentleman out, thank you.
- With pleasure.
- All right, let's go,
sexy firefighter. Go on and get.
Ray.
Can I talk to you please?
Yeah, I'm... mm-hmm.
[SIGHS]
All right, Ray, what's up?
Why haven't you told
Nate that you're leaving?
Because he's my best friend,
and the moment I tell him,
then this all becomes real.
And, um, I know it's my
choice, it's my decision
but I don't... I don't know
if I'm really ready for it.
You remember when we
first moved on the ship?
We left our entire lives behind us,
we had no idea what to expect,
but because we embraced the change...
We made history.
Sure did.
Who would've thought that
we would still be here?
And that we'd be
saying good-bye already.
I'll miss you, Captain Lance.
♪♪
Don't make me cry.
I'm gonna miss you too, Ray.
A lot.
Come here.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Let's hope the actors
aren't off book yet.
You have to talk Shakespeare
out of his superhero play
and make sure you get those scripts.
Back, foul villain!
Whoosh!
Take to the skies, brethren!
For tonight there will be justice!
Behold!
What worthy hero faces me?
My face is silver,
fists like thunder strikes!
We must collect the
gems to save the world!
While learning how to
work more as a team.
- Yes.
- Come hither.
We have much to discuss.
Wow, and it's still
in iambic pentameter.
Okay, you guys take care of
the cast and get the scripts.
- I'll talk to Shakespeare.
- Copy.
Pew, pew, pew! Pew, pew, pew!
Take to the skies, brethren!
I can't believe we
have to destroy these.
This show has potential.
♪♪
[CLEARS THROAT] Hear ye, hear ye.
So there's been a change of plans.
You guys have been
replaced by "Riverdale".
- William Shakespeare?
- Bother me not.
I'm making amendments to my script.
I must elucidate more clearly
what the steel man's takeaway
lesson is from the story.
Oh, well I'm actually
here to speak to you
about your new play.
I know you.
You're one of the constables
that asked for the ring.
And you caused such a glorious
row with Henslowe and his men.
Yes, and now I'm here to say
that you cannot put on the show.
But I finally struck inspiration.
Look, I have a plan.
Romeo and Juliet will form a team,
and I will henceforth
introduce the allies
Hamlet, Viola, and Puck,
who will join forces to
face Richard the Third!
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Now I understand
why you've written this
new version of the play.
You don't want Romeo and
Juliet's story to end.
Exactly!
I love the characters,
so why say good-bye?
Well, if you truly love the characters,
don't they deserve a great ending?
[SOMBER LUTE MUSIC]
♪♪
I have always known how
to finish their story.
If I let them go, I'm
unsure what happens next.
♪♪
I understand, but...
endings are necessary for growth.
No matter how... painful they may be.
You speak quite wisely.
I'm speaking from experience.
I find myself in a similar situation.
When I'm done here,
I am leaving my team
for a new adventure,
and ending our journey
has proven more
heartbreaking than I can bear.
And while I can't
imagine saying good-bye,
I know that I must.
Very well.
I shall do what is needed
for my beloved characters.
Give Romeo and Juliet an
ending no one will forget.
♪♪
All righty. [SIGHS]
If we did our job right,
this cover should change
back to "Romeo and Juliet"
any second.
I know you're leaving, Ray.
Yeah, uh, to my honeymoon.
Oh, would you just knock it off?
I know you're leaving the team.
[SIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Nate, I'm sorry.
I was gonna tell you sooner, I swear,
but I just... I didn't
know how to do it.
Maybe if you had the
balls to say it sooner,
maybe I could've done something like
make us a last mission playlist
or get us matching t-shirts.
That would've been amazing.
But I was waiting for
some perfect moment
which doesn't exist,
because I didn't want to upset you.
Of course I'm upset!
Today could've been awesome.
It could've been amazing,
but now it's just...
♪♪
It's just over.
Eventually,
everything has to change.
Yeah, I know everything
changes eventually.
I didn't think it'd be so soon,
and I didn't think I'd
be the last one to know.
Attention Legends,
there is no record of the
play "Romeo and Juliet"
in the timeline, which means...
Shakespeare didn't put on the play yet.
The final mission isn't completed.
We can still go back
and fix history together!
♪♪
The team has it, Ray.
You should go.
You're right.
Things change eventually,
so why not start now?
Nate.
Nate!
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Billy Shakes, what's happening?
Spare me your whimsical turns of phrase.
Barkeep!
My draught has gone
hollow. I'll have another.
Will, what happened to the play?
Henslowe withdrew the
monies and shut us down.
In his mind's eye, he
thinks I stole back his ring.
Now I have no theater, no actors,
and so, no career.
Well, tell us where Henslowe is.
- We'll help you.
- Just leave me be.
I've seen your help in
action, and it is anything but.
So you're just gonna give up?
It's like the tall one said,
all things must cease.
And this is the end
of William Shakespeare.
- He is so dramatic.
- Yeah.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪♪
Whoa.
- Packed already?
- Yeah.
I figured, why wait?
Well, there's no rush.
You know we can stick
around until they get back.
I think we've stuck
around too long already.
♪♪
What is going on?
Well, we ruined the
Western literary canon,
and Shakespeare hates us,
so here's to Legends of Tomorrow,
who singlehandedly destroyed
storytelling as we know it.
Sorry, so that's it?
First you pick a fight with Ray,
and now you admit defeat?
Are you just trying to prove
that everything's as
miserable as how you feel?
I don't wanna talk about Ray.
Look, Nate, I get it.
I'm afraid of losing Ray too.
Honestly, I don't know
what we're gonna do
without his stupid
optimism and blind faith
and ridiculous plans
that somehow always work.
I know what we need to do.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Gideon, tell the team
it's all hands on deck
here at the tavern.
And fabricate some codpieces.
The show must go on.
♪♪
All right, it's almost showtime.
Remember, Gideon is going
to be feeding you your lines.
Yeah, no pressure, it's
not like we're rebooting
Shakespeare's career or anything.
It really is book club's
greatest mission yet.
I can't believe I let you
guys rope me into this one.
Look, if you wanna find the Loom,
you gotta do things our way.
You this is gonna work, Captain?
Honestly, no, but Ray would.
"My bounty is as boundless as the sea".
- That's crap!
- Just say the words
because you are on!
[GRUNTS]
[HARPSICHORD MUSIC]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Listen up, you uncultured jerks.
[SIGHS]
Two households, both alike in dignity,
in fair Verona, where we lay our scene.
Words, words.
- Where civil blood...
- Words, words...
t-those are my words!
A pair of star struck
lovers take their life.
Just enjoy the show, all right?
Looks like the audience is.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Clubs, bills, and partisans.
Strike! Beat them down!
Down with the Capulets!
Down with the Montagues!
- [GRUNTS]
- [CROWD GASPS]
- What noise is this?
- [GASPS]
Give me my long sword, ho!
A sword? A crutch.
Why call you for a sword?
My sword, I say!
Old Montague has come,
and flourishes his blade in spite of me.
- Thou villain Capulet!
- [GASPS]
Hold me not, let me go.
Thou shalt not stir
one foot to seek a foe.
[GRUNTS]
[EXCITED MURMURING]
[DRAMATIC PERCUSSIVE MUSIC]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Fight.
♪♪
Exciting.
What shall I swear by?
- If my heart's dear love...
- Do not swear.
Although I take joy in thee,
I take no joy of this contract tonight.
It's too rash, too
unadvised, too sudden.
Too rash, too unadvised, too sudden.
♪♪
Too like the lightning,
which doth cease to be.
Ere one could say it lightens.
Sweet, good night.
[AUDIENCE MURMURING]
O, wilt thou leave me so unsatisfied?
- [SHRIEKS]
- What's wrong?
I mean, other than
the fact that this role
clearly should've gone to a woman.
I just need a second, okay?
Acting is hard.
I know it can be hard to face
that your time with
someone is coming to an end.
- [SIGHS]
- Sometimes it's easier
to just send them away
before it hits you,
like Juliet's doing here.
She got all that?
She was meant for book club.
Change is hard, but it
can also be beautiful.
It can be both.
♪♪
You know, it's not too late
to say good-bye to your friend.
♪♪
What about Juliet?
I have it handled.
♪♪
Among my many talents,
I'm a classically trained actor.
Huh.
♪♪
Gidget, I'm off book.
This bud of love, by
summer's ripening breath,
may prove a beauteous
flower when next we meet.
Is that a man?
- Good night.
- Does it matter?
Good night.
As sweet repose and
rest come to thy heart
- as that within my breast.
- Excuse me, excuse me.
O, wilt thou leave me so unsatisfied?
♪♪
All right, Gideon,
it's time for me to go.
Will I ever see you again?
I hope so.
Thank you for everything.
And, uh, take care
of the Legends for me.
Safe travels, Dr. Palmer.
♪♪
Ray, are you there? Can you hear me?
Ray!
You. Again.
[MENACING MUSIC]
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
Ray!
What satisfaction
canst thou have tonight?
The exchange of thy love's
faithful vows for mine.
I gave thee mine before
thou didst request it.
And yet I would it were to give again.
Wouldst thou withdraw it?
For what purpose, love?
♪♪
But to be frank and give it thee again.
And yet I wish but for the thing I have.
[SIGHS]
My bounty is as boundless as the sea.
My love as deep.
The more I give to
thee, the more I have,
for both are infinite.
♪♪
I hear some noise within.
Dear love, adieu.
[AUDIENCE CHATTER]
Ray! Ray, Ray.
♪♪
I missed him.
He's gone.
Nate. Nate, I'm still here, buddy.
Psst. Romeo, Romeo.
Ray, I am so sorry I lashed out at you.
It was just a lot to process,
and I didn't know how to say it.
The thing is, I'm just really sad.
♪♪
But I'm really happy for you guys.
I'm sorry that you found
out the way you did.
And I just... I wish there was some way
that everything and nothing
could change all at once.
♪♪
This sucks.
But I love you.
This totally sucks.
But I love you too.
♪♪
Good night. Good night.
Parting is such sweet sorrow,
that I shall say "good
night" till it be morrow.
♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Zari was pretty good at Juliet.
I mean, not as good as you, but...
♪♪
You okay?
It's a weird thing with friendship.
Starts because you need each other,
and then if you do it right
and help each other grow,
you need each other less.
I guess change is the whole point.
Well, if you, um, you
ever need a bro hug...
[CLICKS TONGUE] I'm your gal.
[CHUCKLES]
Bring it in.
♪♪
Sorry.
It's okay.
Ray was terrible at
bro hugs at first too.
- Yeah.
- But you're really terrible.
- Such a dick.
- Aww.
Why are you so strong?
On a Shakespeare kick?
Didn't care much for those
Italian kids, but this guy...
this guy's a hero.
You know King Lear is a tragic figure
who's stubbornness
and fear of the future
leads to his own misery?
Sounds like someone I can get behind.
You should talk to your daughter.
[LOUD THUMP]
There's no secrets in book club.
♪♪
I'm not hiding from her.
- I'm protecting her.
- From what?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Nurturing fathers
don't run in my family.
But I'm better off because
I had you in my life.
She will be too.
[SIGHS]
It's good to see you.
Consent to hug you?
- [GRUNTS]
- Gonna take that as a yes.
♪♪
So this is part of the Loom of Fate?
Well, I had to disguise the bit
so that mere mortals like you
wouldn't burst into flames
when you looked at it.
Well, that is certainly very
thoughtful of you, Charlie.
Not so fast.
This is too powerful, John,
and honestly, you're too close to it.
This is my mission, Sara.
And this is my ship.
- So what's the plan?
- This is just the beginning.
But with that, we can
find the other pieces.
Mm-hmm. Hmm...
[GASPS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪♪
Oh, I was so worried.
I wasn't sure when you'd wake up.
What did you see?
I-I was in a bar.
And people were laughing, and...
and John was there with his friends.
Did he say what he was looking for?
He's looking for the Loom of Fate.
♪♪
The Loom?
- Oh, so you've heard of it?
- Of course.
The Loom of Fate
is one of the most
powerful tools in existence.
It could completely rewrite your life.
Are you sure you want
to trust that power
in someone else's hands?
Especially John Constantine's?
♪♪
[SIGHS]
- Can't sleep either, huh?
- Yeah.
You know, we all spend
time off the ship,
but people usually
don't feel this, uh...
BOTH: Gone.
How early does a guy have to get up
to get some alone time?
Ray's green juice.
You feeling sentimental, too, huh, Mick?
The juice was taking up
all the room in the fridge.
Now shut up, Pretty.
Missing someone after they're gone
almost makes them more present.
Heard you get up, babe.
- I was awake anyway.
- Hi, babe.
I had a feeling other
people would be up.
Oh, gross. Is that Ray's green juice?
- Yep.
- Give me some.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
To Ray,
who taught me how to be a better friend
by being a better
friend than I deserved.
- [CHUCKLES]
- He told me that
if you're dumb enough to
expect good from the world,
the world might just live
up to your expectations.
And who showed us that
there's never a problem so big
it can't be solved with a smile.
To the big guy.
- To Ray.
To Ray.
I'm really gonna miss him.
- [GAGS]
- [COUGHS]
- Tastes like death.
- It's delicious.
[GURGLING]
Do you think Ray left that
bathroom sign-up sheet?
♪♪
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!