[PINEAPPLE'S "FANTASY"]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ Skyline, danger zone,
all the lights are on ♪
♪ You hear the sonic boom,
I'm already gone ♪
♪ I fly blind like a drone,
I'm here to spy ♪
Look out, world.
I have arrived.
♪ ♪
- 25 quid.
- Oh.
I've got two.
That'll get you this.
[CASH REGISTER CHIMES]
No money, no ride.
Just get me to my house.
There's money there, and I can...
Out!
♪ ♪
Can I ask what your business is?
I reckon you're selling something
if you came all the way out this way.
I came from over there.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm glad the owner
finally got a housekeeper.
If you've got reasonable rates,
me and the missus could use
a hand at ours.
I've a collection of Bethany fixtures,
which need constant dusting.
What's your name, sir?
Robert Truss from number 220.
[BARKS]
Well, Robert,
I'm not the help.
I live here.
We're neighbors.
- [BARKS]
- [LAUGHS]
That's a good one, yes.
Oh, you're serious.
But that can't be. I mean, you living
in an upstanding community such as this.
You don't know anything about me.
I know the kind of people
who do live here,
and you are not the type.
Oh, really?
So what type am I, exactly?
What about me doesn't fit in
with you upstanding residents?
- Is it because I'm tall?
- Ah.
Or female? Or Black?
You stay back.
And I'll not be threatened this way
in my own neighborhood.
And I won't be treated
like a criminal in mine.
[BARKS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Oh, there you are.
I have got a list of things
I need you to fix,
starting with punishing
your racist neighbor.
You'll have to be more specific, love,
and I'm on the clock.
I got a bloke in an alien costume
with another alien inside him,
and I gotta prep my gut
for a purging spell.
♪ ♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[PORTAL BUZZING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
♪ ♪
[EXCITING MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- [SCREAMING]
- [SIGHS]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SIGHS] Dammit.
[PORTAL BUZZING]
Please get me out
of this meat-fumed atrocity.
Oh, what do you mean?
You mean you don't want
any special sauce
- with that big, bad burger?
- Hold it right there.
- Oh, hi.
- Oh, hey, girl.
Hey.
John, where's your washing machine?
I don't need one.
You see, my clothes are bewitched
to clean themselves
whenever they see fit.
Mm, your clothes have thoughts.
- Yeah.
- That's kind of hot.
Creepy.
I also need the Internet.
Yes, the Internet.
I will get right to that.
I will whip up a spell in no time.
I just... I've got to get...
- John.
- Something with... yeah.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ ♪
♪ Fire is coming ♪
[SCREAMING]
You and your empty promises, John.
Yes, I am a U.S. citizen,
but my mother was from Northumberland,
so I'm practically a local.
My background check says I'm only 15?
Okay, yeah, that's because
I spent my adolescence
in another dimension where
time works differently, so...
[LINE CLICKS]
Hello?
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ ♪
- [ALARM BLARING]
- [GROANS]
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ ♪
[PIPES RUMBLE]
Oh! [WHIMPERING]
- [PORTAL BUZZING]
- Oh, God.
Oh, good, you're back. I need you to fix
the kitchen sink and...
what are you wearing?
Have you seen my emergency
pack of smokes?
I knew that I left them here somewhere.
No... I still need the Internet,
and a job, and food apparently.
Living topside takes work, love.
But you do everything with magic.
Which is work!
Bollocks!
[CHANTS IN JAPANESE]
There you are.
Thank you.
How about a spell to fix the sink?
Oh, come on, you have got
to be kidding me!
You try getting a job
when your last employers were
the Triumvirate of Hell.
Just give me my power back,
or I will have your blood drained
to fill my swimming pool.
[GROANS]
I miss my blood pool.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Sterling silver.
♪ ♪
European enamelware.
Hundred-year-old designer luggage, okay.
Huh, Bethany table lamp.
♪ ♪
_
Sorry I never learned
to read music like you, Mom.
My, how the mighty have fallen.
Hello?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Who said that?
Back right corner, my lady.
Further right. Almost there.
And now you've got it.
♪ ♪
Who are you?
Aleister Crowley, at your service.
But enough about me.
My concern is for you, dear girl.
What's become
of the notorious Astra Logue?
You know who I am?
Of course I do.
You're the woman who clawed her way
to the tops of Tartarus.
Looks like you've discovered
the hard way
that you can't take that power
with you, eh?
In some ways, it's easier in Hell
because there aren't any rules,
but here, there are so many,
and following them isn't
getting me anywhere.
It's... humiliating.
A powerful queen has become
a helpless princess,
and Hell is lesser for it.
Look who's talking.
A renowned warlock, Satanist,
and alien enthusiast
trapped in a portrait.
[LAUGHS] Touché, my lady.
That scoundrel John Constantine
summoned me from Hell
to learn my secrets,
and when he was done with me,
he banished me
into this blasted painting and tossed me
into this rubbish heap.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
John made me promise to give living
like a normal human being an honest go,
but he did not prepare me for
how hard it would be up here.
This house is falling apart.
I am completely broke.
I don't know how to fix any of it.
Master Constantine has
neutered us both, hasn't he?
But your predicament is
easily rectified.
A simple set of spells will
give you the power
to change things around here.
I can teach you how, if you'd like.
You're offering to teach me magic?
It would be my greatest honor.
[TENSE MUSIC]
The infamous Sara Lance.
I've been waiting a long time for you.
So you must be the all-powerful
space lord behind all this.
When you put it that way,
I sound like a super-villain.
Such a bummer. Not at all my speed.
- Oh!
- [FUNKY MUSIC]
[CHUCKLES]
[VOICE DISTORTING]
But I have been waiting
a long time to meet you, Sara.
Is it okay if I call you that?
I feel like I've known you
my whole life,
like we're old friends, simpatico,
dancing to the same drummer.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Bishop,
but that means literally nothing, right?
You've never heard of me.
There's no context for that
label whatsoever, but...
♪ who am I to you? ♪
- [GRUNTS]
- Ooh.
You were stung by a Zaguron.
Its venom has almost reached your heart.
You've got about ten seconds
before it's lights out.
You'll have come all this way
for nothing,
and you'll die with no answers
as to why.
So... ♪ Who am I to you? ♪
I'm the man who's going
to save all of humanity,
starting with you and this antidote.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Five, four, three...
♪ To you, to you ♪
♪ And to this great big universe ♪
[ECHOING] ♪ We're spiraling through ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, no, no, don't struggle.
Your muscles need time to adjust.
What is this stuff?
Medicine to vitalize your organs.
The transition can be tough.
Bishop saved your life.
I don't want anything from him.
Get me out of here.
How's our patient
this morning, Nurse Ava?
Pissed off and calculating
the different ways
she can kill you.
- Back to her old self.
- Perfect.
I've got the presentation
all ready for her.
Let me go.
But you haven't even seen the pitch yet.
A/V Ava worked on it for days.
She'll be crushed if you don't give it
even just a little peek.
[SWEEPING MUSIC]
Our planet was perfection.
It had everything
carbon-based life-forms needed
to coexist in harmony with nature
and each other,
but humanity would not be satisfied.
Human greed destroyed Earth
and all who lived there.
Everyone perished,
except for one man...
[ANGELIC MUSIC]
Me.
As a pioneer in bio-engineering,
the founder of A.V.A. Corp.,
and the designer-creator
of the AVA clone,
I alone have the knowledge
and means to restart humanity
in the stars!
- [FIREWORKS WHISTLE]
- [NOISEMAKER TRUMPETS]
The problem with Earth wasn't
its finite resources.
The problem was man,
which is why I am creating
a new version of mankind,
one with a body that can
withstand the harsh conditions
of our new home
and with a spirit to adapt and thrive
under any circumstance.
That is a terrible plan.
You can't save humanity
by creating a bunch
of monster people like Amelia Earhart.
No one gets it right
out of the gate, okay?
But I have perfected a process
of enhancing human capabilities
by adding extraterrestrial DNA.
I just needed the raw materials
to work with.
That was what was in those other pods,
and that's why you kidnapped me,
to be raw material?
Well, if that's the case,
then here you go.
There's your raw material.
Now take me home.
Eugh, don't sell yourself
so short, sweet cheeks.
You're here to be my partner.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
These new humans need to be taught
to have a fighter's spirit.
That's where you come in, Sara Lance.
You want me to teach
your hybrids to be badasses,
to be their trainer?
Who better to imbue those qualities
than you, the woman who can't be killed?
There you go.
I know it's a lot to take in, sweetie.
Don't call me that, ever.
Right, because of the bossy Ava
you were attached to back on Earth?
She is not "bossy Ava".
She's Ava, and she's human,
and she has her own thoughts.
Aww.
You may believe that,
but all Avas have affinities
and weaknesses that I built
into their genetic blueprint.
Hey.
You found and fell in love
with one of my greatest accomplishments.
It's as though the universe
knew to bring us together.
- You're a sick son of a bitch.
- Think about my offer.
We've got all 15 seasons
of "Wynonna Earp"
all cued up for you, so...
♪ Take all the time you need ♪
Season two's my favorite.
[JILL ANDREWS' "TELL THAT DEVIL"]
Here you go.
♪ 'Cause I gave you all I got to give ♪
♪ I know that ain't no way to... ♪
Transformation is
the most vital cornerstone
of the dark arts.
To do this spell, twist your wrist
in the direction of the object,
and visualize what you want
your object to change into.
A little more fluid. That's almost it.
- Try again.
- Just tell me the damn words.
[CLEARS THROAT] Permuto!
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Permuto.
My stars!
You're a natural.
Well, my mother was a powerful witch.
Well, you've made her proud, dear girl.
Smashing job.
But that was an easy one.
You know, "permuto" has
several meanings in Latin.
One is to transform,
but the other is to exchange.
If you provided an able body
with whom I could change places,
I'd be able to teach you
with greater expediency.
So some poor fellow would be
trapped in the painting,
and you'd have a body you could
use to stab me in the back.
Nice try.
I wouldn't dream of it.
I promise the spell is easy
to do and easy to undo
if you so wish.
So it's the same spell,
just a different intention.
If I could nod, that's what
I'd be doing right now.
All we need is a body for me to borrow.
[PORTAL BUZZING]
Astra, you home, love?
What's all this?
What the hell is he doing down here?
I'm teaching this brilliant
young lady how to use magic.
It's like you said, John.
Life topside takes work,
and this is me getting to it.
Magic is a slippery slope,
all right, love?
Your mother knew that,
and that's why she got out of it.
I mean, she left me
because I wouldn't give it up.
She wouldn't want this
for you, all right?
You don't get to speak for her
or tell me how to live my life.
Well, you are in my home, aren't you?
Okay, so now this is your house.
I mean, how about when
it was falling apart
and the bills weren't being paid?
Was it your house then, too?
God, you are such an
insufferable hypocrite.
She's got you there, old chap.
Sneaky old bastard,
preying on her desperation.
- [GRUNTS]
- Whose fault was that?
You vile old snake.
I should've locked you
in the cellar where no one
could've found you.
- Put him down.
- You going on about all your...
- That's enough!
- Put him down.
- And all of your...
- Permuto!
What the bloody hell?
My word. It actually worked.
Brilliant job, dear girl.
Astra, put us back.
Permuto!
- Oh, damn.
- [LAUGHS]
Easy to do, easy to undo.
- Oh, Astra, don't...
- Permuto!
Oh. Mm.
Astra.
Astra, undo this right now.
Crowley is dangerous.
He can't be trusted!
Bravo, dear girl.
Bravo to you.
Here's the deal.
You have 12 hours to stretch your legs
and teach me magic.
12 hours, and then back
into the painting.
If you do one unsanctioned spell,
it is over.
You got me?
Like the clap, my lady.
Now let's get to work, shall we?
♪ ♪
While studying the secrets of Egypt,
I learned that sorcery requires a...
fruitful imagination.
One must find potential
in the dullest of things
to be truly magnificent.
[CHANTS IN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[REPEATS CHANT]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
[CHANTING IN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN]
Finally.
[REPEATS CHANT]
Oh, my.
There you are, killer.
[CHANTS IN ANCIENT EGYPTIAN]
[LAUGHS]
I have never seen anyone
take to the dark arts
with such ease.
Your natural talents are unparalleled.
No one likes a kiss-ass, Aleister,
and I am not extending your parole.
Understood, my lady.
What happened to my money?
Oh, dear girl, you didn't
think the treasure
was real, did you?
These transformations are
but a glamour, a trick.
They are effective in deception,
but temporary by nature.
So everything I just made...
the money, these clothes...
Will disappear before your very eyes.
Such are the rules
of beginner-level magic.
What if I level up?
No, no, no, no, you're not ready.
It takes ruthlessness and concentration
unlike any you can muster.
Oh, Al.
You clearly don't know me.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Time for your checkup.
[DEVICE WHIRS]
Hmm.
Vitals are good.
Just gonna check your mobility.
So are you an Earper for life yet?
Oh, yeah, I'm digging it.
You were totally right about season two.
They really figured out
what the show was,
and they went with it.
Well, I really hope
that you're a Wayhaught shipper
because if you aren't, I have to...
Listen to me carefully.
You're gonna take me out of here
and help me find a power source
to fuel my ship, understood?
[LAUGHS] I can't do that.
It's not in my DNA to disobey.
That's just what he wants you to think.
Look, the only thing that's
holding you back is you.
And you with that thing at my throat.
Just promise you'll help me escape.
Go ahead and kill me. I'm disposable.
He'll have another Nurse Ava
ready by lunch.
God, you are a human being!
You have a soul.
You can decide for yourself
what's right and what's wrong.
Look, Bishop may have created you,
but he doesn't control you.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Well, at least I can verify
that your mobility
is working very well.
Back to bed, you.
Ava.
Please just think about what I said.
♪ ♪
[THUNDERCLAP]
Astra, don't fall for his tricks.
He's too dangerous to be out and about.
Why do you think I trapped him
in the bloody painting
instead of sending him back to Hell?
He will go back into the painting
as soon as I get what I want.
What, magic power?
Astra, you don't need it, love.
Start from the bottom and work
your way up like everyone else.
I am not like everyone else, John.
My bottom was just a little
deeper than everyone else's,
but at least down in Hell, I was a boss,
a ruler, and richer than God.
Do you have any idea how hard
I worked to get there?
To go from being that traumatized,
terrified little girl
with nothing to a queen?
I won't go back to nothing, John.
I can't.
John, are you meddling?
Astra, please switch us back.
I didn't realize how hard
it was for you.
I thought you had everything in hand.
I promise I'll help you.
John and his empty promises.
Shall I remove the distraction?
Be nice... mm, ish.
Don't worry, I know exactly
where to place him.
You're a right bastard, Aleister.
Trapping you in a painting was merciful.
It should've been the loo.
You're not so tough now,
are you, my boy?
How does it feel to be powerless?
To find yourself stripped
of everything you ever worked for?
Astra and I have both felt that sting,
but now we will be unstoppable.
I can finally complete my search
for the Fountain of Imperium
out there in the heavens.
Don't wrap her up in your mad theories
of alien magic.
The fountain is real,
and with my loyal protégé at my side,
I will finally possess it.
Now,
let's bring you up
to your final resting place,
shall we, Johnny?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[PORTAL BUZZES]
Oh, no.
Finally, we're here.
You would think at least one of us
would have this address memorized.
What, John always zaps us
in and out of here.
Speaking of, where is he? John!
What are you all doing here?
We are out of a timeship.
We need a place to regroup.
We've been walking around Northumberland
for hours trying to find this house.
Now is really not a good time.
See, I'm in the middle
of something, and I just...
Ooh, are you expecting someone?
Is it a date? Are you dating?
Look, I am starved, y'all.
What is there to eat?
I'll make something.
Astra, where's your Wi-Fi router?
I need to hook up Gideon.
Hoo-hoo, whatcha making?
Something with ferret liver extract?
- You all need to leave now.
- And gangrene oil?
Astra, your router?
There's nothing
in the fridge... it's sad.
You won't like me when I'm hangry.
Can I borrow your phone?
That's a lot of ferret liver extract.
- [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- Permuto!
♪ ♪
Wow.
Sorry, guys.
Astra, what have you done?
I will turn you back as soon
as I'm done, I promise.
- Ahh!
- Let go.
Am I a flip phone?
- Hey, let go!
- [ALL GROANING]
Astra!
- Oof!
- Oh!
Ah, I've got that chatterbox,
John Constantine,
up in the attic.
Distraction is the enemy
of accomplishment.
No distractions here.
Let's make some real power.
We will first create
a magical energy-containing amulet.
[CHANTING IN GREEK]
Yes, yes.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Brilliant work, my lady.
Your amulet is ready to be charged.
There is only one thing powerful enough
to sustain this amulet...
a human soul.
Great.
I have got
Christopher Columbus, Ed Gein...
No, we will need a live human soul
from a beating heart.
You conveniently left that
off the ingredient list.
As queen of Hell,
you spent millions of souls
like they were pennies.
What's one more
before it goes down below, eh?
You said you wanted power.
This is the price.
[PHONE LINE TRILLS]
Hi, Robert.
It's Astra Logue, your neighbor.
Anyway, I was cleaning out my attic,
and wouldn't you know it,
I uncovered a Bethany lamp.
I know you have a collection,
so why don't you come by
and take a look?
♪ ♪
Wonderful.
See you soon.
Astra.
Are you really luring
an unsuspecting neighbor over
so you can steal his soul?
My unsuspecting racist neighbor?
Yeah, I sure am.
If y'all got a proud boy
who needs talking to,
let me at him.
- I'll fork his eyes out.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No one is going to do anything.
Astra, using humans as currency
is wrong, remember?
- [PHONE VIBRATING]
- Ow!
Yeah, and what did you do with John?
Who is this weirdo possessing his body?
John is fine. Just leave me alone.
And let you backslide?
You've come a long way since Hell.
You're one of us now.
Yeah, I don't think
she wants to be grouped
with the household objects, Cheese.
Not helping, Z.
Think about what you're doing, Astra.
- That guy is a human being.
- He is a jerk.
His soul is gonna end up in Hell anyway.
I'm not worried about his soul.
I'm worried about yours.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Stay out of my way.
Astra, wait... ahh!
A little late for a checkup, isn't it?
I would've come sooner,
but I had to wait
until Bishop danced himself to sleep.
- I want to help you.
- You do?
What you said to me earlier
really struck a nerve.
We are human.
We do have souls and wants
and dreams and opinions.
What Bishop is doing here...
it's an abomination.
I knew there was some
of that real Ava spirit in you.
All right, the ship that I crashed in,
it isn't far from here.
We just need to find something
to power it up.
I brought you a fuel cell.
Look at you, thinking ahead.
Let's go.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
It's much tidier in here
than I thought it would be.
You cleaned up well, too.
Charming how you changed for company.
Playing posh, eh?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Here's the lamp.
What do you think?
♪ ♪
Floral mosaic,
favrile glass.
It's not in stellar condition, though.
- Blemishes on the base...
- Yo, you can still back out.
- Shh.
- Did you say something?
No. Must be a draft.
Really think about
what you're doing, Astra.
- Hey!
- There's that noise again.
He's a fussy grandpa. He's not worth it.
Excuse me while I'm just
gonna tidy up a little bit.
That condescending snob
is not helping his own case.
I think you've left the telly on.
Maybe. I just... I'm gonna go check.
Hey, put me down!
- Oof!
- [ALL GRUNTING]
What a splendid specimen.
His bitter soul will more
than suit our purposes.
Just tell me what to do.
Hold it up to his heart,
and it will leech his very soul
from his mortal coil.
Great.
[CHUCKLES]
I hope Earl Grey is okay.
Yes, that'll do.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Let's talk about price, eh?
I was... I was thinking 50 pounds
to take it off your hands.
50? [SCOFFS]
That lamp is an antique, Mr. Truss.
Oh, I know, but...
what would someone like you
want with a dusty old lamp?
♪ ♪
Fine, fine, 75 then.
But you better clean it up for me first.
- It's filthy.
- To be honest,
I was thinking of making you
pay a lot more than that.
♪ ♪
What's all this, then?
Dammit, just get out of here,
Mr. Truss, now.
All right, I'll go to 80,
but that's my last offer.
- Who the bloody hell are you?
- No!
- [GROANS]
- [DEMONIC SHRIEKING]
[LAUGHS]
[SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
[CHUCKLES]
That's it, Crowley.
Time for you to go back
to where you came from.
Permuto!
[LAUGHS]
Those parlor tricks are no match
for my newfound power.
I am terribly disappointed
in you, dear girl.
I'd hoped that you would make
yourself a queen again,
but all you really wanted
was a dark prince
to come and save you.
Sadly,
you're just another helpless princess.
[CHANTS IN GAELIC]
[LIGHT MUSIC]
- [GASPS]
- Hello!
[GARGOYLES LAUGH]
[LIGHT MUSIC]
♪ Why, oh, why must I be forced ♪
♪ To sing? ♪
- Ooh!
- Pity.
You would have made
a smashing evil witch.
♪ Your very harsh words ♪
♪ They hold no sway ♪
♪ Sure, you can run ♪
♪ But you won't get away ♪
[LAUGHS]
And are you going to stop me
all by yourself?
♪ Annoying Legends I tried to hide ♪
♪ So glad they're here ♪
♪ And they'll fight by my side ♪
Get him!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Ha-ha!
Charge!
Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew!
Legends, roll out!
[GROWLS]
Nom, nom, nom, nom.
Ahh!
Vámonos!
- Ching!
- [SCREAMS]
This guy's toast!
Wh... ow!
Hiyah!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Impressive, my lady.
Transforming your friends into objects.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Lucky for me, their souls will
infuse even more power
into my amulet.
Now, out of my sight.
Whoa!
Ugh.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC]
♪ Oh, how will I ever flee from... ♪
Nope, sorry. No more singing.
Oi, what the hell has Crowley done?
Since we're all trapped
in a bloody cartoon,
I'm guessing he's betrayed you
and is about to gain untold power.
Oh, John, whatever shall I do?
That evil wizard is much too powerful.
He has the Legends at his mercy.
He's got the Legends?
He'll kill them all.
They're doomed unless you stop him.
I'm afraid I don't know how.
Astra, listen to me.
Years ago, your mum created
a powerful cleansing spell,
like an enema for magic.
It expels all sorcery from a vicinity.
There wasn't any reason
to use it, until now.
Goodness me.
Why would she ever create such a spell?
For me.
If I ever went too far.
Those days, I was reckless.
She was afraid I'd overdose,
so she created a spell
as a fail-safe.
I reckon it's somewhere
among her things.
You don't suppose it's
in this charming little book,
do you?
Of course, Natalie's music notebook!
The spell must be a song.
♪ ♪
Goodness gracious, I found it.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
My mother never taught me
how to read music.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Wait, I can read the music!
But how? I never could before.
Because every cartoon princess knows
how to sing, love.
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
You unlocked the door!
That ain't the first lock
I've ever picked.
Now, come on, princess.
We've got some saving to do.
[ALL GRUNTING]
You won't get away with this.
Oh, I think I will.
Now, hold still, my friend.
This won't hurt...
much.
- ♪ Rest your head ♪
- Astra?
♪ It's time to sleep ♪
- ♪ Dreams are calling ♪
- [YAWNS]
♪ Count the sheep ♪
♪ Lie in bed ♪
♪ Turn off the lights ♪
- ♪ So we can spy ♪
- [YAWNS] That spell.
- ♪ The starry night ♪
- It's making me weak!
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
♪ The moon is bright ♪
♪ In the sky ♪
♪ Close your eyelids ♪
♪ Say goodbye ♪
♪ Put your troubles ♪
♪ In the ground ♪
Ahh! [CACKLES]
♪ You'll be with me ♪
♪ Safe and sound ♪
- [GASPS] Oh, no!
- [SOBS]
- [CACKLES]
- ♪ Rest your head ♪
♪ It's time to sleep ♪
♪ Dreams are calling ♪
♪ Count the sheep ♪
No!
♪ ♪
[GROANING]
- It worked!
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, I never thought I'd be so happy
to see this coat again.
[SOFT MUSIC]
You guys okay?
I'm so glad to have my arms back.
So over being cheese.
That smell was getting aggressive.
Yeah, I was gonna say something.
Yeah, why was I a fork?
So how about that Bethany lamp, eh?
ALL: Get out!
Who are these people?
These are my friends,
and this is my house.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Now, get out.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
You can't just leave me here, John!
I know what that spell did to you,
and I can help.
Out there in the cosmos,
in the great beyond,
there's an unlimited source of power.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there you go again,
yammering on about
the Fountain of Imperium.
The fountain is out there.
It's a well of unexplored, untapped,
and unstoppable magic.
We could work together,
brothers in arms.
Just don't put me away again!
Yeah, so long, Master Crowley.
[MUFFLED] No, I ask you to reconsider!
I'll do anything! I'll do the dusting!
I'll polish your boots!
I don't think that's gonna be enough.
Well, it was enough
until you set him free
with your bloody meddling.
If you'd helped out with the house
and the bills and the damn Internet,
then Crowley wouldn't have been
able to get his hooks in.
You know, you're right.
It's my fault that you
sought out Crowley's help.
I should've listened
rather than being stuck
in my own bloody world.
And I wasn't ready for how
hard it would be up here.
I just... I felt like
that lost little girl
in Hell all over again,
completely powerless...
you wouldn't understand.
Actually, I do.
Your mum's expulsion spell,
let's just say that it was
pretty effective.
[SOFT MUSIC]
It didn't just strip Crowley
of his powers...
John, I...
I knew very well
what the spell would do.
It had to be done. Listen, Astra.
Magic, it takes a lot of patience.
There are no shortcuts, love.
But seeing as I have to start
from the bottom
and work my way up,
how's about you and I do it together?
♪ ♪
All right.
- See you later, study buddy.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
All right, we just need
to connect the fuel cell
to the ship's mainframe.
♪ ♪
What did you do?
What I had to.
He's my maker.
Sara.
[TUTS]
I'm not only disappointed
because our time together
obviously meant nothing to you,
but also because you didn't
realize that this fuel cell
is just my sleepy-wakey nightlight.
So soothing, right?
I'm gonna be honest.
I actually needed you
to lead me to the location
of this ship so I could
retrieve the rest of my cargo.
Yeah, well, good luck
with that, because I ejected
all of them into the deep void
of outer space.
[LAUGHS]
Sara Lance.
It's called "data redundancy".
Those capsules not only
kept you safe during transport,
they also extracted DNA samples
from each and every one of you.
I prefer to have live creatures
to work with,
but this is the next best thing.
♪ ♪
What the mother...
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That was quite an adventure
we had out in the woods.
I think we had a real
breakthrough, you and I!
We're closer than ever now.
Some might even say...
inseparable.
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -