Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Is this your new girlfriend?
- Um, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
You and I dating would be totally weird.
Totally weird.
Wow, that's beautiful.
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
Step away from the creature, miss.
You murdered him!
[GASPING]
[SNARLS]
Hank is running some secret project.
He's not just taking the fugitives.
He's testing on them.
I don't need you anymore.
I don't need you anymore, either.
- [WHOOSHING]
- [GRUNTS]
What did you do?
I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
[WHOOSHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Maybe I shouldn't intrude.
Nate needs all of our support right now.
Well, what am I supposed to say to him?
"Sorry the woman I've been
exchanging love letters with
- in prison killed your dad"?
- [CHUCKLES]
They ought to put that
on a condolence card.
Look, we are going inside
and we are going to strive
with grace to help our
friend cope with his loss.
Damn it.
Here, let me help.
Hey, uh, thanks for sticking
around this past week.
What are pretend girlfriends for?
My mom's gonna be so crushed
when I tell her we broke up.
Then don't.
I... I mean, she's going through a lot.
We can pretend break
up any time we want.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We should, um... we should
probably get out there.
You ready for this?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS]
[STRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Nathaniel.
I need you to make a toast later.
Tell everyone what an amazing
man your father was.
Yeah, Mom, I don't think
that's a great idea.
What? Of course it is.
And Zari, I am so glad that
you're here for Nathaniel
to lean on right now.
Yeah, um, you know me.
I'm... I'm his rock.
I can't. I... I can't face him.
Wait... wait.
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
I hope you're not stress-eating, squire.
[PLAYFUL DRAMATIC STING]
I don't know what else to do.
I can't believe this is happening.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
You feel the energy in this room?
It's like sitting on a keg of dynamite.
You see, wakes are notorious soft spots
where the supernatural
meets the living world.
See Nate's aunt?
That particular prayer is
to ward off evil spirits
and they've covered the mirrors,
so the bad lads can't get in.
Well, that's creepy.
Yeah, well, creepy is my business.
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
And it looks like business is good.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
♪ ♪
- BOTH: Oh!
- [CANDY CLATTERS]
Nate, Nate, I'm... I'm
sorry. I'm... I'm so sorry.
No, it's... it's okay, Ray.
No, no, no, it's not.
I keep giving Nora second chances and
she goes and does this.
Look, you thought Nora could change
and I never thought my dad would
be torturing magical creatures,
so I guess... I guess we're both wrong.
[SIGHS]
Can't believe you're
the one comforting me.
Oh, come on. I love you, bro.
That's never gonna change.
[STIRRING MUSIC]
Love you, too.
♪ ♪
[GLASS CRACKING]
Oh, no. Don't, no-no-no, don't.
Don't, don't, don't do it, Ray.
Don't... you're gonna do it.
You're gonna do it.
[GLASS CRACKING]
[SCREAMS]
- Nora?
- [EXCITING MUSIC]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
How... how are you doing that?
It's a reflection spell.
I can't hold it much longer.
Well, good, because
there's nothing you could
possibly say that would
make any difference.
This time there will be
no more second chances.
Ray! I didn't kill Nate's dad.
Oh, thank God, you're innocent.
Tell me where you are.
I need to talk to you in person.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
Now, who wants a nice, juicy steak?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Charlie, uh, you know
that I'm a vegetarian.
No, no, no, you used to be a vegetarian
when you were a normal, boring human.
- But now you are...
- A monster?
Exactly. I mean, how cool is that?
Wait, are you trying to get
me to shift into Wolfie?
Of course I am.
You've been moping about the ship,
thinking about your lost love.
But I think that he would
really want you to just
embrace your wild side. [CHUCKLES]
Konane liked me as Mona.
Whoa.
[SOFT WHOOSHING]
The words on your shirt.
These are the names of my favorite
Jane Austen characters.
It appears that you're experiencing
the impact of a magical fugitive.
BOTH: Oh.
- [DEVICE BEEPS]
- This better be good, Mona.
A fugitive got to Jane Austen.
She never wrote "Sense and Sensibility."
And "Pride and Prejudice"
disappeared, too.
Whatever it is, it's gonna have to wait.
Did someone say history's in trouble?
Legends assemble!
Okay, I really need to
get out of here, too.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing.
Uh, there's a fugitive
alert, but it can wait.
No, you should go.
It's hard enough I have to play pretend.
You guys shouldn't.
Okay.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Bye, Nate.
- Bye, Zari.
♪ ♪
Gideon traced a new
Fugitive to a wedding
Jane Austen attended in
Bath, England, 1802.
I already had Gideon chart a course.
Can I come on the mission?
Please?
Sure.
Yeah, and as much as I
love a good wedding sneak,
I'm gonna QB from,
um... from my bedroom.
♪ ♪
Is he acting weirder than normal?
BOTH: Yeah.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- [SNIFFS]
Speaking of weird...
I think my sense of smell has
improved because of Wolfie.
And you smell exactly like... Nate.
♪ ♪
No, I don't.
It's definitely Nate.
Nate and something else.
[SNIFFS] Arousal?
- [LAUGHS]
- No, I don't...
I don't like Nate.
- That would be wrong and...
- He likes you.
He confessed it when he
swallowed the truth bug.
We're so not passing the
Bechdel Test right now.
It's okay to talk about guys sometimes.
Come on. I bet it's been
months since you got laid.
Now, why don't you just go smash Nate?
Or better yet, you should go
smash somebody else because
if you're still thinking
about Nate then you know
you're really into him.
Why don't you talk to Nate?
Tell him how you feel.
- Oh, boo.
- That is a terrible idea.
Okay, I'm going. Bye.
- _
- [CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
This is like a Jane Austen
novel come to life.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [WIND WHOOSHES]
- Oh, my bonnet!
- [HORSE HOOVES CLOPPING]
- Look out!
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- Whoa!
- Whoa.
- Oh.
[GRUNTS]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Forgive me, miss. Are you hurt?
Only my pride.
Injured pride is a small thing...
if it allowed us to meet.
What's the holdup there?
- Come, come, I say.
- Duty calls.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Apologies, Lord Remington.
We'll be on our way shortly.
- [LAUGHING]
- Here.
[CLEARS THROAT] Not a word.
Was that a curtsey?
[LAUGHS] "Only my pride."
Okay, let's go. Shut up.
- A damsel.
- [LAUGHS]
[ORGAN PLAYING]
♪ ♪
- [SIGHS]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
If you don't jump that
buff coachman's bones,
I will.
We are at this wedding to
catch a magical creature.
If that's the groom, then
I'm glad I'm not the bride.
A man's charms are
equal to his fortunes.
And Mr. Dockerty's
fortunes are prodigious.
[SHUSHES] Jane.
Don't be rude.
That's Jane Austen.
♪ ♪
I cannot marry you, Mr. Dockerty.
[ALL GASPING]
- My heart yearns for another.
- [ALL GASP]
Our family's scullery maid.
Ellen, are you here?
- I'm here.
- [GASPING CONTINUES]
I love you, too!
- [LAUGHS]
- Scandal!
- [GASPING]
- Oh, dear Lord.
Oh.
I give not one fig, Miss Sinclair,
for my heart and my
lower extremities yearn
for your mother.
Get over here, gorgeous.
[ROUSING UPBEAT MUSIC]
- Come to me, my love.
- Ooh!
[LAUGHTER AND CHATTER]
♪ ♪
[KISSING]
This is what I call a wedding.
[WHOOSHING]
Coast is clear.
[SNEAKY MUSIC]
I really don't want you to get
in trouble with your friends.
Oh, it's no trouble.
It looks like everyone
else is still on mission.
Okay.
Uh, so, who did kill Hank?
- The demon.
- Okay, good.
I... obviously, I mean...
obviously, it's bad.
If it's a demon, that means that
John will be able to find proof and
you just need to lay low
until he comes back.
You really don't mind me staying here?
Yeah, no, it'd be nice
if you stayed here.
Oy, Rayge. Where are you?
I've got an update on the mission...
- "Rayge"?
- It's a long story.
- ... need to do some research...
- What's... oh... oh...
♪ ♪
[DOOR HISSES] What...
What are you hiding in there?
Hmm? What? Nothing.
Ah, buffing the old bishop, was we?
- [SOFT LAUGH]
- It's all right, mate.
No judgment here, all right?
- Come on.
- Oh, yeah.
So, the bride and the scullery maid,
- that was...
- Insane?
- Romantic.
- I was gonna say hot.
Regardless, that
definitely did not happen
in actual history.
- [DEVICE BEEPS]
- Ray, Charlie, what you got?
This wedding was the second of a series
of lust outbreaks in 1802.
Yeah, the sexual revolution came
a couple hundred years too early.
Why would it make Jane
Austen stop writing?
We need more info.
Well, Jane Austen was known for being
a keen social observer, so
if anyone would have noticed
a new magical arrival in
town, it would be her.
Okay, let's go interview Jane.
Oh, wait, hang on a tick.
People with the real dirt,
always the servants.
Like a handsome coachman perhaps, hmm?
Fine, I'll go ask him some questions.
- But that's it.
- You go get it, girl.
Okay.
[HARPSICHORD MUSIC]
[DOOR OPENING]
Sister, dear, this is
Miss Lance and Miss Wu.
They're new in town.
Try not to scare them away.
I shall do my best, Cassandra.
♪ ♪
We are so sorry to interrupt
your writing, Miss Austen.
This? Just a letter.
Uh, shall we take a turn around
the room while we converse?
We'd be delighted to.
[WHISPERS] It's a Regency
thing. Go with it.
♪ ♪
So, the bride, Miss Sinclair,
her behavior must have
been quite a shock.
Ever since Lord Remington
arrived a week ago,
the entire town has been
acting most imprudently.
But Miss Sinclair's situation
is truly horrendous.
Oh, I'd think you of all people
would celebrate the triumph of romance.
What's to celebrate?
Miss Sinclair will be cut
off from her fortune
and the two women will
have nothing to live on.
But it's because of
you... I... I mean...
I have come to believe that
love will find a way to
overcome any obstacle.
Then you're either lying
or you're a fool.
Tell me, has love worked
out so well for you?
- No, but...
- Then you are a fool.
For you shouldn't have
to learn a lesson twice.
[DARK GROWLING]
[SNARLS]
- [EXHALES]
- Let's go find Lord Remington.
We should be going.
Hello?
[SIGHS] This is stupid.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
[CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
What a pleasure to see you again.
[STRING MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Hey, man.
What's up, pretty?
This whole toasting is
eating me up on the inside.
My... my dad was such a dick.
He lied about everything and now
he's turning me into a liar, too.
Listen, your old man's gone.
Whatever you say out
there, that's for you.
You know what, Mick?
I think you're onto something.
- [DARK WHOOSHING]
- [SOFT CRACKLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SOFT WHISPERING]
[INTENSE WHOOSHING]
[ECHOING] Nathaniel!
♪ ♪
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Hey, where's Nate?
Well, we need to find him
because Hank's spirit
is still here.
[DOOR SHUTS]
Hey, cheer up.
I mean, what does Jane Austen know?
How to be witty and wise and
mix satire with romance.
[WOMEN GIGGLING]
I bet you these girls know
where Lord Remington is.
They do look like fan girls.
Okay, you know the era.
You take the lead.
He's simply the handsomest
man I've ever laid eyes on.
[GIGGLING]
I know what you mean.
Lord Remington is such a fine specimen.
I can't say I share your sentiment.
[SNORING]
[GAGS]
His coachman, though,
what he lacks in means,
he makes up for in magnetism.
[GIGGLES] I concur.
His arrival has sent
many hearts aflutter.
[ALL GIGGLING]
Coachman,
as in the guy we pushed
Zari to hook up with!
Zari's gonna smash the fugitive!
BOTH: Oh...
[BOTH MOANING]
Sorry. This is moving really fast.
- I agree.
- You do?
What's your name?
[SOFT LAUGH]
Uh, my name is Zari. What's your name?
You know what? Don't...
don't answer that.
You don't kiss like any
man I've ever known.
What are you?
[WHOOSHING]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC]
[ECHOING] I am Kamadeva,
the Hindu god of love.
Awesome.
[UPBEAT SITAR MUSIC]
- Oh!
- We're too late!
[GRUNTING AND MOANING]
Zari!
We think you might be dealing with...
The fugitive?
Yeah, I know.
This is Kamadeva.
As in the namesake of
Kama Sutra, Kamadeva?
That I did not know.
Look, I'm not going to sleep
with a magical fugitive.
You are incredible.
A woman has never before
resisted my charms.
All right, you're coming with us.
I would follow Miss Zari
to the world's end.
[PLAYFUL DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[FORCE FIELD WHOOSHES]
Well, your days of ruining
Regency-era marriages
are over, Kamadeva.
I only sought to grant
people the courage
to follow their hearts' desire.
Oh, I think he likes you.
Gideon, get us out of here.
I'm not so sure we can go yet.
[WHOOSH]
Miss Wu is correct.
The historical records still indicate
that Jane Austen's
career is in jeopardy.
We caught the fugitive.
What's the problem?
Well, it's too late to knock
on Jane Austen's door tonight.
We'll talk to her tomorrow.
So, I'm to spend the night...
Alone.
Oh, what a waste.
All right, everybody out.
- Hi.
- Come on.
Surely I can have a bed.
[KISSES]
[DOOR HISSES]
Well, I had Gideon fabricate
some jim-jams because, uh,
you know, it's a slumber party.
Oh, uh, thanks.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Uh, obviously since you're my
guest, you will get the bed.
Oh, well, it's big enough
for the both of us.
We can just share.
Oh, okay.
You can turn around now.
Hmm.
It really covers everything.
[SIGHS]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC BUILDS]
♪ ♪
Thing is, I pride myself
on being a gentleman
and the gentlemanly thing to do
would be to sleep in the chair.
So... [CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
[STAMMERS] But you... you...
you can't... there's no way...
Oh, that's not...
[SNORING]
Okay.
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
Hey, Nate. How's the old toast going?
Is there one or two N's in "conniving"?
Right, then.
Uh, may I suggest a
slight change of plan?
No. Mick is right.
It's time for me to tell
the truth about my dad.
How was I supposed to know
Hank's ghost was here?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Wait, what?
Yeah, that's about the
gist of it, Natey boy.
You see, your old man's
spirit is working very hard
to stay attached to the mortal realm.
I can only surmise that he has something
he wants to say to you,
so if you wouldn't mind
leaving off your roast for a bit,
joining us for a brief séance,
and I'll have him on his way in no time.
No.
There's nothing Hank can
say now to excuse him
from embezzling money
and hurting creatures.
In fact, I'm glad he's still here,
'cause it's his turn to listen to me!
- [DARK WHOOSH]
- [RECORD SCRATCHES]
[OMINOUS SCREAMING FROM RECORD PLAYER]
You don't scare me, Hank!
[RECORD SPINNING INTENSIFIES]
[SOFT WHOOSH]
[MAGICAL CLINKING]
[ROMANTIC SITAR MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
Ray?
♪ ♪
You want me in bed with you?
Yes, I did. I do.
I do.
♪ ♪
[SOFT GASP]
[MOANS]
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
♪ ♪
Ava.
[MOANS]
[SNARLS]
[LAUGHS]
[SHOUTS, LAUGHS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪ ♪
Damn it, this is definitely a dream.
[CLEARS THROAT]
The fugitive get to you, too?
Yeah.
Well, personally, I
really enjoyed my night,
blowing David Bowie's mind.
[LAUGHS]
Who'd you get a leg over, Z?
Wait, let me guess. Nate?
No, Kamadeva.
- Both?
- It was both!
Blimey, Z, I didn't
know you had it in you.
What about you, Wolfie?
You dreamt about Konane.
Mona...
I'll get it.
[TENDER MUSIC]
- [CRYING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
Hey, hey, hey. It's okay.
He had the sweetest eyes.
And when he would look at me,
the whole world would disappear.
And now he's dead. [CRYING]
Mona, I know it's hard, but
try to have some perspective.
You didn't know him for very long.
So, you think I'm a fool, too?
No, I just don't think anyone
should give their heart away
without thinking about the consequences.
But romance is taking
a chance on someone
without knowing how it's gonna end up!
Romance is something used to
sell novels. It's not real.
Well, it'll never be real for you.
Not if you never try.
Not if you never take a risk!
You know, it's hard to
take advice from someone
whose boyfriend turned
her into a werewolf.
- [SNARLS]
- Hey, guys.
Let's just take a breath.
You're right.
I might be stupid for being a romantic,
but it's not Konane's fault.
[INTENSE GROANING]
[BONES RUMBLING]
- Bloody hell!
- [SNARLS]
Finally! You look wicked, mate!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[SNARLS]
Mona, wait!
[SNARLING]
Jane Austen.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
It's time for you to pay!
- [SNARLING]
- Stay back, beast!
If I'm a beast, it's because of you!
Your books made me an
incurable romantic!
You're the reason I risked
everything for love!
[SNARLS]
And now Konane's dead!
And look at me!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You don't believe in romance!
Your writing is all lies!
[HOWLS]
Are you the girl from earlier?
Mona is weak.
Wolfie is strong.
[SNARLS]
Well, Wolfie, I believe from the depths
of my soul that one should
only marry for love.
You do?
So much so that I rejected
the only man who has ever
asked for my hand.
He was a smug simpleton
who only read sermons.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BONES RUMBLING]
How remarkable.
You shouldn't mess with people's dreams.
[CHUCKLES]
My powers don't create
passion out of thin air.
Whomever you dreamt
about, you truly desire.
It doesn't mean I have to act on it.
It's called impulse control.
You sound like a woman
who has never let herself fall in love.
Where I'm from, love is a liability.
And yet a life without
love is no life at all.
Tell me, what does a god
know about the human heart?
[SITAR MUSIC]
My real name is Sanjay.
I was born thousands of years ago.
When the actual Kamadeva
was immolated by Shiva,
I gathered his ashes in this vial.
They bestowed powers I could
have scarcely imagined.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I like you.
And I think you secretly yearn
to be impulsive and free.
♪ ♪
Unless you lack the courage.
[FORCE FIELD WHOOSHES]
Okay. Give me a hit.
- Might I suggest...
- Nope.
If I'm gonna do this,
I want to experience
love, lust, the whole shebang.
That is, unless you lack the courage.
[ROMANTIC SITAR MUSIC BUILDS]
♪ ♪
[MAGICAL CLINKING]
One, two, three.
♪ ♪
[SOFT WHOOSHING]
Oh, wow.
♪ ♪
Most of you here, uh, knew Hank well.
Or, thought you did.
I'm gonna talk about a different Hank,
a Hank I got to know this year.
- [ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
- [SOFT GASP]
[CROWD MURMURING]
[UNEASY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hank was a workaholic who
never took a day off.
Well, Hank, you can, um,
finally rest in peace.
[CROWD MURMURING]
[SIGHS]
Um, Hank never knew his own father.
That's why he wanted to be there
for Nathaniel growing up.
But work often got in the way.
So one year, we planned
to use Hank's leave
to stay for a week in Disney World.
[SOFT LAUGH] Nathaniel
was over the moon.
But the morning that we
were to fly to Orlando,
we ended up having to take Nathaniel
to the hospital instead.
When Hank saw the look of disappointment
in his son's eyes, he went out
and rented a Mickey Mouse costume,
put it on, and went to the hospital.
He convinced everyone
there that Mickey Mouse
had come to see them.
Hank Heywood was not a perfect man.
But when he was at his
best, that is who he was,
a man who could make
you believe in magic.
[STIRRING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
To Hank.
ALL: To Hank.
♪ ♪
[GLASSES CLINK]
Why did you tell me that
by following their hearts,
those women would only
fall into despair?
Because my decision was
a result of my pride.
When my father dies, my
sister and I will be
- reduced to penury.
- But your writing...
Has been rejected by every publisher.
It's no wonder.
I satirize the manners
of a society that seems
to have lost all sense of decorum.
Therefore, I've decided to stop writing.
But you will publish.
You can't give up now,
because your books are timeless.
How can you be so sure?
Because...
you're my favorite author.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
May I offer you a bit of advice?
My books advocate a
partnership based on love
and mutual respect,
not on losing control.
♪ ♪
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[ROUSING SITAR MUSIC]
What shall we do next?
I have an idea.
Let's get married.
[SOFT SITAR MUSIC]
Do you hear that?
No. Hear what?
There's definitely music playing.
Kamadeva loved music.
Perhaps you should sing.
I don't sing.
♪ Every day I find a way ♪
♪ To shove my past and anger down ♪
Go on, my love. That was beautiful.
♪ My humor's dry I never cry ♪
♪ If I start I'd surely drown ♪
♪ When I'm on my own I can't
help wanting something more ♪
♪ Today instead of closing
off I'm opening a door ♪
[UPBEAT MUSIC BUILDS]
BOTH: ♪ Now I'm tossing sense
aside and I surrender ♪
♪ To the fantasy and
pleasure I surrender ♪
♪ To my happy ever after ♪
♪ I won't fight it ♪
♪ Won't deny it ♪
♪ Do you have a ring? I'll try it ♪
♪ I surrender ♪
In the morning we should go
ask the parson to marry us.
A Christian wedding?
For a Muslim woman and a Hindu man?
Let's not think with our heads,
but feel with our hearts.
♪ ♪
Gideon, where's that music coming from?
I took the liberty of broadcasting
- Miss Tomaz's comms.
- Huh.
It's rather infectious.
♪ ♪
Ray, this music,
- I think it's magical.
- You're right.
I want to express my
feelings to you in verse.
Is that really necessary?
I had a dirty dream of you.
I'll bet mine was dirtier.
Why didn't you go and make a move?
I would have, if you'd been flirtier.
- [SIGHS]
- Okay.
It's just complicated.
If Nate knew, he'd be enraged.
I know, and I'm sorry,
but my desire's been uncaged.
Don't let this moment pass us by.
It could be our only chance.
You're right. I need you now.
Sorry, Nate and Captain Lance.
[DEEP GASP]
♪ I fixed the timeline as a cat ♪
♪ Saved a cowboy kept his hat ♪
♪ Took Salem's breath away ♪
♪ Got stuck reliving the same day ♪
♪ Through it all I kept my cool ♪
♪ Never thought I'd play the fool ♪
♪ Now I've surrendered to you ♪
♪ It's time for me to say I do ♪
"I do"? What are you talking about?
We need to find Mona.
Wait a sec, is this a
Bollywood musical number?
You bet your ass, it is.
[MAGICAL WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
ALL: ♪ Now we're tossing sense
aside and we surrender ♪
♪ To the fantasy and
pleasure we surrender ♪
♪ To our happy ever afters ♪
♪ We won't fight it won't deny it ♪
♪ Losing all control we'll try it ♪
♪ We surrender ♪
♪ I want you badly as my bride ♪
♪ Please make my wish come true ♪
♪ These feelings can't be denied ♪
♪ So yes I say I... ♪
Stop! You're making a mistake!
♪ Zari ♪
Whoa, why did I just sing that?
Okay, I guess I'm just gonna roll with
the whole singing thing.
[SIGHS]
♪ Every day we find a
way to hold grief ♪
♪ And not let them see ♪
♪ We feel so wrong we often long ♪
♪ Get swept away in fantasy ♪
[WHOOSH]
♪ ♪
♪ You've been so brave wise and strong ♪
♪ By opening your door ♪
♪ Please Zari have courage now ♪
♪ To wait for something more ♪
Don't listen to her, my love.
No, Mona's right, Z.
You don't even know this guy.
He's been using the powers
of a love god for years.
Guaranteed he's got a wife.
Is that true?
Not exactly.
I have 1,000 wives.
But lucky number 1,001
is the most important.
Seriously?
So, you still want to marry me?
♪ ♪
No, I definitely do not.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ Now I've got my senses back ♪
♪ But I'll surrender ♪
♪ Life's not done I'll love again ♪
♪ I'll surrender ♪
BOTH: ♪ With my friends now by my side ♪
♪ I won't hide it won't deny it ♪
♪ Real love comes my way I'll try it ♪
♪ I'll surrender ♪
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Voi-bloody-là.
Now, only the particular
spirit we're after
will be able to enter the vessel.
What vessel?
The vessel's you.
I'm gonna kill you, weasel.
[WHOOSH]
O spiritus veni.
Quod praecipio, solacium
capere spiritus.
[WHOOSHING]
Hank Heywood, I summon you.
Quos eici!
[WIND WHOOSHING]
Hank?
[HANK'S VOICE] Who else would it be?
Where's Nathaniel?
Oh, well, Nate gave you
the big middle finger,
so I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Still angry, is he?
Us Heywoods, we hold a good grudge.
Now, what's so important that
you had to stick around?
[SIGHS]
It pains me to admit it, but
I made a terrible mistake.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
A man approached me about a deal.
♪ ♪
Unlimited funding.
And all I had to do was give him access
to all the magical creatures
within the Time Bureau.
But this man was no
ordinary beltway bandit.
He was a demon.
♪ ♪
[CONTRAPTION CLICKING]
[BOOKCASE CLANKS, RUMBLES]
♪ ♪
Only after he murdered me
did I realize the truth.
What was the demon's name?
Promise me you'll keep Nathaniel safe.
Yes, yes, yes, I promise.
Now, come on, Hank,
you can't delay the inevitable forever.
What was the demon's name?
His name was Neron.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSH]
[CLICKS]
♪ ♪
_
[CHIMING]
[BEEPS]
Hey, world. I'm Hank Heywood.
And I'm here to tell you about
an exciting opportunity.
When I learned about the existence of
magical creatures... yes,
magical creatures exist...
I ran right home and
pulled out a drawing
made by my son,
Nathaniel, when he was
only nine years old.
My son envisioned a theme
park where everyone
could gaze in wonder at
dragons and unicorns,
werewolves and minotaurs.
This is insane.
Now, you may be thinking,
"This is insane."
But what great man hasn't
been thought of as insane
at one point in his life?
I believe this park can
bring our country together.
And with your help,
I'm going to turn my son's
dream into a reality.
I call it Heyworld.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
[EXHALES]
Oh, Hank.
Why?
[SOFT MUSIC]
I have so many questions.
You weren't torturing magical creatures.
You were training them
to be in a theme park.
That is nuts.
♪ ♪
But I gotta respect
you for dreaming big.
It was your moonshot, your way of
risking it all to make the
world a better place.
♪ ♪
I was so wrong about you.
At the end of the day,
you were just as wacky
and well-intentioned as any Legend.
And I wish I had a chance to
get to know that side of you.
[SNIFFS]
♪ ♪
I'm gonna miss you.
I love you, Hank.
[SNIFFS]
I love you, Dad.
[WHOOSH]
[DARK VOICE] Look at you.
Take a look at yourself,
you miserable git.
That's right.
[NORMAL VOICE] Soak it in.
Your big sacrifice, it was for nothing.
But instead of rolling up your sleeves
and taking it to that demon bastard,
you're getting rat-ass drunk in a shed.
I can't fight him.
He's too strong.
Oh, this isn't about Neron.
You failed Desmond.
You failed Astra.
And you'll fail Nate. And you know why?
Because deep down,
you want them all to go to Hell.
You want the company.
You liar!
[GRUNTS]
[DARK VOICE LAUGHS]
[GROANS]
Hey, Johnny.
Miss me?
Des.
I'm surprised you haven't
figured it out yet.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Neron.
[ROARING]
[CACKLING]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --