- Not even the six can stop me now.
- _
Beebo want cuddles!
[BOOMING]
Guys, guys!
Dad.
I'm sorry, Nora. He died a good man.
He died a demon, Ray.
- ♪ Oh, I've been cleaning up some Beebo ♪
- _
♪ Just to scrub the
time anomalies away ♪
♪ Hey, can't you see
the blue fluff blowing ♪
Hello?
Who's there?
Okay, I'm just gonna use my hand
to block out the sun's glare
so I can see you. [EXHALES SHARPLY]
You. No!
No, it can't be you!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[SQUEAKS]
♪♪
[ENGINES WHIRRING]
The Loom of Fate,
an ancient artifact that has the power
to change any person's life story
without wrecking the timeline.
- Anyone's, like...
- Astra's.
We give her a life
where her mom never died
and where she never goes to hell.
Well, if you think I'm helping you,
you're daft as a bush.
I destroyed that thing
for a bloody good reason, John-o.
Come on, Sara.
You know this can solve
all of our problems.
It can erase all of the Encores.
Yeah, and make all of
our dreams come true.
John, I'm sorry,
but I'm with Charlie on this one.
That kind of cosmic power doesn't belong
in the hands of anyone.
Astra has made her choices, John.
It is not up to you to undo them.
Now, this will be the
solution to our Encore problem.
Captain Lance, there is
a new Encore detected
- in Salvation, 1874.
- I love my Prognosticator.
All right, Legends,
grab your cowboy hats and leather straps
because we are going to...
- [MACHINE WHIRRING]
- Where is everyone?
Yeah, I might have got a bit sentimental
on my deathbed and encouraged Raymond
to carpe his diem.
- Nice rock.
- Yeah.
She'll love that.
And when she finds it,
I'll pop the question.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
She's here. She's really here.
Oh, man.
It's really happening.
Our work here is done.
Our boy's all growns up.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[DISTANT WHOOSHING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪♪
Nora Darhk. Welcome.
I will have the pleasure
of serving you this evening.
Thanks, Gare.
Whoa, wow, Ray.
You really went all out for date night.
- [EXHALES]
- I thought we were just having pizza.
Oh, I got a little inspired, I guess.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah.
[STAMMERS]
[GAME BEEPING]
I see Pippa is still your charge.
Yes, until we figure out
her heart's deepest need.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [GROANS]
Oh, big talker, I see.
[TIN CAN CLINKS]
[SPITS]
Defiling the library, I see.
Yeah, well, uh, you
know, I've quit smoking,
so, uh, I need a new habit.
- Doing some research?
- Yeah, yeah.
I need to find the Loom
of Fate to save Astra,
but since, uh, Charlie
isn't making it easy for me,
I am doing it the hard way. [SPITS]
- Why not ask a historian?
- [LAUGHS]
All right, then, Mr. Professor.
Tell me, what do you know?
Well, when I was in grad school,
my professor showed me a diary
of an explorer named Ernest Shackleton.
Now, Shackleton was
obsessed with the Loom,
and he believed a piece of it
was buried under the South Pole.
So if I'm to find the Loom,
I've gotta search the South Pole?
- Shackleton thought so.
- Wow, bloody hell.
Nice one, Nate.
Don't worry, John.
We'll figure out another
way to help you and Astra.
That ought to cool his jets.
[CHUCKLES]
[DOOR WHOOSHES]
Hey, Mick! Saddle up!
- We're going to the wild West.
- [KNOCKS]
[MUFFLED CRASHING AND GRUNTING]
Is everything okay in there?
[CRASHING AND GRUNTING CONTINUE]
He's been in there for days.
What are you still doing here?
- Exfoliating.
- [CRASHING CONTINUES]
Mick, get out here right now!
[DOOR WHOOSHES]
- What?
- What is going on?
Someone's trashing
Rebecca Silver online.
Oh, cute. You have a troll.
What's wrong with your face?
[DOOR WHOOSHES]
Zari, your mission is to help Mick.
Okay, I have so many makeover ideas.
With his troll problem.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hmm.
[WHOOSHING]
Did I just fritz out of existence?
- [TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
- _
- Oh! The train's coming!
Help me! Oh, ooh, yes!
H-help me! Untie me!
I'm too beautiful to die so young!
- Train's coming!
- [SCREAMING]
[ALL SHOUTING]
- Stand up, stand up, stand up!
- Oh, no!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
The train! Oh, God!
Director Sharpe! You saved me!
- Okay.
- [CRYING]
Wait, wait, wait a second.
Did you just say "Director Sharpe"?
- Yeah.
- Gary, what year are you from?
- The present, 2018.
- Okay, listen.
I need you to tell us who did this
and then immediately
Courier back to the Bureau.
I can't. He stole my Time Courier.
Who?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[THUNDER BOOMING]
Hi, Nora doll.
Daddy's home.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Dad?
Oh, Nora doll! I missed you so much.
This is amazing. How are you?
You are an Encore.
Look, all I know is,
I'm up here right now
as part of some
soul-harvesting pyramid scheme.
Honestly, I can't keep
up with these millennials
and all their newfangled
world domination plans.
So you're doing the
whole villain thing again?
Well, you know... no, I mean,
it's part of my parole agreement.
But after spending two years in hell
worrying about my little girl,
I had to come and see you first.
But look at this place!
You must be a master sorceress by now.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This is just a place where I hang my hat
and do my dark rituals.
- Dark rituals!
- Um, how did you find me?
Blood magic?
Your PalmerTech watch,
it still has location sharing on.
PalmerTech. Right.
- Ray!
- Oh, sorry for the delay.
- Gary seems to have run off.
- My dad's here.
- What?
- My dad's here!
- Your dad's here?
- Shh!
Oh, oh, man! Is he an Encore? Oh, man!
And Sara just found herself
a Hell Sword, which means...
- She'll kill him.
- What do we do? What do we do?
- You have to leave.
- What about Pippa?
- Pippa. Pippa!
You have to take her.
You have to... ooh...
keep her comfortable so
that she doesn't summon me.
That's it! That's gonna work!
- Thanks, Ray.
- Okay.
"Rebecca Silver knows as much about love
as a teenage boy's sock drawer".
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
Okay, bad reviews, they
just come with celebrity.
You should have heard what
they said about my perfume
when it made people
bleed out their noses.
[GRUNTS] He's gonna get
more than a bloody nose.
No, don't stoop to his level.
Inside every troll is the heart of a fan
just dying for some attention.
And some swag.
One signed book and he'll be
a Rebecca Silver Stan forever.
♪ Ta-da ♪
- [CHUCKLES]
- What's that?
Oh, this is a TV show I used
to watch when I was a kid.
Really helped me dig deep
and communicate my feelings better.
It's called "Mister
Parker's Cul De Sac",
and I think you're really gonna like it.
[RELAXING MUSIC]
♪♪
Hi.
♪ Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend ♪
♪ That's a street that
ends in a circle ♪
♪ The thing about circles
is, they never end ♪
♪ So our friendship will be universal ♪
This is very dumb.
Hi, boys and girls.
Oh, well, just give it a chance, okay?
Today we're going to have
ourselves a wonderful...
And... [CLEARS THROAT]
- How about 20 bucks?
- We get to spend together.
I'll be right back.
Have you ever imagined what it'd be like
to live underwater?
- [DOOR WHOOSHES]
- [SIGHS]
- Ah!
- [HISSES]
So? Bachelor party?
No.
Nora's dad literally
came back from the dead
- and ruined the evening.
- Damien Darhk? Ooh.
Anyway, Nora said she can handle it
and so she's handling it,
but we can't let anyone interfere,
especially not Sara.
I mean, he is your future father-in-law.
You don't think we could talk Sara down?
If I see Damien Darhk,
I'm gonna kill him for good this time.
What about Nora?
Well, ideally she never finds out.
- Gideon, any hits?
- Yes, Captain.
In fact, I'm detecting
new Encore activity
at Constantine's home in 2020.
All right, let's do this discreetly.
Just us, no boys.
You know how sentimental they can get.
- Yep.
- You also received a call
from a wild dog while you were away.
Yep, got it. Thanks, Gideon.
What was that all about?
Oh, I'm sure it's nothing.
This is extremely pornographic.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[COMPUTER CHIMES]
Ooh, troll made a post. Must
have gotten his swag bag.
Oh, look.
He's showing off your signature.
This is perfect.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[GASPS]
What the...
Oh!
Oh, that little punk!
Okay, change of tactic.
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- What are you doing?
Scouring the metadata from his post
- to composite his location.
- You hack?
No.
- ♪♪
- _
[KNOCKING]
♪♪
- It's a girl.
- It's okay. Just go.
- Do you know who I am?
- Yeah.
What are you doing here, Becky?
I'm Rebecca Silver,
and you will listen to
me, you pimple-faced...
- But she doesn't have pimples.
- Just go with it.
- Keep going.
- I'm a celebrated author.
My latest novel was a
triumph, and you know it.
Uh, wh-what the hell have
you done with your life,
and who are you to judge others?
- Mick?
- Ali!
- Mick, wh-why are you here?
- Why are you here?
I live here. [STAMMERS]
Why is she filming us?
This your kid?
♪♪
Well, I guess since you're here,
I might as well tell you.
She's your kid too.
This is Lita, your daughter.
♪♪
[BODY THUDS]
Twist!
Oh, he's fine.
Mm.
Well, that was my wizard's tower.
I love it.
You can just smell the dark forces
- at work in here.
- Mm.
[SNIFFS DEEPLY] Ah. Ooh!
- Safe neighborhood?
- Super safe.
People just mostly keep to themselves.
Good.
You know what the worst
kind of neighbors are?
- Hmm?
- Kids.
Ooh, I hate kids.
You know, all I've ever
asked for are neighbors
- I don't have to kill.
- Mm.
But for people like us,
sometimes it's kill or be killed.
- You know what?
- Hmm?
- Better safe than sorry.
- [LOCK CLICKS]
Right, Dad?
- Attagirl.
- Did she see us?
I don't know.
[TENSE MUSIC]
- [CLICKING]
- What was that?
You know what?
I have a surprise for you in the study.
Oh, well, hey. I love surprises!
♪♪
Yes, I saw you!
Listen, I know you're
here to kill my dad,
and I know you have good reason,
but I'm asking you as my friends
just to give me this one
night to handle it my way.
And what exactly is your way?
[LAUGHING]
Dad, may I present my... henchmen?
Women. Just people.
- Henchpeople.
- Wait a minute.
Are you saying the
head of the Time Bureau
and the captain of the Waverider
work for you now?
Well, I can be very convincing.
♪♪
Ooh.
[LAUGHS]
That is a heck of a find.
Mm-hmm.
11th-century Mongolia,
if I'm not mistaken.
Oh, yeah, that's just a little something
they picked up for me. Thanks.
It's not for indoor use,
though, so I'm just gonna...
Safety first, Nora doll.
[METAL CLINKING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
- Thanks, you guys, for playing along.
- _
Ticktock, ladies.
I could really use
that cocktail about now.
Remind me again why I
shouldn't go in there
right now and stab
him with Khan's sword.
He's my dad.
He's also one of the most
powerful dark warlocks
- on the planet, so...
- Wait.
What if he was just a man?
- Hmm?
- What?
There's a potion that can
strip him of his powers.
It's complicated to make,
but there are ingredients
here in this house.
I know we can make it work.
We can put it in his dinner.
[DOOR CLATTERS]
- I volunteer as tribute.
- Gary?
What the hell are you doing in there?
I was cowering from the men
who almost killed me with the train.
[ALL EXHALE]
Give me the recipe to your potion.
- I will not fail you.
- Bad idea.
- Uh-huh.
- Do it for Book Club.
- What?
- Are you seriously invoking
- Book Club right now?
- Yeah.
You get one of those. You get one.
Are you sure?
Ava, I am invoking Book
Club to ask you to give me
one night with my dad,
and if he is a harmless,
normal man by the end of it...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You let him live.
[BOARD SCRAPING]
Where you going, Captain Cold?
Antarctica, of course.
Yeah, that place is the worst.
Well, I'm following up
on the lead that you...
[TENSE MUSIC]
Bloody shape-shifters.
- What?
- Charlie.
She used your face to send
me on some dead-end trail.
Sending me to Antarctica,
freeze my bloody ass off.
No.
I'm getting off this gormless jam jar.
Since there's no one
here that can help me,
I'll do it my way... alone.
[BOOT THUDS]
All right, I think I got
these stupid crostinis right.
How's the salad?
Uh, just needs to be dressed,
and then there's the soup.
How many courses did Ray have planned?
By my count, five.
Six if you include cocktails.
Come on, Ray!
Nobody gets laid after six courses.
Gary, how's the potion coming along?
Don't rush me; everything
has to be done precisely
- or it will not work!
- Okay.
- Are you talking entrée?
- It'll be done by dessert.
Then let's get this dinner started.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING] _
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Uh, hello, you've reached
the office of Sara Lance.
How can I help you?
Well, hello, Mr. Dog.
What is this in reference to?
- Mm, cheers.
- Hmm.
[SLURPING]
- Mmm.
- Oh, more crostinis.
- [PLATE CLATTERS]
[LAUGHS] These are delicious.
- Mm.
- Bloody hell.
- Gary!
- [COUGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[COUGHS]
♪♪
- Damien Darhk.
- John Constantine.
You know, I don't think we've
actually ever met before,
seeing as you're still breathing.
Ah, but you have died
before, though, right?
So what's about to happen
should feel a little, uh, familiar.
♪♪
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [SPEAKING LATIN]
- [GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪♪
- [LAUGHS]
- That was a heirloom, you...
- Stop it, both of you!
- This vagrant's trespassing!
This is my house, you plonker!
Your house? Nora, I thought...
Well...
Technically...
it is his house.
His name is on the title. [CHUCKLES]
But in practice...
It's our house.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Right, babe?
[WHISPERING] Just go with it.
Right, love... my love,
that is, because we are
indeed, uh, together.
Oh, Nora doll.
Here I thought you were all alone,
but now I know that you have
a powerful warlock in your life.
Johnny C, you bring it in here!
You rascal! [LAUGHS]
♪ The thing about circles
is, they never end ♪
♪ So our friendship will be universal ♪
Why does he keep changing his shoes?
Oh, changing his shoes
is a soothing ritual
which takes him from
one space to another.
Where's my fairy godmother?
She's busy with her father.
So why are you here and not there?
She asked me to give them space,
and I am respecting her boundaries.
She's hiding you from her dad.
Mr. Parker says you can
love whoever you want to love
- and to not be ashamed.
- [SCOFFS]
Well, you don't have
to quote season eight,
episode 15 to me, okay?
But look, she's not... I mean,
she's not trying to hide...
Fairy godmother! Fairy godmother!
- Come here right now!
- [SHUSHING]
- [SHIMMERING TONE]
- [SPUTTERS]
- It's too late. Too late.
- Damn it, Ray!
I said no summoning!
Do you have any idea how many
plates I'm spinning right now
- trying to keep my dad happy?
- Many.
But quick question.
Um, are you hiding me?
Of course I am.
I am telling him 1,000 lies right now
to make sure nobody gets killed.
Oh, well, um,
why not just tell him the truth?
Oh! Oh!
Why not just tell him the truth?
Um, okay.
Why don't I just tell
my megalomaniac dad
that his little girl is a slave
to the whims of children
and is schtupping an Eagle Scout?
That sounds amazing.
The longer you lie
about who you really are,
the harder it's gonna be when
the truth finally comes out.
Listen, can you just give
me this one night, okay?
Just help me out and
save the guilt trip?
Please, okay?
- Of course.
- Okay?
- Good?
- Of course.
Everything good? Ah, okay.
Great.
[SHIMMERING TONE]
Good night, boys and girls.
Do you need to change your shoes?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I think I do.
I named her Lita after, um...
Yeah, Lita Ford of the Runaways.
Sorry I never told you.
I actually looked you up after
I found out I was pregnant,
but you were in jail.
Again.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So it, um... it must
have been challenging, uh,
- raising a kid by yourself.
- I made it work.
I mean, sure, Lita
would ask about her dad,
- but whenever she did I...
- She would just say, you know,
"My standards were low and
his sperm count was high".
- [SNIFFS]
- Okay.
But, uh, when I learned that
Rebecca Silver was actually him,
I guess I let it slip that we
had hooked up at our reunion.
Lita's a smart kid.
Guess she figured it out.
Yeah, my dad writes crappy novels.
- They're brilliant.
- Debatable.
Either way, I still hate you.
Lita, he... he didn't know.
But I guess now that
the pussy cat's out of the pouch,
get to know one another and...
- [SCOFFS]
- Mm.
Sounds like fun.
[EQUIPMENT WHIRRING]
No. What the hell are you doing?
We were never here.
♪♪
- True story, that.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
I never knew that.
- [BOTH CHUCKLING]
- [SHIMMERING TONE]
- Wine!
- Ooh!
Good to see you two getting along.
Oh, we're just telling
stories, aren't we?
You know, I shouldn't be shocked
that you'd be drawn to a fellow
after your pop's old line of work.
Oh, well, you know me, Dad.
I can't help but keep
the family business going.
- That's my girl.
- Not that I could ever live up
to a great collector of artifacts
- such as yourself.
- Mm, mm.
Oh, but sadly some things
could never be found.
You take, for instance,
the Loom of Fate.
- [BANGS ON TABLE]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
I never did find that one.
That's because it was
scattered across the multiverse.
Oh, well, it's all on one Earth now...
- ours.
- Mm.
Intriguing.
Still, you need a Fate
to put it all together
- and operate it.
- Mm.
Right, sounds like there's no
point in even looking for it.
- Right, John?
- Yeah.
Especially with so many
exciting opportunities
to think about. Right, babe?
Yep, maybe not the time.
I'm sensing something juicy
bubbling with the help.
- Mm, no. I-I don't...
- [BOTTLE THUDS]
- Is there trouble in paradise?
- Know what?
It's none of your damn business.
Oh, sit and spill.
Uncle Damien wants to hear everything.
- No, they don't have to talk...
- You know what?
Someone forgot to tell their girlfriend
about a job offer they
received to work in Star City.
- Oh? Ooh.
- Babe.
- Permanently.
- [GASPS]
I was gonna talk to you about it
before it became permanent.
So you're actually considering it?
- Yes.
- I don't unders...
Okay, how is that supposed
to work with you there
and me one of Nora's henchpeople?
Sara, she's right.
You know, long-distance
relationships can be tough.
Thank you.
It wasn't going to be a
long-distance relationship.
I thought that we could go together.
This is why I always have
a "no fraternizing" policy
- with my staff.
- Mm.
- Next course, please!
[TENSE MUSIC]
The potion is now
purple and therefore...
ready to depower the supervillain.
[RUMBLING]
♪♪
So let me get this straight.
You stood up for yourself
and she shut you down?
She just doesn't think
that Damien would accept me.
But aren't you setting yourself up
for a lifetime of lies?
Will you have to lie
when Damien comes to visit
or when you guys have kids?
Because you know those babies
are gonna have that
beautiful Palmer jawline.
The Palmer jawline is a dominant gene.
- Damn right.
- [SIGHS]
- Am I rushing into this?
- Yes!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
We couldn't say something
unless you said something.
Ray...
It feels rushed.
She's embarrassed of you,
after you made the perfect dinner,
took a massage class,
and hid an engagement
ring in the mousse?
[SPITS] The ring is in the mousse!
Mm, well, I hope you
saved room for dessert.
[GASPS] Chocolate mousse.
ALL: Mmm-mmm-mmm!
Yum.
- Yeah, you should try it.
- Mmm.
There's no chocolate in hell. Mousse.
- What are you do...
- Hmm?
- What's that?
- Mmm!
Chocolate mousse.
This has always been
your favorite, right, Dad?
Mm-hmm, this just looks sinful.
ALL: Mmm.
Everybody, isn't this delicious?
Perfection!
[COUGHING]
A ring?
Well, that's unexpected.
[LIGHT MUSIC]
♪♪
I'm surmising that perhaps that cup
was put in front of the wrong person.
John, was there a question
that you wanted to ask?
Question?
Oh, right, yeah. Um...
[CLEARS THROAT] The question, of course.
- [LAUGHS]
- [CHAIR SCRAPES]
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Nora Darhk, uh, will you marry me?
Ooh! Oh, God!
Just when I thought this
night couldn't get any better.
My daughter has found
the love of her life.
Forget the mousse. More champagne!
- No.
- What?
What? I'm sorry, what was that?
I'm sorry, I thought you said no.
- No.
- [CHUCKLES]
Sh... I know she... she just said...
I thought she... did she say no?
No, I won't marry John,
'cause I can't lie to you anymore, Dad.
Oh, thank God.
No, Johnny C, Johnny C, Johnny C!
Don't... don't... why?
What are you doing?
Dad, Sara and Ava aren't my henchwomen.
They're just my friends.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
And I'm not a powerful sorceress.
♪♪
I'm a fairy godmother.
Dad, this isn't my house.
John isn't my boyfriend.
He is.
- [CHUCKLES]
- And I love him madly.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Damie... Mr. Darhk, since you're here,
I was wondering if I
could get your blessing
to have your daughter's
hand in marriage.
♪♪
You deceived me, Nora doll.
Your own father.
[SIZZLING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪♪
You tried to poison me.
That's... that's not as bad as it looks.
[SQUEALING]
I've been gone for less
than two years, and you...
you're a completely different person.
[SIGHS]
♪♪
And I know who's to blame.
- [GROANS]
- No, no, no, no, no, no, Dad!
Stop! Stop!
- [SPEAKING LATIN]
- Brexit!
[GASPS]
- Go!
- Let him go!
Stop, Dad!
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[BOTH GAGGING]
Dad, I am not a child!
You can't just kill my friends anymore!
♪♪
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
Did you think you were gonna kill me
with that little toy, Lance?
Why don't you give me
a chance to find out?
L...
[WHOOSHING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪♪
[GASPING]
[WHOOSHING]
That's no Mongolian relic.
[SIGHS]
That's a Hell Sword.
My, oh, my.
I am so going to enjoy
obliterating all of you.
♪ It's after 5:00 and I
could use a cold one ♪
Is Mr. Parker getting tipsy?
I mean, the guy has done
4,000 hours of children's television.
He's earned it.
Oi, how have you guys not
noticed the Encore alarm?
BOTH: Oh!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
It's at Constantine's house.
- Ray.
- Let's go.
I wanna go.
ALL: No.
I wish it.
[SHIMMERING TONE]
[ALL GAGGING]
[SPEAKING LATIN]
[BOTH SHOUTING]
[ALL GROANING]
[SHIMMERING TONE]
[BOTH GROANING]
Now, that guy is marriage material.
Quit insulting Ray!
He made you poison your own father!
No, he didn't! That was my idea!
That's because he twisted you.
Look at you. You're a powerless fairy.
- Oh!
- That's it!
- Pippa, make a wish.
- Yes, you can stop this.
This is the only way you'll learn.
[WHOOSHING]
I wish you were all
on "Mister Parker's Cul De Sac".
[SHIMMERING TONE]
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
♪♪
♪ Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend ♪
♪ That's a street that ends in a circle ♪
♪ The thing about circles
is, they never end ♪
♪ So our friendship will be universal ♪
♪♪
Hello, boys and girls.
Hi, Mr. Parker.
Hope you're having a wonderful day.
I sure am.
Come with me.
[WHOOSHING]
What the... [GROWLS]
Ah, boys and girls,
please welcome my
friends Nora and Damien.
Now, why don't we discuss our problems?
Damien, what seems to be on your mind?
Well, you simpleton,
my child means everything to me,
and you've completely
corrupted her into this!
See, this is why I had to lie.
I knew you couldn't handle
it because emotionally,
- you're the child.
- [GROANS]
Well, I think this is gonna be tougher
than we thought, kids.
Why don't we travel to
the land of Make 'Em Ups
with Gary the Unspeakable
Train Abomination?
- [TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
- A-chugga-chugga, chugga-chugga, chugga-chugga.
- Hi, Gary.
- Toot-toot, everybody!
- Toot-toot!
- [TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
Toot-toot to you.
Chugga-chugga, whee!
♪♪
[GASPS]
Ah.
Hello, John.
Hello, Charlie.
- Hey, Ava.
- Yes, Sara?
- Are you bloody kidding me?
- Puppets?
Again?
I wanted to say that I feel bad
that I made you feel bad.
Oh, well, maybe we should communicate.
I'm sorry I kept the job offer
in Puppet Star City a secret.
I was only considering
it because I thought you
- wanted to settle down.
- Well, I used to want that,
but I've been having a
lot of fun on the ship.
Oh, then I'll tell Puppet
Wild Dog to shove it!
BOTH: Yay!
Maybe you can work out your
problem with communication.
Yeah!
You were gonna send me to
the South Pole, Charlie.
You don't understand how dangerous
that Loom is, John-o.
It gave my sisters and me control
over everyone's lives.
Now, I smashed that
thing so we could be free.
People could be free
rebel, free to be weird.
Oh, come on, Charlie.
If you sensed that the Loom
was in one universe again,
what's to say your
sisters didn't feel it too?
And what's to stop them going after it
for the wrong reasons?
Listen, I will use
the Loom to help Astra,
and then I will help you
destroy it forever this time.
Forever.
Deal?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Deal.
BOTH: Yay for communication
and cooperation!
Yay! [CLAPPING]
- [DOORBELL RINGING]
- Oh!
I wonder who that is.
- [BIKE BELL RINGING]
- It's bike messenger Behrad.
I hope you're having a wonderful day.
- Let's see what was delivered.
- Open it!
Open it!
It's the Safe Space Sombrero.
Please make it stop. Make it just stop.
I am going to just... [GIBBERING]
Only the person wearing the
Safe Space Sombrero may speak.
[GIBBERING]
[GRUMBLES]
You've ruined her life.
Her life is absolutely
in shambles because of you
and the idiot brigade
she hangs out with.
I mean, look at her!
She's trapped in this
horrible fairy godmother job!
- Horrible job?
- Mm-hmm.
You know what, Dad?
My life now, that's not Ray's choice.
It's mine.
I know you think all magic
should be self-serving,
but I like helping kids,
because being raised by a demon cult
instead of my own father...
that wasn't my choice.
That was yours.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So maybe working with kids
helps me cope with that.
And you're right.
I'm not the Nora doll you remember.
I like who I am,
and I'm never going back.
♪♪
I've been an ass.
I've had this vision of this...
life that would make you happy.
Obviously I was wrong.
I just want you to be proud of me.
Proud of...
Nora doll, I am.
Really?
♪♪
I really am.
[BELLS CHIMING]
Oh, kids, look!
The sun is smiling!
[GIGGLING]
I thought my family was messed up,
but these guys are truly deranged.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
I wanna be with my own family now.
Fairy godmother, I release you.
[SHIMMERING TONE]
It worked! [EXHALES SHARPLY]
I've been cured.
I'm not afraid of trains anymore!
No hard feelings, Ray?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Yes.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yes?
Yes. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. [GIGGLES]
I love you so much.
I'm so sorry I tried to hide you.
[GIGGLES] I can't wait to marry you.
I can't wait to marry you.
So let's... let's do it.
Let's do it. Let's do it right now.
- Right now?
- Right now.
I'm off duty. My dad's here.
His schedule's unpredictable,
so let's... let's... let's do it.
Right now. Tonight.
Yeah. Okay.
- Okay.
- [LAUGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
You're not married yet.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪♪
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
♪ You send my heart
higher than a firework ♪
♪ I can feel your adulation ♪
- ♪ Confetti falling down from the universe ♪
- Champagne?
I wanna tell you how much I appreciate
everything you've done for my daughter.
Thank you, but, um,
I haven't really done that much.
She's pretty incredible all on her own.
Yeah, but you make her happy.
That's something that
I ultimately failed at
when I was the main man in her life.
Well, you know, I-I think
you're being too hard on yourself.
I don't need a pep talk.
But I do need you to
do something for me.
- I need you to support her.
- Of course. Always.
No, I don't think you understand
what I'm trying to say.
Nora's job is very important to her,
and she can't do it on that
silly little ship of yours.
Nora belongs in the real world,
and you belong together.
I hope you understand what
I'm trying to say here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Do the right thing, son,
or I'll come back and get you.
[LAUGHS] I'm only kidding.
Okay. That's what I thought.
But not really.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
Eating your feelings, I see?
She's better off without me.
She reached out to you for a reason.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪♪
She's an idiot. I'm an idiot.
She's a pain in the ass.
I'm a pain in the ass.
The fact that she's not
already in juvie is a miracle,
- and it proves one thing.
- What?
- I'm no good for her.
- Are you sure about that?
♪♪
- You know what?
- Hmm?
You've inspired me to
forgo this evil thing.
Maybe this old dog can
learn some new tricks.
So you'll stick around for a bit?
Oh, I think it's time both of us
move on to the next chapter.
Promise you'll check in
on me once in a while?
Of course.
I'll never be far.
♪ I used to question everything ♪
♪ My eyes couldn't see ♪
I love you, Nora doll.
- ♪ Never been religious ♪
- I love you, Dad.
♪ Yeah, but now I believe ♪
♪♪
♪ You're the reason at
the end of the day ♪
♪ 'Cause I get to love you, babe ♪
♪♪
- Let's go.
- Okay.
♪ I get to love you, babe ♪
♪♪
- Hey!
- [APPLAUSE]
♪♪
[SIGHS]
- Taking off already?
- [CHUCKLES]
Oh, I hate prolonged good-byes.
I'd rather slip out
while everyone's in there
- still having a good time.
- Mm.
So where are you going?
I was given this Encore
under certain conditions.
I was ordered to cause pain and misery
and damn more souls to hell.
But instead you decided to
check in on your Nora doll.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I just wanted to make sure
that my little girl's okay,
and she is,
thanks to the help of you idiots.
Plus, Astra's gonna recall me
soon to an eternity of torture.
I didn't wanna bum my daughter out
with all of that on her wedding night.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
I know you'll never forgive me.
To tell you the truth... I won't either.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[SWORD SHINGS, ECHOES]
♪♪
[BLADE CLATTERS]
[CROW CAWING]
♪♪