- Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
- I'm Charlie.
We're The Smell. We're a band.
She's a shape-shifter.
Remember when we dented history?
I have encountered a glitch
during the Heyworld Event.
- Find me.
- Your sister is the dent.
Maybe her being here,
she'll remember who she was.
- [UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
- _
♪♪
_
Hope The Smell plays
"Assassination Nation" tonight.
Could give a rat's ass what they play,
long as Charlie isn't
AWOL two nights in a row.
♪♪
_
Six quid. Don't be cheeky.
- [GROANS]
- [BODY SQUELCHES]
[BODY THUDS]
♪♪
- [BODIES SQUELCHING]
- [VARIOUS PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Ian's dead, Dec.
We gotta get out of here
before that psycho finds us.
[BODY SQUELCHING]
♪♪
What do you want?
Clotho.
What the bloody hell's a Clotho?
The lead singer of your band.
You mean Charlie? She left days ago.
Don't hurt me.
My sister should know by
now she can't outrun Fate.
[RINGING LOUDLY]
[RINGING INTENSIFIES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[SHIP HUMMING]
Mm.
[DREAMY PIANO MUSIC]
[MOANS]
- Ah!
- BOTH: Ah!
- Wait.
Are we screaming because it's
weird or because it's awesome?
This is
a nightmare.
How did I even get in your room?
You slept-walked into Dr. Heywood's room
at approximately 2:30 a.m.
I tried to wake you,
but you assaulted my mainframe,
repeating Snooze.
Hey, let's just be
cool about this, okay?
I still have my pajamas on,
which means we didn't...
- Oh, my God.
- Take it easy.
You slept-walked into my room,
which means something must
have brought you in here.
And let's not forget, in
another timeline, you and I...
Don't start with the dream girl crap.
I'm still trying to process
how I spent the last five hours in...
- What is this, 200 thread count?
- Yeah.
I gotta go.
- Ah!
- You're up early.
Um. What are you doing?
Looks like somebody
was playing Operation
with Gideon's mainframe.
Or maybe it was something.
You think they have raccoons
in the Temporal Zone?
Actually, Mr. Tarazi, it was...
Snooze, Gidget.
Hey. You left this in my bedroom.
- Oh.
- Well, looky-looky.
- We did not hook up.
- We didn't hook up.
It doesn't have to be a walk
of shame if you enjoyed it.
But, if you are walking at all,
you didn't enjoy it enough.
Gross, Charlie.
Hey, B, uh. Me and Z did not do...
you know... the nasty.
This is a judgment-free zone.
I'm not one to shame the sexual activity
of two consenting adults.
Shame's a good thing.
Keeps you from hooking up
with someone and ending up
the parent of a 16-year-old daughter.
[PORTAL BUZZES]
Oh, ooh, well, what naughty business
have I stumbled across, then?
Uh, nothing. We just... we like, um,
hanging out in hallways.
Nothing, good-bye.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, then, Charlie.
We have some business
- to attend to, love.
- We do.
- But first, whiskey.
- All right, then.
A stiff drink may indeed be in order.
I have some rather unfortunate news
for you, Charlie.
[MUFFLED ROCK MUSIC]
♪♪
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Charlie.
We came as soon as we heard.
Look, the Prognosticator's
scanning the timeline
for Encore activity. Trust me,
we're gonna figure out
who's responsible for this.
This wasn't the work of an Encore.
This was my sister, Atropos.
How can you tell?
"The victim was burnt from the inside".
She's a god. That's her signature move.
Well, I'm sorry about
your friends, Charlie,
but, uh, your sister just fired
one hell of a warning shot.
Now we need to get back out there
and find that Loom
piece before she does.
God, will you just piss off, John?
[EXHALES]
Hey, Charlie. Look, I'm sorry.
I... I've lost friends, too.
I know what you're going through.
Look, I respect your condolences,
but you don't have a bloody clue
what I'm going through.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Well, she's right.
We're putting the hunt
for the Loom on hold.
And it's probably for the best.
With Ray gone, we're still
trying to find our feet.
That gives us time to make a game plan.
But we do have a game plan.
We need to get the next piece.
Look, John, if you wanna help,
then look into what we're up against.
She's a god.
I don't wanna take the team
into a situation we can't get out of.
Yeah, yeah. All right, all right.
I overstepped the mark, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
I am sorry, Charlie,
but my promise to Astra and her mum
cannot wait for your tears to dry.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Ostende mihi viam.
[RING AND PENDANT RESONATING]
Ah.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪♪
Welcome back,
sis.
Lachesis.
You smell of that slowly
dying world filled with apathy.
Any luck?
Clotho has taken on
a vulgar, mortal name:
Charlie.
Oh, this is too good to be true.
Elaborate.
My protégée, Astra,
happens to know of a time traveler
who's looking for our Loom.
One of his companions is a woman.
Goes by Charlie.
A time traveler.
That's how Clotho has eluded me.
Fortunately, I can
track John Constantine.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Without Fate,
mortals are making a
mess of their lives.
[PENDANT RINGS]
With our Loom, order can be restored.
Find John Constantine, and
you will find our sister.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
And when you do...
make it a hell of a family reunion.
Gideon, next time John
steals the jumpship,
a little heads-up would be nice.
Thanks to Ms. Tarazi,
I'm still stuck on snooze mode.
Is your sister just looking for you,
or is she looking for the Loom?
- Both, I reckon.
- [SIGHS]
- We have to go after him.
- We?
That bastard's the reason I'm mortal.
I don't owe him squat.
He's going after the ring.
You're the only one
who knows where he's headed.
Look, we'll be in and out.
Okay, fine. Soon as we get going,
the sooner I can get
back to drinking in peace.
Great, let's portal.
[PORTAL BUZZES]
Parenting sucks!
[AWKWARD MUSIC]
- Hmm.
- Maybe I should stay, huh?
Are you volunteering for Rory duty?
Ava Sharpe, you are
a better woman than I.
[PORTAL BUZZES]
Okay, babe. Catch you on the flip side.
- Stay safe.
- [EXHALES]
The ring's that way.
He couldn't have gotten too far.
Let's gear up in the jumpship.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Kid's not into bears, huh?
- She ripped its head off.
- Yeah, I see that.
Well, like father, like daughter.
I mean, hey, you should be proud.
At least she's tough, like you.
She said I ruined her life.
Now I gotta portal back to
that stupid reunion party
and stop myself from sleeping with Ali.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There are so many reasons
- why that's a bad idea.
- Don't care.
Stop. You can't just erase
your daughter's existence, Mick.
There has to be another option.
What?
What if we go back
through the last 15 years,
and we... and we place you
into all of her key memories?
Like a highlight reel.
Yeah, I mean, it's kind
of what Rip did with me.
Programmed me with a bunch of memories
that added up to be a childhood.
It wasn't perfect,
but I turned out okay.
- She's not a clone.
- Ouch.
Yeah, she's not a hmm,
but she is programmable, in a sense.
- Won't work.
- Why?
I spent the first ten
years of her life in prison.
Right.
♪♪
I have an idea.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING] _
- [SIGHS]
You sure hid this one well.
Didn't think I'd ever be
coming back here, did I?
Huh. That's cool.
Looks like "Supernatural's"
filming here.
- Super-what?
- You've never seen it?
It's this show about
these two hot brothers
who fight demons.
I wonder if the Winchester
brothers are here!
- Seriously?
- Dean is my hall pass.
[SIGHS]
I bet you used to wild
out back in the day.
There was no drinking on the job.
It's kind of the occupational hazard
of having the Fate of
humanity in your hands.
So you guys literally
used to weave Fate?
I mean, it's not like
it is in the storybooks,
but yeah.
I spun up the threads of each life.
Old Lachesis... she measured
out how long each life got to be.
And then, Atropos, she...
- So she killed...
- Everyone.
[SIGHS] And she bloody loved it.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[CAT MEOWS]
[CURIOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
[VIDEO GAME CHATTER]
- Hello?
- Greetings, sibling of mine.
Meow?
You okay, Z? Is this
about the Nate thing?
I hope not, because then I'm
wondering why you just said,
"Meow", and I definitely
don't want to know.
[HEAVY BREATHING] I
think I may be losing it,
and not like when I saw Tupac's hologram
at the 2044 Grammy's.
But, like, mentally losing it.
Something is wrong with me.
Hey, hey. Deep breaths.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
This is like a form of therapy
where you get to beat up your problems.
Trust me.
[VIDEO GAME CHATTER]
[VIDEO GAME GRUNTING]
- [GASPS]
- Whoa, did you just beat me?
Behrad, I don't know
how to play video games.
But it's like I'm being haunted
by someone who does,
someone who dresses like a teenage boy
and makes me do awful
things like eat donuts
and... cuddle with Nate.
[AIR TOTEM ACTIVATES]
BOTH: Whoa.
[WIND BLASTING]
- How did you do that?
- How did I do that?
[PENDANT RINGING]
Well, what have we got here?
[CALM ROCK MUSIC]
♪♪
[GRUNTS] Oh!
What the bloody hell is that?
- It's a prop.
- [EXCLAIMS]
And what did I tell
you about Loom patrol?
Yeah, well, we're out here, aren't we?
So let's just find the damn thing.
Oh, yeah, have you scanned
the woods for activity?
Huh? Do you have a plan
if Atropos shows up?
Ah, well, I clipped
Charlie's shapeshifter wings,
so, no offense, love,
I think I can handle her sister.
Have you not heard
anything Charlie's said?
'Cause it's not gonna be that easy.
- Clotho.
- [WINCES]
You are my responsibility,
and I say we are going back
to figure out a secure way to do this.
Yeah, well that Loom is your
ticket to stopping the Encores.
You can't hide from your family.
Guys!
[EXPLOSION]
Jumpship.
- [FEEDBACK]
- [WINCES]
I'm coming for you, Clotho.
My sister.
She's here.
Ava, we need backup. Ava?
Damn it, with the jumpship
gone, the comms are down.
What, so we're stuck here?
The team will come
looking for us eventually.
We need these more than Sam and Dean.
You've walked us right
into a bloody death trap.
And that was my only option, all right?
If she gets her hand on
one piece of the Loom,
then she can get the next, and
then she's that much closer
to controlling us all.
And I'll bet my bottom dollar
she's out there now looking for it,
not standing around having a row
in the middle of the bloody forest.
Damn it, John.
The stupid thing's that way.
By building Heyworld,
we changed the future,
which caused the
bifurcation of the timeline
radiating from that one moment.
Think of it as a
historical traffic accident,
and you're the dents.
Yeah, I'm not thinking
of myself as a dent.
Okay, so what you think of as a haunting
is a temporal echo.
She is the you before, well, you.
Okay, let's just get something straight.
There is only one Zari Tarazi.
I filed a trademark.
Do you know what this means?
You were a Legend.
From what you said about the hacking,
you were probably our computer expert.
And the air totem responded to you.
You two probably shared it.
BOTH: [GASP] Wonder twins.
And we probably had a really
super cute couple name.
Just off the top of my head,
probably something like SteelHacker.
Three of us probably
hung out all the time...
- Ah.
- Getting stoned...
- Oh, man!
- Playing ring toss with donuts.
She probably helped you save the world.
- More than once.
- Yeah.
She sounds pretty cool, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, she does.
We've gotta move faster.
She could be anywhere.
- [FEEDBACK]
- Clotho.
You can't escape.
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
We need to keep moving, love.
- Where are you?
- [FEEDBACK]
Come to me,
or your friends will die.
[TWIGS SNAPPING]
Charlie?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
_
Uh-oh. Mick?
What?
I think Ali was discharged
from the hospital early,
because a taxicab
just pulled up outside.
Wait, this is supposed to be a s...
Surprise.
Is that what they're gonna say
at Iron Heights when
they find your empty cell?
What the hell are you doing here, Mick?
Oh, uh, hi. I'm Ava Sharpe.
I'm Mr. Rory's CO.
Yeah, I arranged for some visitation
in exchange for some information.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Mr. Rory's helped us bring in
- some of history's most dangerous criminals.
- What?
- Yup.
- Okay, well, visiting hours are over.
- Me and my baby are tired.
- Right.
Wow.
Ah. From Victorian England times...
Collection. Collection at Pottery Barn.
I don't know much
about Victorian England,
but it's really beautiful.
I bet she is too.
[BABY COOS]
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
Mick, meet your daughter.
[BABY COOS]
Mmm.
Lita.
Hey, how about we all get together
so that Lita can remember this moment
with her dad forever? Yeah?
Let's take a picture.
Aww, Mickey!
[SQUEALS]
[COOING]
Smiles!
Wait a minute. Did you
break into my house?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
- Garibba lifted the king's decapitated head.
- _
[CHUCKLES]
Dumb bastard. [CHUCKLES]
You like that?
- Daddy?
- _
Ah!
Do you believe in the Tooth Fairy?
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- Yay.
♪♪
Whoa!
_
Say cheese.
- ♪♪
- _
- [FLAMES WHOOSH]
[SMOKE ALARM BEEPING]
Say cheese.
_
Kirk, we can get you new pants.
How's that for a highlight reel?
[GIGGLES] Pretty good.
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪♪
Hello, Clotho.
Look at you, alone,
after destroying our family.
Look, I didn't do it
to hurt you, all right?
We took care of you, and
you took everything we had.
People deserve to be free.
And what have they done with
this freedom you gave them?
They got women the vote.
They invented punk rock.
Introduced mass genocide,
nuclear bombs, pollution,
- systematic incarceration.
- No, I didn't...
And after all you did to help them,
how did they thank you?
[EXHALES]
By locking you in prison.
We would never let anyone hurt
you like that, little sister.
Now lead me to our Loom,
and perhaps, in time,
we can forgive you.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
Hey!
Why don't you pick on
someone your own size?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
John, I could use a little help!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm on it, I'm on it.
Where'd you go? Hemlock!
All right, yes. Oh!
Toadstool. Got it.
[GRUNTING]
Now all I need is a little bit of...
blood.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Te vocare, veni in auxilium mihi.
- [WINDS SWIRLING]
- [LEAVES RUSTLING]
♪♪
Go, grab Charlie. Get
the hell out of here.
I'll find ya!
You're gonna be okay. Come on.
♪♪
- [GRUNTS]
- [FLAMES IGNITING]
♪♪
Hey. Let's wait for John here.
John's dead, Sara.
Atropos doesn't let people live.
Come on. We've got to keep going.
- Look, it's okay.
- It's not.
I mean, you saw what
happened back there.
I'm one of them.
No matter what I do, I'm never
gonna be able to escape them,
and now I've gone and got John killed.
- Hey, look. John always finds a way.
- [LEAVES RUSTLING]
Always finds a way to do what?
- [BOTH GASP]
- Oh, thank God.
Yeah, I'd rather not, love.
[GRUNTS]
Well, your sister... she's
a nasty piece of work,
but it takes more than
amateur knife tricks
to do me in.
Well, let's get the hell
out of here, shall we?
Before she realizes I'm not bleeding out
on the forest floor.
[SERENE MUSIC]
[SERENE MUSIC TURNS TO EERIE MUSIC]
♪♪
Who are you?
Talking to donuts now?
LOL.
This alternate timeline stuff's got you
really shaken up, huh?
Ever since Mithra came into my life,
I've been the center of attention.
It's weird to have to
share the spotlight.
Says the older sister
to the younger brother.
Right. Sorry.
Back to me. It's a lot to take in.
I mean, this other Zari sounds so...
smart and substantive,
like a cool, third-wave
feminist superhero
that you and Nate seem
to like better than me.
First off, Nate is just a sucker
for doomed romances.
Secondly, of course
I don't like her better than you.
You're my favorite Zari of all time.
But...
But?
You said you wanted to leave
your whole Z-Nation life behind,
find out what else you're capable of.
This whole situation seems like
a gift-wrapped opportunity
for self-exploration.
Self-exploration?
I propose a totem quest.
Go into the totem,
speak to our ancestors.
Mm-hmm. Um, how do I go into the totem?
- With a little psychotropic assistance.
- Hmm.
I knew this would lead to drugs.
It's totally safe.
I've done it in the past
when I've been wrestling
with a big problem.
It's no crazier than talking to a donut.
I know that face!
That's the one where you
don't want to admit I'm right.
No, it isn't.
- Totem-town, here we come.
- Hmm.
[SCOFFS] She played me like a fiddle.
I almost gave her the loom.
Family knows all of our weaknesses.
I don't know. Maybe she's right.
- I belong with them.
- Come on, Charlie.
I'm a coward, Sara.
I can't even stand up to my own sister.
Hey, listen to me.
No one is responsible
for the family they are born into.
All that matters is
who they decide to be,
and you've decided to
be brave and big-hearted.
[TENDER MUSIC]
Thanks, boss.
But I am what I am.
♪♪
[SIGHS] She's gonna love it.
_
- Surprise.
- What's this?
[GRUNTS]
Nice, it's a keepsake album
so I can never forget all the
times that you bailed on me.
Well, I was in prison...
Not since 2015.
You know I never actually
went to homecoming.
I went back inside to get my purse,
and when I came back out, you were gone.
And I kept telling Kirk to wait
because I wanted to say good-bye to you,
but you had bailed. Like always.
So keep it.
Fine.
Uh, and there is that
patented Mick Rory fade.
You know, good old dad.
Just run away like you always do, yeah?
Wait. W-w-w-w-wait... I...
[SIGHS] I'm sorry.
Rory, it was a terrible idea,
and I never should've
suggested it, okay?
Rory, we can... listen
to me. We can fix this.
- No, we can't.
- Yes, we can.
I... look, I made a mistake
and I feel really bad,
but that doesn't give us
the right to keep hurting Lita
any more than we already have. Right?
Maybe it's not about the gifts,
and the money,
and the big birthday parties, you know?
I think it's time that
you go back in there
and do what we should've
done from the beginning.
Go back and kick myself in the...
No. No.
Just go tell her you're sorry.
Hmm. Guess you're right.
No shortcuts.
- [TENSE MUSIC]
- [BIRDS SQUAWKING]
What happened to this place?
Whoa.
[MUSIC SWELLS]
Oh, it's the crew!
Wait, if they're dead,
who's shooting season 15?
You leave a piece of the Loom of Fate
somewhere long enough,
there's gonna be consequences.
Don't worry about it. I'll nab it.
No, John.
Look, this is my mess, all right?
I'll do it.
Look, all I've gotta
do is run over there,
put my hand in that hole,
grab the ring, and Bob's your uncle.
All right, well then let's go,
before your sister shows up.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[MINOR TRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
♪♪
[PORTAL BUZZES]
- Uhh, what's going on?
- Shh.
Hey, girl.
Zari just took some Lyoga root.
She needs a little totem
trip to figure out her stuff.
Uh, Gideon, what's the
status with the away-team?
The jumpship is not responding.
Gideon, we talked about this.
Un-snooze. You need to tell me
about things before
they happen, not after.
Okay, we should help them.
Ooh, ooh. I feel high already.
Is it too late to detox?
That's the fun of drugs.
You can't un-take them.
- Hmm.
- Besides, this is important.
Everything's gonna be fine, sis.
Okay.
I surrender. [BREATHES DEEPLY]
[WONDROUS MUSIC]
♪♪
Hello?
Ancestors?
Where are all the old people at?
Who you calling old?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So, if you're here, does that mean
Maman and Baba... Behrad?
Oh, B's back on the Waverider.
Who do you think gave me the drugs?
He's alive.
Yeah, of course. Maman and Baba too.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
So why are you even
asking me about Behrad?
I thought this was about me
and the strange visions
I've been having.
Wow.
New me came out
shockingly self-absorbed.
Who are you calling the new you?
Who even are you?
Well... you,
if the Legends hadn't saved the world,
and you grew up in dystopian Seattle.
Once the timeline crystallized,
you were out in the real world,
and I was thrown in here
with the rest of the totem bearers.
Wait, does that mean Nate was right?
[SIGHS] Are you the cooler me?
Ugh. [SIGHS]
We have a lot to talk about.
♪♪
Hey, do carbs count if
you eat them in a totem?
- Nope.
- Ah.
♪♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GROANS]
- [FIRE WHOOSHES]
- Whoa!
- [ZOMBIE ROARS]
- Ah!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ZOMBIE GROANING]
♪♪
[EXHALES] Thanks.
[ZOMBIES GROANING]
[BODY SQUELCHES]
- [GRUNTING]
- [ZOMBIES GROANING]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
Okay.
♪♪
[SQUISHING]
Yes. I got it!
[YELPS]
Charlie!
♪♪
Sara, no!
[RINGING LOUDLY]
No!
[RINGING INTENSIFIES]
Sara, no!
♪♪
[BODY THUDS]
[EERIE MUSIC]
[LABORED BREATHING]
You're bleeding.
You're mortal, just like them.
Pathetic.
- [BODY SQUELCHES]
- [GROANING]
Apologize, and we can heal you.
We can restore order to this madness.
I like the madness. Sara was right.
I'm no Fate. I'm a Legend!
And now she's dead,
which makes you nothing.
♪♪
- [BODY SQUELCHING]
- Ow!
You'll never find the other pieces.
[RING HUMMING AND RESONATING]
♪♪
[RING RESONATING]
No...
Once again, your humans
have let you down.
Good-bye, little sister.
[LABORED BREATHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
So, um...
How are things with Nate?
Hmm, um, good. You know.
Yeah. Super, super cool.
Weird to feel jealous of myself.
Well, don't be too jealous.
Sorry, are you not together?
He's my brother's best friend.
It would... it would be weird.
Sorry. He and Behrad are friends?
They have this ridiculous handshake.
It's sweet.
Behrad, a Legend.
I wish I could see that.
You must be disappointed.
Yeah, I was hoping Totem-town
would have a few video games.
No, I mean disappointed in me.
Why?
I mean, you were a superhero
who wielded a totem and saved the world,
twice.
I'm just a failed Cat-Chat celebrity.
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
My family's alive.
And you... you actually
seem like a lot of fun.
♪♪
I'm good with that.
They could be anywhere out here.
Sara! Charlie!
[LABORED BREATHING]
[ZOMBIE GROANING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[ZOMBIE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- [BODY SQUELCHING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [EXHALES]
- [BODY THUDS]
I thought you were dead.
Me too.
My sister... she's...
she's heading for the ship.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[RING RESONATING]
[DISQUIETING MUSIC]
♪♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- Uh, Ava?
We have a problem.
There is a very slinky lady
in a red leather pantsuit on the ship,
which usually I would I would be into,
but she's giving off a super
"I wanna kill you in the
worst possible way" vibe.
Oh, my God. That must
be Charlie's sister.
Listen, you need to wake up
Zari and get off the ship.
Already on it.
Ava, come quick!
♪♪
[GASPS] Oh, my God.
- I think he's dead.
- [COUGHING]
- Oh!
- Don't count me out so soon,
handsome. [GROANS]
The forest is a natural apothecary.
[HUSHED] Zari. Zari!
Wake up. Wake up.
Zari. Wake up.
Zari. Zari!
Where's the ring?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hey.
Look, since you're Charlie's sister,
can't we just be cool about all this?
[BOTH RINGS RESONATING]
♪♪
You two share blood.
She's your sister.
Yeah.
Pretty.
I'm taking the ring. Whether
she dies is up to you.
♪♪
[RING CHIMING]
You don't belong here.
[LIGHTS SHATTERING]
No more defying Fate.
No!
♪♪
Behrad.
- Is he?
- Get the ship in the air.
- She's still on the ship.
- Just do it!
♪♪
You're not getting off this ship alive.
You saw my true form and survived.
What are you?
Your worst nightmare.
[GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SWORD RINGS]
♪♪
- [SWORD RINGS]
- [BODY SQUELCHES]
You can't kill me.
I'm a god.
Yeah? I've faced worse.
Gideon, you'd better be awake,
'cause I need you to open the doors now!
- [ALARM BLARING]
- [GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Fate's a bitch, innit?
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC CALMS]
♪♪
Not bad.
Nice.
Come back soon.
Maybe next time, bring Behrad.
I'd like that.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪♪
[EXHALES]
Oh, my God, guys. I just had
the most amazing experience.
Where's Behrad?
Z, um...
What's going on?
Where is...
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
Oh, my God.
♪♪
Behrad.
Behrad, Behrad, joon... Behrad.
[SOBBING]
How did this happen?
How did you let this happen?
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪♪
[INAUDIBLE SOBBING]
He's dead.
Wait, who's dead?
Behrad.
You got us into this mess,
and now he's dead because of you.
Can that Loom bring him back?
If we get the last piece, yeah.
- Great. Get up, let's go.
- H... hold on a second.
It's not that simple, all right?
We're being hunted by
a pair of bloody gods.
This situation just got a
hell of a lot more dicey.
I can handle dicey!
I can handle whatever it
takes to save my brother.
And until you bring him back,
I am with you every minute
of every damn day.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Greg, move your head.