Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
- It's a dragon egg.
- You're possessed.
Ray's gone. I've taken over his body.
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would have killed him on the spot.
I need you to open up a doorway to hell.
It's to bring someone
here from the other side.
Tabitha.
I'm sorry. It wasn't
me. It was my nipple.
- Save me!
- As you wish.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Do you really think
that everyone in hell
deserves to be there?
This is your opportunity
to make things right.
I'm gonna save Ray.
Honey, time to go.
Come on, honey, let's
go. We're gonna be late.
Zari? You better not
be eating the Halva.
No, Mommy.
Zari Jaan.
Dessert's not for after breakfast.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
What?
It's only a kick.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Behrad must be anxious to meet you.
Now go put your shoes on
so I can take you to school.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
[ON TV] You might just
want to soak it all in.
Violent people are pouring
into our country...
illegal immigrants,
terrorists, meta-humans.
Politicians promise to keep you safe
but they've been hiding the truth.
There's a dangerous new threat
already within our borders.
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer.
Yes, that Ray Palmer...
former CEO of Palmer Tech.
And I am here to warn you
that creatures once thought only
in legends and fairy tales are real.
[SCREAMS, GROWLS]
Yes, folks, monsters are real,
and they walk amongst us.
And they will stop at nothing
until they destroy humankind.
Interested in learning more?
Then join me at PalmerX 2019,
where the power is in
the Palmer of your hands.
[GROWLING]
I don't care if Neron's
wearing my best friend's face.
- I want to punch him.
- Get in line.
Ogres are big softies... that
one wouldn't even hurt a fly.
Neron's been a step
ahead of us for too long.
- We need to play offense.
- Agreed.
Sorry, what are we agreeing to?
Look, it's time for us to fight back.
We're retaking the Bureau.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Gideon, pull up the
blueprints at the Bureau
and start fabricating an arsenal.
- Right away, Captain.
- Look, Gary has bonded
with the Fairy Godmother, and
while he might be an idiot,
she is not to be underestimated.
Mick, Nate, you think
you can handle Tabitha?
- Granny's dead.
- Good.
Ava and I will handle Neron.
Yeah, I want a crack at him.
It's my bureau he's
running his operation from.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but even John and Nora
couldn't out-magic Neron.
- I just felt a kick.
- Oh, I want to feel!
Right now the smart play
would be just to bide our time.
Wait for John-o to
return with Ray's soul.
Shockingly, I agree with Charlie.
- I love you, little Wicksty...
- Oh, I felt it!
I told you, it's kicking.
Okay, can you guys stop being
dragon-baby crazy right now?
Look, this commercial
is proof that Neron
is up to something big, and we need
to stop him before it's too late.
Captain, I have an incoming
communication from Nora Darhk.
- [SIGHS] Put her on.
- Sara?
Talk to me. What's your status?
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
I'm tired of skulking around air ducts.
- I'm going after Mona.
- [ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. We're gearing up
for an assault. Hold your position.
- Hey! [SCREAMS]
- Too late.
- Wait, where's Gary?
- In Ava's office...
getting real comfortable.
Mmm.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
[WHOOSHING]
Yes, my pet?
I want to dig deeper on my next wish.
Excellent idea. What
do you have in mind?
[MELLOW MUSIC]
Well...
we've already redecorated my office.
I now have three nipples
because a spare never hurts, and...
Perhaps you could make a
wish regarding the Legends?
You want me to wish something for them?
I'm talking about revenge.
- Oh.
- They lied to you, Gary.
Promised you could be an interim Legend.
One wish, and you can send them
all to hell with John Constantine.
Speaking of John, you
think he's all right?
That warlock sent thousands
of demons to rot in the pits.
[LAUGHS] I think he's well
and truly screwed, dearie.
[CHUCKLES]
[SCREAMING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Does this mean we're straight?
I got a more important
collection to make.
♪
Who is that guy?
That, my friend, is John Constantine...
in the flesh.
[ENGINE TURNING OVER]
Congratulations, Mona.
I have selected you for
a very special assignment.
That's okay, Ne-Ray.
Can I call you that? I'm okay here.
You see, before Nate's
father decided he wanted to be
P.T. Barnum, we were working together,
training monsters to do our bidding.
Actually, I worked extensively
with your dear friend Konane...
I mean... [CHUCKLES]
Your dead friend Konane.
[GROWLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SCREAMS]
I found Mona. Hurry.
♪
Copy that.
This seems like overkill.
The Legends never included
me in their pizza parties...
or asked me to play Dungeons & Dragons.
Make them suffer, Gary.
I can make them do whatever you want.
I just wanted to be part of the team.
As soon as Ava opens the portal,
we go in firing.
Time to burn some freaks.
I wish...
Opening a portal in three, two, one.
♪
- [MONA SCREAMING]
- No.
♪
Welcome to book club.
[KAZOO PLAYS]
- Why, you little...
- [CLICKING TONGUE]
I'd be careful how
you speak to my charge.
Gary, why are you doing this?
Because I would like to discuss...
"The Collector."
- [GROANS]
- Forget the book, Gary.
You helped a demon take
control of the Bureau.
What happened to the Bureau creed?
Oh, I could ask the same about you.
Article 27? Hmm?
A supervisor must never show favoritism?
You started a book club
with another employee.
Gary, Mona is being tortured right now.
Neron said he's trying to protect
humans from monsters.
You saw Mona gnaw off my nip.
- She did you a favor.
- Okay, um...
maybe we should just reschedule
until after we've read the book?
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Oh, no. Wait.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[CHUCKLES]
♪
- Ow.
- [GROANS] Book was terrible.
Oh, my head.
That's the spirit.
Sara, Ava, come in. Where are you guys?
Hey, Nate. Can't talk right now.
Are you talking to Nate on comms?
Tell him I say hi.
Gary says hi.
And we are at book club.
[MUFFLED] Move on to plan B.
- What's plan B?
- I only listen for my name.
I assume it's like plan A,
but, you know, with less people.
Well, without the Captain and the clone,
the Bureau's a suicide mission.
Mick's right.
We need to sneak into PalmerX,
do some recon, find
out what Neron is up to.
Now that sounds like a plan Z.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING, INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪
- Mmm.
- Hey, baby.
Hey, you looking for
a good time, handsome?
I'm always looking
for a good time, love,
but, uh, regrettably,
my time here is limited.
Maybe you can help me.
I'm looking for broker
in the soul trade.
He goes by the name of Masher.
I might know something.
Well, this here is holy water.
Now, you can use this to burn the skin
off any demon tosser
who messes with you.
Uh-uh-uh.
Masher likes to hang
out at the strip club
after trading is done...
John.
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know who you are.
Half of demonkind is
searching for John Constantine.
♪
The holy water?
Oh, this? Nah, this
is just whisky, love.
♪
Sure, our protagonist
was keeping people hostage, but...
that's only because he never
received love as a child.
Aah!
They don't want you in
their book club, Gary.
Doesn't that make you angry?
Make a wish, and they will pay.
[TENSE MUSIC]
You're right. They
don't want to spend time
with Gary Green, lowly
Time Bureau agent.
But they would love to spend time
with Gary Green...
Captain of the Waverider!
♪
Welcome aboard, Captain Green.
[CHUCKLES]
Thanks.
I have no quarrel with you, dear.
You didn't send me to hell
like John Constantine and the Legends.
Yes...
I was in hell for 327 years.
And what was my crime?
I sprinkled a little magic over Salem,
trying to help a girl whose mother
was accused of witchcraft.
Okay, well, you're out now.
Why help Neron?
Neron rescued me in hell.
What can I say?
True love bloomed.
I know what you're thinking...
he's so much older than me.
Sometimes you have to look past age.
You know, in another life,
I think you and I
could have been friends.
- Toodles.
- Wait, wha...
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
Ray?
Without all of the idiotic tendencies.
[GRUNTS]
Make a move on me, and Mona dies.
Ray is good and strong.
He can fight his way back from hell.
[CHUCKLES] Who do you think
is having a worse time in hell?
Ray, or your father?
Turns out Daddy dearest isn't so tough.
I hear Damien Darhk is going
stark raving mad in the pits.
Why am I here?
Well, you and John tried
to kill me... nearly did.
If the doofus in the
skin suit I'm wearing
hadn't have interrupted,
I'd have been obliterated.
I spent many nights just dreaming
about how I was going to get my revenge.
And then it came to me...
what better punishment
than making you sit front row
to all of the fear and rage
I'm about to unleash on the Earth,
all while in the body
of the man you love.
♪
Now...
[REPORTERS SHOUTING]
Smile for the cameras.
- ALL: Mr. Palmer!
- Are monsters real?
What's tonight all about?
Now, all of your questions
will be answered soon.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
- Oh. Excuse me.
- What's wrong with you?
Well, you know, a room full of people
fearful of magical creatures
just makes me a little
bit fearful, all right?
The worst part is,
Ray loves tech events.
♪
Good evening, D.C., and welcome
to PalmerX 2019.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Now, you're all probably wondering,
what in the heck is Ray Palmer
doing back in the public eye?
Well, folks, for the past
two years I have been hunting
magical creatures.
[CROWD MURMURING]
Hang with me here.
I have created an exosuit
capable of combating
the most ferocious of their kind.
What a douche.
But I can't do it
alone. I need your help.
I need you to help me
find these creatures...
creatures that may be
hiding right here amongst us.
Now, everyone take out your smartphones.
Better be Palmer Tech. [CHUCKLES]
I have created a small, simple app,
that will change the world.
And I want you all to
download it right now.
The app is called Eyes.
Now, on Eyes, you will be
able to share real-time,
life-saving monster sightings.
Share them, and I will
be there to save you.
Remember, the power
is in the Palmer of your hands.
You really expect us to
believe monsters exist?
I thought you were
going to offer us proof.
Thank you, Cindy. You
are absolutely right.
Here is your proof.
Now, this may look
like a helpless hipster
who should be working at a bookstore,
but believe me, she is something
altogether more dangerous.
[GROWLING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Masher.
- John?
Yeah, yeah, all right,
keep your hair on.
No need to tell the whole bloody club.
Oh, buddy, now I know
you're out of your mind.
- What are you doing in hell?
- I'm here to save a friend.
His soul belongs to Neron.
Cheers, love. He's paying.
Nobody gets into Neron's
soul vault without his say-so.
Except the Triumvirate,
and I have a plan
to deal with them, but
first, there's a hunch
I need to confirm.
What's Neron trading at?
He's steady, but I'll let
you in on a little secret.
His stock is about to rise.
I'm talking a massive
soul collection on Earth.
You know what that means?
Neron is finally making his play
for the throne of hell.
Oh, cheers, Masher. I can use that.
Be careful, John.
Not every demon you've sent to hell
is as forgiving as I am.
Yeah, don't I know it.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC]
♪
You're dead, demon hunter.
I was going to be a demon proctologist,
but the pay wasn't as good.
♪
- Hold him.
- Oh!
Oh, Calibraxis. Hey, looking good, mate.
- You grow your beard?
- John Constantine.
I'm really going to enjoy
watching you breathe your last.
I invoke a parlay.
I demand to speak to the Triumvirate.
I'm a demon, not a pirate, John.
I thought you understood the rules.
Well, you little maggot,
as long as I'm alive,
then the Triumvirate can pass me around
like a little sparrow amongst the cats.
But as soon as I die,
you dim-witted dick,
then my soul belongs to Neron,
and then the Triumvirate lose out
on all the tasty little bits of torture
that they've got planned for me.
So you've got two choices:
You can either kill me
and royally piss off the
old bags that run this place,
or take me to speak
with the Triumvirate.
♪
I'm detecting a fugitive
alert... stop it...
at the Inquisition, Captain Green.
Oh, I don't do torture.
- Could've fooled me.
- Hey. Play nice.
We have to distract Gary
while the B team is plan B... ing.
Would a fairy at the
Great British Bakeoff
suit your fancy?
Shall we, uh...
keep calm and pastry on?
[LAUGHS] I'll plot a course, Captain.
Get it?
"Keep calm and pastry on"?
- [BOTH LAUGH MOCKINGLY]
- Good one, Cap.
- Hilarious.
- Thanks, guys.
Thanks. Yeah.
Take a good, long
look at her... Mona Wu.
You saw her on the street,
you wouldn't think twice.
Come on, Mona. Don't
give him what he wants.
But she has a strange
and violent condition...
brought about when she fell in love
with a repulsive creature.
I feel like a bridge scene
should have more people.
Oh, no, we love
three-people bridge scenes.
Yeah, otherwise we just end
up standing around all day.
Oh, that's why Mick's always grumpy.
Come on, Mona.
I promised these fine people a show.
Let's not keep them waiting.
♪
Shift now or end up dead like Konane.
[GROANING]
♪
[SCREAMING]
Folks, proof
of the world's very first werewolf.
- [ROARING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
♪
That's what we're missing... the boys!
- No.
- Yeah.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ROARS]
♪
Fairy Godmother?
- Z.
- B.
[PEOPLE GASP]
- She made him disappear!
- Well, well, well...
what do we have here?
More magic in the audience?
- She's one of them!
- [GASPS]
He's right. I am.
♪
She's a witch. Witch. Witch.
[ALL CHANTING] Witch, witch, witch!
Witch, witch...
Don't worry, folks.
The witch won't get far.
Not as long as everyone
downloads the Eyes app.
Share your sightings.
We'll find the witch.
It's only a matter of time.
♪
[ENGINE THRUMMING]
Sara, you guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine, as long
as we keep placating Gary.
I guess Charlie and Z are our last hope.
- Great, we're toast.
- Welcome to hell.
Good evening, this is
your captain speaking.
[MUSICAL FLOURISH]
- Just...
- [MOUTHS WORDS]
What?
We'll be cruising at a high altitude
on our way to save a bakeoff in Britain.
- Whoo, yeah.
- Yeah.
Gary, is that the Kid Steel costume?
Uh-huh.
You like-y?
Why would anyone wish to be a sidekick?
- Close your legs.
- Oh, he's such an idiot.
- What?
- [BOTH LAUGH MOCKINGLY]
Nothing, they're just teasing you.
- Oh.
- You're my Gar-bear.
We're gonna have so much fun.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Okay?
#EyesApp is trending on Twitter
below Kanye's surprise album
and a cat getting a bath.
Mm. How many downloads?
Only 2,000, Mr. Palmer.
News cycle is so fast these days,
it's hard to cut through all the noise.
But a monster attack on the capital
will dominate the headlines for weeks.
And then what?
More people will download some app?
That's your big plan?
Why, yes, it is.
Ah! My love.
Would you please escort our guest
to a cell?
Let's go, dearie.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Neron didn't say which
containment cell to put you in.
Why are you helping me?
Because you're a fellow witch,
and I think we can help each other.
♪
Mona?
How do you feel?
I've been better.
Remember, I'm just a
"Fairy Godmother" away.
[WHOOSHING]
Trust me, we'll be safe here.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Where are we?
My childhood home.
I thought you grew up
in a dystopian city, Z.
You had a pool?
In a couple years,
A.R.G.U.S. will use people's
growing fear of meta-humans
to seize control.
Of course, it didn't
help that we were Muslim.
We were forced to move to
a ghetto district in 2021.
Humans are so easy to manipulate.
I mean, you just show them a scary ogre
or a dangerous meta, they just go barmy.
Haven't even been able to
get into the Eyes app yet
because the terms of
service are so long.
No one bothers reading those.
It's a demon app. I'm
gonna read the fine print.
[SIGHS] I can't believe
it's just us left.
I mean, you and I both
knew from the start
that it was madness to storm the Bureau.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Z?
In New Orleans,
John said Neron needed more
souls to take over hell.
Here it says in
exchange for the service,
the user agrees to
forfeit their eternal soul
to the demon Neron.
What, you're saying that anyone
who downloads the app is going to hell?
Yeah.
Oh, that is mental.
This little fairy was
causing quite the fray
around the soufflé. [CHUCKLES]
- [LAUGHS AWKWARDLY]
- I think I know
just the place for you, madame.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna kill him.
Hey, Z, Charlie, please
tell me you have something.
Well, we figured out Neron's
app is a way to collect souls.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah, it gets crazier.
To drum up fear and increase
downloads of his app,
we think he may be
planning a monster attack.
Okay, well, we'll stall Gary,
but you got to get every
single one of those monsters
out of the Time Bureau.
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
- Who are you talking to, Sara?
- What?
[CLEARS THROAT] Gary!
Baby, bubby, bubelah.
[LAUGHS] There's a whole
big world of problems.
You know, Neron and
your Fairy Godmother,
they're not really your friends, but...
Do you know who your friends are?
These guys.
Huh?
Are you trying to schmooze me?
Feels good, right?
Uh, actually, it feels a little false.
Gary! You are our friend.
I mean, would we lie
to an interim Legend?
Ah, you see, that's just it,
because I'm not an interim Legend.
You just promised me
that to use me as bait.
- Pfft.
- You know what, Gary?
It's a little hard to feel sorry for you
when you're holding us all hostage.
You're not getting it.
This whole time, Tabitha has been trying
to use me to hurt you.
All I wished was for us to hang out.
I was trying to protect you.
I get it. I'm not cool.
But I don't deserve to
be treated like a joke.
So, now...
now the joke's on you.
- What's he talking about?
- Oh, Fairy Godmother!
[WHOOSHING]
Yes, my pet?
Mick thinks he's a tough guy,
but I think he's a big baby.
[LULLABY MUSIC]
♪
And Nate, who's never been
bullied a day in his life,
welcome to my high-school years.
[WHOOSHING]
[GASPS]
And, Sara and Ava,
the cool girl and the class president,
you know what I want you to do for me?
Dance!
[WHOOSHING]
Five, six, seven, eight.
[RAGTIME MUSIC]
♪
Faster!
Gary, stop it!
♪
Faster!
Charlie, I get that you're scared,
but the team is counting on us.
I'm not scared. It's
just, breaking the monsters
out of the prison is
a multiple-person job.
- You can be multiple people.
- Look, Z, yeah, I can,
for a second, and you know what?
It takes its toll.
Now, I could end up back in prison
or even worse, dead.
When A.R.G.U.S. came for my family,
my brother, Behrad, told me to run.
And I did.
I've never forgiven myself.
You won't either.
We can't change my family's future,
but we can save their present.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Zari Jaan, make sure
you take your shoes
off before you go in.
- I know.
- Charlie?
If I die, I'm gonna
come back and haunt you.
I would love a ghost friend.
Come on.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[CRINKLING]
Cool.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[BELL TOLLING]
♪
Greetings, Satan, first of the fallen.
It's been a long time, John.
Belial.
We've been looking forward
to hearing the bunk you're pedaling.
And Beelzebub.
Not as popular, but you were
always my personal favorite.
This is a waste of our time.
I take it you've noticed
a certain demon's stock
has been on the rise.
Neron's been doing
very well for himself.
Neron is trying to take control of hell.
And let me assure you,
his method for collecting souls,
it won't be to sign on
the dotted line in blood.
He's, uh, young,
by your standards at least.
And let's just say, he
means to disrupt the system.
If we interfere with
Neron, we'll look weak.
Well, that's precisely
where I come in, Bubby.
And what do you want in exchange?
Not your own soul, I hope.
I'm here for the soul of Raymond Palmer.
You let us two leave
hell, and I pledge to you
that I will dedicate all
of my crafty, wicked ways
to thwarting Neron and
securing your reign.
Are you really here
for Raymond Palmer?
♪
We thought there was another...
A young girl whose life you destroyed.
Astra.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well, you know, I
didn't want to be too greedy.
But, yeah, I'll take them both.
Both of them?
That is greedy.
But if you were to choose,
well, then that's a different matter.
John, help me.
John, you're here. You got
to get me back to Earth.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Please, John. They're hurting me.
Make up your mind, John.
This offer won't last.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[ECHOING] John?
- Astra?
- It's following me!
Make it go away!
[WHOOSHING]
Come here, I've got you.
You can't have her!
You can't save her.
You can't have her! You can't have her!
John, get me out of here!
[SCREAMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm sorry.
I choose...
Astra Logue.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Stick to the plan, Charlie.
You mean the plan where I need to rely
on my shoddy shape-shifting
to portal creatures one by one
out of their cells and
on to the Waverider,
where Gary may or may not
wish them to Kingdom Come?
Yep, that plan.
[RAGTIME MUSIC]
[LISPING] This isn't you, Gary.
Why are you being so cruel?
Please!
[MUFFLED] Stop! You're killing them!
[TENSE MUSIC]
I don't do mime, dearie.
Just stop! Everything!
[SIGHS] As you wish...
[WHOOSHING]
- Ooh.
- Ugh.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Huh.
Mona? Hey, wake up.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[WEAKLY] Hey, Nora.
Hey.
Oh, you're still here.
I'm book club forever.
Book club forever.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
Uh, I have to pop off
for a second, Gary.
I thought we were going to
play Settlers of Catan later.
Don't be silly.
We're not friends.
Oh.
I am so sorry, Gary.
I took you for granted.
I never, ever should have let you
do my dry cleaning or
work overtime without pay.
I mean, that's illegal anyway.
I'm so sorry.
I still want to kill you.
Gary, when Rip first
recruited the Legends,
he picked the people
that were insignificant
to history... the original losers.
You don't have to be
cool to be a Legend.
And maybe we forgot that
somewhere along the way, but...
- you are one of us.
- Now, come on, Gary.
Ray and Constantine
are both stuck in hell,
and you can help them.
Just use your Fairy
Godmother powers for good.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[WHOOSHING]
Save her.
Sadly, my hands are tied.
But if you become
Mona's Fairy Godmother,
she could wish to be healed.
How do I do that?
If another witch takes the wand...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You'll take my curse...
but with it, all of my power.
[WEAKLY] Nora.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Nora, no.
No...
♪
Oh, it worked.
Quick, Mona. Make a wish.
Wow.
Uh, Fairy God-Nora,
I wish to be safe on the Waverider.
[CACKLING]
Oh, how I've missed me.
Sadly for you,
when you took on the wand's
power and responsibility,
you also took on its charge.
- Gary?
- I'm afraid so.
[GRUNTS]
Fairy Godmothers are prisoners.
Their magic is dependent on whiny humans
and their petty demands.
You lied.
Obviously.
Toodles.
♪
[WHOOSHING]
[CLEARS THROAT] Excuse me.
- Oh. Marilyn Monroe?
- Why, yes.
I seem to have gotten a little lost.
Can you help me get back home?
[STAMMERS] Of course, ma'am.
Let me just program in a year.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[BODY THUDS]
Ah. Yeah. Uh... [MUTTERS]
♪
Thank you, sir.
Oh, my love! My love.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Uh, still no luck with Nora?
- No.
- Oh.
Well, she'll take your curse soon.
After all, you are very convincing.
Well, I better head back.
Evil deeds to do and all that.
♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY, SNIFFS] No.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
♪
Well, that was bloody close.
I'm at the first cell. Anytime now, Z.
Okay, just give me one second.
The public doesn't always
know what's best for them.
So tonight we will release the Minotaur
and scare them into
accepting our protection.
It is done, mon amour.
How do I look?
But you were just...
Oh, the shape-shifter.
♪
Can someone sound the alarm?
[ALARM BLARING]
Charlie, Tabitha and Neron are onto you.
Yeah, I figured.
You need to get out now.
Open all the doors, turn
off the force fields.
I'm not leaving.
[FORCE FIELDS SHUDDERING]
♪
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
[ROARING]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
♪
Are you waiting for an invitation?
It's a bloody jailbreak!
[ENGINE THRUMMING]
I mean, there are pros
to trusting your apologies
are sincere, and cons.
- [GRUNTING]
- Maybe I'll make a list.
Gary... Gary, just go with your heart.
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
[WHOOSHING]
- Nora.
- Oh...
Go find John and help
him rescue Ray from hell.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
- ALL: Wait, wait!
- Gary!
Gary, you dick!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [SIGHS]
- Oh.
♪
Come on, you lot. Get a move on.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Faster, sassy!
♪
You're all right, little one.
Oi, ogre. Catch!
[GROWLING]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Charlie, you're out of time.
Z, get out of here. See
you on the other side.
I'm going after Mona.
♪
Mona.
- [GROANS SOFTLY]
- Come on, my love.
- Let's get you out of here.
- [GRUNTS]
♪
Ugh. I hate shape-shifters.
Break her neck.
Patience, mon amour.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Get Mona.
No!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Looks like things ain't
going so well for you, Neron.
You wanted a monster to attack D.C.
Now we have every single monster...
in one.
♪
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
You promised me you'd
take me to see Astra.
Patience, John.
I made a pledge to you, and I expect you
to keep your end of the bargain.
♪
What the hell are you playing at?
John?
John, is it really you?
Yes. Yes, Astra, love.
It's me. It's me. This is Johnny.
Thank God...
God? You know better than to thank Him.
♪
Astra?
John is here to take you back to Earth.
You're welcome to go.
Yeah. It's all right, love. It's me.
♪
No.
Wait.
Hold on.
What do you mean no?
Looks like the deal is null and void.
Neron is a thorn in our side, John,
but torturing you...
is too much fun.
[ECHOING] John?
It's following me.
Make it go away!
Please!
John, get me out of here!
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Astra, love.
- This isn't you.
- Oh, of course it is.
Or would you rather I stayed
that terrified little girl,
crying and waiting for
you to come and rescue me?
I would have been waiting a long time.
I am so, so sorry, love, but...
this place, it's twisted you.
If anything...
it's made me more like you.
Right, John?
You're not like me.
You're not.
You chose wrong.
You should have saved your friend.
♪
[DOOR CLANKS OPEN]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[BLADE CLINKS]
[CHUCKLES]
♪
- [SCREAMING]
- [BLADE SLICES]
Hey, watch it! Back off, freak!
It's like a demented Noah's Ark.
What about Charlie?
It's my fault. I'm the
one that convinced her
to risk everything.
Hey, don't go down that road.
We'll do what we always do.
Yeah, forming stupid Beebos.
[SNARLING]
Hey, where are you going?
Well, after everything, I just figured
you wouldn't want to
have me around anymore.
It's all hands on deck, Gary.
Yeah.
We're gonna need all our
friends to defeat Neron.
Aye, aye.
You all right?
Not really.
I'm glad you and Wicksty are okay.
[TENSE MUSIC]
What happened?
Oh, my God.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
Hi.
My name is Zari.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --