Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
An unknown number of other
dangerous magical beings
got spat out across the timeline
and now must be sent to hell.
[CHANTING]
Your shapeshifting days
are over, sweetheart.
- No!
- Is that a Kaupe?
This is a prison, Mona.
And they are our prisoners.
Not our friends.
People around me get hurt, killed,
or far, far worse.
But you can't mess with your past.
Dez.
[LAUGHTER, CHATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Order up.
Next one. [CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
♪ I want a little more ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Ah-whoo ♪
Oi, oi!
Wake up, John-O.
Piss off, will you?
Oh, not today, you lying geezer!
[SQUELCHING]
What the...
Now, you said that
my shapeshifting days were over.
You call that abomination
shapeshifting, do you?
Well, if I can shift at all,
that means that your
spell is reversible.
You see, that's where
you're wrong, sweetheart.
There's no taking it back.
Smart man like you, John-O,
you can figure it out.
Yeah, well...
mortal life is full of disappointments.
Best get used to it, love.
It's all right.
That's all right.
You know how I survived
in the prison dimension?
Trading favors.
Now, sooner or later,
you're gonna need something from me.
Then we'll talk, chum.
[SCOFFS QUIETLY]
Thanks for staying at
my place this time.
Oh, I love sleeping next to you.
I just wish that your place didn't mean
sharing a bathroom with...
Beer.
- Yes, Garima.
- Beer.
It's the only word Rory taught her.
Wait, Rory's still using Brigid's diary?
That thing is an
ancient magical artifact.
Yeah, but it keeps him happy.
Sara, be reasonable.
You can't let Rory keep the diary.
I see you've met Garima.
What she lacks in vocabulary
she makes up for in personality.
And everyone knows that a happy Mick
is better for the entire ship.
Whoa.
Oh.
Killer 'stache.
- Interesting.
- You think?
I had Gideon stimulate my hair follicles
to grow it overnight.
I read in one of Nora's letters
that she had a thing
for mustaches, so I...
Sorry, but how are we all being so blasé
about the diary?
What if Rory goes from
writing sci-fi to horror?
Do you want killer clowns
running around the ship?
The only killer on this ship
is the amount of sugar in this cereal.
"Big Easy-O's"?
They taste like beignets.
So sweet it makes your lips pucker.
- Oh!
- There's a quiz on the back.
Who is the most prolific serial killer
- in the United States?
- Ted Bundy.
Although in my opinion John Wayne Gacy
had way more victims than he confessed.
What?
Everyone has their hobbies.
Well, sorry, Ava, but according to
this not-so-kid-friendly cereal,
is answer is New
Orleans' own Marie Laveau.
What?
A high-profile female serial killer?
No, I would have heard of her.
The box is wrong.
Unless...
Gideon?
You are correct, Captain.
It appears a Fugitive is on the loose
in New Orleans in 1856.
According to local lore,
there were a series of murders
perpetrated by a criminal
who could walk through walls.
Sounds like we're going mindhunting
in the Big Easy.
Gideon, plot a course.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[THUD]
Ah...
Ow... [GROANS]
Ugh.
Unbelievable.
You just ran into my car, earmuffs.
[STAMMERING] But your car...
This scratch will easily
cost you a couple hundos.
You want me to pay for it?
Yes.
No worries, sir.
I can have the money tomorrow.
They really need to stop
giving delivery girls drive-ons.
I'm actually Assistant Coordinator
of Creature Upkeep.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[GROANS]
Ahoy, matey.
It seem to be pirate day
once again, ya scurvy wench.
- Argh.
Don't be late again or Ava will give you
another peg leg.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hey, Catch-a-Predator, what was that?
Well, that, my fellow rebound artist,
- was flirting.
- Oh, Gary.
That was not flirting.
- No.
- What do you mean?
I mean, I made extended eye contact,
picked up on some personal information,
and then I negged her.
All right, don't tell me
you're falling for this, like,
Neanderthal misogynistic dating advice.
You're a modern man
surfing the sexual spectrum.
Just be cool and ask her out.
Or, and I'm just spitballing here,
you can ask her out for me.
This isn't high school.
[SNAPPING]
Oh, sorry.
High school's a bit of
a trigger word for me.
Wow. You are really broken.
Okay, look, I will...
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm not gonna ask her out.
But I will do some recon.
You'll be my time-bro wingman?
See, you do things like that,
and it makes it very
hard to help you, Gary.
All right, Legends.
Next stop, "N'awlins."
We have a Fugitive serial
killer, and it's a weird one.
Yeah, it says here
that all of the victims
were wealthy blonde ladies
stabbed to death inside
their locked bedrooms.
Spooky.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Blondes killed in locked rooms.
That's the MO of Mike the Spike.
Am I gonna find a murder
board in your closet?
New Orleans is a crap town.
Although anything's better
than that tush tickler.
This?
Well, the cops pinned it
on voodoo priestess Marie Laveau,
one of the only women of color
with power living in 1856.
Surprise, surprise.
You stole my diary, weasel.
Oh, you mean the one that
you nicked from my trunk?
That one, eh?
Gentlemen. Gentlemen, gentlemen.
I "mustache" you both to calm down.
Get out of my way,
otherwise I'll knock that fur ball
off your lip.
I confiscated the diary.
It's Time Bureau property now.
Don't worry, Rory.
Garima will always be
right where she belongs.
In your imagination.
Garima...
Rory, look. I'm sorry.
Ava was just doing her job,
which is exactly what
the rest of us need to do.
Ray, Mick, we're gonna protect
the Fugitive's first victim,
Miss Didi Charbonnet.
She's hosting a party this afternoon.
John, I need you to talk to Laveau.
Find out how she's mixed up in all this.
I'll go with him. Yeah.
I love me some voodoo.
- Great.
- Zari, you're on their mission.
You can just say the B-team.
No, there's no...
There's no such thing as B-team.
But there is such thing as an A-team.
Laissez les bons temps rouler!
[SWEEPING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Belles calas, toutes chaudes!
Wow, this doesn't
even look like America.
Oh, it's not.
This is New Orleans, baby.
You've been here before?
After London, best city in the world.
I mean, just look at this
hodgepodge of humanity.
It's the perfect place to pick a face
and just have some fun.
[DRAMATIC TONES]
[LAUGHING]
[ECHOES, LAUGHTER]
John?
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just, uh...
This city just brings
back memories, is all.
[MOURNFUL BRASS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Monsieur Constantine.
Would you come with me, please?
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I'm not really in the habit
of going home with strangers, mate.
At least not recently.
Ugh. Not again.
[GASPING]
Oh, what...
Oh, no.
This is not good.
[GRUNTING]
Bloody New Orleans!
[GASPING, COUGHING]
[COUGHING]
Ah, Priestess Laveau.
Oh, cheers, love.
You saved me the trouble of finding you.
That was a little bit theatrical,
to be honest with you, but then again,
I do appreciate a flair
for the dramatic.
Arretez.
- [GRUNTS]
- You have something of mine.
Oh, I have no idea what you're on about.
I felt its presence as soon
as you arrived in New Orleans.
This medallion honors Saint Marron,
the patron saint of runaway slaves.
Now, what do you know
about bondage, mon cher?
Buy me a pint at the local pub,
and I'll tell you all about it, love.
You don't have to say a thing.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[DISTORTED SPEECH]
I am back, and it is time
for me to cook you breakfast.
One full English coming up.
Hey, Johnny.
♪ I hope that I'm forgiven ♪
♪ ♪
Dez, you, uh...
you have to leave town.
This thing that's after me,
it's no ordinary demon.
This medallion has been in
my family for generations.
It's imbued with a protection spell.
Take it, Johnny.
As long as you promise
to leave town.
It's just until I get this
mess sorted out, all right?
- All right.
[PANTING]
My great-great-grandson.
He must have loved you
to give you my medallion.
Did you love him?
[LAUGHTER, CHATTER]
Does anyone have eyes on
the Fugitive's first victim?
Annoying blonde in the middle.
- That's Didi Charbonnet.
- [GIGGLING]
Good. Stay with her.
According to Gideon, the murder
is going to happen within the hour.
What kind of Fugitive stabs a woman?
I know a woman I could stab.
Rhymes with Shava.
Rory, play nice.
Don't worry, I can handle myself
against the cretin.
Whatever, man-pants.
Hey.
Look, I know you're
mad at Ava right now,
but she's right.
The diary is not a toy.
Garima helped me write.
Would you just try to
be nice to her, please?
For me?
Guys, keep an eye on the
creepy ginger by the door.
Copy that.
We have a possible Fugitive alert.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Gideon, we can't find
John, and he's not on comms.
Mr. Constantine has refused to wear
his communications device.
Stupid blighter.
However, Captain Lance requested
I fabricate a tracker
in every pair of his undershorts.
That cheeky little minx.
Okay, great.
As soon as you trace
him, send us his location.
Tell me what happened to my Desmond.
A demon.
Neron.
Dez was collateral damage.
Just go ahead and curse me, all right?
'Cause I bloody deserve it.
Why would I curse the man
who could save the last of my line?
You don't understand.
Dez is gone.
No amount of magic can bring him back.
[GASPS]
Save my kin.
[RUSHING WIND]
Let him go!
Hey, hey, that's a nice rescue, loves,
but, uh, Priestess Laveau and I
were just, uh, just having
a little chat, weren't we?
Now to our business.
Have you sensed any
other magic in your city
besides my own and theirs?
I've sensed a spirit. A Dybbuk.
And, like you, from another time.
What's a Dybbuk?
It's the dislocated
soul of a dead person.
Someone so wicked that their
spirit never crossed over.
Sara? I don't think he's a Fugitive.
I think this guy's just
looking for the bathroom.
[SOFT CRYING]
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What's going on?
This doll...
is going to kill my mama.
This doll?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Sara, is it possible
that our Fugitive killer
is a possessed doll?
Horror movie 101.
♪ ♪
Well, hello, dolly.
[EERIE BREATHING]
[THUD]
[SHRIEKS]
♪ ♪
Wrong doll, ya dick!
Well, we'd best be going, then.
If we don't catch this Dybbuk
then the good people of New Orleans
will blame you for its mayhem.
I believe...
this belongs to you,
Monsieur Constantine.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Guys, this Fugitive
we're looking for is an evil spirit.
Crap.
Damn it, Ray, where the hell are you?
Ray?
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What happened?
[SOBS]
Sara, any sign of the Fugitive?
I think we may have a
Chucky situation here.
What does that mean?
I reckon the Dybbuk is in a doll.
Rory, Ava, Sara needs backup.
A word.
I'm all ears.
You, uh, still want
your powers back, yeah?
Come on then.
All right. Come on, big guy.
Sara...
Oh, I had the weirdest dream.
[PANTING] I dreamed that
I was attacked by a... doll!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm gonna kill you, Goldilocks!
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
♪ ♪
Agh!
[GROANING]
You're late.
Still moving. Kill it!
No, no, no, no, no.
We need to question it and find out
if it's really Mike the Spike.
Who are you?
Your worst nightmare.
[LAUGHING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Aloha.
I brought you some meat.
[SIGHS]
[GROWLING]
Oh, my cut.
Um...
I stupidly ran my bike
straight into this guy's car door.
No.
No, he didn't look before
he opened the car door.
[GRUMBLING]
I know, I know.
I shouldn't have to pay, but...
I don't want to lose
the world's best job.
[GRUMBLES SOFTLY]
You're a really good
listener, you know that?
[GIGGLES]
What happened?
Did someone hurt you?
♪ ♪
[WHIRRING]
So how does helping you
make me a shapeshifter again?
Well, it's simple, really.
If I never meet Desmond,
then this demon scum that's
after me doesn't hurt him,
which means that my guilt-ridden ass
never joins the Legends and
doesn't turn up to London
to give you a magical lobotomy.
- Now...
- Simple.
Now, the me from five months ago
is having a drink in there.
Now, I'll recognize you as Amaya.
All you have to do is
play the part, all right?
American accent, stick up my bum,
and in love with Nate.
Do me a favor, just...
Make sure I get out of there
before I meet Dez, all right?
- All right.
- Okay.
I'll meet you back on
the jumpship, John-O.
All right, Charlie-O.
Good luck.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
John?
As I live and breathe.
Amaya.
- Nice bonnet, love.
- Thank you.
Last I heard you were in, uh, Zambesi.
So where's Nate and the
rest of the crew, then?
Oh, Nate, my boyfriend.
And my crazy gang of best friends.
Oh, it is such a long story.
- Right.
- But a really good one.
How about I tell you all about it
over a glass of chardonnay?
Chardonnay, eh?
All right, barkeep!
Uh, no, no, not here.
I... I know a better place.
All right, well, you owe me dinner.
That is a fair price.
All right, go on.
Order up!
Hey, Mona.
How's life? Liking the Time Bureau?
Settling in? Dating anyone?
Uh, good, great, yes.
I mean, there is someone.
Lay it on Nate.
I think it might be inappropriate.
'Cause I work here.
And he's here too?
Wow.
Exactly.
Yeah, I think I know
who you're talking about,
and trust me, he has a crush on you too.
- He does?
- Mm-hmm.
I swore I was just imagining it.
We don't even, like,
speak the same language.
Well, he does have a unique way
of expressing himself.
I'm afraid people would
think it was weird.
I mean, that hair.
Well, he just needs the right product.
What about the man meat?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Um, well, what... What about it?
I think he's, you know...
[WHISPERING] Had some.
It wouldn't surprise me.
I mean, it's 2018. I don't judge.
Mm, I should probably forget about it.
No. Carpe datum.
What do you got to lose?
My job.
I will make sure you're not fired
for following your heart.
Okay. I'll do it.
I'm gonna let him know how I feel.
[LAUGHS]
One thing I learned
from the Chucky movies
is the doll always comes back.
Gideon, how's the timeline?
History is on track, and Marie Laveau
lived a long and celebrated life,
inspiring an Emmy-nominated portrayal
by Angela Bassett.
See? Rory killed the Dybbuk.
Which is unfortunate because
now I have to explain to Mr. Heywood
why I'm bringing him a seared doll
instead of a magical creature.
Well, at least we get to find out
why they call it the Big Easy.
Did you happen to notice that
Rory robbed that party blind?
I believe it.
I don't understand why
you enable his bad behavior.
At the Bureau, we would fire people
for lesser offenses.
[SIGHS] Well, at the Bureau,
you don't have to eat, drink,
and sleep with your team.
Point taken.
It's just... this is supposed to be
a professional operation, babe.
Look, deep down, Rory's a good guy.
And, honestly, a friend.
I get it.
You run your team, I'll run mine.
- Thank you.
- Speaking of,
I should get back to the Bureau.
How 'bout you stay for dinner?
I could use a shower.
Hmm.
It's not like that
thing's going anywhere.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So?
When are these changes
to history gonna set in?
'Cause you know I've got some big plans.
I'm actually thinking of Vegas first.
Well, time takes a moment to cement,
or so I'm told enough by Sara.
But don't worry, love,
we'll have you shapeshifting
again in no time.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DISTORTED CHITTERING]
John-O? You all good?
♪ ♪
We stopped me from meeting Dez tonight,
but now I meet him a
few days later instead.
We have to go back.
I'm afraid returning to New Orleans
is impossible, Mr. Constantine.
And why is that?
Because I know you two
are up to something.
And as much as I hate babysitting,
I hate being played even more.
Gideon, bring them
back to the Waverider.
They have some serious explaining to do.
♪ ♪
Here's one thing you need to understand,
is that I don't go in
for all that love crap.
Romance is for little girls
crying into their pillows,
not for a devious tosser like me
who knows the score.
But then...
six months ago, I met him.
Desmond.
[SOFT MUSIC]
And that first night was like
a second line had marched
into my useless heart
and breathed some life into it again.
Desmond knew who I was,
exactly what I'd done, and...
he didn't care.
So I was all in.
Rented an apartment.
And then this demon shows up.
Neron.
Wanted me to help him usurp
the triumvirate ruling hell.
Well, he must have had something
on you to expect that.
The deed to my soul.
When I die, the bastard owns me.
And he's already worked out lots of...
excruciating torments for
yours truly in the inferno.
So, naturally, I told Neron to piss off.
Naturally.
I begged Dez to run.
I knew that Neron would
use him against me.
[RUMBLING]
Johnny?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
The bloody fool didn't listen.
So Neron...
dragged Dez to hell because of me.
I didn't think there was
a way I could save him.
That's the thing about
time travel, right?
There's always a way.
I joined the Legends thinking
I could outrun my guilt,
but being back in New
Orleans, I realize...
I was just taking the coward's way out.
So I had to save him.
So.
Now that you, uh,
know what we was up to,
uh, do you mind explaining
why it didn't work?
Some points in history are fixed.
Maybe John and Desmond
were supposed to meet.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to find a loophole to save Desmond
and keep history intact.
You do that, love.
♪ ♪
[GRUMBLING]
I know.
Um, an unscheduled visit.
[GROWLING]
It's good to see you too.
- [GROWLING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
I brought you something.
Mm.
O... [LAUGHS SOFTLY]
Uh, "O... o mona...
ko'u inoa Mona."
[SOFT MUSIC]
O wai kou inoa?
Konane.
♪ ♪
Um...
"Shining like the moon."
That's a really pretty name.
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
♪ ♪
Mona.
Yep. Yep.
That's me. [LAUGHING NERVOUSLY]
[SNIFFING]
[GROWLING]
E holo a huna!
- A huna!
- Well, "a huna"...
- Uh...
- [GROWLING]
"Run and hide."
Is someone coming?
Mona.
[ALARMS BLARING]
[ROARS]
[MUFFLED ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
[CRACKLING]
[WHOOSHING]
Hello?
Is someone there?
[SIGHS]
[WHOOSHING]
[HUMMING]
[OMINOUS LAUGHTER]
Compelling story back there.
Still, you're hardly the
kind of guy to open up,
unless, of course, you were stalling.
Well, you see,
magic has rules, just like time travel,
and I just so happen to write the book
on breaking them.
So, if meeting Desmond
is a fixed point in time,
then I need to go back
to after I met him.
Stop him from falling for me.
That's how I save Desmond's life.
History be bloody damned.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
[DARK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS LAUGHTER]
Well, you went all-out.
What the hell is he doing here?
Leaving.
Wait.
Wait. Both of you.
Please look.
I roasted a roast.
Technically, Captain, I fabricated...
Shut up, Gideon.
Ava, you are my love,
and Mick, you are my family,
and it would mean the world to me
if both of you would try to get along.
Please.
So I was thinking...
maybe you two could
find some common ground.
- [CHUCKLES]
- For example...
Ava, you love to read.
Mick here is an author.
Oh. Well, that's something.
Though I would be shocked if his novel
wasn't sexist and derivative.
It is.
Okay, well,
Mick, you love to eat.
Ava is a fantastic baker.
She makes one mean snickerdoodle.
Fancy sugar cookies.
Snickerdoodles are actually
completely different.
It's a cream of tartar base, but...
- Garbage cookies.
- That's rich,
coming from a man who's so
lacking in personal hygiene
that he had to resort to sleeping with
a three-breasted alien sex toy.
Well, at least Garima isn't a clone.
Only I get to use the C word.
Too far, Mick. Too far.
Why do you get to
have a fake girlfriend,
and I don't?
Clone.
Dick.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SOFT MUSIC]
Hey.
Any luck?
I'm sorry, John. [SIGHS]
Sometimes with history,
if you change one thing,
it creates a whole domino effect.
It's all right.
Listen, I...
I get being tempted
to save someone you love.
The anger and frustration.
It's...
John?
Yep.
Turn around.
I... I'd rather not.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SQUELCHING]
[GROANS]
That is the last time that I try that.
I thought you couldn't...
You know what, it doesn't matter.
Where is John?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
The last time we did
something like this,
we almost destroyed the entire world.
All right, all right. Okay, enough.
How are you planning to find John?
Well, his tracker...
- Which you told him about.
- Yep.
Old John-O's changing history commando.
You know, I understand why John's being
so colossally stupid,
but what's your excuse?
I'm dying.
What?
Look, every time that I shapeshift,
it's like I'm born all over again.
But stuck in this body
for the first time in centuries,
I'm getting older.
But if John saves Desmond,
then he never joins the Legends,
and I'm immortal again.
Let me get this straight.
You helped John risk
a catastrophic rupture to history
because you're afraid of aging?
Okay.
Maybe John succeeds and you go
on your immortal, merry way.
But if he fails,
I will personally make sure
you spend the rest of your
short, dreary, human life
in the deepest, darkest prison cell
the Bureau has to offer.
♪ ♪
[ROARS]
[ALARMS BLARING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GROWLING]
[ROARING]
♪ ♪
[GROWLING, ROARING]
Let's move.
♪ ♪
Look, I'm... I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
I shouldn't have forced
it on you and Mick.
No. He was just stating
a fact, you know.
I am a... clone.
[SOFTLY] Hey.
No, it's okay.
Sometimes I just wish I could
be more like you and
the Legends, you know.
Loosen up. I...
When did that happen?
What?
Oh, no.
I'll get a broom.
Ava, wait.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Are those tiny little footprints?
The Dybbuk is alive.
[WHIRRING]
What?
Okay, we shouldn't split up.
Classic horror-movie mistake.
Well, we're not exactly helpless.
Fine. I'll go fix Gideon.
And I'm gonna go catch a serial killer!
You are way too excited about this.
[ROUSING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[JAZZY BLUES MUSIC ON RADIO]
♪ I want to do a lot of things ♪
♪ ♪
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
What the hell?
[TENSE MUSIC]
[PHONE RINGING]
John.
How the bloody hell did you find me?
John, you have to stop this.
If Desmond isn't dragged to hell
and you don't join the Legends,
the effects could be cataclysmic.
Neron didn't drag Dez to hell.
I did.
What do you mean?
When I told Dez to run,
he went behind my back.
Made a deal to protect me.
In exchange for sparing my life,
Dez had to bind his soul to Neron's.
I couldn't send Neron to hell
without sending Dez down with him.
Johnny?
Johnny.
[DISTORTED] Johnny!
♪ ♪
[SCREAMING] No!
[SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
I killed the man I loved, and for what?
To buy New Orleans a little more time?
Neron needs souls to take over hell,
and mark my words, he is coming
back to Earth to get them.
John, we can help you.
Yeah, spare the team bit, all right?
I work alone.
[JAZZY BLUES MUSIC ON RADIO]
- You back already?
- Yeah.
Dez, I'm, ah, back already.
♪ ♪
Hey, Johnny.
♪ And I hope that I'm forgiven ♪
Hey, Dez.
I'm gonna get some clothes on.
♪ It will take a lot of prayers ♪
♪ To save my soul ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EERIE MUSIC]
It's dead.
[EXHALES]
The Dybbuk must have
found another vessel.
Is there another doll on
the ship somewhere, Rory?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
What the hell was that?
Block the exit.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DARK WHOOSH]
Okay, so whatever it is,
it has tiny little feet,
so it's not that big.
[GRUNTS, CRIES OUT]
Ow.
Ya dumb blonde!
It's not size that matters,
it's how you use it! Agh!
♪ ♪
[SCREAMING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Agh! Agh!
Ragh!
Professor Stein?
No! It's Mikey, you dick!
[KNIFE CLANGS]
[GRUNTS]
Here.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
Thank you.
Where is he?
[OMINOUS LAUGHTER ECHOES]
It really is Mike the Spike.
[GROWLING]
[WEAPONS BUZZING]
Stop!
- Where are you taking him?
- You.
I am the Assistant
Coordinator of Creature Upkeep.
It's my job to take
care of magical beings.
- Not for long.
- Let him go!
I'm warning you.
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
Konane, no!
[GASPS]
[GROWLS, ROARS]
Agh!
[SCREAMING]
You have to go.
They'll kill you...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GROWLING]
- You okay?
- Shh.
- Mike's up there.
- Mike the Spike?
Yeah, and he's found a new vessel.
Much, much worse.
Hold on.
[WHIRRING]
What could be worse than
a creepy antebellum doll?
[OMINOUS LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
Where are the eggs?
Thought you said you were gonna cook.
Yeah, I changed my mind.
I'll finish getting dressed,
and we can go out to eat.
You know, it's, uh...
it's not about the breakfast, Dez.
Mm. Kay.
I see what you're doing.
You know what your problem is, Johnny?
You don't think you deserve to be happy.
Dez, your feelings for me
are a bloody lie, all right?
See, I just wanted to
get you into my bed,
but I couldn't be bothered
to put the work in, so...
I used a love spell on you.
This a joke?
Afraid not, mate.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Hey, uh...
I really care about you.
If there's something
going on in your life,
just be honest with me.
Yeah, do you know what?
This thing between us? It isn't real.
It never was. It doesn't exist.
♪ ♪
I put myself out there like this,
and you're playing games?
You should go.
Yeah, you're right. I should.
But this...
this thing between us?
♪ ♪
This was real, Johnny.
[RUMBLING]
[BOOMING]
Sara, do you read me?
John's done something awful.
Well, he hasn't done anything yet.
I'm still stuck in this form.
Uh...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What's that?
♪ ♪
[GASPING]
[GROANS]
[OMINOUS LAUGHTER]
Guys! Guys, guys, guys!
I have a real emergency here.
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- [LAUGHING]
Marty!
[GAGGING]
[CACKLING]
Die, you putz!
- [GASPING]
- I hate puppets!
[GRUNTS]
Suck my...
[CRACKLING, BUZZING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[TICKING]
Blast...
[SIGHS]
Oi, Z! Check this out!
I got my powers back!
Don't be mad, I'm myself again.
Whoo! [LAUGHS]
[CAT MEOWING]
Where's Zari?
Zari?
[MEOWS]
Oh, blimey.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --