- Previously
on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
- Some of the most evil souls
in all of history
have been raised from hell.
- Nate, Zari. Zari, Nate.
- Your sister
is the secret woman
from the hologram message.
- I know Behrad's
been lying to my parents.
I know who you are.
It's time they
finally heard the truth.
- Guys, meet Zari.
She's my sister.
- Help!
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Freddy Meyers,
you stand convicted
of seven counts of murder,
all occurring
on June 2, 1989.
You have been sentenced to
death by a jury of your peers.
The state will now proceed
with your sentence.
Do you have anything to say
before your sentence
is carried out?
- Only...
♪
That I love my mother.
[generator whirring]
[electricity crackles]
- [sobs and cries out]
- [grunting]
- [sobbing]
Freddy, Freddy!
[cries out]
They took my Freddy!
- ♪ Ooh, baby, do you know
what that's worth? ♪
- ♪ Mmm, heaven
is a place on earth ♪
♪ They say in heaven,
love comes first ♪
♪ Who made heaven
a place on earth? ♪
[odd thumping]
The hell was that?
[Belinda Carlisle's
"Heaven Is a Place on Earth"]
What the...
[engine revving]
Oh! Ah!
[music grows louder]
[car horn blares]
[tires squeal]
[shouts]
[ominous music]
[groans]
♪
Who's there?
[gore squishes]
[dramatic music]
♪
[dramatic music intensifies]
[punk rock music]
♪
[ship humming]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Going somewhere?
- [chuckles]
Spare me the sendoff, Lance.
I'm leaving before you
and your band of botherers
can suck me into another
world-saving sing-along.
- Actually,
I was just gonna say
we're still waiting
for you to move out.
There's a box in the library
labeled "arcana"
that's been sitting there
for months.
- I'd avoid touching that
if I was you.
- Yeah, Behrad already
tried to move it
and now he thinks he's being
haunted by a forlorn mariner.
- And he's right, but I can't
stick around to help the bloke.
I'm off to research
a more lasting solution
to your encore problem.
- Did someone say encore?
- I also said
no musical numbers,
so please don't start.
- Listen, I might have
a solution to your problem.
- I can't take you with me
on this one, squire.
Where I'm going,
I need to walk alone.
With Gary.
- Okay, but look...
We're on a timeship.
And let's be honest,
we're a little past the whole
"should we change history"
debate, right?
So what if we go back
to when the encores were kids
and reform them
before they break bad?
- Ray, we're dealing with
the villains of history
fresh out of hell.
They can't just be reformed
like you're...
- Ray, where are you?
- Like your
fairy god-girlfriend.
Speaking of which,
I think that your
services are required, squire.
- [sighs]
Well, look who's
finally off the clock.
Oh, no, not again.
- Oh, yes, oh, yes.
It's the same thing every time.
Kid gets a fairy godmother,
what do they wish for?
[chuckles]
You get a pony
and you get a pony.
Everyone gets a damn pony.
- Well, maybe next time,
you should say, "neigh."
- Ugh.
[blows raspberries]
- Well, right now
it's all about what you want.
- [groans]
What I want
is to be done with this gig.
[sighs]
- I know, but look...
At least with this job,
you have the opportunity
to make people's lives better.
- How am I supposed to
help kids in need
when these kids don't even know
what they need?
Because trust me...
No one has ever become
a better person with a pony.
- Probably true.
But look, I'm setting the mood.
Gideon, dim the lights,
and play
"You're the Inspiration"
by Chicago.
And now,
it's whatever you wish, Nora...
- [snores]
- Gideon, don't play Chicago.
- I wasn't going to,
Dr. Palmer.
[peaceful music]
- [snorts]
- Oh.
- You sure being here
doesn't bring back
some fond memories?
- If I had fond memories
of this place,
I'd book a lobotomy.
Okay,
whatever you people do here,
just show me the exit.
I'm due for a content drop.
Oh, and also
to tell Mâmn and Bâb
you're not really
in business school.
- But before you do that,
let's make sure
you can't do that.
Look over here.
- Ooh, is that a camera?
- Wait!
- Ugh, I don't want
my picture with him.
- You can't wipe her memory,
all right?
There's a timeline
where she was here, okay?
So maybe her being here,
she'll remember
what we did and who she was.
- Look, I know Zari.
And there's no way
she was ever anyone but her.
- Hey, what's with the Wi-Fi?
I need to clap back
at Blue Ivy on CatChat.
[cats meowing]
CatChat's the chat app
that lets you clap back...
- I didn't say tell me.
- Mr. Tarazi and Mr. Heywood,
you're needed on the bridge.
- Look, no one wants you
out of here more than I do,
but I need you to stay put
until we finish this job.
- Wait.
Wait, are you...
Are you taking me prisoner?
[keypad chimes]
[no audible dialogue]
I have a sneaker drop
and I'm supposed
to be releasing
a new fragrance
for Dragoness today.
We have been working
on this launch for months.
This is high stakes!
- A serial killer
has been freed from hell
and is on the loose in 2004.
- And somehow, the scariest
thing about this mission
is going back
to the early 2000s.
- A coroner was found dead
while transporting the body
of a famed serial killer.
- [gasps]
Oh, my God.
It's Freddy Meyers,
the Prom Night Slasher.
Come on, guys.
I ranked him #5 killer
of all time on Stab Cast.
My podcast
about serial killers... babe?
- Oh.
- As I was going to say,
Freddy killed seven
of his peers before...
- At his high school prom
in 1989.
He used a kitchen knife
and he wore a creepy mask.
I actually did
a whole series on it.
So none of you open my emails,
clearly?
- And following the murders...
- He spent 15 years
on death row
before he was executed in 2004.
- Which is when
the timeline changed,
starting with
the death of the coroner
and the disappearance
of Freddy's body.
- I don't even want
to think about
what a serial killer would do
with his second act.
- Tiffany!
She was the final girl.
The one target...
Together:
That survived Freddy's attack!
- It's informative
and entertaining.
It's good.
- See?
Thank you.
- Guys, check this out.
"The Central City High
class of '89
"is planning to memorialize
their fallen peers
at their 15-year reunion
this Friday night."
- We have to go.
That's where Freddy will be
to finish the job.
- Well then, babe,
grab your autograph book,
because we're gonna
go catch a serial killer.
Gideon, take us to 2004.
- And order
one of these mattresses
using promo code "LACERATION."
[engines roar]
- We're heading in.
You guys keep an eye out
for a crazy masked killer.
- The only thing killing it
out here is my wardrobe.
- I can't believe I'm here.
Seriously...
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
This is the lobby
where he stalked his victims.
You guys...
He made his first kill
in this cafeteria!
[gasps]
Babe!
- What, what?
- Babe!
That's the trophy
that Tiffany fashioned
into a makeshift weapon.
- Why didn't you tell me
we were coming back
to my old school?
- You went to school here?
- What?
- Mick, this is why you need
to come to team meetings.
Do you remember anything
about Freddy?
- Yeah.
He was a loser.
- Oh, come on.
- Frickin' Mick Rory.
[chuckles]
Allie, remember?
Is that you, or...
- No.
- Are you sure?
'Cause you look, like,
exactly like Mick.
Mick Rory.
- No.
My name's...
Dick.
- Tellin' ya, Dick.
Team meetings work wonders.
- [gasps]
It's her!
It's Tiffany.
[suspenseful music]
Tiffany Harper.
It's really you.
- Who are you?
- [stammers]
- I'm Lisa and this is Kelly
and you wouldn't remember us
'cause we were losers.
Total zeroes.
- I don't.
Isn't time weird?
- So weird.
[chuckles]
- Well, see you inside.
- Thank you.
- And go Cavaliers!
[giggling]
- Oh, my God!
- Okay, go, keep going.
- Hope you're enjoying
your reunion out there.
Keep on dancing, class of '89.
- [groans]
No sign of Freddy.
But I got eyes on crudités.
- Ooh,
save me some raw broccoli.
[exhales deeply]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[groans]
I never thought I'd say this,
but I think I've lost
my appetite for broccoli.
- Whoa.
Guys, Freddy's on the scene.
He's got his first victim.
- We're ready for him.
- Uh, hello!
Hello, everyone.
Welcome back.
It means so much
to see all of you here tonight.
And here to unveil our memorial
to our fallen peers
is our very own survivor,
Tiffany Harper.
[polite applause]
[tense music]
[chuckles awkwardly]
Has anyone seen Tiffany?
- Something's wrong.
[audience murmuring]
♪
Of course she makes
a dramatic entrance.
[chuckles]
We didn't cover this
in rehearsal, Tiffany.
[audience murmuring]
All right, that's it.
I'm unveiling it myself.
[audience screaming]
[terrifying music]
- All right, everybody!
Just stay calm.
Okay, he's here.
We need backup.
- It's him.
♪
[wind whooshes]
- Guys, watch out.
You're stuck in the school
with the Prom Night Slasher.
[panicked murmuring]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Master,
I'm sorry I'm so late.
I tried a teleportation spell
to get here ASAP
and now I'm stuck
walking backwards.
- [speaks Latin]
Damn it, Gary.
Pull yourself together,
will you?
We've got work to do.
And the answers we need
lie behind this door.
- What is this place?
- I can't say I've ever had
anything as comfy as a home,
but I lived here once.
And not a soul has stepped foot
inside since I left.
[laughter]
[suspenseful music]
What the bloody hell?
Oi, what are you doing
in my house?
Hey, go on!
Get off my stairs.
All right,
who's responsible for this?
- And lo, and I thought I was
the one with the magic touch.
- [groans]
All right, everybody out.
Any of you wanna party you do
it somewhere else, all right?
♪
How did you even find
this place, Charlie?
- You told me about it
when you were wasted once.
- You found your way here,
you can find your way out.
- What is with him, huh?
What are you doing here?
- Do the Constantine trick
again.
- All right, everyone.
Stay sharp.
The killer could be anywhere.
- We gotta get everyone
out of here.
[all scream]
- Thanks for the heart attack!
- Sorry, Swiss Army Knife
usually solves a jam in a jiff,
but these doors are
telekinetically sealed.
No way in or out.
- This place
always felt like a prison.
- Telekinesis,
it makes perfect sense.
Killers often act
out of feeling powerless
and now he has
the ultimate power.
I need to adjust my rankings.
- Yeah,
and we need to save Allie.
I mean, the class of '89.
- All right, immortal killer...
How do we stop it?
- We can't from in here
but maybe you guys can.
Look, Ray, it's time to put
your crazy plan to the test.
We gotta go back
and fix Freddy.
[school bell rings]
- All right.
Let's find our future encore.
- Freddy!
Hey, Freddy!
Heard you couldn't
find a prom date.
Guess your mom turned you down.
[laughs]
Loser.
[laughter]
[bratty laughter]
- Nice one, Brad!
- Losers.
- Brad's such a jerk.
- Oh, it's okay. You don't have
to do it, it's all right.
I got it, thank you.
- Actually, I wanted
to ask you something.
Turns out I don't have a date
to prom tonight
and I was thinking...
would you go with me?
- [stutters]
Me go with you to prom?
- Exactly. Meet me in front
of the school at 8:00.
Don't be late.
[peaceful music]
- [clears throat]
- Oy vey, this is bad.
Why would the most popular girl
need a last-minute date,
let alone ask him?
She's working with those boys.
This could be
what sets him off.
Okay, we gotta talk this kid
out of his dream date.
[funky suspenseful music]
Let's rap, Freddy.
- Who are... who are you guys?
- New teachers.
Cool new teachers.
And, uh, judging by
your test scores here,
maybe you should skip the prom
and hit the books.
Turn this A into an A+.
- Or maybe go to the movies.
1989's a great movie summer.
"Last Crusade,"
"Ghostbusters II"...
- Yeah, I gotta go, so...
- Hey, no running
in the hallway.
- We're not just your teachers,
we're your pals!
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Picture a dark hallway.
It feels like the killer's
there with you.
Shafts of moonlight
claw at the floor.
Glowing exit sign
you may never reach.
♪
- Come out here, Freddy!
We know you're there.
- Yeah, come on out!
There are gaps in
your psychological profile
that you need to answer for.
- Babe.
- And we're gonna
send you back to hell.
- Yeah!
♪
- Did you find a way out?
- Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
Get back in the gym.
[metal creaks]
- [screaming]
- Babe!
♪
- Whoa.
- [screaming]
♪
[ominous music]
[blood trickling]
♪
- Freddy ran off on us.
- We need his address.
- I got you.
♪
- [groans]
- Nora?
♪
Nora, what's wrong?
- I can hear them, their...
Their voices.
Fairy godmothers have sort of
a special radar
that tunes into kids' wishes,
and prom night is
a minefield of teenage need,
so when it locks onto the kid
with the deepest need
I just go straight to...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, it's happening.
[ethereal twinkling]
- Where the hell
did you come from, huh?
- Oh, Freddy.
Uh...
- Huh?
- I am your fairy godmother.
So...
Please don't kill me?
- You're a fairy godmother?
My fairy godmother?
- Uh-huh.
- Prove it.
- You think I'd be wearing this
if I really had the choice?
Huh?
- So anything I ask for
you have to do it.
- So you should really think
about what you want,
especially the consequences.
- I already know what I want.
Prom's tonight and...
[knock at door]
- Freddy, honey!
- Hide... no!
[suspenseful music]
- Hey, Freddy.
Ready, Freddy, for movie night?
I got the Jiffy Pop going.
- Uh, actually, Mom...
- Ray, I'm with Freddy.
- Nora!
Good, that's great.
- How is that great?
I'm a serial killer's
fairy godmother.
- This is perfect. Old Freddy
didn't have a fairy godmother.
So if you give him the prom
every kid dreams of
maybe he won't hurt anyone.
- Except this kid's dream
is for everyone to be dead.
Oh!
- Mm, prom?
- Mm-hmm.
- Wow, Freddy.
Uh, do you need a ride, or...
I could help you with your tie.
- Oh... you know, I got it.
But, um, I love you, okay?
I just gotta go.
- Oh.
- Okay.
Now, back to my wish.
[suspenseful music]
I'm gonna make it so those kids
never make fun of me again,
because I wish for...
a suit.
- A suit?
- Yeah,
if I'm gonna take Tiffany
I gotta look good,
so I want a cool suit.
Can you do that?
- Yeah, I can do that.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
[ethereal twinkling]
[peaceful music]
Check it out.
Oh, my...
Okay, okay.
Now I gotta show up in style.
I want a pony.
- [groans]
Seriously, kid?
['80s rock music]
♪
- ♪ I've fallen in love
♪ And there's
no turning back ♪
- Hey.
Ready?
- Hey, Tiffany.
- Wow.
Cool suit.
- Thanks.
Here.
- ♪ You're like
a heart attack ♪
- Thank you.
- Should we, uh...
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- ♪ You open my eyes
- Looks like your plan
just might work.
- Well, only thanks to you.
- Hey, Palmer.
Will you go to prom with me?
- Aw, shucks.
[melodramatic '80s rock]
- All right.
- ♪ The way you make me
feel inside ♪
- [strains]
- Whoa, whoa, hey.
Cool it.
[door mechanism whirs]
- [laughs]
I knew it.
You stole our family's totem.
- It's not like that, I...
I needed to take it.
- I mean, you could've just
asked for it.
Mâmn and Bâb would've
given it to you.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Oh, you really don't know?
[scoffs]
You're never around,
you don't do any work,
and they still treat you
like you're some kind of hero.
- If you only knew
what I've done,
what I've survived,
without getting any credit.
Not that you'd understand,
'cause you only
care about yourself.
- Whatever, don't tell me.
But wait till they see you've
turned it into
a stupid stoner bracelet... hey!
- What up, Z-listers?
[chuckles]
Turns out even a sacred totem
couldn't reverse the sucking
void that is my soul.
- Hey, screw you.
I'm not a void.
I'm a business.
- Not like
it works here anyway.
[keypad chimes]
[peaceful music]
♪
- Everybody, stay calm.
Once the power's back
we'll get help.
- Where do you think
you're going?
- I'm gonna find a way
out of this school.
Look at them,
just waiting to be picked off.
Never fit in with them
when I went here
and I'm sure as hell
not gonna die with them.
- Hmm.
I like the way you think.
There's an old vent in the wood
shop I used to sneak out of.
- I knew it.
Mick frickin' Rory.
[laughs]
Come on, let's get the hell
out of this school.
- You have a husband?
Boyfriend?
Girlfriend?
- Eh.
No one's waiting at home
for me.
Still haven't quite
gotten that together.
- Hmm.
- And you?
- Um, it's behind here.
- Hey.
Do you ever wonder
where we'd be if, you know,
that prom had gone differently,
like if...
we'd...
[gore squishes]
- [gasps]
[tense music]
- [exhales]
♪
- You'd better be
fixing this in '89.
[thumping dance music]
♪
- So this is prom.
- I know it's lame, but...
- No, no, no, no.
Actually I think I kinda
get the whole nostalgia thing
for once.
- And we're gonna
slow it down for the next one.
So everyone, grab your sweeties
and get on the dance floor.
[cheesy '80s ballad]
♪
- ♪ Down this lonely road,
you walk away ♪
- Oh, I love this song.
- Yeah, me too.
- You know,
you're a really good dancer.
- Thanks, I...
I watch a lot of music videos.
- Oh.
- Aww, they look so happy.
- Yeah, but they don't.
♪
So that's the prank.
She leads him to
the center of the dance floor
and they drop trash
on his head.
Classic "Carrie."
Bet these bullies
don't know how that ended.
- Well, we gotta keep them
from walking in the drop zone.
- I think it's gonna be okay.
- ♪ And I'll wait
- It's a little crowded
over there.
- Is this good?
- Yeah.
- ♪ There's just one thing
I know ♪
♪ I'll never let go
- Hey, Freddy.
- [grunts]
[crowd exclaims]
- Nice suit.
It would suck if it got ruined.
- Brad, wait.
- Come on, Tiff!
This is how the prank
was supposed to go, right?
- Prank?
What are you talking about?
- He still doesn't get it.
[laughter]
You think she actually
wanted to go out with you?
It was a setup, butt lump.
[laughter]
[tense music]
- Tiffany, is that true?
- No...
I mean not anymore, Freddy.
♪
- No, Freddy.
Freddy, it's gonna be okay.
[bullies cackling]
♪
- We just went from
John Hughes to John Carpenter.
- I take it back.
High school sucks.
- Come out here and face me,
you bastard.
- Rory, are you trying
to get yourself killed?
- He killed Allie.
He's gonna pay!
- She wasn't just some girl,
was she?
- [growls]
She was my prom date.
We went to
the same school together
and we kind of had a thing.
Then I went to juvie
but we still wrote letters
to one another.
I was gonna break out
and take her
to the stupid dance,
but then I blew her off.
- Rory.
- What?
I was young, stupid.
- Mick, look, I'm sorry, okay?
But if this plan works then
Freddy never becomes an encore.
Maybe everything that happened
can be undone.
Maybe we can still save Allie.
- [sniffles]
- Freddy, wait.
- Leave me alone.
What?
- You don't want
to be alone right now.
- How would you know that?
How would you know what I want?
I spent years wanting
these kids to be my friend
and I couldn't even make it
happen with a fairy godmother!
I cannot wait to be done
with this stupid place
and I hope they all
get what they deserve.
- No, you don't mean that.
- Yeah, I do.
- No, you don't.
Look, I get it.
I have given in to my demons.
I know what it's like
to want to make the world
feel your pain,
but that is not who you are.
I see so much more in you.
[soft uplifting music]
Listen.
- [sniffles]
- God, being yourself...
That is a magic
stronger than any wish.
Being truly okay with myself,
scars and all,
is how the right people
truly found me.
Now, if you had
one more wish...
To show all of them
who you really are,
what'll it be?
♪
[crowd exclaims]
- Uh, how concerned
should we be?
- I say medium.
Medium concerned.
- ♪ We're J.J. Fad
and we're here to rock ♪
- ♪ Rhymes like ours
could never be stopped ♪
- Hit it!
[J.J. Fad's "Supersonic"]
- ♪ Supersonic
♪
♪ Supersonic motivating rhymes
are creating ♪
♪ We know you like us girls
so you better get stirl' ♪
♪ 'Cause we are
the home chicks ♪
♪ That are
rockin' your world ♪
[ethereal twinkling]
[crowd gasps and exclaims]
- ♪ Supersonic is a word
when people start to listen ♪
♪ Especially bigger people,
they pay close attention ♪
♪ You might not believe it,
you might not even buy it ♪
♪ But when it comes
to our lady ♪
♪ Beatbox!
You might even try it ♪
♪ Supersonic
♪
- What the...
[jovial shouting]
- [chuckles]
- ♪ S-s-so you better listen
good to what we have to say ♪
♪ 'Cause when it comes
to J.J. Fad ♪
♪ You can't get no play
♪ Supersonic
♪
- [exhales deeply]
Computer, just tell me h...
How many CatChat followers
have I lost
since I've been stuck
in this dump?
- I can't do that,
Miss Tarazi.
- It's probably best
I don't know.
Wait, does this computer
get internet?
[soft peaceful music]
♪
It's a computer program
I designed to hack it.
♪
- How did you bypass my
encrypted security protocol?
- Oh, just by being
a businesswoman, makeup guru,
bad bitch, and overall genius.
Now call me a ride, computer.
[peppy '80s dance music]
♪
- Hey. You were really good
out there, Freddy.
- Takes some real confidence
to bust out backup dancers
at prom.
- So this gets to be,
like, your job,
making things better for kids?
- Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
- Look, there's gotta be
a bunch of kids out there
that could probably
use your help,
and I think I'm gonna be okay.
Thank you, though.
For everything.
♪
[ethereal whooshing]
- Oh, there's my ride.
Ugh, vintage.
Well,
at least the computer knows
I like to travel in style.
[synth-driven ambient music]
♪
- That was fun.
- Yeah, and the night's
just getting started.
- I know.
Well, you can take my limo
wherever we want to go.
After you.
- Thank you.
[laughter]
♪
- Ugh, she booked me
a shared ride.
♪
[ominous music]
[communicator chimes]
- Guys, they fixed it.
- Ray's plan actually worked?
- Apparently, Freddy's
a really solid dancer.
And he's not gonna go
on a killing spree at prom.
[clatter]
[ominous music]
- Then who is that?
- Die, you bastard!
♪
[shouts]
- Nick!
Hey.
No, no.
[solemn music]
[supernatural whooshing]
- Sara, look.
[ominous music]
♪
Kathy Meyers?
She must be the encore.
- They wanted to take my Freddy
away from me.
But when that girl
asked him to prom,
I knew I had to kill her
and all of his new friends.
Now I get to finish
what I started.
- Hey, are you guys
getting any service?
Oh, I know
what you guys are thinking.
Yes, it's me.
The Dragon Girl.
Wait, why aren't we moving?
- Driver, what's going on?
[screaming]
- Close it!
Close the door, close it!
- [yells]
- You killed our friend.
You killed those kids.
- But you're not gonna
get away with it this time.
- I won't let anyone
stand between me and my boy.
And you're next.
[yells]
[cymbal clanging]
[grunting]
- Sara!
- Close the door!
[screaming]
[ominous music]
♪
[thumping]
[dramatic music]
- [yells]
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[stutters]
Before you kill me,
there's just something
I don't understand, huh?
How did you get here?
Come on,
every killer has a story.
Why don't you
tell me yours, yeah?
- After I killed those brats,
my Freddy took the fall.
He wanted to protect me,
but I knew I couldn't
live without him.
And I was right, because he's
not the only one who died
the night of his execution.
[crying]
I had a heart attack
right there in Iron Heights.
I died with him!
But then,
I was sent back from hell.
Given a second chance,
a chance to bring Freddy home
where he belongs.
A chance to finish
the job I started.
And no one can ever take
us away from each other.
[yells]
[screaming]
♪
- Babe, it's happening.
- We're final girls!
♪
[screaming]
[girls screaming]
- That's right!
Feel the burn of Dragoness,
you psycho!
♪
- Mom?
[suspenseful music]
What are you doing?
- Freddy,
I'm doing this for you.
For us.
I can't lose you, Freddy.
I can't live without you.
Let me do this, Freddy.
[supernatural droning]
- I can't move.
[droning continues]
♪
- You don't need them,
you need me.
We could get away with this
together.
- No, no.
I-I know who I am now and
I'm not gonna lock myself away.
- Then this is
for your own good.
[groans]
[both grunt]
- They did it!
- [exhales deeply]
- Behrad?
- It's all right.
You okay?
- I totally get
why you stole that.
Fair enough.
Wow, this is a lot.
[police sirens
wailing distantly]
[police radio chatter]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- I know she needs help, but...
she was all I had.
And they took her away.
[sniffles]
- Mm-hmm.
- So what do I do?
- Survive.
Freddy, my upbringing
was only dysfunction.
But dysfunction doesn't
get to choose who you are.
You do.
You hear me?
- Yeah, okay.
[sniffles]
- We should, uh, head back
and check on the team
and make sure everything's
back to normal.
♪
- I know you're gonna
be okay, kid.
♪
[soft uplifting music]
- Dr. Gideon
treating you right?
Pretty cool, huh?
- So this is what you do?
Travel around time
and save people using wind?
That's...
I wouldn't say cool,
exactly, but...
no wonder you're the favorite.
- The favorite?
Mâmn and Bâb
only treat me how they do
'cause they're worried
about me.
I mean, I've been in
business school for five years.
You were a self-made
millionaire by the age of 19.
- You're right,
I am very impressive.
- Like, how did you jailbreak
your way out of here anyway?
- I was poking around
your weird little screens
and suddenly I knew
how to hack my way out.
- Right.
Yeah, time travel always has
these weird side effects.
- Huh.
Well, hopefully it wears off
because I was thinking
of sticking around for a while.
- Huh.
I weirdly wouldn't hate that.
- Hey, guys.
We're still in 2004.
Where the hell are you?
- You coming?
♪
[upbeat music]
- How about this for a reunion?
All: Hey!
♪
- And, uh,
what's your sister doing here?
- Probably CatChatting.
No judgment here.
- Yes.
- Wait.
Where's Mick?
- Mick?
Mick Rory?
[Belinda Carlisle's
"Heaven Is a Place on Earth"]
- Allie.
- ♪ Heaven is
a place on earth ♪
♪ They say in heaven,
love comes first ♪
- Hey, Freddy.
Hey, Tiffany.
- ♪ Ooh, heaven
is a place on earth ♪
- Nora, may I have this dance?
- Ah, but of course.
♪
- I cannot believe I got to
get an exclusive scoop
for Stab Cast
and I got to be the final girl.
- Well, technically,
I never died, so.
- Technically, you've died
more than three times,
so just give me this one, babe.
- [clicks tongue]
You are my final girl.
- [chuckles]
- Hey, guys.
Photo booth.
[both groan]
- Whoo!
- Do we look okay?
♪
- ♪ When you walk
into the room ♪
♪ You pull me close,
now we start to move ♪
- Wait!
[needle scratches]
Where's Mick?
[DJ scratches]
- ♪ Ooh, baby, do you know
what that's worth? ♪
♪ Ooh, heaven
is a place on earth ♪
♪ They say in heaven,
love comes first ♪
- [moans]
Wow, Mick.
- That's my gun.
- Oh.
[gun hits floor]
♪
[ominous music]
- [groans]
I thought I told you
to piss off.
- Gary just filled me in
on that business with Astra.
So why are you
drowning your sorrows
instead of doing something
about it?
What happened here, John?
- [chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
I used to run with a bunch
back in the day.
Became known
as the Newcastle Crew,
spent most of our misbegotten
youth in this place.
One of them was
a powerful witch.
I'm back here
to consult with her.
She's through there.
- So what are you waiting for?
Come on, get off your ass
and go and do it.
- Because it's not that easy,
all right, Charlie?
That witch is
Astra's dead mother.
Her spirit is waiting on the
other side of that door and...
none too happy with me.
- There are things in my past
that I haven't told anyone.
So I get the whole
wanting to do it on your own.
But if there was some door
that I could walk through
to solve all my problems,
I sure as hell would
take that chance.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- I call upon Hecate,
lady of keys
and guardian of crossroads.
♪
Sever this seal.
By my blood, be open.
[flames crackle]
- Don't look back, Johno.
You got this.
- Let's hope
you're right, love.
[tense music]
♪
- Greg, move your head.
[flames crackling]