[DISQUIETING MUSIC]
- [SIGHS]
- [JOINTS CRACK]
Total mind-bender, right?
You have no idea how many times
I've stumbled across
one of my dead bodies.
When I said, "I'm gonna
save all of humanity,
starting with you", I wasn't lying...
But tragically,
there is no antidote
for a Zaguron sting.
See, what I gave you was a primer...
The nanobots have completed their scan.
So I could make a new you.
The transition can be tough.
Sara 2.0, alive and well!
And that's just the beginning.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hey. Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, come here.
I got to let you in on a little secret.
All right, David-freaking Bowie?
Because tonight, tonight,
I am gonna propose to my girlfriend!
[DESOLATE MUSIC]
Hey. Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, come here.
I got to let you in on a little secret.
All right, David-freaking Bowie?
Because tonight, tonight, I am...
Just want to check on you.
Gideon said you haven't eaten.
- Not hungry.
- Hey, but you got to eat.
What's the point?
She's gone, Nate. I'm just done, okay?
Okay, well, if you need anything,
I guess you're gonna ask Gideon,
but I'm here for you, too. We all are.
Thanks. How's everybody else doing?
They're grieving in their own way.
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
- How is she?
- Worse.
She still won't eat, and Gideon
made her favorite quiche.
- What about that bloody video?
- Still watching it on a loop.
We got to do something.
We just need to give her some space.
When I lost Behrad,
that's what I needed.
- Speaking of, where is B?
- He won't leave the lab.
He's taking Sara's death
almost as hard as Ava.
All right. So we'll give Ava space,
but as your reluctant default
interim captain,
I am ordering the rest of us
to stay together for moral support.
I'll go get B.
You know what? I'll come with.
You're more of a reluctant
default interim co-captain.
What about Rory?
If Sara is dead, then...
Mick Rory is like a cockroach.
The bugger will survive anything.
- [BANGING NOISES]
- Yeah!
[ROARING]
[UPBEAT TECHNO MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That was great.
Except for the ear thing.
You want to go again?
Why don't you see if Bishop
put the barrier back up?
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
How can I tell if it's safe?
You just did.
Once you're done with that,
we rescue Sara.
Once I'm done, I'm off this planet.
What? You owe me.
For the sex?
I saved your life.
"This" for "that", such a
human way of thinking.
You have until the third moon sets.
♪ ♪
Deal.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, finally.
Do you mind?
♪ ♪
Much better.
Ooh, I hate having broken bones.
They make these awful crunching sounds.
Now, where was I?
Oh, yes, the plan. You're gonna love it!
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Merging alien and human DNA.
I knew that was the answer,
but it turns out that
kind of merger requires
an awesome degree of mental fortitude.
Hard to find, mental fortitude,
but you know who's got it in spades?
I'll give you three guesses.
Never mind, I'll give you zero.
I got them off these old
romance novels by some lady,
Rebecca... Steel? No, Gold. Mm, Silver!
Anyway, your story was so inspiring.
Resilience, it seems, is the key.
Otherwise we get
an Amelia Earhart situation.
You're sick.
You want to see something sick?
Check this out. Hmm?
Photoshop Ava put
this concept art together.
See? That's you, and that's you.
That's you, but also not you,
a better you.
They're alien-Sara Lance hybrids,
and together, we'll colonize
every planet in the galaxy
and begin the next chapter
of the human race.
You're gonna put millions
of alien mes onto planets
billions of miles away. What are you, 6?
♪ It's cloud printing ♪
[GUNS WHIR]
[LAUGHS] Uh-uh.
This is a symbol of your old life.
♪ You need to engage ♪
♪ With your future ♪
Why would I help you?
Because I died and you cloned me?
I die about once a year,
and my girlfriend is a clone.
Now, I'm gonna get off this planet,
and I'm gonna propose to her
with that ring.
Now, give it back to me, you son of a...
Bummer! Thought this version
of you would be cooler.
Take her to the incinerator.
I'll just keep tinkering
until I get a version that cooperates.
No version of me will ever help you!
♪ I love that fighting spirit ♪
Oh, and save the dress!
I'd hate to waste
such a fine piece of silk.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
This is B squad. Delta sector's clear.
I really hate clones.
Yeah, we don't care much for you either.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Whoa, whoa!
Give him some time.
Mick is an acquired taste.
- Gary.
- I believe
the words you're looking for
are "thank you".
B!
[GENTLE TWANGY MUSIC PLAYING]
B?
That's weird. That's his thinking music.
Gidget, where's my brother?
Mr. Tarazi is not on the Waverider.
♪ ♪
Oh, no.
It's his thinking weed.
[SYNTH MUSIC]
As your reluctant default
interim co-captain,
we need to work on our shorthand,
because I don't understand
what you're saying.
- Oh, no.
- _
Guys, we need backup.
- [UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
- _
♪ ♪
Where the hell are we?
- Last year's finale.
- What's a finale?
You'll see. They're pretty fun,
I mean, except for the one where I died.
Okay, shh. Has anyone seen our Behrad?
There he is.
The Smell is up next! Come on!
I bloody love The Smell!
- Ooh!
- Hey.
Did you think we wouldn't notice?
I know there are a million reasons
why I shouldn't do this,
but I am stopping Sara
from being abducted and dying,
and you can't stop me!
Stop you?
We're here to help you do it right.
Should we really be strategizing
across from the Hole?
None of us came here that night, mate.
The only other building in the area
was a fireworks factory.
All right. So what's the plan, bro?
All right. We need to get
Sara onto the Waverider
before the aliens arrive.
I'm thinking fire alarm.
No, the Hole doesn't have fire alarms.
The place is a death trap.
I felt like I was back in hell.
Why don't we ask Ava for a plan?
No, no, no, no. Ava would never allow
something like this. It's too risky.
It's up to us to save Sara
without interacting
with our former selves,
so at any point during the night,
did anyone slip away that would
give us a window to step in?
Honestly, mate, that night was a blur.
Do you remember anything?
Well, I said goodbye forever
to the love of my life,
so, yeah, I went pretty hard. Blur.
Look, if we could pull this off,
we not only save Sara,
but we prevent aliens
from scattering across the timeline.
Wait, if there are never any aliens,
I never look for Spooner.
And I never join y'all. [LAUGHING]
I mean, y'all are great,
but there were perks to my old life:
you know, never getting attacked
by alien Amelia Earhart,
never getting turned into a fork.
- That was one time.
- Don't trust you.
[PHONE PLAYS MUSICAL ALARM]
All right. Smoke o'clock.
Wait, that's it!
I smoke every night
at midnight, and tonight,
I went on the roof to smoke!
That means the other you
is out of the picture.
And I can get Sara on the Waverider!
"Sara, the Fates are back!"
Nah, too obvious.
"Sara, Sara, your
sister and dad called".
Are they even alive in this timeline?
- B?
- Yes.
It's me, your current friend, Behrad.
Okay.
You're needed on the
Waverider immediately.
It's a timequake-wave-mergency.
Well, that is the beauty
of having a time machine.
I can always just go back
in time and fix it.
- But, Sara!
- B, look, I'm not gonna go.
All right?
Come here.
I want to let you in
on a little secret, okay?
- Okay.
- So I just picked this up
because I am going to propose
to Ava tonight.
Where'd you get this? Versailles?
The Romanovs?
- My mom.
- Go figure.
Sara Lance, old-school romantic.
Yeah, you know me,
and tonight is the night, and nothing,
not even a timeline emergency,
is gonna get in my way.
- There you are.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- What are you two doing?
Ah, just talking rings, Fates, looms,
- Yeah.
- You know, recap stuff.
Mm. Wait, wait, wait.
Wasn't that silver streak in your hair
on the other side before?
- Yeah, actually.
- Oh.
Babe! Charlie is about to go on.
- Yes!
- Come on, let's go!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
- I'll meet you inside.
- You're not coming?
- Smoke o'clock.
- Ah.
[SIGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Stop! Avas, we're on her side!
They're helping us rescue you.
- Us?
- Yeah.
Mick!
Oh, my God, you're alive!
He flew here with Kayla.
Wait, why didn't she try to eat you?
- We got to go!
- I can't until I stop Bishop.
He's got this crazy intergalactic plan
to try to clone me.
A planet of clone Avas and Saras?
Are we sure we want to stop that?
I speak for all the Avas
when I say it would be an honor
to help thwart him.
Great. How do we do it?
Well, redundancy is Bishop's religion.
If we take down one generator,
the backup kicks in,
but I guess if we destroy them
all simultaneously,
his whole operation would go down.
Well, you better make it fast.
When those moons set, Kayla is gone.
All right, let's split up
and cover more ground.
I'll get some explosives.
Thank you for finding me.
The ship sucked without you.
Come on.
Sara is not leaving
until she proposes to Ava.
Yeah, but Sara never
proposed that night.
Why not?
No clue, but if we get Sara to propose,
we could get her on the ship
before the aliens come.
Unfortunately, we were all
with Sara the rest of the night.
Well, not all of us.
Do you two have something
you want to share
with the rest of the class?
There is a 20-minute window
where we'll be out
of the picture, so to speak.
- More like a generous 10.
- 15!
- Hmm, 8.
- Just go get Sara to propose!
[ROCK MUSIC]
Where the bloody hell is Sara, eh?
Hey, girl!
Hi.
Have you seen Sara?
Yeah, she's in the bathroom. Why?
She borrowed my makeup,
and John needs it now.
You look great. So good to see you.
[COUGHING AND RETCHING]
Sara, you all right? Are you pissed?
No, I think I just need
to drink more and a mint.
She's nervous about proposing.
Wait, how did you... ugh, Behrad!
Hey, hey, hey, you
listen to me, all right?
You are Sara fricking Lance.
Now, who's gonna turn you down, eh?
Now, you go out there,
and you get on bended knee.
You put a ring on it
and you take that lady
home to celebrate.
All right? Because you deserve it.
- What's it to you?
- What?
I just love love.
You just "love love"?
Yeah.
Hey, Charlie. Is that you?
Just stop messing with me. All right?
I'm gonna do it my way in my time.
- Hey, what was that?
- What was what?
Willingness to go along
with a crazy plan,
corny lines about love.
This is somehow about you.
You don't have your magic, do you?
And before...
- Astra covered for me.
- Yep.
Look, rehab is not working. All right?
I say the words,
but I can't rekindle the flame.
Resetting the timeline
might be my only chance
of getting my magic back.
Yeah, and you thought telling Sara
you love love would be your best bet?
- Too much?
- Yeah.
Fine.
- Hey, John?
- Yeah?
No more lies.
In words!
No more lies!
Good.
Okay, now we have to find the team
and come up with a plan C to save Sara.
Yeah, and a plan D to save me.
Wow.
♪ ♪
- She's nervous?
- How do we fix that?
Hey!
I knew it.
Oh, hey, girl. We were just...
Celebrating the finale
by eating mushroom curry, like we do!
You and those Shake Weights.
- Cisco, am I right?
- Cisco.
- Just...
- Don't even!
I know you're not my Legends,
okay, and where am I?
Huh? Nowhere,
which is how I know that
whatever you're all doing
is a terrible idea, okay? Am I dead?
No, no, no, never mind.
Don't answer that, please!
Did you just nod your head?
- Mm-mm.
- Okay, girl, you're right.
We are from the future,
but we have a really good reason.
La-la-la-la, no, stop, stop.
I don't want to hear any more words.
Guys, how many missions
is it gonna take for you
to realize that you can't just
change one thing from the past?
It always causes millions of ripples.
Okay, that's the danger
of what you're doing here,
is chaos to the timeline.
So you're confiscating our drinks?
No, these are for me
because now, thanks to you,
I have to get blackout drunk to forget
that this ever happened. Damn it!
Mm. All of you, back to your timelines.
- I'm not even kidding. That's an order!
- Oh.
Jeez, I didn't think
y'all would be this upset
about losing me.
This isn't about me, is it?
[HORN BLARES, TIRES SQUEAL]
Come on! I'm walking here!
Arriving at the last
generator now, Mick.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ugh!
Oh, no! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It's just...
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Wow.
Have you always been able to do that?
Regeneration.
Bishop. What did he do?
I swear, I have no idea.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Finish up here.
Stand by.
I'm blowing up the generators,
There's someone I got to see first.
♪ The music's got me grooving ♪
♪ It's got me swinging to the beat ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Doing my thing ♪
♪ You really got me going ♪
Ugh!
What have you done to me?
Ugh. Shouldn't you be...
oh, the Avas.
That one is on me.
Should've seen it coming.
What did you do?
Show-and-tell time!
What the hell is that?
That...
is you.
I merged you with this beauty,
making you the Eve
of alien-human hybrids.
You're welcome. Ooh!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
This is getting a bit tiresome.
What's the big plan?
You gonna kill me again? [SNORES]
Not this time.
No new Bishops.
You're stuck with this one.
Now, tell me how to make
myself human again.
This is just your pain cycle
speaking, Sara!
Look past your rage, Sara,
and imagine the possibilities.
You, with wings!
You, with the ability to live
in subzero temperatures!
Fun!
You fought so hard to save
the timeline, but for what?
Humanity has no future
without me, without us!
♪ So what do you say? ♪
Hard pass, and if you won't fix me,
then I'll make a clean clone of myself,
and then I'm gonna blow up this place
and get the hell off this planet.
Good luck with that.
No generators means
no electrostatic barrier,
which means, yes, Zagurons.
If I were you,
I wouldn't book a venue
for your wedding just yet.
Goodbye, Bishop.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Behind you.
Mm, thank you.
Ew. I mean, honestly, leave it to Ava
to bring up some very valid concerns.
Very valid concern-itunities.
Exactly. We need to get creative.
We got to find a way to get Sara back
and make sure everything
else stays the same.
So our present doesn't change.
And I still join the Legends.
Shh. Okay, so how?
I might have a way.
With a mannequin?
No, with an exploding mannequin!
- Ava.
- There you are.
Can you make a clean version of me?
Me? No.
Bishop does all the cloning.
He's the brilliant scientist.
But you? You're the brilliant nurse
who helped him.
- Hmm?
- I know that you can do this.
All right? I trust you.
Sara!
The generators are ready to blow!
Give me it.
We have to get to the ship now!
You go. I'll meet you there.
Did she just hang up on me?
How many bowls is that?
What's the point of time travel
if I can't enjoy the local cuisine?
B, I love you, and I cosign
your creativity 100 percent,
but this plan is...
- It's absolute rubbish, mate.
- Yeah.
Those fireworks will have to go off
at just the right time
in just the right place
with just the right amount of force.
I don't like those odds.
And her hair is trag.
The alien is definitely gonna know.
Gary is on the ship.
He'll pick up what I'm laying down here.
I had Gideon run a reverse model
on the pods' disbursement,
and, accounting for temporal drift,
in 12 hours and 14 minutes,
the ship will be in the
exact location it was
when Sara sent aliens into the timeline.
The bomb goes boom, scattering
aliens across the timeline.
We get our Sara back.
All I need now is my
woman on the inside.
All right, I'm here. Now what?
Keep your eyes peeled.
Let me know when the Legends
are on the movie,
and whatever you do,
don't interact with Sara.
Look, I don't even know the lady.
What would I possibly say to her?
Hey. How's it going?
Rough night?
I've been having a weird one myself.
Cheers.
So, lay it on me.
Oh, come on. I could use a distraction.
♪ ♪
What the hell.
Twenty years ago,
I was abducted by aliens.
Now, they did something to me,
and ever since, I feel things,
hear voices from aliens,
and it's freaking me out.
What if there's something
inside me that I can't control,
and the people I live with...
They're gonna think
I'm some kind of monster.
And now you think I'm crazy.
No, crazy is the word people
use when they're afraid
of what you're capable of.
I'm not afraid. I am intrigued.
Wow. You really are cool.
Look, it sounds like
you're on the beginning
of an amazing journey,
and if I could give you
one piece of advice,
from experience, don't go at it alone.
- And what if I hurt them?
- What if they help you?
Well, what if I can't live up
to their expectations?
Yeah, I feel you on that one.
I was supposed to propose
to my girlfriend tonight,
and then I realized that she's
probably gonna say yes.
- That's great, right?
- Oh, I don't know.
I've been so many different
people in my life,
and I am worried that this version of me
might just be a phase,
and I would get a lifetime
of the woman I love,
but I can't promise she'd
get the same in return.
Look, I just met you,
and I certainly don't know
your girlfriend,
but my gut tells me
that she can handle change.
Hell, might even be good for her.
And what if I hurt her?
What if you help her?
We're The Smell.
Now, welcome to the best show
of your lives, you wankers!
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
She is perfect just the way she is.
Maybe just a cup of coffee
before I propose.
Maybe two.
You lads are out of this world.
David freaking Bowie?
You're a Smell fan?
- They're something else.
- Wait, wait, wait, I got to...
I got to let you in on a little secret.
All right, David freaking Bowie?
Because tonight, tonight,
I am going to propose
to my girlfriend...
Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, well, girl, at least you
stand a fighting chance
of getting through the door now, ish.
[STOMACH GROWLING]
Are bombs supposed to make that sound?
That's not a bomb. That's not a bomb.
Man of Steel, intestines of Play-Doh.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Run this back to the bathroom.
I'm gonna need it in 90 seconds.
- No.
- Who are you?
I'm Nate, from the timeline
you're currently creating
with that blonde bomb-equin.
Why are you wearing my coat?
Shh. Let it happen.
Because of your stupid plan,
this bomb drops the aliens
in New York during the Gilded Age.
They take over Wall Street.
John, you're poisoned by
a Calavax in the trading pit.
I got to go undercover as Constantine
and join a magic cult
to stop this invasion.
- What about Sara?
- What about her?
It's a mannequin, B.
Gary and his alien friends
just make a U-turn
and come back and grab her.
I'm sorry. She's gone.
- Hey.
B, Sara is heading out
to the parking lot.
I'm not gonna let her die!
B! No!
Could've used that a minute ago.
So what'd I miss?
I'm really going to miss you guys.
I'm gonna miss you.
All right. Go on! Get out of here!
Go and enjoy your vacations.
- Whoo!
- You earned it.
- Va-ca-tion.
- Vaca...
- Vacacione!
Vacacione!
Sara! Sara!
Listen to me, when you...
No!
Ugh, those idiots are trying to save me.
They're gonna destroy the timeline
if I don't get back there soon.
I'm almost done.
What will you do after
we print the new version?
Human me will go home,
and then this me will stay here.
Are you sure you...
All right. How long is this gonna take?
With these new specifications,
10 minutes.
Well, let's just hope Rory
and Gary don't get too antsy.
♪ ♪
Sara?
Well, well, look who I underestimated.
Where's Sara?
I can arrange for you to see her
most expeditiously.
Oh, that's much better.
Oh, no, no, no. You ruined everything.
He's a psychopath.
Now he's a dead psychopath.
He's not dead. He's everywhere.
Sara definitely picked the right Ava.
The rest of you are nuts.
Much obliged, Mr. Rory,
for giving my transformation
such poetry.
Damn it. It doesn't matter!
You won't have time to reprint
before I blow this place up.
Thinking too small again, Sara.
Why be where you're not wanted
when the universe has offered
- a standing invitation?
- _
Oh, no! His consciousness is digital,
and he's uploading it to the cloud.
Once that upload is complete,
he'll be able to print
himself from any...
- Anywhere in the universe.
- Exactly.
All right. So we stop it.
The only way to do that is
to detonate the generators.
How long until he's uploaded?
Three minutes.
[TENSE MUSIC]
What will you do, Sara:
save yourself or stop me?
What a sticky little wicket.
Can't this thing print any faster?
Leaving your fate
in the hands of a printer?
I'm disappointed. Make a choice, Sara.
Shut up!
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What is that?
- It's me.
- What?
- I died.
- Again?
Yeah, but this time,
I didn't make it back.
- So who am I talking to?
- A monster!
Which is why you need to make sure
that you take this version
of me home with you.
All right? This body, it's not me.
One minute until Bishop's
upload is complete.
- Then blow it!
- No, don't! Don't.
Look, I can't go back
to the team half-alien.
What if I hurt you guys?
What if I hurt Ava?
Listen, that creep
can't get away with it!
That creep changed me, Rory!
Look, I don't even know
what I am anymore.
All right? You cannot see it,
but I'm damaged.
Damaged? No.
I see someone who's been through hell
but never stopped being herself.
I see Captain Lance.
I see Sara, my oldest friend.
We need you.
Please.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Mm.
Come on.
Gary, let's blow this place.
[DRAMATIC CHORAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[STATICKY] No!
Whoo! We did it!
Viva la Avalucion!
Let's move!
Okay, so once the barrier is gone,
it'll be cold, and you'll
need masks to breathe.
You'll also need these
to fend off the Zagurons.
They hate light. Okay, good luck!
You sure you won't come with us?
This is my home.
Are you gonna be okay?
We're a team of trained
warriors, medics,
engineers, and gourmet chefs.
We'll be fine.
[MONSTROUS ROARING]
The Zagurons have broken
past the barrier.
We got to go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Mick! You out there?
[MONSTROUS ROARING]
The third moon has set!
- She'll wait!
- How can you be so sure?
I just am.
Kayla wouldn't leave without me.
Where's the ship?
Don't take it personally, Mick.
♪ ♪
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Let's move.
Let's go, go, go, go, go!
♪ ♪
[ZAGURONS SCREAMING]
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
She came back for me.
Well, I guess you were
right about Kayla.
Those dirt rats were starting
to scratch up the finish,
so I had to get my ship off the ground.
- You're Kayla?
- And you're still the woman
who almost destroyed my ship.
If we're done standing around,
let's get off this stinking planet.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Kayla!
Mick!
Yeah, Sara!
Kayla! Kayla!
Mick! Get Kayla's ship ready to go.
- On it!
- Mick, we got to go.
- I'm not leaving without her.
- We'll wait inside the ship.
♪ ♪
[ZAGURONS SHRIEKING]
Guys, we got incoming.
♪ ♪
Gary, get this bird in the air.
Aye, aye, Captain!
♪ ♪
[MOURNFUL MUSIC]
Are you okay?
It's my fault.
I got Sara abducted.
If I never tried to warn her,
she just would've kept walking,
just never would've been
sucked up into space.
I'm pretty sure they would've
gotten her elsewhere,
but all right.
You convinced me. It's all your fault.
You have an unorthodox comforting style.
Yeah, we don't really do
a lot of comforting
where I grew up.
Look, if you hadn't tried to save her,
you would've spent the rest
of your life wondering,
"What if I had?" I should know.
You still miss her? Your mom?
Every day, but losing her
brought me here,
and that's not all bad.
I'd say it's pretty good.
Hey, you two.
I'm sorry, Behrad joon.
I learned the hard way, mate.
Some things can't be changed.
Well, I'm still here.
I'm guessing the plan didn't work.
Well, there's one silver lining.
I just can't believe she's gone.
Legends never die.
I could use a drink.
I'll second that, love.
I got to let you in on little secret.
All right, David-freaking Bowie?
Because tonight, tonight,
I am going to propose to my girlfriend!
- I am going to propose...
- Gideon, what's happening?
My apologies, Captain Sharpe.
It appears the file has been corrupted.
No, no. Come on.
This can't be happening!
Ah, God.
Ava?
Is it really you?
Yeah, babe, it's me.
I don't want to turn around,
because I'm afraid if I do,
you'll disappear.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'm not going anywhere ever again.
I promise.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
♪ ♪
Are you okay?
I am now.
I can't believe this.
♪ ♪
Ava will want to know I'm okay, too.
No, she won't.
Do the rest of the Legends
know you're here?
Now that you mention it,
it's eerily quiet.
Maybe they went to John's.
Oh, nope. I know
exactly where they went.
Tonight, we talk the best of Sara Lance.
Yep.
The tallest tales.
It's time to write the Legend.
Who wants to go first?
Hey!
I will.
No!
I knew it in my bones!
- Oh, my gosh, is this really you?
- Hey.
Oh, my God. I missed you.
Oh, Mick Rory, you salty bloody bastard,
I can't believe you did it, mate.
You saved her. Well done.
Oh, Mick, I am so proud of you!
I never lost faith. Mm!
Oh, look who it is:
Alien Gary who kidnapped Sara.
No, I can explain. That's not...
He didn't kidnap me. He saved me.
Be honest: Rory flew up to the planet,
but it was really me
that saved you, right?
Yeah, yeah, B. Let's go with that one.
All right. You guys,
what do you think, huh?
Let's go home.
- Let's go home!
- Home!
- Yes, please!
- Let's go. Come on.
You know, tonight got me thinking.
What if I don't get my magic back?
- Okay.
- Then I still got you.
You do, but I know you're gonna try.
I'll turn hell upside down, love.
Well, it's going to come in handy
having a superhero girlfriend then.
- Yeah.
- Those two sure got serious.
I have so much to tell you
when we get back to the ship.
- I cannot even...
- Man, time travel is so weird.
Here we are again.
It's like nothing has changed,
and yet everything has changed
at the same time.
Yes, but tonight
I'm not leaving you behind.
And tonight, I want to
propose to my girlfriend.
No.
Oh!
Oh, my God. It's happening.
- Ava...
- Yes, I will!
Sorry.
Sorry, I'm just so excited.
Please finish.
When I was up there in space,
floating further
and further away, I realized something.
No matter where I go or when I am,
I will never be lost because I have you.
You are my North Star.
You are my guiding light,
and wherever you lead me,
that's my home.
Do I say yes now?
No, not yet.
[LAUGHS]
Ava Sharpe...
will you marry me?
[WARM MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- This is when you say...
- Yes, yes! Yes, baby!
- Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
You remembered to take the bomb
- out of the mannequin, right?
- [TIMER BEEPS]
♪ ♪
[ALL CHEERING]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -