Last season on
"Legends of Tomorrow"...
We have the six totems,
but you can't fight
what you can't see. What
if the only way to kill
Mallus is to let him out?
- Guys, we did it!
- My father's Time Stone.
He died to give you a second chance.
Don't waste it.
Whose brilliant idea was
it to let an ancient demon
out of his bloody cage?
Well, you opened a door, love,
and Mallus wasn't the
only thing that got out.
[UNICORN WHINNIES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
REPORTER: The newest musical sensation
to cross the Atlantic...
A group of young men from Liverpool
who call themselves the Beatles
have just arrived at JFK.
The Beatles.
That's B-E-A-T,
because that's the
way they keep the beat.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Hey, Z, if you had to sleep with one,
which one would it be?
How can you even tell them apart?
Well, Paul's the cute one,
George is the quiet
one, there's Ringo...
Never met an Englishman
I haven't wanted to
punch in the face.
Relax, Mick,
if it wasn't for the British Invasion,
there would be no Rolling Stones,
no Led Zep,
no Black Sabbath.
- Black Sabbath.
- Yup.
Well, then we... We need to protect
these mopheads from whatever's
- screwing up history.
- That's right, Mick.
So, Gideon sent us
on a wild goose chase.
This event in history is playing out
exactly as it should.
[BLAST]
The British are coming!
Interesting fact: the
real Paul Revere didn't
actually say... Oh, my
God, it's Paul Revere!
- I got this.
- Who are you people?
Where am I? Why are all
those women screaming?
And now for the midnight
ride of Ray Revere.
[WHISTLES] Sorry.
Nate Revere to the rescue.
Now ring the alarm back in 1775.
I got a country to save, suckers!
See ya back on the ship, Nate.
The British are coming!
Whoo!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
- Re-synced by darthfrede -
www.addic7ed.com
[ENGINE WHOOSHING]
[BLOWING RASPBERRY]
Geez, who died?
Oh, come on.
We just met the Beatles
and saved Fourth of July.
No, it's cool; it's just all becoming...
I don't know. Old hat.
Yeah, we did spend all of
last night year returning
displaced people to their
proper place in history.
Four years doing the same old crap.
Yeah, I'm beginning to think
Wally had the right idea...
Taking time off, clearing
his head, traveling the world.
Speaking of the same old crap,
isn't that what he did last year?
Look, all I know is,
Constantine promised us new,
mysterious monsters, so
where they all hiding?
I'm confused.
We are all happy that there
was only one dragon, right?
We don't want to be fighting
werewolves in the Alamo.
Eh.
Well, it would be good for our ratings.
- What ratings?
- Oh, you don't know?
The Time Bureau rates
all their employees.
But don't worry. We have
a few dedicated fans.
Yeah, Gary doesn't count.
Who gives a damn about Time Pig ratings?
I want dragons.
What is wrong with you guys?
Don't you get it? Constantine was wrong.
Our crazy plan to let Mallus out worked.
Finally, we're not screw-ups
forced to clean up our own mess.
For once in our lives,
we are actual heroes.
Captain, I'm receiving a communiqué
from Director Sharpe.
ALL: Ooh!
Put her on, Gideon.
[HOLOGRAM BLIPS]
Captain Lance,
I would like you and your team to report
to the Time Bureau immediately.
Copy that.
Gideon, set a course for Star City...
I'm not talking about our
field office, Miss Lance.
I meant our Time Bureau
Headquarters in D.C.
Over and out.
[HOLOGRAM BLIPS]
Dammit!
Who told Ava about the dragon?
[ENGINE ROARS]
You sure that you can't tell
us what all this is about?
Oh, I'd love to, but the
boss-lady will kill me.
Mick.
- [GRUNTS]
- Talk.
I can't. Director Sharpe said...
Whatever Ava threatened is nothing
compared to what I'm about to do to you.
You told her about the
dragon head, didn't you, Gary?
- What? No.
- Did Constantine
- get you to squeal?
- I wish.
We looked; there are no more monsters.
- This isn't what you think.
- [SIGHS]
Then what the hell is it?
ALL: Surprise!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
On behalf of the Time Bureau,
I would like to recognize
Captain Lance and her crew for
fixing the final Anachronism.
Congratulations!
[CLICKS]
What does that even mean?
Well, it means that...
[CLEARS THROAT] Paul Revere was
the final crack in the timeline.
You, my friends, fixed history.
- The same history we broke.
- Just take the win.
I don't want your stinking medal.
There's an open bar.
Where?
Sorry, Sara, I know you
don't like surprises, but...
I like this one.
Now I was thinking maybe
you could give me a tour
of the Headquarters, Director Sharpe.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Gee, I really wonder how
she managed to escape
from the Time Bureau.
Yeah...
I mean... I mean, if I had to...
If I had to guess,
I'd probably say that
someone must have given Nora
her dead father's Time Stone.
And furthermore, that
someone must have done it
in hopes that she would
turn over a new leaf in life.
Sounds like that someone
forgot about Nora's serious
lack of ethics... around
a murder, for one...
But that someone must have had
a really big heart to
give her a second chance.
You're a good guy, Ray Palmer.
[AIR WHOOSHING]
- Okay, I gotta go.
- No, no, no...
Yes, I gotta get back to the ship.
The Legends aren't used
to being on furlough.
Come on, they will
be fine for one night.
Besides, I was hoping that you
and your team would be
spending more time here in 2018.
But mostly, you know...
You, with me...
In this apartment.
Ava Sharpe.
Are you trying to make
a kept woman out of me?
[GASPS] What? No! I wouldn't dare.
I'm... just...
saying that, you know,
since you fixed all the Anachronisms
maybe you wouldn't mind being kept,
just part of the time.
It would be fun to come home to you.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
Oh, that was stupid.
You just got back into
town, and here I am hitching
the old U-Haul to the
back of the Subaru.
- It was stupid.
- [LAUGHS] No, no.
Hey, it wasn't that. I'm...
I'm just thinking and...
I'm ready to take the next step.
I...
am ready
to be a partially kept woman.
Yes! [GIGGLES] Come here.
Mm. Mm!
Okay, so why don't you, uh, rustle us up
another bottle of champagne,
and let's make this thing official.
- That, I can do.
- Yeah?
[CORK POPS]
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
Hello, John.
You know, tonight really isn't
a night for celebration, Sara.
The darkness, it's rising.
What are you doing? And
what does that even mean?
Mallus wasn't the
only prisoner to escape
when you decided to pull back
the veil between our worlds.
And yet for the past five months,
the Timeline has been quiet.
If you wanted to come and see me,
all you had to do was ask.
Five months is a blink of an eye
for an immortal monster.
Look, this is your bloody mess, Sara,
so stop playing
tiddlywinks with the missus
and get ready for the
fight that's coming.
What if this is who I am now?
Really?
[WHISTLES] This is who you are?
Fuzzy throws and fluffy pink slippers?
I like my pink fluffy slippers.
- [LAUGHS]
- Okay, reunion's over.
Time to go.
[MURMURS INCANTATIONS]
What am I looking at?
The knuckle bones of a
martyred saint, obviously.
They act as a divining rod
able to detect the presence
of beings not belonging to our world.
My team spent the last five
months scouring the Timeline
for another one of
your mystical creatures.
You wanna know what we found? Nothing.
What the hell are you doing here?
[BONES CLINK]
Is everything all right?
Yeah, everything is great.
- I was just telling Sara...
- About an exorcism
that he has to do
tomorrow in Georgetown.
It's really nothing you
wanna hear before bedtime.
Come back again soon now, John.
Don't be shy about that doorbell.
I'll be seeing you around, Sharpie.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
Should I be worried about
your ex-lover breaking
into my apartment, or...
Well, I thought that...
this was our apartment.
[SIGHS] You are smooth.
Don't forget the bubbly.
[BONES CLACKING]
[SIGHS] Bollocks.
Mick, what are you still doing here?
Machine's still spinning,
and I'm still standing.
You know what? Hook me
up with one of those.
Now that we fixed our last Anachronism,
it's only a matter of
time before the Bureau
puts us out to pasture, which blows,
because being a Legend was
the only thing I was good at.
Well, speak for yourself.
I was a great criminal.
At least we got these cool medals.
Actually, the medal has
to remain top secret,
because no one can
know about time travel,
so I'll just take these
back now for safe-keeping...
What do you say you and
I find some real action?
Mick, I am 100% down.
Ooh! I'll come with.
[GROWLS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
I could have just called us an Uber.
You ready to steal something pretty?
Um... [BLOWS RASPBERRY] yeah.
I could do some light theft.
What is this, spring break?
I'm talking about a felony.
- Now get in!
- You know what, Mick?
If we're gonna rob a
house, we really should
make sure there's stuff
in there worth stealing.
And I think I know
just the neighborhood.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Mick, wait, wait, wait!
You are so aggressive.
Why don't you look for a spare key?
- Good spotting, pretty.
- Yeah.
I'm a real criminal mastermind.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[DOOR CLICKS]
Bingo.
[GUN COCKS]
Yes, I'd like to report a robbery.
You will do nothing of the sort.
Oh, Nate, it is so good to see you!
What the hell is going on here?
Um, Mick... these are my parents.
I am Dorothy Heywood;
you can call me Dot. Hi.
And uh, this is my dad, Hank.
Henry Heywood.
And I believe one of
my great grandmother's
silver candlesticks has
found its way into your coat.
Oh, you have exquisite
taste in silver, Mr....
Rory. Mick Rory,
of the Central City Rorys.
We didn't mean to scare you, Mom.
I thought you'd be up
by Martha's Vineyard
this time of year.
Oh, we were! But your father just took
a very exciting job at the Pentagon.
We'll... we'll get going, right, Mick?
- Good idea.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Mr. Rory, do you like sandwiches?
Bet your ass, I do ma'am.
Wonderful, then, um,
I'm gonna fix you boys
a little midnight snack.
You too, Henry; you're one of the boys.
[SNORING]
Gary, wake up!
[GLASS CLANGING]
I got a hunch there might be
a monster loose in history.
Like the dragon you made me
not tell Director Sharpe about?
Exactly.
[SIGHS]
[BLIPS]
No.
The Timeline's only showing a few burps.
This is the only significant one.
What if there's a creature
that no one's noticed yet?
The only way people
wouldn't notice a monster is
if it was hiding.
Or if they were on drugs.
I'm gonna go check it out.
- Ooh, I'll come with!
- Nope.
But if you're going back to
1969, you're gonna need...
Your time courier.
[SIGHS]
Going somewhere, Raymond?
And don't give me any of that
routine maintenance
on the jumpship crap.
Yeah, no. I wouldn't do that.
I... I had Gideon
monitor the Time Bureau.
Someone over there pulled up
unusual activity in Woodstock,
- 1969.
- You think it's Nora,
and if the Time Bureau finds her first,
she's going to tell them you're
the one who helped her escape.
Ray, I'm not going to let
you get on that jumpship.
But...
- Not without me.
- Oh, good.
I was not looking forward to dealing
with those hippies on my own.
What's a hippie?
["GOING UP THE COUNTRY" BY CANNED HEAT]
♪ I'm goin' up the country ♪
♪ Baby, don't you wanna go? ♪
♪ I'm goin' to some place
where I've never been before ♪
Give peace a chance.
Together, we can end the war in Vietnam.
[CHUCKLES] Hey!
Yeah, this place is groovy.
So, tell me, why would
Nora Time Stone to the least
- evil event in history?
- Well, who knows?
Maybe she's turning over
a new, non-evil leaf,
inspired by yours truly.
Right.
- All right.
- What is that?
Oh, it's my old trusty
Eagle Scout compass.
I thought we could locate
the epicenter of the temporal
disturbance the old-fashioned way.
- It sounds like a blast, Ray.
- Yeah!
197, 198, 199...
Sorry, Ray. Looks like
Nora's in the wind.
What is that?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
What is that? Ray!
It's beautiful.
It's like some sort
of magical pixie goo.
No, not that. That!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God,
oh my God, oh my God!
Why? Who would wanna
kill hippies at Woodstock?
Literally ripping people's hearts out!
Now that's the Nora I remember.
You certainly can eat
a lot of sandwiches, Mr. Rory.
Where did you get those big muscles?
Prison.
[LAUGHS] What a hoot!
Isn't he a hoot, Henry?
He's a real barrel of laughs.
[LAUGHS] Excuse me.
So you just drop in on us
in the middle of the night,
after barely a phone call
for the past two years?
I know, Dad, I'm sorry.
- I've just been busy.
- Busy doing what?
History stuff.
You know, the same stuff
you never took seriously.
Maybe that's because
deductive historical
reconstruction isn't
an actual profession!
I'm sorry.
So should I have your mother
just grab her checkbook
now, or would you prefer
your friend here swipe it out
- of her purse on the way out?
- It would be easy either way.
I don't want your money, dad.
Then, why are you here?
Honestly, I don't know.
You don't...
We had a name for people like you,
- back in my day...
- Oh.
Here comes the big rant
about hippies, go ahead.
To tell the truth, I have nothing
but pity for those people.
Yeah, since when?
Since they were slaughtered
like lambs back in '69.
Look, I'm not saying
the Woodstock Massacre
was their fault,
but it wasn't not their fault either.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Mom, thanks for the sandwiches!
Wha...
There's something wrong with history.
Not Noras. Hi!
Not Nora, not Nora...
definitely not Nora.
Ray, I really don't need
to hear your inner dialogue.
Sorry, I'm just...
I'm... I'm... I'm nervous,
and upset. I mean, how
could she be so heartless?
Pun not intended.
Well, her father did give her
over to a demon-loving cult so.
- Nora Darhk is here?
- Sara?
Hey, what are you doing at Woodstock?
Probably the same thing as you are,
looking for whatever
is messing with history.
Huh, I think I just
saw Joan Baez talking to
Carlos Santana. Woodstock...
- Turns into a massacre.
- Nate! You're here too?
Yeah, buddy.
Hey. [GRUNTS]
- Hey!
- Okay, what is going on?
Woodstock is no longer
remembered as three days of
peace and love, but instead,
the end of the hippie movement.
Reports from survivors
are sketchy at best.
But what they all could agree
upon was there was a series of
grisly murders that ultimately
lead to a deadly stampede
when 400,000 kids try to
escape the festival at once.
Yeah, Ray and I just
saw a body in the woods
with a gaping hole in its chest.
We think that Nora did it.
- Well, that's a relief.
- It is?
Yeah, it means we're in the clear.
Look, it's not our fault the
Time Bureau let Nora escape.
Guys, come check this out.
Don't panic, I left Mick alone here.
He's itching to punch a hippie.
That's not good.
Is that what I think it is?
Twilight Sparkle come to life.
[WHINNIES]
You're a brony?
Dude, we're brony bros.
- Mick, join the herd!
- Outta my way.
Hey, hey, hey! What are you doing?
Well, it's not a dragon,
but it'll have to do.
Mick, hold on, it's not
like it's hurting anyone.
[WHINNIES]
[ALL EXCLAIMING IN AWE]
We didn't screw things up
for the better this year.
We screwed things up
for the more magical.
[NICKERS]
It's beautiful!
[DRAMATIC STING]
[SCREAMING]
Oh, my God!
[BODY THUDS]
What!
[GROWLING]
Oh, my God! Is it...
Yup, yup. It's eating her heart.
I'm gonna be sick.
[EERIE MUSIC]
- Mick, shoot it.
- Shoot it!
[GRUNTING]
Damn horse is fire-proof.
[HISSING]
[NICKERS]
[GROANING]
I hate glitter.
[SPUTTERING, GROANING]
Seriously?
- Where'd it go?
- Okay, we can fix this
before the Time Bureau
even has to know about it.
Oh, really? Can we?
Look, Ava still thinks
of me as the woman
who saved the world
last year, and I don't
want her to know that there's a
whole new problem with history.
Yeah, that we basically created.
You go find the unicorn,
and I'll go find Constantine.
Yup.
Every time.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
[MUTTERING] Somebody
can't read bloody signs.
You don't know that there's
a "do not disturb" sign
on the bloody door?
Sara.
Yeah, uh... I can't
talk right now, love.
I've got a threesome
that's about to pop off
in here with some contortionists.
You were right.
Ah.
What was that now?
You were right!
There's a magical creature
at Woodstock. Now let's go!
You know, for someone with
a time traveling machine,
you seem to be in an awful hurry.
John, the unicorn has
already gored two hippies.
- A unicorn?
- Yeah.
Well, all right, I'm in.
But first, I need to know,
was any of your team
musked by the beast?
If that's what you're calling
its sparkle-sauce, then, yeah. Why?
Oh, they're in for one hell of a ride.
[GROANING]
Man, I wish my dad could see us
now hunting a bloodthirsty
creature through Woodstock.
What's the beef between
you and your old man anyway?
- He hit you?
- No.
- Burn you?
- Nope.
Did he dress up like a clown
and scare the hell out of you?
What the hell, Mick? No.
He was emotionally unavailable
to me when I was growing up.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
To the whole world,
my dad was this great
larger-than-life guy, but to me,
he was just cold.
Boo-hoo!
[EERIE MUSIC BUILDS]
Hank?
What?
I'm not your dad!
Oh, so you're ashamed of me?
I'm sorry I didn't follow
in your footsteps and enlist.
But for your information, I
had a medal pinned to my chest,
only you don't have
the clearance to see it!
What's happening?
What?
Axl?
[SQUEAKING]
I'm getting something off my chest.
And you know what, Hank?
It feels pretty good.
I just wish for once, you
would tell me you're proud of me
no matter what I do with my life.
You know what I'd say?
I love you.
I love you too.
- Really?
- I thought you were dead.
I thought you were dead on the inside.
[LAUGHS]
♪ I've been waiting for a long time ♪
Ray. Ray, my hand is glowing.
- Can you see it?
- No.
- It looks like your hand.
- No, no.
You gotta open your eyes, man.
[EXHALES] It's all around us.
What is?
Love.
Oh, those hippies had the right idea.
Woodstock is beautiful.
[GASPS]
- What's wrong, Ray?
- What?
You were hoping to see Nora here.
You like her, Ray-Ray!
No, no!
I do not like Nora.
Uh-huh, because you love her.
No-o, no!
The only reason I ever want
to see Nora Darhk again is
so that I can take
the Time Stone back and
I can lock her up in the Time Bureau.
Oh, my God, she's here!
[CHIMING]
You know, a unicorn is no bloody joke.
You might want to get your
ol' girlfriend on the blower.
You didn't tell Director Sharpe
that you let all the
monsters out to play, did you?
Ava and I are in a
great place right now.
Better than great.
In fact, she asked me to move
in with her, and I said yes.
So, why rock the boat
unless absolutely necessary?
Because when the boat eventually tips,
- you'll both bloody drown.
- Nice.
I'm just trying to look after you, love.
You and I are similar;
we're both survivors.
But our survival comes
at a terrible cost.
Look, you can take it from
a man who's caused nothing
but misery to everyone he's ever loved.
Trust me, end it with
Ava before it's too late.
You ever think that you cause misery
not because of some romantic
"I was born to walk alone" crap,
but because you're an ass
who doesn't know how to trust people?
You know, I trust
that people around me get hurt, killed,
or far, far worse...
You think that I'm not scared?
That I don't know grief?
I'm not willing to turn my back on life,
because that is exactly
what you're doing, John.
Our friends and family,
they don't make us weaker;
they make us stronger.
You know what you need?
You need to be a part of a team.
♪ ♪
You were saying?
This is King Solomon's
original grimoire...
The oldest magical
textbook in existence.
Now, if there's a spell
to quell our equine friend,
it'll be in here.
Well, not to pressure
you, but the entire fate of
the sexual revolution
is in the balance here.
It is my favorite revolution.
- John! Welcome aboard.
- Hey, Ray big-man!
Glad to see you're all
back from the land of milk
- and honey.
- I'm still a little
fuzzy on how exactly we were...
Roofied by a horse.
That beast sprays a powerful
mind-altering hallucinogen
to disarm its prey.
Ah!
"How to expel a magical creature
from the mortal realm."
Now the ingredients for
this spell aren't so easy
to come by.
Don't suppose any of
you lot have the saliva
from a nine-fingered man, now do you?
You could chop off one of my pinkies.
No, Ray. Don't be the Giving Tree.
Now, as every Deadhead knows,
Jerry Garcia was missing
most of his middle finger
on his right hand from
a wood chopping accident.
Cool, so how do we get his saliva?
["WHITE RABBIT" BY
JEFFERSON AIRPLANE PLAYING]
Jerry, my man!
Can I get a hit of that?
This doobie will make you fly.
Cool, cool.
- Spin-move!
- Hey!
Not cool.
We need the Protection
Stone of a powerful shaman.
Watch it...
♪ Go ask Alice ♪
♪ When she's ten feet tall ♪
Brother.
And the lock of a doomed woman.
[WHIRRING]
♪ When the men on the chessboard ♪
♪ Get up and tell you where to go ♪
Janis, this is... This
is quite the honor.
- Little robot man.
- Hi.
My mom is a huge fan.
Your mom? [LAUGHS]
And for our final ingredient...
♪ I think she'll know ♪
Quis virginem.
What?
A virgin.
A virgin, at Woodstock? Ha!
Good luck with that;
this is the least celibate
place in history.
Are you serious?
Yeah, apparently virgins are
like catnip to unicorns
and we need one to volunteer.
Rory, do you see any
virgins where you're at?
♪ ♪
- No.
- Oh, come to think of it...
I do know one virgin.
No, not a chance.
- This feels wrong.
- Well don't worry, we'll be
watching from a short
distance, and you'll be... fine.
What am I supposed to
do with the pomegranate?
Oh, the unicorns, they can't
get enough of them, mate.
Yeah that, and human hearts.
So, the pomegranate is the bait?
Yeah, we wouldn't put an interim member
of our team in jeopardy, right guys?
I'm an interim Legend?
Well, then.
Uh, one more question, are
you sure that I'm a virgin
because that thing we did...
Positive, mate.
Yoo-hoo! Mr. Unicorn!
Come get this nice,
juicy, red pomegranate.
Admit it, this is fun
working with a team.
Well if ol' Gary gets eaten alive,
it only goes to prove my point:
People who care about us die.
- What was that?
- Oh, nothing mate.
You're golden, carry on, yeah?
Oh, hold it up... up a bit. More!
That's the money.
[UNICORN WHINNIES]
♪ ♪
[CHIMING]
Come on, pretty pony.
Come on, come on.
Enjoy your snack.
[HEART BEATING]
Oh, no, that's not pomegranate
juice, is it? Guys?
John, whatever you're
gonna do, do it now!
All right, here goes.
[ROARING]
I don't wanna die a virgin!
[TENSE MUSIC]
[WHIMPERING]
[SNARLING]
♪ ♪
[ROARING]
Seriously, you're meditating right now?
John, hurry!
[MURMURING INCANTATIONS]
♪ ♪
[SNARLING]
Come on, John.
[SHOUTING INCANTATIONS]
[WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
[SHOUTING INCANTATIONS]
Help! Help!
[SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
[SNARLING]
[SCREAMING]
[WHOOSHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSICAL STING]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
Gary, are you okay?
- Just a scratch.
- Where'd the unicorn go?
Sent that bastard
straight to hell, didn't I?
Yup, folks, that is some
Grade A magic right there.
Maybe the Bureau will up our ratings.
People do love the supernatural.
Gary, you're like really bleeding.
Ah!
The unicorn bit my nipple off!
Hey, maybe Gideon can
make you a new one.
Forget it, mate. Come
on, it's a badge of honor.
You see, my soul is
heading straight to hell,
but your nipple... it just
got there first, that's all.
It's like we're two birds
of the same, dark feather.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, mate.
Come on, let's grab a beer.
All right?
Now about this whole virgin situation.
Nathaniel...
I assumed you would
have left town by now.
Yeah, I decided to stay
a couple extra days.
Let me guess, you got fired
from whatever online college
you conned into hiring you.
Sweet burn, Hank, but um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
I was just...
wondering if you wanted
to have a beer with me?
We don't do that.
Maybe we should start.
Wow, you're looking a
little glum there buddy.
Just, uh... thinking about all
the musicians who died after Woodstock.
Janis Joplin overdosed in 1970,
sad and alone.
That's terrible, but this
is obviously about Nora.
When I gave her the Time
Stone, our hands touched,
and... I felt a spark.
Ray, Nora is...
Nora is like a unicorn,
beautiful and dangerous.
She is going to eat you alive.
I guess she and I are doomed.
There's something I want to show you.
Come on.
Okay.
I don't understand.
What are we doing here?
That's my mom, and that's me.
We lived in D.C.
in 2018 before my brother was born.
It would be so easy, Ray...
to just walk over there
and tell her to get her
family and go to Canada
before everything changes;
before this country that
she worked so hard to become
a citizen of betrays her.
You'd be changing your future.
You'd never meet us, you'd
never become a Legend.
Think of all the people you saved.
Yeah, I know. I know.
There's no loophole where I can
save my family, and not screw
up history, but that doesn't
mean I don't feel guilty every
day that I have the power
to change everything, and...
I do nothing.
I'm so sorry, Z.
Look at her, Ray.
How could anyone be afraid of her?
[GENTLE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Hello!
- Smells good in here.
Oh, yeah, I, uh, burned
the first chicken piccata,
but I think I got the
second one just right.
Those our medals?
I wanted to remind you of all
the good you did last year.
Yeah, we, um... We weren't that good.
Would you stop being so
hard on yourself, Sara?
I'm proud of you.
When we freed Mallus,
we accidentally released
magical monsters into the world.
And I didn't want to tell
you because I love the idea
of us living together, and
I didn't want to risk that
or you thinking that maybe
I wasn't such a screw-up.
I know.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
Gary was very proud
about losing a nipple.
- But you cooked dinner...
- Yeah!
Because I love you, you goober, and
nothing is gonna change that.
Even after I went behind your back
to work with Constantine
to send a unicorn to hell?
Okay, yeah, I wasn't so
crazy about that part.
Let's not talk about Constantine.
I'm crazy about you. Come here.
Stop being neurotic.
I don't think that you're a screw-up.
I think that you are
a damn fine Captain,
faced with some
extraordinary circumstances.
God, I love you.
And...
I got a question.
- Do we...
- Mm-hmm.
You and I,
think that maybe right now
is not the best time for me to move in?
You know that I want to;
nothing would make me happier.
It's just... I feel like
I need to be out there.
- With my team.
- I understand.
But can you promise me
that our relationship will
continue to evolve, please?
I want this... You and me... for real.
So do I.
We're gonna figure it out.
[MOANS]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
[INCANTATION]
[DOOR OPENS]
No.
I haven't even asked you anything yet.
It's not even magic,
love, it's deduction.
You need me to join the Legends,
despite knowing that needing me
always causes somebody trouble.
What is up with you?
Something must have happened
in the last five months.
You're more mierable than usual.
Look...
You and I are friends.
And I like friends.
Friends are useful, but roommates...
See, Sara, I would
rather bloody top myself
than move in with you lot.
See you around, John.
[DOOR CLICKS SHUT]
So long, Sara.
♪ One pill makes you larger ♪
♪ And another makes you small ♪
♪ And the pill that ♪
♪ Mother gives ya ♪
♪ Don't do anything at all ♪
[GULPS]
♪ Ah, go ask Alice ♪
♪ When she's ten feet ♪
- [ELECTRICITY WHIRRING]
- ♪ Tall ♪
[CREATURE SNARLS]
All right then, who are ya?
Come on, who wants some?
'Cause I'm a nasty piece of work.
[THRUMMING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[GROANING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
Get your bloody paws off me!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[GARBLED VOICES]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[PANTING]
[CREAKING]
Oh, bollocks.
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
- Re-synced by darthfrede -
www.addic7ed.com