The Legends of Tomorrow are everywhere.
Since they defeated a demon
with the help of a dragon
on national TV, they've
become a worldwide obsession.
Sure, we've all been mesmerized
by the global phenomenon
known as "Legends-mania."
- Yum.
- [GIRL LAUGHS] Yum!
And the Oscar for
best picture goes to...
But who are the people beneath
those supersized public personas?
Roar.
What are they like when
the spotlight is off?
I'm Kevin Harris, and my
documentary film crew is
the first ever to be
granted unfettered access
to their lives and their
ship, the Waverider.
So strap in because
today, we meet the Legends.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So why don't we start with
just a brief introduction,
and let us know what we're
doing today on the Waverider.
Uh, yeah.
Hi, I'm... I'm Ava Sharpe.
After Congress shut
down the Time Bureau,
Sara went off to help
Oliver Queen and, uh,
I had to fight to keep the
Waverider from being impounded.
Bad luck that the senator
chairing the committee
was the same person we
almost killed last year.
Senator Wellington, I know
the Time Bureau may have been
compromised, but you must allow
the Waverider to continue
patrolling the timeline.
Ms. Sharpe, how do we know
these so called "Legends"
can be trusted with time travel?
Well, there's simply no transparency.
Which is why you all are here.
Right? To show everyone what we do.
What could go wrong?
The Waverider was surprisingly quiet
because half the team
was away on a mission.
Oh, the crossover, yeah,
had to take a rain check.
See, when you are a superhero
slash amusement park impresario,
slash historian that
rises from the dead,
your dance card tends
to get pretty full.
For two full minutes, I was not alive.
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
That changes you, man.
Don't get me wrong, I love fame.
No one says no to you about anything.
Hey, man, that's a
cool hat. Can I have it?
[STIRRING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
But still, something doesn't feel right.
[JAZZY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, sorry. Hang on.
[AIR WHOOSHING]
There we go.
Hi, I'm Behrad Tarazi.
I guess you probably think
I'm some kind of awesome future man,
since I'm from 2044.
My literal birthday was yesterday,
which is pretty wild, man.
[WHISPERING] That's me.
Hey baby Behrad, be easy
and go with the flow,
like Wu-Tang Clan and Bruce Lee.
I mean, now that we're no
longer D-list superheroes,
we can just go where we
want, do as we please.
Why have I stuck around?
Tell you the truth,
I have no bloody clue.
I am bored as a post. Ain't I?
Gids, I'm nicking the
jumpship, all right?
I'll see you when I see you.
The jumpship is fully totemed.
She's a mad old bat, that one.
[GIGGLES]
Hi, I'm Mona Wu. I'm a Kaupe.
Uh, that's basically like
a werewolf but Hawaiian.
[JUMPSHIP FIRING]
I'm also a literary agent
for romance novelist Rebecca Silver,
[WHISPERING] who is secretly Mick Rory.
Jeez, Peter, take me out on
a date first before you try to
[CLAPS] you know.
Basically, what I do
is I sell movie rights,
get book advances, that kind of stuff.
You're telling me that you
don't have a single dollar
for a Rebecca Silver book advance?
Okay, now you're not
just disrespecting me,
[VOICE DEEPENS] you're
disrespecting my client!
[ROARS]
Not now! Pay up or I will thrash you!
Hi, I'm Gary Green.
Um, if I had to sum
myself up in two words
they would be, uh, fully forgiven.
A lot of things happened last
year that you could misconstrue
as potentially, maybe being my fault.
But thankfully everyone
agrees that at worst
I was just a hapless
rube who got manipulated
by the forces of Hell
to betray humanity.
I had a fairy godmother named Nora,
but we separated amicably
after she granted me
my heart's deepest wish.
Gary, what the hell are you doing?
Come on, we've got bigger fish to fry.
Nora made me Constantine's apprentice.
Gary!
Call me.
So how does your girlfriend feel
about the documentary being made?
Actually, I haven't, uh, told Sara
about the... the documentary yet.
I just think it was a little
awkward over the phone.
It's better to, you
know, spring it on her
when she gets back from the big mission.
Okay, big smiles everyone.
And nobody mention Oliver Queen.
Why?
Because he died.
Shouldn't have done the crossover.
[DOOR SLIDING]
[PARTY HORN BLOWS]
[TOGETHER] Surprise!
Yeah!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[TOGETHER] Oh, bros.
Orange drink or limeade?
Alcohol.
Hey, love. Welcome back, baby.
What is going on?
Before you object, let me explain.
The only way that I could
stop Senator Wellington
from cutting off our funding was
to be clear and transparent
about our process.
Get it?
So you're shooting a
documentary about the Legends?
Not me, per se. [CLEARS THROAT]
Hi, Captain Lance, huge fan.
Uh, I'm the director, Kevin Harris.
You can call me Kev.
Just carry on, do what you're
doing; we're not even here.
That's Kev. He's got it under control.
And what if I wanna talk
about something in private?
It's not a problem,
that's what the confessional
interviews are for.
Oh. [LAUGHS]
Okay, so I can... I can
just say it to the camera.
Sure.
My girlfriend, she's lost her mind.
[LAUGHS]
She just... she really
probably needs a nap.
She gets a little sleepy
after a long mission.
Um... oh, Mick, why
don't you tell us all
what you do on the ship, huh?
I steal stuff. Get out
of my way, you punks.
Okay, he's just joking. Uh, Ray!
Who else saved the multiverse?
Oh, uh, well The Flash,
Supergirl, Batwoman.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
What, no Superman?
Couldn't have been that big a deal.
Oh, no, no, Superman was there.
He's very handsome.
It's good to have you back, buddy.
Yeah.
Hey, we're missing someone.
Where's Charlie?
Took the jumpship for a joyride.
A joyride to check the timeline.
Right? It's called a timescout.
Now, who wants to
visit the temporal zone?
Shall we?
[WAVERIDER ENGINES HUMMING]
[GROANS]
Guys, I'm still outside.
I'm still outside! Don't leave me!
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer, The Atom.
This documentary is
an exciting opportunity
for me to improve my image.
A lot of people still
confuse me for the demon
who possessed me and opened
up the gates of Hell.
His name was Neron and he is
no longer with me or inside me
or, um...
I really wish that you could
meet my girlfriend, Nora.
But she works out of town
a lot, internationally.
She's got a lot of global
clients, kids mostly.
She is a fairy godmother.
There's something behind you.
[EXPLOSION]
Is this a timequake?
See, I knew the timeline
was still in jeopardy.
What do we got? Time pirates,
time terrorism, time sex tourism?
Jeez, Ava, you could be a supervillain
if you applied yourself.
Gideon, what's the point of origin?
It appears my Jonah Hex
has Beebo lala loves you.
Gideon may have a virus.
Doesn't she make everything work?
We are perfectly safe.
Guys, that was a class five timequake.
That is so dangerous.
Okay, guys, let's just try to
keep our composure, shall we?
I've triangulated the timequake
to 1917, St. Petersburg, Russia.
Let's go and shrink the problem.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
I'm developing a catchphrase?
Executing time jump now.
No, Gideon, we're not
taking a film crew to...
[WAVERIDER HUMMING AND WHOOSHING]
Imperial Russia. Yeah.
Great. This is great, Ray.
All right, Legends,
put on your babushkas
because we are rushing into Russia.
And now you're copying my thing.
Totally, I just got really excited.
Okay, listen, babe, this
may seem like a problem,
but let's turn it into
a "probltunity," huh?
Maybe a party snake is just
what the doctor ordered.
Uh, what's a party snake?
A sneak, party sneak.
The wonder of time travel
is allowing our cameras
to capture some of
the first color images
of imperial Russia as we ride along
on the Legends' patented party sneak.
Turns out it's more
of a fun funeral sneak.
Who died?
Grigori Rasputin AKA The Mad Monk.
Equal parts mystic advisor
and manipulative hornball.
Rasputin was notoriously hard to kill.
It took cyanide, a gun, and
drowning before he stayed dead.
[COFFIN THUMPING]
[MOURNERS SCREAMING]
[SOLEMN VIOLIN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Um, guys, we sure he stayed dead?
Rasputin came back from the dead,
and it caused a timequake.
Ugh, this is the kind of problem
that I can wrap my head around.
So I need you guys to forget about this
documentary film crew and focus
on the mission at hand, yes?
Yes, we need to minimize the mishap.
Ooh, Ray, that's good.
Because saving the day is
what the Legends do best.
[WHISPERING] Ava, you're in my shot.
Oh, sorry.
Gideon, what does the
historical record say?
Perhaps timeloop...
timeloop released him
from Marion Ravenwood.
Of course. Okay.
B-Money, with me.
We're gonna fix Gideon,
get our guests back to 2020.
Mona, Nate, Ray, I want you
three researching Rasputin.
Figure out what his
next move is gonna be.
Okay? Let's do it.
Hey, Ray. Sorry, but just...
hey, is everything okay with Sara?
Oh, um, I don't know.
But I do know that Oliver's
death was pretty tough on her.
Yeah.
Maybe you should write
Sara a condolence card.
It's actually not a bad idea.
I guess I could try to put
my thoughts and feelings
into words on a card.
What if more baddies start coming back,
like, throughout history?
If they do, we can
call them evil do-overs.
Villa-agains.
I like encores.
[SHIMMERING TONE]
It's a good idea.
We could take a vote,
we could take like a...
Okay, let's vote, let's vote. Encores.
Villa-agains.
Encores.
- Eh.
- Don't be a jerk about it.
[VOICE DEEPENS] Encores!
Meanwhile, back in New York,
Constantine and Gary were
doing some soul searching.
We're here with the great
mage John Constantine
responding to an urgent call
regarding the supernatural.
[KNOCKING]
Oh bloody hell, Gary,
you know I must have been
off my rocker when I
made you my assistant.
Mr. Constantine.
It's what the card says, love.
It's my son Edgar.
I came home late from my shift.
Usually he's up playing video games.
All right, love, there you go.
Now why don't you let
me take a look, eh?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[DEEP GROWL]
What's wrong with him?
His PJs, for starters.
[WALL CRACKING]
Do people really wear
matching pajama sets?
Yes.
[ROARING]
Exorcizamos te, omnis immundus spiritus,
omnis satanic potestas,
John, wait.
Masher?
Masher, is that you possessing the lad?
Glad to see you escaped Hell.
Yeah, well, I could say
the same about you, mate.
Demon's gotta have his fun.
Yeah, well, I could murder
a pint right about now.
Fancy a drink?
You're buying.
You've got it, let's go.
Uh, excuse me, greatest of warlocks,
but what about Edgar's mother?
Good thinking, G-man.
We'll take the fire escape.
[WAVERIDER HUMMING]
[BIRD CAWS]
What exe... able do you wi... x
Captain cat... what interval...
Easy on Gideon, Cap.
What are you wix... table
Captain cat, captain cat...
Is everybody just trying
to get on my nerves today?
Camera crew shows up and, what,
nobody can act like themselves?
Spotlight does weird things to people.
But, hey, you know I'll
always be my true self.
Oh yeah? Your true self?
Don't your parents think
you're in business school?
I am a tangled web.
Enough about me.
How you doing with
Oliver and everything?
[SIGHS] I'm fine.
No worries, we don't
have to talk about it.
But, I made you something.
Oh, please don't be a condolence card
'cause those are always super awkward.
Nah, hopefully something better.
It's you, Ollie, and Laurel.
B, this is actually...
it's really sweet.
Thank you.
My condolence card wasn't awkward.
"Dear Sara, I'm sorry the
vigilante you slept with
when he was already
dating your sister died.
Some say it's better
to have loved and lost,
but I hope you never loved him at all."
Sara and I aren't the type to
give each other cards anyway.
I'd rather do something for her.
You know, like, fix
this Rasputin situation
and get the Legends
the heck out of Russia
before they screw something up.
Uh, you can cut the last
part of that out, right?
Apparently, when Rasputin
cured the Czarina's only son,
the two fell madly in love.
I think if Rasputin realized
how much the Czarina loved him,
he would wanna settle down with her,
lead the kind of quiet life
that doesn't disturb history.
Maybe Rebecca Silver's
next series could be called
"Russian Nights."
So the St. Petersburg elite
hated Rasputin's influence
over the Czarina.
So the Czar's own nephew, a
prince by the name of Yusupov,
he spearheaded the assassination.
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GASPS]
[SNAPS]
Ray, what if old Grigori came back...
- to settle the score.
- To settle the score.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We need to stop Rasputin
from killing Yusupov.
I'm going to deliver a
love letter to Rasputin.
I'm gonna kill Rasputin. You in?
Yep.
Rasputin and I are two wandering souls
who got a second chance at life.
He shouldn't waste
his encore on revenge.
- Damn it.
- What?
Mona was right. Encore feels better.
It does.
Plus, with my new Atom cam,
everybody can watch us
fixing history without any bloodshed.
[SCREAMING]
[BODY THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
And Yusupov's dead.
New plan.
Trespassers.
Whoa, hey, whoa. Don't... don't shoot.
You either.
Show me your hands.
- Um...
- What do you want?
I'm here to interview Rasputin.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Grigori!
Razzmatazz. Do, uh,
people call you Griggy?
There's just been a
slight misunderstanding.
Your monk friends here
think I'm here to kill you,
uh, when really I just
would like to chat.
Oh, this? This is my camera crew.
We're producing a news reel
about your startling return.
After all, you're not a big deal
until you're a big deal on camera.
Grigori Rasputin.
Monk, mystic... it is
hard coming back to life.
I think, what will make me happy?
So I kill the man who killed me.
But am I happy? Eh.
I'll give you Yusupov. He had it coming.
But let's talk big picture, Griggy.
- You rose from the dead.
- Mm-hmm.
That's wild.
Nate, what are you doing?
Now you're in my shot.
To be honest with you,
I'm here to find out
what makes you tick.
Are we killing folks
or chilling with folks?
Sorry, Nate, this one's for Sara.
I got your back, Nate.
Size small, standing tall.
Ugh, Ray.
[GRUNTING]
- Get outta there.
- [MUFFLED SHOUTING]
Rory, you're up.
[KNUCKLES CRACK]
Mona's here.
[SIGHS] Of course she is.
Hi, guys.
I forged a letter that's
gonna save history.
That's for Rasputin.
Hmm, not bad.
Nice use of "musky embrace."
[CHUCKLES] I learned
from Rebecca Silver.
Well, you learned from the best.
You know, your aura is quite strong.
I get that a lot. I
rotate hair products.
Like me, you, too, have
experienced the miracle.
God brought you back to life.
But there's something missing.
I sense a hole in your heart.
There, right there.
You once loved someone,
but you have forgotten.
Allow me to hypnotize you
and I will help you recover
everything you have lost.
Don't even think about it, Nate.
Thank you, Rasputin,
but I'm gonna have to say
yes, 100%, let's do this.
As Nate's party was
about to get started,
Constantine's was coming to an end.
It's not right bringing a kid in here!
Oh, piss off you puritan twit.
I've got to ask, Masher.
Has she done it?
I don't know what you're
talking about, John.
Don't be coy with me.
Has Astra released the worst
souls from Hell onto Earth?
What can I say?
The girl's all grown up
and making money moves.
The question is...
what are you gonna do?
Well, I don't need to do
anything about it, all right?
My life is settled right now.
I'm not gonna stir up a
hornets' nest of trouble
because Astra Logue wants to break
the glass ceiling in Hell.
Is that so?
You smug git.
[CHUCKLING]
Right then, sorry about this.
Ah, no, at least let me have a swig.
Exorcizamos te, omnis immundus spiritus,
omnis satanic potestas...
You're a bastard, John!
[ROARS]
In nomine et virtute exorcisazo te.
[WHEEZING]
- Where's my mom?
- Gary.
Yes, master of the dark arts.
Hail the Waverider, will you?
I need to warn the Legends.
Uh, but what about Edgar?
Ah, you know, give him the usual.
One taxi and a lollipop. Coming up.
[SIGHS] I see you, you creep.
What? What do you want?
You want my confessional?
All right, come here,
I'll give one to you.
I confess that I hate this doc.
I confess that I don't
want to be a celebrity.
And I confess that if
you don't get that camera
- out of my face...
- Captain.
I think Gideon is
suffering from phantom data.
Do you want me to come back later?
No, you should stay.
Stay with me, hang out. Let's get lit.
Questionable timing, but
should I get my stash box?
Yes, you should.
Captain, I have an incoming Bollywood.
[STATIC NOISE]
I think that's better.
Yeah, I can see myself.
Sara, what's with the connection?
Gideon has a bug and
we're trying to get buzzed.
What do you want?
Listen up, all right?
Some of the most evil
souls in all of history
have been raised from Hell.
Did you hear him? He said "Hell."
Get... get out.
Relax, Nathaniel.
Focus on my voice and this bauble.
Now drop into the
deepest part of yourself.
Quivering flesh go here.
That's good.
And what if we've already
run into one of these encores?
How do we kill it?
You can't,
not with a chit of their
souls still in Hell.
Where's Ava? Tell her I said hi.
I see a woman in the shadows.
Walk to her.
[CLEARS THROAT]
She's beautiful.
Silky raven hair.
[GUN CLICKING]
Eyes you could just stare into forever.
And she's stuffing her face with donuts.
[GUNSHOT]
[OVERLAPPING SCREAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
God has spared Rasputin again.
Kill her!
- Rory!
- [GROWLS]
[FLAMES WHOOSHING]
[SCREAMS]
[ROARS]
Nate, I'm coming for you, buddy.
[SUIT CLICKING]
Nate, snap out of it.
I remember her, Ray.
Who?
I don't know her name, but
she was on the ship with us.
Mission's blown, we need to retreat.
I'm not done with you, you rat.
Good thing Sara's not watching this.
[EXHALES]
So you guys decided to go off
on your own and face Rasputin.
I thought I could calm him down.
I thought I could make him fall in love?
And I thought I could,
you know, assassinate him.
None of that was ever going to happen.
He's fresh out of Hell.
Well, let's kill him then.
You... you can't.
Look, John said that he can't be killed
with a chit of his soul is in Hell,
or whatever that means.
Look, Sara, we're really sorry.
We thought we could make
things easier for you
by taking this off of your plate.
And risking your own necks.
Look, I already have one
dead friend on my plate.
I'm good there.
And you know, none of you
self-absorbed mega stars
even bothered to ask me how I was doing.
Look, Sara, I told them
not to mention Oliver, okay?
I thought you wouldn't
want to be reminded.
Reminded?
What, did you think
that I could just forget
that my friend died?
No, I... look, I know things
have been crazy around here.
Crazy around here?
You still have no idea
what I saw out there.
What did happen?
Countless Earths died.
I became a Paragon and
traveled back to the Big Bang.
We restarted the universe
and now no one even
remembers what we've changed.
- It's a lot to process.
- Yeah, I know.
So you could see why I wanna
talk to my friends about it.
And instead I get cameras in my face.
Agent Sharpe lacks a delicate touch
and is extremely deficient
at relating to people.
[CHUCKLES]
That is straight from my
Time Bureau personnel review.
Pretty harsh.
I wrote that review.
Yeah, of course I'm bummed
that we let Sara down,
but I am glad I got to meet Rasputin.
Little help?
[AIR WHOOSHING]
I mean, the guy got in
my head and laid a bomb.
- He freaked your bean, huh?
- Oh yeah.
He also told me about the mystery woman
that I was in love with before I died.
I know it sounds crazy but
it just... it feels right.
Sounds like you got some
soul searching to do.
Wanna watch "How Stella
Got Her Groove Back" again?
No, my groove feels fine.
You think I have either split
memory or partial amnesia?
That's like what's
happening with Gideon.
Her memory is processing what
I thought was phantom data,
but maybe it's real data
from a different timeline.
Either you're a computer who caught
the same virus as Gideon...
Or when we fixed Heyworld,
we changed the timeline.
Damn, we deducted the hell out of that.
I have to tell Sara.
Wait, five minutes, five minutes,
Stay on the inversion table.
You're back's gonna thank me.
[SIGHS]
Okay, so clearly we
shouldn't have avoided
asking Sara about Oliver.
But in my defense I
was desperately afraid
I was gonna say the
wrong thing, you know?
I don't know what she needs
and everything I try...
it seems to make it worse.
Hold on, Behrad, so you're
saying Gideon's glitching
because we fractured time?
Look, at least we didn't break time.
We just, sorta, dinged it up.
Hello?
[TAPS LENS]
What is on the feed?
Is this thing on?
Oh, yes we're rolling,
Mr. Rasputin, sir.
Good. Get out.
Now what was it that man
with the hair product said?
Yes,
you are not big deal until
you're big deal on camera.
You are going to make me
big deal, Mr. Kevin Harris.
They left the director behind?
I've invited my dearest
Czarina and her family
over for dinner.
Tonight will be a night
that you can remember.
[GIGGLES]
That... that doesn't sound right.
What?
The laugh, you need to nail the laugh
before we kill the Romanovs
and take the throne.
It's a work in progress. How about this?
[CLEARS THROAT, CACKLING]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
He's gonna kill the Romanovs.
Making him an immortal Czar.
We can handle this.
We can? What about the team?
Shh, they're not thinking straight.
And their cover's blown.
Look, this up to you and me, B.
We are going to stop
this assassination alone.
Yes.
[ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What's this?
Is this a smudge on this goblet?
Every detail must be perfect.
Tonight I am dining
with the imperial family.
Take it back.
They are going to love the teacakes.
I've laced them with cyanide. [GIGGLES]
Hello, Kevin, right here.
Your guests have arrived.
The Romanovs are here!
Welcome.
It is such a shame that your
daughters could not attend.
I know how much they must have
missed their uncle Rasputin.
Word of your death
sent them into mourning,
but none were so heartbroken as I.
Music!
[TRIO PLAYS SOMBERLY]
♪ ♪
How did you manage to
survive being poisoned, shot,
and thrown into the river, Grigori?
Oh, I have a very hardy constitution.
Oh, damn it, the red
wedding's about to start
and I don't see the teacakes anywhere.
All I see is cookies.
- Teacakes.
- My favorite.
The cookies are the teacakes.
[NAPKIN SNAPS]
What is the meaning of this?
Forgive me, sire, I saw a bug.
[AIR WHOOSHING]
Grigori, what is going on?
What have you done?
Whoops, I think we forgot the cameraman.
That's Kevin, the director.
He's really more of an auteur.
We should get out there.
Sara clearly wants to handle this alone.
But are we gonna let her?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Go.
Nicholas, Alexei, come.
Wait!
You will stay exactly where you are.
For years I have flattered you both.
Our subjects adore
you. Our army needs you.
And look at the state
of our beloved Russia.
Hey.
Let me guess, you're the
only one that can save it.
Not today, Grigori.
Who are you? No matter.
Perhaps I haven't given
an adequate demonstration
on my bauble.
[ETHEREAL PULSE]
Attack this serving wench.
[RUSSIAN INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Come on, Behrad. Snap out of it.
Rasputin.
The Grand Duchess Anastasia is here.
No, Anastasia, run!
So glad you could join our soirée.
Me too.
[GASPS]
[CHUCKLES]
You're going to have
to do better than that.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
Sorry.
Come on, come on, follow me, go.
[ROARS]
Move it.
[YELPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[ELECTRICAL HUM]
It didn't hurt.
All right, this way.
We're gonna hide, you'll be safe.
Look, Sara, I wish I was the person
who could say the perfect thing.
Behind you.
[SIGHS]
But listen, I'm just...
I'm not that person, okay?
Emotions are hard for
me and I don't even know
what restarting the universe means.
Behind you.
Listen to me, whatever happened to you,
okay, whatever happens to you,
I wanna be the person
that's there for you.
I'm here for you, Sara.
[SHOUTS]
Ava, that was perfect.
Oh, sorry to ruin the moment,
ladies, but we have a problem.
Oh, come on.
Kill the imperial family.
[GROWLS]
Guys, come on, we don't
need to use violence here.
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
Ray!
Sara, think of something.
Hey, Grigori.
It's your big moment,
don't you want to ham
it up for the cameras?
Oh, yes.
I'm Grigori Rasputin and I'm unkillable.
[LAUGHING]
[GULPS]
Guys?
Where am I? What happened?
Don't think Ray, just enlarge.
Why's it so dark in here?
Am I in a lake?
A lake that smells like pierogies?
Ray, do it, get big now.
Embigify.
Your atomic number is up.
Now, Ray!
Size... matters!
Oh no. What did... what did I do?
You found your catchphrase, Ray!
- What the hell.
- Raw meat.
- Question is...
- Did you get the shot, Kevin?
Uh, yeah I... I got it.
You know, I chalk it up
to saving the timeline,
and history has to be saved,
and sometimes you have take
some people out, I guess.
The public is gonna love this ending
It's only missing one thing.
Hm?
[BODY THUDS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Saving history turned
out to be a messier job
than anyone had anticipated.
To keep Rasputin from reforming,
The Legends stored his
remains in a series of jars
that had previously been
used for condiments.
♪ The sun's in your face ♪
[PAPERCUTS' "SANDY"]
You might have thought
traveling through time
would be a way to find the answers
to life's great mysteries.
But, it turns out, sometimes
you just find more questions.
♪ ♪
♪ Sandy, baby... ♪
But one thing is true
in any time period.
It's being there for the ones you love
that makes the journey worthwhile.
♪ Try and be something you're not ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Hear that applause?
This movie is not even gonna begin
to satiate the Legends craze.
You know what this
is? This is a TV show.
I'm talking cameras on every mission.
Sara, you okay? You look nauseous.
Yeah, she's fine.
And now, when you go out
there, just be yourselves.
But, you know, bigger.
Like, bigger how?
You know, just act heroic.
You guys have a real "Bad
News Bears" vibe going on.
It's not doing you any favors.
Now that you're big-time,
people expect you
to put on a show.
So you're asking us not to be ourselves.
[SNAPS] This guy gets it.
Let's do this.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Hi, everybody.
We are the Legends, and
we just wanted to say
thank you for watching our film.
We hope that you enjoyed it.
- [APPLAUSE]
- We love you, Legends!
Of course, none of it was real.
[CHUCKLES]
No, wait... it's not real?
Excuse me? She's joking.
No, I'm not. Come on, time travel?
I mean, it's the
biggest hoax in history.
- Am I right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's obvious
that this is all fake.
How could Rasputin speak English?
You told me it was temporal
linguistic dysplasia.
I mean, if we had so much as coughed,
our modern germs would have wiped out
half the population. [COUGHS]
Why wouldn't we just find baby Hitler,
and make him wrestle baby
Stalin? Think about it.
The special effects were
kind of questionable.
- We still believe in you!
- [AUDIENCE BOOING]
Shut up, it's not real.
All right, everybody.
I guess that just means don't believe
everything you see on camera.
Yeah, it was all just
a big, fake spectacle
just like Heyworld last year.
We are all a bunch of frauds.
Big frauds, everybody.
You guys ruined my movie.
- Yeah, sorry.
- Legends of losers!
[WHISTLING]
This is for the best, right?
Maybe, maybe not? I don't know.
I feel like I'm supposed to say that.
We're better off. Fame
messes with people.
Still have that money problem.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mick?
[GROWLS]
I steal things.
- Whoa, is that a Fabergé egg.
- Mm-hmm.
What's that worth?
50 million.
[GASPS]
Whoa, careful with that, babes.
Yeah.
John.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I heard your movie
premiere was in town tonight,
so I thought I'd pop in.
Well, just make yourself at home then
[SIGHS] Why can't he
ever just be normal?
What are you doing?
Yeah, I need to borrow something.
Rasputin wasn't an isolated incident.
Not isolated, what do you mean?
Okay, hey, whoa no, no, don't!
Don't... [GAGS]
Ugh.
[GULPING]
[GASPS]
I'm putting an end to this.
Wait, are you trying to go back to Hell?
Soul become my soul,
flesh become my flesh.
Hades, firstborn of Cronos,
I call upon you.
Hey, John, there's gotta be another way.
I'll return when the sigil is complete.
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
John, you take care, you lunatic.
I always do, love, I always do.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[FIRE WHOOSHING]
[SIGHS]
You know, sometimes
what happens on this ship
really would be hard for
an audience to follow.
That love letter you wrote.
It's good.
Very good.
Gee, thank you, Mick.
This means so much coming from you.
Listen, um, I'm giving up the writing.
It's getting in the way of my thievery.
So I'm handing the Rebecca
Silver novels over to you.
Someone deserving.
Me?
This is... this is
so much. Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure. It's why I'm saying it.
There's a novelist inside you.
There's more inside
of me than just Wolfie?
Yes, that's right.
Well, it was great living
with you on the Waverider.
- What?
- Yeah.
I can't stay here to
write. I need to be free.
I need to fall in love and break hearts.
I can't do Rebecca Silver justice here.
- But... but I...
- But you tried
writing on the ship
and ran out of ideas?
I mean, frankly, Mick, your
latest novel "Carjacked,"
it sucked.
But don't worry, Rebecca Silver
is about to have her comeback.
You'll see.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You were my favorite.
How's it going, Gideon?
The phantom memory scrub is
proceeding without a hitch.
The flaws only go as far
back as the last two years.
Oh, it feels good to get
my thoughts straight.
Good work, Giddy.
I'm turning in.
Goodnight, B.
- Don't stay up too late, Nate.
- You got it.
- Doctor Heywood.
- Hmm?
I have encountered a glitch
during the Heyworld event.
Show me.
[DEVICES HUMMING]
Nate.
If you're seeing this, we
altered my future at Heyworld.
I don't know where I'll
be or who I'll be but...
I know that I love you.
Find me.
[DEVICE CHIRPS]
Gideon.
Gideon, who was that? Play it again.
Memory scrub complete.
[DEVICES WHIRRING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --