- _
- [TYPEWRITER KEYS CLACKING]
- [LIGHT MUSIC]
- _
- ♪ ♪
- [PAPER RIPS]
- [ALARM BUZZES]
Dang it.
- ♪ ♪
- _
- [PAPER RIPS]
- [ALARM BUZZES]
- Dang it.
- _
_
- [PAPER RIPS]
- [DINGS]
- _
- [VARIOUS TYPEWRITER KEYS CLACKING]
Man, some days rewriting history
to eradicate any notion of rebelling
and free will is hard.
Yeah.
You ever wonder if what
we're doing is, like, wrong?
How could it be wrong?
The Fates give everyone food
and shelter and television.
You don't want a world that looks like
these history books, do you?
Right... right. Fates be praised.
Just doesn't feel quite right.
[SCREEN DINGS]
Geoffrey Burch.
I am Atropos, the thread cutter.
Ooh. Atropos is calling you.
Uh-huh.
Great.
Your time has come to an end.
Your thread is hereby cut.
It is fated.
Oh, I see.
Well, Fates be praised...
[NECK SNAPS]
Sorry, Geoffrey.
The work period has ended.
Return to your domiciles
for mandatory recreation period.
[WHISTLING MUSIC]
The Fates are always watching.
Relinquish free will.
The world is perfect.
The world is wrong!
Can't you people see?
None of this is how it should be.
He's gonna get his dang thread cut.
Do I know you?
You look familiar. Do you recognize me?
My name is Gary, but most
people call me Crazy Guy.
Stay away from me, you weirdo.
Yeah, they call me that, too.
The world is wrong!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[WHISTLING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
This is your new home, little guy.
[MICROWAVE BEEPS]
Another night, another bowl of Mush.
Let's see what's streaming on Fate-plus.
[TV BUZZES ON]
[LIGHT MUSIC]
I'm back!
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, Behrad.
Did you remember the
Grey Mush like I asked?
I got the Green Mush, the Purple Mush,
the Sticky Mush, the Slimy Mush...
and I forgot the Grey Mush.
- You forgot the Grey Mush?
- I forgot the Grey Mush!
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, Behrad. You're so dumb. [LAUGHS]
♪ They're the "Ultimate Buds" ♪
♪ And they're fated to have some fun ♪
Mama needs her "Ultimate Buds".
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
The oven's taking forever to pre-heat,
and the Mush is still cold.
My boss is gonna be here in 30 minutes.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- [BOTH GASP]
Or maybe she'll be early.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- Nate!
- Nate.
[IN BAD BRITISH ACCENT] I don't
know this Nate you speak of.
Me name is Robin of
Locksley of Starling City.
Why?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] I got an audition
to play Robin Hood in "Arrow",
a show about a vigilante.
Mm, sounds dumb.
If it was dumb,
why would I stop crime with this?
- [ARROW FIRES]
- [GASPS]
The Grey Mush!
I guess I got the Grey Mush.
[LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHS]
At least the family
heirloom didn't get dirty.
I should go clean off.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't leave me here with...
[GROANS] Nate.
Are you still upset about
the time we almost kissed?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I missed the kiss.
[LAUGHTER]
No, I'm mad because
you ruined the place,
and my boss is gonna be here any minute.
[BRACELET THRUMMING]
- What's that thing doing?
- Oh.
I don't know. It's never
done that before.
- I say don't touch it.
- Right.
- But on the other hand, why not?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [ELECTRICITY ZAPS]
- Ah!
[BRACELET WHOOSHES]
This show's off the rails.
There's no ghosts in "Ultimate Buds".
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CROWD GASPS, LAUGHS]
Nate?
Sorry?
[LAUGHTER]
But how... you found me.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, whoa.
- [EXHALES]
- Oh.
[CROWD "AWW" S]
- What was that?
- What?
- Nate?
- Yeah?
Nate Heywood: actor and your neighbor.
Do you remember us?
I mean, I always
wanted there to be an...
Us.
[CROWD AWWS]
Could I be more of a kiss-misser?
[LAUGHTER]
Wow.
Lot going on here. [SIGHS]
All right, we need to take
these off immediately.
[GRUNTS]
All right, I knew the
timeline would be different
and you might not remember me, but
this is just bizarre.
All right, where's the Waverider?
Where's Sara and Mick
and John and the others?
Ava Sharpe?
Mona Wu?
[EERIE MUSIC]
Did they just say "Mona Wu"?
Sure. Sure.
All good questions. Right.
Hey, Behrad, your sister
might have hit her head again.
[LAUGHTER]
Behrad?
Is that really you?
I thought I'd never see you again.
Did you eat, like, an
entire Behrad Brownie?
- What?
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Your boss!
Why don't you just stay in this closet
for a sec while we
entertain your boss...
And your liver processes the brownie.
Welcome. I'm Behrad, Zari's brother.
You must be the...
[QUIETLY] Hot boss.
My!
What a charming brother
the Fates have granted Zari.
[LAUGHTER]
Where is she?
Not in the closet, that's for sure.
[LAUGHTER]
[BRACELET WHOOSHES]
[DOOR SLAMS OPEN, WIND WHOOSHING]
Okay, boss coming over for dinner.
I think I know what's going here.
We're stuck in a TV sitcom.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Zari.
Do you have amnesia again?
[LAUGHTER]
You guys don't hear that? The laughing?
I... she's hearing voices.
Sis, what do you think is happening?
I think you guys fought The Fates.
ALL: Fates be praised!
And you lost.
And for some reason,
you've been loomed here.
- What's behind this door?
- Hm.
I don't know. We never opened it.
- Never even occurred to us.
- Mm-mm.
Well, we're about to find out.
[RING ACTIVATES]
[DOOR RIPS OFF THE HINGES]
[WIND WHOOSHING]
Huh.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Has that been there the whole time?
[EXHALES]
Coming, dummies?
- Buds stick together.
- Like glue.
♪ ♪
Where are we?
Ah.
We've been expecting you.
Welcome to Highcastle Abbey.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[DRAMATIC PIANO MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
Lady Zari and Lord Behrad,
the second footman will
see to your carriage.
What happened to the first footman?
[GIGGLES]
[SNIFFS]
I've taken the liberty of ordering you
some Persian treats to
make you feel at home.
Shall I ask the kitchen
to prepare a tea?
Uh... sure.
Unbelievable.
John Constantine, self-proclaimed
nasty piece of work is a butler.
Hmm.
Please tell me you guys recognize him.
- No, no.
- [SUCKS IN AIR]
Sorry, Sis.
- Do you think this is another TV show?
- Right.
We went from a hilarious
yet heartfelt sitcom,
but now we're stuck on some
stuffy BBC period piece.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
With no obvious way to escape.
[EXHALES]
Well, it seems like the TV show
is adapting to our presence.
So I think we just have to play along
until I can get John to snap out of it.
Okay, it looks like
we're some kind of...
- Aristocrats.
- Nice.
Hmm. That must make you our servant.
[LAUGHING]
Mm.
[SIGHS]
Wouldn't you prefer wearing something
a tad more cheerful, dearest?
I would if the prospect
of your matchmaking
was worthy of cheer.
Lord Behrad is your
father's closest male heir.
Marriage to him keeps
Highcastle Abbey in our family.
Well, how is he, Mr. Constantine?
Lord Behrad is as advertised,
a foreigner.
Oh, not you too.
Lord and Lady Tarazi, may I present
Lady Natalie and her daughter,
Lady Astra.
I do beg your pardon, Lord Tarazi,
but is it customary where you
come from for the valet to sit?
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Ooh. [CLEARS THROAT]
[IN BAD BRITISH ACCENT] Oi!
A thousand apologies, bro.
Mr. Constantine,
why don't you show the Tarazis' valet
to the servants' hall?
Happily, my Lady.
[SIGHS] Please, have a seat.
You must be exhausted from your travels.
I'm so glad we could find the time
to get to know one another.
Yes.
Before we marry and you
inherit our family's estate...
[SCOFFS]
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry. Did you say, "marry"?
I have to go to the bath...
to the lavatory.
[WHISPERS] Don't leave me.
Do you enjoy hunting, Lord Behrad?
Ooh, I like to play among the animals,
not slaughter them.
Well...
that is an unconventional opinion.
In this household,
servants should be seen and not heard
in the company of their superiors.
Which means we should
all be silent round you.
Isn't that right, Mr. Constantine?
Mrs. Hutchens, trying
to hold your tongue
will be as easy as
swimming through custard
in Wellington boots.
Oh, there you are, John.
Well, I do beg your pardon, Lady Zari,
but this is most irregular.
Right, I... I need to talk to you...
alone.
[GASPS] They got the Blue Mush.
- Fancy kind.
- Yum.
[CLEARS THROAT]
How may I assist you, my Lady?
All right, listen to me.
You are not some buttoned-up butler.
You are... are a cynical,
chain-smoking, master of the occult.
You have an apprentice named Gary,
and you are capable of great ma...
Destine!
Magic.
Did she just say "Gary" now?
Maybe that crazy guy
isn't so crazy after all.
Can I confide in you, Lord Behrad?
Confide away.
Sometimes I wish I'd been born a man,
at least then I'd have
a chance at adventure.
Your parents can't hold you here.
You're a diva.
What is a diva?
A diva is a female version of a hustler.
[MYSTERIOUS STRING MUSIC]
[SIGHS] Okay, let me get this straight.
You don't remember me or the Legends,
but you can still cast spells?
To my great shame.
I'm at war with myself.
Part of me is, uh...
seduced by dark magic.
That's the real you.
Are you going to inform Lady Natalie?
Yeah, maybe we should.
Please, please don't. I beg you.
You see, I'll be sacked.
You know what?
If you cast one of your spells
and help us escape this world,
we will keep quiet.
- Maybe.
- We will.
Gary, I think people
are trapped on the TV,
and they know us.
You sound crazy.
You were onto something.
The world's all wrong, and the
cracks are starting to show.
Just watch.
[TV BUZZES ON]
In order for this
spell to work properly,
I must first know where it is
that you intend to go.
Can you send us to someone?
We need to find our captain.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What is your captain's name?
Uh, Sara. Captain Sara Lance.
[GROWLS]
The Jack of Ones.
Daring exploits and dangerous
challenges lay ahead.
- Great.
- I do hope this works.
I shall be glad to be rid of you.
Actually, John,
we really need you to come with us.
Amusing joke, my lady,
but I will never desert my post.
Welp, I tried to stop her.
Mr. Constantine, I have made
the most wonderful decision.
I am moving to London.
London?
What about Highcastle
and your mother?
I am a diva.
My bad.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Everyone that wants to leave, link up.
- Come here.
- Where are we going?
Lady Astra, I beg you.
Please, step away.
To live a life that I love,
I must know the world
outside these walls.
Lady Astra, I must insist.
♪ ♪
Where'd they go?
Did she say "Captain Lance"?
From "Star Trip"?
We have to get into Clotho Productions
and find out what's going on.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS] Officer Maala, report.
It's a Gromulan warship, Captains.
[ALARM WAILS]
Hail them, Officer Maala.
Or wouldn't it be more... logical
to attack the warship
before it attacks us?
By that logic, we would attack
every ship we encountered.
Is there something wrong with that?
Fine, Officer Maala.
- Hail the Gromulans.
- Yes, Captain.
[HIGH-PITCHED ELECTRONIC WAILING]
[SPEAKING GROMULAN]
Can we kill them now?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Space:
the Fatal Frontier.
[SHIP WHOOSHES]
These are the adventures
of the USS Faterider.
Its mission:
to seek out rebellious life forms
and disobedient civilizations
and blow them up with lasers.
- [LASERS PINGING]
- [EXPLODES]
♪ ♪
Captains, we've caught the Gromulans
with their pants down.
Charge the cannons.
Let's give them hell.
Engage the translator, Officer Maala.
I would like to talk to them.
Two captains is an
exciting power dynamic.
Charging cannons and
engaging the translator.
Okay, sorry. Do you
guys not understand me?
We understand you. We come in peace.
Yeah, now prepare to die.
Wait. Hold on.
Don't shoot. Listen.
None of this is real.
This is a fake reality.
Yeah, it's true. We're
all on television.
Watch. I can press this, uh,
plasma cannon button, and
nothing's gonna happen.
No, no, no. Nate, no.
- No.
- On the other hand, why not?
- [BUTTON BUZZES]
- [GASPS]
[LASER PINGS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Oh, God.
Who knew?
That was bad.
- Can't even look.
- Oh, well, I mean,
it's an absolutely remarkable
vessel really, isn't it?
- [ELECTRIC SPARKS]
- [AIR WHOOSHING]
[ALARM WAILING]
Officer Maala!
The crew has perished.
No!
There's no need to
vocalize at that decibel.
They're androids.
Error... error...
Oh. Right.
This battle isn't over yet.
Ooh, crazy episode.
[CLEARS THROAT] Excuse me, my good sir.
My colleague and I are here
to refill your Mush vending machines.
I don't have you on my list.
Lalo, is it?
You don't wanna be known
as the guy who lets the
building run out of Mush,
do you?
All right, go in.
Yes.
Fire laser blasters.
Permanently disabled.
- Photon torpedoes!
- Destroyed.
Hey, ladies, uh,
permission to rescue you?
We could just beam you right over here.
[ELECTRONICS EXPLODE]
Smells like a Gromulan trap.
Okay, you're losing oxygen.
We're gonna rescue you.
[BEAMING DEVICE RINGING]
We're taking over this ship.
Sure. That works.
We're... we're your crew anyways.
I... I know it's complicated,
but we're actually from
an alternate timeline
where you're our captains.
You're our crew?
May I interest you in
some rare Gromulan tea?
Oh, it is grand
to see lady adventurers in pantaloons.
What kind of Gromulans are you?
[TOGETHER] Ultimate Buds.
All right, yeah, I know
it's hard to believe, but...
No. It makes perfect sense.
We encounter this sort
of thing all the time.
You're probably our crew
from an alternate timeline,
and you've been trapped in some sort of,
judging by your mannerisms,
late and early 20th-century
prison dimension,
which calls the question if we ourselves
are existing in a prison dimension.
It's perfectly logical.
Ava, I love you.
[MACHINE CLICKING]
Whoa.
Clotho's control room.
Look.
That contraption is spitting out
a script for "Star Trip".
Looks like it's being
generated automatically
by some sort of scriptwriting algorithm.
What are these?
Those are life threads, Gary.
Someone really is
trapped in these shows.
Oh, my Fates!
What is it?
"Ultimate Buds" swag.
We need to figure out our next move.
Uh, what we need is to
get out of this TV sh...
prison dimension.
We've been investigating an
odd radio wave transmission
coming from the planet Kuldezax.
[RADIO TUNING]
♪ Welcome to my Cul-de-Sac, friend ♪
♪ That's a street
that ends in a circle ♪
Is that a song?
We don't know what to make of it.
This sector should be deserted.
All right. I'm gonna make contact.
With alien beings? Are you mad?
Absolutely do not make contact.
Even I think it's a bad idea.
Okay, okay. I won't.
Mm, on the other hand...
Why not?
[OVERLAPPING NO'S]
[SHIP PINGS]
[SHIP CRUNCHES]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[PEACEFUL PIANO MUSIC]
♪ Welcome to my Cul-de-Sac, friend ♪
[IMITATING LASERS BLASTING]
♪ That's a street
that ends in a circle ♪
♪ ♪
Children,
I think the Fates have
sent us some visitors.
[IMITATING SHIP]
Let's be good hosts.
I'll get the door.
Look who it is, everyone.
It's the Community Helpers.
We're on "Mr. Parker's Cul-de-Sac".
Sewer repair? That's
actually kind of badass.
Could there be such a
profession as a firewoman?
Gather around, friends.
It's story time.
Why don't you take a
walk around the block?
Oof! [LAUGHS]
Actually, Officer Lance,
it is a Cul-de-Sa...
The logic of this world
does not compute.
What exactly is the plan, Dr. Zari?
I have no idea.
Oh, well, we can't just
keep hopping shows
ad infinitum, now can we?
We are on public access.
This is a career-killer.
Come on, sis. What gives?
Look, I don't know.
If you guys would just
remember who you really are,
you could help me figure this out, but
none of you remember.
Remember what?
That you're in the Legends.
What is a Legend?
You guys were heroes.
But it's not because you do magic
or because you have superpowers, it's...
What makes you guys special,
what makes us special,
is that we're just a bunch of...
misfits who are trying
to make a difference.
That is what we need right now.
She's talking about us.
We could be those misfits, Gary.
But how?
I've been sanitizing
history for too long.
It's time to spread the truth.
"The Legends remember
who they truly are".
I wanna do right by Astra.
Make sure she, uh, was happy
growing up in a big house.
And I could keep an eye on her.
Your mom never gave up on you.
You can really bring her back?
I can fix everything.
You don't belong here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SLICES]
♪ ♪
As far as I'm concerned,
we are co-captains for life.
Always.
[OVERLAPPING SCREAMS]
Sara!
We changed history.
We changed everything.
No.
Dude, you just came back to life.
I know that I love you.
Find me.
[GASPS]
♪ ♪
Oh.
I remember everything.
I remember the Legends.
I remember...
Our time with Behrad.
I remember both Zaris.
It's nice to be remembered.
Behrad...
I... I should be dead.
In every timeline, I shouldn't be alive.
But you're alive here, okay? Now.
Look... I actually think
I know what happened.
Look, I... I told Charlie to come up
with a way to outsmart her sisters.
Maybe hiding us on TV was that way.
Bloody Charlie.
A butler?
I feel violated.
What the hell, John?
Did the Loom bring my mom back or not?
I'm sorry, love. I don't know.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You found me.
I'm never gonna lose you again.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We did it, Gary!
You idiots.
Great Clotho! Praise the Fates!
What have you done?
We restored their memories.
Please don't kill us.
You're gonna ruin everything.
If only we could explain.
[IN HER GOD VOICE] Get out!
I can't let the Legends escape.
♪ ♪
Guys, love that you're back together.
And let's just say that I'm processing
what it means that my best
bro is in love with my sister,
who lived my same experiences
in a different timeline.
But where's my Zari?
Took the words right
out of my mouth, mate.
Mm-hmm. Uh...
Well, I'm sort of possessing her body.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I mean, I love both of you. It's just...
[SIGHS] I get it.
She belongs here.
Yeah, but what happens to you?
Did someone say "problem"?
It sounds like being
stuck in a TV universe
and suddenly remembering
two different timelines
is very confusing.
Well, maybe I can try to help.
I hate to question a living god,
but why are you doing this, Clotho?
Because the Legends don't realize
that there are consequences
to disobedience.
I know all about sad feelings.
[DRAMATIC PIANO MUSIC]
♪ Sad feelings ♪
♪ Bad feelings ♪
♪ Make you so mad you
wanna scream feelings ♪
♪ Everyone sometimes
has those feelings ♪
♪ When you do, just sing this song ♪
Mr. Parker, I know you're
just trying to help, but you...
♪ Repress ♪
♪ I'll go back and repress ♪
♪ It's better to bury my feelings ♪
♪ Than feel as awful ♪
♪ As this ♪
Yeah, you're definitely not Mr. Parker.
- [SNAPS]
- [RINGING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Where did you send them?
Why I just pulled the plug
on this crossover, silly.
You all have to go home now.
[SNAPS]
♪ Sad feelings ♪
♪ Bad feelings ♪
♪ Make you so mad ♪
♪ You wanna scream feelings ♪
[SNAPS]
♪ Everyone sometimes
has those feelings ♪
♪ When you do, just sing this song ♪
[TOGETHER] ♪ Ignore, ignore ♪
♪ Those pesky feelings are a chore ♪
♪ Obey the Fates ♪
♪ Eat your Mush ♪
♪ And you'll be happy ♪
♪ Just like two lady bugs ♪
Not today, Satan!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Oh. Oh.
I am so sorry.
I thought I was tackling Mr. Parker.
What kind of Mush are we having tonight?
Um, the "you gotta go" kind.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, how did we not hear that before?
After all that, we're right
back where we started.
Mother-fater.
I wanna see the Buds break free.
[FLAMES IGNITE]
Just try and make a move on us,
and I will burn you, you bastard.
John.
- We need to go back.
- Yeah, sure, love.
Why don't you really listen to her,
construction worker John?
I wanna see my mother.
[FLAMES DE-IGNITE]
What do you think your
mother will suddenly
have all of her memories?
What if Natalie's just a
character on a TV show, love?
I have to know for sure.
♪ Repress ♪
♪ I'll go back and repress ♪
♪ It's better to bury my feelings ♪
♪ Than feel as awful ♪
♪ As this ♪
♪ ♪
[TOGETHER] ♪ Ignore, ignore ♪
♪ Those pesky feelings are a chore ♪
♪ Obey the Fates ♪
♪ Eat your Mush ♪
♪ And you'll be happy ♪
♪ Just like two lady bugs ♪
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Eh, we're back.
And it's Christmastime, apparently.
Yep.
Oh. There you two are.
Mom.
Oh. My love.
What's all this?
Do you remember anything?
About your life before Highcastle Abbey?
What... I...
Uh, London? Magic?
Dad?
Oh, what on Earth are you talking about?
Never mind.
I love you, Mom.
Oh.
I love you too,
you goose.
Now you come upstairs
and change for dinner.
Astra, listen to me.
I know what you're gonna say:
she's not real.
We can stay.
What?
What are you playing at?
It's no trick, love.
[EMOTIONAL PIANO MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Astra, look at me.
What have I got to show for myself?
38 crap years of pain
and broken promises.
You wanna know what my original sin was?
It was you.
Astra.
I rail against the angels and the demons
for being arrogant bastards,
but I'm worse than
the bloody lot of them.
You know, I thought that I could use
your innocent soul
as a bargaining chip
to save your mother.
Bollocks.
If you're happy here, then
I will spend an eternity
as ruddy Mr. Constantine
trying to make it up to you and Natalie.
Is John Constantine really capable
of such a selfless act?
[CHUCKLES]
[IN MR. CONSTANTINE'S VOICE]
Would it be acceptable to dine
at half past seven, Lady Astra?
Mrs. Hutchens is running a trifle late.
Perfectly acceptable, Mr. Constantine.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That's one show back on track.
My algorithm should
take care of the rest.
But I don't understand.
Why are real people trapped on TV?
The Legends, they're my friends.
But my sisters wanted them dead,
so I made a deal:
weave the Legends into
our streaming service
where they help indoctrinate the masses,
and they could live.
Huh.
I always thought of you
as the punk rock Fate.
I didn't have a choice.
Nobody does here.
But that's how it starts,
and then you get used to it,
obeying, I mean.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Come on. We have to escape.
What's our course, Captains?
Sara, wait.
- Let's think about this.
- What's there to think about?
We have to get back to real world.
No, I know, okay? But just...
in the real world, I saw you die.
Okay, and it...
it was awful, and I just keep playing it
over and over again in my head, okay?
So look, out there, we lost.
But in here, we always win, Sara.
Look, come on. You're right.
Okay, and that's why
Charlie did all this,
a crew that can't die,
us beating the bad guys every time,
it's what we asked for
back there in the pub.
♪ ♪
But that doesn't exist.
Ava, life is beautiful and terrible,
all at the same time.
But if we're only living part of it,
then we're not living at all.
♪ ♪
Let's get the hell out of here.
Captains, I'm picking up
a strange transmission.
It's from your old enemy, Dhan.
Captain Lance, Captain Sharpe,
old friends.
- He looks kind of hot.
- Oh, Mom.
What? I'm not dead.
That's gross.
So that's where Rory's been.
It was foolish to think
you could escape my wrath.
Dhan's charging his torpedoes.
Should I raise the shields?
You said that we always win, right?
What if the only way to get
Charlie to set us free is...
we have to lose?
What is she on about?
You left me.
You left her in the
center of a dead planet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just
get to the revenge part.
As you wish.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Torpedoes incoming.
Should I take evasive maneuvers?
Negative, Officer Maala.
What if real people
die in the TV, Clotho?
You have to save them.
♪ ♪
Torpedo impact in five,
four, three,
two, one.
♪ ♪
[MONOTONOUS BEEP]
No!
- What just happened?
- Did they die?
[MACHINE BEEPING]
What did you do?
I canceled their show.
You idiots.
Have you any idea what you've done?
I love "Star Trip", and my hair.
Wait, where are we?
And where are the others?
Darling.
Before we go in for dinner,
just open one present.
And what's this?
I overheard you talking
to Lord Behrad earlier.
It's a ticket to London.
I don't understand.
I couldn't bear it
if you sacrificed your
happiness for my own.
But what about Highcastle Abbey?
Please, don't make me do this.
I can't say goodbye to you.
Darling, darling.
I'll always be here.
But you have your
whole life ahead of you.
Be courageous, my love.
You live it well.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Mr. Constantine.
Your ladyship.
♪ ♪
Is Lady Astra really leaving Highcastle?
[MUTTERS]
Do I have to say it?
Say what, my lady?
You smug bastard.
We can't stay here.
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
Nat would be proud.
Do it fast before I change my mind.
[CHANTING]
John, you made it.
Yeah, just about.
What about the others?
Come on, Z.
You didn't live in a Totem for a year
just to get stuck on a TV show.
I can't go back to eating Mush again,
not even Blue Mush.
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
Yeah, because no one should eat Mush.
It's horrible,
and all the colors are deeply unnatural.
Oh, and it has the
texture of wet cement.
But, Z, the Fates said
we all have to eat Mush.
You know what, Nate?
Screw the Fates.
[AUDIENCE GASPS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Those imbeciles can't do this.
They'll inspire an insurrection.
BOTH: They're gonna
get themselves canceled.
For too long, we've let
the Fates rule our lives.
I happen to like Mush,
but that's not the point.
Stop being so obedient.
Get off your couches and
take control of your lives.
[INSPIRING MUSIC]
[ALL CHEERING]
[BOTH CHEERING]
Oh, it's so good to see you.
[EXHALES] I miss you.
So, hey, that was
pretty crazy back there.
We were, like, engaged.
It's a good thing we're
not brainwashed anymore.
Oh, great. Out of the TV show,
still in heels.
You morons.
You just couldn't leave
it alone, could you?
I gave you everything that you wanted.
You stuck us on TV.
I brought Sara and Behrad back to life.
Mick, I made you a criminal again.
It's just like you wanted.
I even gave Astra a happy
childhood for you, John-o.
Yeah, bollocks. You just used us
to keep people under control.
Well, it's better that
than you lot dead.
I still have your life threads.
I can put the shows back on air.
I'll do rewrites.
Behrad, you want the old Zari back,
I can do that. Look.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Behrad, is that really you?
You're alive.
- What's happening?
- Yeah, it's like a Zari clone.
Totally get it.
Wait, what? Two sisters?
Yeah, this is weird.
Good weird.
[SPEAKING FARSI] It's really you.
Charlie, you can't bribe us
into taking the blue pill.
I'm not bribing. I'm begging.
My sisters will kill you.
That's for sure.
Yeah, well, we'll take our chances.
Lita's out there somewhere.
I'm not staying here.
Let's get out of here.
So long, Charlie.
Wait, just accept your fates.
Don't walk out that door.
On the other hand, why not?
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
They're free!
And I can't help them anymore.