[UNEASY MUSIC]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
John, what happened in there?
There's glass and blood
and... are you okay?
Oh, I'm never better, love.
I'm finally feeling like
my old self again, you know?
What is up with you?
Oh, were you looking forward
to playing the nursing maid?
I'm really sorry to disappoint you.
♪ ♪
- Where the hell is Bishop?
- Sorry, what now?
Bishop stole Rory's comms.
'Cause he knew John
was ripe for the picking.
So he smooth-talked your boyfriend
into springing him.
- Isn't that right, weasel?
- Oh, don't you worry
your pretty little heads about Bishop.
Everything's in hand.
Uh, John,
things feel decidedly
not in hand right now.
Do you know where Bishop is?
Just tell us what happened.
We can help you.
How many times do I have to tell you
I don't want your help?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm sorry, I'm... I'm confused.
You said you wanted to start a new life
sans evil magical potion.
Do... do you remember that
conversation we had?
Oh, yeah I remember.
You see, but I had
a really good chin wag
with Bishop, and then I finally
saw the way forward.
John, you have no idea
how manipulative Bishop is, all right?
Please just tell us where he is
before it's too late.
He's promised to help me
unlock the Fountain,
and that is a promise that
I intend to make him keep.
So you're just gonna
turn your back on all of us?
Oh, let's be honest.
I was never one of you,
now, really, was I?
A Legend.
Nah, I'm a nasty piece of work,
and I walk my path alone.
John, this isn't like you.
Deep down, I know you truly
care about this team.
Oh, come on, grow a pair,
will you, Gary?
I'm not that pathetic, little bastard
that you used to know.
Yeah, you keep saying that
over and over again in different ways.
He's stalling.
Ah! A ghost!
Astral projection.
He's not here.
If he's not here, then...
♪ ♪
The Legends are onto our ruse.
- We need to leave now.
- Almost there.
If you reroute my directory protocols,
you'll short circuit
all communications and navig...
Okay, that's weird.
Yeah. What the hell is going on?
♪ ♪
[EXCITING MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
All right, well,
that ain't England out there.
Gideon, who's flying the ship?
Sara?
Ava? Anyone?
The comms are down.
All right, let's talk about
that ruddy plan.
Well, I'm more of
a fly-by-the-seat-of-my-pants
kind of guy.
That's John and Bishop.
No, no, no, no, if it's us against
John's dark magic, we're gonna lose.
- Yeah, but John...
- Permuto.
All right, lay it on me.
What's next, J-Co?
Oh, you're gonna help me find
another place and time
where the Fountain of Imperium
exists in history.
Ooh, I've always been intrigued
by the legend of the Fountain.
Supposedly, an enormous source of power
gifted by a benevolent alien being.
I encountered the Fountain once before.
It deemed me... unworthy.
But then, if anyone can unlock
an ancient alien artifact,
- that's you, isn't it?
- Well...
I mean, it is the only reason
I set you free.
Oh, and here I thought
you just wanted some company.
[UNEASY MUSIC]
I want my magic back
without having to rely on pesky drugs.
Now, are you up to the task or not?
Easy with the fire hands, Johnny.
I've spent a lifetime hacking
and editing alien genetics.
Believe me, I am just
the super genius you need.
Good, let's get on
with it, then, shall we?
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
Apokalypste ti dynami.
Abracadabra, J.C.
You've unveiled
sub-layers of alien texts
hidden within the map itself.
Nice.
Lucky you, I'm versed
in dozens of alien languages.
Just read the bloody thing, will you?
- Now, that's interesting.
- What?
This symbol here
might just give us a location
to the Fountain.
You see?
You are up to the task, sunshine.
- Let's chart a course.
- Eh.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Okay, those two working together
to find the Fountain is bad news.
We have to go and get the others.
Hell, I can't drive this ship
without Gideon.
Can you?
I don't even have a driver's license.
Then I guess it's up to us to stop them.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Where the hell are we?
1925?
And we're in Texas.
No wonder it seemed familiar.
Definitely explains
the yippee-ki-yay vibe.
[MAN GROANING]
Someone help, please!
Henry will lose his leg.
- Anyone?
- Oh, I can help.
What? Aliens?
No, something else.
Let me through.
I can help, I can help.
There's something familiar about her.
What is it?
Okay, okay.
I can't explain it.
I think that's my mom.
The drilling line snapped.
I tried to move fast, but...
Just try to hold your leg still, okay?
I'm gonna take care of you.
I have something that will help.
You're gonna be okay.
[GROANS]
It's gonna get worse if you keep moving.
Oh, my Lord.
It feels better already.
Get out of my way. Get!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
You look good to go, Henry.
Back on the rig, now.
He needs to rest, Doc.
After his shift.
Need that derrick
up and running by end of month.
Let's go!
♪ ♪
Let me pay you for your services.
No, I don't need compensation.
Sure you do, sweetheart.
Would me buying your land cover it?
You know my answer.
If I don't buy your land,
someone else will.
And they may not offer as much as me
or be as polite.
I have already told you
my land is not for sale.
Maybe you ought reconsider.
♪ ♪
She said no.
So why don't you get going,
sweetheart?
[CHUCKLES]
I'll see you ladies around.
Thank you for your help.
- That man is a menace.
- Happy to.
Dealt with plenty of men
like him in my lifetime.
I'm Gloria.
Have we met?
We're just passing through.
Well, let me thank you with a hot meal.
Wouldn't be a proper
Odessa welcome otherwise.
Hmm? Come.
Where are you going?
- We have to find John and Bishop.
- No, I can't.
That woman, she's... she's my mom.
We're in Odessa, Astra, my hometown.
I thought your mom
was abducted by aliens
when you were a kid;
how could that possibly be her?
I don't know, maybe...
maybe they wiped our memories
and they sent her back in time.
That would explain
why I could never find her.
Hey, hey, hey. I know you feel like
you gave up on finding her too easily,
but I don't want you
to get your hopes up.
If there was a chance
that this was your mom,
wouldn't you wanna talk to her too?
[SIGHS]
Fine. But maybe she knows
something about the Fountain
that can help us find John and Bishop.
Are you coming?
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
The Fountain's near.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no!
Bollocks!
Looks like it's already
dried up, and that's because
you got us here too late, didn't you?
Or we've arrived in the nick of time.
Look at these beautiful mushrooms.
What about the bloody mushrooms?
Right, right, right.
Okay, you don't know this yet.
Earthlings eventually discover
that mushrooms
are actually an ancient alien species.
So you're telling me I've had aliens
in my mushroom masala this whole time?
Think about how weird mushrooms are.
There's nothing else like them on Earth.
And the caps on the ground,
just the tip of the iceberg.
Most of the organism is underground.
What if... go with me on this.
What if these mushrooms
are connected to the Fountain?
That could mean the Fountain
is, in fact, itself
an actual alien being.
Ah...
All of the Fountain's mythology
is connected to caves and grottos.
I thought I was looking
for a body of water,
but perhaps, just like
their alien cousins,
the Fountain can arise from the ground.
Finally, someone who can keep up.
If you can summon the Fountain,
I can make sure it chooses you.
I just need to take some samples
back to the ship, and voilà!
We'll be synthesizing
with the Fountain in no time.
All right, let's get on
with it then, shall we?
[CHUCKLING]
[HUMMING IN DISTANCE]
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Please sit down.
I will get us some tea.
[WARM MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Have you been here awhile?
Since I was about your age.
I built this house myself.
And this Doc guy,
why is he so interested in your land?
He says there's a fountain
of oil underneath it.
My house is the last parcel of
land he hasn't scooped up yet.
Speaking of fountains,
do you know if there's one nearby?
No. Sorry, dear. No.
Where were you from originally?
Los Arenales, El Salvador.
That's my mother.
She was a healer too.
Taught me everything I know.
I never thought I would leave,
but my husband, Celso, he died suddenly,
and it was too painful for me to stay.
So I came here to make a fresh start
with my daughter.
Your... your daughter?
[HUMMING]
Hello, there.
I'm warning you.
Mama taught me how to fight.
Ah, did she now?
Your mama's somewhere nearby, is she?
We live just over that way.
I was just looking at those mushrooms
you're gathering there.
Why?
Are you a healer?
You could say that, yeah.
My mom is a healer.
That's why I'm gathering these for her,
but she's expecting me.
I better go.
Can I show you a trick?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Wow!
You're magic!
Yeah, I am.
Now, tell me,
have you noticed anything else
growing in this forest
even more magical than those mushrooms?
You're sure about that?
Damn it.
Here.
This is for you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
What's your name?
Esperanza Cruz.
♪ ♪
Look, your mom doesn't know
anything about the Fountain.
Spooner, we have to go.
I can't leave yet.
If Gloria has a daughter,
that's gonna mean that aliens
abducted me from here,
wiped my memory,
and sent to me to the future.
Look, if I'm right, then any second now,
kid-me is gonna walk through that door.
Okay, well, maybe it's best
if kid-you doesn't see you-you
for, I don't know, timeline reasons.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Mama!
- [SPEAKING SPANISH]
♪ ♪
Mama, I met this man
who says he can heal people
just like you can!
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Another healer. What a coincidence.
What a coincidence indeed.
Don't worry, we'll get John back.
It'd be a lot easier
if we had a time courier.
Why do we even bother
- taking those things off?
- Don't even...
My eggs are gonna hatch without me.
We need a plan.
Actually, we do know somebody
with a time ship
that could help us. Gary!
- Me?
- No, not you, dummy.
Kayla. We need you to contact her.
[LAUGHS] No.
No, no, no, no.
That's a terrible idea.
Are we taking a vote on this?
I vote nay.
Hey, Gary, listen to me.
We need to stop John
from doing something
more colossally stupid
than he already has.
Go.
Okay.
If we really wanna
get Kayla's attention,
this is how we do it.
What the hell is that?
- It's called an IGCOM.
- What?
It's an intergalactic
communication device.
So, sorry, you're just gonna call Kayla?
Are you kidding?
She would never answer my call.
No, but there's something else
we can do with it.
Okay, Mick.
Let's try to make this
a little more dynamic.
Move your body a little to the right.
Other right. Yup, okay.
Just... chin down.
- Too much.
- Fake eggs coming in hot.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
This is worse than giving birth.
Just sit still, okay?
Are you sure this is gonna work?
- 'Cause, uh...
- Oh, 100%.
Kayla likes to pretend
she's never on Galixiposts,
but she totally is, and once we tag her,
she's gonna lose it.
- Okay, thank you, Gary.
- Okay, Mick.
I think the only thing
left to do is smile.
Be happy.
Okay, center him in the photo.
- There we go.
- Right.
And picture.
♪ ♪
Tag Kayla.
And post.
And now we wait.
Wait? For how long?
Eh, you know,
sometimes reception on Earth
can be a little spotty.
Oh, God.
Oh, my goodness, how rude of me.
I never got your names.
I'm Astra.
Esperanza, but I go by Spooner.
Esperanza? That's my name too.
Yes, and a beautiful one at that.
Tell me, what were you
looking for in the forest?
John.
Oh, I was just foraging
for some medicinal herbs.
Are you sure you weren't
looking for something
more poisonous?
"War of the Worlds"?
Mama and I read it together every night.
That's a pretty scary book.
Space creatures aren't scary.
I want her to stay curious
and keep her adventurous spirit alive.
And I wanna travel to other worlds.
- I have a feeling you will.
- [LAUGHS]
Okay, come help me in the kitchen
and tell me all about
the plants you found.
- This is honey locust.
- Hmm.
You seem different.
What, you mean not overburdened
by guilt and remorse?
Why'd you show up here with kid-me?
I found her while I was
looking for the Fountain.
And do you know what?
It's a good thing that I did,
because our chance encounter
gave me a wee glimpse
into your past and her future.
Don't trust a word out of his mouth.
I don't.
Is everything all right?
- Everything's fine.
- You know, this can't wait.
- Like hell it can't.
- Nunc somnum!
What did you do?
Never mind them.
Come with me.
Boys!
Esperanza, run.
Run, mi amor.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SCREAMING]
Mama!
♪ ♪
Those men, they... they...
They kill your mom tonight.
But you get saved
by the Fountain of Imperium.
You see, it's not just
a source of raw power.
It's an alien being that whisked you off
to keep you safe.
It protected you, Spooner.
My whole life I thought those
aliens took my mom away,
but really, it was those oil men.
You have a choice.
You can let history play out
as it did before.
Or you can save your mother
and your younger self from those men.
Esperanza never has to leave here.
She can have a normal life.
So what do you want from me?
My goodness, I don't know...
I don't know what came over me.
Where did our guest go?
He sends his apologies.
He has some business to attend to.
Outside.
What the hell did John do in there?
He showed me the truth about my past.
The oil men come back
and kill Gloria for her land
while kid-me escapes and is saved
by the Fountain of Imperium.
So I'm staying here
and protecting them both
to make sure that never happens.
Look, whenever John is involved,
things tend to go south.
This is my only chance
to make sure my younger self
has a life with my mom.
I can finally get her back.
That's all I've ever wanted.
I thought you, of all people,
would understand that.
Of course I understand that,
Spooner, but...
But you just gave your blood to John
to open the Fountain,
which is the one thing
we are trying to stop.
You can go after him if you want,
but I'm staying here.
♪ ♪
Are you sure it actually posted?
Well, maybe we need to check the Wi-Fi.
[WARBLING, WHOOSHING]
She's here.
[ROARS]
- Kayla.
- [SNARLING]
Click-clack-clack.
What do you mean they're fake?
We will explain.
- [GRUNTS]
- Look...
We're sorry about the way
we had to contact you,
but Bishop stole our ship,
and you are the only person
that can help us get it back.
And why would I help you guys?
'Cause the eggs on that ship are real.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
And how did you survive?
Miracle of childbirth.
Bishop acted as midwife
and saved Rory's life.
♪ ♪
Those eggs are gonna hatch soon.
I have to go and protect them.
Wait.
Ever since that night on the planet,
I've never stopped thinking about you.
The eggs might be fake,
but my feelings for you are... real.
The only thing I care about right now
is getting back my babies.
Well, if you wanna get
your eggs back from Bishop,
you're gonna need our help.
What were you little fellas doing
in the Med Bay all by your lonesome?
Good thing you have me
to keep you company.
[FUNKY MUSIC]
I do hope that that's a
victory dance, Squire.
The groove is all part of the process.
Don't you worry, I got
the science covered, emo boy.
You just make sure
your hocus is pocused.
Oh, don't you worry about that.
I have a sure-fire way
to summon the Fountain.
Oh.
What's all this malarkey then?
This...
this serum will temporarily
make every cell in your body
mimic those of the most
angelic selfless child.
Which will make the Fountain
think that I am worthy.
Bingo.
The serum will go into this,
which I will hold onto for safekeeping.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You just let me know
when it's all good and ready
all right, squire?
Good.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
John, do you really think
Bishop is just gonna let you
use the Fountain?
Oh, don't be daft.
I know he wants to use
the powers for himself,
but old John Constantine
always has a plan.
So do me a favor.
- Stay out of my way.
- No.
Let me bring you back to
the team before it's too late.
"Oh, let me bring you back to the team
before it's too late, John".
Don't bloody kid yourself. Come on.
You, of all people, understand
what I'm doing, don't you?
You know what it feels like
to be powerless.
To desperately need magic.
You've always had this
selfish streak in you,
and my mom knew it was dangerous.
Now, what would your mum
think about you now, eh?
Her very own daughter
dabbling in the very dark arts
that she ran away from.
♪ ♪
I think she'd be turning in her grave.
Vá embora.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Damn it, John.
So what's your plan?
Just gonna shoot them all?
How do you know they're coming tonight?
Trust me, I know.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GUN CLICKS]
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, Gloria!
I've been playing nice, Gloria.
Now I've come to the edge.
So I'm gonna give you five whole minutes
to come on out here
and sign your place over to me.
Just let me go talk to him.
It's a trap.
They don't wanna talk.
Is this the only gun you have?
I've never used it.
It belonged to Celso.
I don't believe in
fighting with violence.
I'm sure Doc and I can
come to a civil agreement
and nobody needs to get hurt.
[GUNSHOT]
Mamí, what's going on?
Here, Esperanza.
Why don't you read this
in the bedroom, okay?
You'll be safer in there.
No!
There will be no bloodshed tonight.
There will be if you don't fight them.
Why is this even your business?
Because I'm your daughter!
I lost you once, Mom.
I'm not gonna lose you again.
- My daughter?
- I know it sounds crazy,
but it's me, Esperanza,
just all grown up.
And because of some
insane circumstances,
I've traveled from the future
to this moment in time.
And I know that tonight
you and my younger self
get separated for the rest of our lives.
- Separated? How?
- When those men attack,
I lose you for good.
And I escape into the woods
only to end up in a different time.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Please believe me.
I can fix history.
I can save you and little Esperanza.
Esperanza.
It's me, it's me.
And now that... now that I'm here,
you two can stay together.
I'm going to protect you.
[WHISPERS] I'm going to protect you.
♪ ♪
Spooner.
Remember if Esperanza
doesn't go to the Fountain,
then you never come back to save Gloria.
I'd rather protect her now
so I can become the person
my mom always hoped I'd be.
If she does that,
then my little girl and I,
- we can stay together, yes?
- Yeah, you'll stay together,
but history will be completely changed.
And you'll never meet the Legends
or help us save Sarah.
You'll never become you, Spooner.
Which means that...
which means we never become friends.
And I really don't wanna lose my friend.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
I can't let that innocent girl
go through what I went through.
If Esperanza does go,
she will grow up without me,
but she becomes you,
and history will be preserved, yeah?
♪ ♪
Then Astra is right,
and we have no choice.
Esperanzita has to go.
Losing you was the worst
moment of my life, Mom.
I spent every day
trying not to think about
what happened to you,
and it only made me angry and bitter.
♪ ♪
I didn't become the kind
of person you wanted me to be.
- Not even close.
- Yes, you did. You did.
You became that person.
You are brave.
You have a big heart.
You are a time traveler.
Whether it's aliens
or the universe at play,
you being here now is not a coincidence.
We were meant to find each other again.
Whatever powers took you away
also brought you back to me.
♪ ♪
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
We're saved by faith alone.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Stay with Gloria.
I'll get Esperanza to the Fountain.
Well, what do we do now, magic man?
Dance naked around a bonfire?
Ooh, make a blood sacrifice, perhaps?
Eh, we don't need a sacrifice,
but we do need blood.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Sit hoc sanguine, clavis est.
Ancient light show.
You must have started
a chemical reaction
which induced a bioluminescent response
in the cellular structure
of these mushrooms.
Would you stop your incessant
bloody commentary
for one minute?
[RUMBLING]
♪ ♪
Finally.
There she is.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, Gloria!
[TENSE MUSIC]
Everything is going to be
all right, mi amor.
We've got to do what's right.
♪ ♪
Listen to me, mamíta.
Astra, she's going
to take you somewhere.
Where?
Somewhere where you'll be protected.
I need you to be brave, okay?
And to remember everything
I ever taught you.
Why do I have to go without you, mamí?
- I don't want to go by myself.
- I know, honey.
I don't want to either,
but it's what we've got to do.
And before you know it,
we're going to see each other again.
And I know you can do it,
my strong and fearless girl.
We're going to see each other again.
I love you the most, Esperanza.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Time is up!
You better come on out.
Okay. We have to go. Come on.
Astra.
Take care of me.
♪ ♪
Always.
We've been doing this dance
far too long, Gloria.
Just sign these papers,
and we'll be on our way.
I'll say this once.
This land belongs to me
and to my daughter,
and it is not for sale.
[CHUCKLES]
Why you ladies have to be
such a pain in my ass?
Boys!
[GUNS COCKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
Showing you
what real pain feels like.
Because of your greed,
you forced a young girl
to leave her mother
and her home.
I want you to feel the anger,
the isolation,
the anguish
of losing everything you've ever loved.
♪ ♪
What the hell are you waiting for?
[GROANS]
Who are you?
I am my mother's daughter,
and this will never be your land.
[GROANING]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
Ah!
♪ ♪
John must have opened the Fountain.
Is that where I'm going?
Yeah, sweetie, that's
where you have to go.
Will it be scary?
At first, yeah.
But eventually,
you are gonna find friends and a family.
And guess what.
You're even gonna see me again.
Kay?
♪ ♪
Esperanza, I need you to stay
here for a second, okay?
♪ ♪
Esperanza?
I told you to stay out of my way.
Suntok ni demonyo.
Hey, John-Boy?
Is she part of the show?
♪ ♪
What is it?
I can feel it.
She's gone now.
No, she's right here,
with me.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
All right, losers,
we've located your ship.
Odessa, Texas, 1925.
And the Fountain of Imperium
is in Texas.
I only care about my eggs.
The tracker says your ship
should be right in front of us,
but I don't see it.
Oh, hold on. Wait. Uh...
[LOCK CHIRPS]
And bingo.
- There she is.
- Oh, I missed her.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
- Oh, there she is.
Let's go.
Nate, wait.
John's not gonna be on that ship.
All he cares about is the Fountain.
Okay, so how do we find a evil genius
and a crazed wizard in 1920s Texas?
Well, we, uh, follow the weirdness.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
We need to act quickly
before the Fountain disappears.
♪ ♪
John, you snake.
You swiped the serum from me?
Yeah, well, I wasn't gonna
bloody well let you take it
and have all those powers
to yourself, now was I?
[VIAL CLICKS]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
[WHISPERING] Oh, yeah.
I can feel it.
I can feel the Fountain.
[LAUGHING]
[COUGHS]
That's not exactly the Fountain
you're feeling, my friend.
You see, the serum I cooked up
did indeed make you worthy,
but I also added just a touch
of deadly poison.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
There are the eggs.
It's locked!
Well, there's gotta be another way in.
Gideon, are you there?
Guys, what is that thing
attached to the incubator?
Congratulations, Legends!
You found your ship
and triggered this message.
Now, I knew the first thing
you'd do is try to save
these wonderful interspecies eggs.
But if you want them,
you'll have to play a game
I call "48 Pick Up".
Now, when I open the door,
you'll have scant few moments
to gather as many of
the eggs as possible
before the incubator goes boom-boom.
Starting... now.
Grab anything you can
to put the eggs into.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Guys, hurry up!
[TIMER BEEPING]
♪ ♪
[GASPS] Egg!
[TIMER BEEPING]
♪ ♪
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[EXPLOSION BLASTS, GLASS SHATTERS]
Ugh, you bastard.
Oh, look, I'm sorry, John.
It's nothing personal.
You're just collateral damage.
Now that you're linked,
killing you means
I destroy the Fountain.
♪ ♪
Why?
To destroy the planet, of course.
You see, once upon a time,
benevolent aliens
gifted the Fountain to Earth
so it would act as an invisible shield
to protect the planet
from invasive alien species.
[GROANS]
I forgot to mention that, didn't I?
Once it dies,
it's open season on Earth, baby.
I've tried saving the planet twice,
and humans just keep getting in the way.
♪ ♪
Now I'm fast-forwarding
to the inevitable end
so I can finally start anew.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
So long, Johnny.
[SCREAMS]
♪ ♪
Something... something's wrong.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
- [GROANS]
- Esperanza, que pasa?
♪ ♪
John?
- John?
- Astra.
Oh, I'm so...
I'm so bloody sorry.
Just tell me what to do.
There's gotta be a spell
that can help you.
Not this time.
No, you are John Constantine.
You always have a plan.
You have a trick up your sleeve.
As luck would have it,
I'm all out of tricks this time.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
You were my greatest failure...
♪ ♪
And my biggest accomplishment.
God, you look like your mum.
She would be so proud of you, so proud.
No, no, John.
John, I need you to try.
I need you to stay alive.
♪ ♪
[QUIETLY] You hear that?
[FAINT SCREAMING]
The screaming.
♪ ♪
It's the Fountain.
I killed it.
♪ ♪
I killed it, Astra.
John!
♪ ♪
I killed...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -