[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Grab anything you can
to put the eggs into.
♪ ♪
Guys, hurry up!
- It's a bomb.
- Yeah.
[GASPS] Egg!
♪ ♪
Get down!
[EXPLOSION]
Mick, you okay?
Charred. Nothing new.
At least this little guy's unharmed.
Give me that.
You guys saved them. Why?
Those are Mick's kids
you're talking about.
That makes them family.
Look, I get why Bishop
would break the ship,
but why make such
an elaborate prank out of it?
He was stalling,
and mission accomplished.
And now the bomb obliterated
Gideon's mainframe,
which means we are stranded.
You're stranded. I still got my ship.
[COMPUTER CHIRPING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
That gyrating bastard.
Let me guess, Bishop stole your ship.
I'm gonna kill him.
- Oh!
[GLASS SQUEAKS]
Oh, my God, B.
Oh, hey, guys.
What happened to my couch?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I knew something was up with John.
I shouldn't have gone home.
I should've been here.
What could you have done?
We were all fooled.
I know a thing or two about addiction.
When we get John back on board,
he's not leaving my sight.
It's too late, B. John is gone.
"Gone", what do you mean "gone"?
Like he escaped?
He's dead.
Oh, that's not possible.
He... he's John Constantine.
He can't be dead.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
How?
He tried to control
the Fountain of Imperium,
which turns out
is an ancient fungal network
that's been keeping Earth safe
from invasive aliens for eons.
Bishop tricked John
into poisoning himself
to kill the Fountain,
and I watched John die.
♪ ♪
He decomposed into the ground,
and all that was left was this.
Whoa. May I?
♪ ♪
Wait a second. Where's Spooner?
Yeah, about that...
- [SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- _
So you're the time travelers
who found my Esperanza in the future.
It's nice to meet you
despite the circumstances.
I'm so grateful that
she's here with me now.
But I don't know
how much longer she will stay.
Is she dying?
Nothing I've tried
is helping to stop it.
I'm a healer...
♪ ♪
And I can't help my own daughter.
Ay, mi amor.
♪ ♪
How are we doing in here?
How's it look, smart-ass?
The CPU was obliterated.
Found some replacement parts,
but the wiring needs
to be completely rerouted and...
[TIMER RINGING]
- What's the timer for?
- The eggs, dummy.
They need to be rotated
every 12 minutes.
Oh, I got 'em.
Just a quarter turn only.
No, that's too much.
I got it. I got it.
Relax.
♪ ♪
Shouldn't you be strategizing
with your loser human friends,
coming up with some zany hijinks
to save a doomed planet or something?
Nope. I'm staying with my kids.
Your kids?
In Necrian culture,
the mother raises the children alone.
Look, I wasn't around
for my daughter, Lita.
I was lucky she let me
back into her life,
but I'm never making
that mistake again...
♪ ♪
Ever.
We should take her back to the ship.
The med bay is...
scratch that... totally broken.
It wouldn't help anyway.
Spooner is like this
because of what's happened
to the Fountain.
The two of them are linked.
[DEEP RUMBLING]
[DISTANT WHOOSHING]
[DEEP THUD]
Chances of that being a coincidence?
Slim to none.
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That's it? So much for an invasion.
It's a scout. They're watching us.
[CREATURES HUFFING AND HISSING]
♪ ♪
Fountain's dying. Earth is ours.
Send the beacon.
Spooner, Spooner, what beacon?
[CREATURE GROWLING]
You need to run now.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Over here!
Shoot it!
I don't have a clear shot!
- [GROWLING]
- Well, then shoot us both!
I... okay!
[GUNSHOT]
[COUGHS]
Sara, you okay?
- Yeah, where's the other one?
- Huh?
[GROANS]
[COMPUTER CHIRPS]
♪ ♪
If they were the scouts, then...
That was them ringing the dinner bell.
There's more coming.
We are so screwed.
The Zagurons know the Fountain's
dead, and they're coming.
The Fountain isn't dead. It's dying.
Those things are here to finish it off
and take over what's left.
Spooner translated the Zag' thoughts.
The power is still inside her,
but it is fading fast.
Well, that means there's still hope.
You know, we just have
to save the Fountain/Spooner
before the armada of carrion lizards
overwhelms our planet
and kills everyone in sight.
Easy-peasy.
All right, guys, let's brainstorm.
Let's figure out a way
to heal this Fountain.
We're gonna figure it out, babe.
Mm.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What is it?
I think this is Bishop's plan,
for me to watch you
and everyone I love die,
for me and him to be the only two left.
Well, it won't happen. We won't let it.
♪ ♪
[KNOCKS]
What, B?
I know you want to be alone right now,
but I need you to look at the mushroom.
- I'm good, thanks.
- I don't think John's dead.
I think he's inside this little guy.
Just look and listen
and clear your mind.
♪ ♪
Are you high right now?
Did you come to me
after John died stoned?
No, John isn't dead,
and that means he can still help us.
He'll know what the Fountain
needs to heal.
Stop. Even if he were somehow alive,
he's the last person
we should ask for help.
Lest you forget,
he screwed all of us over
for his pathetic ego trip.
♪ ♪
The Zagurons are coming to Earth?
I gotta fix this thing faster.
They almost killed me once.
I am not facing them again.
- You won't be alone this time.
- There is no beating them.
There's only escaping.
You want to take the ship and run.
It's the smart thing to do.
Don't worry. I'll keep the kids safe.
You could... you could
come too if you want.
Oh, I'm back.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
I'm back! Hello, Legends.
Did you miss me?
By the time you see this recording,
I expect John will be dead.
The Fountain will also be dead,
and my Zaguron friends
should be on their way to destroy you.
I hope I've got that right.
Otherwise possible egg on my face, ooh.
And because I can literally
think Sara's thoughts,
about now is the time that Sara Lance
has figured out my plan
for us to live together forever
after everyone else has died
as the new Adam and Eve.
Sara, your mind must be racing,
realizing that the only one
who can save the Fountain is me.
And, spoiler alert, I'm not gonna.
All right, so his message
gave me an idea.
He said he's the only one
who can save the Fountain.
So maybe he should.
Yeah, he's not gonna do that.
Not that guy, but a younger
version of him.
[GASPS] Time-napping.
I love it.
Gang, he wasn't always a supervillain,
but he's always been super smart.
We got the stuff he poisoned John with.
Maybe, just maybe,
the younger version of him
can reverse-schmience it
and get us an antidote.
It goes against every instinct you have,
which means Bishop
would never expect it.
If we only ever do
what makes sense to you,
he will always be one step ahead.
There's only one way
to wage a war against yourself.
And that is to have
a what Would Sara Never Do Day!
♪ ♪
It is a really bad idea.
_
♪ ♪
All right.
Now for the moment of truth.
Come to life, Ava Prime.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'm alive.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
Hello.
I'm... I'm...
dying.
Oh, oh. [SIGHS]
The neural network is still overloading.
[GROANS]
I am never gonna get this right.
[PORTAL WHOOSHES]
Oh!
Oh.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
You're a working Ava.
Well, I work, but I don't let my work
define me, you know?
Why are you... how are you...
was that a chronodimensional portal?
The less you know, the better.
Headline, we're time travelers,
and we need your help.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I must become wildly
famous for my genius
if time travelers come
looking for my help.
I can... I must become
a really big deal.
- The ego on this dude.
- I know.
All right, Smarty Pants,
want to help us save the world?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Wow.
Whoever made this
is a certified genius... an evil genius,
- but a genius.
- Yes.
An evil genius who is not
like anyone in this room.
I mean, there's some
bioengineering in this poison
that... I'm the only one
I've ever met that could think
of anything this diabolical.
Exactly why we came to you.
Now, can you please help us?
Of course, I can.
I just need some space
to work and no distractions.
I spoke to John. He is in the mushroom.
He wants to talk to us...
and we all got to eat him.
♪ ♪
So you ate a strange mushroom,
and you thought you heard John's voice?
I know I did.
It's proof that John's alive
inside the mushroom.
John wants us to eat
the mushroom and talk to him.
He wants to help us heal the Fountain.
John thinking about someone
other than himself?
Not a chance. We have a plan.
That plan is crazy,
but it still makes more sense
than talking to a mushroom.
Zari, wait. Just consider it.
So are we gonna do this?
Communing with a spirit
while in an altered state.
It's pretty on-brand for us.
Guys, I'm sorry, but no.
No, definitely not.
The last thing we need to be
doing is tripping on mushrooms.
Hm, yeah, well, isn't it
What Would Sara Never Do Day?
- I'm just saying.
- We already played that game.
And now it's time to prepare
for an alien invasion.
So please everyone just go
make yourself useful, okay?
You're right.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
Sara.
Eat me.
♪ ♪
- John?
- Eat the mushroom, love.
♪ ♪
- John.
- Sara.
Join me.
♪ ♪
Sara.
- John.
- Hello, Sara.
Are you...
♪ ♪
Are you alive?
Not exactly. I'm... present.
♪ ♪
What I did was unforgivable.
It's okay
because we're creating
an antidote for the poison
that you gave the Fountain,
and we can still stop
the Zagurons from coming.
That won't be enough.
Even if you heal the physical
side of the Fountain,
the spiritual side will remain ill.
John, I need your help.
I need you and the Fountain to help.
The Fountain has a mind of its own.
It no longer deems human beings
worthy of its protection.
Damn it, John, you did this.
You need to fix this.
I cannot separate myself
from the Fountain.
My life force is the only thing
keeping the Fountain and Spooner alive.
If I leave, they both perish.
I must stay as long as I can
and let the remnants
of my soul be drained.
Mushrooms feed off death,
and so I'm gonna feed it.
I owe it that much.
Sorry it had to be this way.
Do you remember all those years ago,
when I said that stable relationships
weren't right for you and me?
I was wrong.
Loving and being loved,
that is the point. I had that.
It should have been enough,
but I wanted more.
Now the whole world, especially Zari,
is suffering because of my mistake.
I think I understand.
There's one last thing
I need to tell you.
It's the greatest thing
I've learned since bonding
with the Fountain.
It's the secret to all life.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
- Gideon, run a diagnostic.
- All systems functioning.
And may I add, nice job
on the repairs, Kayla.
Excellent. Then let's get out of here.
Set a course for the temporal zone.
- Jump coordinates plotted.
- Do it.
Executing.
[ELECTRONIC KEY BEEPS]
- Powering down.
- No, you don't.
We can't stay here. Do you understand?
I am trying to protect our children.
I'm not leaving without my kids.
I'm not abandoning
my friends or this planet.
You know, I could
just snap your head off
and take that stupid button of yours.
Yeah, but you won't.
There's a part of you that cares.
Astounding.
How long until the antidote is ready?
We're kind of on the clock here.
- It's done.
- Guys, I know the answer.
I know the answer
to all of our questions.
It's the meaning of life.
You ate the mushroom, didn't you?
Yes, and I saw John.
- What?
- Yeah.
He told me what this is about.
He told me what everything is about.
He said...
♪ ♪
"We are all connected".
I think I saw that
on a bumper sticker once.
It was really profound in the moment.
[SYRINGE HISSES]
[GASPS]
Whoa.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- That's some strong juju.
- Spooner.
[SIGHS] Good to have you back.
Wait, since Spooner and
the Fountain are connected,
does that mean the Fountain is restored
and we stopped the invasion?
[DEEP RUMBLING]
[DISTANT WHOOSHING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ugh, there are thousands of these
scattered around the area.
I mean, even if we
could destroy the pods,
there are too many of them.
You know, they're too spread out.
This is classic Zaguron
perimeter technique.
They land, wait for dark,
and then they eat anyone
who isn't smart enough
to get out of their way.
- What?
- Which is something we should be doing.
No, we're not running. It's 1925.
They'll destroy the entire human race
before we're ever born.
We got to hold the line.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Heart rate normal.
Blood pressure is good.
I think you're finally back
with us, Ms. Cruz.
How do you feel?
Like I just ran a marathon.
Sweaty, starving.
- Here, darling, try this.
- Gracias, Mami.
So, Spooner, I'm glad
you're feeling better
and not to be a buzzkill,
but can you hear what
those Zagurons are thinking,
find out what they're doing out there?
I got nothing.
The only thoughts in my head
right now are my own.
I don't feel aliens
or mushrooms or anything.
Sorry, I'm... I'm confused.
I thought you and the
Fountain were linked.
If you're fine, then... then shouldn't
the Fountain wake up or whatever?
Scare the Zags away?
Look, the one thing I learned
while being connected
to the Fountain:
it doesn't want to help us.
Then we better have a damn good plan B.
All right, we have about four more hours
left of daylight,
so we've got to gear up,
hydrate, and prepare
for the fight of our lives.
- Ava, will you marry me?
- What?
Babe, we already did the proposal thing.
No, no, I mean, marry me now,
today, before the apocalypse.
What are you talking about?
We can't just...
Why not?
We're gonna have to fight
those things anyway.
We're as ready as we're ever gonna be,
and four hours is totally doable.
Ooh, we can get the whole team on board.
We've produced much crazier miracles
in far less time.
No, I would rather save the miracles
for the actual fight.
You guys, we may not survive the night.
Then let's go out on our own terms,
do things our way,
do what we've always wanted to do.
Babe, we've got our friends,
we've got our vows,
and we've got four hours.
What else do we need?
I don't know, maybe
for the world not to be ending.
Hey, John told me
the most important thing in life
is loving someone and being loved,
and if getting married is the last thing
that we do together, then damn,
I will be just fine with that.
You have really gone to town with this
"what would Sara Lance never do" thing.
Um...
okay, let's do it!
I don't... let's get married.
- Yay!
- Wedding before war!
- Yes!
Come on.
[UPBEAT POP MUSIC]
♪ ♪
♪ Ready for a celebration ♪
♪ I've been waiting my whole life ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Who ever knew it could be so good? ♪
♪ I feel like I'm right on time ♪
♪ You make me a believer ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You're one of a kind ♪
♪ You make me a believer ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Believer, believer ♪
♪ Believer ♪
♪ No doubt in my mind ♪
♪ ♪
The last time I used this tablecloth
was for my wedding to your papi.
I thought I would keep it locked away
until I used it for yours.
I'm not sure that's
ever going to happen.
[SPEAKS SPANISH] _
Stopping aliens is
what my friends and I do.
But I can't protect the planet
if I'm too busy protecting you.
You're too important to me, Mami.
I need you to be safe.
Pero this is my home.
I built it with my own
two hands for you, for us.
I spent my whole life
thinking aliens killed you.
I never thought I'd see you again.
I thought I'd lost you forever.
This... this has been a gift.
I've never been happier
to be wrong about anything,
but if you stay,
then that horrible story
I had to live with
for 20 years will be true.
_
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'll go pack my things.
[WHISPERING] Fabrication...
- Here's your gown.
- Thank you, Gary.
- What are you writing?
- Nothing!
I'm writing nothing because every time
I write something down,
it's stupid and meaningless,
and wedding vows are
supposed to be perfect.
You waited until right now
to write your vows?
Sorry. It's just very unlike you.
I waited until now
because before I was focused
on every tiny detail
of my dream wedding,
and now we're throwing it all the way
and racing into this slapdash ceremony,
and I have no time, and I feel like
I'm gonna just screw it all up here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, deep breaths.
Huh? It's gonna be fine.
How?
Sara already wrote her vows, Gary.
Sara, the person
who never plans anything,
already did the one thing
that every wedding needs.
It's okay. Here's what's
going to happen.
You're going to walk down that aisle...
- Mm-hmm.
- To the love of your life.
She's gonna say some
very beautiful things to you.
- That's not helping.
- No, no, no.
And then you...
you're gonna look deep
into those gorgeous blue eyes
- of hers and say what you feel.
- I feel sick.
- Don't say that.
- I don't...
What do you... you want
me to improvise, me?
- Yeah, you.
- I can't.
Because I know what you say
in that moment will be perfect
because it's true because it's you.
♪ ♪
- Gary.
- Mm-hmm?
♪ ♪
Will you please walk me down the aisle?
It would be my greatest honor,
Director Sharpe.
♪ ♪
[SOFT ACOUSTIC MUSIC]
♪ For you ♪
♪ There'll be no more crying ♪
♪ ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ The Sun will be shining ♪
♪ ♪
Thanks for coming.
It's not like you gave me much choice.
You brought the kids.
Well, last time they
were left on the ship,
they almost blew up.
Yes. Yes, they did.
♪ And the songbirds ♪
- [CHUCKLES]
- ♪ Are singing ♪
♪ Like they know the score ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ I love you like never before ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Like never before ♪
♪ ♪
We're gathered here today
on what may very well be
our last to celebrate the union
of these two amazing people.
I fondly remember the moment they met.
- She had a gun.
- [LAUGHS]
She had a glare.
Destiny was at work.
We've all been through
a lot since that day,
and on that journey,
you've challenged each other
to be the best versions
of yourself possible.
This moment, this wedding,
this is exactly what the world needs.
♪ ♪
We're facing insurmountable odds,
but even during the darkest of times,
when hope seems lost, love.
[TENDER MUSIC]
Love is what matters most.
♪ ♪
Ava, the perfect woman,
what could a mess like me
ever have to offer
someone as special as you?
I can't exactly say
it was love at first sight,
but you did look really good
in that pantsuit.
But the more that I got to know you,
and I got to feel
your kindness and your honesty,
well, this heart, once
so cold and guarded,
it just... it just melted.
And Ava, it's because of you
that I get to know
what true love feels like.
And so, today, here in front
of all of our friends...
♪ ♪
I want to make these vows to you.
I will always be your
champion, your lover.
I will always be your family,
and I will listen to you
even when the words are hard to hear,
and I will let you in
even when I'm afraid,
and I will support you.
I will fight for you.
And above all, Ava Sharpe,
I will love you.
[SIGHS] Wow.
♪ ♪
Your turn.
Oh, oh, man.
I... Sara,
I... my life before you
was a perfect fabrication,
and then you came into my world,
and everything just became
a whirlwind, you know?
You brought chaos into
my tidy, predictable existence,
and you pretty much brought me to life,
so I vow to you
to live this life together.
Co-captains forever, baby.
♪ ♪
I love you so, so much, Sara Lance.
I love you. I love you.
♪ ♪
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh.
♪ ♪
So if there's no objections...
[SPACESHIP SPUTTERING AND WHOOSHING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
That's my ship!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You've got to be kidding me.
What a darling setup you've got here.
Pre-apocalypse nuptials
are all the rage,
but you know it's gonna be you and me
for all eternity, Sara Lance.
Is that me? Am I the villain?
Wait, is that
my younger self down there?
Wow, that's embarrassing.
I did not see that coming.
Well played, but I'm afraid
♪ It's all for naught ♪
'cause you know what your little party
is missing? Wedding crashers.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Ta-ta, you crazy kids.
All right,
anybody without steel skin
or regeneration
fall back and barricade the house.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I ain't running.
Come get your weapons, folks.
I got my own, thanks.
Here. Get out of here.
- I'm staying.
- What?
This family is sticking together.
♪ ♪
Hey, it was a perfect wedding.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
[ZAGURONS GROWLING]
Guys, we might want to
rethink our stance on running.
♪ ♪
Uh, yeah, we gotta go!
- Go, go!
- Go, go, go.
- Run!
- Go, go, go!
♪ ♪
Go, go, go!
Reinforce the entry points,
use anything you can find.
- Go, go, go.
- What's happening?
- You need to hide.
- Should I help?
You've done enough!
♪ ♪
Ah!
Come on.
Spooner, we need
your mom's medical supplies.
I'm on it.
Come on, Behrad.
Hey, just stay with me, okay?
I'm not losing you too.
Oh, no. It's spreading too quick.
- We need a tourniquet.
- That's not gonna help.
♪ ♪
Zari, hold him down. B, close your eyes.
- Wait, what are you doing?
- Saving his life.
That venom is gonna kill him
like it killed me.
There is no cure.
We have to stop the spread.
Now, hold him down.
Hey, you are not touching him
with that thing.
I'm trying to save him.
Not with that, you're not.
- He's gonna die.
- Stop fighting!
You guys seeing this?
You gave him my powers.
It's the Fountain.
I can feel it. It's waking up.
It's like... it's like John said,
we're all connected.
♪ ♪
Come on. Yeah.
Nate's powers to Ava.
I need a weapon.
Spoons!
Ugh, damn it!
Sara, you're up!
♪ ♪
- What's happening?
- Just go with it!
Right. Watch out.
We're not gonna make it.
At least we got to get
married before the end, right?
Wait, you're not married.
We didn't do the "I do's".
I'll buy you some time.
Everyone, huddle up!
We're getting these two hitched
even if it's the last thing we do.
Get married quick
before I change my mind.
♪ ♪
[GROWLS]
Sara, do you take this woman to be
your lawfully wedded wife
till death do you part?
I do.
Do you, Ava, take this woman
to be your lawfully wedded wife
till death do you part?
I do.
♪ ♪
Then by the power vested
in me by the World Wide Web,
I pronounce you wife and wife.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
So that was the Fountain of Imperium.
And it saved us.
It decided we were worth it after all.
Guess getting hitched
at the end of the world
- wasn't such a bad idea.
- Damn right, wifey.
- Mm.
- Ooh.
♪ ♪
The fountain loves love!
Stupid Zags and their
stupid mushroom allergy.
Well, if you want something done right,
you got to do it your damn self.
Give it up, Bishop. You lost.
Never!
Ooh.
[EGGS CRACKING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
It's time.
I'll give you one last chance
to leave and never come back.
I found your younger self once,
and I'll do it again,
end you before you become
the sad, little, deranged man
you are now.
I will blast each and every human
on this stupid planet to bits,
starting with all of you.
I don't care how long it takes.
You and I will be the only two left.
[ALIEN BABIES CHIRPING]
What the... ?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Wait, are those... aww!
Ow! Ah, get off me!
Get off me! Ow, oh, oh, stop!
[SCREAMING]
Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
[BURPS]
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
Necrian babies wake up very hungry.
They'll typically devour
the first thing they see.
Did I not mention that before?
ALL: No.
Oh.
[CHIRPING]
Hey little guy or girl.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Either way, I love you.
♪ ♪
- Aww.
- Oh.
Guys, you got married.
You became parents.
Mazel tov, everybody!
[ALL CHEER]
Let's rage!
I think I understand now.
You brought me here as a warning
to show me what I'll become
if I don't change my ways.
Well, I got the message,
and I swear I will never become that.
Thank you.
- It's a very sweet sentiment.
- It is.
But, unfortunately,
you're gonna have
to live out that destiny.
It's how the timeline works. Sorry.
- Ava Prime?
- Here we go.
Is this a dream?
Click your heels, Dorothy.
You're going home.
I really did love you.
I wish that could've been enough.
What's the hurry, love?
♪ ♪
You... you bastard.
What, you've been sneaking
around here this whole time?
No, no, no, I just got here,
honestly, really.
You know, after the Fountain healed
and could survive without me,
it saw the purity of my sacrifice,
and it's offered to give me
another chance.
Your purity? Don't lie to me.
Okay, all right. I was joking.
The Fountain didn't
think too highly of me,
even less after I contacted
an old associate in Hell.
Long story short, the chit to my soul
now belongs to a demon once again,
and the Fountain is very happy
that I'm no longer bound to it.
Wow, you haven't changed
at all, have you?
You know, people can change
and not change at the same time.
I'm still a bastard. I know that.
But I guess now I know
what I'm missing by being a bastard.
♪ ♪
We mucked it up.
We mucked it up just
like you said we would.
I'd do it all over again
in a heartbeat, love.
Me too.
Listen, I have to walk
a different path now,
- away from the Legends.
- [SIGHS]
But here, take this.
An old key. What is this for?
You'll find out.
♪ ♪
[ETHEREAL WHOOSH]
Life's crazy, isn't it?
Imagine if our first day
on the Waverider,
we travel to this moment
to this house, and we saw me,
a captain with a wife
and you with 48 kids.
49 and a grandbaby on the way.
I don't think we would
have recognized ourselves.
No, got to move forward,
I guess, to the next job.
A new partner.
Yeah, I had a feeling that was coming.
[TENDER MUSIC]
You know you'll always have
a home on the Waverider.
But I guess you'll be busy
taking care of 48 punks.
Well, I've learned a thing
or two about handling punks.
Watched you do it for six years.
♪ ♪
There you go.
What's this?
It's a bridal bouquet.
That means you're next.
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
Well, that's that.
Yeah, I'm kind of nervous.
Things rarely wrap up
in a neat little bow for us.
No, come on, babe. Don't be paranoid.
Life is gonna start going our way.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What the hell?
Ugh.
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -