Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Astra's dead mother
was a powerful witch.
Why did you bring me back?
Natalie, is that really you?
Natalie brought you here
to help me save Astra.
What do you know about the loom of fate?
- You want to know what I'm hiding from?
- Yes, I do.
It's that bloody loom.
He still has 10 years.
Can you make it zero?
Bye-bye, Johnny.
[CHOKES AND GAGS]
- John?
- [WHEEZING]
John, can you hear me?
- [HEART BEATING LOUDLY]
- What happened?
He just collapsed out of nowhere.
After coughing up a bucket of blood.
Come on, Johnny. Stay with us.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Gideon, we'll need to run a scan.
Right away, Dr. Palmer.
[GRUNTS]
[SCANNER WHIRS]
Oxygen mask, please.
[COUGHS]
The loom. Where is it, Charlie?
Not now, John, all right?
You gotta rest.
- What loom?
- Astra's ghost mom, she told...
Oh, my God! Hold me, hold me, hold me!
What the hell's going on?
As you can see from his chest
X-ray, Mr. Constantine
has a very aggressive
form of lung cancer.
I'm afraid it's terminal.
_
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[LIGHTER CLINKS]
Well, there's no point in quitting now.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[GRUNTS]
There's nothing funny
about lung cancer, John.
[CHUCKLES] Who's laughing?
- [COUGHS]
- If you lose your hair,
I'm shaving my head in solidarity.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a minute.
No saucy AI is butchering me
and pumping me full of...
- [INJECTS SEDATIVE]
- I took the liberty of administering a sedative.
Mr. Constantine needs to rest.
Gideon, prepare the jumpship.
Clotho.
Where are you going?
You can't escape us.
Clotho. You can't get away.
- Damn.
- We see you.
♪ ♪
No, you don't.
Oh, mate.
Charlie. You're back.
Well, how are you doing, B-Easy?
Where you been?
Oh, I was just, I was just
hanging out with Constantine.
How is he?
- Dying.
- What?
Oh, no, don't worry. You know John-O.
He's always got a trick up his sleeve.
Bro, that donut you made me
eat had me hallucinating.
Starting today, I'm on a juice cleanse.
Sorry, this is my...
friend, Charlie.
- Charlie, meet my sister.
- Hmm, good fashion.
Team meeting on the bridge.
Does that mean me?
That means you too, Zari.
Hmm, cool.
So you coming?
I wouldn't miss it. [CHUCKLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Oh, Charlie.
We could really use your help right now.
With Sara in Star City
and Rory in a mood,
we are short-staffed.
What's Mick in a mood about?
[GASPS] Ali, his girlfriend.
Ray, they on... they only had sex once.
Well, when you know, you know.
- You know?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
Okay, listen. I know we're all
worried about John, okay?
And we could just sit back
and wait for a miracle.
But does Marie Kondo rest just
because she built an empire?
- No.
- No. No, she tidies up.
And that is exactly what
we're gonna continue to do.
We are gonna tidy up the timeline, yeah?
Gideon, show them what
we've been working on.
Each point represents
a potential encore,
which means we can catch them
before they change history.
I call her,
"The Prognosticator."
[CLAPS]
Um...
Okay, anyway.
There's a category five
in 1997 Hong Kong.
A mysterious gangster is moving in
- on the Triad's territory.
- _
Ray, I want you and Zari to QB.
Oh, you don't have to
tell me to "queen bee."
- It'll look her naturally.
- Oh, you know what.
Hong Kong traffic is notoriously bad.
So why don't we take my new...
- ♪ Scooter ♪
- Whoa.
I call her,
"Scoots McGoots."
- Ah, dude.
- So awesome.
[EXCITED CHATTER]
The scooter, you're all impressed by?
Oh, my God, I need one.
Wanna go for a ride?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Ooh.
- And away we go.
- Totally.
- Okay, I'm next.
- Wait, careful.
- Slow down.
- Okay. All right, speed 'er up.
Hey, hey.
[LIVELY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Never been to Hong Kong before.
So what's the plan?
I had Gideon cook up the same
sedative she dosed John with.
All we have to do is inject the encore
and bring him back to
the ship for naptime.
One problem. We're just supposed to hope
the encore shows up
looking for a copper?
This is no ordinary tea shop.
♪ ♪
It's owned by the Triad.
Nate, how's the perimeter sweep?
No sign of a gangster from hell yet.
So it looks like we've arrived
right as Great Britain was getting ready
to hand control of Hong
Kong back to China.
Oh, well that's probably not pertinent,
but keep up the research.
Psst.
Gary, what are you doing here?
John's trying to leave the ship.
You have to stop him.
You should return to the
med bay, Mr. Constantine.
John, what are you doing out and about?
Listen, Big Man.
[COUGHS] Look, I know you're
only trying to help, all right?
But nobody gets stage four
lung cancer this fast.
Some sneaky git with a grudge against me
is bending the rules of magic.
Oh, who could hate you that much?
[SIGHS] The list is long.
I'm taking the jumpship
home to narrow it.
- [COUGHS]
- John, no.
I cannot let you leave this ship.
You are in need of medical supervision.
Oh, you can't let me?
You forget who I am, Old Son?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Fine.
But I'm going with you.
Hallelujah. [SIGHS]
That was intense.
Your encore's a no-show.
I say we split.
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
13th century armor.
Fu Manchu mustache.
Guys?
I think I know who the encore is.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
It's Genghis freaking Khan.
♪ ♪
How the hell did Genghis
Khan get to 1997
and learn how to ride a motorbike?
Genghis used horses to
revolutionize warfare.
A motorbike's a modern day horse.
Looks like he's meeting with the Triad.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
What sort of man steals my drugs
and my nephew's ear,
only to return them to me?
I have only one interest.
Conquest.
Surrender the Triad to me,
and I will remake the globe.
And if I refuse?
We're not getting in that room.
We should abort.
Regroup on the ship.
What? And stay in Hong Kong longer?
Give me the syringe. Let's finish this.
B., I'm gonna need a distraction.
It's too dangerous.
Any moment.
Charlie, stop. Don't do this.
[SCREAMS]
B., run.
[GROANS]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We're the cops. Freeze, jackass.
Great distraction, B.
♪ ♪
No.
[GROANING]
Genghis is leaving. I'm going after him.
Charlie, wait.
♪ ♪
[YELLS]
Charlie?
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
♪ ♪
- I'm out.
- Me too.
Drop your guns.
[SCOOTER BELL CHIMES]
Shoot him.
[GRUNTS]
- Huh?
- Nice timing.
[PANTS]
Scoots?
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Shoot him!
- He's immortal.
And I'm not.
- [GUN CLICKS]
You're lucky.
Maybe next time, not so lucky.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[WHEEZES AND GROANS]
[COUGHS]
Gary, bring me the foxglove,
a serpent's tongue,
and the hair of an albino.
[WHEEZES AND COUGHS]
- All right.
- John, you need some water?
Bollocks. No mate.
Just do me a favor and pull up the rug.
[COUGHS]
- What are you planning?
- [COUGHS]
Summoning spell.
I'm gonna throttle the
bastard that did this to me.
Are you really up for that?
Yeah, no two-bit demon is
getting the better of me.
I'm John Constantine, and
I am devious to the core.
I added honey, just how you like it.
Good, now give it here.
- [WHEEZES]
- [EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GASPING]
[LAUGHS]
♪ Johnny ♪
Show your face.
The great John Constantine.
Brought to his knees.
There are denizens of heaven and hell
who would kill to see this.
Surprise.
Astra.
Why?
You're bad for business, John.
The cancer was already in your lungs.
I just sped it up.
I swear this magic is
way beyond you, love.
Look, whoever helped you,
whatever you promised them in exchange,
trust me, it's a trap.
I'll keep that in mind.
You know, I would have expected
your purgatory to be a little more...
[PRESSES PIANO KEYS]
Gruesome.
Well, you don't remember
this place then.
Your mother brought you here.
So that's your angle.
I knew you'd try something, John.
Astra, I can change your mother's fate.
All right, she never dies,
you never go to hell, your dad, he...
He never drowns his sorrow in booze.
Your family can be whole again.
Tempting.
But everyone you try to help,
you hurt.
This is different, all right?
I know someone who has a lead
on a very powerful artifact.
[MIMICS JOHN] "I know someone."
John, listen to yourself. It's pathetic.
No, what is pathetic is that someone
who is so content to rule hell
because they are too scared
to make a go at a real life.
Look, this is what Natalie wanted, love.
I just, I need a little more time.
Time is something you're running low on.
[INTENSE MUSIC]
- Oh, thank God.
- [GASPS]
No, the Man Upstairs had
nothing to do with this.
It was Astra.
She owns the chip to my soul.
She's figured out a way
how to spin down the dial
on the time I have left. [COUGHS]
Thanks. [WHEEZES]
John, I'm sorry.
Oh, cheer up, lads.
This dog is still in the fight.
[CHUCKLES]
That went well.
My "queen bee-ing," I mean.
You four almost got yourselves killed.
- I had fun.
- Fun?
You got us stuck in the
middle of a shootout.
That's why I love Bruce Lee.
He never uses guns.
Keep your knickers on.
You have wind powers.
You could have just stopped
the bullets mid-air.
Stop bullets? [LAUGHS] You're crazy.
Look, this is all my fault.
We should have been gathering
intel, not doping the encore.
- Gideon?
- I'm currently tracking
Genghis Khan's whereabouts
via his license plate.
Great, 'cause we need to
figure out how and why
Genghis just showed
up in 1997 Hong Kong.
Charlie, you up for
some undercover work?
Oh, I get it, just because
I'm the shape-shifter,
I have to be the one to
infiltrate the criminal gang.
Sorry, pause. You're a shape-shifter?
Yeah, I am actually.
I can shift into anyone you like.
- Anyone?
- Yeah, anyone.
- Hah.
- All right, come on.
Where's Mick? I'm gonna get a drink.
- I need to smoke.
- Well, I...
[SIGHS]
I don't get it. They
used to be best buds.
Oh, there's only one explanation.
B. and Charlie went to pound town.
Ew, gross, ugh.
- Wait, what?
- Moan zone?
Smash city?
- Ava.
- [GASPS]
They had sex?
[MOTORCYCLE REVS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[LOUD THUD]
[BOTTLES CLINK]
♪ ♪
[SCREAMS]
[SIGHS]
All right, guys.
- I'll see you in a bit.
- Charlie.
Oh, here we go. Another lecture.
No, I just...
Be careful.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
- She won't talk.
- [PANTING]
Ah, the hero cop from the tea house.
Ava, you there?
Yeah, Charlie. You find something?
Genghis kidnapped your cop friend.
[SIGHS]
What do we have here?
Only one child.
How unambitious.
Nevertheless,
give me what I desire,
and I will spare his life.
[KNOCKS]
- John, Nora's here.
- All right, I'm coming.
[COUGHING]
[SNIFFLES AND SIGHS]
Okay, Pippa.
Can you wish our friend, John,
healthy like we discussed?
Yes, but I want something first.
Pippa's made a lot of progress,
but we're still working
on a few challenges.
Hey.
The Master of the Dark
Arts needs your help.
Shut up, four eyes.
Now you listen to me, you little squirt.
Are you gonna make that damn wish?
Because if you don't
and I die, then I'm gonna
come back and haunt you
every waking hour of your life.
Fairy Godmother,
I wish your scary British
friend wasn't sick.
There you go, easy. [COUGHS]
Okay.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
[RETCHES]
No matter. [SNIFFLES]
I'll try something else.
I wish I was home.
Sorry.
Bye, Ray.
Bye, Nora.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
So when did you and Charlie,
you know? [CLICKS TONGUE]
[SIGHS] It's that obvious?
Mm-hmm.
After "HeyWorld."
Wow. That's nice.
How was it? She shape-shift?
That's what we wanna talk about?
100%, but we don't have to.
Look, Charlie's clearly affecting you.
So come on. Talk to me.
- It's stupid.
- What?
She left without saying goodbye.
Mm. Yeah, that sucks.
But if you were thousands of years old,
wouldn't you be over goodbyes?
The least she could've done is texted.
How hard is it to send a ghost emoji?
Maybe it wasn't about you.
Dumb Dumb's got a good point.
B., chin up. You are a catch.
If there was a female version of you,
I would be all over her. Fact.
- Like my sister?
- Absolutely.
But the point is
we don't know why Charlie
didn't say goodbye.
So just check your ego and ask her.
You're right. Thanks, Nate.
My man.
Where's our prisoner?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[BOTH GROAN]
Even with Prince Charles's
motorcade route,
he'll be heavily guarded.
Wait, Prince Charles is the target?
He's here to hand Hong
Kong back to China.
What if The Khan wants Prince
Charles to give to him instead?
An authoritarian power wants
to control Hong Kong.
That sounds familiar.
[GASPS AND GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
The worst part of my resurrection
was finding myself buried
in an impenetrable tomb.
It took me 700 years to dig myself out.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
The best part of my resurrection
was the sword I was buried with.
[GRUNTS]
Genghis just killed a
cop with a hell weapon.
Son of a bitch. Okay,
you got what we needed.
Charlie, get the hell out of there.
Yeung.
What is the status of my fleet?
Your fleet?
The one you are building
to conquer the globe.
Right.
Fleet's great.
In fact, I have to go
check on it right now.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Don't freak out. I can explain.
_
[SCREAMS]
[SHAPE-SHIFTING WHOOSH]
[SIGHS] Never mind.
- Clotho.
- [PANTS]
No matter what face you wear,
you can't hide from us.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
No. Leave me alone, ugh.
[HORN HONKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
So what's the verdict? Can you heal me?
[GROWLS]
Well, then. Screw you.
[SNARLS]
Come with me. He didn't mean that.
Yeah, I did. [COUGHING]
I wish you would just let us
take you to the oncologist.
Raymond, how many times
do I have to tell you? [SIGHS]
This is a disease caused by magic,
and only magic can fix it.
"How to Add Years to Your Life."
Yeah, that should do it.
Although the ingredient
list is a little unusual.
We'll need a medieval knight.
I was once knighted "Sir
Raymond of the Palms."
Great. Gary, grab a knife.
We're gonna perform a little
back alley surgery on the Big Man.
What kind of surgery?
Well, first off, are you uncircumcised?
[STAMMERS]
Well, I'll take that as a
yes. Gary, the knife.
No.
We tried Nora. We tried the Púca.
What if there isn't a cure?
Isn't there anyone you...
that you need to say goodbye to?
What about a bucket list?
[WHEEZES]
[COUGHS]
Goodbyes are for saps.
And bucket lists are for
mealy-mouthed cowards
who don't have the courage
to carpe the bloody diem.
I have a bucket list.
Well, thank you for proving
my point, Raymond.
Stop being so mean.
You know, we're trying to help you...
- Help me?
- Yes.
Captain America and the village idiot.
Well, I don't need your help.
I take care of myself. I always have.
What, you think I'm gonna
let Astra beat me?
I will fight, and I will scheme,
and I will make a deal with
the archangel himself.
You hear that, Gabriel?
Hey, come and get me.
Have I got an offer for you.
Looks like he's not coming.
Well, I'll think of
something, I always do.
Now, piss off, I've had
enough of the pair of you.
Go on. Piss off!
[WHEEZES AND COUGHS]
Hello.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the last queen of France.
Right, just when I thought this ship
couldn't get any more barmy.
Looking for a time courier?
Why are you in such a
hurry to leave? Again.
You know me. Always looking
for the next party.
Usually, I would buy that.
But you just almost walked into a truck.
Something has you spooked.
Is whatever's going on
the reason why you left?
- Here we go.
- Look, I'll admit it.
I liked you.
I was hurt when you left.
And I've felt weird ever
since you returned.
Now, can you be honest with me?
Honestly, you are
starting to piss me off.
You know, we had sex,
and it was mediocre.
Get over it.
[GASPS]
Wow, okay. I'm gonna ignore that.
If you don't wanna talk, fine.
But we're about to go up
against Genghis Khan.
- Don't leave now.
- [SUCKS TEETH]
Just give me the courier.
Bye, Charlie.
Mediocre is no bad.
Charlie's gone? How could
you let her leave?
I didn't. It was her choice.
Okay, hey, how about we
focus on Genghis Khan?
You're right.
We need to stop him from attacking
Prince Charles's motorcade.
Well, he's on his way to a ceremony
ending 156 years of colonial rule, so.
Have you been researching history?
Oh, sorry. That's your thing, right?
- No, but it's cool that you're into...
- Okay. Hey, okay.
- Moving on, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Turns out the person Charlie
impersonated is an engineer.
There's a shipment coming in tonight.
I'll bet you that's the fleet
Genghis uses for his attack.
What kind of fleet?
Whatever it is, it's the next
step of modern warfare.
I'll go to the docks.
I'll try to figure it out.
Okay, Zari and I will
monitor the airspace
above the motorcade,
and you'll be on the street.
I know it's a lot of ground to cover.
If Charlie was here...
I get it. I'm on my own.
I can't believe you stooped
to trying to make a deal
with an angel. Mm.
What the...
Gabriel would have turned
you into his slave.
Well, at least I'd be alive.
[SCOFFS] There are worse
fates than death.
Oy.
I will shove you where
the sun don't shine
- just to shut you up.
- Hmm.
You'd probably enjoy that.
Hell of a way to spend your
last nights on earth though,
you arrogant bastard.
Especially when you could be with two
of the only friends you have left.
Yeah.
Yeah. Nice one.
[STAMMERS] I just feel so helpless.
- You know?
- Me too, Gary.
If he has to go, I just,
I want him to be at peace.
Well, that's not his style.
John's gonna go out
- the way he lived.
- Yeah.
Like a bloody wanker, eh?
You know it occurs to me
that I might owe you two
a bit of an apology.
We accept.
Oh, that's okay. [COUGHS]
Come on, sit... [COUGHS]
All right, okay.
- You're hurting me. Go on.
- Oh.
Sit down. Stop bloody fussing, will you?
[COUGHS]
You know, I can't remember the
last time this room was used
as an actual kitchen.
Well, there's a roast in the oven.
- It'll be ready soon.
- Mm.
[WHEEZES]
Did I ever tell you both about the time
I met the ghost of Winston Churchill?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Behrad, what's your status?
It's complete gridlock.
No one's getting through on the ground.
The fleet must be in the air.
Nate, did you find the shipment?
Oh, no. We're too late.
Whatever there was,
there was a lot of them.
Nate, get downtown and help Behrad.
Hold on.
I think they might have left something.
[MOTORS WHIRRING]
What's that noise?
Oh, my God.
[MOTORS WHIRRING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Scoots.
Khan!
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
♪ ♪
Charge!
[MEN YELLING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MOTORS WHIR]
They're getting through the
gridlock on their scooters.
Heading straight for Prince
Charles's motorcade.
[GUNSHOTS]
Stay down, Your Majesty. Turn here.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I could really use some help!
Nate, tell me you're close, please.
I'd be lying.
B., it's your time. You got this.
♪ ♪
[GUNSHOTS]
- Protect the prince!
- [GUNSHOTS]
Get down. Take cover. Look out.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS] Not again.
Look who it is.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect
you, Prince Charles.
It's not your fault.
But my friends call me Charlie.
Apprehend this imposter.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Show your true form,
or I end him.
Looks like your luck has
run out, shape-shifter.
Where is the prince?
Sorry, Genghi.
He's somewhere you'll never find him.
[ROCK MUSIC]
Your shape-shifting friend
said you need to tell
your team that I'm here.
And I told her I'm on my beer break.
Now shut up, Princess, and listen.
♪ ♪
I've never met one of your kind before.
You will be my 13th wife.
Come again, mate?
Your power will serve my reign well.
Join me as I build a new empire
that will span the globe.
Look, I'm flattered,
but I've had power of
immortals and gods alike.
It blows.
My past is complicated.
And being in a relationship...
Trust me, that wouldn't
end well for either of us.
Wait.
Did you two sleep together or something?
[SCOFFS] What a shame.
Kill her.
What? No. Come on.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WIND WHOOSHING]
[GRUNTS]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Unless you lot want those
bullets firing back at you,
bugger off.
♪ ♪
Run away! Run away!
I told you you could stop bullets.
Not that I wanted to find out.
[LAUGHS] Come here.
- Yeah, that was sick.
- I know.
- Is that Genghis's toothpick?
- Well, yeah, you want it?
- Oh, no, it's disgusting.
- [LAUGHS]
You said you were gonna tell us
what's really going on with you.
[SIGHS] Look, I'm just,
I'm still trying to find
the words, all right?
Can you try to find them faster?
[SMACKS LIPS] Fine.
I'm just gonna come out with it.
I am a Fate.
One of the three old Greek ladies?
That's offensive, but correct.
- Which one are you?
- Clotho, the spinner.
I'm super confused,
but what do you spin?
Look, I don't spin anything anymore,
but I used to spin people's futures.
On your loom?
Oh, lovely. Even Gideon's joining in.
Yes, there was a loom,
but I destroyed it
thousands of years ago.
No one should have that kind of power.
I think people should just
decide their own destinies.
Why didn't you just tell us?
Look, I've been keeping this secret
for my entire bloody
existence, all right?
I've never told anyone.
Can we see your OG form?
Absolutely not.
Is it 'cause you're old?
It's because your eyes
would explode, all right?
And your ears too if you could
hear my original voice.
Why are you running?
My sisters are coming after me.
They have been ever since
I destroyed our loom.
Wait, you've been running
for thousands of years?
Yes, and I've always
stayed one step ahead.
I scattered the loom pieces
across the multiverse,
which took away my sisters' powers.
But now that we're all
in one universe...
thanks to Sara and her
merry band of paragons...
the loom pieces are back on one plane.
And now it's only a matter of
time until my sisters find me.
And when they do?
They'll kill me. And
anyone that I'm with.
Which is why I left.
And it's why I'm out that door
now that we're done playing ask a fate.
Stop running. We got your back.
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
My sisters are no joke.
Well, we're the Legends.
Yeah, we can take down
a couple old ladies.
[SCOOTERS FALLING]
What is with all these damn scooters?
They're a menace.
Oh, hey, guys. What did I miss?
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- John, this wine is delicious.
- And nutritious.
Well, there's no point in
saving the good stuff, eh?
I'm never gonna drink with you again.
Oh, come on, mate. Stiff upper lip, eh?
I'm gonna miss you so much, you know?
Nothing can make me feel better.
Oh, bollocks, all right. [COUGHS]
Look, I didn't want you to
see my will until I died.
But, Raymond, can you do the honors?
Oh, sure.
[CHUCKLES]
You're giving this house to Gary?
[CRYING]
Bloody hell, that was
supposed to make you happy.
Not insufferable.
I promise to take great care
of this place, you know?
I'll feed the hellhounds, I'll vacuum...
You know, why don't we
talk about what you had
on your bucket list, eh, mate?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Give me something meaningful, eh?
Well, eventually I...
plan on asking Nora to marry me.
Can I be your flower boy?
Oh, that's very sweet, Gary.
Odd but very sweet.
Why haven't you asked her yet, Big Man?
I've been engaged twice before.
Both times didn't end as I had hoped.
You know, life, it is too short
to dillydally, Raymond.
I know you... you can
take that from a man
who has nothing but regrets.
So if you love that witch,
you bloody will marry her, right?
[COUGHS]
No, no, no. I'm all
right, I'm all right.
[SNIFFLES] Now how about a toast, eh?
Okay.
No, with this.
Oh, of all the ways that
I'd thought I'd go,
decapitated by a demon,
eviscerated by an elemental,
I wouldn't have picked being
at home with my mates.
- Cheers.
[SIGHS]
[COUGHING]
You know, I just wish I
had more time with you...
lovely idiots.
Well, you're not dead yet, John.
No, but I will be momentarily.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CHUCKLES]
John Constantine.
He always goes out on his own terms.
[GRUNTS]
John?
[EERIE MUSIC]
Couldn't wait to see me, John.
60 seconds and you're dead.
[SIGHS]
Poison does that.
It was the same poison your
mother used to kill herself.
You won't change my mind.
I'm not trying to.
I just want you know that...
even though you gave up on her,
your mum never gave up on you.
[COUGHS AND GROANS]
[SIGHS]
♪ Are you going to Scarborough Fair ♪
♪ Parsley, sage, rosemary, and thyme ♪
- ♪ Remember me ♪
- Stop.
♪ To one who lives there ♪
♪ For once ♪
BOTH: ♪ She was ♪
♪ A true love of mine ♪
That was our song.
Aye, it was.
But she sang it to me first.
You can really bring her back?
[COUGHS]
Answer me.
I can fix everything.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
[GROANING]
♪ ♪
I'm glad that hurt.
Tick tock, John.
I can kill you anytime I want.
- [GASPING]
- Oh, oh, my God!
- I can't take this anymore.
- How are you alive?
Astra, she reconsidered.
She reconsidered, she reconsidered.
She reconsidered. She reconsidered!
Oh, I can't bloody believe it.
I'm back in the game. Oh, Bully.
Bully, Bully, Bully. Bully, I love you!
Bully, Bully, Bully, Bully, Bully.
Yes, I can't believe she
bloody reconsidered!
Mwah! I feel like a new man.
Ah, yeah.
I can't believe I was gonna
leave my house to you.
- What?
- Here, give me that will.
How did you get Astra
to change her mind?
Well, by making a promise
that I intend to keep.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Hail the Waverider.
I need to see a lady about a loom.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --