Come on, Cap. Can't we
just bowl one more?
- BOTH: No!
- Sorry.
We'll have a rematch
at our next date night.
I don't know about all of y'all,
but I'm done with space.
Get these shoes on solid ground.
Agreed, but not in those shoes.
We need to talk about your footwear.
Try to put a heel on me,
and I'll show you where to stick it.
Oh, I'm with Ms. Cruz on this one.
I think it's about time
that we all return
to where we belong, don't you think?
- All right.
- Okay, message received.
You are correct.
It is time for us to swap back.
- It's not forever.
- I know. We got this.
Yeah.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Okay, Fancy Z, time to come out.
♪ ♪
Oh, B and... oh.
John, I missed your face so much.
I missed you so much.
Wait, are we in actual space?
Yep.
- Do I want to know why?
- Desperate times.
The world was at stake,
all that malarkey.
Let me explain it to you
over a nice cup of chai,
maybe a foot massage, yeah?
Talk later, Z. Boos before bros.
Unless your other bro's a...
BOTH: Time Bro.
Hey, babe? Something's wrong.
I can't set jump coordinates. Can you...
I'm afraid my jump drive was damaged
when Mr. Constantine magicked
us across the universe.
Well, I guess we're gonna
have to take the long way.
Calculating the most efficient route.
Taking into consideration
the Waverider's fuel
and energy reserves,
we should arrive safely
in 3 weeks, 2 days, and 21 hours.
Stuck on the ship for three weeks?
I'll be in my room.
When we land on Earth, wake me up.
These damn eggs are
making my head itchy.
I'll bring you
some cocoa butter for that.
And I have a great way to pass the time.
It's this super fun role-playing game.
It's called "Beast/Slayers".
A Gothic mystery adventure awaits?
Well, we have a wedding we have to plan.
Yeah, we have so much to plan.
- We just... we... we're very busy.
- We have to plan.
We have to plan a lot of things.
Okay, I'll just set it up
in case you guys change your mind.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
_
Okay!
I have everything organized by category.
Mm, wow, yep, this is thorough.
We've got group A, those
who need to come, obviously;
group B, those who we would
love to come,
but if they can't, it's okay;
and... come on... group C, the people
that we should definitely
send an invitation to
and pray that they RSVP no.
What about group D?
Yeah, well, those are the people
who it might be better
that they don't know
we're getting married
until it's too late.
Why is Barry Allen on this list?
- I love Barry.
- I know you do, babe.
But you know that if Barry
and Iris show up,
there is a 100% chance
that our special day will be
blown up by a supervillain, so group D.
Okay, D.
Hold on a second.
Gideon, why is our trip getting longer?
I've recalculated the duration based on
our current level of power consumption.
Power consumption?
[GRUNTS]
- You will not survive this.
- Oh, I'm gonna survive.
- Deadly combo coming at you.
- No, no.
- Ha!
- Wait, wait, no.
I'm not out. I'm not out. I'm not... no.
- Hey!
- Sorry, kiddos.
We gotta conserve power,
or we're never gonna get home.
- So no screen time?
- Afraid so.
I got you, Captain.
No power, no problem.
All right, who's next?
Gideon, I would like
a prime rib, medium rare,
with shoestring fries
and béarnaise and...
Ah-ah-ah! Gideon, scrap that order.
Sorry, we can't use the
food fabricator anymore.
How are we supposed to feed ourselves?
I don't know. Oh, look!
Food.
Cook it the old-fashioned way, yummy.
How's that robe fit you, love?
Actually, it's a little bit big.
All right.
[CHANTING IN GAELIC]
Oh, wow, it's perfect now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[GROANS]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
You all right, man?
Aces all around, squire,
aces all around.
I feel magnificent.
How do you feel, good?
Oh.
- Mm.
- Oh, wow, yeah.
Oh, hello, brother.
John is taking me on a spa date.
- Ah, on the ship?
- Oh, ye little of faith.
You see, I finally got
my magic back and no occasion
to use it save for doting
on that delightful deity.
Relaxation awaits.
♪ ♪
_
Deep breaths
as you fire up that back leg.
Oh, steel is not flexible.
Inhale, extend.
Exhale, goddess pose.
Oh, I missed this.
I'll take the positivity
into my energy sphere
with gratitude.
Room for an English one?
We're kinda in the middle of a...
Of course, prepare yourself
for total relaxation.
Yeah.
Atmosphere could do
with a bit of upgrade, though,
couldn't it?
[CHANTING IN GAELIC]
Wow, now, that is how you set the mood.
Oof, what, did you raise it
20 degrees in here?
I'm beginning to schvitz.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Guess we're doing hot yoga.
But in the interest
of preserving the sanctity
of this practice, I ask
that you keep your pants on.
Well, in the interest
of achieving a higher state
of consciousness, I must
bare myself to the elements.
Come on, B. You know how he is.
Sure, but I'd rather not know
all of him right now, okay?
I thought that you of all people would,
you know, go with the flow.
The flow was my flow
till you came and hijacked it.
Hijacked it? Improved it,
don't you mean?
Do you know what? This is bollocks.
Know what? I'm gonna go practice
somewhere more welcoming. Cheers.
Behrad... [SPEAKING FARSI]
Don't mom-voice me, Zari.
Guys, guys, just take a breath.
You're right. This is safe space.
John, you can stay.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, the mood's all wrong now, mate.
John.
Well, if that is the issue,
then why did you put your
fake actor parents in group A?
Whoa, whoa, I have very fond memories
of them that feel real, and I...
Well, Black Siren is
my sister Laurel from another...
I felt like a spare prick
in a dartboard, all right?
I know when I'm not wanted,
and I'm not gonna outstay my welcome.
John, don't be so dramatic.
Go back there and make amends.
- He didn't mean what he said.
- Oh, hold on.
- What is the drama?
- Tensions are very high.
People are feeling very prickly.
How is this already happening?
- It's day three.
- It is very stressful
being cooped up on a timeship.
Worse, it's bloody boring.
Yeah, and without technology
to distract us,
it's only gonna get worse
before it gets better.
We need an activity,
something to bring us together,
like a mission but not a mission,
like a game.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Welcome to the world of "Beast/Slayers".
In this Gothic adventure,
you'll enter a mansion
for a dinner party, only to be
hunted by a horrendous beast.
Oh, I see what's happening here.
It's like "Mafia".
One of us is secretly the beast,
and it's up to the rest
of us to figure it out
before it's too late... go ahead.
After each kill, you will deliberate
on who to accuse of being
the horrendous monster.
- You.
- Accuse correctly,
the beast dies and the humans win.
And if we accuse incorrectly?
Well, then the game continues,
and it's the beast's turn to strike!
[LAUGHS]
I'll be the all-knowing narrator
who will usher the game along.
Meanwhile, you will each need
to select a character and a card.
Ooh, can I go first?
Hmm, eccentric detective.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Hmm, black widow.
- Ooh.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
- Starving artist.
- Wealthy foreigner.
Reluctant soothsayer. Typecast much?
Big game hunter, I'll take it.
Prima donna, obviously.
Consumptive doctor, original.
All right, now, keep each
of these cards secret.
They either say human,
or they say beast.
Know who and what you are...
as we begin.
[MIMICS THUNDER BOOMING
AND RAIN PATTERING]
[WITH EASTERN EUROPEAN ACCENT]
It's a dark and stormy night
as a group of strangers
are summoned to the home
of a rich and powerful lord.
All right, enough of this.
[GRUNTS]
All right, so everybody wants
to go on an adventure, all right?
Well, let's go on a real
adventure, shall we?
[CHANTING IN GAELIC]
♪ ♪
Now, that's more like it.
Game on. Let's hunt this beast.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
What?
You have got to teach me
the spell, John.
Yeah, well, it takes the bored
out of board game, doesn't it?
This is so incredibly realistic,
and I cannot wait
to win this entire game.
Well, I for one did not consent
- to being magicked into a game.
- Oh, come on.
Would you really rather play
with Gary making sound effects?
[THUNDER BOOMING]
Okay, I gotta admit, John,
this is pretty impressive.
But why does it look like your house?
Well, the spell is linked
to the rules of the game,
but the rest of the gaps are
filled in by my imagination.
It's easy to make a place
I know so well.
Now, once we win
and the game ends, poof,
we'll all be back in the ship,
right as rain.
[NORMALLY] Hello?
Guys?
You all right in there?
All right, Gary.
They're counting on you to narrate.
♪ ♪
[WITH EASTERN EUROPEAN ACCENT]
Okay, everyone.
Dinner is served!
♪ ♪
Oof.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- So, Detective...
- Hmm?
How do we figure out who this beast is?
It's all about the first kill.
Once the beast strikes,
there'll be a clear line
from who's chosen to who's guilty.
I've already mapped out who it could be
based on who dies first.
Hey, John, this chicken
smells delicious.
But seriously, babe, do you think
he'd cater the wedding?
- There's no wedding talk.
- Why?
[WITH FRENCH ACCENT] And I do not know
what you are talking about, Detective,
because I am just
a heartbroken, sad widow.
You know I don't drink.
Yeah, but this isn't real, mate.
This may be your one
and only opportunity
to try a truly exquisite
Bordeaux, know what I mean?
- I'll have some.
- No, she won't.
Yes, she will. It's not real.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[NORMALLY] Don't be jealous, Gar.
You're a vital part of this adventure.
[ALARM BLARING]
Gideon, what's that?
I'm receiving a distress beacon
from an approaching vessel.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Who the hell is making that racket?
Trying to concentrate on my puzzles.
We're being hailed by someone
who's lost out in space.
Oh, my God, your hair.
Grew overnight.
Well, don't tuck it in. It's beautiful.
It's a sign you're
in your fourth quadmester.
It means the babies are healthy.
I recognize that ship.
Bishop the Psycho might be on board
or those damn lizard people.
Gideon, blast.
I'm under captain's orders
not to use any systems
not vital for our transport to Earth.
- Where are the captains?
- They're in my game.
Well, if the captains are not
here, makes me captain.
Well, I don't think
that's how that works.
The ship is maneuvering
into docking position
on our starboard side.
Damn it, we missed our shot.
Docking complete.
I urge you to reserve judgment
until we know exactly
who's behind that door.
Shut up.
Whatever comes through
that door, I'm killing.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Kayla!
Hey, dummies, you miss me?
♪ ♪
- [THUNDER BOOMING]
- ALL: Ooh!
- All right, what is happening?
- Ooh, it's time.
The beast will choose its first victim.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
- [GASPS]
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- [NORMALLY] No.
- Dead.
- [MOUTHING WORDS]
- What?
The dead have no voice. How poetic.
- Well, that was pretty tame.
- Oh, well, Behrad?
See? It's all pretend.
I'm sorry, babe, but you're out.
You gotta go. I know.
[WITH FRENCH ACCENT]
I will miss you. Adieu.
So we lost the detective.
She was the only one
who could have figured
this whole thing out,
and now, well, she's gone.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
All right, y'all,
the beast had their fun.
Now it's our turn.
All right, take it easy, Spooner.
In games like these,
it's up to the group
to deliberate on who
we think the beast is.
And then it's up to all of us
to vote on someone to accuse.
- Well, I accuse you.
- No.
I think that you were so impressed
with Ava's methodology that you wanted
to eliminate the competition
right from the start.
[GASPS, SPITS]
Or it's you, and you're quick
to accuse others
to deflect any suspicion.
Just pick me.
I'll gladly go hang
with Ava and be exempt
from decisions like these.
No, no, no. I agree with Sara.
I think it's Nate.
- Thank you.
- What?
Guys, besides Gary, who has
been very quiet, by the way,
I'm the only one who has
any idea how to play this game.
Not exactly, mate.
We'll be fine without you.
- Don't you worry.
- So do we vote on Nate?
- All in favor.
- Mm-hmm.
I abstain.
[NORMALLY] Doesn't matter.
Don't need him.
[WITH FRENCH ACCENT]
You have been accused.
[THUNDER BOOMING, WOLF HOWLS]
[BLADE SHINGS]
- Ahh!
- [GASPS]
[THUNDER BOOMING]
- He's dead.
- Oh, no, no.
Trust me, he is fine, all right?
- Nate is fine.
- Dude, he literally
just got stabbed in the back.
He's not fine.
- Ooh.
- Oh! Oh, that is awful.
Is that supposed to happen?
That's really graphic.
- It's fine.
- [NORMALLY] John, what has changed?
Why is Nate's death
so different from Ava's?
Well, why are you asking me, right?
If you got a problem with the game,
you go talk to that git Gary.
He's the one who picked it.
I just made it into a proper experience.
[COUGHS]
John.
[GASPS] Are you okay?
Yeah.
No, he's becoming his character,
consumptive doctor.
What if the longer the game goes on,
the more realistic it becomes?
And is anyone else starting to
feel more like their character?
I feel like shooting
something, but that's normal.
Yeah, I wouldn't be able to tell either.
Prima donna. [GASPS]
I do feel extra dramatic
and quite squeamish.
What about you, are you
hungry, starving artist?
Turns out seeing my
best friend's dead body
is an appetite killer,
so... I'm gonna be sick.
All right, well, I am definitely feeling
the loss of my beloved Ava.
If we all are becoming
more like our characters
and Ava was the first one
to die, then...
[BEHRAD SCREAMS]
Ava!
No, no, no.
Ava, Ava.
Ava, oh, no, no, no, this is wrong.
This is... damn it, John.
This has gone too far.
I'm putting an end to this.
- Look, I'm the...
- [THUNDER BOOMING]
[FLESH SQUELCHES]
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SHRIEKS]
Was Sara about to confess?
Nah, she was gonna take out her card.
That's it. Everyone show your card.
- Blank.
- Blank!
Blank.
♪ ♪
[GROWLING]
Is hers blank as well?
No, it's worse.
- ♪ ♪
- _
Don't think that putting a Band-Aid
on my wound makes us even.
I'm just trying to help.
Oh, now you care about my well-being.
- I'll be fine.
- You don't look fine.
I mean, you always look fine.
We have a machine that can fix that.
I'm just here for my ship.
Well, your ship's not here.
Then where is it?
I reverse tracked my pod detector,
and it led me here.
That tech should have been on my ship.
But I guess you guys are
thieves as well as deserters.
So what did you do
with the rest of my ship, huh?
It's on Earth, and funny enough,
we're traveling there now.
We can give you a lift.
But in the meantime,
let us patch that up, hmm?
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
What happened to her tentacle?
[GROWLS]
Zaguron stung her.
She had to amputate to prevent
the poison from spreading.
[SNARLING]
- Poor Lefty.
- Lefty?
- The tentacle has a name?
- Sure, it does.
Our tentacles are regenerative,
so they're part of us,
but they're also their own creatures,
kind of like starfish arms
or earthworms.
[GROWLS]
She wants to know what you're doing.
Starting up the meat printer.
She'll have a new Lefty in no time.
♪ ♪
[GROWLS]
Oh, that's the time to destination.
Because we printed you a new tentacle.
- [GROWLS]
- The jump drive is broken!
Why do you think we're traveling
the old-fashioned way?
[GROWLS]
♪ ♪
All fixed. Time to go back to your ship.
Or you could show me
where your mainframe is,
and I'll fix your jump drive.
And then we can all get what we want
a hell of a lot quicker, deal?
Deal.
How did you get off the planet?
I thought you were dead.
- If I...
- If what?
You thought I was alive?
You didn't stick around
long enough to find out.
In fact, you bolted the second
you got onto my ship.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wow, an apology.
That sounded like that took some effort.
You know what else took some effort?
Battling my way through
a Zaguron-infested planet.
You know Zagurons are carrion creatures?
They will swarm a dying planet
and pick it to pieces like that.
They were relentless,
but I was stronger.
With some time,
I finally got Bishop's habitat
airborne again.
Never imagined I'd run into you bozos.
Soon as I get my ship back,
I'll be a dozen galaxies away
from here and forget
that any of you ever existed.
Kayla, there's something I have to...
Hey, hey, Mick.
Can I please get your hand
over here with something?
♪ ♪
What?
Don't tell Kayla you're pregnant.
If she finds out, she may
perform the Necrian love grip.
What?
Males in my species are subservient.
Mm, of course they are.
If she finds that you're an unfit parent
or she doesn't like you,
she could knock you out
and eat your eggy brains.
Please keep an eye on her,
and remember,
do not trust her.
♪ ♪
[THUNDER BOOMING]
All right, hunt's on.
- One of you did this.
- What are you gonna do,
shoot us all till one
of us is the beast?
How do you even know
if one of us is the beast?
- What if it was Sara?
- Then what killed her?
And if Sara was the beast,
this game should be over.
What step are we even on anymore?
[COUGHS] That's a Gary question, love.
The rules are all bloody rubbish to me.
Maybe you should have learned them
before trapping us in this nightmare.
You think I'm enjoying this, squire?
You know, if the beast doesn't
off me, the bloody TB will.
But you know what?
I'm the one that's gonna
get us all out of here, all right?
So sit back.
Yes.
Deadly nightshade, in you go.
Pulverized whalebone. [GRUNTS]
And just a little boost
to make it all sing.
♪ ♪
Bottoms up.
[GRUNTS]
[CHANTING IN GAELIC]
Whoa!
- [GROANING]
- [GASPS]
- John, are you okay?
- Yeah.
[COUGHS]
I'm fine. [GROANS]
[SIGHS]
I guess the game won't allow us
to take a shortcut, so...
we just have to play and win.
And if we lose?
What do you mean if we lose?
Well, there are two outcomes
to this game.
In one, the humans win
by killing the beast.
In the other, the beast
kills all the humans
and the game keeps going.
Characters get re-dealt,
and the game goes on and on and on.
You mean we could be
trapped in here forever.
Time to play offense.
If we're all becoming our characters,
then maybe I can use
my powers as a soothsayer
to figure out who the beast is.
Everyone, circle up.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
With my power as the oracle,
I demand to know.
Beast, where are you?
Speak through me.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I am here. I am one of you.
I will win.
Your blood will smear the walls.
Your screams will fill the air.
Forever here, forever mine, forever.
[GASPS]
Oh, to hell with this.
♪ ♪
I'm finding another way
out of this dumpster fire.
And if any of y'all come after me,
I'll blow your head off.
- Except you. I trust you.
- Likewise.
Let's go.
Wait! Where you going?
Splitting up is a cardinal sin
to survival and creativity!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let's try this door.
Okay, so we're passing
the conservatory now.
- Into the dining room.
- This is exhausting.
All these doors circle back
into the house.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CLEARS THROAT FORCEFULLY]
♪ ♪
[SIGHS] What?
- I'm worried about Astra and Spooner.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna bring them back here.
- Okay.
- Keep an eye on John.
- Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
I mean keep an eye on him
in a defensive way. Here.
- You can't be serious.
- I'm a starving artist.
- I'm nothing but serious.
- He can barely walk.
I'm more of a danger to him
than he is to me right now.
Just take it.
♪ ♪
[COUGHING]
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm sorry I got you into this, love.
Hey, you didn't know
this was gonna happen.
I'm gonna get you some water, okay?
Okay.
[COUGHING]
♪ ♪
[THUNDER BOOMING]
Okay.
[GROWLS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Behrad, is that you?
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
A kitchen, that's new.
Yes, we can try the back door.
Come on, come on!
- You gotta be kidding me.
- No, no, no, no, no!
This cannot be happening!
Aw, screw this.
[SHOUTS]
♪ ♪
- [BLADE SHINGS]
- [BOTH SCREAM]
♪ ♪
What happened?
Don't go in there... Spooner and Astra.
No.
Oh!
♪ ♪
Where's John?
Spooner and Astra are dead.
I know it was you.
Oh, nice tactic, sunshine.
But I lost track of you
just before the attack.
So did Zari, didn't you, love?
I actually saw Behrad find them.
Oh, you saw him find them,
or you saw him
after he found them,
maybe after he killed them?
All of this is your fault!
Oh, there you go again,
blaming the bloody magic.
I'm not blaming the bloody magic, John.
I'm blaming you for abusing it.
You just had to go and show off
your fancy new Fountain powers.
Jealous, are we?
Well, add that
to your petulant brattiness.
♪ Ahh ♪
Stop acting like children.
I think he's the beast.
I've been coughing my bloody lungs up
for the last two hours.
How can you still think that I'm the one
that killed our friends?
I'm not saying how you did it.
- I'm saying I know you did it.
- Okay, so let's vote.
- I vote that it's you.
- And I vote it's you.
Don't make me choose between you.
All right, do you know what?
I will do you both a favor.
I'm gonna go and lock myself
in the attic because,
clearly, I am some unhinged,
egotistical bloody maniac!
John, just... [GROANS]
Thanks.
♪ ♪
Gideon, what's with
all the energy usage?
The device that Mr. Rory
refers to as the meat printer
is drawing a considerable
amount of power.
♪ ♪
Lefty, no.
What are you printing?
Lefty. Calm down, Lefty.
Don't... oh!
Gideon, is the ship ready to jump?
The jump drive is
fully operational, Mr. Rory.
But there is trouble.
Mr. Green is under attack
in the med bay.
Attack? By who?
♪ ♪
Gotcha.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Because you left me. And he got me out.
I owe him.
Him?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'm pregnant!
Not the love grip!
♪ ♪
I don't want to die in here.
Maman and Baba will never know
the truth about me, about us.
If we get out of here,
I'm coming clean with them.
Oh, please.
Like you'd ever risk
damaging Maman's view of her...
[SPEAKING FARSI]
Oh, maybe I should tell her
how your magician boyfriend
got you to drink wine.
You would not.
You're right, I wouldn't.
But how can you not see
what John's doing here?
He told us himself,
he filled in the gaps
of this illusion with
his own imagination.
I mean, this is some
new level of a bad trip.
What is your problem with him?
My problem is that he's being a jerk
and you're not seeing it.
Ever since he came back
from the Fountain,
he's been acting like
an asshat jock on steroids.
Oh, working out your issues
from high school much?
If by that, you mean worrying
about your choice in men,
then yeah, I am.
We need to call him out. He's the beast.
If we vote to accuse him,
we can end this.
- I can't.
- Why not?
I love him.
[SOFT MUSIC]
I've never heard you say
that about anybody before.
♪ ♪
Well, I've never... felt it.
I can be myself with him,
you know, no games, no pretense.
He makes me happy.
♪ ♪
Have you told him how you feel?
No, no, that feels... very scary
to be vulnerable
to another person like that.
I mean, can it even last, you know?
You know how John is.
Yeah, but... you gotta take that leap.
- Okay, now you like him again?
- I never disliked him.
I love the guy, but something
is definitely off about him.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
[COUGHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You can end the game. You know how.
You just can't do it. You won't do it.
I've tried ending it.
By shooting back some
magic potion number nine?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
With every sip, you make
this prison and me stronger.
You're not in control
of the magic, John.
It's in control of you.
Yeah, just do me a favor,
right, and you kill me
or piss off because
I am done playing games.
No, you're not.
You love this world.
You love the power.
You love me.
Like hell I do.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHS]
Oh, don't look so surprised, John.
I've always been here.
You just never looked me
in the eye before.
You never wanted
to confront the part of you
that sabotaged all your relationships,
doomed your lovers.
The game made that possible.
It made me possible,
gave me a playground to sow destruction
before your very eyes.
[GROWLS]
Here I am,
fueled by your new addiction
and loving every moment of it.
It's all tricks and lies.
I'll kill you, you bastard.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
[YELLS]
John.
♪ ♪
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Look at me, John.
Or more like, look at yourself.
[ROARS]
This is who you really are.
♪ ♪
[SCREAMS]
[ALL GROANING AND GASPING]
[GASPS] Sara's the beast.
No, there was an actual beast
who was none of us somehow.
Bloody Gary, innit, you can't give him
a lick of responsibility
without him buggering it all up.
Okay, well, let's play again.
- ALL: No!
- Why?
Do you really want to die again?
I'm not gonna die this time because
this time, I'm gonna win. Let's play.
Wait, you guys.
- Are we home?
- Oh, good,
because I am bloody knackered.
How long were we in that game?
[SOFT MUSIC]
What is that?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ew.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Look.
- Look, I got it.
- Yes, great.
So someone shut down the entire ship.
Yeah, and we have to do
a complete reboot
in order to get Gideon back online
so we can figure out
what the hell happened.
- Where are Mick and Gary?
- I don't know.
- John, have you seen them?
- No, no, I haven't.
No, that spell's left me with
the mother of all hangovers.
- I'll see you guys later.
- Yeah.
Hey, you want some company?
Oh, I'm just gonna chill
back at the house.
I'll be all right.
Well, then I will come over later,
and I will bring you your favorite tea.
Oh, what's a busted-up
old codger like me done
to deserve a woman like you?
I don't know, must be magic.
Yeah.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Are you gonna tell him?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Look, Z, I'm sorry
for everything I said before,
for pinning everything on John.
I went into overprotective brother mode.
Hey, I protect you, not the
other way around, okay?
You don't worry about me.
Besides, have you ever
met someone I can't handle?
Mom?
Hmm, I'd argue she can't
handle me, but...
Speaking of Mom,
I'm gonna head back to 2044
- and visit her and Baba.
- Oh.
I think it's about time I let them know
what really happened
to this old family heirloom.
You're gonna tell them the truth?
On second thought,
maybe I'll just take it easy
and enjoy Maman's cooking.
Yeah, that's a way better idea.
Mm!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GROWLS]
Come on.
Get rid of it. Get rid of him.
♪ ♪
Ah, Gary, what are you doing?
[GROWLS]
Where are your glasses, bud?
♪ ♪
- It's Mick.
- Ay, dios mío.
♪ ♪
- He's alive.
- And he has hair.
John, there's something
I want to tell you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLS]
Whoa, hey, there you are.
Mick needs help. Come on.
♪ ♪
♪ I think I could have loved her ♪
♪ In this world or another ♪
♪ But now I'm stuck
looking up from below ♪
♪ Space girl floating away ♪
♪ Space girl, gravity betrayed her ♪
♪ Space girl, a punk rock treasure ♪
♪ Space girl, goodbye forever ♪
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -