Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
That's my mom.
There's no loophole where
I can save my family
and not screw up history.
I'm so sorry, Z.
[GUN COCKS]
What the hell is going on here?
This is my dad, Hank.
Hello, John.
The knuckle bones of a martyred saint...
they act as a divining rod,
able to detect the presence
of beings not belonging to our world.
[WHOOSHING]
[SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
Where'd the unicorn go?
I sent that bastard
straight to hell, didn't I?
You need to be a part of a team.
No, I would rather bloody top myself
than move in with you lot.
People around me get
killed or far worse.
Oh, bollocks.
_
How's our magical upgrade going, Ray?
Almost done, I think.
Though the they never covered
how to interface time seismographs
and enchanted bones in
the Ivy U PhD program.
Well, that should do it.
My peers would say that
science and magic don't mix,
but to them, I'd ask, "Have you
seen 'The Fifth Element'?"
[CHUCKLES] Right?
Ivy U sounds like a real party school.
Oh, I hope this works.
We need a way to pinpoint
magical threats on the timeline.
I mean, who knows what kind
of creatures are out there
wreaking havoc on history?
Like, uh, vampires.
Gremlins.
Aswangs.
Cannibalistic Filipino were-beasts
with proboscis-like tongues.
I've been doing some
research just in case.
I thought that's why we had Constantine.
Yeah, about that.
Constantine is...
Tired, hungover, and in
need of a stiff one.
[TRUNK THUDS]
Dealer's choice as to what
that's a euphemism for.
He's here.
Yeah, you know, I meant what I
said about joining you lot,
but then I pictured that same
lot squaring off against
some of the manky buggers
that I've come up against,
and I thought, "Yeah, you know what?
You're right. You're all
bloody doomed without me."
One aswang will take you down
without breaking a sweat.
Ha ha! New legend alert.
I better go update the chore wheel.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hang on, sunshine.
I'm not a bloody legend.
I'm merely offering my
services as a consultant,
and as such, I have some stipulations.
I don't do silly costumes,
I expect full benefits,
and I require no less than
two weeks paid vacation.
- Vacation?
- Paid?
Easy!
[DEVICE BEEPING]
Hey, it worked.
Will you look at that?
We already got a...
Do we have a special name for
these magical fugitives?
Well, I was thinking,
since they're mysteries
involving mythical beings,
we could go with myth-teries.
Fugitives it is.
What's it say?
Salem, Massachusetts, 1692.
First day on the job,
and you're taking me to
the bloody witch trials.
Well, I hope you're
feeling morally superior
because we are getting
our Puritan purit-on.
That was too much, right?
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
_
I'm telling you, your machine
is clearly buggered.
There's nothing magical
about Puritan New England.
I know. I was there, but it
could all be different now.
Oh, come on. If a creature landed there,
why would it idle in the absolute
worst possible place for magic?
The people of Salem are
paranoid and petty,
and, besides, every
magical creature knows
that if you want to get
weird, you go to New York.
Then we need to find it before it flees.
All right, well, I agreed
to help you save history,
not take part in your little
role-playing adventures.
Call me if you find anything.
If he's staying, I'm staying.
Besides, no fun in Puritan times.
The Church banned burning
people at the stake.
Well, they didn't actually burn people.
That was the Middle Ages.
The Puritans used the gallows,
but, yeah, sure, stay.
You know, I actually miss
having someone Nate-splain
history to us.
Me too.
Speaking of which,
I wonder how Operation
Dinner with Dad is going.
- [LIGHT MUSIC]
- _
Thanks. [SIGHS]
Good steak.
So, um, what are you doing
for work these days?
Little bit of this. Little bit of that.
You?
Same old, same old.
Sir, your credit card was declined.
I, uh...
I must have given you the...
[CLEARS THROAT] wrong one.
There you go.
And this one expired in 1953.
Then I don't know why I still carry it.
Uh...
[COINS JINGLING]
Do you accept Athenian tetradrachm?
Notgeld?
Nathaniel, I've got this.
♪ ♪
Guess the deductive historical
reconstruction business...
little slow this time of year.
Yeah, and I see it's still paying off
to be a Beltway Bandit.
Really, Nathaniel, that's
how you want to end this?
- After we connect over a nice dinner.
- Have we?
All you've talked about is the steak.
What the hell else am I
supposed to talk about
if you'd rather just sit
there and silently judge me?
Oh, like you're not
doing the same thing.
Of course I was, Nathaniel.
I put you through grad school to what?
To... to collect rare currency?
Maybe I should follow
your example, right?
Make a fortune wasting taxpayers' cash
on some secret government projects
that you can't even explain?
It puts food on your plate.
How's that for an explanation?
I don't need your money.
Matter of fact...
I don't need any of this.
Of course. Running away again, huh?
I'll see you in another
two years. [STAMMERS]
♪ ♪
I forgot my leftovers.
Nathaniel.
ALL: ♪ Ah, poor bird ♪
♪ Take thy flight ♪
♪ High above the sorrows
of this sad night ♪
Good morrow. Good morrow.
Not the friendliest bunch.
Look, tone it down, Ray.
This isn't a fun time period.
These hats say otherwise.
Just try not to stand out.
Salem wasn't exactly
welcoming of outsiders.
Oh, just like every
other time in history.
They're just worse at hiding it.
ALL: [CHANTING] Witch!
Witch! Witch! Witch!
Witch! Witch! Witch! Witch!
Witch!
Wife of Satan, confess your sins.
Tell now what saw thee for
grounds of accusation?
I saw her, Reverend Parsons,
dancing in the woods
bare as the day she was born.
Jane Hawthorne, what say
you to this accusation?
I have done no harm. I swear it.
But this man says he bore
witness to your witchcraft.
She has lain with the Devil.
I would never,
not with the Devil nor with
any man since my husband's passing,
much to your frustration, good sir.
Goody Hawthorne, you are
hereby under arrest
and accused of witchcraft.
Your trial will commence on the morrow,
and if thou be convicted,
we will purge your kind
from our community.
You cannot do this!
My daughter needs me!
Prudence!
- [MUFFLED SHOUTING]
- Mother.
Have mercy, please.
ALL: [CHANTING] Witch!
Witch! Witch! Witch!
Witch! Witch! Witch! Witch! Witch!
Well, there are definitely
monsters in Salem,
just not the magical kind.
ALL: [CHANTING] Witch! Witch! Witch!
[CROWS CAWING]
Crows, that's ominous.
Despite the gothic association,
the American crow is actually a very...
- [CROW CAWING]
- [SCREAMS]
Never mind.
[CROWS CAWING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
The witch... she commands them!
Remove her from here at once! Go! Go!
[CROWS CAWING]
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
Couldn't have been her, could it?
Whatever it is, looks
like we were right.
There is magic in Salem.
All right, let's give this
thing a whirl, shall we?
Gideon, do us a favor and
mix us up some ingredients
so I can restock the old
apothecary, will you?
Out of my way. I need some mustard.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be just a minute, mate.
Now, be a doll, Gideon, and mix together
a pinch of possum's tail with
three ounces of frogs' testes.
Open the door!
I need to take a leak!
Ah! What's that smell?
Spellbook, bound in human skin.
It gets a bit rank if you
don't soak it in water.
[WHISTLE BLOWS, SHOUTING ON TV]
Get out of my chair, you weasel.
I'm watching the football.
The game's on already, mate.
You want a Marmite crumpet?
What'd you call me?
You know, you need to simmer
down a little bit, sweetheart.
You see, I don't like to share my space
any more than you, but, uh, here we are.
And why are you here?
Hey, sorry to break up
the bonding session,
but we found our fugitive, and
we think it's a real witch.
Well, a real witch must
be off her trolley
to hang around here.
Well, we just saw a woman
command a murder of crows,
and now I know why they call it that.
Well, Jane was bound,
gagged, and taken away.
Those birds were just
protecting her from that mob.
I say more power to them.
And I agree with you, in theory,
but we still have to remove that power.
Gideon, what do you
have on Jane Hawthorne?
On October 29, 1692, Jane
Hawthorne's execution
was at the center of
what came to be known
as The Burning of Salem.
"On the day she hung,
"all of the people of Salem
spontaneously combusted.
The whole town was set ablaze."
Sounds like my kind of woman.
Well, the incident was enough
to convince the public
that witches were real.
Whatever it is, Jane's
at the center of it.
Well, now, hang on a minute.
You said that she was gagged.
- Yeah.
- Did any of you actually
hear her cast a spell?
[INHALES SHARPLY] You see,
spells are a verbal game, mateys.
Was there anyone else there,
someone who would want to protect Jane?
- Prudence.
- Her daughter.
Ah, a malevolent demon has
attached itself to the child,
and the mother is being blamed.
I've seen it a million times over.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
Let's get to it, shall we?
Well, look who started to care.
Uh, but I am not wearing a costume.
I'll see you later, big man.
_
[DOOR CLOSES]
Gary?
Is that you?
Did you sleepwalk to work again?
- Whoa, whoa!
- Oh, my God!
What is wrong with you?
Nate? What the hell are you doing here?
And why aren't you wearing pants?
I can explain.
And thank you for not
mentioning the shower cap.
Pretend I did.
Coconut oil makes my hair more buoyant.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
I should try that.
And, uh, the pants situation?
Well, I decided to
extend my trip to 2018,
and I may possibly be living
a little bit at the Bureau.
You couldn't spring for a hotel?
Well, here's a fun fact about
staying in the present...
it costs money, and as a legend,
your salary is the friendships
you make along the way.
- Got ya.
- Yeah.
And you? I know you
love paperwork, but...
Oh, yes, I'm presenting my budget
to the Department of Defense tomorrow.
Rip was always good at
schmoozing the bigwigs.
It was never really my thing.
And now, with this whole
magic initiative,
we're gonna need even more money.
I can help. I'm great at schmoozing.
Hmm? Oh, uh, no... no, thank you.
What? Why not?
I need a place to stay.
You need a wingman.
It'll be fun, and we can hang out.
We'll get into adventures.
Okay, okay, you know what? Let's do it.
Just put some pants on.
Hey...
you just got schmoozed.
There she is.
She doesn't have anyone.
♪ Soul, soul, soul cake ♪
♪ Please, good missus, a soul cake ♪
♪ Soul, soul... ♪
- [DEVICE BEEPS]
- All right, let's move.
♪ Please, good missus, a soul cake ♪
♪ An apple, a plum, a
peach, or a cherry ♪
[CROW CAWS]
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ Any good thing to make us all merry ♪
♪ ♪
♪ One for Peter, one for Paul ♪
♪ Three for Him who made us all ♪
Why dost thou follow me?
Hi, Prudence. We're just here to help.
You're strangers. I have
no need of your aid.
Now be gone with haste.
John.
[RECITING INCANTATIONS]
What magic is this?
Look, it's gonna be okay.
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
Agent of the damned,
show yourself, you fetid creature.
Show yourself, you cursed beast.
Reveal your hideous form!
♪ ♪
Hello.
What in the Disney hell is this?
[MUSICAL FLOURISH]
You got to be kidding me.
That's your monster?
Monster?
Why, I am nothing of the sort.
I am a fairy godmother,
and I mean only to
make dreams come true,
because a dream is a wish your heart...
Don't say another word.
Constantine, please tell me
you have something for this.
Um, this is, uh, new.
Prudence, this is your fairy godmother?
It is. She protects me.
By hurting other people.
Not at all.
I only want to help little Prudence,
for, you see...
There are times the world is scary...
- times the world is bad...
- [ENCHANTING MUSIC]
But when your godmother's a fairy...
♪ There's no reason to be sad ♪
Is that music?
♪ So fear not if things
don't look to be ♪
♪ The way that you preferred ♪
♪ Just make a wish and look to me ♪
♪ I'll sing these magic words ♪
- Shut up!
- [MUSIC STOPS]
I didn't want her to stop singing.
Oh, to hell with this.
[RECITING INCANTATION]
Oh, my, you don't want to do that.
And why wouldn't we?
Because Prudence and I share a bond.
If you send me to hell, she
goes right down with me.
These people want to send us to hell.
You don't want to go to
hell, do you, deary?
No.
Would you like me to make them go away?
As you wish.
[MAGICAL MUSIC]
♪ We'll start with some tree roots ♪
♪ Up from the ground ♪
Prudence, you don't need her.
♪ And then summon some birds ♪
♪ What a beautiful sound ♪
[CROWS CAWING]
Okay, you can stop singing now.
♪ And just as they
gather over your head ♪
[CAWING CONTINUES]
Prudence, you don't have to do this.
♪ I'll tell them, "Attack!" ♪
♪ And you'll all end up... ♪
We're here to save your mother.
♪ Dead ♪
Godmother, wait.
Release them.
As you wish.
But I'm at your call when you need me.
You got to admit, though,
that... that was a catchy tune.
Where am I?
Someplace safe, just until
we can get you home.
I've seen many wonders these past days.
And I believe you, like Godmother,
were sent by the Lord...
the answer to our prayers.
Here...
it's a doughnut.
[DEVICE SQUEALS]
I la-la-love you.
Many wonders indeed.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] All right, guys.
Remember the three Cs of pitching...
confidence, charisma...
Oh, crap. That's my dad.
Wait a second. That's your dad?
Yeah.
This must be one of his
secret government projects
he could never tell me about.
I can't go in there, Ava.
I will make this worse.
Come on, Nate, you're family.
- How bad could it be?
- Oh, last time I saw him,
I insulted his life's work
and literally said, "I
don't need your money."
Oh, okay, that's bad.
Mm-hmm.
Look, I cannot do this alone.
- You don't have to.
- Thank you.
Gary, you know my part
of the pitch, right?
Okay, okay, maybe I can do this alone.
No, look at this guy.
He's got confidence.
He's got charisma.
- He's got...
- Crap.
I got my arm stuck in the poster tube.
- [GRUNTS]
- Listen, Ava, I know my dad, okay?
You're not gonna want to go
in there without backup.
Fine, Gary, you're in.
All right, Director Sharpe.
Let's give 'em the old ham and eggs.
[SIGHS]
Damn it.
The godmother was telling the truth.
We can't send her to hell
without sending Prudence down with her.
Bloody fairy godmothers...
they're like parasites who
feed off their hosts.
Their magic... it only works
at the whim of their charge.
The girl will have to
reject the godmother.
Who's going to give up
that kind of power,
especially in her situation?
We just have to give her what she wants.
If we save her mom, she
won't need the godmother.
Z, we can't.
I checked the historical record.
Jane Hawthorne was executed as a witch.
That was canon before
the fairy godmother
affected the timeline.
We can't change that.
So we're just gonna let them do it?
Sara, this is exactly what
it's like where I'm from...
the tribalism, scapegoating,
persecuting someone just
because they're different,
while other people just
stand by and do nothing.
I don't want it to go
down like this either, Z.
I'm sorry, but we don't have a choice.
Look, I promised her
that I would help her.
Well, you made a promise
that we can't keep.
The priority here is separating
Prudence from her godmother.
That's how we're gonna save more lives.
So, in the meantime,
we just let her think
we're saving her mom?
[SIGHS]
Great.
[MEN SCREAM]
[LOUD THUDS]
[DOOR OPENS]
I'm here to save you, Jane.
- Who art thee?
- We need to go now.
No.
Look, I get that you're scared,
but I can protect you.
You need to trust me.
Come, please.
I believe you mean well...
but I cannot go.
These people are insane.
They're gonna kill you no matter what.
They are afraid,
and fear brings out the
worst in all of us.
Therefore, I must forgive them...
for they know not what they do.
Well, at least one of you Puritans
gets the point of that book.
If I disappear now,
others will pay for my cowardice,
and I will not allow
innocents to suffer.
What about your daughter's
suffering, her powers?
Think about how your actions
are going to affect her.
She is the only one of whom I think.
I made her swear to me
that she would never use
her power henceforth.
As long as she heeds my command,
my Prudence will live.
But what kind of life is it gonna be...
where you died and she
couldn't protect you?
That guilt is gonna follow
her her whole life.
She'll end up mad at herself
and mad at the world.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Please, we have to go.
My daughter is strong.
In time, with God's love,
she will let go of these burdens.
Jane, don't do this, please.
It came from the jail.
It must be the witch.
Thou must go with haste.
♪ ♪
You shall not flee your
punishment, witch.
Your trial awaits.
[INTENSE MUSIC]
It's useless, piece of...
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
I know you're there, you old bat.
Why don't you show yourself, eh?
We'll have ourselves a little chat.
A simple please and
thank-you would do, my pet.
Although it has been quite amusing
watching you prattle on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
all right, Granny.
You've had your fun,
and now it's time to let
go of dear Prudence
and be on your merry way.
All I want is to make the
world a happier place.
You got her mother thrown
in the bloody clink.
And what about that
bloke who had his eyes
pecked out of his skull, eh?
That man was a liar.
They are all liars,
and simple-minded pests like
that must be taught a lesson.
Oh, "pests."
Intriguing choice of words.
Before Prudence, all the girls I helped
were just take, take, take.
"I want a new dress, Godmother."
"I want to go to the ball, Godmother."
So I gave, and I gave,
no matter how absurd the request.
I mean, who would ever choose
to wear glass slippers?
Imagine the blisters!
And what did I get in return?
A thousand years locked away
in a dank and miserable dimension.
So it was humans who put you away, eh?
Well, it serves you right,
you bitter old nag.
You don't want Prudence happy.
You want her raging.
That's how you settle the score,
by using a child's anger
to rain down hellfire
on those poor bastards out there.
Hellfire, you say?
Not a bad idea.
Ta-ta, my pet.
My Prudence will be needing me soon.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[GROANS]
And what situations
require our continued
funding, Director Sharpe?
Sir, do you remember
when dinosaurs took over
downtown Los Angeles?
Or when a telepathic gorilla
tried to kill Barack Obama?
You know that I don't.
And that's because we did our job.
The timeline was in complete shambles,
but I'm proud to say that
we finally put things back
into its proper place.
So your job is done.
What are all these
people still doing here?
See, the timeline is very fragile.
There's always a threat
of one kind or another.
Now there's magic.
- Magic?
- Yes.
You see, last year,
there was a time demon
named "Mollus."
Mallus, but it... it...
We're not gonna...
And in order to kill him,
the legends broke his prison,
which, surprise, surprise,
released an unknown number
of other dangerous magical beings,
all of whom got spat out
across the timeline
and now must be hunted
down and sent to hell.
- Did I miss anything?
- No, actually.
You know, I've had to oversee
some really far-out
projects in my career,
but I can't in good
conscience have the D.O.D.
pay for a department
that fights fairy tales.
Sir, uh, with all due respect,
you cannot shut us down, please.
The damage that these
supernatural fugitives
can cause is unfathomable.
Director Sharpe, you seem
like a very capable leader.
Now, you say there's magic out there.
And I say that I need proof.
- Well...
- Here's proof.
A unicorn ate my nipple.
[GASPS]
Right.
- Um...
- I'm shutting this place down.
Gary, put it away!
Have you guys seen Z?
With the witch?
Prudence isn't a witch.
Not that witches are bad.
Prudence is alone. I
just checked. Gideon.
Miss Tomaz gave me explicit instructions
not to tell you that she
was leaving the ship.
- That can't be good.
- [SIGHS]
Stay with the kid. Don't piss her off.
Where the hell are you, Z?
And, lo, she called upon her
master to set her free.
And were it not for these brave men,
she might have succeeded.
And now...
before your very eyes...
The mark of the Devil upon her flesh.
- [ALL GASPING]
- It's a birthmark, jerk.
Watch now as I attempt to draw blood
from Satan's brand.
It will not bleed.
[SCREAMING]
Oh!
[ALL SCREAM]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Back.
The word of God shall be my shield.
♪ ♪
[ALL GASP]
- The Lord has mercy!
- It's a sign.
ALL: Oh!
The witch... stop her
before she destroys us all.
Stop it. She didn't do anything.
♪ ♪
Why can't you idiots
see what he's doing?
He's convincing you to
kill your neighbors
for imaginary crimes.
If you're looking for the real
source of evil in this town,
it's him.
Witch.
Witch, another witch.
Remove that cursed bauble from her.
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
What the hell am I doing?
Take her now.
I'm sorry.
No.
The Devil's hold over these witches
is stronger than we have ever faced.
Hanging them will not suffice.
They must burn.
[ALL CHEERING]
Burn, burn, burn...
♪ ♪
You feel that, don't you, deary?
Something is amiss.
I worry for my mother.
I thought she'd be rescued by now.
It does seem odd.
You were promised by
those strange visitors
that she would be saved, were you not?
Curious, then, that they
have not delivered.
Shall we see what the delay is?
Can you do that?
I can do anything, sweetkins.
All you must do is ask.
According to the historical record,
Jane Hawthorne was executed as a witch.
That was canon before
the fairy godmother
affected the timeline.
We can't change that.
Looks like your new friends lied to you.
They have no intention
of saving your poor, helpless mummy.
Now, what would you have
me do about that, my pet?
[SIZZLING]
Ho! Prudence, hold on.
Out of my way, you swine.
[PIGS SQUEALING]
Ta-ta.
♪ ♪
Bloody hell. [RECITING INCANTATIONS]
Shut up.
Stay back.
♪ ♪
Come, deary.
Let's show these nasty villagers
what real magic looks like.
[PIGS SQUEALING]
Hey, how'd it go out there?
Well, you better start
packing your things,
because he just gave the entire
Bureau an eviction notice.
Did you tell him about
the magical creatures?
Oh, yeah. He's not buying it.
He needs proof.
Oh, that is such a Hank thing.
Well, maybe he'll believe you.
Why don't you just tell him the truth?
Nate, it can't go worse than
what just happened back there.
Look, I spent my whole life
trying to convince Hank
that I made something of myself,
and most of the time, I
was faking it, okay?
So he's supposed to suddenly
believe I'm a superhero
who fought a unicorn... come on.
Look, I know it's hard doing good
when it seems like no one notices,
but I have seen the good
that you can do, okay?
And that's why I believe
that you can help us here,
not because you're Hank's son,
but because you... look at me...
you are a hero, okay?
Now, Gary's seeing him out.
We still have time.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- You schmoozed me.
- Did it work?
You sure I can't interest you
in a coffee, tea, fizzy water?
Just the validation.
I think you're doing a great job.
Validation.
Okay.
Hello. Is anybody here?
Gideon, I don't have time for this.
I need proof that magic
exists, and I need it n...
[PIG SQUEALS]
Hello, piggy. What are you doing here?
I'm afraid that's no
ordinary pig, Mr. Heywood.
- Shut the front door.
- [PIG SQUEALS]
- Ray, that's you?
- [GRUNTING]
- Slow down.
- You got turned into a pig.
- [SQUEALS]
But you think you'll be better soon
because the team's working
on it as we speak.
Mick got turned, too? Well, where is he?
Listen, I know you're in
a situation right now,
but I could really use
your help at the Bureau.
Yes, of course I'll carry you.
Come on.
[ALL SHOUTING]
In the name of our Heavenly Father,
let these witches burn.
[ALL CHEER]
Cleanse this town and
its people of this evil
and send these wretched souls
to their master in hell.
You don't have to listen to him.
You know this is wrong.
This woman is your
neighbor, your friend.
She doesn't deserve this.
No one does.
This witch is more dangerous
than any we have faced.
She wore this cursed stone.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let the women go.
Light the pyre.
Let God's work be done.
Do it, and he's dead.
My soul will live with
God for all of time.
Screw it.
♪ ♪
No!
[ALL CHEERING]
Stop!
Free them from the pyre.
Mother.
What's wrong with her? What did they do?
She's gonna be okay.
Now, my pet, what shall we do
about that horrid man
who hurt your mummy?
I want him to burn.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hank.
Are you sure this is going to work?
- No.
- Nathaniel?
What are you doing here?
I work here.
That's right, Dad. I'm a time traveler.
How... how do you even know
about the Time Bureau?
What are you doing with a pig?
You want proof magic exists?
Well, here it is.
♪ ♪
Just give me a minute.
Now, Ray. Ray, do it.
[PIG GRUNTS]
What? No, just come to life.
♪ ♪
Prudence, listen to me.
This isn't who you are.
You're a good person.
He tried to kill my mother.
This town, these people...
they've killed so many others already.
They deserve to burn.
And they will pay for their ignorance,
but not like that.
How else will they learn, deary?
If these people aren't
taught a lesson today,
they will go and hurt others
for days and years to come.
You come from the future.
Can you honestly tell this child
that the hearts of men
change in all that time?
Do they?
No, they don't.
People always fear what
they don't understand,
and that fear turns them into monsters.
But we can't let it turn
us into monsters, too.
We have to be better than them.
Be better? What nonsense.
Be stronger, my pet.
Show them the power that you possess.
Make them grovel at your
feet where they belong.
Think of your mother.
Yes, think of your mother.
What would she want you to do...
get blood on your hands
or forgive them...
for they know not what they do?
Godmother...
Fire and brimstone coming right...
I release you.
♪ ♪
Ah, that's more like it.
[PIG GRUNTS]
Son, I don't know who put
you up to this, but...
Oh, yeah, I'm also a superhero.
And this is my friend Ray.
Oh, hi, Mr. Heywood.
Nice to finally meet you.
[CLEARS THROAT]
How much money do you need
to ensure that this never happens again?
[CLEARS THROAT] $4.2
billion a year, sir.
♪ ♪
Done.
Help!
♪ ♪
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
You vile, meddling bitch!
[RECITING INCANTATIONS]
And that is for taking my mouth,
you silly old bat.
♪ ♪
I was so terrified of
losing you, Mother.
And I you, my sweet girl.
So what now?
Am I free?
Yeah, you're free,
but you're gonna need
a change of scenery.
Thank you.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Where on Earth are you taking me?
Oh, not on Earth, love.
Where I'm sending you is a touch hotter,
or so I hear.
You intend to send me to hell.
I could be persuaded otherwise.
I'm listening.
You need a host to conduct your magic,
and let's just say I'm
in need of a miracle.
You want to be my new host?
Tit for tat, deary.
[CHUCKLES] John Constantine...
Yes, my pet, I know exactly who you are.
I know you're on the run,
and I know who's coming for you,
and, believe me, I'd rather
face hell than piss him off.
Well, I am happy to oblige.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[RECITING INCANTATIONS]
This is your last chance, Granny.
There's no helping you, deary.
You're more damned than I.
Bippity, boppity...
Oh!
Miss Tomaz has entered the bridge.
I see that, Gideon.
Exit narc mode.
Narc mode.
You're not the only one on the ship
who knows how to get
Gideon to do things.
I wanted to talk to you.
You don't have to say anything.
I already hate myself.
No, it's not like that.
I-I understand why you did what you did.
I've felt that rage before... a lot.
Well, I haven't.
Turns out sarcasm is a really great way
to hide some seriously
deep-seated anger.
I get it, and that's
all I wanted to say,
is that if you want to
talk to me, I'm here.
Look... [SIGHS]
In 2018...
I found my mom.
I didn't talk to her, but...
she was right there, and...
I couldn't think of a way to save her.
Yeah, it's hard.
I've lost a lot of people, too,
and I still think about saving them.
And I don't think that
anger ever goes away.
It's okay.
You just can't hold it in all the time.
I'm not really sure what I'm
supposed to do with it.
Well, let's figure it out... together.
And then we formed Voltron-Beebo
and opened a serious can
of whup-ass on Mallus,
thus saving the universe
for the second time.
So this is what you've
been doing with your life
for the past two years.
Wow, Nathaniel, you did it.
You finally found a useful application
for that history degree.
Still not letting it go.
Take the win, son.
You've done good here.
I look forward to working with you.
- Dinner Friday?
- Yeah.
Here you go.
Parking is right this way.
Do you hear that?
That's $4.2 billion, hell to the yes.
Meet me uptown, Ava Sharpe.
Mm.
Okay, that was terrifying...
- Yeah.
- But clearly effective.
Thank you.
Anytime. Always happy to help.
How about tomorrow?
Now that I have $4.2 billion
burning a hole in my pocket,
you said you could use some income.
I could use a guy like you around here.
You know, think about it.
Clothes, check.
Non-cloven digits, check.
Portal home...
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Check.
After you, my friend.
Um, you go ahead.
I'm gonna stick around
a little while longer,
give dinner with Dad another go.
Oh.
Oh, okay. Yeah, great.
So, uh, we'll... we'll see
you for the next one.
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
[TENDER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --