Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Mick frickin' Rory. Allie, remember?
She wasn't just some girl, was she?
Remember when we dented history?
Your sister is the dent.
Maybe her being here,
she'll remember who she was.
How did you jailbreak
your way out of here?
I was poking around your
screens, and, suddenly,
I knew how to hack my way out.
Astra and this whole
bloody mess is on me.
She could continue
releasing souls indefinitely.
What happened here, John?
That witch is Astra's dead mother.
She's through there.
Her spirit's waiting on the other side
of that door and none too happy with me.
- [THUNDER BOOMING]
- _
[POUNDING ON DOOR, SHOUTING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [LOUD CRASH ON DOOR]
- [GASPS]
John?
Blimey, he's really
cocked it up this time.
How could you let him go in there?
That thing is hurting him.
- Then he probably deserves it.
- [SCOFFS]
I can't just stand here.
Being an apprentice means
never having to say,
"Sorry I let you get killed
by a poltergeist".
Get your filthy paws off me!
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Move out of the way.
[SIGHS] Are you sure you
know what you're doing?
Yes. Maybe.
[SPEAKING ROMANIAN]
♪♪
[CREATURE GROWLING]
- [SCREAMING]
- Oh, my God.
John?
[SHOUTS]
[GASPING]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
♪♪
- [SHRIEKING]
- Aah!
[GRUNTING]
Oh, Gary, what have you done?
[ROCK MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Resync by TEDI for WEBRip.x264-ION10/AMZN
[WATER RUNNING]
- [SPITS]
- [TOOTHBRUSH TAPPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Sorry, old assassin habits die hard.
Babe, now that you've
given me a heart attack,
I was just about to
jump in. Care to join me?
Whoa, co-showering in
the communal bathroom...
you are getting comfy,
which is a good thing
because I'm gonna need
you to woman the ship.
I've got business in Star City.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's just some stuff
I need to take care of,
but it might take a few days,
which is why I need an interim captain.
- Captain?
- Mm-hmm.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was just starting to find
my footing as a Legend.
Nobody likes the boss, babe.
They like me.
Yeah, because you're cool Captain Lance.
I'm just a button pusher
in a boring pantsuit.
Nah, babe, just have fun with it.
They are going to love you.
- No. No, no, no.
- Yes.
I miss you already, Captain Pantsuit.
No, babe, I'm not...
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪♪
Raise you two.
Make it ten.
Finally, a real hand.
[LAUGHTER]
She folds.
Like hell I do.
[GROWLS] Like hell you do.
What the hell are you doing?
Keeping us in the black.
You lost another account.
First Rasputin, then Bugsy...
- John Constantine...
- Now Meyers.
Your little resurrection
venture is getting too risky.
You turn the tide, or
you'll lose everything.
I've played nice long enough.
Now it's time to play naughty.
- [OMINOUS MUSIC]
- _
[CREATURE SHRIEKING, OBJECTS CLATTERING]
That's one angry ghost.
Yeah, and now she's
loose in the bloody house.
- What, that was Astra's mum?
- Yeah, her name is Natalie.
What did you do to her, John boy?
[SIGHS] It was a long time ago.
She was walking home late from work,
and some drunken idiot
blew a red light, and...
Her husband, Alex, begged
me to bring her back.
You never told me that.
Yeah, well, I never told anyone.
Now, let's just say that
that night in Newcastle
when we lost Astra,
it was a little more complicated
than an exorcism.
Something tells me
that you're not telling the truth.
Look, I'm trying to
fix it, Nat, all right?
I'm trying to save Astra. Now help me.
[WIND GUSTING, CREATURE HOWLING]
Doesn't seem to be the
answer she was looking for.
The demon I summoned
brought Natalie back.
But if you brought her
back, why is she a ghost?
Because I botched it, all right?
I thought I had him under
control, but I didn't.
- You can't have her!
- John, get me out of here!
He took Astra.
Natalie couldn't live
with herself knowing
that the price of her
life was her daughter's.
She killed herself in this room.
That's so sa...
[SCREAMS]
♪♪
[THUNDER BOOMS]
Doesn't look like Natalie's
done with you yet, John-o.
[CREEPY LAUGHTER]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
♪♪
No, it looks like
Natalie wants to take me
on a trip down memory lane.
♪♪
All righty-tighty, then.
You ready for the
official Waverider tour?
- Hmm.
- What would you like to see first?
What do you people do
around here for fun?
If you could just follow me this way,
First stop, the galley.
Gideon can whip up any kind
of food you can imagine.
Last week, Nate and I
made cheddar biscuits
and had her fabricate
some squeezable butter.
That tasty treat has been
off the shelves since 2024.
She can make anything, and you went
with a discontinued condiment.
Wait, can she make clothes?
Of course.
Okay, tell the computer I need a dress
for my perfume launch tonight.
We'll be back in time for that, right?
Yes. And, yes, Gideon can do anything.
She flies the ship, makes our food,
cleans the toilets, tracks the timeline.
Tracks the time...
Do you mean tells the future?
Behrad, we could make billions
off future fall trend reports.
[CLEARS THROAT] No, no.
Rule number one of time travel,
never look into the
future for personal gain.
Totally, totally.
And rule number two, no
social media on the ship.
[PHONE BEEPS]
I thought we were dropping you off.
My brother, the actual superhero...
[IMITATES WHOOSH] Invited me to stay.
Okay, let's just remember
this is a place of business, okay?
We get called on a mission,
you need to keep out of our way.
Aye, aye.
- Okay, we'll talk later.
- [SCOFFS]
Sad, what a waste of
a good head of hair.
Here you go. Hide it.
Can your computer lady
make me some cucumber water?
I'm parched from that dry interaction.
She and her mom have been
living out of their car
for almost a year, and now her mom has
a final-round job interview.
You are incredible.
I miss you, but it feels pretty good
to be out here helping people.
- Out.
- Ah, it's okay.
I have to go anyway.
Okay, uh, well, um, I'll call you later.
I love you.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I just kind of blurted that out.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
You don't have to be sorry.
I love you, too.
- You do?
- I said "get out".
Okay, I'll call later.
- Bye.
- Okay.
[SIGHS]
Mick, are you feeling all right?
My stomach hurts. I can't eat.
I can't drink.
I think Allie gave me an
STD back at the reunion.
Initiating scan.
[ELECTRONIC HUMMING]
Those are not symptoms.
Those are feelings.
Mick, I think you're developing a crush.
Is that when you whiz and it hurts?
No, it's biology's way of telling you
you care about someone else.
Dr. Palmer is correct.
The results of my body scan indicate
that you do, in fact, like like her.
[GRUMBLES]
Interim Captain Sharpe here,
team meeting in the parlor,
over and out.
Okay, that was good. It
was fun yet to the point.
Not too...
Gideon, are you broadcasting this?
Sorry, Miss Sharpe, I'll shut it down.
Okay, thank you, we women
have to stick together.
I always thought of
you as one of the guys.
Okay, I don't know what that means.
He means that as a compliment.
- I do.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
- That's for you.
That's for you.
Okay, then.
Okay.
What did I say about phones?
What? I need to tell my
boyfriend I'm not dead.
Uh, boyfriend?
Yep, internationally
renowned DJ S'more Money.
Ah, okay, we've got Ray.
- Uh, where's Mick?
- He's sick.
- Lovesick. [CHUCKLES]
- Oh.
Oh, lei.
So while Sara's in Star City,
I wanted to introduce you all
to something that I developed
at the Time Bureau.
I know what you're all thinking,
Time Bureau, #stuffy.
What can we learn from those guys?
But we really did have
a lot of fun over there.
Do you remember taco Mondays, Nate?
Yeah, those were some wild taco times.
- Yeah.
- Aloha?
Yes, A.L.O.H.A.
It stands for assess,
listen, observe, hydrate...
- attack!
- What the...
- Cool.
- See?
Uh, how many pages is this?
Ava, you ever heard the proverb
"the fox knows many things,
the hedgehog knows one big thing"?
I have not.
Well, Legends, we're a
fox kind of organization.
Adaptable, off the cuff.
This... this is very hedgehog.
Trying to impose one way of doing things
onto every situation.
And not to be rude...
is there a mission here?
- No, I just...
- Okay, then, I'm gonna
introduce Zari to the wonders
of Gideon's Austrian toast.
- Actually, it's French toast.
- Ah...
- Pretty sure it's Austrian.
- [CHUCKLES GOOFILY]
Gideon, Gideon, check the timeline.
It would appear that
there is a disturbance
at the Bastille in Paris, 1793.
While the details are still hazy,
the aftermath is traumatic.
Thousands die, and the
French Revolution collapses.
Well, looks like we have a mission,
so everybody stop looking
so "Les Misérables",
because we are going to France.
- [ENGINE HUMS]
- _
Behrad, come on, we need to move.
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[ELEGANT MUSIC]
Hey, guys.
I couldn't stop her.
She found the fabrication room.
Great. She's not coming.
We don't do ride-alongs in the field, B.
Ava, I can handle myself in the field.
I once played capture the
flag to raise awareness
about feline OCD, so...
This isn't a PR event, all right?
We're walking into a deadly situation
facing an Encore with unknown powers.
I do not have time to keep
my eye on a party girl.
I do.
What?
I mean, come on, Ava, what's the harm?
It's against protocol to
bring civilians into the field.
- Tsk.
- Don't "tsk".
Tsk.
Yeah, but it would be super cool
if you just let me come anyway.
- Uh, okay, fine.
- Yay.
Just, uh, make sure
you stay out of our way.
Yay! [BOTTLE SPRAYS]
[GAGS]
[COUGHS]
What the hell was that?
My signature perfume, Dragonesque.
I needed to do something to help
that extremely sad outfit.
Spray, delay, walk away.
Okay, we're going this way.
Jesus.
I was just doing a runway turn.
[SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE]
This period in France was
called the Reign of Terror.
Executions were a national pastime.
- Whoa!
- Ooh, yikes.
Yeah, we could definitely
be walking into a bloodbath.
And you want us to go in there?
Yeah, that's our job.
[CLEARS THROAT] Excuse me, sir.
- Uh, we need to get in there.
- [SCOFFS]
No.
It is of vital importance
that we get in there, sir.
Please? Oh.
Stand back.
This isn't a club,
Zari, it's an execution.
An event is an event.
Scoot. Out of the way.
Where do you think you're going?
Um, do you know who you're talking to?
What's your name?
Jean-Paul.
Très bien. Now they'll know who to fire
when they find out you left
Zari Tarazi standing outside.
Un grand faux pas.
Not them.
Jean-Paul, my purse isn't
gonna walk in by itself.
Pshh.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
[SPIRITED CHAMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
♪♪
Um, didn't you say
this was an execution?
Maybe Gideon got it wrong.
Well, if they were misérables,
they certainly aren't anymore.
Stop with the thing.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
You know, you can just say the word,
and I'll put you in a prime spot uptown.
- [CHUCKLES]
- So I can rub shoulders with all those
arrogant soul traders? No, thank you.
I need some help with one
of the coins you constructed.
Help?
When else do you come see me?
- I assume this is why you're here?
- _
- How did you...
- [CHUCKLES]
John Constantine.
I remember making this.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
What do you want for him?
Oh, I don't want to trade him.
I want to kill him.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Tourist attraction number two.
The night Alex begged
me to save Natalie.
He was supposed to pick her
up that night she got hit,
but they had a big fight, so she walked.
Alex was beside himself. He was torn up.
Astra, she hadn't said a
word since the accident.
How was I supposed to say no?
[THUNDER BOOMS]
Alex begged me, but I
knew I should have said no.
Bollocks, John! Come on, try again!
Alex wanted it, and I just
provided the how, all right?
What's the difference, Nat?
So the resurrection was your idea?
Yes, all right?
Nat and I, we were best friends,
How could I not try and save her?
See? The truth can set you free.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[ON STEREO] ♪ I was on this
world when you went away ♪
Is that Mucous Membrane?
♪ So clearly till this day ♪
♪ I don't want to do this ♪
[CHAMBER MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
This place doesn't seem too evil.
Yeah, well, appearances
can be deceiving, okay?
We need to figure out who this encore is
and what powers they may have.
We start with the
A.L.O.H.A. method, okay?
Assessment, lay low, don't engage.
We know how to party sneak.
Listen to me... you see
something, you say something.
- Captain.
- Yeah.
You're trying too hard.
[WHISPERING] It's really desperate.
♪♪
So this is your job?
Walking around parties?
Isn't this kind of what you do?
Hmm, touché.
No.
But something definitely feels off.
At this point in the French Revolution,
most of the royals had been
separated from their heads.
Even wearing a nice dress could
get you sent to the guillotine.
Uh, and you let me come
out in this because... ?
I'm sucker for a corset and an updo.
[MAN SHOUTS IN FRENCH]
[GRUNTING]
Napoleon?
He should be marching
on southern France,
not getting freaky.
Wha... okay.
Guys, steer clear.
Exercise extreme caution.
- Relax, Ava.
- I'm trying.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Nora?
Ava, I think we found our encore.
She's in the VIP area.
Nora's our encore?
No, Ray, that's Marie Antoinette.
And she should definitely
be without her head by now.
Oh, great, on to phase two of A.L.O.H.A.
It's listening.
Now, her powers could be anything...
teleportation, pyrokinesis.
Fatal attractiveness.
- I mean...
- BOTH: Right?
- [GIGGLES]
- Guys?
Guys?
They're not usually like this.
Well, you're not usually captain.
Thank you.
I just swapped crepe recipes
with a French cooking legend.
This is the best party ever.
Excuse me, since when do you drink?
Whoa, where did I even get that?
You know what? You're right.
Something is definitely wrong.
[DOOR OPENS, MAN SPEAKING FRENCH]
Move out of the way.
[WOMAN SPEAKING FRENCH]
It is time.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Of course, the perfect revenge,
a magical guillotine.
Shh.
Guys, be careful, I think
Marie's about to make her move.
♪♪
Now!
Let them eat cake!
[CROWD CHEERING]
- Cake, cake.
- Need some cake.
[ALL MUNCHING EXCITEDLY]
Crazy.
- [FRENCH ACCENT] Pardon me.
- Pardonne-moi.
So it's not a guillotine.
What day is it?
Uh, how long have you been here?
[GASPS]
Oh, my God, he's dead.
Ugh, he literally
partied himself to death.
So tacky.
Look, no, he's not the only one.
What is happening?
That's why I don't eat carbs.
This woman is next-level popular.
People would rather die than leave.
Talk about FOMO.
My God, that's it.
Marie Antoinette was
beheaded for partying
while France starved,
and now she is literally
killing the Revolution
with a nonstop party.
Legends, we figured it out.
Charm is her superpower.
Hello?
Ray, Nate, Behrad?
It's like she's gotten
to everyone except for us.
So we have to stop this.
Wait, I'm on the team?
Sure.
Okay, what's the plan?
Uh, we have to find a way
to get Marie Antoinette
out of here without a riot.
[GASPS]
The only way to get a celebrity
to leave her own party quietly
is to make her think
there's a cooler party
somewhere else that she's not at.
Let's go tell her.
Uh-uh, girl, you're not gonna
get anywhere in this ensemble.
What are you doing? Stop.
Hey, trust me.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Ugh.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Come on.
[ON STEREO] ♪ Don't you walk away ♪
That's her, Natalie.
Oh, she's good.
Yeah.
♪♪
[BOTH LAUGHING]
You loved her.
It's quite the track record, isn't it?
One lover sent to hell,
the other one a ghost.
[THUNDER BOOMS, DOOR OPENS]
Please, John, it's eating you up.
You have to stop.
Look, Natalie, you're
gonna have to trust me
on this one, all right?
I've got it under control.
If Lester hadn't been there,
I would have lost you tonight.
Look, let's just leave all this behind.
We'll go to New York. We'll start clean.
You have to choose.
Magic or me.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Screw you, John Constantine.
All right, that's enough, all right?
I don't want you in my
head or in my memories!
No more games!
We're trapped in this house
with a knife-wielding ghost,
and you're still refusing
to own up to your past.
You are a fine one to talk, aren't you?
Well, why don't we poke around
in your closet for a while, eh?
- Why did you leave, Charlie?
- Uh, guys?
I'm no hero. It was time to go.
Yeah, what, you just wandered
into my house looking for a party?
What are you really doing here, eh?
Don't even try and turn
this on me, all right?
It's your lies that
have trapped us here.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
♪♪
She's right, John.
Natalie, is that really you?
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[BRIGHT PIANO MUSIC]
♪♪
Every level of the
party has its guardians.
Getting past the bouncer, easy.
Getting past the friends,
you need to know someone.
But we don't know anybody.
I know that guy.
- You know Napoleon?
- No, but they don't know that.
- Bonjour, Napoleon.
- [SPEAKING FRENCH]
We're with him.
♪♪
Oh, she separated from the pack.
- Now's the time.
- Oh, good, work your magic.
Oh, teaching moment.
The big secret to
being cool, confidence.
It makes people think you
have something they don't.
- You got this, Captain.
- No, but I don't... ah...
[LAUGHS] Thank you.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I do not know you.
What are you doing here?
- Uh...
- Hmm?
- Ah...
- Ah?
- Leaving.
- Ugh, leaving?
Ugh.
Actually, I am going to the after-party.
What is this "aprés-party"?
Mm, it's a party after the party.
It's the best place to be.
Where is it?
Mm, I can't tell you.
- Ugh.
- But I can take you.
- Oui, take me.
- Mm.
[EXHALES IN ANTICIPATION]
Oh, oh, this is my bestie,
Zari... she's coming with.
Yas, queen. Mm.
Guys, I have Marie, and we're
taking her to the Waverider.
That's a good idea.
We can have her all to ourselves.
- Whoo!
- Marie, come back.
[SCOFFS, SPEAKING FRENCH]
There is an "aprés-party".
[CROWD CHEERING]
Guys, we have company.
Oh, the after-party's right this way.
[PUNK ROCK MUSIC]
Guys, I need backup.
♪♪
Corsets are so impractical.
Marie, where's the party?
♪♪
I do not think this is a good idea.
We're gonna party our faces
off... it's gonna be great.
Oh!
[GASPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[SCREAMS]
Ew.
Should've seen that coming.
Return me to my body this instant,
or I will have your head for this.
- Get her to the Waverider!
- Oh, this is weird.
This party stinks!
Oh, so true, girl.
[SIGHS] But not the point.
She's annoying, you can just...
BOTH: Yeah.
Ah, get this thing off of me.
Ugh, I can't believe I tried the drink.
Can't believe I ate all
that gluten-filled cake.
I can't believe how heavy that head is.
Yeah, she really had
you under her spell.
If it weren't for our
interim legend here,
you guys would've partied to death.
Well, just to play it safe,
I'm gonna take this into the library.
- [CRUNCHES]
- Aah! You see?
- Oh, I'll help you.
- Don't get creepy, Ray.
- So, my sister the superhero.
- Hmm.
Should I get Gideon to make you a cowl?
Mm, cowls are for middle-aged women
who want to hide their necks.
But I do need a dress
for the party tonight.
Fabricator's all yours.
Yay, thank you.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Is that really you, Nat?
I need to hear you say it.
Why did you bring me back?
Because I loved you, Nat.
I never stopped.
I'm not here
for the John Constantine
broken hero act.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
♪♪
Say it to my face.
I need to hear the truth.
I brought you back...
to prove to you that I was right...
to show you that I was right
to choose magic over us.
♪♪
Thank you.
I needed you to admit to
yourself what you did...
because if you're going to save Astra,
you need to do it for
her, not for your ego.
Oh, I have tried to save her, Nat,
I have tried, but I don't know how.
I think I found a way.
♪♪
Follow me.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
Uh, yoo-hoo.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
Hello? E-excuse me?
Can you help me? Where's my body?
You were throwing a party
intended to kill people,
so, no, not gonna help you.
[SIGHS]
When I was 14, I was
forced to leave my family.
People saw the dresses,
the parties, the hair,
and they assumed I was a spoiled brat.
Really, I was just a
lonely Viennese girl
trying to fit into French society.
I've been famous since
I was six years old.
I don't know if people
love me or love to hate me.
What they don't understand
is how hard I work
to create a fantasy for them.
The secret is to never
let the party stop.
If I had known then what I know now...
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Gidget, is there anything
I need to worry about?
Interim Captain Sharpe instructed you
not to look at your future.
[SIGHS]
Just a peek, little lady computer.
As you wish.
October 7, 2045.
Zari Tarazi faces major
backlash from her fans,
known as Z Nation, after the FDA
banned her perfume Dragonesque
for destroying users' sense of smell.
[GASPS] Oh, no.
I trusted her.
- I wanted to be her,
- _
but now I'll never smell
another flower because of her.
From Z-Nation to Zero-Nation,
Zari Tarazi's Cat-Chat followers
have plummeted to almost zero.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [GAGS]
Meow! [LAUGHTER]
But I didn't know
there was anything
wrong with the perfume.
This is so unfair.
Okay, I have to get
out in front of this.
Maybe Gidget can make me a new perfume.
Or I can just take yours.
No, you cannot have it.
I mean, it's not like you're using it.
You have half a neck.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
Why do you care so much
about a bottle of perf...
Oh, you're not super charming,
you used magical popularity perfume.
Honestly, that makes me
feel better about myself.
Hmm.
Huh, what are you doing?
- Shh.
- [MUFFLED FRENCH]
Can't have you ratting me out.
[MUFFLED FRENCH]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- _
[ELECTROPOP MUSIC]
♪♪
Oh, there you are. Thank God, thank God.
I have been so worried,
but, uh, don't worry...
No, I've totally been keeping
up your Catchat account.
Yesterday I posted a picture of a cat
licking a tube of Dragonesque lipstick.
Gross, Les-Lay. I would never post that.
I'm so sorry. I will delete it.
Here is the hero bottle
for the photoshoot.
Actually, change of plans.
- Oh, so retro. [GIGGLES]
- Thanks.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey, Z.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, watch the s'more.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, babe.
So have you decided where you
want to do the proposal yet?
The what?
Didn't my agent call you?
Yeah, um, I haven't had a
chance to tell you yet, Z,
but S'mores' team came up
with the most epic idea.
He should...
[WHISPERING] propose to you
at next week's MTV Movie Awards
in advance of your DJ and Z
co-branded sunglasses launch.
Sorry. We're getting married?
Yeah, or we can do it
somewhere more chill,
you know, like, at the DJ S'more Money
spring break house party live cast.
- Something like that?
- How romantic.
Yeah, it's gonna be dope.
- Okay, let's do this.
- Ready for this. Let's go.
- Hey, hey!
- So exciting.
Okay, one spritz should be safe.
Spray, delay, walk away.
[LAUGHS] You have to do a 23andMe.
I mean, she must be related to you.
Here, doesn't she look exactly like you?
Ray, I am looking at a
gagged, decapitated woman.
If that's what you think I look like,
we have a lot of processing to do.
Oh, no, look...
Sorry, Miss Antoinette.
[SPITS] Thief!
- Can you taste the cardamom?
- I can't.
I can't taste anything
because your sister's perfume
clogged up my entire olfactory system.
Everything tastes like...
Zari, Zari stole Marie
Antoinette's perfume.
You should see what
Mick stole from Mexico.
- It's disgusting.
- Should consider ourselves lucky.
At least she didn't do
something to screw up history.
Oh, my God, the perfume.
That's how Marie did it.
Zari and I weren't affected
'cause we couldn't smell
because of the Dragonesque.
Who knows what kind of
damage she could do with that?
It's all my fault. I
shouldn't have let her stay.
I knew it was too early
to pat myself on the back.
Ah, look, it wouldn't
be a true Legends mission
- unless something went wrong.
- [LOUD THUDDING]
Or several things.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪♪
Uh, wasn't there a
body on that stretcher?
[PAPARAZZI SHOUTING]
[ELECTROPOP MUSIC]
♪♪
Have I told you how hot
you look in that dress?
No, but you can tell me now.
Super hot!
[SNIFFS] And you smell fantastic.
You know what? Screw our agents.
I don't want to wait
till the fall launch
of our sunglasses in October
to begin my life with you.
Hey, listen up!
S'more Money has an
announcement to make!
Zari Tarazi, will you marry me?
Uh, S'more... Oh!
[SHIMMERING TONE]
Ugh.
[EERIE MUSIC]
[PEOPLE SNIFFING]
I think I just got a little too popular.
Oh, oh, God.
♪♪
Here, body, body, body, body, body.
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
Okay, body. No one wants to hurt you.
Speak for yourself!
Hey, come on, Mick. She's harmless.
It's just a headless body.
Oh, whoa.
[GRUNTING] A little help here.
No, Mick, don't!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
She's mine!
Okay, we need to protect ourselves.
Zari's deployed Marie's perfume.
- Ah!
- [COUGHS]
[ALL COUGHING]
Okay, team, A.L.O.H.A. time.
♪♪
Run, run!
Nate, what do you got?
I'm assessing Zari used
too much of the perfume,
'cause this crowd is bananas.
Behrad?
I'm listening, and I
hear another mob coming.
Okay, I'm observing, and there are
way too many people for us to stop.
We need to get that perfume
off of her to stop this.
- How?
- I have an idea. I need your help.
♪♪
[CROWD SHOUTING EXCITEDLY]
Behrad, now!
[WHOOSHING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
You guys came back for me.
A Legend never gets left
behind, even an interim one.
Follow me.
- What are you doing?
- Trust me.
There's too many of them.
I can't stop them all.
[WHOOSHING]
- Come on!
- Okay.
♪♪
Well, we've tried the A.L.O.H.A. method.
The A.L.O. haven't gotten us anywhere.
What does the H stand for?
Hydrate!
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- S'mores.
- Yeah.
- Zari's boyfriend?
- That's me.
Ha.
- Okay, guys.
- Oh, God.
Party's over.
Did Zari just jump into the fountain?
Whoa, talk about desperate stunts.
I'm calling my agent
to schedule a divorce!
Wait, what does that last A stand for?
Attack!
[MICK ROARS]
♪♪
Hey.
[SPOOKY MUSIC]
Look at us.
We thought we could change
the world with our little loom.
This one's to bring me mum back.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
The Loom of Fate... it's
not just a story, it's real.
Three old Greek birds cutting threads,
hunkering down over a
loom to weave together
the fate of humankind.
If it's real, how come I
haven't heard of it, eh?
You're asking the wrong person.
Why do you think I brought her here?
[GASPS]
What the bloody hell was that?
What do you know about the Loom of Fate?
I know bugger all.
- How did you find this place, Charlie?
- You told me about it.
Oh, bollocks, I've never
told anyone about it.
Natalie brought you here
to help me save Astra
and stop those encores, so tell me,
what do you know about the Loom of Fate?
Fate's a load of crap.
You haven't answered
my question, Charlie.
Look, you want to know
what I'm hiding from?
- Yes, I do!
- It's that bloody loom!
♪♪
- So it is real?
- It was...
Until I destroyed it.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
"Lady in cheap pantsuit ruins party".
Ava was right about
no phones on the ship.
Had Gideon whip you up some new clothes.
- Hope you like flannel.
- I do not.
Ew.
Listen, I know, you're gonna tell me
how selfish I was for
stealing the perfume
and burning the team.
You guys toil away in
obscurity to save humanity
from unknown baddies,
and I just go and spray
evil perfume all over New York City
without a second thought.
I'm jerk.
I'm sorry.
I was just gonna ask if
you wanted a doughnut.
I haven't had a doughnut in 1,743 days.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, what is this, eh, doughnut?
BOTH: Shut up, Marie.
Ah, phoo!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey.
Wow.
Nice shirt.
Hmm, you would be into lumberjack chic.
There's an incoming
hologram from Captain Lance.
Captain.
How'd the mission go?
Oh, um...
- Well, I...
- Killed it.
She was a foxy hedgehog out there.
[HISSES]
Okay.
We got our encore, Captain.
Oh, good. I'm glad to hear it.
Ava, call me later so I
can thank you properly.
[LIGHT MUSIC]
Oh, Captain, my captain.
"Call me later so I can
properly congratulate you".
- Guys, come on.
- She doesn't sound like that.
[SERIOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
Zari! [WHISTLES]
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I was...
I was just, uh, enjoying this doughnut
and thinking...
You locked Marie Antoinette
up, but you let me off the hook.
I mean, she killed people, Zari.
You screwed up. You
know, everybody screws up.
- Not you.
- Me?
[LAUGHS] I feel like I'm
screwing up all the time.
You were so on mission.
You crashed an A-list
party in a pantsuit
and threw yourself into a fountain.
Ugh, see, it's a perfect example.
No, it was amazing.
You didn't care what anyone thought.
You were just being you.
I've been trying to
get people to like me
for so long that...
I've forgotten who I really am.
I have millions of followers but...
zero friends.
You got one.
Really?
[PEACEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
Come on.
Hmm. Well, as your friend,
I have to tell you...
- no more pantsuits.
- Mm.
- [CHUCKLES]
- You're better than that.
Deal.
[EERIE MUSIC]
He still has ten years
before the lung cancer
catches up to him.
Can you make it zero?
It's a nasty way to go,
especially all at once.
You sure that's who you want to be?
Why is it so hard for people
to let little girls grow up.
John may be the villain in your story,
but in mine, he's just
cocktail party conversation.
I have a few enemies of my own.
One day, I'm going to call you,
and you are going to do me a favor.
You make favor sound like sin.
[SCOFFS]
This is hell, sweetie.
Do it.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
You broke the Loom of Fate?
How old are you?
Old.
Well, if you broke it,
why are you still running?
I scattered those damn pieces
all across the multiverse.
Just put an end to it all.
Recently...
I sensed that something had changed.
It's like my past was
catching up with me, so...
[COUGHING]
John, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I just got a...
[HACKING]
[RETCHING]
Bye-bye, Johnny.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[NO AUDIO]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Resync by TEDI for WEBRip.x264-ION10/AMZN