Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
If you're seeing this, we
altered my future at Heyworld.
I don't know where I'll be
or who I'll be, but find me.
- John, wait!
- Masher?
Has Astra released the worst
souls from Hell onto Earth?
I'm unkillable!
[LAUGHS]
I'm putting an end to this.
Are you trying to go back to Hell?
I'll return when the sigil is complete.
[SIGHS]
♪ Time is breaking up my soul ♪
♪ It's using it to mold ♪
♪ It's so, oh, oh ♪
Ma'am, we caught him lurking outside.
It seems you're having a hard time
staying away from Hell these days, John.
Well, what can I say,
I'm a creature of habit.
You might as well get used to it.
You'll be living down here soon enough.
What do you want?
A whiskey, neat, and a steak, well done.
Oh, yeah, and all those
souls you released.
Call 'em back.
Look, there is enough evil on Earth
without you giving the
damned a second chance.
Those damned souls are
making me rich, John.
Any humans corrupted or killed
by them all belong to me.
And after years of being under
the boot of the Triumvirate,
it sure feels good to grind
my heel on someone else.
[SNAPS]
- Masher?
- John.
Help me.
John's better at getting
his friends into trouble
than out of it.
Something you should have
known when you squealed on me.
[PAINFUL GROAN]
You don't have to do this, Astra.
I like doing this.
No more, please.
[GROANS]
Astra, look, I came down here
for a friendly chat, all right?
Now, we don't have to be enemies.
You're not my enemy, John.
You're an important
step in my evolution.
I crawled my way up from the bottom
and I finally have some
real power around here.
So if you want to stop me,
you'll have to kill me.
But really, what's the point?
My soul would just end
up back down here anyway.
[FIRE WHOOSHES]
[EXHAUSTED GRUNT]
John.
[COUGHS]
What happened down there?
- I need a drink.
- [MOUTHING WORDS]
[LIGHT MUSIC]
No post-mission debrief?
It's part of his process.
- [METAL THUMPING]
- Come on, Gideon,
play the damn message again.
You can mistreat me all
you like, Mr. Heywood.
But I assure you, there
are no secret messages
hiding in my memory banks.
Everything okay, bro?
Oh, um, yeah.
I was just, uh,
double-checking something.
Little help?
[FLUTTERS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
I think I'm starting to see things.
I know what's going on.
You do?
You get into my stash again?
[LAUGHTER]
Dude, no worries.
- Sara's gathering the team, come on.
- Thanks.
And that is the truth of it, mateys.
Astra and this whole
bloody mess is on me.
And she can't be reasoned with.
So we need a more permanent
solution to stopping her
or she could continue
releasing souls indefinitely.
Surely, Astra can change.
She's still human, right?
I mean, even a master of
the dark arts must believe
there's still some good left in her.
Forget it, big man.
Astra's lust for power,
it zapped the humanity out of her.
Well, on the bright side,
at least the encores
aren't our fault this time.
Hey, up top.
Is there any point in
sending these encores to Hell?
It sounds like Astra would
just send them straight back.
Correct.
Well, then until we find
a more permanent solution,
we'll house the encores on the ship.
We're gonna need a bigger pantry.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Hey, Cap.
Normally, I'd be all
for rolling up my sleeves
and pitching in, but I
gotta take shore leave
for my pop's birthday,
and Nate's coming with me.
- I am?
- You are?
My parents are always asking
questions about my life.
He could pretend to be one
of my biz school professors.
[BOTH MOUTHING WORDS]
I still can't believe
that you haven't told
your parents the truth
about what you do.
You mean that I'm a
time traveling superhero
who stole the family heirloom?
Hmm, okay, yeah, stick
to business school.
We'll be back before
you can say "timequake".
Don't jinx it.
Too late, Captain,
a new timequake has been detected.
You are needed on the bridge.
[SIGHS]
Mm.
What are we looking at?
Ah, the epicenter of the timequake
is in Los Angeles, 1947.
It's the golden age of Hollywood
and the height of
organized crime in the city.
The real golden age.
All right, people, we're
gonna need two teams for the...
Sorry, honey, I think I'm
in your spot, aren't I?
Hey, don't sweat it, babe.
As Ava was saying, two teams.
Ray, John, with me.
Mick, Ava, QB from the ship.
Now, let's do it.
Hmm, you hear that?
It's only my second official
mission with the Legends,
and I'm already being
trusted with the football.
Really?
QB means staying on the
ship and doing nothing.
Or it could mean
providing the team
with vital information.
Gideon, pull up a topographical survey
of the city, please.
_
- How you feeling?
- [EXHALES] Great.
I just needed to get off the ship,
clear my head.
[SPEAKING FARSI] _
_
Guys, this is Nathaniel Heywood.
He's one of my professors.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Oh, we've never had a
professor over for dinner.
What do you teach?
Advanced macroeconomics,
- behavioral economics...
- Hey, guys.
- [WHISPERED] Brace yourself.
- Z here.
So I'm at my parents' house
celebrating my dad's birthday.
After all, family is everything.
Speaking of which, it looks like we have
a surprise guest this year.
My brother, Behrad.
Say hello, B.
Hi.
Anyways, guys, I gotta go.
Big love to the Z nation. Khodafez.
Insert that clip at the
end of the current file.
We'll start cutting tonight.
You two can set up glam in
the bathroom for touch-ups.
Hey, I thought this was
supposed to be a family party.
Oh, says the woman who just invited
her 48 million followers into our house.
It's 51 million.
Try to keep up.
Zari, darling, isn't it marvelous.
Your brother brought home one
of his professors from grad school.
Zari, Nate. Nate, Zari.
Hi.
It's you.
[WHISPERING] I saw the video.
Oh, thanks for subscribing.
You know, it's the fans that really make
all the hard work worth it.
What a weirdo.
_
[WHISPERING] Yo.
Your sister is the secret woman
from the hologram message.
Secret wha...
I thought I was hallucinating,
but Gideon was scrubbing her memory
and there was a secret
message from your sister
telling me to find her
and she's the reason I came back.
Are you having a psychological break?
No, I'm being serious.
Remember when we dented
history at Heyworld.
Your sister is the dent.
- [CAR HORNS HONKING]
- _
- [JAZZ MUSIC]
♪♪
[SPELL WHOOSHES]
The traces of magical
energy lead into this office.
There's an infernal residue in here.
Sure is.
Residue of a dead guy.
Oh, whoa, stand back.
Ugh.
The victim was consumed
by ignis inferni.
It's hellfire.
Whoever did this to him
was not of this world.
Well, looks like our
killer's the encore.
Bollocks.
Ah, there's the ticket.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Don't come any closer.
All right, easy. You can
put the gun down.
We're here to help.
Where's Webb?
Uh, we are the "and
Moore" of Webb & Moore.
We work with Moore... Webb.
You must be Moore.
[IN AMERICAN ACCENT] Sure, that's me.
Johnny Moore.
Sarah is my secretary
and this fella here...
Has got a cop face.
Oh, thank you. [CHUCKLES]
Sergeant Palmer at your service.
I'm undercover.
Tell Webb to call me when he's back.
He's, uh, on holiday... vacation,
which leaves me handling
your case, Miss...
Hill, Jeannie Hill.
I hired your partner to
protect me from my boyfriend.
Oh, well, you're in good hands, ma'am.
Oh, give me a break, Johnny Law.
Half the PD is in Bugsy's pocket.
Bugsy as in...
Benjamin Siegel.
Doesn't like it when you call him Bugsy.
But here's the kicker,
He died last week.
And now he's back from the dead.
And he's more dangerous than ever.
[UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC]
♪♪
He took over a joint on Sunset Boulevard
called the Blue Iguana.
Playground of gangsters
and the Hollywood elite.
Whatever vice floats your boat,
that's where you'll find it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Welcome to the Blue Iguana.
Now, have fun, I insist.
If you don't, I just
might have to shoot ya.
[REVOLVER HUMS]
[LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE]
Mr. Siegel.
Here, smile for the camera, Mr. Siegel.
♪♪
[JAZZ MUSIC]
Just, uh, cleaning up
a little bit of crumbs.
Please, Ms. Hill, continue.
I was there when Bugsy was assassinated
by a mob hit man.
Saw the whole thing.
But then, the very next day,
lover boy shows up at my doorstep,
takes me to his club
like nothing had happened.
And that's just the biscuit,
here comes the gravy.
He's different now.
More ambitious and fearless.
I wanna leave him but I can't
because I know he'd kill me.
Look, Ms. Hill,
we can protect you from your boyfriend.
But you're gonna need to get
out of town for a few days.
Stay in a motel. Things could get messy.
But I don't have any money.
Bugsy takes care of all that.
[GASPS]
How can I ever repay you?
No need to worry about that.
We just wanna make sure you're safe.
Secretary Sara, can you
show Ms. Hill the way out?
Oh, she took you for
an easy mark, Raymondo.
What? She was absolutely terrified.
Sara?
Jury's still out on the
missus, but it sounds like
we need to pay a visit
to the Blue Iguana.
- [JAZZ MUSIC]
- _
♪♪
All right, this is more like it.
Feels good to be back in the field.
Ava, what's your status?
Uh, beer.
Rory and I are just
sidling up to the bar now.
We're gonna keep an eye on things.
I'm seeing two zones of egress.
Back door's a gray zone,
front door's got about
four guys sitting around it,
which, quite frankly,
feels like overkill.
What do you think, Mick?
I think you need to relax.
Ray, you ready to grab
Bugsy when he comes out?
Ready and walking the beat.
Gotta say, feelin' pretty
spiffy in this uniform.
Bugsy has drawn himself
quite a crowd of ass kissers.
Yeah, and judging by the cheap threads
and conservative haircuts,
I'd say they're politicians.
Well, if it isn't our
damsel in distress.
It's gonna be kinda hard
to protect her from her beau
when she's hanging on his arm.
I knew it, she's as
bent as a nine-bob note.
Let's go.
Not so fast, sister.
What happened to getting out of town?
You think a cab ride could get me away
from what Bugsy's got on me?
You and the rest of
town, by the looks of it.
Look, ever since Bugsy came back,
he gets whatever he wants,
and everyone answers to him.
Politicians, studio heads...
Even the cops.
Then tell me, how'd he
get so much juice so fast?
By using America's
favorite pastime, of course.
Blackmail.
He's got a secret stash
of compromising photographs
he uses against all of them.
And what does that have to do with you?
Everything.
I'm in those pictures.
Bugsy used me as bait to lure
men and women into his trap.
When I first moved here
from Shaker Heights,
I thought I was gonna be famous.
And sure, I became famous all right.
Just not the right kind of famous.
I can't leave without those pictures.
Satisfied?
You know, if Bugsy likes
honey traps so much,
why don't we give him a
taste of his own medicine.
[JAZZ MUSIC]
♪♪
I couldn't help but notice you,
and I gotta tell you,
I like the way you walk.
I learned to do it all by myself,
Mr. Siegel.
Oh, please, Benjamin.
Hmm, Sara Lance, at your service.
Lance, huh?
What's the matter, you don't like it?
Well, I don't know yet,
just trying it on for size.
You know, even if it fits,
I'm a little curious
about the price tag.
Well, if you have to ask,
it's probably too expensive.
[CHUCKLES]
I take what I want.
Does that make you a thief, Mr. Siegel?
I am a lot of things, Ms. Lance.
And I am especially a thief.
Well, then let's stop
all the tiddlywinks
and get straight to the
big reveal, shall we?
Now, I'm a reporter
for a new gossip rag,
and I've got some dirt on
half the city councilmen
and the new archbishop.
It's in my car.
What do you say we go out back
and you can take a
peek what's in my trunk.
I say, you keep talking like that,
I just might follow you anywhere.
[CHUCKLES]
Ray, I'm outside with...
Benjamin, car's this way.
You know, on second thought,
why don't we ditch the club.
How 'bout, you and me,
we go someplace with
a little less company.
Actually, I think we
already have company.
Your eyesight's 20/20 doll.
Those are Mickey Cohen's boys.
But after going through Hell,
I ain't afraid of nothing on this Earth.
You might wanna jump outta the pot.
Water's about to boil.
[GROANS]
[REVOLVER HUMS]
Drop the gun, put your hands in the air.
[SIRENS WAIL]
Stand down, son, we'll
take it from here.
Feels weird to be
foiled by the good guys.
What's the plan B?
Well, it looks like you're
going downtown, Sergeant.
Tomorrow is huge.
We're making a line of dressy sneakers.
- It's gonna be so major.
- That's nice, dear.
So, Behrad, any girlfriends
we should know about?
No, Ma, there's not really
much time for dating,
given all the coursework.
But you need to take your nose
out of your books on occasion.
Otherwise, you'll never find
a nice Persian girl to marry.
[UPBEAT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[CLEARS THROAT] Behrad.
[SPEAKING FARSI] _
By all means, add to your entourage.
How much does worshipping
you pay these days?
My team is my extended family.
They help me manage a multi-platform,
multimillion dollar brand,
and I didn't even have
to go to business school.
Wow.
Is that the air totem in the painti...
[KICKS CHAIR]
Why, yes it is, professor.
How do you know about
our family heirloom?
Behrad told me.
Really, what did he tell
you about the air totem?
Just that I was so broken up
when I found out it was stolen.
We keep the painting up as a memento.
Even though it's lost,
I feel like it's still
here with us today, in this very room.
[CHOKES]
So, Sara, do you want
us back at the ship
for a post-mission debrief?
No, mission ain't over yet.
I need you guys posted at the club.
Keep your eyes peeled
and your ears open.
Great.
What?
Hmm? [LAUGHS]
You wouldn't understand.
That you were the boss
of a massive government organization,
and now you do diddly-squat.
Wow, take it back, Rory.
You just summed up my life perfectly.
Can I get a double?
Bugsy is gonna be pretty hard to catch
if he still has that gun.
Well, we best get our hands on it pronto
because only a weapon from Hell
can eliminate a Hell-spawned encore.
And that gun may be useful
in more ways than one.
Oh, good thing I have
my best man on the job.
- [JAZZ MUSIC]
- _
♪♪
Jeannie was right.
Bugsy really does have
the LAPD in his pocket.
I'm gonna have to figure out
another way to get that gun.
Can I take those arrest
summaries off your hands?
I'm on my way to records.
Sure, ah, that'd be super helpful.
Thanks.
It's tough to watch the department
kowtow to a gangster.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Oh, good cops like you are hard to find.
Name's Sullivan.
Palmer, Ray Palmer.
Well, see you 'round, Sergeant.
Officer Sullivan.
Can certainly set your
watch to that fine constable.
We need a plan B.
If Ray can't get this gun,
the last thing we need
is Bugsy blasting anyone
else out of existence.
Yeah, well, maybe a
stretch of the old legs
and some fresh air will
give us some clarity.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- _
I think I know how to get Bugsy's gun.
So you got my message.
Look, if this is about the
money your friend gave me,
I already spent it.
I knew you were on the grift
from the moment I laid eyes on ya.
And I never once fell
for that Yankee accent of yours.
[LAUGHS]
Well, all right then.
Well, now that we've dropped
the charades, tell me,
what is your angle?
I wanna take Bugsy down.
Free this town from his sway.
The only way to do that is to
destroy his blackmail stash.
Webb said he'd found
it, but I'm guessing
Bugsy killed him for snooping too close.
Well, that's bad news for
Webb and good news for me,
because I know where the stash is.
Well, aren't I the
luckiest girl in the world.
What do you want in exchange?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I want Bugsy's gun.
You lookin' to ice Bugsy?
No, that bloke's not worth it.
I'm aiming at the person
who brought him back.
Then we have a deal.
You get your guy, I get my freedom.
Now, how exactly are you planning
on stealing Bugsy's prized weapon, eh?
When we kiss...
I'll press my hand against his chest,
and then I'll run my hand
all the way down his body,
and then I'll grab it like this.
[GRUNTS]
[JAZZ MUSIC]
♪♪
[FURNITURE CRASHING]
- [JAZZ MUSIC]
- _
- You wanna know a secret?
- No.
I just turned in my
keys for my place in D.C.
Yep.
Everything I own is now stuffed
inside a Time Bureau
softball league duffel bag.
I am essentially homeless, Rory.
Congratulations,
you're part of the team.
Uh-uh, I'm a vagrant. A vagabond.
Mm, no job, no rent, no kids.
- Uh-uh.
- Perfect.
It's just... I had so
many responsibilities
at the Time Bureau. People needed me.
You get it?
You see that clown sitting over there?
The one riddled with responsibilities.
Look at him.
He's miserable and he's welcome to it.
I just can't get over the fact
that nobody needs me to do anything.
Wait.
Nobody needs me to do anything.
You two still at the Blue Iguana?
Uh, yes Captain, just following orders.
Great, I need you and
Ava to create a diversion.
Clear the place out.
I'm gonna draw Bugsy back to
the club so we can capture him.
I can do that.
[APPLAUSE]
Always a pleasure, Chief.
The lobster was excellent.
Stop right there, Mr. Siegel.
What's the problem, officer?
I, uh, I just need to
search you before you leave.
This is highly irregular.
Actually, it's quite regular.
A new directive just came
down from Deputy Chief Wiggum.
- It's just gonna take a second...
- [PHONE RINGS]
What are you doing, son?
Mr. Siegel, call for you.
Sounds urgent.
Siegel here.
Benjamin, darling. It's me.
Your new favorite source
for all things juicy.
Lance, what's the rumpus?
Must be pretty heavy if you're
calling me on the blower.
Well, something is
going down at your club.
Primo blackmail material.
Better leg it over here PDQ.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS] Sorry, guys.
Bugsy's leaving the station
and he still has the gun.
No worry, big man.
I've got it covered.
You take care now, Mr. Siegel.
Hey, baby.
[ENGINE REVS]
You back to working the beat, Sergeant?
Ha, I was just admiring
Mr. Siegel's automobile.
I guess crime really does pay.
Not today it doesn't.
'Cause I'm gonna do something about it.
You in, or what?
[BELL BIV DEVOE'S "POISON"]
♪♪
♪ Girl, I must warn you ♪
♪ I sense something strange in my mind ♪
♪♪
♪ Situation is serious ♪
♪ Let's cure it 'cause
we're running out of time ♪
Tell him, girl.
♪ It's oh so beautiful ♪
♪ Relationships, they
seem from the start ♪
♪♪
♪ It's all so deadly ♪
♪ When love is not
together from the heart ♪
♪♪
♪ It's driving me out of my mind ♪
♪ That's why it's hard for me to find ♪
♪ Can't get it out of my head ♪
♪ Miss her, kiss her, love her ♪
♪ That girl is poison ♪
♪♪
♪ Never trust a big butt and smile ♪
♪ That girl is poison ♪
[CROWD BOOING]
- What's going on in there?
- Oh, it's awful.
The worst thing I've seen in my life,
and I was there when
the Hindenburg went down.
♪ Bum bum ba dum bum ba dum ba dum ♪
♪ She's driving me out of my mind ♪
That's my girl.
- ♪ Hard for me to find ♪
- [MICROPHONE FEEDBACK]
♪ I can't get it out of my head ♪
What now?
We wait and hope that
John gets that Hell gun
before Bugsy gets here.
♪ That girl is poison ♪
Right.
See you at home, baby.
That was horrible.
Come on, sweetheart,
let's get out of here.
I gotta go. Something's stirring.
What is all this?
♪ A warrior ♪
You bring me all the way
down here just so I can watch
some no-name dame
humiliate herself on stage?
First of all, she is not a no-name.
That is my girlfriend.
And second, she is not
humiliating herself.
- Yes she is.
- She's enjoying herself.
So this was just a lousy trick
to get me down here.
There's no dirt, is there?
The dirt is you.
You're supposed to be dead.
Instead you're blackmailing
your way to the top.
After I came back, I realized
that violence and murder...
that only gets you so far.
Information.
That's the real power in this world.
Well, whatever your deal is,
you're screwing up history,
and it is my job to stop you.
So you don't have to go to Hell,
but you can't stay here.
Oh, I ain't going anywhere, Lance.
Jeannie!
[GUNSHOTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GROANS]
Ugh.
♪ Never trust a smile ♪
Should we tell her the mission's over?
Nah, let her finish.
♪ Bum ba da bum ba da ba da ba sing ♪
- [SOLEMN MUSIC]
- _
♪♪
So embarrassing.
Dragon girl. Is this when
you became famous?
Yep, first agent when I was 11.
He was a real piece of work.
Eventually, I took
control of everything.
- Can I ask you something?
- Hmm?
When you first saw me,
did you feel like we met before?
Maybe. I meet a lot of fans.
No, I mean, we met in another life.
Oh.
Yeah, I totally got that vibe.
Oh, so it's not all in my head.
I feel like I've been living
out this Taylor Swift song,
but it feels crazy good.
We're definitely connected somehow,
but something feels off.
I think the you I remember
wasn't a professor.
Come on, I know Behrad's been lying
to my parents about
business school for years.
I only wanna make sure
that he's been taking
really good care of our family's totem.
Which he has been, right?
[MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
Yo, dude, we're cutting the cake,
and they're asking
for the special guest.
Come on.
Chill, B, your friend
and I were just talking.
- Sure you were. Let's go.
- Good talk.
- Bye, Professor.
- I warned you.
Bye. Stop pushing.
_
How did you figure out
what these numbers meant?
I spend more time in graveyards
than I care to admit.
Elysian is a common moniker for them.
And those numbers, they represent
a specific location for
a particular gravestone.
There's something here.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Let's see, shall we?
- [GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
That's it.
Well, aren't we a
pair of jammy bastards.
Now, it's time to destroy.
Forget the matches.
Step away from the briefcase.
Oh, hold on now, love.
We're all on the same side here.
There's only one side I'm on, John,
and that's mine.
You told me you wanted
to destroy that stash
so that you and everyone else
in the town could be free.
Yeah, but I figured why destroy it
when I could just use it for myself?
I'm sick and tired of people
taking advantage of me.
With this briefcase,
I'll finally have some
real power around here.
Look, I understand your anger,
but as soon as you touch Bugsy's dirt
then you'll have a target
on your back just like him.
But if you leave now,
you can start over,
have a new life.
Look, you don't have
to do this, Jeannie.
Just walk away.
Walk away?
Do you really expect
me to give up this power
after being so powerless my whole life?
You know what? You're right.
Who am I to tell you what to do anyway?
See, it's working already.
Okay, what do we do now?
Once Bugsy's girl gets back
to her car with the stash,
we're gonna take care
of the whole situation.
Take... what do you mean "take care of"?
You really are a straight
arrow, aren't you?
Wait a second, you
wanna destroy the stash
and Jeannie along with it?
W... why?
She's just collateral damage.
It's the cost of war.
You're a police officer.
Did you ever hear the one about
the last good cop in Los Angeles?
It didn't end well for him.
Well, how's this for an ending?
Get outta the car. Now.
You sure you wanna do that?
[TAPPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
If you were coming
all the way to Burbank
just to meet up with
your mobster friends
and kill Jeannie, why
even bring me along?
'Cause we needed a fall guy.
Come on, boys. Drinks are on the LAPD.
[LAUGHTER]
Well, I guess this is where
we say good-bye, Johnny.
It's been swell.
Five bullets left. Use them wisely.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- [CAR HORN HONKING]
- No, no!
[CAR HORN HONKING]
♪♪
Jeannie.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
John, Jeannie.
Jeannie.
Jeannie! Jeannie, no!
[ENGINE STARTING]
They killed her.
Forget it, Ray.
It's Burbank.
[SOMBER JAZZ MUSIC]
♪♪
[BEEPING]
Hey, holding cell still works.
Who are you people?
You communists?
Idiots.
I know you're probably
pretty confused, Mr. Siegel,
but you might as well
make yourself comfortable
because you may be here for a while.
I should blast you straight to oblivion,
you damn bastard.
You made Jeannie's life miserable
and now she's dead because of you.
I may have corrupted a wannabe starlet.
But you? You created a real monster.
Astra Logue.
You know what?
It's funny that you mention her.
I was just about to go and see her.
John, if you're about to do
what I think you're gonna do,
then you'd better be sure.
Hand him over, big man.
Go on.
Yeah, that's it, big boy.
See, you're my ticket to Hell.
[GRUNTS]
Ah.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Flesh become my flesh,
soul become my soul.
Hades, firstborn of Cronus and Rhea,
I call upon you.
Light her up, big man.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hey, Astra says you're banned.
Is that so?
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
You just can't stay away, can you?
Careful, he's still got one bullet left.
Oh, I appreciate your concern, Benjamin,
but I'm not worried about him.
We're old friends, aren't we, Johnny?
So why don't you tell me
what you came all the way down here for?
I came all the way
down here to tell you...
That I'm not giving up on you.
And even if it takes me
till the end of my days,
I promise you that I will find a way.
Another meaningless promise
made by the great John Constantine.
- You've gone soft.
- [LAUGHTER]
Not that soft.
This one's for Jeannie.
[YELLS]
I'll be seeing you around, love.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
So what happened down there?
I need a drink.
Not this time.
Is Astra...?
When I got down there, I was swarmed.
Astra had the drop on me.
She knew I was coming.
- And the gun?
- It's gone.
We'll figure out another way.
Yeah.
Hey, whatever really happened
back there with Astra,
I'm sure it wasn't easy.
What are you talking about, big man?
Just so you know, if I
had taken care of Nora
back when we all thought she was evil,
we wouldn't be happy
and together right now.
Oh, I had the chance
to pull the trigger,
to end all this.
But I couldn't do it.
What's all your grinning about?
Just happy there's still
good guys out there.
Even if one of them is a
master of the dark arts.
You know, you're wrong about me, Ray.
But I will save Astra,
and you should know
it's just as much for me
as it is for her, all right?
Hey, don't give Ava a hard time
for getting on stage, all right?
I don't want her to be too embarrassed.
She's not gonna remember a thing.
[SIGHS]
Well, hello! Ha.
Where's my invite to this
party, huh, Mickey boy?
I spat in that.
Old prison habit.
Mmm.
I cannot believe that I sang
in front of all those people.
I w...
I was awesome.
I killed it. I k...
And did you see my backup band?
They were like, "Ooh, tsh tsh, mwah".
Uh, please, please tell
me somebody got a video.
- Actually, we...
- Uh-uh.
Mm, and another thing.
Seriously, Sara, I love you so much.
Working that side mish with Rory
was way more fun than running
any stupid Time Bureau.
Like "responsinilities".
Wha...? Who needs 'em.
Oh, good babe, I'm glad you had fun.
Just know there is no
small role on this team.
Right, Rory?
Right.
[SNORING]
Mm-kay, night-night, sweetheart.
Look, there is more to Zari
than you give her credit for.
She is buried down deep inside
underneath all that fame.
You were getting' played, man.
Don't feel bad.
She does this all the time.
I know who you are.
- You do?
- Yeah.
The more we talked, the
more you looked familiar.
Then I realized where I knew you from.
The Waverider.
What's a Waverider? No.
Heyworld.
Tell me that's not you there
in the star spangled outfit.
In fact, you were both there.
That's totally you, Behrad.
Can't believe I never noticed it before.
What I don't get is how
Heyworld was 24 years ago,
but you two haven't aged a day.
What the hell is going on?
Zari, you've finally lost it.
You accuse me of being a fake,
but you're the one living a lie.
Maman, Baba...
Okay, shh. Just hang on.
No, I will not hang on.
It's time they finally heard the truth.
[BEEPING]
What the hell? Where am I?
You are on a 22nd century
timeship, designation WR2059.
Currently situated in the temporal zone.
Hey, guys, who's your friend?
We can explain everything.
Yeah, ya better.
Who are you people?
Guys, meet Zari.
She's my sister.
Whoa, oh, oh. Help!
Help! [WHIMPERING]
Help!
[QUIETLY] ♪ That girl is poison ♪
- Ahh!
- ♪♪