[SOFT UPBEAT MUSIC]
All right, Legends, let's
get this show on the road.
Can't let this immortality
buzz go to waste.
For your convenience, I
started a countdown timer.
23 hours and 45 minutes
to save my brother.
- You're welcome.
- All right, you heard the lady.
Clock is ticking.
Yeah, let's get back to the ship
and fire up the Loom
before it's too late.
Has anyone seen Gary?
Because someone at your party
has stolen my Shadow Stone.
So if you come across
a disembodied voice
floating around, crying out like a baby,
then that's your culprit.
Yeah, Gary went back to the ship.
His Bunny has IBS.
- Yeah, and serious gas issues.
- [CAN CRUNCHES]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Ooh.
Wow, that is some
arctic breeze blowing in.
Why are we in England?
Where the bloody hell's the portal?
[SIGHS] Has anyone seen Astra?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
How's your tummy, my bunny-wummy?
[SQUEAKS]
Gideon, can you do me a favor?
Can you fabricate more
veggies for Gary Junior Two?
[SQUEAKS]
[SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Gideon, you there?
♪♪
- Huh.
- [SQUEAKS]
Gary, the ship's compromised.
They're shutting me down...
[POWER THRUMS]
♪♪
[ENGINE ROARS]
If Gideon is down, then
who's flying the ship?
Oh, come on, are you
not off your trolleys?
I mean, why would Astra
steal the Waverider, eh?
I know we're "friends" with her now,
but maybe she wanted to use the Loom.
Or what if my sisters got to her?
If they get control of
the Loom before we do,
we'll never get a chance
to bring my brother back.
Okay, let's all just keep our cool.
Gideon, what's going on?
Gideon?
Okay, no Gideon.
Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.
We'll figure this out.
[DRAMATIC MUSICAL SPIKE]
What just happened? Did
you have another vision?
Uh, no, it's, um... no, it was nothing.
As in you saw nothing, or what?
It... it was just a... a flash,
and then it was nothing.
I think it's the Chalice.
It's probably messing with my powers.
So what, now you're just blind?
- That's not helpful.
- Come on, that's insensitive.
[GASPS] Wait, wait, wait.
I think I just came up
with an amazing plan.
Rip set up Time Bureau safe
houses all over the world,
some of which are still standing...
like the one in London, yes?
We go there, we get a Time Courier,
it'll to take us to the Waverider.
- Yes.
Yeah, babe. That is a perfect plan.
And you know what?
We're gonna do it,
we're gonna go to London,
because we are immortal superheroes.
- Except me.
- Except for Zari.
And nothing is gonna stand in our way.
We're immortal, and we're superheroes,
and we have to wait for the bus.
Ugh.
Well, at least Constantine
got us these nice, warm clothes.
We're ready for anything, right?
- Yeah, like a pheasant hunt.
- [CHUCKLES]
But in our defense,
we do look pretty good.
Okay, tell me this.
How do you live here and not have a car?
Never needed one, love.
Always bummed a ride.
So exactly how far is it to London?
Well, according to my
phone, it says 275.8...
Miles or kilometers?
Doesn't matter. It's far.
When is the bus supposed to get here?
According to the schedule,
it'll be here in either
one minute or three hours.
Wait. Guys, is it a holiday?
Is it a holiday?
Ah, finally.
- Yes.
- There we go.
- Okay.
- Oop.
[SOFT UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪♪
Hold up. Who's paying the fare?
- Does anyone have any money?
- No.
Uh, sir, I know this sounds ridiculous,
but the fate of the world
depends on us getting on this bus.
I don't care who depends on who.
When I'm driving this bus,
everyone pays their fare.
Have it your way.
- [GRUNTS]
- [YELPS]
Well, come on!
♪♪
I really am so sorry, sir.
Believe it or not, we're the good guys.
♪♪
Bollocks!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Thank you for delivering
this lovely timeship.
And Atropos, thank you
for shutting off that
aggravating talking computer.
She thought she was so witty.
[SIGHS] You don't have to thank me.
It's not like I had a choice.
You called in your favor, after all.
Everything comes at a price, Astra.
I gave you a shot at
killing John Constantine,
and you squandered that.
You drank from the Chalice of Dionysus.
You're immortal for a day and
can operate the Loom of Fate.
Are you asking me to work with you?
Because I'm not hearing a question.
Fine, I'll join you,
but I have some demands.
- Demands, really?
- Yeah.
Now I've experienced
life on Earth again,
some things have gotta
change, like prunes.
Disgusting. I want them gone.
And dogs?
They should stay puppies forever.
Oh, and there's just one more thing.
I want to bring my mother back to life.
Let's kill her.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm immortal, remember?
For now.
Astra's friends will be
searching for us by now.
Do something productive
and take care of them
while I chat with Astra
about this list of demands.
♪♪
Now, tell me about these prunes.
Um, should I tell Mick
that he's driving on the wrong
side of the road, or just...
No, definitely not.
It'll just confuse him more.
Okay.
Speaking of driving,
maybe you should run
point on this mission.
What?
[STUTTERS SOFTLY] Is
this because you're blind?
Because you totally
killed it at beer pong.
Thank you, but now that I
can't see the future, you know,
just thinking I'm maybe more
useful as a foot soldier.
And plus, you're exactly
who the team needs right now.
Uh...
okay, fine, but this is only temporary,
because as far as I'm concerned,
we are co-captains for life.
Always.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
♪♪
[SOFT OMINOUS MUSIC]
[SPEAKING ANCIENT GREEK]
♪♪
[OMINOUS ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Oh.
Who's that?
♪♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
- We're gonna get your brother back.
- _
We're just taking, you
know, the scenic route.
[LIGHTER CLINKS]
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
You must be joking. What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just having a little
chin wag with an old friend.
- Come on, give it here...
- This is not your friend.
I thought you quit. Why
are you starting again?
Because I trusted Astra,
and then she betrayed me
by siding with Charlie's sisters.
You know once they use the Loom,
we're all as good as dead, anyways.
This doomsday act is getting super old.
Look around.
The sky hasn't fallen,
the world is still here,
and for whatever reason,
the cabal of mystical seamstresses
hasn't started spinning yet,
which means we still
have time to stop them.
So just don't do that.
- Fine.
- So gross.
♪♪
[BRAKES HISS AND HORN BLASTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[WIPER LEVER CLICKS]
[WIPERS WHIR AND SQUEAK]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Oh, damn, Mick. You killed her.
No, I didn't.
- How do you know?
- She's moving.
♪♪
Uh, uh, ma'am, maybe you
should just stay down.
Are you okay?
♪♪
- [SNARLS]
- ALL: [SHOUTS]
What is it?
[SNARLS]
Punch it, punch it!
Nice one.
Well, we've seen this
before in the forests
when Atropos was chasing us.
My sister will do everything
she can to stop us.
Then we're probably gonna start seeing
a lot more of these zombies soon.
- Or now.
- Hmm?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ZOMBIES SNARLING]
Let's go!
♪♪
[RUSTLING]
[SNARLING]
[GUN BLASTS]
♪♪
[BATTLE CRY]
[TEETH CLINK]
♪♪
- [PANEL CRACKLES]
- Oh, come on, really?
Ew.
♪♪
What the hell, John?
Now you have a death wish?
Oh, come on. Don't be daft.
See, apparently the good thing
about having a damned soul
is that these zombies
aren't interested in me.
[SNARLS]
- Ew, ew, ew.
- [CHUCKLES]
Cool demo. Can you do something now?
Yeah, okay. Watch.
[FLAMES WHOOSH]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
All right, team. We
gotta stick to the plan.
Let's get this bus up and running
before more of these come back.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SQUEAKS]
Maybe this cable will
get Gideon back online.
♪♪
Gideon?
Oh.
Should've paid more
attention in computer science.
[ELECTRICITY ZAPS AND SIZZLES]
[ELECTRICITY ZAPS]
- Wake up, sleepyhead.
- [GASPS]
[PEACEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
Are you an angel?
Am I dead?
Oh, you're not dead, Gary.
And I'm Gideon.
- You're Gideon?
- Mm-hmm.
But you're so...
you're so...
human.
Are you real?
Well, I could explain, but
it wouldn't matter one bit.
Now listen to me very carefully,
because you have a rather
important job to do.
- I do?
- Yes.
You must hide those very
important and powerful rings
from those evil sisters.
The fate of the world depends on it.
Now, come on, Gary.
It's time to get to work.
Guys, come on. We've
got to keep moving.
What if my sister sends
something else our way?
Well, the engine's
busted after the fight,
and the fuel pump's got no power.
Even if we fix the pump,
all this leaking fluid tells
me this is a lost cause.
Okay, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, relax.
Remember when we all worked together
to defeat a Time Demon?
We can make it to London
if we just work together.
All right, how long is it
gonna take to fix the engine?
- An hour.
- Maybe two.
To be honest, I don't know
anything about mechanic stuff.
All right, we're running out of time.
You live around here. You must
know someone with a car.
Uh, yeah, I might know a bloke.
Great.
Wait, Zari, shouldn't you stay with us?
You're not immortal.
[SIGHS] Look, I can't just
sit here and do nothing.
- What...
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I got her, it's fine.
- Hey, no, no, no, no, no.
Where are you guys going?
We're not supposed to split up.
It's not a part of the plan.
Astra, dear, we have been
very patient with you,
especially considering you betrayed us
without saying a word.
You betrayed me first.
Besides, I had to take my
destiny into my own hands
and try to bring my mother back myself.
And I appreciate your gumption,
but I'm afraid you don't
fully grasp what that means.
Right now my mother is dead.
I would like her to be alive.
Fairly simple concept.
But as you know, life as
a human is very difficult.
If you insist on having a
normal life with your mother,
you will be bound to
the rules of nature,
which are not kind to humans.
See for yourself.
[GASPS]
[COUGHING AND WHEEZING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[EKG FLATLINE TONE CHIMES]
[CRIES]
[GASPS]
♪♪
Why would you show me that?
Because that is what is going to happen
if you bring your mother back.
Life as a human is a life
of pain and suffering.
Constantine promised to
bring your mother back
as if it would solve all your problems,
but what he didn't tell you
was you're just
postponing the inevitable.
Why bring your mother back
only to lose her all over again?
Look, I couldn't just sit
in that bus and do nothing.
Well, I suppose it's good
to go through the motions.
At least it gives you
the illusion of control.
Yeah, I'm not just going
through the motions.
I'm actually doing
something to save my brother.
Yeah, and I was actually
trying to help Astra,
and look what happened there.
You may see no point in
trying, but I'm not giving up.
Have you ever considered the possibility
that your brother's fate
is doomed in every timeline?
Apparently, this bloke Rip
Hunter used to say that,
you know, certain things
are just inevitable.
Go to hell, John.
You know, I've been
there and back, love.
Look, I'm just trying to save
you the disappointment is all.
You know what? Let's
just walk in silence.
Cool? Cool.
Yeah.
Real smooth, Johnny. Real smooth.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
She's so intriguing.
Gary, she's positively evil.
But she's so talented
with those weird knives.
Well, ever mind her many
splendid talents, Gary.
I must ask you to focus.
Pay attention now.
Okay, but how are we gonna distract her
to grab the ring so she doesn't notice?
[GASPS SOFTLY] I've got an idea.
Wish me luck.
[SMOOCHES]
Good luck.
♪♪
[SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
What's up?
I really don't think I
should've let John and Zari go.
What if we get the bus up and
running before they get back
or even worse, more zombies?
- Then what am I supposed to...
- Hey.
Don't sweat it if the plan falls apart.
Sometimes the best solutions come
when there is no plan at all.
Besides, Legends are
all about improvisation.
It's kind of like, uh,
freeform jazz.
Ugh, I hate freeform jazz.
Oh, me, too.
Uh, it sounds like we have company.
Whoa, I think those are soldiers.
Uh, maybe they can
help us get to London.
What'd I tell ya?
♪♪
- Oh, hey, guys. Hi.
- Hands up.
Oh, oh, we are so glad you found us.
Stay where you are.
They've got blood on their clothes.
They might be infected.
- But...
- No.
- No, it's not.
- No, no, no, we're not infected.
- [GUNSHOT]
- ALL: [SHOUTS]
Ava!
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GASPS AND SHOUTS]
[GROANS]
Oh.
[SNARLING] Ow!
[GROANS]
[BULLET CLINKS]
Ow.
My God.
These zombies can withstand headshots.
Since when do zombies talk, you idiot?
Super-zombies who have become sentient.
Round them up and take
them back to base camp.
♪♪
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Lachesis?
Yes?
The rings are gone.
♪♪
I don't understand.
How could this happen?
There must be someone else on the ship.
♪♪
You're right. Someone else is here.
And I know exactly who it is.
I got the rings. We
make an amazing team.
We should have our own spin-off.
♪ Gideon and Gary, having adventures ♪
♪ Solving problems
and saving the world ♪
Brilliant song, Gary!
You must teach it to
me once you've managed
to wrestle control of the Waverider
from those pesky sisters.
- I know how we can do that.
- Mm-hmm?
We'll blow up the ship.
Or perhaps we'll do something
just a smidge less suicidal?
Oh, that sounds like fun.
Let's track down a Courier
so we can jump the rest
of the Legends here.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's go to the lab and
make those Couriers ours.
Gary, you're making
me blush. [LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
Let's go.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC]
This is charming.
- [FOOT SPLASHES]
- [SIGHS]
How'd you hear about this place?
Well, back in the day,
Old Man Joe called me about
a demon-possessed '75 Fiat.
It was a right messy exorcism.
And a right crappy car.
Ah, now there's a beauty.
All right, come on.
We don't want to be out here
any longer than we have to be.
[ZOMBIES SNARLING]
What was that?
It's not a sound we want
to be waiting around for.
[SNARLING AND GLASS BREAKING]
Okay, come on, let's go. This way, go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Come on, quick!
Okay, I'll go find the van keys.
Yeah, all right, yeah. You do that.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
Okay.
Thanks, Old Man Joe.
[RASPS]
[SNARLING]
♪♪
[GAGS]
What is that infernal
racket? Are you all right?
Yup, yeah, I'm fine. Just... [SIGHS]
filing this away for future therapy.
[GAGS]
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
We better leg it to that chip van
before you become zombie fodder.
John, there's too
many of them out there.
But they're not interested in you.
You need to take the van,
find the team, and save Behrad.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no. That is a terrible idea.
Why, because you didn't think of it?
Because I'm not leaving
you here to die, all right?
♪♪
That's it.
Oh, and now you're good
with leaving me to die?
Well, yes to death, no to leaving.
You see, there was this spell
that the ancient Egyptians...
I don't need the history
lesson, John, just do it.
Yeah, all right, but it
means stopping your heart.
And when I do that, we've
only got a few minutes
before the rest of you stops.
It's risky, and anything can go wrong.
- [GLASS BREAKS]
- You know what?
This whole day has gone
wrong, so why stop now?
Why, indeed.
♪♪
You're making a huge mistake!
What sentient zombies
are this well-dressed?
Damn it, I promised Lita I'd
never get locked up again.
This stays between us.
Okay, I'm just gonna make up a speech.
About what, I don't know.
Just made it up on the spot.
Ava's lost it? She's lost it.
Shh, she's thinking.
Ah, okay! You know what, guys?
Wha... um...
we're not wasting any
more time in this tin can.
And let's try to get creative
and think about what resources we have.
Okay.
Look, we've got a guy
who turns into steel.
We've got a shapeshifter, right?
That's fricking amazing.
We've got a kickass blind assassin.
And a reformed thief
turned romance novelist.
Who you calling reformed?
- Oh, well...
- Whoa, wait a minute.
I've been locked up
in one of these before.
[GASPING]
There's a weak door...
down here somewhere.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR PANEL]
Ah.
Steel Boy, punch.
I'd be honored.
Well, wait, what,
so we're gonna just
jump out of a moving car?
Uh, yeah, well, you know,
we're not gonna die,
but it's really gonna hurt.
♪♪
Okay, who's first?
- You!
- Hey!
- [STEEL SCRAPES LOUDLY]
- Oh, God!
Outta here, sucker!
All right, then. Well,
come on, step right up.
- Got her?
- Yeah, I got her, Ava.
Oh, I'm actually glad I can't
see what's about to happen.
- Okay, and jump!
- [BOTH SCREAM]
This actually wasn't part of the plan!
[SHOUTS]
- [JOINT CRACKS]
- Ow.
ALL: [GROANING AND CRACKING]
- [POWERS WHOOSH]
- [SIGHS]
Well, Ava, as far as
inspirational speeches go,
I'd give that a gentlemen's seven.
Know what? I will take it,
because now we are 80 miles from London
- which is, you know...
- [JOINT CRACKS]
ow... closer than we were before.
- Yeah.
- We're never gonna make it.
Hey, never say never.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey! Can you help us?
[GRUNTS UNINTELLIGIBLY]
Don't stop, Wilbur! Zombies!
Ay, ay. Damn it.
[CAR PANEL THUMPS]
[KNEE CRACKS]
You're giving off a vibe.
Oh, man.
- Come on, babe, we gotta walk.
- I'm coming.
♪♪
All right, love, can you give
me a bit of room here, eh?
[CLEARS THROAT] Sure.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
♪♪
If I die, I can't believe
the last thing I'm
gonna see is your face.
[CHUCKLES] Well, better than
those zombies out there, eh?
- Debatable.
- [CHUCKLES]
Yeah? All right, love.
Close your eyes now.
Okay.
[TAKES DEEP BREATH]
[SPEAKING MIDDLE EGYPTIAN]
♪♪
[HEART BEATING]
[HEART BEAT SLOWING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
[GRUNTS]
[SNARLS]
♪♪
[SPEAKING MIDDLE EGYPTIAN]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[SPORADIC HEART BEATS]
[HEART BEATS ONCE]
No, no, no, no, no, no,
don't do this to me.
Don't do this to me.
Come on, Zari, come on.
Come on, don't do this. Come
on, come back to me, love!
Come back to me!
[GASPS]
Oh, come on.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Is this what a hangover feels like?
[ZOMBIES SNARLING]
♪♪
We need to get out of here.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
♪♪
- Got one.
- Smashing job, Gary.
Now let's go get your friends
so we can finish this
adventure once and for all.
Easy enough.
- [TENSE MUSIC]
- Drop it.
[GASPS]
She means it. She'll skin you alive.
[WHIMPERS] What are you doing, Astra?
Why are you working with them?
Now give us the rings.
We know you have them.
♪♪
Gideon, run! Save yourself!
[SQUEAKS]
The moron is speaking to the rabbit.
The rings are in your pocket.
Give them to us.
Gideon, help me.
I can't, Gary.
I'm just a figment of your imagination.
But you must believe in yourself
and don't give in, no
matter what they do.
[QUIRKY DRAMATIC MUSIC]
How could I give you the rings
if they were never really here?
♪♪
Trickery.
Yeah, I may have been electrocuted
by Gideon's mainframe,
but I could still do a
simple obfuscation spell.
Time for more persuasive tactics.
Ah!
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Those headlights are coming in fast.
All right, everybody.
Just be cool, yeah?
Try to act as un-zombielike as possible.
Maybe Mick should stand in the back.
Ooh.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Get in, losers. We're going Looming.
[CHEERS]
["RULE BRITANNIA"]
_
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
Uh, hello?
Ex-Director Sharpe here.
Who's manning this post?
♪♪
_
[DEVICE HUMS AND CHIMES]
[REGISTER BELL RINGS]
A-ha.
Well, cheers to this nightmare of a day
coming to an end soon.
I will drink to that.
Yeah, well, we're not out
of the woods, yet, love,
but you can sign me
up for a beer anytime.
♪♪
Yeah, John was right.
We are not out of the woods yet.
- Is it dead?
- Yeah, how did you know?
♪♪
Great, that's just great.
My brother's gone forever,
and the world's gonna end
because someone forgot to charge it.
Great.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
Smoke break?
Actually...
I quit smoking.
Again.
Mm, don't tell me.
You finally found something to live for?
There's no point.
The Fates are literally against us.
I mean, how else do you explain
an overnight zombie apocalypse?
Or the fact that we're now
at the mercy of a charger?
♪♪
You know, I gotta say.
All this doom and gloom attitude
really don't suit you, love.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you had a monopoly on doom and gloom.
No, no, no, I'm just saying, you know,
you stick to what you know best is all.
Yeah, I'm not gonna take advice
from a "professional"
exorcist with a savior complex.
[LAUGHS] Come on, I do
not have a savior complex.
Are you serious right now?
Oh, save me from my
demons, John Constantine.
Oh, well, what about you, then?
I mean, you talk about savior complex,
what with all your
self-help and advice videos,
saving your minions
from a life of drudgery.
I give my followers
something to aspire to.
Aspire to, really? What's that, then?
Oh, yeah, it's, uh,
being a superficial git.
If you think I'm superficial,
then why are you here with me?
Do you know what? I don't know.
I just think I haven't had
enough punishment for one day.
Punishment?
You should just go, then. Right now.
You want me to leave?
Because I will leave.
I will go right now and
I will not come back.
Good, great, leave.
I wouldn't want to be with you right now
if you were the last man on Earth.
Well, good, because I
wouldn't want to be with you
- if you were the last woman...
- [GROWLS]
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
So, where should we start?
Head, shoulders, knees, or toes?
How about none of those things?
You can hand me those rings
or you can give me your hands.
It is that simple.
This isn't you. You're not like them.
[YELPS]
You don't know a thing about me.
I do know that when you
had to choose between
staying in Hell or putting
your trust in the Legends,
you grabbed Ava's hand
and took a leap of faith.
♪♪
That was a mistake.
A moment of weakness
when I still believed I
wanted to see my mother.
Wait, you don't want your
mother to come back anymore?
Not if it means losing
her all over again.
Lachesis opened my eyes
and showed me her death
and what it would be like
if I brought her back.
You actually had to see your mother die?
Are you okay? 'Cause if I were you,
I... I... I'd be a big puddle...
Of course I am not okay.
It was bad enough losing
her when I was a kid.
But did this Lachesis lady
show you anything else?
Like, what about all the good
moments before she died?
Why bother?
Those memories would
be painful reminders
of what I would one day have to lose.
You must have some memories of your mom
when you were little that
make you smile, right?
Well, maybe instead of torturing me,
you could, I don't know, share one?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
You guys good?
Yeah. Feeling a little better.
Wow, are those yams?
Horrible, aren't they?
- [GROANS]
- Look, guys.
I know today was...
[TAKES DEEP BREATH] was rough.
I mean, you got shot in
the head, for Pete's sake.
Why'd you have to bring that up?
If I could, I'd spend
every day like this,
sitting around with my pals.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Aww.
Well, you can end every
day any way you like
with the Loom of Fate, mate.
You know, after we best your sister,
any one of us might be
called to use the Loom,
and you got to ask the question,
what kind of temptations we'd have.
I'm actually
pretty happy just flying
through time with you guys.
- I got my lady.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm pretty happy.
- Same.
I'd be a criminal again. A simple life.
You know, if Behrad were alive
and we were together and happy, I...
I don't know, I would use my talents
to make the world a more...
inclusive, better place, I guess.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Well, I, for one, would
throw a multi-continent rager.
[CHUCKLES]
Would you really, though, John-o?
I would, yeah.
There's nothing a little deeper,
a little closer to your heart?
♪♪
Oh, you know, uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
even after everything that's happened,
I'd want to do right by Astra, you know?
Make sure she was happy
growing up in a big house
and I could keep an eye on her.
♪♪
- Sure is nice to dream.
- I drink to that.
Cheers.
- OTHERS: Cheers.
- [GLASSES CLINK]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Okay.
What are you not telling me?
- Nothing.
- [SCOFFS]
Come on.
Let me guess, you didn't
really lose your powers, yeah?
You had a vision, and
you saw the future,
and you don't want to tell
me about what happened,
am I right?
The Courier's not gonna charge in time.
- In time for what?
- [EXHALES DEEPLY]
In time to escape before that
front door gets busted down
by what's outside.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC]
Why'd you lie to me, babe?
[SIGHS] Because my vision
ended with me dying here.
♪♪
In this pub.
Sorry, what?
Oh, my God, I can't
really think straight.
- I just...
- It's okay.
This is why I didn't want to tell you.
I didn't want to distract you
from getting the team to this moment.
Okay, so you've been saying goodbye
and just pushing me to
take over this whole time?
Yes, but it... it's a temporary,
goodbye, all right?
Because you guys... you're gonna...
you're gonna fix this, and
you're gonna save the day.
Did you happen to have
some sort of vision
of how we save the day, Sara?
Because that would be
really helpful right now.
I wish, but no.
I couldn't see anything past my death.
That was it.
Okay. And what if we don't succeed?
I have faith in you, babe.
And I have faith in this team,
and after I go, you
will fix it, I know it.
Um...
I don't want to freak
you guys out, but...
we're completely surrounded by zombies.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
[ZOMBIES SNARLING]
Looks like they're biding their time
until our immortality runs out.
Well, that means the
inevitable has arrived.
Kiss your immortality goodbye.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- _
♪♪
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
It's strange, the
memories you hold on to
when someone's gone.
♪♪
My mom loved strawberries,
and one year, we went
strawberry picking at this farm.
And we just ate them right off the vine.
They didn't even make it to the basket.
We just spent the whole
day stuffing ourselves.
Sounds like a cool lady.
She was.
Think about all the
strawberries you could pick...
- if you came...
- Okay, enough wheedling.
Just show me how to use this damn thing
so we can get help and I
can bring her back already.
Okay, yeah.
- So...
- Congratulations.
You're just as weak as any other human.
Your immortality's run out. Time's up.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
The rings...
or join your friend on the floor.
♪♪
We just have to hold out
until the Courier charges.
♪♪
[STRAINS]
That door's not gonna hold.
Once they're inside, I'll
hold them off as long as I can.
♪♪
Sara.
- Co-captains for life.
- Always.
♪♪
Come on!
[BELLOWS]
[COURIER BEEPING]
Bloody thing's still charging!
Hey, deadheads!
Over here!
♪♪
[FABRIC RIPPING]
[GRUNTS AND SHOUTS]
Sara!
[ZOMBIES SNARLING]
♪♪
- [CHARGER CHIMES]
- It's charged.
Charlie, you have to go.
Deal with your sisters and fix this.
- How?
- You outsmarted them
once before. You can do it again.
♪♪
[METAL CLANGS]
[PORTAL WHOOSHES]
♪♪
[ARM THUDS]
[MUFFLED SHOUTS]
- Gary.
- [MUFFLED SHOUTS]
[GASPS] Charlie, thank God you're here.
Your sisters took over the ship,
and they somehow convinced
Astra to work with them,
and then I convinced her she was wrong,
which was how she ended up on the floor.
Where's everyone else?
There's no time to explain.
Where are the rings?
Okay, yeah.
♪♪
We have to be careful.
Your sisters were just...
[GRUNTS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
What a pity.
You've come crawling back.
You're just in time, Clotho.
♪♪
I'm done running. [TAKES DEEP BREATH]
Now...
let's get to work.
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -