Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Only a weapon from hell can eliminate
- a hell spawn to Encore.
- We could use those.
Yeah, let's just get them
and get out of here.
The Loom of Fate is one
of the most powerful tools in existence.
It gave our sisters and me
control over everyone's lives.
None of this is how it should be!
Screw the Fates.
Stop being so obedient.
They're free!
Then I can't help them anymore.
[CAN HISSING]
_
- Oi, stop it!
- Free will rules!
Look, even I like the Blue Mush!
[SIGHS]
Bollocks.
The Fates are always watching.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
The world is perfect.
What kept you, sister?
Oh, you know, running a
TV empire is not as easy
as snipping threads, sister.
I was skeptical when
you pitched the idea
of the Legends on TV,
but they've helped pacify the masses.
Well, should we get started, then?
We don't want to keep
our worshippers waiting.
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS] Any luck finding the Loom?
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Yeah, I think we found it, all right.
Yeah, well, our ride
is still very much MIA,
so don't destroy the Loom
until we find the ship.
She has a weird voice, right?
[DRAMATIC WHOOSH]
- You okay?
- [STIFLED VOICE] Acid reflux.
Too much Green Mush.
Ava better find that ship,
because if we succeed,
then we're gonna have three
very angry Fates on our hands.
- Hey.
- God.
You're all from the TV, right?
Yes.
Can we get your autographs?
That depends.
How attached are you to your clothes?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Oh, my Fates! It's the Legends!
[SIGHS] Gary, Mona, you're okay.
It worked! You're out of the TV!
Okay, I've been dying
to ask... was I a Legend
or a lovable rogue or
a manic pixie dream boy?
Time dweeb! Where is the Waverider?
Is that like the "U.S.S. Faterider"
on "Star Trip"?
Yeah, sure. Have you seen it?
No, but I bet it's
in the Forbidden Dump.
Well, that sounds ominous.
It's where we send all
the contraband items.
I know 'cause I work
for the Historical
Sanitation Department.
Okay, great.
So, uh, how would we
infiltrate this Forbidden Dump?
[RORY YELLS]
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
The Waverider better be here!
If we stay, we'll raise suspicion.
Good luck, teammates!
I don't get it.
Fuzzy dice, waffle maker, massage chair?
This is all, like, the good stuff.
You know, if you make life bleak enough,
people become so focused on survival,
they forget they can revolt.
Start clicking, Mickey.
[CLICKING]
♪♪
[EXCITING MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪
You're not allowed back here.
Yeah, for good reason. Now!
[GRUNTS, YELLS]
Oh, nice one, love.
Hope they had benefits.
♪♪
Yeah.
- What do you need me in there for?
- You'll see.
All right, keep your eyes
out for any more guards,
and let's get rid of these two.
Okay.
All right, you take that
one, I take this one?
- [CHUCKLES]
- [SIGHS, GROANS]
[STRAINS] I hope I have benefits.
[ETHEREAL MUSIC]
What is your request?
More Blue Mush, please.
We shall weave it into the
fabric of time this afternoon.
[CHUCKLES] Thank you.
Thank you.
Speak, child.
Can you put my shows back on TV?
Well, they'll be back in a tic.
The actors just need a bit of a rest.
- That's all.
- Why?
Are they tired from the crossover?
What is a crossover?
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
The Legends are here.
♪♪
Clotho...
I have let you play your
childish game long enough.
It is time to grow up
and face the music.
The Legends are my friends.
Are they?
Time and again they have
sown chaos into this world.
Well, sometimes they screw
things up for the better.
I mean, think about it.
Encores, that wasn't their fault,
and they've been
mopping that up all year.
That's true. The Encores
are not the Legends' fault.
They're yours.
Ambitious villains are the product
of the chaos you birthed.
Look at these people now!
Do you see a future Joseph Stalin
amongst these lambs?
Of the three of us,
you always loved these
mortal creatures best.
What do you think they would want?
More choices or a lifetime of peace?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Peace.
♪♪
Wise choice, sister.
[BEEPS]
♪♪
I really wish you could see this, love.
Well, I can feel it.
♪♪
Oh, it's beautiful.
Now destroy it once and for all.
All right, we found the Loom.
John's working on it as we speak.
I'm standing guard. Any
luck finding the ship?
Yeah, we still haven't found it.
Mick, how do you know the
batteries in that thing even work?
For all we know, the Waverider
could be anywhere in this mess.
- [ALARM BEEPS]
- Shut the front door.
- No.
Do you hear that?
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
I hope you find the ship.
Now I'm gonna find my kid.
Okay, Mick will be fine on his own.
A spell to destroy something
as powerful as this,
it requires a
considerable well of magic.
[CHUCKLES]
I played hooky at Hogwarts.
I learned magic the hard way, John...
in hell, it's dangerous.
You're Natalie Logue's
daughter, aren't you?
[SIGHS]
Your mother, she was a
natural conduit for magic.
Her blood flows through your veins,
meaning that you're a conduit as well.
Close your eyes and
go with me, all right?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Gideon, bring all systems online.
- G, you there?
- Guys, we have a problem.
There is no Gideon,
which means no flying.
Damn it, Fates. Well played.
What would it take to get the
ship off the ground manually?
I mean, we'd need a superconductor
to transfer a huge surge
of energy to the Time Core.
We could look in the junkyard.
Or...
Huh. I have an idea.
- [SIGHS DEEPLY]
- [POWER SURGES]
You sure this is gonna work?
Honestly, I'm 60, 40,
but I believe in you.
60, 40?
You know, we haven't really caught up.
I don't know what you've been up to.
You spent a year in a totem.
- I mean...
- Guys, can we just focus?
- I don't want to do this.
- I know.
Steel up now!
[GRUNTS, YELLING]
♪♪
All's quiet on our end.
What do you guys see?
♪♪
[SIGHS] Sara, I've got
eyes on Charlie Fate
and Hippie-Mom Fate,
no sign of Psycho Fate.
Found her.
You bear the scars
from out last encounter.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
My scars only make me stronger.
♪♪
[CHUCKLES]
I need you to connect to your mother.
Now think back to the
last time you saw her.
Feel your mother's power.
Let it flow through you.
[SPEAKS IN ANCIENT GREEK]
That's good.
Now harness your connection.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ Are you going to Scarborough Fair? ♪
♪ Parsley, sage, rosemary, and thyme ♪
♪♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ To one who lives there ♪
Mom.
♪♪
It's working.
Natalie's helping us drain its energy.
♪ For once she was ♪
♪ A true love of mine ♪
I love you, Mommy.
♪♪
My sweet girl, you mother is gone.
- No, no, no.
- [WHIMPERS]
Forget her, or you will never
be the powerful woman.
I know you can be.
No! [GRUNTS]
- Whoa!
- [GASPS]
♪♪
Your power comes from me.
I alone am its master.
My power comes from my team.
John, open the door!
Behrad, now!
♪♪
[GRUNTING]
If my power comes from you,
then maybe I can do this.
♪♪
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
♪♪
[YELLS]
- Ava, where are you at?
- Pulling up now.
♪♪
Oh, Clotho, what have you done?
Go, go! Let's move!
[RAPID BEEPING]
I don't think we can hold this altitude.
Jump the ship!
Do it!
♪♪
[ALL SCREAMING]
- Oh.
- Ow.
[ALL GROAN]
- Wait, when are we?
- I don't know.
It's hard to see through all this trash
That's not trash.
That's some of history's
most iconic mementos.
I don't care what it is.
All I care is that I can see this face!
Mm!
Oh, I think my powers are gone.
Yeah, well, your powers
were bestowed by a God.
And once that God kicked the bucket,
then bye-bye powers.
Everything's back to normal?
Well, there's only one way to find out.
Gideon's down. Got to
do it the old-fashioned way.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
- All right, let's go check it out.
- All right.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Okay, well, this feels
like an improvement.
All right, this says
we jumped a few months.
Okay.
Well, it gives the world some
time to get back on track.
Hey, Fate, what's the
best way to work today?
- [WATCH BEEPS]
- The subway.
Hey, Fate, what should
I have for lunch today?
- [WATCH BEEPS]
- Two soups and a smoothie.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
[WATCHES BEEPING]
Uh, what are the chances
that everyone's watches
got a weird update over
the last four months?
I'd say one in a monkey's ass, love.
[SIGHS] Great.
So not only do Charlie and
her sister have the Loom back,
but now it's wearable.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Don't let choices get in
the way of your destiny.
Trust in fate with FateWatch...
your link to the Loom.
Always connected.
♪♪
I get the Fates rebuilt the Loom,
but how did they put it in a watch?
Well, that's why we're breaking
into the bloody temple...
get some answers.
- What the hell? It's a...
- History museum.
It can't be all that bad.
Well, it's certainly an
improvement on the Loom Temple.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
"Welcome to the History Museum.
Here you will learn
the truth about free will
and the atrocities it has
brought upon humankind".
Atrocities?
"Join us as we examine
the tragedies of choice
and the horrors of our past,
that we shall, with
benevolence and fate,
never suffer again".
So, they went from trashing history
- to weaponizing it.
- But why?
Well, if we want to know
what happened in the past,
we certainly came to the right place.
[SIGHS] All right, first up,
the Hall of Bad Ideas.
♪♪
- Huh.
- Grey has that suit.
♪♪
What the hell's a Shake Weight?
Oh, you don't want to know, babe.
♪♪
Cigarettes. Oh, come on.
The bloody cheek of them.
John, you died of lung cancer.
- Come on, you know they're right.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
- [LIGHTS CLICK]
♪♪
Whoa.
Okay.
What's the "Thong Song"?
Seriously?
"She had dumps like
a truck, truck, truck.
Baby, move your butt, butt, butt"?
♪ I think I'll sing it again ♪
Man, screw the Fates.
That is a Spring Break classic!
As a matter of fact,
I'll play it for you.
- I don't give a damn!
- No, you won't.
Come on, we have to go
to the Hall of Villains.
Later, Sisqó.
Okay, Other Z, I just
rerouted the nav system.
Anything popping up yet?
No. Nothing yet.
Hey, try patching it to
the secondary hard drive.
[ECHOING] Maybe we can pull
something up from the backup.
♪♪
Zari, come on! Run!
- Behrad!
- [GASPS]
Hey, you okay?
I don't know. It's...
[SIGHS] There were these guys.
A.R.G.U.S. agents, they had guns.
Huge guns.
I thought they were gonna shoot you.
[SIGHS]
I must've smoked something way off.
Oh, um, I thought you were... sorry.
I-I am.
No, I mean, totally. I know.
- Uh, it's just... it's weird.
- Yeah, I-I know.
Tell me about it.
Yeah, I'm hanging out with myself,
and myself, it has the
hots for John Constantine.
- You caught that, too?
- Yeah.
It wasn't something you smoked.
It happened.
You told me to run, and I did.
You didn't.
And then I died?
Every day since then,
everything I've done
has been to save you.
[LIGHTS CLICK]
♪♪
[LIGHTS CLICKING]
Whoa, this is, like, really uncanny.
Wait a second. Are
these villains ranked?
I don't know. Uh, who
do you have over there?
Uh, I got Vlad the Impaler,
but he's number 14.
Hey, if he's number 14,
who's number one?
♪♪
Oh, hey, Mick. You're okay.
What did you expect?
You left me... us behind!
Okay, calm down, please.
We were waiting for four months.
What took you so long?
Yeah, that's a question
for the other Zari.
Oh, book club lady. What
are you guys doing here?
Well, when you guys broke
the Loom, people panicked.
Suddenly all these
memories came flooding back.
- No one knew what was real.
- Or what to do.
They were so used to Fates telling them.
So Gary and Mona found me and Dad,
and we went into hiding.
- Hiding? Why?
- Because we're Legends.
Yeah.
And if you were listening
to what the Fates had to say,
- we were...
- God killers?
♪♪
I've been called worse.
Is it weird that I'm offended
that we're only number two?
Well, then who's number one?
[LIGHTS CLICK]
Charlie.
[GASPS]
No. No.
How... how did... you can't be here.
You have to leave right now.
What are you talking about?
Charlie, it's over. You
have to come with us.
No, Fate says to stay.
Fate... Fate says...
She's gonna kill you if she finds you.
You have to get out while you can.
Charlie, I'm sorry, but
you'll thank us later. John?
- [SPEAKING ANCIENT GREEK]
- No.
Charlie? Hey, it's okay.
- You're home, Charlie.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no. I have to go back.
She's gonna know!
Where's my watch? I need it!
That's how the Loom tells me what to do.
Why the hell do you listen
to that thing, Charlie?
Because I never should've
destroyed the Loom
to begin with.
I mean, greed and war. Human suffering.
Yeah, all those Encores
we were up against...
that's all on me!
I'm the Loom Breaker.
I'm the creator of chaos.
Charlie, that used to be
a badge of honor for you.
What happened?
We left, that's what happened.
You know, Charlie, you
were left all alone.
It's no wonder Lachesis
has got into your head.
Lachesis, she's my family.
Family sticks together.
Hey, we are your family,
and we're here now, all right?
Charlie, what happened?
Lachesis rebuilt the Loom.
She saved everyone.
She restored the peace.
♪♪
I replaced my own mother, John.
Well, summoning a
ghost can be difficult,
even under the best of circumstances.
No, I mean in hell.
I was terrified, helpless.
Lachesis found me. She took me in.
But the price for her
protection was my humanity.
She trained me to let go of
anything that made me feel.
And so I had to forget the
person I'd loved the most.
Ah, you were just a kid just
trying to survive, is all.
But I wanted to forget.
I saw what happened to
good people down there,
and I swore that would never be me.
You listen to me, all right?
You are still her daughter.
[CHUCKLES] Whose?
Natalie or Lachesis?
♪♪
Okay, I know you think free
will is a bad, scary thing.
So we did a little Dumpster diving
to give you some counterpoints.
Two words... The Beatles.
All right, they taught
an entire generation
that even during war and tragedy,
we can still make beauty.
Whilst also inspiring Charles Manson
to commit some of the most
brutal murders in history.
Also, they let Ringo sing
a song about an octopus.
Damn it.
- Okay.
- Just get out of the way.
"Mamma Mia! 2".
A celebration of free love,
reckless abandon,
and following your bliss,
even if that bliss means creating
a two-hour ABBA-palooza
where Cher plays Meryl Streep's mom.
Weren't the Legends
almost murdered by Napoleon
because of ABBA?
[WHIMSICAL ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Two words... "Octopus's Garden".
Gary, no.
♪♪
Would this have happened in
a world without free will?
I mean, seriously, Charlie.
Look, I'm a clone.
- She's a clone!
- You don't have to...
Anyway, think about all
the people on this ship.
Think about how they
came to be together.
Yeah, Nate's crazy conspiracy theory.
Mick's turn as a
futuristic bounty hunter.
Zari and B's dystopian future.
You in that disco outfit.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, come on, Charlie.
We were all in our own worlds,
but a twist in our stories
brought us together
and made us a family.
But humanity, they've
made so many mistakes.
Sometimes a mistake
is really just destiny.
What, you learn that being a Paragon?
No, I learned that being a person.
[SOFT MUSIC]
So what do you think?
Can we track the Loom
signal with that thing?
[SIGHS] Yeah, I just
need an external computer.
Something with GPS and Wi-Fi.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Well, that's perfect.
- Hey!
- [CLEARS THROAT]
♪♪
[GASPS]
We all make sacrifices
for the greater good.
Oh, really?
How much THC is running
through your system right now?
I'm self-medicating for my Loom anxiety.
You know, the brain processes
phone screens and drugs the same way.
Hmm. Ha!
That's why they're both so addicting.
Oh.
♪♪
[DEVICE BEEPING]
All right, the Loom signal
is coming from somewhere
inside the building.
[SIGHS] Okay.
[DRAMATIC WHOOSH]
♪♪
Okay.
John, other me?
We're gonna have to go floor by floor.
Well, that's a dodgy
spot for the Loom of Fate.
You know, I've hosted
many an exclusive party
in a place like this.
Antithetically, it
keeps the riffraff out.
Ah, hiding in plain sight.
Bloody brilliant.
Also, you can do whatever you want,
and no one needs to know.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
[JOHN MOANING]
Oh, God. This is weird.
[CLEARS THROAT]
All right, uh, no windows, thick walls.
That's where I'd stash my artisanal,
world-altering apparatus.
All right.
Guys, I think we found it.
[SIGHS] I'm the worst.
Timing is impeccable.
Sara, we got to the Loom,
but there is no Loom.
Blimey.
Gideon?
[GASPS] Gidget.
Currently running Fate Protocol.
I cannot be interrupted.
She's controlling everyone with Gideon.
The watches are just running a program
telling everyone what to do.
Wait, so there... there is no Loom?
We actually destroyed it.
Yeah, all we have to do
is shut down the network.
What, and inspire panic
when Fate abandons everyone all at once?
You know, my sister
was right about you lot.
You shoot first and play doctor later.
It won't matter anyway.
Lachesis will find another
way to keep her hooks in
because that is what she does best.
Okay, fine.
So we just expose her
for what she really is.
She's a fraud. We take her down a notch,
show everybody that she
can't control them anymore.
Yeah.
Charlie, she's your sister.
You're the only person
that can stand up to her.
♪♪
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
The museum is now open.
For centuries, after my
sister broke the Loom of Fate,
the world was filled with pain...
[WATCHES BEEPING]
ALL: Boo!
Horror...
- [WATCHES BEEPING]
- ALL: Boo!
Outrageous hubris and brutality...
[WATCHES BEEPING]
- Chaos!
- [WATCHES BEEPING]
But I could not let
people suffer any longer.
Alone, I rebuilt the Loom
and imprisoned my sister
so that now and forever
you may live in peace.
Here she is...
- [ALL GASP]
- Loom Breaker.
Creator of calamity.
Do you accept your fate?
No.
- [ALL GASP]
- What did you say?
♪♪
- I said no.
- [ALL GASP]
Your story is a load of crap.
Astra.
Where is Clotho?
That was always the question, wasn't it?
Did you ever love me,
or were you just looking
to replace your sister?
You wanted a mother.
I had a mother.
A woman who understood
that, to love someone,
you have to set them free.
Shut your mouth, dear, before
you say something you regret.
Make me.
Come on, all powerful Fate, smite me.
Strike me down!
[ALL MURMURING]
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Why should these good
people listen to you?
Because she's telling the truth.
- Oh, take forever.
- [ALL GASP]
How's it looking, Zaris?
I need to get into her
mainframe to shut her down.
This might take a minute.
You tricked everyone into
giving up their freedom
by making them afraid of the past.
That's rich,
coming from some of history's
most notorious criminals and killers.
[WATCHES BEEPING]
ALL: Shame! Shame!
All right! Yes, you're right.
We've made mistakes.
But sometimes things get
messed up for the better.
Take Marie Antoinette, for instance.
Her indifference caused
a revolution in France.
It gave them democracy.
Look, if you listen to her,
your stories are over.
They're right. Don't listen to me.
Listen to the Loom.
[WATCHES BEEPING]
Oh, come on, Zari.
Okay, I made it past the first firewall.
- Wait, is that...
- [POWERS SURGES DOWN]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Very well.
If it's chaos that you want,
chaos you shall have.
That's more like it.
[SPEAKS IN ANCIENT GREEK]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
That's our move. They stole our move.
Enjoy your free will, Legends.
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLADE CLINKS]
- [CRUNCHES]
- [SNARLS]
Stalin, Caligula.
If they get out,
they'll destroy the city.
Okay, got any ideas, Cap?
Oh, just a lot of bad ones.
♪♪
Let's go save the world.
[SISQÓ'S "THONG SONG" PLAYING]
This thing right here...
Is letting all the ladies know...
what guys talk about.
You know, the finer things in life.
[CHUCKLES] Check it out.
♪ Ooh, that dress so scandalous ♪
♪ And you know another
[...] can't handle it ♪
♪ So you shakin' that
thang like who's the 'ish ♪
♪ With a look in yer eyes so devilish ♪
♪ You like to dance
on the hip hop spots ♪
♪ And you cruise to crews
to connect the dots ♪
♪ Not just urban, she like the pop ♪
♪ 'Cause she was livin' la vida loca ♪
♪ She had dumps like a
truck, truck, truck ♪
♪ Thighs like what, what, what ♪
♪ Baby move your butt, butt, butt ♪
♪ I think I'll sing it again ♪
♪ She had dumps like a
truck, truck, truck ♪
♪ Thighs like what, what, what ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Let me see that thong ♪
♪ Baby ♪
- [YELLS]
- You again?
I see your manners have not
improved, you smelly peasant.
- [GRUNT, CLANG]
- Thief!
♪ Ooh, that dress so scandalous ♪
♪ And you know another
[...] can't handle it ♪
♪ So you shakin' that
thang like who's the 'ish ♪
I liked you better when you were a coin!
[CLANG]
♪♪
Ah! Not again!
[CLANG]
♪ Baby, move your butt, butt, butt ♪
- ♪ I think I'll sing it again ♪
- [SPEAKS EGYPTIAN]
These prats just won't stay dead.
- [GRUNTS]
- ♪ Let me see that thong ♪
Because they're not Hell weapons.
♪ That thong, thong,
thong, thong, thong ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
- Oh, thank God!
- Come on!
You got to get over yourself.
So 49% of life is crappy.
Fine. 51% isn't.
And that's the 2% that's
worth fighting for.
And how can you be so sure?
'Cause I am that 2%.
I'm the product of
complete and utter chaos.
I mean, my dad time-traveled
to his high-school reunion
and then slept with his
ex in a broom closet.
I don't think it gets much
more chaotic than that.
And then he tried to
erase you from existence.
But out of all of that
insanity, I got a Dad.
And I love him.
And life is messy, but that's
what makes it beautiful.
You want to go make a real mess?
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪♪
- We can't let them out.
- We can't keep them in.
Then why not destroy them?
Now grab a Hell weapon,
and let's drop the curtain
on these bloody Encores!
[CLANG]
♪♪
Hey, need a hand?
[YELLS]
♪♪
I should've been here with you.
You're wild and unpredictable,
just how we like you.
I guess it's time for me to stand
up to my sister once and for all.
Well, you're gonna need this.
[SIGHS] Good luck, Captain.
♪♪
Gideon, reboot Fate Protocol!
Gideon! Gideon!
It's over, Lachesis.
Our whole lives, you humiliated me.
You made me feel so small.
I tried to run away,
and you hunted me down.
What do you want?
And all that time...
I thought that I needed
your forgiveness.
But it turns out, it's you
who needs forgiveness.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪♪
I forgive you.
You, who have left me with nothing.
I gave you back your power.
I gave you back your immortality.
When you destroyed our
Loom, we all lost that gift.
I was a God!
Now I'm...
I'm nothing.
You're not nothing.
You're a human.
[SIGHS]
And that means that you
only have one life to live.
Now, don't go wasting that
trying to keep everything
under your control.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
♪♪
All right, that should do her.
Hola, konnichiwa, bonjour,
ni hao, ciao, marhabaan, zdravstvuyte.
- What's she doing?
- English detected.
Hello, what is your name, Captain?
Captain? Ooh, I like that.
Working on Giddy without me?
We tried comming you this
morning, but you didn't answer.
Oh, uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
Broken eye contact, flush cheeks?
Mm!
I mean, that's not fair.
I can't keep a secret from myself.
What are we keeping a secret?
Well, bro, when a man and a woman
love each other very much...
Are you talking about sex with Nate?
That's not a secret.
Now, you and John, that's a secret.
- Behrad!
- Behrad, nice.
[DRAMATIC WHOOSH]
[GROANS]
Hey, what's...
- What's happening?
- It's fine. I'm...
You're not fine.
You're bleeding!
- [GROANS]
- It's me.
By being here I'm causing
a temporal disturbance,
and it's killing you.
What does that mean?
It means there's two timelines
fighting for control of Behrad's life,
and in mine, you're dead.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I have to go back in the totem.
Uh-uh. No way.
Behrad-jan...
it's my turn to save you.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Can I text you in a totem?
No, there's no technology allowed.
Not even, like, a pager.
[VOICE BREAKING] I'm gonna miss you...
so much.
♪♪
Me too.
You know I have to do this, right?
♪♪
Yeah.
I just wish...
I wish I was leaving you with some...
something...
[CLEARS THROAT] You...
you are, and you have.
I mean...
I've lost everything at Heyworld...
all of our memories,
but you brought those back to me.
♪♪
Now I get to remember
the woman I love forever.
♪♪
No regrets.
- Hey.
- [SIGHS]
It's not fair. We
only just got you back.
Yeah, there has to be
something that we can do.
You already did.
You found me and brought me home.
♪♪
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
♪♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait,
there are two of them?
Mick.
- [CHUCKLES]
- So, uh...
how are you gonna get back?
Totem Master, remember?
[BRACELET WHIRS]
Bye, guys.
♪♪
I need so many drinks.
Yeah.
I know the perfect place.
- [FEEDBACK WHINES]
- We're The Smell.
Now welcome to the best show
of your lives, you wankers!
[CHEERS]
[PUNK ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪♪
♪ Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend ♪
♪ That's a street
that ends in a circle ♪
♪ The thing about circles
is they never end ♪
♪ So our friendship can be universal ♪
♪♪
♪ It's Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac ♪
♪ Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac ♪
Weren't they dead?
I mean, who hasn't died?
Whoa.
♪♪
Hey.
- Finally, some time travel.
- Mm.
I can't believe Charlie is
the lead singer of The Smell.
That's insane. They're my favorite.
Oh, and the Runaways.
We can go see them next.
It's a school night.
How about the weekend?
Yeah.
♪ Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac ♪
Excuse me, boss.
♪ Cul-de-sac ♪
♪♪
So, what's next for you, love?
I guess I'll give life
above ground a fair shot.
Ah, New York, Paris, Tokyo?
I was thinking about this haunted house
out in the sticks.
[CHUCKLES] Were you, now?
Got my rent covered.
Aha.
Finally.
All right, then.
Cheers.
♪ So, if you're looking
for a friend that's new ♪
[SINGS INDISTINCTLY]
♪ A friend like you ♪
♪ Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend ♪
♪ It's a street that goes on forever ♪
[SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
♪♪
♪ Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
That's my girl!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Guys, guys, guys, guys.
I can taste the moon.
And that's enough of these.
All right, all right.
We came, we partied, we conquered,
and now it's time to
go... it's time to go home.
- Home!
- Whoo-hoo!
Actually, guys...
I think this is the
end of the line for me.
- What?
- Wait, what?
- For reals?
- Yeah.
It's time for me to
just stay put for once
and set down some roots.
All right, well, if you
ever need anything...
and I mean anything...
you know where to find us.
Thanks, Captain.
[GROANS]
Once a Legend...
- Always a Legend.
- Thank you.
[CHUCKLES] Well, come on, all of you!
- [CHEERS]
- Get in here!
Oh, I love you!
- I'm really gonna miss you guys.
- We'll miss you.
All right, come on. Get out of here!
- Go and enjoy your vacations.
- Whoo!
- You've earned it.
BOTH: Vacation! Vacaciones!
- Vacation!
- I really like this spot.
[DRAMATIC WHOOSHING]
I think I'm gonna text Dion,
or is that too desperado?
This is why I don't have a phone.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪♪