Previously, on "Legends of Tomorrow..."
Come with us. The choice is yours.
What's next for you, love?
I guess I'll give life
above ground a fair shot.
Aha.
Finally.
I think this is the end
of the line for me.
- Ah, get in here.
- Aww.
Whoo.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- [BELL TOLLS]
- _
[QUIRKY, SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[DISTANT INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Piss off, you bloody guv'nor!
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
- [WHISTLING TUNE]
- _
[ENDS TUNE]
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
Punks, can't handle their liquor.
- Is that the ocean?
- No.
And you look like garbage.
I feel like garbage.
Why don't you, huh?
Where the hell were you last night?
I dropped Lita off at her mom's.
Oh.
Well, aren't you just a good dad, huh?
Ow.
Hey.
How come nobody tucked me into bed, huh?
- You're asking me?
- Yeah.
- Where's Sara?
- Don't know.
[STOMACH GURGLING]
Oh.
What do you... Gideon, where's Sara?
Sara Lance is not on
board the Waverider.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Sara's missing?
[SIGHS] Everyone's missing.
[SIGHS]
Gideon, who is on board?
Ava Sharpe, Mick Rory,
and several punks.
Uh, where could they be?
Skyemont.
- Why do you say that?
- It's on your hand.
- [GASPS]
- _
Mick, you're a genius.
Maybe it's from Sara. Let's go.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, God. Okay. No, no, no, no, no.
[EXCITING SYNTH MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
London, 1977.
The tangled knot of grime,
the stodgy monarchy.
This collision of punk
rock and aristocracy
slamming into each other like
two doomed worlds, this...
This is a lot at 7:00 a.m., John.
I'm glad you're in a good mood though.
Well, why shouldn't I be?
You see, my soul finally belongs to me.
Astra is redeemed,
and... [GRUNTS]
I get to wake up next to
you, you lovely creature.
Mm.
How are you feeling?
I think a no-strings-attached
hookup every now and then
- is good for the soul.
- [CHUCKLES]
Even if it's with a guy whose only coat
smells like booze and cigarettes.
- [LAUGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
Ugh. Oh, hel-lo.
Oh. Sorry, guys.
You, uh, missed the party.
Wait, are you two...
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Okay, sorry. I'm not judging, I just...
it's none of my business. I'm fine.
[GAGS]
It's an involuntary reaction.
We should burn the room.
Hey, at least we know
how to use protection, Pops.
[EXHALES SHAKILY]
Do either of you know where Sara is?
Uh, we seem to have lost track of her.
[SIGHS]
Oh. Someone did hand me this.
Is this anything?
[TENSE MUSIC]
I call.
♪ ♪
Full house, fellas.
That's three in a row.
She's a shady card sharp.
Oh, no. Just lucky.
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
What about now?
[HEAT GUN POWERS UP]
Still lucky and now also richer.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ ♪
I just love toying
with these poor mortals.
Oh, yeah, well you are one of
these poor mortals now, love.
Try remembering that the next time
you come across one with a gun, yeah?
Astra, have you seen Sara?
Uh, not recently. Maybe ask Behrad.
Yeah, where is my brother?
I can't believe how much
we have in common.
It's like we're riding the same
cosmic vibe, you know?
We just click.
It's like we were destined
to connect in this moment.
Hey, wrap it up Behrad.
We gonna pick this up later.
[IN BRITISH ACCENT] Cheerio.
Hey. Have you seen Sara?
- No.
- Ugh!
Maybe she's with Nate.
He was headed back to the club.
Back? Why?
We met Starman at the after-after.
Said he had to prep for
his show there tonight.
What the hell's a Starman?
Major T?
Ziggy Stardust?
Bowie!
He's talking about David Bowie.
[STRUMS]
See, my girlfriend's from another time.
Oh, like the future.
No. Well...
technically, yes, but
she's from the future
with a different timeline entirely.
Now she lives in a Totem.
And I'm forced to be at peace with it.
What's her name?
Zari.
Her name is Zari.
And I'm afraid I'm never
gonna see her again.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Hi, Zari.
Hey, guys. This is David Bowie.
Marvelous.
Okay, Nate. We're looking for Sara.
Is she here with you?
Last time I saw her was at the concert.
I figured she was with you.
- [SIGHS]
- ♪ She had an air of doom ♪
♪ I ain't tripping on mushrooms ♪
♪ The girl disappeared from this place ♪
Did he just say "disappeared"?
Sara disappeared. Is
he singing about Sara?
Deh, deh, deh... do not
interrupt David's process.
He's trying to cheer me up
by singing a song about Zari.
- 1.0, not you.
- Obviously.
[SIGHS] Still weird.
♪ She was a blonde haired punk ♪
♪ In a blue light funk ♪
♪ I'll always remember her face ♪
Guys, blonde hair.
Does that not remind you of Sara?
♪ Space girl ♪
Bowie! Cut that crap out!
Hey, listen, mate.
Is that song you're singing
about Nate's sad love life?
No, mate.
Are you singing about Sara Lance?
Is that her name?
Your friend who got sucked up
into a spaceship?
W... sucked into a spaceship?
Isn't it wild?
So you saw this with your own
beautiful, asymmetrical eyes?
I was filming that night on my Super 8.
See for yourself.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Okay. Film is developed.
Let's see what Bowie saw.
[PUNK ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend ♪
♪ That's a street that
ends in a circle... ♪
You lads are out of this world.
David freaking Bowie?
- You're a Smell fan?
- They're something else.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta... I gotta let you in
on a little secret, all right,
David freaking Bowie?
'Cause tonight... tonight, I am going
to propose to my girlfriend!
[EXCLAIMS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[SOFT BRIGHT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
Holy...
[LAUGHS]
Wish me luck.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Whoa.
She's a space girl.
- Ava...
- Okay.
Um, Sara's been abducted so,
uh, Sara's been abducted.
Uh... I'll be right back.
♪ ♪
So she's a mess.
All right, so let's just
give her some space.
In the meantime, what
do we know about aliens?
Literally nothing.
They're green.
Listen, you fools.
Sara's missing
because you guys were
partying last night.
We have to find her.
We're running out of time.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GASPS]
♪ ♪
[GAS HISSING]
[COUGHING]
♪ ♪
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[COUGHING]
♪ ♪
Time to get organized.
- Ava, you're back.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh. Whoa.
Here you go.
- Girl, are you okay?
- What?
I'm fine. Why?
Well, we just thought that...
You know, with Sara being lost,
you may wanna sit this one out.
Uh, she is not lost. She is pre-found.
There's a solution to every
problem including this one.
Wow, indexed. Thorough.
You are all the best of the best.
If we handle this
logically and rationally,
we will get Sara back, okay?
Right, well, uh, this a waste of time.
- I've got a better idea.
- Oh?
Yeah, ever since I rescued
her from Purgatory,
Sara and I have a psychic connection.
It'll allow me to locate her,
and everything I need is at the mansion.
Damn it, John. That's insubordinate.
- But I won't try to stop you.
- _
You know, he's actually most effective
not left to his own devices.
- I can just...
- Thank you, Z.
- We're gonna fix this.
- Mm-hmm.
- ♪ ♪
- _
Astra, would you mind keeping
them on mission please?
Uh, I'm not really on the team, so...
We're accepting outside help. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
- Okay. I think I need to just calm down
- _
and do some "research".
Really? Right now?
Dude, Sara needs us!
I'm freaking out here, man.
- Aw, come on, B.
- _
Ah, Mick. Perfect timing.
I need you to check on
any leads you may have
in the underworld please.
Not gonna work.
This whole thing's not gonna work.
Nothing works without Sara.
Okay, so what? Are you just gonna drink?
That's real mature, Rory.
- [SIGHING] Real mature.
- _
Wow. You really got
this team figured out.
- Mm-hmm.
- So what do we do?
Uh, we are gonna call
the experts, the D.E.O.
- Good idea. Eesh...
- What?
Is it gonna get weird
between you and Alex Danvers
'cause she and Sara had a fling?
It's... swing a dead cat.
Sara never liked to be alone.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[GAS HISSING]
Are you okay?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Whoa.
Who are you?
I'm Spartacus, the Undefeatable.
Oh. Yeah, that "undefeatable" part
didn't quite stick, but...
[GRUNTS]
- Uh, wait.
- [HORN, DRUM MUSIC]
Hey, get back here!
♪ ♪
[CHANTING IN UNKNOWN LANGUAGE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Sorry. Did you find Sara?
No.
Care to wet your whistle?
I'm confused. What did you learn?
[SIGHS] That Sara Lance is
far beyond my reach.
You told Ava you could reach her.
Yeah, well, I overpromised.
You can't just give up on Sara.
There's got to be something you can do.
- Come on. Anything?
- Look...
aliens took her, all right? To space.
This is really not my area of expertise.
Now if it was a ghost, or a demon,
or even a handle of whiskey,
I could help you out
with that, but I'm sorry.
All right? I'm an astrologer.
And you need an astronomer.
What an ass.
Yeah, he does have that going for him.
Look, he's right.
This is out of his league.
This is out of all our leagues.
I disagree.
Astra, let's talk about your "network".
My network? [SCOFFS]
I've been on Earth
for, like, five minutes.
Exactly.
[PHONE RINGING]
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
Gideon, why isn't the D.E.O. answering?
The Department of Extranormal Operations
was destroyed in the infamous
year 2020 by Rama Khan.
Nate, this is a huge setback.
We needed the D.E.O. Aliens
is their jurisdiction.
- Yeah.
- [SIGHS]
Captain Sharpe, I believe we are dealing
with a temporal anomaly.
According to the original timeline,
there was no alien spacecraft
over London in 1977.
Meaning this is our jurisdiction.
- Huh?
- We're the experts.
[LAUGHS] No.
We're... we're the experts?
Damn right we are.
You, me, the Legends.
We're the only people who are capable
of handling time-traveling aliens.
Nate, if I trusted the team,
I wouldn't have made an entire
binder to get rid of them.
Okay? The D.E.O. was plan A.
Well, Ava, you are now
in charge of the Legends.
So welcome to plan B.
Now breathe it in.
- Breathe with me.
- No.
Come.
[BOTH INHALE DEEPLY]
Plan B smells like pot.
I got something.
You are a walking contact high.
You're welcome. Gideon, put this up.
That's a cute little kid.
B, that's a tabloid.
Yes, tabloids help me not think
about how we live on
a technological terror
hurtling through a
swirling green nightmare.
Damn.
So this girl, Esperanza Cruz,
says that she was abducted by aliens,
and from then on, she could
communicate with them.
They implanted something in her head.
B!
I'm s... this is a tabloid, okay?
From how... what, 20 years ago?
It's probably totally fabricated.
- I need real leads.
- She's real, man.
- Gideon located her.
- I mean...
little kid with alien tech in her head.
Not a bad lead.
Okay, sure. Fine.
You know? Whatever. It's all we've got.
I mean, Rory's probably
good and boozed up by now,
so why don't you take Micky
and go investigate this Esperanza...
- what is her last name?
- Uh, Cruz.
Are we really sure bringing
Mick to talk to a kid
- is, like, best practices?
- No, n...
You're gonna go see her present day.
Some of us are still trying
not to mess with the timeline.
Right. The timeline.
Aye-aye.
You're excused.
Ugh!
[INTENSE DRUM, VOCAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- What is it?
- I was confined to one
of these glass prisons.
You were as well.
Which means there are
also others inside.
You just figured that out now?
I did.
I also commanded an army
of 120,000 slaves,
gladiators, and peasants
against the Roman republic.
- Yeah, I've heard.
- Mm, excellent.
Then we'll liberate our fellow prisoners
and we'll lead a rebellion
against our captors.
Wait, no. We don't know who's in there.
[GAS HISSING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Rise, compatriot.
I am your savior. I am Spartacus!
♪ ♪
[WARBLES]
[GROWLS]
♪ ♪
[ROARS]
What, pray tell, are you?
- A Saxon?
- [ROARS]
Nope, that's definitely an alien.
[GROWLS]
[ROARS]
[YELPS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
Hey, a little help here!
[ROARS]
[GAS HISSING]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[DRAMATIC SYNTH MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[ELECTRONIC TONE]
[EXHALES]
The thrill of the battle.
Reminds me of being
back in the Colosseum.
Yeah, you just stand there
in the Colosseum too?
I was letting it tire itself out.
If it had slain you, I would've
been well-rested
and easily avenged your death.
[GRUNTS]
Being an avenger is stupid.
The goal is to prevent
death. I am a Preventer.
You wanna join the Preventers, Sparty?
Yeah... yes?
Good choice.
Now stop opening pods.
We're gonna go find
who's flying the ship,
and we're gonna prevent
them from breathing.
[SUSPENSEFUL COUNTRY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'm telling you.
Sara ain't here. It's
a waste of our time.
We're gonna find Sara.
The fact that we found
this person is a sign.
And when the universe shows you a sign,
you should believe it.
Is that right?
The universe exists for one reason.
To kill you.
♪ ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
[RADIO STATIC]
Hello. Miss Cruz?
Ma'am?
Hm. Must not be home.
[HEAT GUN WHIRS]
♪ ♪
Let's not tell Miss Cruz we broke in.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
[BOTH SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
When they split up, we'll
take them out one by one.
Nonsense.
We have the element of surprise.
We attack both savages now,
and we slay them in one fell swoop.
We have no idea what they're capable of.
Look, I was an assassin.
Rule number one: isolate your targets.
Do not fight from the shadows.
I commanded an undefeated
army of 120,000 warriors.
Well, I assure you
they are all dead now.
Then I must avenge them.
No, no avenging. No avenging.
It's preventing!
Prepare to die, savages!
[YELPS]
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
♪ ♪
[SCREECHES]
[YELLING]
♪ ♪
[BELCHES]
[BOTH SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[HIGH-PITCHED CHITTERING]
I am very, very sorry, David,
you're under pressure.
[MUTTERING] Look, maybe I can help you.
[MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY]
- [CHUCKLES]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
[YELPS] Ooh, whoa, whoa.
- Why would you do that?
- Astra has a lead.
Okay.
All right. She has a lead.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Go ahead.
So I heard about this guy
who was once in hell.
Raved about aliens.
His name was Aleister Crowley.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Aleister bloody Crowley.
Come off it. Crowley's a kook.
That is the conventional wisdom.
But he had this tome of secrets
called the "Book of the Law".
In it, Crowley detailed
these alien encounters
and spells that these aliens taught him.
But he disappeared from hell.
Maybe he used these
alien spells to escape.
Yeah. Crowley didn't escape.
All right?
I summoned him, and then
I trapped him on Earth.
You trapped... sorry...
isn't that a felony?
No.
But like most things I do,
it probably should be.
[CLEARS THROAT] So, what'd
you do with the book, John?
All right, okay.
Being as we don't have any other ideas,
I kept it safe right over...
Gary!
What'd I tell you about
nicking my things, eh?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[HIGH-PITCHED SHRIEKING]
♪ ♪
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[PIPE SLICES THROUGH AIR]
[SHRIEKS]
Why did you kidnap me?
Gary!
Bloody hell Gary would
be reading Crowley,
I have no idea. There it is.
Find it?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What the hell is that?
Ew.
[SQUELCHING]
♪ ♪
- [SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
- You better help me understand you,
or this is gonna end quick.
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Hey! Hands where I can see them.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Gary?
Please don't be mad.
If she could talk to aliens,
why would she live in a
redneck dump like this?
Maybe you're right. But
isn't it worth making sure?
Besides, Ava really needs a win.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
I don't need a win. We all need a win.
This isn't about me. Oh, my God.
- Don't give me that look.
- What look?
You know exactly what look.
"You'll feel better not bottling up
- your emotions" look?
- I'm not bottling them up.
I just don't wanna talk about them.
Okay.
- I'm just gonna say one thing.
- Nate.
You have not mentioned
Sara's proposal once.
I am setting aside my feelings
to focus on the goal
of getting Sara back.
Okay? You should too.
[SUSPENSEFUL COUNTRY MUSIC]
I wonder what's in there.
Let me guess.
More dumb redneck stuff.
♪ ♪
Guess she's not such a
dumb redneck after all.
[MUFFLED GUNSHOT]
[BODIES THUD]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Guess not.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Behrad, Mick, answer me.
Great. Two more abductions.
This is why we don't talk
about emotions during the mission.
Okay, Gideon's scanning
for heat signatures.
It's... it's gonna be okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Three Legends are missing.
Things are pretty far from okay.
Yeah, well they just got further, love.
We found something in Gary's room.
A human-sized chrysalis.
Guys, we don't understand.
Gary is an alien.
An alien? Oh, my...
Okay. I don't buy it.
Well, we also found these.
Gary's glasses?
Oh, allow me to demonstrate.
And brace yourselves.
[WHOOSHES]
No.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
[GASPS]
Gary abducted Sara.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I was sent to Earth to kidnap
the quintessential human.
Spartacus?
Oh, no, no, no. You!
Spartacus was just my boss's lunch.
But don't worry. I don't eat humans.
Anymore.
Terrific.
The point is, I couldn't go
through with your abduction
because I fell in love with you,
with Ava, with all humans.
Yeah, well that's funny
because I still feel
very abducted, Gary.
Well, my boss, Kayla, found us.
But I remained loyal.
That's why I saved you.
- You saved me?
- Yeah!
I rigged the pod to open
with your handprint.
Okay... Gary, where are we going?
No clue. Kayla doesn't trust me anymore.
I don't blame her.
Yeah, well, you and I are also not okay.
Do you have any idea how wrecked
Ava must feel right now?
I mean, yeah, I'm sure she's
pretending to keep it together
for everyone else's sake, but inside,
- she must be dying.
- Stop, stop!
It's torture to even think about
what Ava's going through.
Do me in. I deserve it.
I've destroyed the
very thing I most stan.
Knock it off. You're gonna
help me get home.
Now tell me everything that
you know about this ship.
[EXHALES] Well...
when you first met, you butt heads.
But any fool could tell you two
were meant for each other.
This spaceship, Gary.
Oh.
[YAWNS]
[ACOUSTIC MUSIC]
What the... what the... hey!
- [ELECTRONIC BEEP]
- Ava?
- Nate?
- Behrad, are you guys okay?
Yeah, it is very far from chill in here.
2100 hours.
Trespassers have regained consciousness.
They were armed with some fancy weapons.
Not sure why.
Only one way to find out.
[TENSE MUSIC]
I told you the universe
was trying to kill us.
What was that, old timer?
I wasn't talking to you, Miss Crazy.
♪ ♪
I don't like being called that.
He didn't mean that, Miss Cruz.
Spooner.
I go by Spooner now.
Okay, Spooner, ma'am.
This is all just a misunderstanding.
The alien communicator in your head,
we need you to use
it to find our friend.
So y'all's plan was not only
to break onto my property,
but to kidnap me?
We were gonna ask.
In fact, we still are.
- What?
- Shh.
Will you come with us?
Come with you?
Oh, but you ain't going.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Please hurry.
She's getting real friendly
with her knife.
♪ ♪
Who you talking to?
Uh, he's a schizophrenic.
- He talks to himself.
- It's true.
It's a nervous tick actually.
Uh... could... could... hey.
Wait. Hey, hey, hey... hey.
Wait, wait. Hey, hey!
- [YELLING] No!
- [ELECTRONIC INTERFERENCE]
Behrad? What's happening?
[WHIMPERS]
Uh, the universe ripped his comms out.
[MUFFLED ELECTRONIC TRANSMISSION]
Captain Sharpe, I've
pinpointed their location.
Oh, thank God.
I'm not losing any more Legends today.
Gideon, take the ship to that location.
A ship?
[ECHOING] Nate, you're with me.
Wait, hang on. Why is my voice echoing?
She hacked my comms.
She can hear everything you're saying.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SHIP APPROACHING]
[WEAPON WHIRRING]
That thing against the Waverider?
[GRUNTS]
Whoa!
♪ ♪
Touché, Spooner.
[PORTAL WHOOSHING]
Please stop shooting my ship.
Don't come any closer.
I ain't gon' let y'all abduct me again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, hold on.
That's what you think this is?
You think we're aliens?
- The hell else could you be?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- We're time travelers.
- Time travelers?
Yes! That's our time ship.
Which is also a spaceship,
but that's beside the point.
Look, I'm sorry that
we trespassed, okay?
It was wrong.
But... [SIGHS]
We're desperate.
Listen.
The woman I love was
abducted by aliens last night.
And I just found that
she's gonna propose to me.
I will do anything
if you can find her.
Will you please help me?
♪ ♪
[WEAPON WHIRRING]
Exactly what an alien would say.
- Just...
- [YELPS]
[BODY THUDS]
[HUFFS]
Now can I burn this place down?
♪ ♪
Can we go over the plan one more time?
Because it still feels
slightly suicidal.
Well, we don't have enough fuel
to turn around and go home, right?
- Uh-huh.
- So we commandeer the ship.
From Kayla, my vicious, violent,
and very vindictive boss.
Then we open a wormhole back
to Earth's temporal zone.
An unstable rip in spacetime itself.
And then we fly the ship through it.
On whatever fumes remain
after we burn everything
opening the wormhole.
Well then, we better get moving.
First things, you gotta
go get rid of your boss.
Right. Okay.
Here goes nothing.
Gary, your glasses.
Whoops.
[WHOOSHES]
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[SUSPENSEFUL SYNTH MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BOTH SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
All right. Guess we'll do it this way.
[SCREECHES]
♪ ♪
Okay. Wormhole time.
[GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPS]
[QUIRKY, SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Morning, sunshine.
Tables may have turned,
but I ain't going down without a fight.
Whoa. We're not gonna hurt you.
Look.
Where the hell am I?
Like Ava said before,
we're time travelers.
- This is our time ship.
- Admit it.
You're only being nice so
I'll help you find your friend.
100%. Yes.
Even if I wanted to help y'all, I can't.
Why not?
This thing in my head
is like an antenna.
If I send a signal to your friend,
the aliens who put it
there could find me.
Look, we have the technology
to remove whatever's in your head
if... if you help us find Sara.
How is my signal gonna locate her?
It doesn't have to.
Our friend will direct it to
the aliens that she's with.
[LAUGHS] Oh! If you think we're weird,
wait till you meet John.
♪ ♪
So I send out my signal and
connect to this alien guy.
His name is Gary.
- He's an alien named Gary?
- Gary Green.
Ah, Green. Yeah, now it makes sense.
Once you make the connection,
I'll step into that Sigil
then Astral Project myself
to Gary's location.
- And then I'll look for Sara.
- Right.
And how do I connect
to this Gary alien who I've never met?
You'll drink a potion of sorts.
One delish smoothie coming at you.
- [WHISPERS] Good luck.
- Crowley's spell requires you
to ingest something of Gary's.
The chrysalis is all we've got.
- Seriously?
- No, she's not gonna...
The sooner this is over,
the sooner this thing's out of my head.
But I hope it works.
Salud.
- Oh, God.
- Oh.
She did it.
Eh. Kinda tangy.
All right, um, ready?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Yeah, after my abduction, I
started wearing tinfoil hats.
It blocked any alien signals
I could pick up.
Huh. Nifty. Right.
[CLEARS THROAT] On with the show.
[CHANTING IN ARABIC]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SIGIL WHOOSHING]
I can feel him.
♪ ♪
I found the alien.
A lot dweebier than I thought.
- Bloody Crowley was right.
- I can sense him.
He's worried and wants
to come down to Earth.
It looks like he's trying to help Sara.
Oh, I just need to step into the Sigil
and find her.
[YELPS]
- John, are you okay?
- [GROANS]
Spooner's connection is unstable.
I'm giving it everything
just to maintain it.
- I'll do it.
- No, whoa, whoa.
Are you crazy? You'll kill yourself.
Look what's happening to John.
It's plan B, Nate. Embrace it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGIL WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
[SHALLOW BREATHING]
Sara?
[LIGHT PIANO MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ava.
Wait, how...
How are you...
Are you here?
Hey, hey, hey. Stay with me.
Look at me.
Yes.
Yes, what?
When you get home, I'll marry you.
So you better get home, okay?
♪ ♪
I love you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
He's killing himself.
We have to stop him.
[GRUNTS]
John. Look at me.
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
[GROANS]
[KAYLA WARBLES]
[ROARS]
♪ ♪
Round two.
Wormhole's open, Sara!
[SCREECHES]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
♪ ♪
Whoa! [GRUNTS]
No, no!
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EXCLAIMS]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
[ROARS]
[DOOR WHIRRING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[PEACEFUL MUSIC]
[LAUGHS]
Once again, I wake to Zari Tarazi.
Oh, you're up?
I almost died.
But you saved me.
Yeah, well I couldn't let you die
right after getting
your soul back, so...
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Gidget said you might be dehydrated,
so I made you a green smoothie
to help you recover.
Sans alien cocoon.
Oh, cheers.
Mmm.
Yep.
It's very tasty.
Hey, uh, let me know when
you have your strength back.
[COY MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
It's a fling.
Uh-huh.
You know I can tell when
someone's bluffing, right?
It looks like Crowley wasn't.
Yeah, well, even if alien magic is real,
Crowley is a slippery fish.
He's not to be trusted.
Hm. Whatever you say, roomie.
Hey, that was a short residence
on the Waverider, eh?
Yeah, I can't keep getting
roped into Legends missions.
Let's just say I'm not as enamored
of the timeline as everyone else.
It's like you said,
I'm mortal now.
I wanna see what it's
like to be... normal.
Maybe I can love this world
like the rest of you do.
You've come a long way,
you little Hellspawn.
[CHUCKLES]
And come on, John.
Just a fling?
She's got you on a juice cleanse.
♪ ♪
Sure you won't stick around?
You've got a pretty chill vibe
beneath your gun-toting outcast vibe.
Look, we contacted your friend,
and I'm sorry she's not back yet.
But I want this thing removed
so I can finally live a normal life.
I get that.
You wanna keep it zen in the brain stem.
Dr. Gideon will fix you up.
What do you see, Gideon?
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Really? Can you look closer?
If I removed and thoroughly
dissected her brain,
we might something the
scan did not detect.
May I proceed?
What's going on out there?
No. Don't kill her, Gideon.
Yeah, I can hear it.
I wasn't gonna let her...
You can't hear it, can you?
[DISTANT ALIEN WARBLING]
They're all around us.
[PORTAL WHIRRING SPORADICALLY]
I've never seen anything like this
in a temporal zone.
Aliens. Lots of 'em.
They're falling into the timeline.
[ALIEN SCREECHES]
♪ ♪
[ROARS]
[SIGHS]
Why are you smiling?
We gotta clean this mess up.
I know.
It's just that the only person
who could create this
much mayhem is Sara
which means she's alive.
Well, if the universe shows you a sign,
you should believe it.
Mm!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Engaged?
- I'm so happy I could cry.
- Gary, if we don't get
through that wormhole,
we are stuck here.
I'm going as fast as I can.
[STRAINING] I'm sorry.
I'm not as good a pilot as my fiancé.
Wait, you and that
other alien are engaged?
Her name's Kayla, but yeah.
I assume the wedding's off now.
- Did I not mention that?
- We can talk about this later.
Right now, just get us
through that wormhole.
Yeah. [GROANS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
We're gonna make it.
- We're not gonna make it.
- We're gonna make it.
♪ ♪
[YELPS]
We didn't make it.
[SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -