Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Sara can never find
out the truth about Ava.
- I'm a...
- You're a clone.
Future clone thing?
The first totem bearers
imprisoned a great evil.
And time is his cage.
[DEEP VOICE] If you cannot
defeat me in this vessel,
how will you stop me once
I've assumed my true form?
Our family's destruction looms in 1992.
You promised you'd save us.
[GRUNTS]
- [WATER WHOOSHES]
- [SCREAMS]
[GASPS] Kuasa.
Gideon, set a course. I
have to save my family.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Code 1-3-1! All hands on the bridge!
- What's going on?
- Yeah.
I gotta get back to "Lord of the Rings."
- You read?
- [GRUMBLES]
Code 1-3-1.
Come on, guys, I wrote
a whole a whole memo.
Yeah, nobody read it.
- I did.
- Thank you, Ray.
- Pancakes for breakfast.
- No, 1-3-1 is not... is it?
Yeah. Does that mean no pancakes?
Anyway, I wrote a song to
help us remember all the codes.
It goes like this. From the top!
♪ If the code is 1-1-1 ♪
♪ Mallus escaped the time dungeon ♪
♪ If the code is 1-1-2... ♪
All right, Nate, just tell us.
Someone stole the jumpship.
♪ ♪
Where's Amaya?
Uh, according to the jumpship logs,
Zambesi, 1992.
Right before the warlords
destroyed her village.
And she dies.
The old her, that is.
[SHIP RUMBLES]
Whoa, the temporal zone
is getting real choppy.
Yeah, the timeline was
crumbling even before Amaya
decided to change history.
If that happens, the Darhks will be able
to free their demon.
Oh, well, I'd better
get back to my movie.
And we'd better stop Amaya
before she does something reckless.
- Gideon, plot a course for...
- Pardon me, Captain Lance.
But we are receiving an
urgent call from Mr. Hunter.
- You good?
- Gideon, put him on.
[BEEPING]
The Bureau needs backup.
Grodd's going after Barry.
[SHIP RUMBLES]
Well, that explains the time turbulence.
The Flash is always in trouble.
- It's kind of his thing.
- Not that particular Barry.
[SHIP RUMBLING]
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
[TYPEWRITER DINGS]
[GROWLS]
[SNARLING]
Barack Obama.
It will almost be an honor to kill you.
[ROARS]
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
[SHIP RUMBLING]
All right, people, we're dealing with
two anachronisms now,
Zambesi and young Obama.
Wally, Nate, I want you guys
to go talk some sense into Amaya.
You mean, convince
her to stand down while
her village and family is torn apart?
What if I use my temporal
simulator to find some loophole
that Amaya can use to help save Zambesi?
[SHIP RUMBLES]
All right, do it.
The rest of us, we're on Obamacare.
[PANTING]
♪ ♪
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
You will not escape.
- Grodd will complete his mission.
- Whoa.
Time to make America Grodd again.
Clearly, you have some grievances.
[SNARLS]
But perhaps we can look
for a common ground.
- [SNARLS]
- Whoa!
[GRUNTS]
Or not.
[ROARS]
[EXHALES]
I can feel his arrival.
[MOANS]
Oh, goodie.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING, DEEP GASP]
[BELLOWS]
[BELLOWING]
[GROWLING]
Yes, resist.
You will only prolong your suffering.
[GAGGING]
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
[GROWLS]
[ROARS]
Should have wasted
your hairy ass in 'Nam.
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
[ROARS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC POUNDS]
Run, Barry, run!
- [SNARLS]
- [GRUNTS]
A hairless ape who fights with fire.
How primitive.
[WHIRRING]
[SNARLING]
[PANTS]
[BELLOWS DEEPLY]
[HAUNTING CHORAL MUSIC]
Nora. Nora, honey.
- You okay?
- We were so close.
My master was escaping his bonds.
What happened?
Grodd's mission must have failed.
Maybe that could be a good thing.
It gives you and me
time to figure out what
the big guy's arrival really means.
♪ ♪
It means the end of history.
A chance for us to live as gods.
As gods?
Man, that sounds fantastic and all.
But what I just saw, it seems like
there won't be a "you" anymore.
It'll just be him.
That's what we always wanted.
Isn't it?
Totally. 100%.
You know, I'm just gonna
check on our grumpy gorilla
and see how he screwed this thing up.
♪ ♪
I'll see you later.
No, you won't.
Of course.
'Cause once I complete Grodd's mission,
you will be gone.
What I meant to say was,
I'll see Mallus later.
♪ ♪
Goodbye, Nora doll.
Grodd will destroy you. You're dead!
Nice work. Let's get
him back to the ship.
Yeah. Come on, teeny-tiny Grodd.
I think we still have
some chew toys left over
from the saber-toothed tiger.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a PhD student
doing history research, Andy Watkins.
No one cares about the cover story.
Shut up, Darren Applebottom,
talent scout for the New York Knicks.
[PERCUSSION MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
♪ ♪
Preventing the genocide
of my people tomorrow.
We know. We're here to stop you.
Peacefully.
Look, Amaya, I know you're
upset about what happened
to Kuasa, and all I can say is I am...
I'm truly sorry.
I don't blame you for
my granddaughter's death, Nathaniel.
I blame the warlords who
draw closer by the minute.
And I intend to stop them,
so stay out of my way.
I must say, it has been
such an honor, Barack.
- Oh, I go by Barry.
- I really like Barack.
Well, Barack is what it
says on my birth certificate.
Yeah, you might want to hold on to that.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
So, what's the backup plan?
Well, according to Ray's
song, this is a code 2-2-2.
What's that?
It means we're screwed
no matter what we do.
All right. Crisis averted.
- [ELECTRICAL WHOOSH]
- And a new one's just begun.
You're not getting Obama.
I'm not here for him.
I'm here for my daughter.
And I need your help.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I assure you, this is
completely unnecessary.
I come, as they say, in peace.
And I, as they say,
think you're full of crap.
I'm a changed man, Sara.
The only change I want to see
you go through is from alive to dead.
Ray, how we doing with
Constantine's spell?
Just need one more splash of bat spleen.
Sorry, bat.
And that should do it.
[SPLASH DROPS]
Mm.
Maybe I missed an ingredient.
Your Ankh symbol,
it's... it's upside down.
Uh...
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
- No, it's not!
- Ooh.
I knew it'd be difficult
to get you guys to trust me.
Hmm. Try impossible.
Which is why I brought
this gesture of good faith.
The Water Totem.
I borrowed it from my daughter after
she ripped it from Kuasa's chest.
Sorry about that, by the way.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Do you guys mind if I
give you a hand with this?
You seem to be struggling a bit.
Yeah? Okay, great.
[WHOOSHING]
[SYMBOL SCRAPES]
[WHOOSH]
Cool. Uh, now, uh, try to choke me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[WHOOSH]
[LAUGHS] You... you can't.
- Satisfied?
- Yeah.
That Water Totem's
gotta be worth something.
With all six, you guys might actually
have a chance against Mallus.
You mean the same demon you've been
creating anachronisms to release?
That was before I realized
what our partnership would cost me.
Nora...
Dies the moment the demon escapes.
Now, I know this might
rankle you a bit, Sara,
but our interests are aligned.
We can save Nora and stop
Mallus from being freed,
together.
- No.
- Excuse me?
Rory, kill him.
- [DEVICE WHIRS]
- Wait, nono-no.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay, look.
I... I know Damien has done
terrible things in his past
which cannot be forgiven,
but I know that he loves his daughter.
- We can't just kill him.
- He was already dead.
Killing him would be
repairing an anachronism.
Yeah, so would incarcerating
him in the Bureau.
I agree with Rip.
We need to think through
this situation rationally.
Boss?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- Stand down.
- [DEVICE WHIRS]
I'm glad to see you came to your senses.
Think this makes us
straight, you're wrong.
[SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
What are we even doing here, man?
We need to stop Amaya,
not party with the village.
[APPLAUSE]
There she is.
Okay, great, well, let's
get her out of here.
Not our Amaya.
That Amaya.
[SOFT MUSIC]
- [SIGHS]
- What's wrong?
Nothing, it just means...
my Amaya comes back to Zambesi
and we don't grow old together.
For thousands of years,
the Anansi Totem has been in my family.
And tonight,
it is my great joy... [SOFT LAUGH]
to pass this totem
down to my own daughter.
[APPLAUSE]
Make way
for the new protector of Zambesi, Esi.
[APPLAUSE]
[APPLAUSE FADES]
[CROWD WHISPERING]
Kuasa, where is Esi, child?
I'm sorry, Nana Baa, but
Mother isn't coming.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
My daughter has chosen
to reject her destiny and her duty.
I am sorry.
We have come here for nothing.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CROWD MURMURING]
Amaya. What just happened?
My daughter rejected the totem.
You sound more excited
than I thought you'd be.
Esi never bonded with the totem.
This is why the warlords were
able to destroy my village.
You think you can convince
Esi to be a totem bearer.
She'll protect the village tomorrow.
She'll protect Kuasa.
Everything will change.
That's the problem.
I saw what happened with
Barry Allen when he went back
and stopped his mother's murder,
a little thing called Flashpoint.
We can't change history. I'm sorry.
Tell her, Nate.
Nate?
I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
t screw history for once.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
Okay, so you go talk to your daughter,
and I go talk to you,
the older you.
Hmm.
You always had a way with her.
[SOFT LAUGH]
Come on.
Wait, we doing what?
So, listen...
Are you okay?
The hardest thing I
ever had to do in my life
was let Darhk live.
And now he's back, and it is taking
every ounce of self-control
not to kill him.
And I keep asking myself, "Why?"
For the good of the mission.
"For the good of the mission."
Listen to yourself.
You sound like some government...
- Clone?
- I was gonna say "stiff."
You know, Rip thought I could
talk some sense into you,
- but maybe...
- Wait.
You're here because of Rip?
Why would you do anything for that man?
Ava, he lied to you.
He implanted false
memories into your head.
He hired actors to
pretend to be your parents.
I mean, what more is it gonna take
to get you to confront him?
I am prioritizing the mission
over my own personal baggage.
You and your team
should try it sometime.
[SCOFFS]
No, that's not what you're doing.
You're covering,
because you're afraid of
what you might find out.
What else is there to find out, Sara?
I'm one of thousands.
I was grown in a lab.
There has to be more to the story, Ava,
and you deserve to know.
Look, you need...
[WHISPERING] You need
to talk to Rip now.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ah.
Could do with a wee nip myself.
Everything good, Director Sharpe?
Peachy.
Are we good to
transport Mr. Darhk back to the Bureau?
No, Rip, we're not.
Where are you going?
To go talk to someone
who can think straight
when the whole world has gone crazy.
So what you're saying is
you won't aid the man
that killed your sister,
even if it will prevent
Mollusk from escaping...
"Mallus."
From escaping his
inter-dimensional prison
and wreaking havoc across time?
Yeah, when you put it that way,
it does sound kind of petty.
Not at all. It sounds...
It sounds human.
Okay. But then what?
I'm just supposed to
hand Darhk over to Ava
and let the Time Bureau deal with him?
Your ex is clinging to
rules and regulations
in the face of the startling revelation
that she is...
I'm sorry... a clone, was it?
But here's the thing.
I'm not convinced the
Bureau is best equipped
to stop a demon.
No, it sounds like that calls for
a much more unorthodox approach.
[ROUSING MUSIC]
I really miss you.
[DEVICE WHIRS]
♪ ♪
Oh, hi guys.
I do hope you're not feeling all
killy-killy, stabby-stabby.
I want you to listen to me carefully.
I don't believe for a
second that you've changed.
You're still the same
cowardly son of a bitch
that put an arrow in my sister.
But I will work with
you to defeat Mallus
under one condition.
After this is over,
I'm putting you back in
the ground where you belong.
Deal.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[WHOOSH]
♪ ♪
Huh.
Is... so, do any of
these flashing screens
actually do anything?
Focus, Damien.
How do we capture your demon daughter?
Um, if we coordinate a strike
between the Legends and the Time Bureau,
we might be able to take her down.
How did that work for
you in Victorian London?
Besides, my little angel's
only gotten more powerful since.
What if we just ask Nora nicely?
I did have a bit of a
connection with her in Berlin.
- [SOFT GROAN]
- Not that kind.
All right, maybe she'll
listen to her dear old dad.
Not anymore. Nora only
listens to Mallus now.
He's always in her ear.
That's it. What if I got inside Nora?
Not like that.
What if I shrunk down,
flew into her ear and
pretended to be Mallus?
Okay, new guy on the team here.
Is that a joke plan or a real plan?
- We are so screwed.
- No, this could work.
We just have to convince
her that it's actually him.
This is how you would serve your city.
You would risk its utter ruin.
That's it.
I did what I judged to be right.
What you judged to be right?
You sent the Ring of Power into Mordor,
in the hands of a witless halfling!
Whoa, the vocal similarity
to Mallus is uncanny.
- Quiet!
- Gideon?
Who is that actor?
And how can we get him
without dealing with his agent?
Red leather, yellowl eather. Yeah?
- Mis... mister Noble?
- What?
Uh, we have some, uh,
last-minute rewrites.
No worries! We'll fix 'em in post!
Tell Peter Jackson
no more chickens, huh?
I ate four this morning, eh?
- So what's up, mate?
- Yeah, so.
Rewrites, uh, from Peter.
And he'd like me to,
uh, run lines with you.
- You're kidding.
- [SOFT LAUGH]
Okay. Uh, let's see.
"Nora, you must heed my command."
That's good. That's good.
- Who's Nora?
- Nora.
Nora, she's a new character that, um,
well... they wanted to beef up
the female presence in the film.
You can't do that, mate.
It's Tolkien, "Lord of the Rings."
I know... But it's a studio note.
Oh, studio note. Very
good note, yeah, all right.
- Yeah, from the top?
- [MUMBLES] Hmm.
"Nora, you must heed my command."
Uh, "What is it, Master?"
"Go to the Waverider, Nora."
"I cannot go to the Waverider."
"The totems are ripe for the picking."
This is crap, isn't it? Aye?
- Oh, well...
- I mean, who wrote this?
- I mean, somebody...
- Don't... don't worry about it.
- Took a lot of time...
- Don't worry about it.
"The totems are ripe for the picking.
Your father will lead you to them."
"My father?"
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Esi.
Who are you?
I am a distant cousin.
I came for the ceremony.
Sorry to disappoint you.
[SOFT MUSIC]
I love it here.
When I was a child,
I'd come here and lose
myself in the stars,
think about where my life would lead.
For as long as I can remember,
the Anansi Totem has been my destiny.
But now,
I'm not sure I want it.
- You wouldn't understand.
- Try me.
♪ ♪
My mother is the great Amaya Jiwe.
She's protected our
village her entire life.
She never doubted, never wavered.
That's not true.
Every totem bearer starts
their journey with doubt.
Even your mother.
I will never live up to her legacy.
You have her strength
and the strength of all
others who've come before her.
But there is danger coming,
and your people need
you to stand up for them.
[ROUSING MUSIC BUILDS]
♪ ♪
All right, you fathwoom
into Amaya's hut,
grab the totem, and we'll
give it to her daughter.
Nate, I... now that you
have some space from her,
I need you to come to your senses.
Amaya can't see this, she's too close.
But she's going to
cause more harm than good
if this releases Mallus.
- We don't know that.
- We do.
You do.
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I can't not help her, Wally.
I love you, man, but I will stop you
if you take this too far.
[WHOOSH]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Like stealing candy
from a very old baby.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[SOFT BREATHING]
[INTENSE WHOOSH]
[INTENSE GROWL]
Ow! Oh, Amaya, wait.
[COUGHS] It's me.
You know, I didn't think
this would do it for me,
but it actually kind of does.
- Who are you?
- Oh!
- It's me, Nate.
- Who?
Nate.
I know it's been a while,
but we used to travel
through time together.
You know, do other things... [GRUNTS]
If this is some kind of a joke...
[CHOKING] It's not a joke.
I have pictures of us
on my phone.
Ow.
[EXHALES]
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SOFT GROAN]
This is me.
Of course.
You really don't remember, do you?
How is this possible?
We were part of a bitchin' team
that travelled through time together...
I mean, the 1942 you.
Why are you here, time traveler?
To keep my promise to you,
by making sure your daughter Esi
gets the Spirit Totem tonight.
She didn't even show
up to her own ceremony.
Her head is always somewhere else.
She doesn't know what she wants.
[SOFT LAUGH]
Yeah, you had a hard time
figuring that out too
when you were her age.
♪ ♪
But, look, if Esi believed
you were truly in her corner,
she wouldn't doubt herself.
She would accept the
totem and be unstoppable,
just like you.
[WHOOSH]
[CLEARING THROAT]
Uh, hey there, Nora doll.
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE]
Why am I still here?
Why is the Master still in prison?
You failed me!
I know, it's terrible.
The Legends captured Grodd,
and this whole Obama
thing is just not working,
so perhaps Mallus can advise us
as to what to do next.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
Mallus only speaks when he desires.
I can't just "summon" him.
Well, maybe we'll just, uh...
[INTENSE RUMBLING]
Wait here until he
gets the itch.
[EXHALES]
- [BEEPING]
- [LOUDLY] Nora.
You must heed my command.
It's him. He's speaking to me.
Very loudly.
[BEEPING]
Really? Mallus is speaking to you?
Shh! I need to concentrate.
Go to the Waverider, Nora.
The Waverider, why?
The totems are ripe for the picking.
Your father will lead you to them.
My father?
What... what... Mallus has plans for me?
I... I wonder what those are.
The... the... the Legends' ship.
The Master wants you to take me there.
Oh, I would in a heartbeat,
but we are hopelessly
outnumbered, honey.
There's just no way...
He must take you there now, Nora.
Just do it!
God, do it! Don't be a fool!
No problemo. Let's go.
[WHOOSH]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Those totems should be
around here somewhere.
[WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
You.
[WHOOSH]
[STARTLES]
What is this?
I'm sorry, sweetheart,
but it's for your own good.
No.
♪ ♪
[DEEP VOICE] No!
[WHOOSH]
I get it.
You think that I failed you
because I joined with the Legends
and trapped you here.
Well, you're right.
I did fail you.
But that's not how.
I was a terrible father.
I was obsessed with world domination.
- Because of that...
- [SOFT GROWLING]
I died,
leaving you all alone as a child,
trapped with my name
and my foolish dreams.
Oh, I turned you into a
demon long before Mallus did.
[DEEP CHUCKLING]
It's why I'm begging you,
do not let him take you away from me.
[DEEP VOICE] Your daughter is long gone.
No!
I know you can hear me. Fight him!
Oh, there was no fight.
Her soul...
her flesh...
were freely given.
You sick son of a bitch.
[HAUNTING CHORAL MUSIC]
One more alteration to the timeline
and my cage crumbles.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
Can't believe that worked.
I can.
Sara knows what she's doing.
I may have my flaws, but I do know
how to pick the best people for the job.
So why did you pick me?
What? Come on.
Brilliant mind, calm
demeanor, incredible strength.
And, unlike the Legends,
you actually follow rules.
It almost sounds like
I was made for the job.
What are you getting at?
I know I'm a clone, Rip.
I see.
So why me? Hmm?
Of all the clones in
2213, why did you pick me?
You're special.
So why'd you erase my memory?
- I thought it would be easier.
- Easier?
Easier for you or easier for me?
Don't lose focus, Ava.
You are too critical to this mission.
Well, the good news is if I die,
you can just skip off to 2213,
and get yourself another clone.
[TENDER MUSIC]
Oh, my God.
I wasn't even the first one, was I?
We both know how hard it is
to find agents as talented as you.
And to find one who is also
replaceable is invaluable...
How many?
You're the 12th.
The 12th?
So I wasn't even your first choice?
Or your second or...
You don't understand.
- You are exceptional.
- Don't, Rip.
Just don't.
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
[NORA THRASHING ON SCREEN]
Nora's gone.
It's just Mallus now.
You must be enjoying this,
seeing your nemesis with a broken heart.
I didn't know you had a heart to break.
Where was it the night
you murdered my sister?
Look, what I did was unforgivable.
But back then, I hadn't
loved anyone enough
to understand the pain that I caused.
Not that it's any comfort, but
if I could take it all back,
I would.
We all have regrets.
But we can't undo the
things that we've done.
True.
But even the worst of us
can be made whole again.
You, for example.
League to Legend to killer to captain.
That's not a bad makeover, is it?
- It's not good enough.
- Why?
Because you put on the Death Totem
and almost killed your entire team?
- Yes.
- But you didn't, did you?
And you know why?
The same reason I'm spilling my guts to
a woman who's imagined
my death 1,000 times over.
More like 10,000.
Love! Sara.
'Cause without it, people like us,
we're left alone with the darkness.
That's not good for anyone, is it?
♪ ♪
[GENTLE DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I'm so proud of you, my child.
Esi's embraced her destiny.
Tomorrow when the marauders
come, she'll be ready.
And if she's not, we'll be right there
to fight alongside her.
You don't have to stay, Nathaniel.
I know that what I did was selfish.
You couldn't be selfish if you tried.
Now, you see that
boomin' granny over there?
She doesn't remember me,
or the Legends.
You know why that is?
I must have erased my memory.
And why would you do that?
Because if I chose to come back here,
after everything we've
been through, then
erasing you would be the only way
that I could be the
protector my people deserve.
Otherwise, I'd always be split in two.
And part of me would
be in love with you.
I tried to reason with
them, but they won't listen.
Amaya is dead set on saving her village.
And Nate? He's just...
- Whipped.
- I was gonna say "in love."
But, yeah, same thing.
Zari, please tell me that
you found a loophole that allows
Amaya to save her village.
There is no loophole.
I've tried billions of variations,
but this event has too
many ripple effects.
The village has to be destroyed.
Or Mallus is freed.
And we're all doomed.
What if we're not?
Hmm?
[ROUSING MUSIC]
We have the six totems,
the only thing that Mallus is afraid of.
But you can't fight what you can't see.
What if the only way to kill
Mallus is to let him out?
Are you really suggesting
that we allow Mallus to escape
because you have a
collection of magical stones?
Look, we have two choices: we
fight Amaya or we fight Mallus.
And I know it sounds crazy
to let a time demon out,
but it's a hell of a
lot easier to stomach
than turning on a friend.
Okay, yes, but didn't
the original totem bearers
try and face Mallus and... and blow it?
Constantine said the only
reason they couldn't kill Mallus
was because the Death
Totem betrayed them.
And that's not gonna happen this time.
How can you be so sure?
I needn't remind you what happened
the last time you tried to wield it.
She won't have to wield it.
- I will.
- [SCOFFS]
The Death Totem was
attracted to Captain Lance
because of a unique
quality we both share.
We were both brought back from the dead.
Plus, I have a personal stake
in wanting to send
Mallus straight to Hell.
He took my little girl.
True as that may be,
there is no chance that Captain Lance
would trust you with
such a dangerous weapon.
♪ ♪
Death Totem's all yours.
- [SIGHS]
- Sara, you can't be serious.
Ava, we don't have a choice.
Our only choice is to stop
Amaya and stop the anachronisms.
This is insanity.
Insane is what we do best, Ava.
I will not condone this behavior,
and the Bureau certainly
does not stand behind you.
Rip, let's go. We have work to do.
Remember when I told you
that we would need the Legends
before this was through?
Perhaps it is time that
we set aside the scalpel
and let them be the chainsaw.
I will consider that your resignation.
Ava.
Ava, wait.
[TOTEM HUMMING]
♪ ♪
This plan can work and you know it.
You just need to trust your gut.
My gut?
You mean the one that was
manufactured to factory settings?
- [SIGHS]
- That's the same gut that
11 other Avas used and got killed?
Ava, please. Just trust me.
You don't understand.
This plan breaks every
rule in every book,
and all I have right
now are the rules, okay?
You have me.
[TENDER DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
I'm admitting something
that could save us both.
I love you.
[SNIFFS]
There is no "me" to love.
♪ ♪
- [BEEP]
- [WHOOSH]
She looks good out there,
ready.
Like mother, like daughter.
[TWIGS SNAP]
The warlords are early.
Hey! Oh, no.
- Don't puma-pounce us.
- Really, Wally?
- You're gonna do this?
- It's not like that, Nate.
- I know why you're here.
- No, no, you really don't.
Short version: Nora's on the
ship, tripping on Mallus juice.
Damien Darhk gave us the Water Totem
after they saved Barack Obama.
And, uh, we are here to help you
create the anachronisms
so we can release Mallus,
and then we can kill him.
Oh, and I met John Noble.
[ENGINES WHOOSH]
So you're working with Damien Darhk?
Please, don't rub it in.
And you're letting him
wield the Death Totem.
In order to do justice
for someone I love.
Sure you can understand that.
Thankfully that is our only similarity.
- Hm.
- So.
Who gets Earth? Who gets Water?
Well, as a man of steel,
which is an element,
I always felt a strong
connection to the earth.
Actually, steel is an
alloy of iron and carbon.
Also, I've watched every single episode
of "Planet Earth" on Blu-ray,
and I was only stoned all of the time.
Can I just please have the damn totem?
- Thank you.
- All yours.
And Water? Anyone?
Actually, water is really powerful.
It... it's crucial to life on Earth.
And did you know that we
are made up of 60% water?
- If...
- All right, I think we get it.
Take a totem.
Oh, I wasn't making a pitch for one.
Just take the totem!
Okay, cool.
All right, so is there, like,
an instruction manual? A YouTube video?
You better figure it out.
Warlords are coming, and that means
Mallus is about to make his debut.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC POUNDS]
[ECHOING] Dad?
Nora.
You're here but... how?
The totem means you're dead.
No, not yet.
Mallus is trying to take me,
but I'm still fighting him.
For now.
But Dad?
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
[CRYING] I don't want him to take me.
Please don't let him
take me. I'm scared.
You ready?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Yeah, let's do this
before it's too late.
♪ ♪
[INTENSE WHOOSHING]
[DEEP GROWL]
This place has been sacred to my people
since the dawn of time.
The totems will be strongest here.
Well, they'd better be,
'cause mine's not turning on.
[DISTANT SHOUTING AND GUNFIRE]
It's time.
As soon as Esi defeats the warlords,
our fight against Mallus begins.
[SNARLING]
[MEN SHOUTING]
- [WHOOSH]
- [RHINO BELLOWS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [RHINO BELLOWING]
- [MEN SCREAMING]
Should we help your daughter?
Esi's got this.
Nono-no! No-no-no!
Looks like it's time
to meet our monster.
Or our maker.
I'm not dying today.
[DEEP SCREECHING]
Here's Mallus.
[SCREECHING]
[GRUNTING]
Why isn't she transforming?
Rip, what gives?
The historical record is showing
that Zambesi's still destroyed.
That doesn't make any sense.
The battle's over. The good guys won.
- [DEEP ROAR]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- Rip, what's going on?
- Oh, my God.
The warlords don't destroy the village.
The village was destroyed by
an angry gorilla.
[BROODING DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I had to. She's my daughter.
You released Grodd.
I need history to run its course.
- [GRODD ROARING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Your time must end.
This way! Quick.
You should go too, Maame.
I can handle this beast.
I believe in you, Obabaa.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC POUNDS]
♪ ♪
[ROARING]
- [WHOOSH]
- [GORILLA ROARS]
[ROARING]
♪ ♪
Esi.
No.
- [GRUNTS]
- [WHOOSH]
[THUD]
- Amaya! Amaya!
- [TOTEM RINGING]
Hey, hey, are you okay?
[SOFT GRUNT] I'm okay.
[GRODD ROARING]
Nate, my family... [PAINED GROAN]
I won't let them die.
I promise.
Damien, Mallus is coming.
This won't save Nora.
If there's a chance in
hell, I'm gonna take it.
I'll handle this.
[WHOOSHING]
[INTENSE WHOOSH]
"Always incapacitate
your speedster first."
That's day one stuff.
[INTENSE TONE]
[SKIN CRINKLING]
- [TOTEM WHOOSHES]
- Let him go.
[AIR WHOOSHING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[WHOOSH]
I'm warning you, don't stand in my way.
I was powerful before
I had this trinket,
but now I'm unstoppable.
Yeah, we've heard that one before.
- [GRUNTS]
- [WHOOSH]
- [ALL GRUNT]
I don't want to kill you.
I want to kill them to save my daughter!
Why can't you understand that?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC POUNDS]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[MYSTICAL WHOOSH]
Can't move.
What is happening?
Foolish human.
You are now mine to control.
You will not harm my village!
Maame! Get away from him!
[GROWLS]
[SCREAMS]
[CLANK]
[WHOOSH]
It worked!
[SOFT GROAN]
Amaya.
[SOFT GROANING]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Nathaniel.
[SOFT LAUGH]
I... I didn't take
you for a totem bearer.
That makes two of us.
♪ ♪
[DEEP SNARLING]
Nora.
[SNARLING]
[INTENSE WHOOSHING]
[CHAINS CLANK]
I'll find you. I promise.
Go.
[CHAIN CLANKS]
Go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hey!
[GRUNTS]
Performance anxiety, Raymond?
You're only proving my point that
this plan was never gonna work.
Do this.
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [WHOOSH]
It's too bad, really.
I was just beginning to
like you after Berlin.
- [BLADE PIERCES]
- [GROANS]
[GROANS]
[TOTEM HUMMING]
♪ ♪
[DEEP SNARLING]
You literally stabbed me in the back.
It only seemed fitting.
You're lucky I wasn't
aiming for your heart.
I am not gonna let Nora be taken by him.
Nora's gone, Damien.
[DEEP SCREECHING]
[INTENSE WHOOSHING]
[HAUNTING CHORAL MUSIC]
[DEEP VOICE] Finally, I am free.
♪ ♪
[ROARING]
[INTENSE WHOOSH]
[DEMONIC SHUDDERING]
No.
- Nora.
- You can't help her, Ray.
Oh, my God.
[SNARLING]
I am so much more than a god.
[WINGS RUMBLING]
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
[CACKLES]
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44