[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Uh...
Uh, you... you need some help
with that, Mick?
Maybe you should just,
you know, take it easy.
I'm pregnant, not paralyzed.
Yeah. Okay. Well, do your thing.
Are you sure this is the right spot?
I'm just following the beeps.
Then why are you going in circles?
Maybe the tracker's busted.
[SIGHS AND CHUCKLES]
Moment of truth.
And that is not right.
Oh, what's up, squire? What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
They're soggy in the middle.
Maybe I can help.
Fiery flames, burning blazes,
infernal conflagration!
[YELPS]
- Dude!
- Sorry about that, Behrad.
Guess I just don't know
my own strength lately.
Let me make it up to you.
Cannabis edible, euphoria incredible,
- brain matter bendable...
- Oh, uh, no!
Please don't fire a spell
at my brain, hmm?
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
♪ ♪
Yeah. Good point.
You're feeling mighty magical
this morning.
Almost overcharged.
I feel astounding.
Where's Zari, eh?
I wanna share this with her.
Sorry, my friend.
My sis swapped places
with Flannel Zari,
who's currently on a date with Nate.
And you just missed the pod squad too.
So Nate is with the Zari
that lives in a Totem.
That seems very problematic.
Where's he taken her?
Watch the Beatles perform live?
Maybe the fabled
pleasure domes of Kublai Khan?
Great outdoors.
Nothing beats Mother Nature.
Yeah, feel like we've seen
all the nature.
Yeah.
All seriousness, I am
very glad to be here with you.
We're almost there.
Look, I know you only have 24 hours
before you have to go back
into the Totem.
Right. 24 hours.
So I just wanted to spend
some time together,
you know, with no distractions.
Yes, I would like that too.
Hello, neighbors!
Looks like the campsite's
double-booked.
That's okay. We love company.
I'm Jeff. This is Jamie.
Rock and roll. [CHUCKLES]
[ROCK MUSIC BLARING]
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, we kinda got it all,
as you can see.
- Who wants dogs?
- Oh, uh...
you know what, Jeff?
We're, uh, gonna go off
on our... on our own, thanks.
[SLURPING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Aha.
- [ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
- [GASPS]
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
Last pod in the timeline
and it's a total dud.
Wait, there's something inside.
♪ ♪
Nothing's happening.
Here. Could be dangerous.
♪ ♪
Oh, it's one of those, uh,
puzzle things.
You gotta solve it to open it.
Hey, I'm not done yet.
- Give me that...
- No, I... I can do it.
Hey, babe, I think
we're gonna be a while.
Yep, take all the time you need, babe.
There's seriously no rush.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- [GASPS MELODRAMATICALLY]
- [GASPS]
- Oh, no.
- What?
It's bad luck to see you
in your wedding dress
before the big day.
It's not bad luck.
I'm not marrying you, Gary.
And besides, this isn't the one.
It makes me feel...
I don't know. It's not right.
Stop whatever you are doing.
No, no, no. Okay?
- I have a job for you, yeah?
- Anything.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
You're gonna help me find
the perfect wedding dress.
- [GASPS SOFTLY]
- Mm-hmm.
- Give it to me!
- Give this... I got it.
Guys, can we please just
get it together?
Give me the damn...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- [PINS CLATTER]
- Where the hell are we?
♪ ♪
One minute, we're in a gross junkyard,
and the next,
we're in a gross bowling alley.
Spooner, are you getting something?
Uh, this place, major alien vibes.
I don't see any aliens.
I got a bad feeling about this.
♪ ♪
Sooner we get out of here, the better.
[GRUNTS]
[YELPS]
♪ ♪
Whoa, where is, um... everything?
I have a feeling
we're not in Kansas anymore.
[PINS CLATTER]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com
[PINS CLATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
So we've been abducted by aliens.
ALL: Again.
Ava, B, can you guys hear us?
Courier isn't working either.
Wherever we are, we are stuck.
Okay, well, if these guys are aliens,
maybe we can bum a ride home.
Yeah, sure. Go for it.
♪ ♪
I'm gonna see if this guy
knows anything.
Thanks for catching me,
but I think I'd rather you let me die
than spend another minute here.
I'm taking a leak.
[SCOFFS]
♪ ♪
Hi, um, sir.
The name's Buddy.
What's your shoe size?
I'm not here to bowl, but I was hoping
you could tell me
how the hell I got here.
I would wager you opened an invitation.
No, I didn't get an invitation.
Shiny, irresistible,
drags your ass
across a universe instantly?
Okay. Yeah, maybe I did.
Damn it, the puzzle box.
How do we get back to Earth?
♪ ♪
Earth?
But you just got here.
And I'm so happy you did,
because I bet you're
incredible bowlers.
Why is that?
Bowling was invented
by earthlings, after all.
Everyone else here just looks human.
Why don't I show you around? Come on.
Okay.
[BLOWING FORCEFULLY]
Coming down to the wire, folks!
[LAUGHS]
Sorry to bother you,
but, uh, my friends and I are stranded
and we're looking for a ride
back to, uh, Earth.
Earth, huh?
Yeah, sure. We'll give you a ride.
But you and your friends have
gotta beat us in a game first.
We're kind of on a tight schedule.
Oh, come on. What's one game?
Unless, of course,
you're afraid of losing.
[LAUGHTER]
I can roll with anyone.
Then how about
we spice things up a little
and play a game of cosmic bowling?
Is that with the neon balls
and the black lights?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah,
that ain't really my thing.
All I'm saying is, if you
wanna get a ride out of here,
you gotta roll against us.
All right, then. Game on.
I was hoping you'd say that.
[SHIMMERING TONE]
Cute trick, but it's what you
do on the lanes that counts.
Once we're through
putting these Redshirts
out of their misery,
you're next.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHTER]
- Yeah.
The guidebook said
we should be able to see
the northern lights,
but I can't see a single star.
Huh. Maybe it's too cloudy.
Listen, I know this is super on-brand,
I'm feeling kind of hungry.
- Hungry, you say?
- Mm.
Hmm, well, I happen to have made
your favorite Persian delicacy,
abgoosht.
- [CHUCKLES] Really?
- Yep.
And for dessert,
the very exotic doughnut.
That's very sweet.
No.
Ugh, this must be Spooner's bag.
Oh, that makes sense.
The only food in here are MRE rations.
Maybe they're super delicious.
[MOUTH FULL] Wanna try?
Rock and roll!
[MOANING AND GRUNTING]
- Is that what I think it is?
- Yep. [SIGHS]
Rock and roll!
What's the point of unplugging
if all your camping gear has a cord?
Meanwhile, we're out here
trying to squeeze in one date
before I turn into a Totem pumpkin,
and they're over there
with all the carefree time
in the world.
I'm jealous of those two idiots.
Me too. It's insane.
That's it. That's it.
We're getting another campsite.
- Okay, let's go.
- Gideon. Gideon.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[TIME COURIER CHIMING]
Huh, my Time Courier's going nuts.
Yeah, something's wrong.
Something's wrong.
♪ ♪
It's funny. It even smells
like a bowling alley.
Yeah, I included everything you'd find
in a bowling center on Earth.
That's how much I love bowling,
the greatest sport in the universe.
I'm sorry, you created this place?
Does that mean you were the one
who sent out the invitations?
I had nothing to do with
those cursed invitations.
That's the work of the Pin Killers,
the guys in the purple shirts.
They came here and ruined
my little bowling paradise.
I need you to beat them.
They're the top dogs now.
And you only get one game
to try to knock them off.
So don't challenge them
until your team is ready.
Guess what.
I found us a ride home.
All we gotta do
is just beat those aliens
in those ugly purple shirts.
We got next.
♪ ♪
Will you hand me that?
Mm, just need to adjust the frequency.
The sun is missing.
It's night everywhere on Earth.
Massive unexplained chasms
that have appeared in Mexico,
- Canada, and Alaska.
- We're in Alaska.
Who did this? Aliens? Demons?
Did God give up on us?
Either way, it's the end of the world.
We're all gonna die.
We're all going to die.
- Alaska, Canada, they're gone.
- Nate...
- They're just gone.
- I think the world is ending.
We need to get out of here.
This is one of the top five
worst dates I've ever been on.
We're all gonna die. We're gonna die.
We're all gonna die.
Jamie and I can go
anywhere in the world
and I could still blaze us
a Neapolitan pizza
at 800 degrees
supes quick! [CHUCKLES]
That's so fantastic, Jeff.
Yeah, the char on this
is something else. [CHUCKLES]
- Mm.
- Mm?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Say, Jeff... sorry, bro.
Can I borrow your truck supes quick
so we can go into town
and pick up some stuff?
Uh...
sure. What are neighbors for?
There's a bro.
Hey...
- why don't we all go?
- No.
Rock and roll!
- BOTH: No, no, no, no.
- Yeah!
Nate, you're riding shotgun.
Boys in the front.
Oh, my God. [INHALES SHARPLY]
[ROCK MUSIC BLARING]
♪ ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ We got this feeling right ♪
[ENGINE GRINDING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Battery's dead.
I don't know, Jeff, maybe
all your devices drained it.
Well, good luck, guys.
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Where you going?
- We're heading into town.
Great. We'll come with.
Maybe we can find some folks
to jump the truck battery.
Rock and roll!
♪ ♪
Looks like we're hiking.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
All right,
enough of this ding-dong
dallying, waiting around.
I say we get out there
and we find Sara and her gang.
I'm sure they could use
a magical assist.
Come to think of it,
we haven't heard from them in a while.
Gideon, let's go visit Sara,
Kansas City 2021.
Calculating. Calculating.
Huh, that is impossible at this time.
Come on. You're Gideon.
Everything's possible.
I'm sorry.
I'm having trouble locking on to Earth.
Never seen that before.
I came looking for my summer
wedding inspo binder,
but did Gideon just say
we can't get back to Earth?
- Yeah.
- This is bad.
Ava cannot be marooned in the
Temporal Zone away from Sara.
- This could be triggering.
- Calm down. Just breathe.
Keep Ava occupied.
We'll figure something out,
right, John?
Oh, most assuredly.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
All right, team,
we are stranded
on the edge of the universe,
and the only way out
is to beat the Pin Killers.
- Question.
- Yes.
I don't bowl.
I don't either, but how hard can it be?
Pretty sure you just pick it on up,
and then we just roll it on down.
[PINS CLATTER]
Nice, Sara!
Well, what can I say?
Guess I'm a natural.
Mick, let's see what you got.
All right.
All right, it's gonna be good.
It's gonna be great.
Go, just right on... oh.
Whatever feels natural.
Just nice and smooth.
Okay.
[PINS CLATTER]
Wrong lane, but hey,
you got some pins, right?
You know, if you lose the
gloves, you'll drop more pins.
Watch and learn.
Here you go.
O... kay.
Ah, we got a standard house
oil pattern.
A bit chilly,
so the lanes will be slick.
We got a dip in the 16th board.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[DRAMATIC LATIN GUITAR MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS AGGRESSIVELY]
[PINS CLATTER]
Yeah!
What the hell was that?
I learned the art of bowling
when I was 13.
Kept me out of trouble.
The footwork concentrates my mojo.
You keep that mojo
concentrated. Nice moves.
All right, Astra, lace them up.
Let's go.
I am not putting my feet
in those fungus-filled shoes
or my fingers
in those fungus-filled holes.
All right, then you can cheer us on
from that fungus-filled chair.
You're just gonna let her skip?
Whatever she wants.
♪ ♪
- [PINS CLATTER]
- [SIGHS]
I'm getting a good feeling
about this one.
It is amazing.
This is the one. I'm sure of it.
Okay, well, I can't show
Sara, obviously,
but I can tell her that it's done.
- Gideon...
- Actually, uh,
you're fine with the shoulders?
Um, the shoulders?
Yeah, what's wrong with them?
Nothing at all. It's your wedding.
As long as you're fine with it...
Gary, spit it out.
[QUIRKY DRAMATIC MUSIC]
They're a little plain.
They lack pizzazz.
- Pizzazz?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Now that I look at them,
they do seem really boring.
Well, I mean, they're not that bad...
Gary, what am I gonna do?
I... I can't get married
in plain shoulders.
Gideon...
we're gonna need some alterations.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So you're saying we're stuck?
Every time I plot an exit vector,
it fails to reach Earth.
My safety protocols do not allow us
to attempt a doomed jump, so yes.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES HEAVILY] Right.
Like John Henry, I will prevail
where the machine could not.
How?
I will compel the ship to Earth.
Whoa. Sounds big, even for you.
Yeah, well, I am feeling
invigorated, squire.
I need you to bring me the four
elemental aspects of our world:
earth, fire, air and water, all right?
- Got it.
- Yeah.
Hey, maybe your powers
are growing stronger
since you drank
from the Fountain of Imperium.
Oh, yeah, the fountain. That's right.
Good.
Well, uh, hop to it, Skippy.
♪ ♪
[ELECTRONIC BLIPPING]
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Final frame.
[PINS CLATTER]
[ELECTRONIC BLIPPING]
Redshirts, game over. [CHUCKLES]
Boom, another one bites the dust.
Pin Killers can't be stopped! [LAUGHS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY] Now you're mine.
[TENSE MUSIC]
You don't have to do this, Mike.
You won. Isn't that enough?
Well, here's the thing.
I do it for the trophies.
- You're a bastard, Mike!
- [CHUCKLING] Yeah, well.
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
[INTENSE MUSIC]
[GROANING]
[LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
♪ ♪
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
They have a lot of balls.
That whole team
just vaporized into thin air.
Yeah, and I'm guessing
that's what's gonna happen
to us if we lose too.
I hope you warmed up,
because Mike the Strike
says it's game time.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
Can't tell you how many
trucks I've had to abandon
in some of the most scenic
places on Earth.
So you and Jeff are big campers, huh?
Rock and roll.
Right, of course. Rock and roll.
I get the vibe that you and Nate
are doing the long-distance thing.
I didn't know we gave off
that vibe, but yeah, we are.
And you two can handle the distance?
Yeah, Jamie, we can handle distance.
Well, if you can stand to be apart,
doesn't that just kind of prove
you don't need to be together?
What? No, no.
I'm sorry if I touched a nerve.
It's just, that's what
all the magazines say.
You didn't touch a nerve.
It's fine. I'm fine.
Nate and I are fine.
Our relationship is fine.
Our vibe is very fine.
Everything is fine, yeah.
Everything all right back there?
Fine.
Rock and roll.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
All right, everyone,
we've got ourselves
a game of cosmic bowling,
the Pin Killers versus the Legends.
Ten frames, ten pins,
and 60 feet of wood.
May your rolls be true.
[FUNKY MUSIC]
♪ Right on ♪
- All right, buddy.
- You've got this, Merv.
♪ ♪
[PINS CLATTER]
- Yeah!
- All right.
That's my Merv. Merv the Curve.
All right, baby.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS AGGRESSIVELY]
[PINS CLATTER]
Yeah!
♪ Feel so nice ♪
♪ Right on ♪
[PINS CLATTER]
[LAUGHTER]
- You got it. You got it.
- Hey.
Clare the Spare
always picks up the spare,
- always.
- Better believe it.
Lose the gloves, Mick.
Have respect for the game.
Quiet.
[CHORTLES]
♪ ♪
[PINS CLATTER]
Yes, yes. That's it. That's it.
Just keep doing your thing.
Keep doing your thing.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
- What'd I tell you, Mick?
- Shut up.
[GRUNTS]
If you don't get those two
to play nice,
we may never get out of here.
[LAUGHTER]
I think you've almost nailed it.
I'm thinking lace.
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
- Perfect.
- Yeah?
Yes, lace, it brings out
your skin tone.
Bigger with the veil.
♪ What have you got now,
I say hey, man ♪
Um...
- [SIGHS]
- Okay, so we're good.
- Nope.
- What?
You need something floral.
♪ Yeah, it's one of a kind ♪
♪ Yeah, just like me [CORK POPS]
♪ But I ain't reached my prime ♪
♪ Ain't got no suit ♪
- Ah, we're done.
- I love it.
- Good.
- What about a bustle?
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Oh, what have you got now ♪
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
All right, I got them all.
Oh, excellent.
We make a good team, Smokey.
John, when you started
dating my sister,
I was worried you'd be a bad influence.
I mean, most people you date
end up dead or worse.
But I can see how much
you've changed for the better.
You're a good man, John Constantine.
Well, I am glad to hear that, mate.
Now, shall we begin?
♪ ♪
Earth.
Water.
♪ ♪
Fire.
[GROANS]
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Are you okay?
[SHOUTING]
♪ ♪
It's gorgeous. Very on-trend.
- [CRASH]
- [GASPS]
What the hell was that?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
- Gary?
- It's nothing to worry about.
I'm sure you'll see Sara again.
What? What happened to her?
It's more what happened to us.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS] What the hell is going on?
Well, we were stuck
in the Temporal Zone
because Gideon couldn't find Earth,
and now, well, we're not
in the Temporal Zone, at least.
Trippy dress, Ava.
That's not what
I was going for, Behrad.
Why did no one tell me
we were stuck? Gary?
I was trying to distract you
so you wouldn't be upset.
Okay, so where the hell are we?
I cast a spell to bring us to Earth.
It's here somewhere.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There is something out there.
♪ ♪
[EERIE MUSIC] [PINS CLATTER]
We're at a floating
bowling alley in space.
Thank you, everyone here,
for making my day
about a floating bowling alley.
You dumdums stay here.
♪ ♪
Hi. Hello? Hi.
[KNOCKING]
- Ava?
- Sara, you're here.
What's with the bowling shirt?
Well, I'll tell you
about the bowling shirt
if you tell me
about this wedding dress.
The wedding... [GASPS]
Oh, my God.
I forgot that I was wearing it.
I was so mad at Gary because
he didn't tell me about...
Babe, you look gorgeous.
- Really?
- Yes.
Anyway, why won't these
freaking doors open?
Can we get a little help here, please?
League champs took control
of those doors.
No one enters without an invitation.
[GROANS]
What is that sweet man talking about?
Ugh, when we tracked down
that last pod,
We found this device,
and it zapped us here.
And now the only way for us to leave
is for us to beat
this team of alien bowlers
who are surprisingly good.
Wait, how did you find us?
Gideon couldn't find Earth,
so Constantine cast a spell
to bring the Waverider to
Earth, and it brought us here.
What, so you're saying that
Earth is in this bowling alley?
I guess. Who would be
a cruel enough jerk
to hide the Earth
in this bowling alley?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
♪ ♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hey, look at that. Light.
See that, Zari? Daylight.
Maybe everything will be fine.
Yeah, maybe everything will be fine.
Or maybe we're doomed.
Wait, what?
♪ ♪
What the hell is that?
[EARTH RUMBLING]
Earthquake!
♪ ♪
[PINS CLATTER]
- [LAUGHS]
- Yeah, whoo!
[RUMBLING SUBSIDES]
Everyone okay?
What the hell is going on?
What was that thing?
What the...
♪ ♪
Whoa.
Where is... everything?
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Hey.
- It's the end of the world.
Jamie, I can't die
without you knowing the truth.
I got a secret vasectomy,
and that's why you never get pregnant.
- Are you friggin' kidding me?
- Wait, wait, baby.
Not rock and roll, Jeff.
Not rock and roll at all!
If we have kids,
we won't be able
to afford our stuff, right?
Wait, wait, where are you going?
Into town to find someone
whose truck works.
Wait!
Oof.
That's rough.
Hey, am I a bad person
if I found that very, very enjoyable?
No, no, no. They're terrible people.
- Okay, good.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
Totally off topic...
but does that cloud
look like Mick to you?
[GROANS]
Yeah, from here,
you can tell how fragile
and beautiful it really is.
Coming through.
- [GASPS]
- Hey, take it easy!
- Uh...
- Oh.
♪ ♪
So you're literally bowling
with planet Earth?
That's why it's called cosmic bowling.
You go mano a mano for
the survival of your species,
and if you lose,
you and your entire home planet
get banished to our trophy shelf
for eternity. [CHUCKLES]
Wow, that's godlike power.
I'm not a god.
I'm just an average Joe
who loves to bowl
and destroy countless worlds.
- [LAUGHTER]
- You got it, Mike.
Buddy, wait, with this is your place.
Why don't you just
kick 'em out of here?
Can't. Rules say they can
stay as long as they're champs.
Now they've taken root and taken over.
It's your fault we're
playing this dumb game.
Place if full of bad energy now.
Hey, look, at least
I was being proactive
and trying to get us out of here.
Be less proactive.
They made the game so competitive,
no one wants to play here.
This team is falling apart.
Hey, yo.
Come on, Legends.
What are you waiting for?
You got a game to lose.
Let's get going.
They turned my bowling alley
into a bullying alley.
Game on. [CHUCKLES]
[FUNKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Damn it.
You're not listening to anything I say.
I am listening.
I'm just choosing to ignore you.
Bowling's stupid.
Bowling is not stupid,
you ignorant lug.
You can't control the ball
if your fingers aren't
in the hole, see?
- [BONES CRUNCH]
- [GROANS]
You son of a...
Oh, my God, I think I jammed it.
- Son of a...
- Ooh, that's gotta hurt.
All right, time-out! We're at time-out.
Let's take a walk. Come on.
We'll get you some ice, and we'll...
- This is stupid.
- Do something.
Okay, let's get ice.
We'll get some ice. All right.
[GROANS]
- Why did we come back here?
- We need a plan.
Okay, plan: I'll steel up.
You use your wind power.
- Shoot me like a bullet.
- No, we...
We need a plan for us.
- Us, us?
- Yeah.
You know,
I was thinking about it, and...
this will give us a chance
to end things amicably.
What?
The world is ending
and you wanna have
a relationship talk now?
Just trying to be mature
and... and... and pragmatic.
Okay, look, Zari,
I know we're gonna have
to spend time apart, like, a lot
so the timeline doesn't collapse,
but the time we do spend
together will be worth it.
I don't know, will it?
- Get your strike.
- Mm-hmm.
See, I feel like we're
on this doomed path
and just blindly
walking towards a cliff.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
All right, look, obviously I can see
dating a woman from another timeline
that's stuck in another
dimension might end bad.
Well, doesn't that mean
we shouldn't do it?
- [PINS CLATTER]
- Yeah!
[EARTH RUMBLING]
No.
Because the alternative is way worse.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Zari, I cannot stand
being away from you.
It actually hurts my heart.
♪ ♪
That is...
what I needed to hear.
♪ ♪
Mm-mm-mm-mm. But listen.
If we're gonna save
this relationship, we...
We need to go save the world first.
Yeah.
Okay.
♪ ♪
[ENERGY WHIRRING]
Rock and roll.
[SIGHS] I just...
I need to clear my head.
Okay.
Why the long face?
Well, Buddy, team's falling apart,
and every human being alive
is about to be annihilated.
Shame.
The way I see it, bowling is all about
bending elbows with friends
and wetting your beaks.
Best bowling happens when
you're not thinking at all.
Can't beat bad energy with bad energy.
You're right.
I've been going about this all wrong.
- Buddy, can you do me favor?
- Yeah.
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
[FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Nachos and fries,
breakfast of champions.
And a Cherry Coke for the lady.
Thank you, Buddy.
Whoa, the game isn't done yet.
The scoreboard looming over
our head is stressing us out,
and besides, it doesn't matter
if we win or lose
if we're not a team first.
You do realize
that the Earth gets destroyed
if we lose, right?
Well, okay, yes,
the outcome does matter,
but we're not gonna win
by tearing each other apart.
I mean, guys, we're not even losing
to the Pin Killers right now.
We're losing to ourselves.
And what we do from this moment on
decides the fate of our planet.
So I'm asking you,
are we losers, or are we Legends?
Huh, do I have a Legend?
Do I have a Legend?
There we go, that's that team spirit.
Cheers.
♪ ♪
Here.
There.
Thanks.
I suppose that's one good
reason to keep your gloves on.
- There's others.
- Hmm.
My past is not for everyone to see.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS] So, Astra,
we're gonna need you to roll.
I've never bowled before.
Not even once.
Come on, don't you wanna de-ball
that "Jersey Shore" wannabe?
Hmm?
♪ ♪
Welcome to the team.
Hey, I might know how you can bowl
and not have to take your gloves off.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC]
ALL: Rory, Rory, Rory, Rory!
Ah, here he goes.
♪ ♪
What...
[PINS CLATTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
That's what I'm talking about!
- Come on, Astra.
Come on, Astra.
Come on.
You got it.
[LAUGHTER]
- It's all right. That's okay.
- Told you this was a bad idea.
That was a great warm-up.
This is the one.
Breathe, breathe.
♪ I'm loud and restless again ♪
[PINS CLATTER]
- We'll take it.
- Whoo!
We'll take it! Yes, Astra!
♪ ♪
[BURPS]
- Darn it!
- No spare there, Clare!
Our bowling party
is definitely putting a cramp
in their style.
Gary, what are their chances?
At this point,
we're gonna need a miracle.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
We still don't really know
what's coming from the sky.
- A middle finger?
- What?
There's a dial here set to three,
but it goes all the way up to...
Well, Spooner
just drew a middle finger.
All right. Okay, let's go for that.
Middle finger it is.
Got this.
- Come on Mike, yeah!
- Come on, Mike!
[ENERGY WHIRRING]
Let's give it the middle finger.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
[FUNKY MUSIC]
What the hell was that?
- Poor Mikey Mike. Aww.
- Aww, you missed it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Wow, that is a lot of backdraft.
Would have been dumb
if we broke up for nothing.
♪ ♪
[TIME COURIER CHIMES]
My Time Courier's working.
Go!
♪ ♪
[TENDER MUSIC]
Oh, looks like you guys had a fun date.
Rad.
Oh, there's a whole
bowling thing going on.
Sort of high stakes.
Okay.
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
How we doing?
It's the last shot, and Astra's up.
[SIGHS]
- Sara, are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
Uh, if Gary's calculations are correct,
you guys can actually win this thing.
♪ ♪
But Astra needs to roll a strike.
[ELECTRONIC BLIPPING]
[PINS CLATTER]
Of course the stakes
couldn't be any higher
my first time bowling.
Look, it's gonna be all right.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
We need to change tactics.
It's a very classic style.
All you gotta do
is get right in the middle.
Nice, deep bend,
and roll it on through.
I left hell to bowl granny style?
[SIGHS] What has become of my life?
Hey, you got this, all right?
You have the whole team behind you.
♪ ♪
Here goes nothing.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
[LAUGHTER STOPS]
♪ ♪
[PINS CLATTER IN SLOW MOTION]
Go.
♪ ♪
Go. Go.
Go! Go!
♪ ♪
[ALL CHEERING]
[ELECTRONIC BLIPPING]
Yes!
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let's get out of here.
- Come on.
- Huh.
You forgetting something?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
How about a rematch?
Not a chance.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let's put you back where you belong.
[STRAUSS' "ALSO SPRACH ZARATHUSTRA"]
♪ ♪
How about that?
I control the alley once again
thanks to you,
and I say it's open for everyone!
- Yay.
- Babe! You did it!
[GASPS] Babe, hi!
- We're out of here.
- Rude.
Buddy, one last favor?
Another round of nachos for my friends?
- You bet.
- You're the best.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Aren't you curious?
I sense in you powers
both mighty and abundant.
Huh. Do you, now?
Well, you've a keen eye,
bowling alley denizen.
Keen eye.
♪ ♪
Powers that will be the death of you.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Sorry called bowling stupid.
Bowling means a lot to me.
The old man who fostered me
brought me to league night every week.
Helped me feel like
I belonged to something.
Well, you belong with us now.
You know it's bad luck
for you to see me in a wedding dress.
Look, babe, you looked amazing.
You look amazing in whatever you wear,
but I love you too much
to let you get married in that thing.
♪ ♪
It's great seeing folks
have a good time
in the bowling alley again.
How about a team photo?
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
[GROANING] Okay. All right. Come on.
Say cheese.
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com