- [EERIE MUSIC]
- _
- ♪ ♪
- I'm telling ya, I know what I saw.
- _
There was a dinosaur creature
runnin' right through my backyard.
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
You don't say.
And there were glowing lights
coming from the treetops.
You don't say.
And these giants orbs fell from the sky!
Then, after I came out of hidin',
they'd all disappeared.
Something ain't right.
Well, that's that.
Yeah, I'm kind of nervous.
Things rarely wrap up
in a neat, little bow for us.
Come on, babe, don't be paranoid.
Life, it's gonna start going our way.
[EXPLOSION]
ALL: Whoa!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What the hell happened?
Did that look like another
Waverider to you guys?
Why is someone trying to kill us?
There must be hundreds of reasons
why someone would want to kill us.
Well, we're not gonna let 'em
get away with it, are we?
I say we portal back in time
and on to that rogue Waverider
and make them pay.
That is a perfect plan.
Now let's go gear up,
'cause we're gonna storm that ship
and save our Waverider.
Remember, when we get on that ship,
stealth is our friend.
Silent takedown. Got it.
Wake me when the firefight starts.
You guys take out the crew,
and Behrad and I'll
take control of the ship.
Nate, let's do this.
Here we go.
[ELECTRIC ZAPPING]
It's out of juice.
- What?
- Every time with those things.
Wait, no time couriers, no Waverider...
we're stuck in 1925.
- [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- Everybody just calm down.
We just need a little time,
and we'll think of a plan.
Well, we definitely don't
belong in this time period.
We need to avoid any unwanted
attention from the locals.
[KNOCKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Afternoon, ma'am. Name's Pastor Hanson.
Is Gloria home?
Yeah, she's not here right now.
Oh. I just heard this, uh,
loud explosion over yonder,
and I wanted to make sure
everything's all right.
[FAKE COUGHING] Flash him.
What? Oh!
Well, you know, there's all sorts
of strange things happening in Odessa.
Everyone in town has seen
these bizarre lights in the sky
and strange lizard creatures
in their backyard.
Yeah, well, nothing strange around here.
Flash him.
It's out of battery. I don't...
Say, are those claw marks?
Yeah, I... I'll tell Gloria
you stopped by.
Goodbye now.
Hoo! So much for laying low.
So town's already buzzing
with conspiracy theories
after the Zaguron invasion...
you guys, if we stay here,
- it could get really bad.
- It's gonna be okay.
And now that we have no timeship,
we are just a bunch of weirdos
with truly random superpowers.
And John, the one person with
a useful ability, is gone, so...
Well, hey, I was his student.
I mean, I'm not
a master sorcerer yet,
but maybe I could...
What, turn the townspeople
into household objects?
- Come on.
- Too bad we don't have
the Time Bureau timeship or
it would have that fail-safe.
Gary, you're a genius.
The last time the Waverider
was impounded,
I had a fail-safe installed.
- And fail-safes are?
- T-they're indestructible
lockboxes filled
with emergency supplies,
like a time courier or a mind flasher.
Breath mints, if we're lucky!
You realize the blast
could've sent that thing
flying anywhere on Gloria's
property, right?
So, we will split up
so we can find this damn thing
and get the hell out of here.
Now, let's go. Come on!
How you holding up, Z?
If you want to talk, I'm here to listen.
I know a thing or two
about getting dumped.
I was not dumped.
It was a mutual mucking up of things.
I am, however, annoyed that
John poofed his way out of 1925
without making sure
the rest of us were okay first.
To be fair, when he left, we still had
a working time machine.
Defending him is not listening.
Right, sorry. Continue.
I just can't believe,
after everything
we went through together,
all he left me with was this.
Ooh, freaky old key.
- Yeah.
- What's it for?
All he said was, "You'll find out",
with his trademark dramatic delivery.
In hindsight,
I probably should've gotten
- a little more clarification.
- Probably.
Whatever! I'm just gonna do
what I always do in these situations.
I need a makeover.
No, no, no, not a makeover.
I need a reinvention.
Like Madonna.
I think there's a headpiece.
[SIGHS] Wandering through the woods.
Why am I not surprised
this is our honeymoon?
I know, babe, but as soon
as we find the safe,
we can get out of here, all right?
Yeah, well I'm way out
of my comfort zone.
- Which is?
- The Waverider.
- BOTH: Lists.
- Rules. Don't...
Well, mine is improvising, so together,
we are unstoppable.
Come on.
Based on the blast radius,
we're basically looking
for a needle in a haystack.
Look, I can track animals and people,
but random futuristic safes, not my bag.
All right, so what you got?
Any magical cheats to find this thing?
Yeah, I think I can remember
John's tracking spell.
Hmm.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Adiuva nos invenire aliquid.
[MAGICAL WHIRRING]
Hey, not bad.
[MYSTICAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I think someone moved it.
That's not good.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Where did you find it, anyway?
Amongst them bushes at the
edge of Gloria Cruz's property.
Okay, the good news,
we found the Waverider's safe.
- Oh!
- Yeah, bad news,
it's at the Sheriff's station.
Pastor found it nearby and turned it in.
That guy will come poking around again
now that he's even more
suspicious of your mom.
Yeah, and other neighbors could get nosy
and discover the remains
of the Waverider,
which would be disastrous
for the timeline.
We just need to buy
ourselves some time so we can
- come up with another plan.
- How?
We need to go on the defensive.
Right, and keep the heat off
of Gloria and this property.
And how are we supposed to do that?
If we don't have time travel
or mind flashers?
[GASPS]
Rule 44.
- Rule 44.
- Yeah.
- I love Rule 44!
- Yeah!
What's Rule 44?
Uh, it's from our Time Bureau training.
The intent of Rule 44
is to create a diversion,
a cover story, when things
go sideways on a mission.
Specifically, Rule 44 states
that our cover story
must be a circus.
That is oddly specific.
We talking Cirque? Sideshow?
Straight up three-ring affair?
No, research shows
that the general public
is willing to accept the bizarreness
of any kind of circus without question.
So we have to put on a circus?
What? No, we... he's not listening.
We just have to make them
think we're in a circus
to allay their suspicions.
[GASPS]
Group makeovers. Yes, I love it.
I'm gonna reinvent
each of you as performers.
Friends, you're in excellent hands.
Well, you heard her,
let's circus up, eh?
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
Good, 'cause I need your magic
to help fix my mom's porch.
- Sure.
- Hey, Nate,
while we are playing
defense as a circus,
you will be playing offense.
Time to use your superpower.
So, you want me to turn to steel
and knock around some skulls?
No, your other superpower.
You are a white man in 1925.
You go sweet talk that sheriff
and get him to give you the safe.
- Ava will go with you.
- What? No.
All right, come on, Gary.
Those period costumes
aren't gonna sew themselves.
[PLAYFUL OLD-TIMEY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[COUGHS]
Okay.
Yes.
Tie.
Button, please.
Mm, voilà.
My mom's not gonna be happy
when she sees
what we've done to her stuff.
Sorry, it's desperate times.
Oh! Nate borrowed your dead dad's suit.
Hope that's okay.
He better not ruin it.
Good afternoon, Odessa!
Come one, come all!
I know you have seen and heard
some peculiar things lately.
Well, I am here to assure you
that it is just business
as usual for us.
Why, you ask?
Because my compatriots and I,
we are members...
of the Guggenheim Circus.
[APPLAUSE]
You know, it's actually a very good fit.
Hey, do I look like a grandma?
- Yeah.
- [SIGHS]
- You the sheriff?
- Yes, sir.
I was just finishing up some paperwork.
How can I help you?
My name's John Edgar Hoover.
I'm the newly appointed director
of the Bureau of Investigation
in Washington, D.C.
This is my trusted secretary, Ms. Gandy.
You seem different in real life.
You probably saw an old photo.
I've been cocktailing my hair products.
But that's neither here or there.
Now listen up, Sheriff.
We're here to talk to you
about a very important matter.
There are so many exciting
things to see at our circus.
For example, exotic animals.
My cohort and I, we are animal handlers
from a land far, far, far away.
And of course,
what circus would be complete
without a little fire?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
That's hot, that's hot.
Ah. [LAUGHS]
Now, don't be alarmed,
but several of our creatures
escaped their confinements last night.
You may have, uh, heard some explosions
or seen some mysterious
lights yesterday.
That was just me,
testing out some, uh, displays.
True story, so if
you saw something yesterday
that looked like a dinosaur,
for example,
it was actually a Komodo dragon,
which is just a big, smelly lizard,
despite it's terrifying appellation.
Pastor Hanson found this strange box
over by Gloria Cruz's property.
I thought maybe it belonged to her,
since she's foreign and all.
Oh, well, we can tell you for sure
that it's not hers, sir,
but it is very dangerous.
Say, how did you boys
in Washington learn
about the safe so quickly?
The pastor only found it this morning.
[SCOFFS] I mean, if I told you
all of our nation's secrets,
they wouldn't be secrets
anymore, would they?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] Yes.
And who knows, there may even
be a commendation for you
from President Warren G. Harding,
once the case is declassified, you know.
I believe she means Calvin Coolidge,
'cause Mr. Harding is dead.
People always get their
interwar presidents mixed up.
I need you to focus.
Are you ready to do the right
thing by your country?
Mister, mister,
tell us when the circus is.
I want to go.
When is it, you ask?
Like, uh, exactly what time?
You told them what?
I'm sorry, Sara, I just panicked.
I didn't mean to invite
the whole town over tonight.
Just take a breath, Gary.
We'll figure something else out.
Okay, wait, you're saying
people are coming here
for an actual circus?
[OVERLAPPING TALKING] Gary!
All right, all right, everyone!
Just calm down.
Everything's gonna be fine
once we open the safe.
Ah! That's right.
When the whole town comes over,
we flash the hell out of 'em,
and then we time courier
our butts out of here!
- Yes! All right.
- Classic. Classic.
That's right, another successful
Legend missions in the books!
Ugh, it feels so good
to be back on track.
All right.
- [WHIRRING]
- _
Hm?
There's no time courier.
There's a note.
"Taking courier, beer run. Rory".
- Classic.
- What?
There's no couriers,
there's no flashers.
There's no...
At least there's a Time Bureau manual.
And gummy bears.
That's where I stashed
my emergency supply.
So that's it. Just a book
and some gummies.
- No couriers.
- No flashers.
- No mini-Gideon.
- No breath mints.
Hey, look, it's okay.
You guys, it's gonna be okay.
Look, as long as the town
keeps buying our cover story,
then we'll come up with plan B.
It's gonna be great.
That fella wasn't Mr. Hoover at all!
Hair products, my foot.
Is this the Bureau of Investigation?
This is Sheriff Thomas Wood
of Odessa, Texas.
I've got a situation down here
you ought to know about.
Wow, so we're really doing this?
We're living in 1925 for a spell.
1925 is a total hayseed year.
These people are covered in sunspots.
Microdermabrasion, still decades away.
Main thing I know about the '20s is that
they invented a lot of dance moves.
Maybe we should get out
of this small town
- and find the parties...
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, that goes against Rule 23,
which states that in order
to limit potential damage
to the timeline, marooned time
travelers should stay in one...
one location.
Okay, then we will stay put. All right?
We'll figure it out. First things first,
we got the whole town
coming over tonight,
and they are expecting a circus.
We have to put on a show
to protect our cover.
If there is no circus,
they may inadvertently
- see the Waverider wreckage...
- Whoa!
Which violates, like,
half of this manual.
- That cannot happen.
- Okay, well,
I just hope that
we get this done before...
Mami!
- You're early!
- ALL: Hi!
It looks like the humans
won the War of the Worlds.
We're all still here. [CHUCKLES]
Mija, tell me, why are people in town
asking about a circus on my property?
We need to talk.
Are those my curtains?
- Is that Celso's suit?
- Yes.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
I don't see how this circus act
gets us any closer
to getting out of here.
This is just triage, Astra.
Dealing with the problem at hand.
Without the Waverider,
we don't have a lot of options.
So if we are to convince
these town people
that we are actually a circus,
we need to practice. Let's go.
Want those juggling skills on point!
- You juggle, right?
- Is it that obvious?
They need to distract everyone
from seeing the remains of the timeship,
which blew up.
After the aliens attacked the house,
and we were saved by space mushroom...
[SIGHS] Look, mija,
I'm already on thin ice here.
It's not easy for these people
to accept a magical hero
from another land living in their town.
But I trust you.
And if I am ostracized
or arrested,
then so be it, I'll deal with it.
Because you're my daughter,
and I would do anything for you.
[EXCITING CIRCUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Looking good, looking good.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm pulling the plug on this circus.
What? What's wrong?
Look, what's wrong is
that this circus is going
to bring a lot of unwanted
attention to my mom,
and she already feels persecuted.
This isn't just about us anymore.
Every time we try to fix something,
we just dig a bigger hole,
and my mom is going to be
the one stuck paying for it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Look, we're sorry, Spooner.
You're right. This isn't just about us.
We'll get out of town and...
we'll figure something else out.
No more circus, no more commotion.
Thank you.
Where's Astra?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Surge a mortuis.
- What are you doing?
- What does it look
like I'm doing?
Well, it looks like
you're trying to fix the ship
using John's resurrection spell,
but that would be stupid,
because it's for humans,
not for timeships.
If John were here, this is
exactly what he would do.
Now shut up and let me concentrate.
You might want to stand back.
♪ ♪
[DOOR SHUTS]
- Sheriff Thomas Wood?
- In the flesh.
You called the office in D.C.
about someone impersonating
a federal agent,
namely me.
J. Edgar Hoover.
Luckily, we were just
down the way in Midland,
so I thought I'd pay you a visit myself.
Welcome to Odessa.
I can't believe
the top lawman in the country
is standing in my very own station.
Again! The real one this time.
Now, tell me more about this scoundrel.
♪ ♪
Surge a mortuis.
[MAGICAL WHOOSHING]
Surge a mortuis!
[METAL CLANKING]
♪ ♪
Is she doing what I think she's doing?
Whatever it is,
it's pretty cool.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
It's likely that this
imposter is a member
of the Midland Robbery Gang,
an outfit we've been
tracking for some time.
- Bank robbers.
- That's right.
And you just handed that degenerate
a brand new safe to crack.
Now, which way did he go?
Hell's bells, he could
be anywhere by now.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Astra? Maybe you should stop.
You know, 'cause of the blood?
If John could do this, I can do this.
Damn it, Astra, stop it!
Multi facti sunt...
[ELECTRIC ZAPPING]
Astra!
[EXPLOSION]
[DISTANT RUMBLING]
Well, Sheriff, I reckon I know just
where this imposter is trying
to blow open that safe.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GROANS QUIETLY]
Ow.
Mm.
I feel like I was run over by a bus.
Ow.
And since isn't the med bay,
I'm guessing my spell didn't
resurrect the Waverider.
No, it didn't.
What were you thinking?
Hey, a little sympathy?
I got injured trying to help you.
By creating another huge
spectacle at my mom's house.
Not what she needs right now.
I was the only one doing anything
to get this clown show out of Texas.
Think it through next time.
No offense, but your mom
lives in the boonies.
I doubt anyone noticed.
[CAR ENGINE APPROACHING]
Someone did.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Guys, it's J. Edgar Hoover.
The real one.
He's gonna want to know who we are.
So, we are doing the circus!
No, no! Esperanza and I,
we will talk to the men.
Astra has to stay in bed,
but the rest of you cannot be here.
- Okay, um...
- Go, hide!
It's too open concept in here to hide!
Bedroom, bedroom. Go, go.
Go, go, go.
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Evening, ladies. J. Edgar Hoover,
Bureau of Investigation.
Which one of you is Gloria Cruz?
I am.
How can I help you, sir?
I've heard about some
bank robbers in the area.
Unsavory fellas.
Just checking to make sure you're safe.
Oh, well, no bank robbers.
Just enjoying a quiet afternoon.
If you don't mind,
I was talking to the owner
of the property in question.
- I don't think it's working.
- Why not?
- Shh.
- Try the closet.
- It's locked.
- Zari, the key.
John said we'd find out what it's for.
Maybe it's this.
Okay.
Fine.
[GASPS]
No!
[WHOOSHING]
I think we'll have a look around.
Just to be sure.
I have a patient in there.
She's recuperating.
[FLOORBOARDS CREAK]
Go, go. Just go, go, go.
Where are we?
♪ ♪
The Mansion?
Hey.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
So if we're in the Mansion,
does that mean it's present-day?
Did we make it out of 1925?
No, and yes.
But we're not in any year at all.
Gary.
This isn't really the Mansion.
It's a pocket dimension
that John made for himself.
John wanted a place
where he could be all alone,
so he... he conjured it.
So, if we go out the front door...
[FLAMES WHOOSHING]
[SCREAMING]
Is this a pocket dimension
in Hell, Gary?
I'd recommend only exiting
through the door we came in.
Why would John give me this place?
Is it possible that man is so conceited
he thinks I need an alternate
dimension to get over him?
I don't know everything about John,
but I know he loved you.
Maybe he just thought
you could use a nice,
quiet place to be alone,
out of the spotlight for once?
Out of the spotlight?
B, I thrive in the spotlight.
It's where I'm most me.
You're acting like I need to
find myself,
but I'm not hiding. It...
[GROANS]
There's an answer in here somewhere.
It's just a book of rules, babe.
Rules we should be following, okay?
We almost ruined Gloria's life,
and we almost interacted with Hoover,
which means we almost changed history.
Yeah, but we didn't, huh?
Just...
Babe.
Hey, will you look at me?
I know it feels like
the walls are closing in,
- but we will figure this out.
- You keep saying that.
Okay, Sara? But we're getting sloppy.
And without memory flashers
or time couriers or Gideon to guide us,
we are lost, okay?
And you really think
that manual will help?
Probably not, but I just...
I need to.
- Okay.
You keep reading.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I have reason to suspect
that the Midland Robbery Gang
are holed up around here.
Sheriff Wood said
one of the gang members
got ahold of a peculiar safe
that was in his possession.
Mind if we search your property, ma'am?
Does it really matter
if I say yes or no?
Smart woman.
Okay, I overheard Hoover leaving.
All right, guys, let's go!
Hey, you coming?
Actually, I think I'm gonna just
stay for a little bit.
Oh, good for you, sis.
And in case you feel like
slowing things down a little...
What does that mean?
Oh, brother.
[MAGICAL WHIRRING]
Come on.
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
- You're back.
How did Hoover not see you guys?
Oh, we just hopped over
to another plane of existence
where space and time
don't function normally.
- No big whoop.
- You know, we could just
hide out in the Mansion.
We'd be out of Gloria's way.
Hiding isn't gonna get us
back to our timeline
or help us figure out
who blew up our ship.
- So, where do we go?
- New York City.
Guys, the manual mentions
an obscure scientist
who laid the foundation
for all of time travel,
a guy named Dr. Gwynn Davies.
He's alive right now, in 1925,
and he lives in New York.
- That could work.
- Right?
And you're okay if we leave here?
I guess, as long as we have a plan.
Good, because y'all gotta go.
I mean, J. Edgar Hoover's
suspicious of my mom.
Thinks she's harboring
some bank robbers,
the Midland Gang or something.
Hoover's indefatigable.
He's a bloodhound.
He won't let go of our scent
until he's won.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Then let's give him what he wants.
Make him think he was right.
We will be the bank robbers.
We'll lead him out of Texas,
away from Gloria,
and all the while, making
our way to New York City.
Bank robbers were a big deal
in the 1920s.
And we'd certainly grab his attention.
Yeah, and all we have to do
is rob some banks.
I mean, yes, please...
Can I just have a word
with you for a minute?
You want to go on a crime spree?
I mean, I don't even like
the idea of leaving this house,
but since we have to... listen to me,
we need to make very small footprints.
And remember, we don't
even have our equipment.
- What if somebody...
- Babe, look, you're right.
And I'm scared too.
But I believe in us,
and I believe in our team.
We're more than
time travel and superpowers
and gadgets and manuals.
We are the Legends,
and we can pull this off.
I know we can.
And as soon as we can time travel again,
we'll go and fix all
the changes that we made.
You can make a... you can make a list
of timeline IOUs.
You love lists.
And then we will cross
them off, every single one.
- Every single one.
Hmm?
Mm! Fine.
All right, crime spree it is.
But just until we can time travel again.
I'd like to stay here
with my mom for a bit.
Astra should say too,
until she's fully recovered.
Okay, we'll just pick you guys up
after we help invent time travel.
Guys.
Hoover's back.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Y'all are gonna get my mom arrested.
Gloria!
Do you have any rope?
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Gloria Cruz,
you've been withholding information.
It's the Midland Gang. They just left.
They forced us to cooperate!
They said they were going to kill us.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Come on, babe, let's go!
- Hurry, Sara!
- I'm coming, hold on!
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Get in the car!
Come on, Nate! Come on, come on, get on!
- See ya later, J. Edgar!
- Whoo!
Should've peed before we left Gloria's.
[SUAVE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
Hmm.
Sorry.
♪ ♪
[GUNSHOT]
Hit the floor, boys, this is a robbery.
♪ ♪
Not our first rodeo.
Whoa, sorry, little lady.
Uh, bank's closed.
Little lady? Who do you think you are?
Why are your teeth so pretty?
Fluoride.
Now, you heard me. Go on, get. Get!
This is a robbery.
I know robberies.
You're running crowd control.
Ya heard the lady.
Get on the ground.
And you, I want you to go to the safe
and get me $93.65.
Okay, okay.
- 93...
- Yeah.
I did the calculation, babe.
It's all we need
to get to New York City.
Small footprints, you promised.
- And give me the money!
- Well, actually,
I have enough here in the till.
No need to open the safe.
All right, look.
We weren't gonna say anything
till after the robbery, but come here.
[WHISPERING] We're the Midland Gang.
- No, way!
- Yeah.
I love the Midland Gang!
Huge fan.
[GUNSHOT]
I said get all the way
down on the ground, boys.
Ava keeps shooting the ceiling.
She hates ceilings.
Two women?
There's no women in the Midland Gang.
You can steal money from a bank, fine.
But you don't steal
somebody's gang name!
All right, lady, look,
we don't have a gang name.
- Okay?
- Well, gotta have a gang name.
It's patriotic.
Oh, oh, what about
the Legends...
of Tomorrow?
Uh, it's wordy.
It is.
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
The Bullet Blondes.
Well, it's not just Sara and Ava.
We're in the gang too.
They're doing all the heavy lifting.
Bullet Blondes.
Damn it, B, it is catchy.
- Hmm, the Bullet Blondes.
- The Bullet Blondes.
The Bullet Blondes.
This robbery is the work
of the Bullet Blondes!
The Bullet Blondes!
You gotta be kidding me.
Now, y'all gonna put your heads down
and count to 100,
and pretend you never saw us.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
Ooh, wait, wait, and, um,
go about your lives like
none of this ever happened,
completing any historically
significant events
you might otherwise have done.
Let's go.
Make way for the Bullet Blondes!
Whoo, the Bullet Blondes! Whoo-hoo!
Thank you all for you cooperation!
Sorry about the guns!
The Bullet Blondes! Bullet Blondes!
The Bullet Blondes, I like it.
Have to admit you were right, babe.
That went off without a hitch.
Guess we're the Bullet Blondes now.
[CROWD CHEERING]
♪ ♪
Come on, Gary, let's go!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Whoo! $93.65 never felt so sweet.
I don't think that's gonna
change history,
but I am gonna write it down
on our to-do ledger,
just to be sure that it doesn't.
Hopefully Hoover is on our scent.
He's gonna follow us out of town,
away from Gloria's house.
Next stop, New York City.
- Whoo!
- Uh-oh.
Guys, something's up ahead.
What he already roadblocked us?
Damn, that Hoover works fast.
He's indefatigable.
It's over, Bullet Blondes.
Get out of the car and put
your hands on the ground.
- Gun it.
- What?
Are you sure?
I bet he's a pretty good aim
with that gun.
That's a good point.
Nate, get behind the wheel
in case he opens fire. Come on, Gary,
Let's go, come on, let's go.
- Go, Gary.
- [STRUGGLING]
Feet out of my face.
- [EXHALES]
- Oh, God, oh, God.
- All right, let's do it.
- Everyone else,
get down, get down, get down.
I said small footprints, Sara.
Don't worry about it, babe.
We'll fix everything, I promise.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNFIRE]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[BULLETS RICOCHETING]
♪ ♪
Whoo!
Yeah!
We made it!
- [THUMPING]
- Did you guys hear something?
Yeah.
[BREATHLESS] Oh! It's a fan...
- What?
- It's a fabbable.
- What are you trying to say?
- Something about bubbles.
- Indefatigable!
- What?
[ALL SCREAM]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, my...
- what did you do?
- I don't know.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
This is not happening.
This is not happening!
Hoover can't die.
Hoover... Hoover can't die!
- [GRUNTS]
- Oh!
Oh, my God. Thank God, he's alive.
Indefatigable.
[MUMBLING]
What? What'd he say? What'd he say?
- I don't know.
- What'd you say?
I said... [WHEEZES]
"I never miss twice".
[GUNSHOT]
- Ah!
- Oh!
♪ ♪
I killed J. Edgar Hoover.
I killed J. Edgar Hoover!
I didn't mean to. I didn't mean to.
That was... that was...
- Sara, I am sorry.
- I know, I know.
He's, uh, very important
to the timeline.
The timeline? The timeline is ruined.
History is ruined, and
we don't even have Gideon here
to tell us how badly we've ruined it.
That's it.
I want to die. Goodbye.
I give up.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye.
- Goodbye!
- Babe?
Did we break Ava?
Hey, hey, babe, you okay?
- No.
- Yeah, you're okay.
Look, I know I talked you
into this plan,
and it has admittedly gone sideways.
But we are... we're
pretty committed, okay?
So we gotta see this one through.
- I can't...
- Yes, you can, and then
when we get back to 2021,
we are gonna go on a real honeymoon.
It'll be on the beach,
we'll walk hand-in-hand.
We'll... we'll listen to one
of your Stabcast podcasts
and watch the sunset. It'll be like...
Stabcast. [GASPS]
That's it.
There are no witnesses.
We're lucky.
We gotta hit the road, fast.
But first,
we gotta get rid of the body.
- Ava?
- Gary, that's your job.
Lose the glasses.
Oh!
You want me to eat
one of the most important figures
of the 20th century?
We gotta get to New York,
and we gotta there fast.
We gotta find this Gwynn Davies
without messing up
the timeline any more,
and the first thing to do
is to eat this body.
What has gotten into you?
I have been reading true
crime stories my entire life.
This is my time to shine.
Shut up and eat up, Gary.
You're in the Bullet Blondes now.
I'm a Bullet Blonde?
I swear I take no pleasure in this.
Beyond just the taste of human meat,
which as you know, I find...
quite delicious.
Do it, Gary.
♪ ♪
[GRUMBLING]
Astra, you're up.
Yeah, thought I'd make myself useful.
That's very sweet.
You're capable of so much more
than picking vegetables.
I have just recovered.
You have a terrible bedside manner.
Tell me, what did you do
to hurt yourself so much?
I tried to perform a spell
that I wasn't ready for,
and it nearly destroyed me.
My former mentor would be
so disappointed
if he were here right now,
saying I have to be willing
to walk alone
and risk it all if I want to succeed.
You know, my mother was a great healer.
She taught me everything that she knew.
But I was terrible at it.
It wasn't until I was able
to cast off her training,
start fresh in a way
that reflected who I am,
that I truly became a healer myself.
Yeah, but...
walk alone, sacrifice yourself,
that's what magic is about.
Your mentor taught you
how he did magic, yeah?
But you're not him.
R.I.P.
So you're just gonna bury
the pieces of the Waverider?
Well, it ain't gonna bury itself.
I'm gonna miss the old girl.
Really?
Astra Logue getting sentimental.
Look, I'm sorry
I brought the cops to your mom's place.
I don't blame you
for being pissed about it.
No, I get it. You were trying to help.
I wasn't just trying
to help you, though.
I was trying to prove myself
to replace John.
I just wanted to show everyone
that I was worthy,
which I guess I'm not.
John?
We don't need another John.
We need you.
Astra, I wasn't mad about the cops.
I wasn't happy about them,
but I was upset that you almost died.
I like having you around.
You're like my best friend.
No one's ever said that to me.
But you're mine too.
Good.
And if anything goes wrong,
we'll handle it.
I got your back.
You know, it's too bad.
I almost finished that spell.
You didn't finish it?
No, it was too much for me.
I bet John would've finished it.
Unum.
That was the last word.
Unum? Sounds mysterious.
Wish Gideon was here
to make us a nice steak.
Steak? Okay, I wish Gideon was here
to make us a drink.
- BOTH: Mezcal.
- Eh?
[WHOOSHING]
Who the hell is that?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Ay, dios mio.
BOTH: Gideon?
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -