THEOG, HIMACHAL PRADESH
Let me go!
Leave me…
Release me!
Let go of me!
It's confirmed, boss. He's our target.
No…
Don't kill me.
Ask him to text me
after transferring the money.
Where is that guy? What's he doing inside?
He may land us in trouble.
What, boss?
- Boss, my foot!
- Okay, boss.
THEOG, HIMACHAL PRADESH
Breaking news for our viewers!
The news I'm about to share
has never happened earlier in this area.
It's a rampage all around.
A hyena has been spotted here.
Saffron TV will give you
live updates by the minute.
People from nearby villages
have gathered here.
We have no idea
what the hyena is going to do.
Tell me, Joshy.
Sathya, I tried to call Parthiban.
His phone is not reachable. Where's he?
He must have gone
to drop Siddhu at school.
Try calling Siddhu.
His phone will be in the car.
If he gets in touch,
please ask him to call me.
Handle this properly!
Place a barricade there. Hurry up!
- Kumar.
- Sir?
- What's happening?
- Sir, nothing's right here. Everything…
Sir, nothing is right here.
- If it continues, many will be injured.
- Whom have they sent?
Two experts have come
from Wildlife SOS team.
They've handled only cheetahs,
but this is a hyena.
Nobody knows how to handle this, sir.
Parthiban, we have a situation.
It's an emergency.
Can you come here?
All right. First, see the photo
that I've sent you.
Footprints are large.
Maybe it's a spotted hyena.
If so, it will be extremely ferocious.
Okay. How soon can you get here?
Promise me, you won't tell your mom
that you were late for school today.
You promise me that you won't tell mom
that I took my phone to school
just for today.
Please, Dad!
The situation
is not under control, Parthiban.
Hyenas are social animals, Joshy.
They live in packs.
If a hyena is alone here,
either it has lost its way
or the rest of its clan is dead.
People will fear it and try to kill it.
But we have to capture it alive.
If you think like your men,
it will feast on us happily.
What to do now? What are you suggesting?
Walkie-talkie.
- Hey, Channel 3. We are on Channel 3.
- Got it.
Dad, I'll come along. I'll be helpful.
Stay in the car, my dear son.
That will be the biggest help.
I don't want to get chided by your mom.
Okay?
Put it! Put up the barricades.
Push it here, quickly. Hurry up. Come on.
- Why did you place the barricades?
- DFO's orders, sir.
Watch out.
Do it fast!
Sir, why did you place
the barricades here?
The animal will barge into the school.
It's risky. Please remove it.
Ranger, listen to me.
I'll give you my uniform.
Do my job as well.
Scoundrel!
What are you all looking at?
- Make it fast.
- Come in, Parthiban.
- Yeah, Joshy.
- They think it's a joke.
I don't know what to do.
The situation is out of control.
Get a tranquilizer from the sanctuary.
I'll tell you from where to fire.
Yes, okay.
Catch it…
It's scared and is looking
for a place to hide.
They are trying to kill it
without understanding that.
So, the hyena will
soon enter the school.
Bring the tranquilizer
to the west end of the school.
Help!
Help…
All the kids should go in!
Kids, get inside!
Students,
go to your classrooms immediately.
It's an emergency! Teachers and staff!
Please take all the children
safely into the classrooms.
There is no time. Hurry up!
Get in…
Go. Get in!
I got permission for a tranquilizer gun.
I'm taking it, okay?
Okay.
Give it to me.
Parthiban.
I'm in position.
Joshy, wait!
Don't aim at its neck
like our usual procedure.
Its striking force will be as heavy
as its pitch of laughter.
Aim for the lungs!
Shoot.
Darn.
- Hang on.
- This is the perfect time. Shoot, Joshy.
The gun is jammed, Parthiban.
A gun can't adapt
to the situation and operate.
It's a machine.
You need to service it every month.
- Siddhu?
- Dad.
Get your spear.
- Give your shoe lace to Joshy.
- Okay, Dad.
- Don't go…
- Run away.
You heard your dad, right?
Give me your shoe laces.
- Uncle, give the javelin to me.
- What?
Get inside!
Let's go!
Parthiban, the spear you asked for
is on its way.
- Tell my dad that I'm throwing it.
- Parthiban, here it comes!
Hey, come on, move.
Who is he?
Who is that man?
His name is Parthiban.
He's a Malayali.
Animal rescuer.
He runs a coffee shop nearby.
Hey!
- Get inside.
- Please, sir.
Come on, start.
Wait a minute.
Ask the questions in an order.
The DFO will answer you.
Look. This issue is not something
out of the ordinary.
It is our daily job.
Animals migrate
in search of food…
We've got exclusive news.
Why don't you cover it?
There's nothing to cover here.
These forest officers didn't do anything.
A middle-aged man in a white shirt
that was tucked in.
Find him and get
the real information from him.
That is exclusive.
- White shirt. Middle-aged man?
- Yes.
Where do I find him in this crowd?
Thalapathy
Thalapathy!
You wanted a shirt urgently.
- What happened?
- Stitch it and bring it.
- What's this? It's blood-stained.
- Stitch it.
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
- Hi, chief.
- Hi.
- Morning.
- Morning, sir.
My life is in this town…
Hi, Thalapathy!
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down…
Why isn't the temperature increasing?
Some problem with the thermostat, sir.
I've called the service team.
They will visit today.
- The cakes are ready for delivery.
- Okay.
Can we dispatch them, sir?
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Just an ordinary person
Yeah
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah, I'm just a…
Sir, this shirt is ripped badly.
It can't be stitched.
Do you know which shop
my wife bought this from?
- I don't know.
- I'm in trouble.
Hey, what's going on?
How did the police get our photos?
They are checking
at the borders and checkpoints.
Those who told us to kill the collector
double-crossed us.
Not only that, they leaked our photos.
Don't go out for a week. Hide yourself.
Please don't get caught.
Go to the hills.
What do you mean?
Where can we go right away?
The four of us have no clue
what is going to happen.
We trusted you and
you got us into trouble.
Do you think I'm mad?
We can't go anywhere.
We don't have money.
We can't hide anywhere.
Help us to come back.
Understand the situation.
All those who were against the collector
are under radar.
It will take a week
to get help from the Center.
Don't call me again. I'll call you.
- Now hang up!
- Hey…
Why are you looking at me?
Eyes on the road!
What, boss?
In the early hours of yesterday morning,
some unknown men
broke into the collector's guesthouse
have throat-slit and brutally murdered…
You didn't get ready yet?
Oh, my shirt?
I spilt chocolate on it,
so I put it to wash and changed…
I bought you that shirt
for our anniversary.
You've ruined it in every way possible.
I have nothing to say now, let it be.
My mood won't change today
no matter what excuse you give.
Do whatever you want.
There's no change in my plan.
I'm leaving in an angry mood.
Half of my soul is yours
You are the light of my eyes
Your love is piercing like a weapon
This brave warrior's heart
Your hair is soft like flowers and shiny…
Shall we pick up the kids from school?
You are the love of my life…
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
- Hi.
Yes, tell me.
Chintu…
M-Mathi's mother is unwell.
Siddharth's father isn't well.
I want to take her home.
- Who are you?
- His mom.
Her dad.
Like a snowflakes in the wind
I rose up just for you
Only love…
- A small peg?
- No, I don't drink.
- It's healthy and good for the weather.
- Really?
- How do you drink this, sir?
- True that!
- Dad.
- Don't be afraid.
We will be adopting this hyena.
What name would you suggest for it?
Elsa.
Ghost.
Hachiko.
I'll suggest a name,
but you guys shouldn't laugh.
Actually, Subramani sounds good, right?
Everyday, when I wake up…
Look ahead!
I want you with me
Your love is piercing like a weapon
This brave warrior's heart
- Chintu, come here.
- No, no.
- Come on, it's okay.
- Okay, go.
Slowly.
Come.
You'll hug me, with your chest
as my divine headrest…
Do you like him?
Your love is piercing like a weapon
This brave warrior's heart
Open it.
Chintu.
You're not supposed to help.
Please wait.
Go! Hurry!
Sir, no.
- Is the shop on the left or right?
- Over there, sir.
Give me the bill.
Sir, your shop seems empty.
When do you have regular consumers?
They will come after 6:00 p.m.
- Good day, sir.
- Bye.
We don't have any luck here.
Shall we go elsewhere?
What do you say?
We will wait.
Six o'clock.
He and his useless thugs
will be the death of me.
I don't know what will happen.
Everyone on the road is panic-stricken
and running around.
At that time, the serial killer
stands in the middle of the road
and shoots blindly.
There's already a pile of corpses
on the road.
He is notorious.
He shoots whomever he sees.
At that time, a brave and bold
police officer arrives
and fires at the serial killer.
The serial killer runs and hides.
The police officer reloads the gun
and in that gap, the serial killer fires.
Hey…
So the wounded police officer
falls at your feet.
He falls behind the car where
you were safely hiding.
Now the police officer's gun
is in your hand
and you have a clean shot.
The serial killer doesn't know
that you are there
but you can easily shoot him
from your position.
We got only 300 rupees.
And just this phone.
Get rid of this
and look for a bigger vehicle.
And you have an easy way out.
You can even escape
without being seen by anyone.
What will you do? Picture yourself.
I'll just sleep.
Oh! Will you just sleep?
- Yes.
- Siddhu, it's getting late. Go to bed.
Wait, Mom. Just two minutes.
I'll take the easy way out
and bring in more police officers.
By then, the serial killer
will kill more innocent people.
When the moon sails by
In the night blue sky
She showers love and makes me yearn…
I'll give the gun to the police officer.
And say,
'Look, here's a clear shot, fire.'
He's bleeding, dude. How can he shoot?
Picture yourself.
P-Please help…
- What is the number?
- Please!
She's a nuisance…
- Hello? Wait.
- Where are you, dear?
Here.
Ask for ATM PIN. Say that
I'll kill him.
- We can't move due to the police.
- Tell me.
- Please do...
- Don't raise your voice at me!
I would've been better off
marrying a tree instead.
Help me!
- PIN?
- Please don't hurt me.
- What's the PIN?
- Don't hurt me.
- Please.
- No.
- What's the PIN?
Please don't.
Then I'll shoot him myself.
If you shoot him,
you'll also become a murderer.
It is against the law.
Think of something else.
Picture yourself.
Hey! Why did you shoot him?
How did you get this gun?
- PIN?
- What?
PIN?
I don't know what else to say, Dad.
Whichever way you see it,
my hands will be blood stained.
How does it matter if it's the blood
of a saint or a sinner?
Siddhu, go.
Go upstairs and sleep. It's getting late.
Chintu, come.
Dad!
The only option is to shoot him.
Shoot whom?
The killer in the picture-yourself story.
Picture yourself?
I already told you.
Then you'll also be a murderer.
You'll end up in jail.
You can't even sleep peacefully.
Is that okay?
I won't be sent to jail.
I'll be sent to a juvenile home.
And if I'm lucky,
I'll get a sewing machine.
I Googled it.
Go!
- What were you busy chatting?
- Nothing.
What time is the wedding?
We'll drop them at the school
and reach on time.
He knows everything, right
up to getting a sewing machine!
Both of you, please sign.
Congrats.
Are you guys witnesses?
Please come and sign.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much.
I'll see you guys.
- Bye.
- Yeah, see you, sir.
You can touch her only after I say so.
Take good care of her.
- Bye.
What about you, madam?
I've some work in the record room.
I'll go home by myself after that.
Do you wish to say anything?
Stop telling Siddhu
such nonsense picture-yourself stories.
- Why? What happened?
- Show me your phone.
Browser history.
Browser history? Mine or his?
- His, of course.
- Oh!
"How to hunt? How to kill a deer?"
"How to kill a hyena?"
"How to get successful in life..."
Is it a joke?
No, I'm just reading it.
Who taught him all this?
How does he know?
Okay, I'll ensure
this doesn't happen again.
- I'll keep an eye too!
- Okay.
Great horned owl, Joshy.
It's already
in the protected species' list.
Where did you get this?
Sir, this owl is from Australia.
We caught it. We know about it.
- He's lying, sir.
- I'll slap you!
Why are you courting trouble?
How many more owls did you catch?
Just this one, sir.
I hit it with my slingshot.
It fell down unconscious.
Joshy, inform Blue Cross.
It needs immediate treatment.
Send for our veterinary doctor too.
He's no more.
- What?
- Yeah, I forgot to tell you.
He died on the spot
in a car accident last night.
I think he lost control
and fell headlong into the valley.
Yeah.
What?
Okay, I'll come. Yeah.
It's not a car accident.
But a planned murder
of the veterinary doctor.
Murder? How come?
He was shot dead.
I just got the information.
Did they use a gun in our town?
Last week, when the sub-collector died
I thought it was a hit-and-run case,
but now the veterinary doctor…
Looks like a killing spree.
I don't get it, Joshy.
I've been living here
for the past 20 years.
I've never heard of anything like this.
How did anyone get a gun
in this town, Joshy?
Parthiban, why are you anxious?
We'll take care of it.
I'll go now and check.
Shall I come along?
Last week, when the sub-collector died,
I thought it was a hit-and-run case.
But now, the veterinary doctor.
Looks like a killing spree.
Dad, it is your turn.
Dad!
- Your turn.
- Okay.
My sweet honey, dark as ebony
Why did you become my fair lady?
I won't touch you, my princess
But if I do, I can't stop my caress
My sweet honey, dark as ebony
Why did you become my fair lady?
I won't touch you, my princess
But if I do, I can't stop my caress
My king is so handsome
With a smile so winsome
Love-goosebumps you give me
I won't let you go Scot-free
Without you caressing me
Shall we share our desire
Like the warmth of blazing fire?
Soft as cotton am I and ready
Shall we ignite in rhapsody?
Shall we share our desire
Like the warmth of blazing fire?
Soft as cotton am I and ready
Shall we ignite in rhapsody?
My sweet honey, dark as ebony…
Sir, I've finished work. May I leave now?
Sir, don't tease me.
I'm going back to the hostel.
Go.
My song is much better than yours.
Wait for the next special item.
Shall I play it?
First look there.
The shop is closed, sir.
Thirupaachi…
I want chocolate coffee.
It's closed, sir.
Didn't you see the sign outside?
Chocolate coffee.
- The shop is closed, brother.
- Chocolate coffee.
Sir!
I've cleared up everything inside, sir.
Can I come an hour late tomorrow?
I'm going to visit the temple.
The shop is closed, sir.
Shruthi, leave now. Hurry up.
I'm talking to you.
Can you hear me or not?
- The shop is closed...
- Shruthi. Go, I'll talk to him.
Hey! Let go of my hand!
Let me go!
Sir, he...
Brother.
Shall we share our desire
Like the warmth of blazing fire?
Soft as cotton am I and ready
Shall we ignite in rhapsody?
Shall we…
Hey! The gun is missing.
Check if he has taken it.
Let me go!
- Brother.
- Yes?
I've brought all the cash I've got here.
Let me know if you want more.
I'll give you.
Let her go, please.
This is wrong, brother.
Let her go. Please, I'm begging you.
Chocolate coffee.
Let me go.
Stay right here.
Don't come out till I tell you, okay?
Sir!
- I went crazy…
- Let me go!
On a spell so dizzy…
Boss, he is inside.
This is my job daily,
to think of you gaily
My job is to think of you
Night and day all through…
- Hey! Shut the gate!
- Let us think this happened, indeed
Let us transform our thoughts to deed
- Sir!
- When…
- Spread a mat and then…
- Sir!
- Sir, do something.
- Hey!
What did I tell you
and what are you doing?
Like the warmth of blazing fire
Soft as cotton…
Sir!
Hey, our job is done. Let's go.
Hey!
Come with me or just die!
The guy, this girl, the child
and the CCTV here
are all aware of our identities.
If we leave like this,
we will be nabbed by tomorrow.
What do we do?
Do you want chocolate coffee?
Like the warmth of blazing fire
Shall we share our desire…
- Sir.
- Good boy.
Sir!
Hey! Clear the CCTV footage.
Sir...
The lotus and its water
Never fight with each other
No one is around,
Hug me in a tight embrace
Like salt in pearl millet adds to treat
My porridge of life turns into a feast
Hey!
Your face is embedded in my heart
With my tongue, I can touch my nose
You touched my soul with your glance
You're trying to kill me! Kill him!
No one is around, embrace me
The way IR8 rice boils well and blends
You bonded well with me
You irrigated so well
My drought-ridden heart swell
Like a mother cat with her kittens
You swirled at my feet smitten
Feeling sorry, I petted you softly
You snarled to bite at me
- Dad!
- I own your soul, heart and body
Dad!
Shruthi! Chintu!
Your hands caressing my cheeks gently
Chocolate coffee?
Dad!
Will a bud blooming into a flower now
Without feeling shy, express love?
Is it fight or honey-duet
To the flower and bee in pursuit?
The lotus and its water
Never fight with each other
I want to hug my dearest beloved
Even though he isn't yet my husband
Let's go to the riverside with a tree
It is a solitary love-spot
When the tide ebbs aside
Let us return gratified
I can teach you to swim happily
Come with me, my one and only
Let me tell you right now, hush!
Here and there my hands brush!
Even spots on the Moon can be wiped clear
But you can never be reformed, dear
Even if overturned and hit
A turtle's shell won't break a bit
Sir…
Hey! Let him go!
Or I'll stab her!
Sir!
Stab him now.
Where are you off to?
Dad!
Chintu!
Parthiban!
Parthiban.
Drive to the hospital first.
It doesn't look like a clot.
No physical injuries.
But she is showing signs of PTSD.
This child is in shock.
She is bound to feel anxious.
But there's nothing to worry.
I'll give her some medicine.
Take good care of her, okay?
Parthiban.
Parthiban, stop thinking about it
and getting upset.
Anyone in your place
would've done the same.
We will face the consequences.
I'll be there for you.
I'll take care of the children
till you get released.
- But don't regret...
- Sathya, I don't know what happened.
He went towards Chintu.
I saw him.
I was…
After that…
- Sir, I can't wait any longer.
- May I go in?
Parthiban, the police officers
are waiting outside.
I told them not to come in.
- Joshy, without this remand...
- Sathya, are you kidding?
Do you know the seriousness of this?
Five of them have been killed.
What do you want me to do?
He's a murderer now.
He has to be remanded for 15 days.
We have to follow procedures.
Once he is produced at court,
We can handle the rest.
Don't panic, okay?
Parthiban, let's go.
Before you proclaim the judgment,
I have one question.
According to the ballistic reports,
five bullets fired from the gun
penetrated the victims' foreheads
at point-blank range.
Not a single bullet misfired.
A person who has never
handled a gun before
was able to fire five bullets
in a split second. How?
Sometimes, even trained police officers
struggle to shoot below the knee.
But without being least perturbed
how could he shoot five times
at point blank range?
Inspector Bhawar Jetha.
Compare Mr. Parthiban's shooting skill
with that of a few ordinary men.
This court orders proper proof
backed with adequate explanation.
Nazrat!
Go and stand over there.
- Hey! Stop!
- Shahid.
Note down everything.
Sashikanth.
- What are you doing?
- First lower the gun.
Parthiban!
Step forward.
- Kumar.
- Sir?
Give him the 9 mm.
The man who killed my husband
and my younger brother…
Only after I send him
with his family to their graves
will I allow the funeral rites
of my husband to be performed.
I take this vow! I swear!
I swear!
It's okay.
Parthiban, here…
Your action was only a general exception.
Don't worry.
Parthiban! The ones you killed
weren't good people.
They are all gangsters.
It will come under self-defense.
Okay? Nothing to worry.
We'll take care. Okay?
Your Honor, a few days ago,
when a spotted hyena
strayed into our town,
everyone wanted to kill it.
But my client risked his life
and saved the hyena
from the people's cruel assault.
This is my question, Your Honor.
How can a man who loves
even a beast to this extent
kill those five men?
He killed those ruthless men
in an act of self-defense
with the intention of saving
the woman, child and himself.
Your Honor,
the mighty penal code may insulate
this gentleman's act of self-defense.
Bearing in mind the interrogation,
arguments and statements debated here,
having scrutinized this case thoroughly,
Mr. Parthiban, the accused,
has been proven innocent,
as per IPC Section 103 and 106.
The court pronounces its verdict.
Parthiban,
walk free with your head held high.
Move!
- Move them out of the way.
- Move aside.
Move out of the way.
Ask them to move out of the way.
- Is the decision to acquit you right?
- Move.
What's the reason
you had to shoot five people?
Come.
Give me that.
Get in.
Move!
Move. Move out of the way.
- Sir…
- Sir!
You okay?
Dad.
- Yes?
- You were right, Dad.
Even if we're holding a gun,
we shouldn't shoot.
That isn't easy.
I can picture myself.
I feel sorry for you, Dad.
I can't bear to see you like this.
The dead men have many cases against them.
They aren't ordinary criminals.
This is a loss to their acquaintances.
Do you think they will keep quiet?
Be careful, Sathya.
MUMBAI
SALEM
PEOPLE'S HERO FREED IN A MURDER CASE
SHIMLA
D'Souza, here you go!
PEOPLE'S HERO KILLED THE LOOTERS
WHO BARGED INTO HIS CAFE.
TELANGANA
GOVIND FINANCE
I can't forget everything
and go back to normal
at the coffee shop, Sathya.
I'm unable to focus.
I'm scared of the voices
Of the click, of the beat
Of the music I've been hearing all night
Pause, play, repeat!
I'm scared of the mountain
Of the river, of the fire
Of the sound of lightening in the sky
Those sounds make me wanna cry
- This light above me
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those colors
- These speakers
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those woofers
- Bad trip
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those chills
Shit scared of A, shit scared of B
Okay, I'm gonna pee!
I'm scared of the night
I'm scared of the day
I'm scared of my shadow
Get it out of my way
I'm scared of my past
I'm scared of my future
I'm scared of the present
Can't take this torture
- Dad!
- I'm feeling cold, I'm feeling hot
Just living in fear of getting caught
I'm scared of the creepy
I'm scared of the crawly
And I swear, I'm not on molly
This light above me
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those colors
- These speakers
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those woofers
- Bad trip
- I'm shit scared of that
- Those chills
I'm shit scared of that
Shit scared of A, Shit scared of B…
I kept it somewhere here.
Where is it?
What are you looking for?
You won't find anything there.
You need to buy something
to claim that it's missing.
How much longer will you hide
at home, Parthiban?
The cafe has been closed for ten days.
You aren't even sending
your daughter to school.
Just look at their faces.
Not only have you confined yourself
to the home
you've kept your family locked up
within these four walls.
How long will you shut your ears
when you hear a slight noise?
Go get some fresh air.
I'll take care of the house.
Take your family out first.
Go!
I feel like drinking coffee.
I'm stepping out to buy a packet of milk.
Do any of you want anything?
- Greetings, sir.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi, sir.
- Greetings.
He is a brave man.
Parthiban, I need to buy
something from there.
You guys come with me.
Buy whatever you wanted. Come, Siddhu.
- Take care.
- Okay, Dad.
Mom, I want bread omelet.
Okay, I'll buy it for you.
- One bread omelet, please.
- Okay, ma'am.
- You give it, I'll be back.
- Okay, Mom.
- Hello?
- Sir, Kumar here.
- It's a pitch deck info.
- Yeah.
There's some suspicious activity in town.
Parthiban's family is in danger.
We got this information
from an undercover agent two weeks ago.
But the inspector hid it.
Tell his family not to go out
without protection.
Yeah, okay. I'll call you back.
Parthiban, where are you?
- I'm at the market.
- Does anyone seem suspicious around?
Parthiban?
No. Why?
The department got information
that some unwanted elements are here.
Drop whatever you're doing
and get back into the car.
Right now, please…
Hey! Only after I kill you and your family
and take your head with me,
will I bury my brother-in-law.
Behead him!
Parthiban!
Hey!
How dare you lay your dirty hands
on my family?
Dad!
Parthiban, don't! Listen to me.
Parthiban!
Parthiban! Parthiban! Listen to me!
What are you doing?
Parthiban! Parthiban!
Move!
Parthiban! What are you doing?
Leave him alone.
If I let him go, they will kill us!
Parthi, I'm scared to see you
sitting here like this.
We can come
when the inspector calls.
Let's go home now.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Kumar!
- Sir!
Why is it so crowded outside?
Is it a fish market?
- Go and check.
- Parthi.
What are our men doing outside?
What is it? I'd asked you to file
a complaint and leave, right?
Why do you insist on meeting me?
Don't we have any other damn work?
Go to the writer's table
and he'll write what you say.
Sign or stamp your thumbprint
and leave, understand?
I'll see to it.
Hey! Send my tea inside.
Where are you going?
What will you see? Will you see us die?
Do we have to live in fear, wondering
who will attack us every time we step out?
Why are you getting worked up?
Two days ago, one of the corpses
from the shoot-out
went missing from the mortuary.
The department asked you to alert us.
Why didn't you caution us, sir?
Who told you all this? The ranger?
Look here.
Do we have to think of you
24×7 and serve only you?
In all fairness...
- Wait, Sathya.
- Let's go.
In all fairness,
I did what you should've done.
I had no choice but shoot
when he tried to kill my daughter.
He died! That's all.
Please. No need. Let's go home, please.
- Please.
- I want an armed guard
posted at my house 24×7.
I won't leave until then.
Hey! Get up, man!
I'm telling you to get up!
Get up! Get up from here!
Please. Let's go.
As if you are
an influential political leader!
Get out!
Out!
He wants an armed policeman, it seems.
You can't just order
and get an armed cop at your disposal.
The law and the government
must pass the order.
Let's go.
You are neither the law
nor the government.
You are a common man
who sells bun and butter, Parthiban.
- Let's go, Parthi!
- Come in. We were waiting for you.
- He can't tolerate noise.
- Let's go, Parthi.
We should stand outside his house
holding a gun for his safety, it seems.
And he'll sit inside the house,
hugging his wife...
Hey! You're a police officer!
Mind your words!
What did you say!
- Hey!
- Parthiban!
- Let go!
- Parthiban, let him go!
Parthiban, don't!
He's a police officer, leave him.
Let go!
Parthiban! Listen. Let go of him.
Hold him back, guys. Come on.
Parthiban, you've already
been arrested once.
Let him go. Listen to me.
He is a policeman.
- Please! Let him go!
- Parthiban, stop!
- Listen to me!
- Listen to me, Parthiban!
He will die. Let him go!
Sir, are you alright? Is your neck okay?
Parthiban.
Why did you do it, Parthiban?
I told you not to.
They won't give you police protection
as and when you ask, Parthiban.
There's no proof of assault against you.
You haven't sustained any injuries.
Who said that I'm not injured?
Parthiban, are you really sure?
Joshy, I may go overboard
if I do it myself.
So, you do it.
You asked for it!
SP sir, can you come to my residence?
Now. Yes, it's urgent.
Sir, one small request.
Please give me a police officer
from Kerala.
900 KILOS OF DRUGS SEIZED
Napoleon reporting to duty, sir!
Where is my position?
Hush!
Who is this man?
You requested
for a high-ranking Kerala police officer.
He is that high-ranking police officer.
You must've heard
of a drug bust in Trichy.
I heard he was responsible
for finishing off 50-60 of those men.
- Move this table over there at once.
- Okay, sir.
Fast.
Hey!
Put your phone down.
Listen!
What do you want?
Wait!
Are you a Malayali? Hey, don't run!
Load the stuff fast!
TELANGANA
What is it?
What?
Are you transferring our own stuff
without our knowledge?
Come here!
Boss!
Move aside!
Out of my way! Move aside!
Boss?
You better pray to God
that it's important news.
Or you'll die here.
Look at this picture.
Hey!
He is a freaking badass, man
He's a badass, run for your life quickly
He's a badass, stay in your limits
Badass, man
Leo Das, man
He's a badass, run for your life quickly
Got you, rascal!
Hey!
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
He is a freaking badass, man
A feast at the forest
where the lion is on the prowl
Fearing his hunt, they scatter
Hither and thither
Putting an end to gangsters countless,
He'll punish them ruthless
Till now, he was a good soul
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
But now on, he will be a demon
He is a burning ember
Don't you come near him
He will spill your guts out!
Just remember that!
Hey!
He is a badass!
Stay in your limits
Badass, man
Leo Das, man
He's a badass. Run for your life.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
How many people should we send from here?
If he's really Parthiban,
four people will suffice.
But if he is Leo…
- We'll chop him!
- We will chop him
- We will chop him into pieces!
LEO DAS, BORN: 13-05-1977
…our entire town won't do!
Don't act too smart, man
He will give you grief and strife
Beat you to a pulp and end your life
He is a burning ember
Don't you go near him
He will spill your guts out!
Just remember that!
He is a badass!
Run for your life
Badass is he
Stay within your limits
Hey!
Thank you.
- Is it sweet?
- Bloody sweet.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Leo
He's a freaking badass, man
Leo!
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
LEO
Rest in peace!
This one is…
Almost the same.
- I'll make it better.
- Yes.
A girl over there has been
watching you for a long time.
Don't turn around immediately.
Could she be from the press?
Did she leave?
Also, a man at the back
has been here for a long time.
He isn't saying anything.
Go and have a word with him.
- Where? Behind?
- In the backyard.
- Okay. Go, I'll handle him.
- Okay.
"Pleasure is mine."
Hi, sir. What would you like to eat?
- Coffee.
- Sugar?
You know very well
whether I take sugar or not.
How would I know
whether you prefer sugar or not?
- With sugar.
- Okay.
Sorry, sir.
- One sugar cube or two...
- You know that too.
Sir, I don't know that.
You've mistaken me for someone else.
I am thrilled to hear you speak Malayalam.
I'm just humoring you.
Your coffee, your sugar.
Leo?
Leo!
Parthiban.
I don't know anyone named Leo, sir.
There's already a lot of confusion here.
Please don't add to it.
Please drink your coffee and leave.
Do you mind?
Can you make it a little stronger?
Sure, sir.
Do you know this brand, Leo?
No, sir.
I don't have the habit of smoking.
- I can't even stand the smell.
- D Slash.
You used to call it Honey Badger,
but it is Black Devil.
Twenty-five puffs.
The flavor that you created.
You really like nocturnal animals, right?
Once a honey badger
entered our tobacco field.
Do you remember?
It didn't get caught in your trap.
It didn't get killed
by Harold's spear either.
In the end, it died
by the bullet that I fired.
I think you've forgotten it.
Do you want anything
other than coffee or shall I get the bill?
Have you convinced yourself
that you are dead, Leo?
Wait, what?
Listen.
I've many problems on my mind.
I've a splitting headache.
I'll tell you in a way
you'll understand, one last time.
You've mistaken me for someone else.
I have very less patience, dear.
So don't waste my time.
Mount View Lodge.
Come of your own accord
and admit that you're Leo.
Sir, alcohol is not allowed.
No alcohol!
No alcohol.
A friend of my friend is in Kadapa.
I sent him a photo
of the D Slash cigarette box
and got some details.
Going by what he says,
the chap who came here
is Antony Das.
Once upon a time in Andhra Pradesh,
he ran a huge tobacco company.
- After a big fire accident...
- Hold on.
Why should I know
the history of the one
who barged into my cafe
and blew cigarette smoke in my face?
No, but this is important.
- No, I...
- Let him complete.
Go on, Joshy.
Antony Das has a son named Leo.
Okay.
Leo Das.
I couldn't find any details
other than his name.
One group says that he committed
a grave mistake and died.
Another group believes he is still alive.
He can fool this town.
He can fool the world.
But he can never fool me.
In some odd way,
you have a striking resemblance to him.
I saw his eyes.
I know his eyes.
It is him.
Parthiban, you grew up
in an orphanage, right?
- Do you remember anything from before?
- What is this? This is not fair!
We are the victims here.
You are treating
the victim like an accused.
- Let's leave, Parthi.
- Wait.
Sathya, one moment.
Joshy.
I get that you are asking this
out of concern.
But since my childhood
until I was 20, I grew up
in Sathyamangalam Orphanage.
And I met her there…
What was that, Sathya?
Munnar trekking.
There's where we met.
I saw her. I got to know her.
Within two days,
I asked her if she'd marry me.
That's all.
After marrying her,
we settled here because of her job.
This has been my town since then.
This is my story.
They have also come
from the south, Parthiban.
If they've crossed so many miles
and come by road to our place
in search of you, something is amiss.
Whatever came to a grinding halt
because of him
needs to be restarted using him.
I know how to bring him back
into our fold.
My world is very small, Joshy.
It's like a snow globe
that fits in the palm of my hand.
A small independent house,
surrounded by trees.
Snowfall, cool breeze...
Why is this happening to me?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I'm sorry.
It's alright. I understand.
If they come back
to cause further trouble,
we'll inform the police.
Keep an eye on his family and friends.
I'll take care of it.
I feel like someone
is watching our home, Sathya.
I don't know, Sathya. The eerie silence
makes me restless. I feel very disturbed.
Look here. Understand this.
You should feel this way
only if I suspect you.
Have I ever questioned you?
Stop thinking about these things
and sleep peacefully, come.
Won't you come?
Okay, shall we stand like this and sleep?
Don't touch the engine,
just fix the heater.
I want my vehicle.
Get it ready by evening, okay?
What do you want?
I saw you.
That's enough for me.
I'm so mad at you, if I slap you now
your mouth will be injured badly
and it will seem like
a weird smile is plastered.
I'm sorry.
- Get out!
- I'll leave!
I'll leave.
- Tell me, Sathya.
- I bought the tablet you wanted.
Do you want anything else?
I've given the vehicle
for service.
I told you that we can go later
to the pharmacy?
- Why did you leave the kid alone at home?
- I brought Mathi with me.
Priya is also with me.
You could've waited.
What was the hurry?
Some things can't be delayed, right?
It's not a problem.
I'll take an auto home.
- You take care.
- Go home and call me.
Do you wanna get something to eat?
There's nothing to panic about.
It is the same blood.
Do you know who she is?
My granddaughter.
My blood.
Yesterday you were the one who…
You better leave
or I may have to call the police.
Police?
I haven't come to trouble you.
For the past 20 years, you've been living
with a guy who you believe is Parthiban.
When you realise he was a ruthless killer
who committed many murders,
come and meet me.
I'll show you the true colors
of your husband.
- Hello?
- Why don't you pick up, Parthi?
- He was here.
- What happened?
Who? Who was there?
The same guy!
You said he visited the cafe yesterday!
He came to medical shop
looking for me.
Where are you now?
At home.
They followed me in their car.
It is parked outside.
Close the doors.
Give the phone to the police officer.
He is missing. No one is here.
I'm scared, Parthi.
Lock yourself in our bedroom safely.
Siddhu is coming. I'm also on my way!
Answer the call!
- Dad, what is it?
- Siddharth! Go home immediately.
- Pick your spear and go in.
- What happened?
If anyone tries to enter the house,
throw your spear at him.
Okay.
Will our lives be like this now, Parthi?
We have to be on the run.
We have to hide.
We should live in fear
wondering what might happen
to our kids. Right?
Tell me. Who is he?
He claims that our daughter
is his granddaughter.
I feel terrified when I look at him.
I felt like dying.
I was running for life.
Chintu, come here.
Don't call her! She's already terrified.
Listen…
I forced the Police Department,
I fought with the law,
and went to great lengths
to bring you to my doorstep.
I asked you to protect my family.
Do you possess
any integrity or job ethics?
There's no use
talking about compassion or concern
to those who work for money.
Instead of doing your duty like this
by just eating and sleeping uselessly,
pick up your belongings and go away!
- Don't say that, sir.
- What?
Don't act on impulse.
Under the pretext of making excuses
don't provoke me to swear at you.
- I went to recharge...
- Don't talk.
Don't talk!
I'm letting you go out of respect
for your age, or…
You've misunderstood me.
- Dear…
- Go. Just go.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Dad.
- I didn't know that it was you…
- It's okay, Son.
Good throw.
- You knew it was me and threw it, right?
- No, Dad.
When you realize
that the man sharing your bed
is a ruthless killer with no mercy,
come and meet me.
Was it a dream?
I wish it was.
I think some major conflict occurred
between the family members.
It seems this is also a reason for
their tobacco industry to get destroyed.
I have sent the certificates
and photos to you.
Check if they are forged.
- I will check.
- Okay. Bye.
It's a myth that stands still, Joshy.
But I believe a man who knows
the full story is alive in Shimla prison.
His name is Hridayaraj D'Souza
in the records.
If the Intel is right,
he must be very close to Leo Das.
So if you want to see him,
you have only two days.
Practically, I don't know
when you can reach.
- Can I try to connect him in a call?
- No…
I-I'm on my way,
make the arrangements, please.
I'll reach by tonight.
- Sure, Joshy.
- Thank you.
Who is the villain here?
It's late. Your mom isn't back yet.
Recently, she has been
returning late everyday.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
That's her.
- Tell me.
- Parthi, I'm not coming home tonight.
Don't wait for me.
Have your dinner and sleep.
- Why? What happened?
- I've taken many days off, right?
So there's a lot of pending work.
I thought I'll finish it
and come home in the morning.
I yelled at Siddhu,
so he isn't picking my call.
Is he back home? Where is he?
Poor boy, I was quite harsh.
Check on him, Parthi.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your kind attention?
Okay, where are you now?
- At the head office.
- Is that so?
- Chintu.
- Yes?
You don't suspect your dad, right?
- No.
- Why?
Because you are my dearest dad.
Your dearest dad.
Hey! It's your dad.
Siddharth, get into the car!
- I'm calling you, get into...
- Let go of my hand!
Sir, leave him alone
if he doesn't want to come.
Don't force him.
What? Will you kill him too?
Okay, don't come.
Who is the villain here?
Who is the good one?
Who is the friend and godsend?
If I see any of you
following my family hereafter…
Who is the villain here?
Sir.
Why are you sitting here
in the cold at this hour?
No intruder will barge in now.
I don't care anymore who shoots
and who dies, go to sleep.
It's okay. It's okay, sir.
A courier was delivered in the noon
in your wife's name.
Sir, one moment.
I wanted to tell you something.
I understand all your worries and fears.
I see how well you take care
of the people who depend on you.
You are anxious
that something might happen to them.
I'll retire in 60 days.
If anyone troubles your family
in any way during this time,
I'll take him down with me!
Even if there is any emergency
needing my attention back home
I won't leave this place.
I swear this Napoleon doesn't work
just to eat like a glutton, sir.
I don't work just to fill my stomach.
Trust me.
Did you really lift such a big gun
at the commissioner's office
and shoot all of them?
I just read the manual and instructed
which button to press.
Dilli took care of the rest.
Don't tell anyone.
This is my means of livelihood.
Okay.
- Chintu.
- Dad.
What is it, dear?
Why don't you sit?
- How is he doing?
- He is fine.
It's been nearly three weeks
since he called me up.
All okay, right?
Why take the trouble
to visit me at this hour?
Had you told me, I'd have couriered it.
The government registration is pending
without proper certificates.
We came here on some other job.
- So we decided to collect it.
- Oh.
It's in the attic. Let me get it.
Sir, this is Hridayaraj D'Souza.
You have 20 minutes.
I'll wait over there.
Finish your conversation soon.
You asked for this brand, right?
Hridayaraj D'Souza.
I'll come straight to the point
because of time constraint.
Das & Co Tobacco Factory.
The duo associated with it,
Antony and Harold.
We have identity records on both of them,
but we have no details about Leo.
You are the only one alive
among Leo's associates
who were present at the time of his death.
I have only one request for you.
If you can tell me
whether this is Leo or not,
four lives will be saved.
I understand.
I can see the fear of death in your eyes.
I heard you are due
for a death sentence in three days.
If you can narrate what actually happened,
I can send a petition now
and appeal for a review
of your death sentence.
If you could tell me
the actual sequence of events…
Hridayaraj, don't test my patience.
If you're here for a fair and just cause,
why this back door entry
and sitting near the toilet?
I've said what I had to, in the court.
No one can stop my death sentence.
What else?
What happened at Das & Co Tobacco Factory?
Is Leo alive or dead? Or how did Leo die?
I'm not saying this for you
or your damn bribe of a booze.
Anyway I'll die in three days.
After that, I can't talk about him.
That's why I'll tell you now.
In the year 1999, Das & Co
was the most flourishing tobacco factory
in Andhra Pradesh.
The one who built
and ruled that empire was Antony.
Antony Das.
Das & Co Tobacco Factory was just a front
to conduct many illegal businesses.
He developed the business
to local, national
and international levels.
Antony was never the kind to forget
or forgive those who opposed him.
He would kill them mercilessly.
Gradually that became
a habit in their family.
Before starting any business,
he'd always sacrifice an animal.
He believed the growth of his empire
was only due to this sacrificial ritual.
It started with goats and cows
and he went to the extent
of performing human sacrifices too.
He was very superstitious.
Harold Das was his younger brother.
Harold was the only man
whom Antony trusted.
Harold.
Harold!
He went to Canada to study
but got acquainted with
international drug cartels over there.
He expanded their business
on foreign soil.
His dream was to make Das & Co
the number one drug cartel in the world.
So he created a drug called Datura.
It was a drug unseen,
unheard of and untried in the market.
They grew Datura
amidst their tobacco plants.
They began to manufacture it
in their factory.
Datura was more lethal than cocaine.
Gradually its demand increased
in the market.
At the same time, this news was leaked
to the Narcotics Control Bureau
by some of his men.
He threw Datura on the faces
of those whom he suspected
without even questioning them.
He killed them in wild fury ruthlessly
and piled them in heaps remorselessly.
Even if Antony and Harold took care
of managing the business at the top level
they still needed someone trustworthy
working at grass-root level, right?
Antony's son…
I raised him from the time
he was a toddler.
Das. Leo Das.
All this hassle is because one of your men
leaked the information to NCB.
Have you faced this issue
before in all these years?
Think about me. What you do
is not at all trivial.
I can't show a wrong count
for namesake.
If you want me
to release the seized Datura,
one among the three of you
must surrender.
That's why I want Leo to surrender.
If he is jailed for a week
I can silence the higher-ups
and release the stash.
If it gets out of hand,
I can't help you, remember that.
How do we trust
that you'll release him in a week?
If you want your stash,
you've to trust me, Das.
- Antony?
- Is Leo there?
Leo isn't here.
He said he'd cross the border
with the drugs.
He must be at the check-post.
I think he's outwitting them.
Hey, who is smoking over there?
Give him a tight slap!
Tell me, sir.
Yes, sir. I'm at the spot.
Rest in peace!
- Gabby! Start the vehicle!
- Hey! Go!
Load it! Hurry up.
L-E-O Das is a badass
He's gonna kick your sad ass
Rest in peace!
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Go fast! Go…
L-E-O Das is a badass
He's gonna kick your sad ass
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Hey! I worked for you risking my job.
But you're outwitting me
and getting me in trouble.
I'll see how you take the stash out
without my help.
Leo!
Hey! Don't!
Rest in peace!
Leo found out
who gave information to the NCB
from within our camp.
- Gabby!
- Tell me.
I don't care what bloody issue it was.
Why halt and discuss en-route?
You're gathering allies and mediating
with so many tons of drugs at stake!
Who is mediating? Go ask Daniel.
Whenever I instructed him,
he said, "Call Leo.
This load won't move an inch
till he comes here and settles my share."
That smart-ass threatened me.
You say he is smart and your friend.
Where is he?
What is your problem?
What issue do you have to work with him?
He is my problem!
He has taken my place.
I can't work under this mongrel.
If he does it again,
I will hold back the drugs.
I'll show you I'm important too.
What do you want me to do?
I don't want him butting in, that's all.
If he does, we can't dispose the drugs.
He asked for it.
Right?
I care two hoots for friendship
or whatever crap other than this stash.
I'll do as you say.
Hey!
- Remove the damn knife.
- Hey!
I know who you are going shoot next.
Put the gun down and step back.
Have you watched the movie, Jeans?
Hero Prashanth plays dual role, right?
A small change.
Both are men in that movie.
Here, it's a man and a woman.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Rest in peace
Leo.
It isn't easy to cross all the check-posts
with 2,000 kilos of Datura overnight.
They are killing our men like mongrels.
It's too risky to transfer it overnight.
Tell me what to do.
Even though it was
an almost impossible task
Leo dismissed the risk
of transfer overnight.
Leo took it as a challenge
to transfer 2,000 kilos of Datura
by crossing two inter-state borders.
Imagine! 2,000 kilos of Datura.
It was worth millions at that time.
He kept his word
and finished it without any hitch.
He took matters in his own hands
for his dad's sake
without a second thought.
Amidst all this, Antony's quest
for human sacrifices didn't stop.
For two years, he was searching
for a unique horoscope.
He believed that if such a person
was found and sacrificed,
his tobacco factory
and business would flourish again.
We were least bothered about this.
We were happy
that the drugs reached safely
and celebrated.
Bro, come here.
Bro! Come on!
Please. For the sake of these boys.
Come on!
I'm ready. Shall I make an entry?
I'm your dear bro. Shall I come now?
Don't taunt this lion
With the sting of a scorpion
No matter who tries to obstruct my route
It won't change
I'm ready. Shall I make an entry?
Your favorite bro, shall I come solo?
Let's beat the drum
to the rhythm of happiness
Pick the best goat and slaughter
So I can appease my hunger
If God is granting total bliss in one go,
caution is advisable.
Because no one can predict
what will happen next.
I have good news and bad news for you.
Only these two horoscopes
will suit our purpose
out of all the horoscopes
I searched for, till date.
Please take a look and decide.
I'm ready to harvest
And weed out my opponent
It is our fate at stake
To get rid of this headache.
If he acts smart,
We will tie him in a sack
Dump him in a lorry
To get dissected in the factory!
Hey! We know all the blueprints
Our mission will be a success
If you interfere,
I will sacrifice you to our family deity
Don't drink too much
and your threaten my friend
As a team we work and think
Sharing a worldwide link
Everywhere, it's our rules
Don't flick our tools
We move and groove in unity
Our sync is our identity
I am tired of winning
every match I wrestle
Just one drum beat quick
Sure-shot power kick
I shouldn't have shown Elisa's
and Leo's horoscopes to you
but I had no option.
I'm not sure
if we can find a similar horoscope
with the same star and date of birth, Das.
Hey! Is there no other way?
Can't you come up with any other option?
I feel really sad to say this.
If you ask my opinion,
I'll choose Leo.
No.
The decision… the decision is all yours.
Marinated with spice and pepper
let's fry them in the pan
Those limbs so amazing and super
Fist fight that strikes like lightning
Flashes into our kitchen and dining
Inviting and awakening
Many a knife waiting to stab me
That's their account to tally
He is like the tip of a knife
I don't want to be targeted
- Now stop talking.
- Oh! Okay.
I'm known by another name too
You'll tremble in fear
Upon hearing it, dude
Print out the poster
All-ready is your brother
Celebrate and how! Set it ablaze now
Here I am…
Hey! Make way for our bro!
Here I am, your dear bro.
Don't taunt this lion
No matter who tries to obstruct my route
It won't change
I'm ready. Shall I make an entry?
Your favorite bro, shall I come solo?
Let's beat the drum
to the rhythm of happiness
I will bring you the best delicacies
Now celebrate to your heart's content
I had to do this, Leo.
Even now, between you and your sister
many chose you,
they opted to sacrifice you.
My brother also chose you.
I was the one who saved you!
You need not thank me for that.
Just pardon me.
From my childhood till date,
I've killed countless people
for your sake.
I took your word as gospel
and killed my friend too.
That was for our business.
But this is mere superstition!
Let go of Elisa!
Leo!
This is also for our business.
- Understand that!
- Hey!
She isn't just my sister.
She is my twin.
A part of me, my other half!
If anything untoward happens to her,
no matter how many births you take
the day I see you will be your last day!
The day I meet you
will be your last day on Earth!
Are you begging him?
Didn't I tell you the day
our mother passed away?
That he has something
to do with her death.
If he has decided
to sacrifice his children,
I don't consider him my dad anymore,
none of them here are my kith and kin!
Will you do me a favor, Leo?
Don't spare any of them alive.
Hey!
Don't you dare!
Let her go!
Dad!
Hey!
Release her! Let her go!
Elisa, try to understand!
Understand my plight!
Leo!
Hey!
Leo, burn down the entire factory.
Harold, don't let them escape.
Harold! Don't let them escape!
Leo!
Come!
- Come on.
- Come!
- Catch…
Hey! Don't spare anyone.
Don't leave anything out!
Burn everything down!
Everything!
Hey!
You wanted to sacrifice
your children for this, right?
Hey, Leo!
This shouldn't exist anymore!
Hereafter this…
Hey!
…shouldn't exist!
Leo, stop it!
Hey! Throw me a knife.
Elisa!
Elisa…
I won't survive, Leo.
Go somewhere far away.
Elisa!
I raised him.
He collapsed and died in front of my eyes.
Tell me if it's Leo in this photo.
No.
If you just identify him,
all the problems will be solved.
Even if he stands amidst 1,000 people,
I can identify Leo from his eyes.
This isn't him.
Don't play unnecessarily
with an innocent man's life.
Warden! Take me away.
I feel sleepy.
If you say the truth
and do good, the world...
It may spill.
These are the documents
and photos I have with me.
- These were taken at the orphanage.
- Show me.
We clicked this during third grade.
This is in fourth grade.
And this is in fifth grade.
This is the letter he wrote to me
during his college days.
IT'S A SCARY EXPERIENCE TO STEP OUT
OF OUR SHELTERED EXISTENCE
May I ask you something?
I consider you my brother
and I'm asking you this.
I know what's on your mind.
I won't tell him about your visit.
Make sure that he doesn't find out.
If he finds out, he'll be devastated.
- Hello?
- Sir, is this Parthiban?
- Yes.
- Sir, come to the coffee shop at once.
It's an emergency.
He was drinking with us, sir.
I don't know why he kept saying
that he saw his friend.
He was happily drinking.
He even bought booze
for everyone, sir.
Then he left in an inebriated state.
He stood on the road
talking to someone over the phone.
Then some men came in cars
and took him away.
- Was it a black car?
- Yes, sir.
Hey!
He claimed to be your friend
and came to your cafe.
He chatted with you.
He has even taken your photo.
How do you know him? Can't you hear me?
Sir! If he was a regular customer
at my cafe,
I should've at least been
slightly upset, right?
Look into my eyes. Are there tears?
I don't know him, sir.
How can I be responsible
for him dying in front of my cafe?
I'll come to the station when you call me.
You can interrogate me there.
I've left my little girl alone at home.
I'm scared for her. I need to go.
- Okay, go.
- Thank you, sir.
I don't know whether to feel sorry
or be suspicious of Parthiban.
Listen.
Every human being
has a limit to lie and pretend.
He can do it only up to a breaking point.
He can't continue to put on an act
beyond that point.
Because no one is mentally strong
to that extent.
I feel Parthiban isn't acting.
He is Parthiban indeed.
Beyond this, if truth has to be told,
Leo, who is allegedly dead
has to come in person and say it.
Parthi, are you back?
I heard you got a call
and left in a hurry.
Where were you?
The work was so hectic
at office in the past two days?
Why is your dinner untouched?
Parthi, what happened?
Why are you sitting here quietly?
Beyond this,
I have nothing left to lose, Sathya.
I'm a loser.
From my tip to toe,
you are suspecting every part of me.
- It's not like that, please...
- Don't touch me!
Don't touch me.
This whole world can suspect me.
But how could you doubt me?
How did you see me as a stranger?
Sathya?
Oh, no! No matter what
explanation you give me,
the fact that you suspected me
will haunt me forever.
Is our bond so fragile?
The life that we led so far
has lost its meaning.
That's it, right?
I am not him!
Parthiban isn't that kind of a person.
Despite repeating that
over and over again,
just because some
random chap resembles me…
- What happened, Mom?
- Nothing, sweetie.
I wasn't feeling well. Go to sleep.
Dance for me. Oh…
I've never seen anybody do the things
you do before
Move for me
And when you're done,
I'll make you do it...
Hey, you.
Some random fellow…
If they torture me claiming
I resemble some random riff-raff,
what can I do?
You've forsaken your trust in me.
My son asked me if I'm a good dad.
You asked me if I'm a good husband!
Who am I? Tell me.
That's correct.
I don't know who my parents are
or what my place of birth is.
I'm an orphan.
Maybe if they were alive,
they wouldn't have suspected me.
I'm an orphan, after all.
- Don't say that.
- Just an orphan.
Parthi, you're not an orphan. Look at me.
I'm telling you to look into my eyes.
I didn't do this
due to lack of trust in you.
When other people ask me,
I need to tell them with certainty, right?
"He is not that man."
I should confidently assert
this is my husband, Parthiban.
Why can't you understand?
Sathya.
I need to ask just one question.
After you suspected
that I was someone else,
how could you touch me?
Didn't you feel disgusted?
Wasn't it like itching,
like a hairy caterpillar
crawling on your body..."
Trust me.
Sathya.
Please trust me.
Trust me, Sathya.
Trust your Parthiban.
Leo, the time I gave you is over.
You didn't come. So I am here to see you.
Look outside.
Hey! Who the hell are you all?
What are you doing here?
You better leave!
I'll shoot you all down!
You won't leave this place alive!
Don't you understand?
This need not have gone so far.
If you had come of your own accord
and admitted to me that you are Leo
I wouldn't have come here now.
Sir! Don't come down
for any reason whatsoever.
I'll deal with them!
I came to meet you
but a mongrel is barking over here!
Okay.
Amidst all this, give some thought
to where your son is.
Sathya?
Where is Siddharth?
- What happened?
- Where is Siddhu?
- Check on Siddhu.
- You won't be able to find him.
- He would've reached his destination.
- He isn't here!
Siddharth!
Bring our daughter.
But your son is so damn cute.
He came out to smoke, got trapped
and made it easy for us.
Can you hear me?
Parthiban, what is happening here?
Where is Siddhu?
Whom are you talking to?
If anyone except me enters the house,
you must stab them.
Why?
You will do it. Hold it! Come on!
Go in.
Lock the door from inside, Sathya.
You don't have to live as Leo.
But ask your conscience.
Why should I kidnap your son?
Twenty-two years ago, your sister died
on this very day.
I'm taking your son today
and you know the reason behind it.
Don't you understand?
I don't have a sister or any damn sibling.
Let go of my son, rascal!
- Sir?
- You'll come on your own, Leo!
Go away! Didn't you hear what I said?
Sir, open the door!
Go!
- Sir, they have kidnapped Siddhu.
- I didn't know they took him.
Siddhu!
Hey!
Go!
Load the gun.
Sir, hold tight!
Watch out!
Where is my son?
Answer me! Where is my son?
Hey!
Siddhu?
Siddhu!
Where is my son?
I failed to kill you, Leo.
But I won't fail to kill your son!
I'm not the man you're looking for!
Presuming that I'm your son
you ruined my life!
Where is my son? Come on, tell me.
Speak up! Where is my son? Tell me!
Accept that you're my son.
And I'll let your son go.
Oh, God! I'm not your son! No.
I'm not your son!
Tell me.
You're him, right?
Harold, Antony is no more.
I'm bringing the boy.
Napoleon needs bed-rest.
But I don't think they would stop at this.
They keep coming for you.
Your son will be safe for now.
We will send a task force and find him.
But you shouldn't stay here.
If you stay here,
your life will be in danger.
Please listen to me.
I've arranged a car.
It's parked at your doorstep.
Collect your essentials and leave. Now!
Who is this?
Leo, no matter where you go and hide
you know very well
that I'll come and get you.
All I want is your life.
Don't send your family to doom.
If you want your son back
hand over my elder brother to me.
Bring him here and take your son.
Parthiban, take it.
Go fast.
Das, I've sent boss' body.
We have boarded him on the train.
We will reach in an hour.
Sir, as per your request,
I've given your brother's body.
Please give my son back, I'll leave.
I know, you won't believe me
no matter what I say.
- That's why I...
- Hey!
Don't be scared.
This is just my son's school bag.
Sir, these are my birth certificate
and mark sheets.
Ration card, Aadhaar card,
wedding photos.
My daughter's ear piercing ceremony.
My son's first birthday.
Have a look.
When I was in 10th grade,
I got first prize
for my speech
about Kappalottiya Thamizhan.
This was taken then.
You can see my name.
Look here. This is you and your sister
on your 10th birthday.
A honey badger
had entered our tobacco field.
This photo was taken after it was killed.
Look how smart you look
with that blood-stained face.
I understand, sir.
I can't blame you
for mistaking me for Leo, sir.
He bears a striking resemblance to me.
Hey! Do you think I am
a fool?
- Sir…
- Do I seem like an imbecile?
Leo.
You know what I did to your twin sister.
I hope you haven't forgotten that.
You better accept that you are Leo.
Sir, I don't have a sister.
How do I make you understand?
Siddhu?
Tell me.
Sir.
In all these years,
he is scrutinizing someone
for the first time.
Human beings can lie.
Certificates can be fake.
But he can never lie.
I've never seen an eagle
at such close quarters in my life, sir.
Ask it to step back. I'm scared, sir.
Hey.
This performance
is just to protect your family, right?
You committed a blunder even there.
You came here to save your son
but left your wife and your daughter
all alone at home, my dear boy.
Shall I ask my men
to slit their throats?
Hey!
Okay, sir.
Sir, don't harm them.
Sir, please.
Hey!
Instruct your guys not to harm them, sir.
Poor souls, sir.
I will kill them!
What's this?
They have planted bombs here!
- What is it, Mom?
- Nothing, dear. Go back to sleep.
Sir, tell them not to go in.
- Hey, what happened...
- Sir.
Come with me.
Hey! You climb up.
Hey!
- Sir…
- Hey!
Sir, don't hurt them.
Tell them not to go inside.
Please, sir.
Instruct them not to enter
my house. Please, sir.
Come here. He is here.
- Who are you.
- I am scared.
Climb, I say!
My side is all clear.
Check those who are entering
through the main door.
Hey! Stupid guy, come!
Now it's your turn!
Sir.
I killed all those who barged in
except for one guy.
He climbed in from the side
and went upstairs.
Yeah. Okay. I will take care of him.
Do something, sir.
Hey!
Are you playing the fool with me?
I'll chop you into pieces!
- Sir, please…
- Hey!
- Sir.
- Why are you hanging up on me?
- What is going on there?
He's no ordinary fellow, sir.
He has set traps all around the house.
All our men are dead.
I know him like the back of my hand.
I confirm, he is Leo.
Who is in front of you?
His wife and daughter.
Shall I slit their throats?
No need. Put the phone on speaker.
Give the phone to his wife.
You better obey me.
- Admit that you are Leo.
- Sir.
I'll let all of you go.
Parthi!
Sathya, don't panic.
Admit it.
Subramani.
Hey!
I'm talking seriously
and you're laughing!
Me?
I think it's a dog.
Go away!
I told you to instruct your men
to not go in, sir.
Poor fellows. Right, sir?
Now the Leo we know will emerge.
Chittu, make him admit that he's Leo.
Hey!
Leave me!
Hey! Stay with his son.
Come on.
Hey!
I used this to kill your sister…
Now I realise
you are not Leo.
You are Parthiban.
Now I believe you.
You are not the one
whom I was looking for.
Let's call it quits.
What do you say?
Drop your gun.
Hey!
Lower your gun.
Lower it.
Come on! Shoot, you scoundrel!
Shoot!
Leo…
Leo!
- If I'm sweet, you're bloody sweet, Uncle.
- Hey!
I should've killed you
on that fateful day, right?
The mistake was mine.
Leo…
Was this necessary for you?
"I want to see Leo. I want to find Leo."
Didn't you ask for it?
See me now.
Leo…
Come on, Leo. Come.
Drop your gun, Leo.
Check if there are any vehicles outside.
If a person says about his past frequently
he must have done something good.
I have done no good deed.
In my past, knowingly or unknowingly,
I have committed many crimes.
My family is the last chance
I got to reform myself.
I will go to any extent
to protect this family.
The man called Leo is dead.
If I have to convince others
that he is dead
first I have to believe it myself.
Leo is dead. I believe it.
How are you?
But despite all this, if someone
finds out about my past,
he must be ready to die soon.
Or he must be dead already.
Of course I'm Leo.
Leo Das!
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
Just an ordinary person
Yeah
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person, yeah!
Peace-loving soul
My life is in this town
I came here and said that I'm not Leo.
No one believed me. They hit me.
Finally they accepted that I'm not Leo.
Other than this, nothing happened.
Promise me that
you won't tell your mom.
You promise me
you won't tell mom that I smoked.
I'm just an ordinary person!
Yeah
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person!
Yeah! I'm just a peace-loving soul
Peace-loving soul
- Who scratched your face, Dad?
- Chintu, keep quiet.
Siddhu, switch on the TV.
I'm a wicked man, so ruthless
I never lie, I confess
I'm a wicked man
I think the main door isn't locked.
I'll go and lock it.
I never harbor any grudge in my heart
Hello?
Just because you destroyed
a single Datura factory
do you think all the problems
got solved, Parthiban?
Oh! I'm sorry.
Leo.
If you want to make
this society drug-free,
there are a lot more left throughout India
to be burnt down, Leo.
Do you recognize my voice?
He is a badass, deadly!
Subtitle translation by: Mary