THEOG, HIMACHAL PRADESH
Let go of me!
Release me!
It's confirmed, boss. He's our target.
No…
Ask him to text me
after transferring the money.
Where the hell is that guy?
Why isn't he here yet?
He will get us into trouble.
What happened, boss?
-Boss, my foot!
-Okay, boss.
THEOG, HIMACHAL PRADESH
Breaking news for our viewers!
What I'm about to share now
has never happened before in this area.
It's a rampage all around.
A hyena has been spotted here.
Saffron TV will give you
live updates by the minute.
People from the nearby villages
have gathered here.
We have no idea
what the hyena is going to do.
-Tell me, Joshy.
-Sathya, I'm trying to reach Parthiban.
His phone is not reachable. Where is he?
He must have gone
to drop Siddhu off at school.
Try calling Siddhu.
They both must be together.
If you talk to him,
please ask him to call me.
Handle this properly!
Place a barricade there! Hurry up!
-Kumar.
-Sir?
-What's the situation update?
-Sir, the hyena has caused havoc.
Sir, if this continues,
-many people will be injured.
-Is anyone coming?
They've sent two experts
from the Wild Life SOS team.
They've only handled cheetahs before,
not hyenas.
Nobody knows how to handle it.
Parthiban, we have a situation.
It's an emergency.
Can you come here?
I've sent you the photo
of the footprints. Check that.
The footprints are big.
It could be a spotted hyena.
They are extremely ferocious.
Okay. How soon can you get here?
Run!
Help!
Promise me, you won't tell your mom
that you were late for school today.
You promise me you won't tell mom
that I took my phone to school today.
Please, Dad!
The situation is totally
out of control, Parthiban.
Hyenas are social animals, Joshy.
They live in packs.
If a hyena is alone here,
either it has lost its way
or the rest of its clan is dead.
People will fear it and try to kill it.
But we have to capture it alive.
If we follow your advice,
we will become its prey.
Then how should we capture it?
The walkie-talkie, please.
Hey, Channel 3. We are on Channel 3.
Dad, I'll come along. I'll be helpful.
Stay in the car.
That'd be the most helpful
thing for me.
I am not in the mood
to get chided by your mom.
Okay?
Put up the barricades!
Push it here, quickly. Hurry up. Come on.
-Why did you place the barricades?
-The DFO's orders, sir.
What are you looking at? Do it now!
Sir, why did you place
the barricades here?
The animal could barge into the school.
It's very risky.
-Please--
-Ranger, do one thing.
I'll give you my uniform.
Do my job as well.
-Hey! What are you guys doing?
-Idiot!
-Place the barricade properly!
-Come in, Parthiban.
-Yeah, Joshy.
-They can't do a thing.
We'll have to handle the situation.
Get a tranquilizer from the sanctuary.
I'll tell you when to fire
and from where.
Yes, okay.
Catch it!
It's scared. It's looking
for a place to hide.
They don't understand it.
They are trying to kill it.
If this continues,
the hyena will enter the school.
Bring the tranquilizer
to the west end of the school.
Help!
Help…
Kids, get inside!
No one should be outside! Go!
I said get inside!
Students,
go to your classrooms immediately.
It's an emergency! Teachers and staff!
Please take all the kids
safely to the classroom.
There is no time! Hurry up!
-Get in!
-Hurry up!
Get in!
I got permission for a tranquilizer gun.
I'm taking it.
Run!
Move!
Come in, Parthiban.
I'm in position.
Joshy, wait!
Don't aim at its neck
like we usually do.
Its striking force will be as heavy
as its pitch of laughter.
Aim for the lungs!
Shoot.
-Hang on.
-This is the perfect time. Shoot, Joshy.
The gun is jammed, Parthiban.
A gun can't adapt
to the situation and operate.
It's a machine.
You need to service it every month.
-Siddhu?
-Dad.
Get your spear.
-Give your shoelace to Joshy.
-Okay, Dad.
-Don't go out!
-Run!
Watch out!
You heard your dad, right?
Give me your shoelaces.
-Uncle, give the javelin to me.
-Why?
-Get inside!
-Let's go!
Parthiban, the spear
you asked for is ready.
-Tell my dad that I'm throwing it.
-Parthiban, here it comes!
Hey, come on, move!
-Move.
-Move!
Who is that man?
His name is Parthiban.
He's from Chennai.
He's an animal rescuer.
He runs a coffee shop nearby.
-Hey!
-Move!
-Go inside.
-Yes, sir.
All right…
-Come on, move!
-Let's go.
-Move!
-Quiet!
Ask the questions in order.
The DFO will answer you.
Look, whatever happened
is not out of the ordinary.
It is our daily job.
Animals migrate
in search of food and water…
The DFO will give us some
exclusive news. Come on.
There's no point in asking them anything.
They didn't do anything.
A middle-aged man in a white shirt.
Find him. You'll get
the real information from him.
That'd be exclusive.
-White shirt, middle-aged man?
-Yes.
Where do I find him in this crowd?
Thalapathy
His entry spells power
Who is our brother? Thalapathy!
You wanted a shirt urgently.
-What happened, sir?
-Get it stitched.
-What's this? There is blood on it!
-Stitch it.
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
Hi, Chief.
-Morning.
-Morning, sir.
…is in this town
Hi, Thalapathy!
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down…
Why is this not heating up?
Some problem with the thermostat, sir.
I've called the service team.
They'll be here today.
-The cakes are ready for delivery.
-Okay.
Should I ship them?
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning.
Just an ordinary person
Yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person
Yeah, I'm just a…
Sir, this shirt is ripped badly.
It can't be stitched.
Do you know which shop
my wife bought this from?
-I don't know.
-I'm in trouble.
Hey, what's going on?
How did the police get our photos?
They're looking for us
at every checkpoint.
The man who told us to kill
the collector betrayed us.
He's the one
who leaked our photos.
Don't go out for a week. Hide yourself.
Please don't get caught.
I'll do something. Stay hidden.
Hey, we have no money!
We have to get out of here!
We have no clue where we are
and what is happening.
We trusted you and came here,
and you're bossing us around?!
We can't go anywhere
without money.
Do something, and send us money!
Please understand the situation.
The police have become alert
because of the collector's death.
It'll take a week to get
the situation under control.
-Don't try to contact me until then.
-Hey!
You--
What are you looking at?
Eyes on the road!
-What happened, boss?
-What should I do with them?
In the early hours of yesterday morning,
some unknown men who broke
into the collector's guesthouse
-and throat-slit and brutally murdered…
-You didn't get ready yet?
Oh, you're mad about the shirt.
I-I spilled chocolate on it,
so I decided to wash it and changed…
I bought you that shirt,
especially, for our anniversary.
But you ruined that shirt
as well as my mood.
I have nothing to say to you now.
Now, my mood is not going to change
no matter what you do.
But the plan won't change.
I can also be mad.
Your breaths and my breaths
Are entangled now
I see you everywhere
This is your magic
Small moments of excitement
Shall we pick up the kids from school?
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
-Hi.
Yes, tell me.
Chintu-- No.
M-Mathi's mother is not well.
Siddharth's father is not well.
Her mom is missing her.
-Who are you?
-His mom.
Her dad.
My soul and your body
I see you everywhere…
-A small peg?
-No, I don't drink.
-Think of it as medicine.
-Really?
How do you drink this, sir?
Stay away from the cage.
We will be adopting this hyena.
What should we name it?
Elsa.
Ghost.
Hachiku.
I also have a name in mind,
but promise me you won't laugh.
How about "Chakadbangadu"?
You are my first wish
Look ahead!
DONATION BOX
You are with me at every step
You are unique
Don't be scared.
-Chintu, come here.
-No.
-Come on, it's okay.
-Okay, go.
Slowly.
Come from this side. Don't be scared.
Do you like him?
You are with me at every step
My heart is flying high like a kite
Open it quickly.
-Sir, you're not supposed to help.
-Please wait.
Go! Hurry!
Sir, no.
-Is the shop on the left or right?
-It's over there, boss.
How much is it?
Your shop is pretty empty.
When do customers usually come?
After 6:00 p.m.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome, sir.
I checked everything.
All of their chests are empty.
What do we do now?
We'll wait here until nightfall.
What? You want to cut my hair?
This idiot will be the death of me.
Everyone on the road was panic-stricken
and running around.
That's when the serial killer
stood in the middle of the road
and started shooting at everyone.
There was a pile of corpses
on the road.
He was notorious.
He was killing everyone.
At that time, a brave and bold
police officer got there
and fired at the serial killer.
The serial killer ran and hid somewhere.
When the police officer
was reloading his gun,
the serial killer fired at him.
Hey!
Then the wounded police officer
fell at your feet.
He fell at the place where
you were safely hiding behind the car.
Now, the police officer's gun
is in your hand
and you have a clean shot.
The serial killer doesn't know
that you are there,
but you can easily shoot him
from your position.
We only got Rs. 300.
And this phone.
Hey, go and find someone rich!
And you have an easy way out.
You can quietly escape from there.
What will you do then? Picture yourself.
I'll just sleep.
Oh! You'll sleep, I see!
-Siddhu, it's getting late. Go to bed.
-Wait, Mom. Just a few more minutes.
I'll take the easy way out
and bring in more police officers.
By then, the serial killer
will kill more innocent people.
I'll give the gun to the police officer
and say,
"Look, here's a clear shot. Fire."
The police officer is shit-scared.
How can he shoot?
Picture yourself.
Let go of me!
-Hey, what is the number?
-Help me!
She's a nuisance!
-Hello? Wait.
-Where are you, dear?
-Here.
-Hey.
Hey, tell us your ATM PIN,
or I'll kill you!
-Tell me.
-Why are the police here?
Hey, stop screaming!
No… please don't.
-I can't move. Help me.
-Tell us your ATM PIN.
-Your PIN.
-Let me go.
-The PIN.
-Please let me go! No!
Let me go! Don't do this!
Tell me the PIN.
Then I'll shoot him myself.
If you shoot him,
you'll also labeled a murderer.
It is against the law.
There is one more way.
Picture yourself.
Why did you shoot him?
Where did you get this gun?
-PIN!
-What?
PIN!
I don't know what else to do, Dad.
No matter what I do,
someone will be killed.
Either an innocent or a criminal.
So, it'd better be the criminal.
Siddhu, go. Go and sleep.
It's getting late.
Chintu, come.
Dad!
The only option is to shoot him.
Who are you talking about?
The killer in the Picture Yourself story.
He's still thinking about that.
As I told you, if you shoot,
you'll be labeled a murderer.
You'll end up in jail. You won't even
get sleep. Are you okay with that?
I won't be sent to jail. After all,
I will have saved innocent people.
If I'm lucky, I'll get a medal.
Ain't I smart?
Get in the car.
-What were you talking about?
-Nothing.
What time is the wedding?
We'll go there
after dropping Chintu off at school.
He couldn't even think
of the right answer.
And he's thinking
of becoming a writer!
Both of you, please sign here.
Congrats.
Are you guys witnesses?
Please come and sign this.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you so much.
See you later.
-Bye.
Hey, you can touch her
only after I say so. I'm kidding.
-Take good care of her.
-Yeah.
-Bye.
Where should I drop you off, ma'am?
I have some work in the record room.
So, I'll stay back.
Do you want to say anything?
Stop telling my kids
such rubbish stories!
-Why? What happened?
-Give me your phone.
Check the browser history.
Browser history? Mine or his?
-His, of course.
-Oh!
"How to hunt? How to kill a deer?
How to kill a hyena?
-How to get successful in life--"
-Is this a joke?
No, I'm just reading it.
Who taught him all this?
You, right?
Okay, I'll ensure
this doesn't happen again.
-You'd better!
-Okay.
Great horned owl, Joshy.
They're becoming extinct.
Where did you find this?
Sir, this owl is from Australia.
I know everything.
-He's lying, sir.
-I'll slap you!
Since when have you been doing this?
How many more of them do you have?
Just this one, sir.
I hit it with my slingshot.
It fell unconscious with a thud.
Joshy, inform Blue Cross.
It needs immediate treatment.
Ask our veterinary doctor
to come here right away.
He's no more.
-What?!
-Yeah, I forgot to tell you.
He died on the spot
in a car accident last night.
I think he lost control,
and his car fell into the valley.
Yeah?
What?
Okay, I'll be there. Yeah.
It was not a car accident.
It was a planned murder.
Murder? How come?
He was shot dead.
I just got the intel.
A murder in our town?!
Last week, when the collector died,
I thought it was a hit-and-run case.
But now, after the doctor's death,
I don't think it's a coincidence.
I don't get it, Joshy.
I've lived here
for the past 20 years.
I've never heard of anything like this.
Who could be openly
roaming around with a gun?
Parthiban, don't worry.
We'll take care of it.
I'll go and check.
Shall I come with you?
Last week, when the collector died,
I thought it was a hit-and-run case
But now, after the doctor's death,
I don't think it's a coincidence.
Dad, it's your turn.
Dad!
-Your turn.
-Okay.
Sir, I'm done for the day.
May I leave now?
Oh, stop teasing me!
I'm going to the hostel!
Go. He must be waiting for you.
My song is much better than yours.
I know a better song than this.
Do you want to listen to it?
First, look there.
The shop is closed, sir.
I want a chocolate coffee.
We're closed, sir.
Didn't you see the sign outside?
Make that two.
-The shop is closed, sir.
-Three.
Sir!
I've cleaned up everything.
Can I come an hour late tomorrow?
I need to go to the temple.
The shop is closed, sir.
Shruthi, leave now. Hurry up.
I'm talking to you.
Can't you hear me?
-I just--
-Shruthi, go. I'll tell him.
Hey, what are you doing?
Sir!
Sir, calm down.
I'll get it.
Hey, he took the gun again!
Go and stop him!
Let go of me!
Sir…
I've brought all the cash I've got here.
If you want more,
I'll withdraw it and give you.
Let her go, please.
This is wrong.
Let her go. Please. I'm begging you.
Chocolate coffee.
Let me go.
Stay right here.
-Don't come out until I tell you to, okay?
-Sir!
Let go of me! Sir!
Boss, he is inside.
Go and close the gate!
Sir!
Save me, sir!
-Sir!
-Hey!
Did you forget what I told you?
Let go of me!
Sir!
Save me, sir!
Hey, our job is done. Let's go.
Hey!
-Come with me, or just die!
-Let go of me.
All three of them and the CCTVs here
have seen our faces.
If we don't want our faces
to be on the news tomorrow,
we have to finish them.
Let's have chocolate coffee. Sit.
Good boy!
Sir!
Hey, delete the CCTV footage.
Sir, save me!
Sir--
Sir!
Help!
Help me!
Sir!
Save--
Hey!
Hey! Let go of him!
Sir!
Hey, hit him, not me!
Hey!
Dad!
-Dad!
-Shruthi! Chintu!
Got your chocolate coffee?
-Dad!
-It's okay.
Sir!
Hey! Let go of him!
Or I'll stab her!
Sir!
-Save me!
-Kill him.
Where are you going? Kill him!
Dad!
Chintu!
Parthiban!
Parthiban.
Go to the hospital first.
It doesn't look like a clot.
No physical injuries.
But she is showing signs of PTSD.
This child is in shock.
She is bound to feel anxious.
But there's nothing to worry about.
I'll give her some medicine.
Take good care of her, okay?
Okay.
Parthiban.
Parthiban, whatever happened
was not your mistake.
Anyone in your place
would've done the same.
We will fight in the court.
I'll always be with you.
I'll take care of the children
until you get released.
-Don't worry. I'll handle--
-Sathya, I don't know what happened.
I saw him going…
toward Chintu.
And then…
all this happened.
-Sir, we can't wait any longer.
-May I go in?
Parthiban, the police officers
are waiting outside.
I've asked them to wait for some time.
-Joshy, is there no other way--
-Sathya, try to understand.
This is very serious.
Five people have been killed.
Even I can't do anything.
He'll remanded for 15 days.
We have to follow procedures.
We'll decide what to do
after he's produced in the court.
Don't panic, okay?
Parthiban, let's go.
Your honor, according
to the ballistic reports,
five bullets fired from the gun
penetrated the victims' foreheads
at point-blank range.
Not a single bullet was missed.
A person who has never handled
a gun before was able to fire
five bullets in a split second. How?
Sometimes, even trained police officers
struggle to shoot below the knee.
But this person's aim
was absolutely perfect.
Inspector Bhawar Jetha.
Compare Mr. Parthiban's shooting skills
with that of a few ordinary men.
And submit the court proper proof
backed with adequate explanation.
-Nazrat!
-Yes?
Go and stand over there.
-Hey, leave it!
-Shahid.
Sashikanth.
What are you doing?
Parthiban!
Step forward.
-Kumar.
-Sir?
Give him the nine-mm rifle.
Only after I send
the man who killed my husband
and younger brother…
to his grave along with his family
will I allow the funeral rites
of my husband to be performed.
I take this vow!
This is my promise to both of them!
Don't cry. It's okay.
Parthiban, here!
Your action was just a general exception.
Don't worry.
Parthiban, the ones you killed
weren't good people.
They were all gangsters.
It will come under self-defense.
Okay? Don't worry!
We'll handle it. Okay?
Take care of Chintu.
Your Honor, a few days ago,
when a spotted hyena
strayed into our town,
everyone wanted to kill it,
but my client risked his life
and saved the hyena
from the people's attack.
I only have one question.
How can a man who even loves
wild animals so much
kill those five men?
He killed those ruthless men
in an act of self-defense
to save his employee,
his daughter, and himself.
Your Honor, I request the court
to release my client
under the IPC
Right of Private Defense Act.
Bearing in mind the interrogation,
arguments, and statements debated here,
the court pronounces
Mr. Parthiban innocent
as per the IPC Section 103 and 106.
He has been acquitted
of all charges and honored.
Also, I propose
the Indian government to award
Mr. Parthiban with
the National Bravery Award for this year.
Parthiban,
walk free with your head held high.
-Move!
-Sir…
-Please move!
Get out of the way!
All of you, step back!
-Is the decision to acquit you right?
-Move.
-Why did you have to kill five people?
-Move!
-Make way!
Step back! Move!
Give me that.
-Get in.
-What are you doing? Step back!
Move!
Get out of the way!
-Sir!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Dad.
-Yes?
-You were right, Dad.
Even if we have a gun in our hands,
we shouldn't shoot.
That isn't so easy.
Now, I understood everything.
Dad, I can't see you
disheartened like this.
Those dead men have
many cases filed against them.
They were dangerous.
They must have acquaintances.
Do you think they'll keep quiet?
Just to be safe,
be careful, Sathya.
MUMBAI
SALEM
PEOPLE'S HERO FREED
OF THE MURDER CHARGES
SHIMLA
D'Souza, here you go!
THE CITY HERO
KILLS THE THUGS IN HIS CAFE
TELANGANA
I can't forget everything
and start working
at the coffee shop like before, Sathya.
I'm unable to focus.
I'm scared of the voices
Of the click, of the beat
Of the music I've been hearing all night
Pause, play, repeat!
I'm scared of the mountain
Of the river, of the fire
Of the sound of lightening in the sky
Those sounds make me wanna cry
-This light above me
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those colors
-These speakers
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those woofers
-Bad trip
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those chills
Shit-scared of A, shit-scared of B
Okay, I'm gonna pee
I'm scared of the night
I'm scared of the day
I'm scared of my shadow
Get it out of my way
I'm scared of my past
I'm scared of my future
I'm scared of the present
Can't take this torture
-Dad!
-I'm feeling cold, I'm feeling hot
Just living in a fear of getting caught
I'm scared of the creepy
I'm scared of the crawly
And I swear, I'm not on molly
This light above me
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those colors
-These speakers
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those woofers
-Bad trip
-I'm shit-scared of that
-Those chills
I'm shit-scared of that
Shit-scared of A, shit-scared of B…
I had kept it somewhere here.
Where is it?
What are you looking for?
You won't find anything there.
There is nothing left in the house.
How long are you going to sit at home?
The cafe has been closed for ten days.
You aren't even dropping off
your daughter at school.
Just look at their faces.
The court has declared you innocent.
Then why are you living
the life of a criminal?
You've not only locked yourself
inside the house but also your family.
Go get some fresh air.
I'll take care of the house.
Take the kids with you.
Go!
I feel like drinking coffee.
I'm going out to buy some milk.
Do any of you want anything?
-Greetings, sir.
-Hello, sir.
-Hi, sir.
-Greetings.
He is the real man.
Parthiban, I need to go to that shop.
You two come with me. Let's go.
Buy whatever you want. Come, Siddhu.
-Take care.
-Okay, Dad.
Mom, I want a bread omelet.
Okay, let's go eat.
-One bread omelet, please.
-Okay, ma'am.
-Eat it. I'll be right back.
-Okay, Mom.
-Hello.
-Sir, this is Kumar.
-I've got an intel.
-Okay.
There's some
suspicious activity in town.
The undercover source has informed us
that Parthiban's family is in danger.
We got this intel two weeks back,
but the inspector hid it.
-We have to stop them from going out.
-Yeah, okay. I'll call you back.
Parthiban, where are you?
-I'm in the market.
-Do you see anything suspicious around?
Parthiban?
-What's wrong?
-Listen, I've got intel
that some goons are after you.
Do me a favor. Drop whatever
you're doing, and just go home.
Immediately!
Hey, only after I kill you and your family
will I bury my brother-in-law.
Finish him!
-Hey!
-Parthiban!
Hey!
Sathya, go!
How dare you lay
your dirty hands on my family!
Dad!
Parthiban, don't! Listen to me!
Parthiban!
Parthiban, what are you doing?
-Let go of me!
-No! Parthiban!
Parthiban, what are you doing?
Let him go!
If I let him go, he will kill us!
Parthi, I'm scared to see you
sitting here like this.
Let's come back
after the inspector summons us.
Let's go home now, please.
I'm not going anywhere.
-Kumar!
-Sir!
Why is it so crowded outside?
Is it a fish market?
-Parthi, let's go.
-Go and see.
What are our men doing outside?
What is it? I'd asked you to file
a complaint and leave, right?
Why do you insist on staying?
Don't we have any other damn work?
Go and tell him everything.
He'll note it down.
Just sign that and leave, got it?
I'll see what I can do.
Hey! Send my tea inside!
Where are you going?
What will you see? How we die?
When we step out of the house,
we're scared of who might attack us.
Why are you getting worked up?
Two weeks ago,
one of the corpses from the shoot-out
went missing from the mortuary.
The department asked you to alert us.
Why didn't you do that?
Who told you all this? The forest officer?
Do you expect us to think
about you 24-7 and serve only you?
-Don't we have other work?
-Just wait.
In all fairness,
I did what you should've done.
I killed those
who tried to kill my daughter.
What did I do wrong?
Let's go home, please.
I want an armed guard
posted at my house 24-7.
I won't leave until then.
Hey! Get up!
I said get up!
-Get up! Get lost!
-Please. Let's go.
Do you think
you are a big shot?
Get out!
Out!
He wants an armed policeman, it seems!
You can't just order us around
and get an armed cop at your disposal.
The government will decide
whether to give you security or not.
You are neither the law…
nor the government.
You are just a common man
who sells bread and butter!
Come in. We were waiting for you.
He is scared of sounds.
So, we should stand outside his house
holding a gun for his safety!
And he'll make out
with his wife inside--
Hey! You're a police officer!
Mind your words!
What did you say?
-Parthiban!
-Hey, hold him!
Parthiban, let go of him!
Parthiban, he's a police officer!
Let go of him!
Parthiban, let go of him!
Let go!
Hey, hold him!
-He'll die. Let go of him.
-Parthiban, let go of him, please!
-Hey!
-What are you doing?
Parthiban, what are you doing?
It will create problems! Parthiban!
-What are you doing?
-Parthiban!
Parthiban, control yourself!
Calm down!
Parthiban, stop it!
Parthiban, what are you doing?
Control yourself!
Sir, are you okay? Is your neck okay?
Parthiban.
Are you crazy?
What was wrong with you?
You want police protection,
but why should they give it?
There's no proof of assault against you.
You haven't been injured at all.
Who said that I'm not injured?
Parthiban, are you really sure?
Joshy, I may go overboard
if I do it myself.
So, you do it for me.
Okay. As you wish.
-SP.
-Yes, sir?
-Can you come to my residence?
-Right now?
-Now. Yes, it's urgent.
-Okay, sir.
Sir, I have a small request.
Please summon a police officer
from my village.
900 KILOS OF DRUGS SEIZED
Napoleon reporting to duty, sir!
Where should I stand? Tell me, sir!
Whom have you sent?
Parthiban, you asked for
a high-ranking officer from your village.
He is the highest-ranking police officer.
You must've heard
of a drug bust in Trichy.
I heard he was responsible
for catching 50-60 of those men.
-Move these tables here quickly.
-Yes, sir.
Hey!
Put your phone down.
Hey, listen!
What do you want?
Hey, come here!
I'm talking to you! Hey!
Hurry up! Load the stuff!
TELANGANA
What happened?
What?
Hey!
-Boss!
-Move!
-Get out of my way! Move!
Boss?
You'd better pray to God
that it's important news.
Or you'll die today.
Look at this picture.
Hey!
He is a freaking badass, man
He's a badass, run for your life quickly
He's a badass, stay within your limits
He's a badass man
Leo Das, man
He's a badass, run for your life quickly
Got you, rascal!
Hey!
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
He is a freaking badass, man
If the lion is on the prowl fearsome
Feast is for the forest wholesome
Fearing his hunt, scatter
Hither and thither, helter-skelter
Putting an end to gangsters countless
He'll punish them, he's ruthless
Until now, he was a good soul
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
In this story, he has a demon's face
He's a badass man
Not a matchstick, he's a volcano
Don't mess with him
Those who stay away from him are fine
Keep that in mind
Hey!
He is a badass!
Stay within your limits
He's a badass man
Leo Das, man
Badass bona fide, dude
Take to your heels
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
How many people should we send from here?
If he's really Parthiban,
four people will suffice.
But if he is Leo…
-We'll finish him!
LEO DAS
BORN: 13-05-1977
…even all our men won't be enough.
Don't act too smart, man
He will give you grief and strife
Beat you to a pulp and end your life
Not a matchstick, he's a volcano
Don't mess with him
Those who stay away from him are fine
Keep that in mind
He is a badass
Run for your life
Stay within your limits
He is a badass man
Leo Das, man
Run for your life
Thank you.
-Is it sweet?
-Bloody sweet.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Leo
He's a freaking badass, man
Leo!
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Leo
Rest in peace!
This one is…
It could be better.
-I'll make it better.
-Yeah.
The girl sitting here has been
staring at you for a while.
Don't turn around immediately.
Maybe she's a reporter.
-She left.
-Sir,
the man at the back
has been here for a while.
He isn't saying anything.
Could you please check?
-Where is he?
-In the backyard.
Okay. Go, I'll handle him.
"Pleasure is mine"?
Hi, sir. What would you like to have?
Coffee.
-Sugar?
-You know very well…
how many spoons of sugar I have.
How would I know whether
you prefer sugar or not?
-I do.
-Okay.
Just a moment, sir.
Sorry, sir.
-One sugar cube or two--
-You know that too.
Sir, I don't know that.
You're mistaking me for someone else.
I'm just being friendly to you
because you're my customer. That's it.
Here is your coffee
and your sugar.
Leo?
You are Leo!
Parthiban.
I don't know who Leo is.
There's already a lot
of confusion in my life.
Please don't add to it.
Please enjoy your coffee and leave.
Do you mind?
Can you make it a little stronger?
Sure, sir.
Do you know this brand?
No, sir. I don't smoke.
-I can't even stand its smell.
-D Slash.
You used to call it Honey Badger,
but it is Black Devil.
Twenty-five puffs.
You invented this brand.
You like nocturnal animals, right?
Once, a honey badger
entered our tobacco field.
Do you remember?
It didn't get caught in your trap.
It didn't get killed
by Harold's spear either.
In the end, it died
by the bullet that I fired.
You'll remember it now.
Do you want anything else,
or shall I get your bill?
So, you believe
your old identity doesn't exist, Leo?
Wait, what?
Listen.
There are already
many problems in my life.
Let me tell you nicely one last time.
You're mistaking me for someone else.
Look, I don't have patience.
So, don't waste my time.
Mount View Lodge.
Come there and confess that you're Leo.
Sir, no alcohol, please.
Start the car.
No alcohol.
My colleague's friend stays in Kadapa.
I sent him a photo of the D Slash
cigarette box and got some details.
As per the details he gave me,
the chap who had come here
was Antony Das.
Once upon a time, he ran
a huge tobacco company in Andhra Pradesh.
-There was a fire at his factory and--
-Hold on.
Why should I know
the life story of a guy
who barged into my cafe
and blew cigarette smoke in my face?
Because this is important.
-No, I--
-At least hear him once.
Go on, Joshy.
Antony Das had a son named Leo.
Okay.
Leo Das.
I couldn't find any details
about him other than his name.
Some people believe
he did something before he died.
And some believe he is still alive.
He can fool everyone.
He can fool the world.
But he can never fool me.
In some odd way,
you have a striking resemblance to him.
I saw his eyes.
I know those eyes.
It is him.
Parthiban, you grew up
in an orphanage, right?
Do you remember anything
about your childhood?
What is this? This is bullshit!
We are the victims here!
But the police
are treating us like the accused.
-Let's go, Parthi.
-Wait.
Sathya, wait.
Joshy.
I understand you're asking me
all this because you care about me.
But from my childhood, until I was 20,
I grew up in Sathyamangal Orphanage.
And I met her for the first time at--
What was that place?
At the Munnar trekking.
That's where we met.
I saw her. We became friends.
Within two days,
I asked her to marry me.
That's it.
After marrying her,
we settled here because of her job.
I have been here since then.
This is my story.
They've come here
from the south, Parthiban. It's quite far.
By road. If they came here
looking for you from so far,
it must be something important.
The factory was closed down
because of him.
Now, only he will start it again.
I'll make him do it.
My world is very small, Joshy.
It's like a snow globe
that we get at a shop.
It has a small independent house,
surrounded by trees,
snow, and cool breeze.
Why is this happening to me?
At least you believe me.
Sorry.
It's alright. I understand.
If they come back
and cause you any trouble,
we'll inform the police.
Keep an eye on his family and friends.
Okay, boss.
I feel like someone
is keeping an eye on us, Sathya.
This eerie silence is making me restless.
I feel very disturbed.
Look at me. Understand this.
Even if the whole world suspects you,
I will always stand by you.
Have I ever questioned you?
Stop thinking about these things,
and sleep peacefully.
Let's go, Parthiban.
Are you planning
to sleep here standing up?
Don't touch the engine,
just fix the heater.
I want my jeep back ASAP.
Get it ready by tonight.
What do you want?
I got to see you.
That's enough for me.
I'm so mad that if I slap you right now,
your face will be distorted for life.
Sorry.
Get out!
Keep walking.
-Yes, Sathya?
-I got you the tablet you wanted.
Do you want anything else?
I've given the jeep for servicing.
I had told you we'd go
to the pharmacy later.
-Why did you leave the kids alone at home?
-Mathi is with me.
Priya is also with me.
You could've waited for a day.
What was the hurry?
Some things can't be delayed.
Don't worry.
I'll take an auto home.
-Take care.
-Okay. Call me once you reach home.
No!
Don't be scared.
We're the same blood.
Do you know who she is?
My granddaughter.
My blood.
You were
at the cafe yesterday, right?
You'd better leave,
or I will call the police.
Police?
I am not here to trouble you.
The person you've been
living with for 20 years
is not Parthiban but someone else.
When you realize he is a ruthless murderer
who committed
many murders,
come and meet me.
I'll show you the true colors
of your husband.
-Hello--
-Why didn't you answer the call?
-He was here.
-What happened, Sathya?
Who are you talking about?
The guy who came
to your cafe yesterday!
He came to the medical shop
looking for me.
-Okay. Where are you now?
-I am at home.
They followed me in their car.
It is parked outside our home.
Sathya, close the doors.
Give the phone to the police officer.
He is missing. I am alone here.
I'm scared.
Go to our bedroom and lock the door.
Siddhu and I are on our way.
Answer the call!
-Dad, what is it?
-Siddharth, go home immediately,
-and keep your spear handy.
-What are you saying--
If anyone tries to enter the house,
attack them with your spear.
-I'm coming too.
-Okay, Dad.
Is this how our life is going to be now?
Always on the lookout. Always hiding.
We'll have to keep worrying
if the kids are fine at school. Right?
Tell me. Who is he?
He claims that our daughter
is his granddaughter.
I feel terrified when I look at him.
Today, he cut someone's throat
in front of us.
And he did that just to save us.
Chintu, come here.
Let her be. She's already terrified.
-Sir…
-I pleaded with a lot of people,
I fought with a policeman,
and I pleaded with the judge,
just to get you here…
so that you could protect my family.
Do you not have any honesty
towards your job?
Don't say that.
I am expecting honesty from those
-who work only for money!
-It's not like that.
Instead of doing your duty,
you're always just sleeping!
It'd be better if you just left!
-You're getting me wrong.
-I don't think so.
Now, don't give me that crap
and make me cuss you out!
-I just went to recharge--
-Stop talking.
I said stop talking.
I'm controlling myself
considering your age.
You're getting me wrong.
-Sir…
-Go. Just go.
Such a pain in the neck!
I'm sorry, Dad.
-I-I didn't know it was you…
-It's okay, son.
That was a good throw.
You proved today that you're my son.
The person you've been living with
is not Parthiban but someone else.
He is a ruthless murderer
who committed many murders.
A bad dream?
Yes. A nightmare.
I think some major conflicts
happened in that family.
Maybe that's why
their tobacco empire got destroyed.
I have sent you
the photos and certificates.
Check if they are forged and tell me.
Okay? Bye.
There were many rumors about this.
But there is a man in the Shimla
jail who knows the truth.
His name is Hridayaraj D'Souza
in the records.
As per the intel we got,
he was Leo Das' friend.
If you want to meet him,
you only have two days.
I don't think you'll be
able to get here by then.
-Would you like to talk over the phone--
-No.
I-I'm leaving now.
Make the arrangements.
-I'll be there by tonight.
-Okay, Joshy.
-Thank you.
-Who is the villain?
It's late. Your mom isn't home yet.
She has been coming home late
every day lately.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
That's her.
-Tell me.
-Parthi, I'm not coming home tonight.
Don't wait for me for dinner.
-Why? What happened?
-I took many days off this month.
So, there's a lot of pending work.
I thought I'd finish it all tonight.
I yelled at Siddhu this morning,
so he isn't answering my call
Is he home? I was too harsh on him.
Ladies and gentlemen!
May I have your kind attention, please?
Where are you going by plane?
-To the head office.
-Oh, the head office!
-Chintu.
-Yes?
You don't suspect your dad, right?
-No.
-Why?
Because you are my dearest dad.
My dearest kid.
Hey, it's your dad.
Siddharth, get in the car!
-I said get in--
-Let go of my hand!
Uncle, don't force him
if he doesn't want to come.
What? Are you going to kill him too?
Okay, don't come.
Who is the villain?
Who is the hero?
You'd better not be anywhere
near my family from now on!
Who is the villain here?
-Sir--
-What are you doing out here in the cold?
No one will barge in now.
I don't care who shoots
and who dies anymore. Go to sleep.
It's okay, sir. I'm good.
This courier came in today.
It's for your wife.
Sir, one moment.
I wanted to say something to you.
I understand all your worries and fears.
I see how much you love your family.
You can't see them in pain.
I will be retiring in 60 days.
If anyone troubles you or your family
in these 60 days,
I'll take them down with me!
Even if my family
is in an emergency back home,
I won't leave this place.
I swear this Napoleon doesn't work
just for money, sir.
I consider my work my God, sir. Trust me.
Tell me, did you really kill
all those men with such a heavy gun
at the commissioner's office?
I just read the manual and told them
how to operate the gun.
Dilli took care of the rest.
-Dad!
-Please don't tell anyone about this.
Okay.
Chintu!
Have a seat.
-How is he doing now?
-He is fine.
It's been three weeks
since he last called me.
All okay, right?
Why did you come here at this hour?
If you had told me,
I would've couriered it.
The government registration is pending
because they don't have certificates.
So, we thought we would
come here and collect them.
They're in the attic. Let me get them.
Sir, this is Hridayaraj D'Souza.
You only have 20 minutes to talk to him.
I'll wait outside until then.
You asked for this brand, right?
Hridayaraj D'Souza.
We don't have much time,
so I'll come straight to the point.
Das Company Tobacco Factory.
Its owners, Antony and Harold.
We have some information about them,
but we have no details about Leo.
Leo's associates died with him.
Only one of his associates is alive,
and that's you.
Just tell me one thing.
Is this Leo? Remember,
it's a matter of four lives.
I can see the fear of death in your eyes.
I know you will be hanged in three days.
If you tell me the truth,
I will send a petition now
and appeal for a review
of your death sentence. So, tell me.
Tell me everything from the beginning.
Hridayaraj, this is your last chance.
If you're here for a fair and just cause,
why did you come in from the back door
and sit near the toilet?
Whatever I had to say,
I said in the court.
No one can stop my hanging now.
Anything else?
What happened in that tobacco factory?
Is Leo alive or dead? If he's dead,
how did he die?
I'm not giving you this information
'cause you gave me booze.
I'll die in three days anyway.
No one is going to come
and question me then. So, I'll tell you.
In 1999, Das Company
was the most flourishing tobacco factory
in Andhra Pradesh.
The one who built
and ruled that empire was Antony.
Antony Das.
It was pictured to be
a tobacco business,
but Das Company used to run
many illegal businesses in their factory.
First, it was a local business.
But soon, they started
doing business internationally.
Antony used to never forgive
those who betrayed him.
He would kill them mercilessly.
He was someone who could
even scare the death angel.
Before starting any business,
he'd always sacrifice an animal.
He believed his empire would grow
if he sacrificed an animal.
Initially, he used to sacrifice animals…
but soon, he started
sacrificing humans too.
He was very superstitious.
Harold Das was his younger brother.
Harold was the only one
whom Antony trusted completely.
Harold.
Harold!
He went to Canada to study
but got acquainted with international
drug cartels over there.
He expanded their business
on foreign soil.
His dream was to make Das Company
the number one drug cartel in the world.
So, he created a drug called datura.
It was a new drug on the market.
Nobody had heard about it.
They grew datura
amid their tobacco plants.
They began to manufacture it
in their factory.
Datura was more lethal than cocaine.
Gradually, its demand
increased in the market.
That's when some
of his men gave this news
to the Narcotics Control Bureau.
He threw datura on the faces
of those whom he suspected
He killed them all so ruthlessly
that even today,
people in the mafia world
have not forgotten about it.
None of his men betrayed him after that.
Even if Antony and Harold were
managing the business at the top level…
they still needed someone trustworthy
working at the grass-root level.
Antony had a son.
I have seen him grow up
in front of my eyes.
Das. Leo Das.
All this hassle is because one of your men
leaked the information to NCB.
Have you ever faced a problem
because of me to date?
I'm helpless, sir.
It's almost 200 kgs of drugs.
I can't show a wrong count
and dismiss the case.
It's not possible.
One of you has to surrender.
Ask Leo to surrender.
Then you'll get your stash.
I can't do anything
if my seniors find out about this.
Don't worry.
I'll release him in a week.
What's the guarantee
that you'll release him in a week?
If you want your stash,
you have to trust me.
-Yes, Antony?
-Is Leo there?
He isn't here.
He said he'd cross the border
with the drugs.
He must be at the checkpoint.
I think he's outwitting them.
Hey, who is smoking over there?
Hit him and get him here!
Tell me, sir.
Yes. I'm here.
Hey, move!
-Move!
-Rest in peace!
Get him!
-Gabby! Start the vehicle!
-Hey! Go!
Load the stash! Hurry up!
Take this!
POLICE
Hey! I worked for you risking my job,
and you're outwitting me
and getting me into trouble?!
Let me see
how you take your stash…
Leo!
Don't!
Rest in peace!
Leo found out
who ratted us out to the NCB
from within our camp.
-Gabby!
-Yes, boss.
I had told you not to stop the truck
anywhere, come what may!
Then why the hell did you stop there
with all our stash loaded in the truck?
Why are you asking me this? Ask Daniel!
Every time I instructed him,
he said, "Call Leo.
This load won't move an inch
until he comes here and settles my share."
That smart-ass threatened me.
You call him a friend,
so he takes advantage of you.
Summon him.
Hey!
You think you're a smart-ass!
What is your problem?
Why can't you work with him?
He is my problem!
Until yesterday, he used to work under me.
Today, I am working under him.
If you don't stop all this,
I'll put a halt to your business!
-What now?
-I don't want him butting in, that's all.
If he does, we can't work together.
He was being a pain in the neck.
Right?
I don't about anything else but the stash!
I'll do as you say.
Hey, let go of him!
-Hey!
Remove the damn knife!
I know who your next target is.
Put the gun down and leave!
Have you watched the movie Judwaa?
The one in which Salman plays
the role of twin brothers, right?
There is a tiny change here.
Both the twins in the film were men.
Here, it's a man and a woman.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Rest in peace
Leo.
It isn't easy to cross all the checkpoints
with 2000 kgs of datura overnight.
The police target our men
as if they're shooting mongrels.
It's too risky to transfer it overnight.
Tell me what to do.
Even though it was
an impossible task,
Leo decided to transfer
the stash overnight.
Leo took it as a challenge
to transfer 2000 kgs of datura
by crossing two inter-state borders.
Imagine! Two thousand kilos of datura!
It was worth millions at that time.
He kept his word
and completed the task.
Later, he took matters into his own hands
for his dad's sake.
Amid all this, Antony's quest
for human sacrifices didn't stop.
For two years, he was searching
for a unique horoscope.
He believed that if such a person
was found and sacrificed,
his tobacco factory
and business would flourish.
We couldn't care less about it.
We were just happy that the drugs reached
the godown safely. We partied hard.
Bro, listen!
Bro, come here!
Please come here, brother! For our sake!
Yes! Come on!
I'm ready, come on!
I'm ready and fresh
My grasp is like that of a lion's
No matter who tries to come in my way
I won't budge
I'm ready, come on!
-Bro!
-Come on, dear! Try me!
Beat the drum
I'll make everyone dance to my tunes
A little bit of everything
Gets me going
If God promises you to shower you
with everything you want,
he snatches something
from you in return.
I have good news and bad news for you.
Out of all the horoscopes
I have checked to date,
only these two horoscopes are of our use.
Please take a look and decide.
I'm ready to harvest
And weed out my opponent
It is our fate at stake
To get rid of this headache
If he acts like Smart Alec
We will tie him in a sack
Dump him in a lorry
To get dissected in the factory
Hey, we know all the blueprints
Our mission will be a success
If you interfere, you'll also be akin
To a lamb offered to our family deity
Lamb for offering booze, cigarette, bidi
Everybody in our gang is trustworthy
As a team we work and think
Sharing a worldwide link
Our rules hold well in every city
Don't flick our tools to play dirty
We move and groove in unity
Our sync is our identity
I fight world wars not just a battle
Tired of winning every match I wrestle
Just one drum beat quick
Sure-shot power kick
I shouldn't have shown Elisa
and Leo's horoscopes to you,
but I had no other option.
I'm not sure
if we can find a similar horoscope
with the same star and date of birth, Das.
Hey! This cannot happen!
This cannot happen!
Both Leo and Elisa are like my own kids.
But if you ask for my opinion,
I'll choose Leo.
No.
The decision… the decision is all yours.
Even a lion is nothing in front of me
I am great at hunting
If I really want
Even my eyes can start firing
My sword is more dangerous than a bullet
I know, I am great
But I can also be the reason
For someone's death
-Do you get it, mister?
-Yes, master!
I'm known by another name too
You'll tremble in fear
Upon hearing it, dude
Print out the poster
All ready is your brother
Celebrate and how
Set it ablaze now
Hey, make way for our bro!
I'm ready and fresh
My grasp is like that of a lion's
No matter who tries to come in my way
I won't budge
I'm ready, come on!
-Bro!
-Come on, dear! Try me!
Beat the drum
I will make everyone dance to my tunes
A little bit of everything
Gets me going
Forgive me.
Between you and your sister,
all of them chose you to be sacrificed.
Even your uncle chose you.
I was the one who saved you!
You need not thank me for that.
Just forgive me.
Since I started managing our business,
I've killed countless people
for your sake.
I took your word as gospel
and killed my friend too.
But not anymore!
Enough with these superstitions!
Let go of Elisa!
Leo!
This is not just about our business!
-Why don't you understand?
-Hey!
She isn't just my sister.
She is my twin. She is a part of me.
If you do anything to her,
no matter how many births you take,
the day I see you, I will kill you!
The day I see you
will be your last day on Earth!
You're begging him?!
The day our mother died,
he didn't shed a single tear.
If he has decided
to sacrifice his children,
I don't consider him my dad anymore!
None of them are my kith and kin!
Will you do me a favor, Leo?
Don't spare any of them!
Hey!
Don't even think about it.
Hey! Don't you dare!
Let her go!
Dad!
Hey!
Let her go! Hey!
Elisa, try to understand!
You will be fine!
-Leo, burn down the entire factory!
-Elisa, stop!
Harold! Kill both of them!
Leo!
-Come on!
-Hurry up!
-Run!
-Come on!
-Catch them!
Hey! Don't spare anyone!
Don't leave anything out!
Burn everything down!
Everything!
Hey!
You wanted to sacrifice
your children for this, right?
Hey, Leo!
This shouldn't exist anymore!
I will…
-burn all of this down!
-Leo, stop it!
Hey! Give me the knife!
Elisa!
Elisa…
-Elisa…
-Leo.
Don't be with them, Leo.
Elisa!
-Elisa--
-Go somewhere far away.
Elisa!
That day, I saw the dead body
of the person whom I raised
with my own hands.
Tell me if this is Leo.
If you identify him,
all the problems will be solved.
Even if Leo stands among 1000 people,
I can identify him from his eyes.
This isn't him.
Don't play unnecessarily
with an innocent man's life.
Warden! Take me back!
I am feeling sleepy. Let me go.
Come on, get going!
We clicked this
when we were in third grade
and this in fourth grade.
And this in fifth grade.
This is the letter he sent me
when he was in college.
A NEW AND SCARY EXPERIENCE
TO STEP OUT
OF OUR SHELTERED EXISTENCE
FOR THE FIRST TIME
Can you do me a favor?
I'm asking you this as my brother.
I know what's on your mind.
I won't tell him you were here.
Make sure he doesn't find out.
Or he'll be devastated.
-Hello?
-Sir, is this Parthiban?
-Yes.
-Sir, come to the coffee shop at once.
It's an emergency.
He was drinking with us, sir.
He kept saying he saw his friend.
He was very happy.
He even paid for everyone's booze.
Then he left in an inebriated state.
He was talking to someone over
the phone in the middle of the road.
Then some people arrived in a car
and took him away.
-Was it a black car?
-Yes, sir.
Hey!
He claimed to be your friend
and came to your cafe.
He even took your picture.
How do you know him? Tell me!
Sir, if I see my customer in this state,
I will be upset, right?
Look into my eyes. Do I seem upset?
I don't know him, sir.
Even though he died here at my cafe,
I have nothing to do with him.
I'll come to the station when you call me.
You can interrogate me there.
I've left my daughter alone at home.
I'm worried about her. I'm leaving.
-Okay, go.
-All right.
I don't know whether to feel sorry
for Parthiban or be suspicious of him.
Listen.
Every human being
can lie only up to a limit.
He won't be able to lie
after a certain point.
He can't continue to put on an act
beyond that point.
Because no one is that mentally strong.
I think he is not lying.
He really is Parthiban.
Only Leo can tell us
what the truth is.
Parthi, when did you come back?
Chintu said you had gone out
somewhere in a hurry. Where did you go?
I had so much work today.
Why didn't you have dinner yet?
Parthi, what happened?
Why do you seem so down?
From now onward, I have nothing to lose.
I'm a loser.
You can tell what the truth is
-Please…
-just by looking into my eyes, Sathya.
-Parthi--
-Don't touch me!
Don't touch me.
I don't care even if
the whole world suspects me,
but how could you suspect me?
How could you think I am someone else?
Sathya!
Everything's over. No matter what
justification you give me now,
the fact that you suspected me
will haunt me forever.
What did you do?
You broke the trust we had built
over the years in a minute!
I am not Leo!
I'm tired of telling everyone
that I am Parthiban! I am Parthiban!
What can I do if somebody looks like me?
-Sweetie…
-What happened?
I was not feeling well. That's it.
Go to sleep.
Dance for me…
I've never seen anybody
Do the things you do before
They say, move for me
And when you're done
I'll make you do it all again
Tell me something.
Just because
some random fellow,
some goon looks like me,
you'll blindly believe it's me?!
You've broken my trust!
Just because that man
said he was my father,
you started suspecting if I am
really your husband?! Why?
All right.
I don't know who my parents are
or what my place of birth is.
I'm an orphan.
Maybe if my parents were alive,
no one would've suspected me.
-I'm an orphan, after all.
-Don't say that.
Parthi, you're not an orphan. Look at me.
Look into my eyes.
I didn't do this
because I didn't trust you,
I did this so that I could give people
answers when they questioned me.
"No. He is not that man."
I want to say confidently
that this is Parthiban!
Why don't you understand?
Sathya!
I want to ask you just one question.
How would you stay with me now
despite having a doubt
that I could be someone else?
Won't you feel disgusted?
Won't you feel like you're
staying with a stranger--
Trust me.
Sathya.
Please trust me.
I'm your Parthi. Trust me.
Leo, the time I gave you is over.
You didn't come to me.
So, I am here to see you.
Look outside.
Hey, who the hell are you guys?
What are you doing here?
Get lost from here,
or I'll kill all of you!
You won't leave this place alive!
You took it too far.
If you had come to me of your own accord
and admitted that you are Leo,
I wouldn't have come here.
Sir, don't come down at any cost!
I'll deal with them!
I just came to see you…
I don't know why
this mongrel is barking over here!
Okay.
Just tell me, where is your son?
Sathya, where is Siddharth?
-What happened?
-Where is Siddhu?
-Where is he?
-Do you see all these cars?
-Your son is in one of them.
-He isn't here!
Siddharth!
Get our daughter!
But your son is damn cute.
He came out to smoke
and got stuck in our trap.
You won't find him.
Parthiban, what is happening here?
Where is Siddhu?
Who are you talking to?
If anyone other than me
comes here, kill them. Just kill them.
-I can't do it--
-Don't let them go. Here.
Go.
Lock the door from inside, Sathya.
Okay, let's say you are not Leo.
But just think about it.
Why would I kidnap your son?
Today, 22 years ago,
your sister died.
On this day.
And now, I kidnapped your son.
Just imagine what I would do to him.
Don't you understand?
I do not have a sister!
Let go of my son! Tell me where he is!
Hey, step back! Get lost from here!
-Get lost!
-You'll definitely come, Leo!
Napoleon, open the door!
Hey!
-Napoleon, they've kidnapped Siddhu.
-I don't know when they took him.
Hey!
I'm also coming.
Here, sir! Shoot at them!
Load your gun.
Napoleon, handle the bike!
Watch out!
Where is my son?
Answer me, or I'll kill you!
Hey!
Siddhu?
Siddhu!
Where is my son?
I failed to kill you, Leo.
But I won't fail to kill your son.
I'm not the man you're looking for!
I told you so many times!
Where is my son? Come on, tell me.
Speak up! Where is my son? Tell me!
Accept that you're my son.
And I'll let your son go.
Oh, God! I'm not your son!
I'm not!
Tell me.
Who are you?
Harold, Leo killed Antony.
I'm coming there with his son.
The doctor said Napoleon needed bed rest.
They won't stop here.
They will come looking for you.
Your son will be safe.
The entire police force
is looking for him.
But you shouldn't stay here.
Your life is in grave danger.
Please listen to me.
I've arranged a car.
It's parked outside your house.
Collect your essentials and leave. Now!
Who is this?
Leo, no matter where you hide,
I'll come and find you.
Don't play with my ego
just to fan your ego.
If you want your son back,
hand over my brother to me.
Bring him here and take your son.
Here, Parthiban.
Go and save your son.
Hands up.
Keep walking.
Das, I've sent the boss' body.
We have boarded the train.
We'll be there in an hour.
Sir, as per your request,
I've given you your brother's body.
Please give me my son back.
I know, you won't believe me
no matter what I say.
-That's why I--
-Hey!
Don't be scared.
This is just my son's school bag.
Sir, this is my birth certificate,
and these are my educational certificates.
This is my ration card, Aadhar card,
and wedding photos.
This was clicked
when my daughter was born.
on my son's first birthday.
Look at this.
This was clicked when I first sang
a patriotic song on the stage.
You don't believe me? See,
my name is here on the certificate.
Look. This is you
and your sister on your birthday.
This is the honey badger
that had entered our tobacco field.
This photo was clicked
after it was killed.
Look how smart you look
with that blood-stained face!
I understand, sir.
It's not your fault
that you mistook me for Leo, sir.
He looks just like me.
Do you think I'm a fool?
-Sir…
-Do you think you're too smart?
Leo.
You know what I did to your twin sister.
I'm sure you haven't forgotten that.
You'd better accept that you are Leo.
Sir, I don't have a sister.
How do I make you understand?
Siddhu?
Sir.
In all these years,
he is scrutinizing someone
for the first time.
Human beings can lie.
Certificates can be fake.
But birds and animals never lie.
I've never seen an eagle
so closely in my life, sir.
Get it away from me. I'm scared.
Hey. You're putting up this act
just to protect your family, right?
But you committed a blunder there.
You came here to save your son
but left your wife and your daughter
all alone at home. You're not that smart.
How would you feel
if I asked my men
to kill your wife and daughter?
Hey!
-Get started.
-Okay, boss.
Sir, don't harm them.
Please, sir.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
Hey!
-What happened?
-Ask them not to harm my family, sir.
-What is it, Mom?
-Nothing, dear. Go back to sleep.
Sir, ask them not to go in.
-What's happening there?
-Sir, please.
Keep moving.
Come with me.
Hey, you, climb up.
-Hey!
-Sir…
-Someone, please tell him.
Tell them not to go in, sir. Please.
I am Parthiban, sir. I told you.
Badass, Mr. Leo Das is a badass
-You climb up.
-I'm scared of heights.
Hey! Just go!
My side is all clear.
Some of them are entering
through the main door.
Hey!
Hey--
Sir.
I killed all those who barged in
except for one guy.
He came in from a window.
Okay, Napoleon. I'll handle them.
Hey!
Are you playing the fool with me?
I won't spare you!
-Sir, please…
-Hey!
-Sir.
-Why are you hanging up on me?
-What is going on there?
He's very smart.
He's set up traps all around the house.
All our men are dead.
Believe me. He is definitely Leo.
Who is in front of you?
His wife and daughter.
Shall I kill them?
No need. Put the phone on speakerphone.
Point the phone towards his wife.
You still have time.
Accept that you are Leo.
Then I'll let them go.
Parthi!
Sathya, don't panic.
Accept it.
Chakadbangadu.
Hey!
Did I make a joke?
Why are you laughing?
Me?
I think it's some rabid dog.
Hello?
I'd told you to instruct your men
not to go in, sir.
The poor fellows are all dead.
Now, the Leo we know will emerge.
Chittu, he has to accept that he's Leo.
Don't let go of him!
Chop him into pieces!
Hey, keep an eye on his son.
Hey, Leo!
Remember? I used this to kill your sister.
Now, I am sure…
that you are not Leo.
You are Parthiban.
You are not the person…
I was looking for.
Let's call it quits.
What do you say?
Drop your gun.
Hey!
Lower your gun.
Didn't you hear it? Lower it.
Hey, either shoot at me or drop it!
Come on!
Leo!
-If I'm sweet, you're bloody sweet, Uncle.
-Hey!
I should've killed you
that day itself!
I made a mistake.
-Go to hell!
-Leo!
You dug your own grave!
"I want to see Leo. I want to find Leo."
You called me here!
Happy now?
Leo!
Drop your gun.
Go outside and check
if there are any vehicles.
When we talk about one's past,
we get to hear some good things.
But that's not the case with me.
Knowingly or unknowingly,
I have made many mistakes in the past.
The last chance I got to rectify
those mistakes was my family.
I will go to any extent
to protect this family.
The man called Leo is dead.
Now, if I have to convince
everyone that he is dead,
then first, I have to believe it myself.
I've accepted that Leo is dead.
How are you?
No matter how many people
come and ask me if I'm Leo,
I'll convince them all.
Even after all this, if someone
insists on knowing my story,
I'll tell them, but then
I'll kill them the next minute.
Of course, I'm Leo.
Leo Das!
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
My life is in this town
And I ain't going down
You think that I'm crazy
But I don't want the crown
Just an ordinary person
Yeah, I'm just a peace-loving soul
I'm just an ordinary person, yeah!
I'm just a peace-loving soul
Peace-loving soul
My life is in this town
I tried to tell everyone
that I am not Leo.
But no one believed me. They hit me.
Finally, they accepted that I'm not Leo.
Other than this, nothing happened.
Promise me this is
what you'll tell your mom.
You promise me
you won't tell mom that I smoke.
I'm just an ordinary person!
Yeah, I'm just a peace-loving soul
Yeah! I'm just a peace-loving soul
Peace-loving soul
-What happened to your face, Dad?
-Keep quiet.
Siddhu, switch on the TV.
All you crazy people, try to recognize me
From where I came and who I am
I think I forgot to lock the main door.
Shall I go and lock it?
Hello.
Just because you burned down
one datura factory,
do you think all your problems
will be solved, Parthiban--
Oh. I'm sorry.
Leo.
If you want to make
this society drug-free,
you will have to burn down
many other factories in India.
Do you want to know who I am?
Subtitle translation by: Sanika Munagekar