Is there no one at home?
Grandma is. She's
hard of hearing.
Don't! That is her room.
This is mine!
-Good night!
-Hush!
I will be right back.
Chetan Bhagat! Chetan Bhagat!
Chetan Bhagat!
Oh!
The Perks of Being a Wallflower!
You read it?
I read the book. Watched the film.
And I am one!
What are you? A
wallflower or a perk?
You are a wallflower,
aren't you?
You find yourself a corner.
Hear and see everything
but never do anything.
I need to do something.
You read Sophie Kinsella?
I tried but couldn't finish.
Why?
It's too difficult Natasha
asked me to read it.
You understood Wallflower
and not Kinsella?
That was an easy read.
-A wallflower or a fly, it's the same.
-Wow!
Oh!
You are smart!
What's wrong?
Is this your first time?
Really?
Yes.
Let me teach you.
Coffee?
Tea?
What happened last night...
was good, right?
-Yes.
But it was fun, right?
It was natural, right?
Don't ruin it by
talking about it.
Don't talk about it.
I spoilt it by talking about it?
-You won't fall in love, right?
-No.
Don't over-think it.
Let's not make a
big deal out of it.
-Okay.
-All right?
I just really hope he
doesn't get emotional.
But...
Mihir told me that
the problem with guys
tend to get emotional after sex
and they fall in love and...
you know, they get obsessed
and they start stalking you.
Like... why were you
talking with this guy...
why are you loafing
with that guy...
why don't you take
my phone calls?
I don't understand why they
can't separate between the two.
I'll see you in college?
Sure.
-Bye.
Hello! Sorry.
Sorry. Good afternoon.
Okay. Let's start where
we left yesterday.
What is it?
Why are you smiling?
Do we share a secret?
No?
Page number 93.
Mihir and I got married,
when I was twenty-six.
He was 12 years older than me.
And Mihir was my
first boy friend.
I had never dated anyone.
But Mihir had dated many girls.
So it was an adventure for me...
marrying a guy twelve
years older than me.
My parents were against it.
He has so many stories to share!
Like he had gone somewhere...
there was a girl...
they saw each other...
and they started talking
and something happened.
His stories were
straight out of a movie.
It's like books.
I don't have any
of that in my life.
We talked and he made
me try to understand...
that you will
resent me if you...
meaning, I will resent him...
meaning...
if you did not live your life...
do what you wish...
Go and see... explore
what you feel...
Examine your life.
Like, take... Amrita Pritam...
She had a lover, Imroze,
who was younger than her.
They lived together,
they were happy together,
but the love of her life was...
Sahir Ludhyanvi.
Draupadi lived
with five Pandavas.
She loved them and perhaps,
they loved her too.
Meaning... whatever it is...
Mahabharata did not happen
between the Pandavas.
They all fought
for her together.
I feel like an animal, but
animals don't know sin.
I'm married and I cannot
be with anyone else.
What if I fantasize
about someone?
It's not okay.
How can you expect
everything from a person?
You want him to be your friend,
you play young with me,
you play older with me
like... I see something
else in Tejas...
and something else in Mihir.
Now can Mihir become Tejas
and Tejas become Mihir? No!
What do I do?
One more actress has
come out saying that
she was sexually
harasses by the producer.
It's good that they are
finally speaking out.
They remained silent
for so many years.
But how can they prove it?
People play the victim
card for publicity.
Did you read this?
American high school teacher jailed
for having sex with students.
The case opened when the
husband learnt of it.
He divorced her.
Here, we read that things
like that happen there often.
But it's wrong.
Just because it
keeps happening...
it's wrong. You cannot
say that it is okay.
Did you see the student's age?
The student must have an age?
-He is 18.
-So he is 18... an adult.
How does 18 justify it? If he is 18...
it's okay?
18 or 21...
you can't have a
relationship with a student.
That too a physical
relationship.
But at 18, he is an adult!
How do you know
it was consensual?
His silence means it
was not consensual.
If there is no consent,
then it is non-consensual.
Excuse me.
-Tejas Bhave?
-Yes.
I need to talk to you.
Don't you think she is weird?
Listen! How old are you?
Why?
-Just tell me your age!
-21.
-Sure?
-Yes.
You did not increase it
during you admission?
-No.
-People say that. So I'm asking..
-I'm not sure.
-How can you not know?
Do you have your
birth certificate?
-Yes.
-Can you get it for me?
You can take it from
the college office.
I have to submit it there.
Should I ask the college that I
want Tejas Bhave's certificate?
What if they ask me why?
Why do you need it?
Listen.
What happened that night
was consensual, right?
I did not force you.
What do you mean?
Did I force you to have sex?
No. But...
What?
You made the first move!
Did you say no?
-No.
-Exactly.
So, it was consensual, right?
So, do something.
Say it. Say that
it was consensual.
What do I say?
Say that whatever happened
between us was consensual.
-Con... what is that word?
-Consensual!
-Consensual.
-Consensual. Yes. Say it.
It was consensual.
'Whatever happened between
us was consensual.'
-Whatever happened between us...
-Yes...
-Was consensual!
-Was consensual.
Say it in one go.
The complete statement?
Yes.
Say this. 'Whatever
happened between us,'
'Ms. Kalindi, was consensual.'
-Between us...
-'This is Tejas speaking. Ms. Kalindi...'
'Whatever happened between
us was consensual.'
Ms. Kalindi, this is Tejas speaking.
Whatever happened between us...
whatever happened...
whatever happened
was consensual!
Now say it properly!
Ms. Kalindi, whatever happened
between us was consensual.
-I am Tejas.
-Okay.
As if it's my fault!
If I go late, what can they do?
They have to hit me.
See! That's a... that's a...
that's a gutsy girl.
A gutsy girl is not
someone who screams out...
says masturbation.
You don't know, see...
Just go home today.
Play some sexy music.
Shut the door.
Wash both your hands first.
#
Okay. Think of Hrithik
Roshan and have a good time.
Can't you see, none of
these fuckers were guilty.
Now look here and there at her.
When I said masturbation
and she hid her face!
Ms. Kalindi!
I came by to apologize.
Why?
That day you I scared you when
I recorded your statement.
No. I did not
understand anything.
What was that word
'consensuous'?
Forget it.
-Listen, now we're friends, okay?
-Yes.
As in real friends...
who tell everything
and share everything.
Okay.
-But without benefits.
-What do you mean?
I mean I have a boyfriend now.
-Professor Neeraj!
-Yes.
-The Mathematics professor?
-Have you seen his hair?
-So nice, right?
He isn't like the other guys.
With someone in the night,
someone else in the morning.
Do you know what he says?
Did you know that
penguins are monogamous
and that helps them survive
in the extreme cold?
I want us to be penguins.
He believes in monogamy.
He does not wants to share
me with anybody else.
And he doesn't feel
that I'm weird.
Unlike what your Natasha feels.
-My Natasha?
-Yes! Your Natasha.
I know everything.
Anyway...
You don't hurt the
people you love.
I said, you're right.
Intentionally you don't.
But you always hurt
people that you love.
You can't hurt somebody
that you don't love.
If I love Mihir...
and if I love Tejas too,
what is wrong with that.
Anyway, we'll talk
about that later.
Because he's younger and all that,
but we'll talk about that later.
If I love Tejas and Neeraj
as well..., suppose...
Now... now... what was my point?
Now... now... will they feel...
bad...
and jealous and insecure?
Yes, they might.
But I will not ration my love.
I'm gonna give wholesale.
Like I'm gonna
give all of myself.
Hello.
Where are you?
Where the hell are you?
What happened?
You called and
said it was urgent.
I took care of it.
-So easily?
-It's not working out with Neeraj.
What happened?
I thought he was so
smart, so intelligent!
That he knows everything.
Everything.
He knows physics, statistics...
But not chemistry.
He doesn't know when to finish
the viva and start practicals.
After 17 days, 16
hours and 32 minutes,
you know what he said to me...
I think...
I should...
fornicate.
Fornicate.
Fornicate?
I also asked him
the same question.
Fornicate?
Uh...
Coitus.
-You mean we should fuck?
-Huh?
Yes.
Yes!
Now, I think I should
take off my pant...
Light.
Okay? Now! Switch.
There... there's one more there.
Listen! Listen!
-Condom?
-Yes. In the drawer next to you.
-Should I put in on you?
-No.
I'll take it.
Okay.
-What happened?
-Nothing!
What happened?
Oh. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Found it!
-Answer it.
-It's alright.
-Who called?
-I don't know.
-Was it Natasha?
-No.
So what's happening now...
you and Neeraj sir...
It's over.
Over?
Did you have sex
with Natasha yet?
No.
Liar.
Why do you care?
-Don't I share my stories with you?
-Do I ask you to?
You yourself tell me.
You've made me your dustbin.
I'm just asking...
What's happening with Natasha?
Nothing.
Now that you and Neeraj
sir have broken up,
should we... again...
No?
Oh!
Did you come here to
Whatsapp or study?
Sorry, ma'am.
Give me your phone.
Type in your pass code.
Actually, I don't remember it.
Type the pass code.
See. I don't remember it.
Collect it from the office.
And get out of my class.
I said... get out of my class.
get out!
I am leaving.
Are you guys studying?
In the classroom,
You sit with Rahul, no?
In the cafeteria, with Aakash.
And here, with Tejas.
Your parents live in Dubai...
and they send you money, right?
Do you live alone in the flat?
How privileged?
What a waste.
I don't want to disturb you.
Please order.
Ma'am?
Why did you do that?
Why?
Is she your girlfriend?
No.
Oh!
Sorry.
Mihir, can you hear me?
No one is ever honest with
anyone, I'm telling you.
Even my mom and dad were
not honest with each other!
No sonofabitch in this
world is honest with anyone.
Inspite of the fact that Mihir
was with me, I was feeling guilty.
So then I thought,
let me explore that.
Let me explore the guilt.
Okay. I'm feeling guilty.
Why am I feeling guilty?
Where is the guilt coming from?
You know...
Point is...
if you want to love,
love selflessly.
You know...
they say that if you love
somebody, set it free.
Selfless.
Mihir loves me like that.
Nothing!
Where are you?
Hello.
Shh. No! No.
I know you are dating Natasha,
so you might as well tell me.
Where are you?
Huh! Huh!
Are you or aren't you?
Tell me! Are you or aren't you!
Answer!
-Go to sleep. Good night.
-Tell me...
He hung up on me?
That's what he
doesn't understand.
That communication is the key.
You know...
Mihir and I...
we're having a long
distance relationship.
But we tell each
other everything.
If anything happens, he calls
me up and tells me everything.
Whatever is happening to me now,
I'm going to tell him.
Something happened
between Tejas and me.
We shared something.
So we owe this
much to each other.
When something happened
between me and Neeraj...
I went myself and
told him about it.
When he did not even know
the meaning of fornication,
I told him.
Even when I got fed up,
I went and loyally told him.
So why?
I mean...
I'm just sitting here wondering
where he is all the time.
I don't want to do that.
Romanticism has never
been judged properly.
Who is there to judge it.
The critiques?
I am selfish.
I love Ayn Rand.
She said selfishness
is a virtue.
Of course, she said
it in another context.
But I feel it is...
applicable...
to my life. See,
I cannot be Mihir.
He is selflessly loving me.
In this context, he's selflessly
given me the freedom...
to explore my life. And...
if I'm doing that, I'm selfish.
So, yes. I am selfish, because
I have to be selfish to...
him being selfless towards me.
It is a gift.
That, be selfish.
Explore your own self. Uh...
why do I have a
problem with Natasha?
I don't have a
problem with Natasha.
She's just young.
But, uh, she's insignificant...
to me.
But Tejas lied to
me when I asked him
if you are having an
affair with her or not.
He lied to me.
That is my problem.
See, I am selfish.
I have expectations.
Do not lie to me.
I had a problem
because he lied to me.
He shouldn't have lied.
Because, I want honesty...
right now... and that
is my expectation.
Tejas!
Tejas?
He's inside.
Tejas!
Open the door!
Oh great lady!
Tejas.
Please open the door!
Are you listening?
-Grandma?
-Tejas.
Open the door!
You're here? Who is in there?
That crazy girl!
She just ran inside.
Open the door!
What's going on
between these two?
-Whose is this?
-I don't know.
Whose is this?
-I don't know!
-Is it Natasha's?
No.
I'm asking for the last time!
Is it hers?
Why should it be hers?
Why not? She may have
forgotten it here.
I don't know whose it is.
-Oh, you don't know!
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-I said I don't know!
I will hit you!
-Don't you know?
-No.
Don't you? Wait.
-Don't break that!
-Why not?
-It's expensive.
-How much is it?
Fifty five thousand rupees.
If it breaks, how can I
watch Raj Kapoor's movies?
I know you are
sleeping with her.
When I catch you red-handed,
one day, you'll know.
Move!
You like Boomerang very much?
Why do you kiss like a child?
You should have eaten her.
You lied to me and
dated her under my nose?
You flirt with her on
Whatsapp in my class.
You were dating and glued to
each other at the Comedy Club!
Do you think I don't know?
Did you play Raj Kapoor's
songs for her as well?
You played Raj Kapoor's
songs for her, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Don't make fun of me.
I didn't realize
you would be so hurt.
You don't know
girls like Natasha.
She is just using you!
Girls like Natasha do things
to show off to the world.
On Instagram, Twitter...
She wants to show-off that
I too have a boy friend.
She is using you like
an Instagram filter.
You are the filter today.
Tomorrow, it will be Rahul.
Don't laugh.
You should break up with her.
Do what you want.
Kalindi ma'am?
-I didn't realize you would be hurt.
-Why are you repeating yourself?
Really...
I didn't realize you
loved me so much.
I want to be with you.
-I will leave her for you.
-Have you lost it?
I'm married!
Please hand me a towel.
Not going to shower?
Dirty bitch!
Naked dog!
How are you, Sudha?
-All good?
-Yes.
Bless you. Bless you.
You look very pretty.
Amit said you are taking
good care of the house.
-There are fragile things in that.
-Okay.
Okay?
The house is very clean.
-Do you need anything?
-First, I will take a shower.
Take it.
It's so humid here!
-Sudha! Put the water heater on.
-Okay.
Listen, should I give her these?
-Give her one.
-Okay.
Keep this bag inside.
And, take this home.
Okay?
Come.
Close the left nostril and
inhale using the right nostril.
Now close the right nostril and
exhale using the left nostril.
Again, close the right nostril and
inhale through the left nostril.
Now close the left nostril...
Four terrorists killed in Bandipore
district of Jammu & Kashmir
while attempting to
attack a pilgrimage...
-And?
-Three.
I have entered the number.
Wait for the OTP.
I'll get it.
-Come in.
-Greetings.
-Greetings!
-Welcome.
-Greetings.
-Hi, dear. Come.
-Hello, auntyji.
-Hello.
-Hello...
-Did you find parking?
-No, no no...
Please sit.
-Please.
-Sit.
You guys are early.
People are always
late in Mumbai.
We left after the peak hours
and the roads were empty today.
We've been to this
neighbourhood before.
I see.
When you told me the
name of this building,
I didn't remember it..
But when we entered the gate...
I remembered that her
cousin used to live here.
Actually, my cousin's
wife's family.
-Sorry.
-I see.
-This is a good society.
-Absolutely.
Finding a flat in such a locality
in Mumbai, is a big thing.
He has this one-bedroom flat
because he's a bachelor.
Here 2 - 3BHK
flats are nice too.
I'm sure.
Yes.
Thing is, he comes
home just to sleep.
Look at the mess here.
I have asked him to hang
a painting at least.
I keep busy.
I am happy that he
got the house painted.
Nowadays, boys don't
bother about these things.
That they order food for
themselves, is an achievement.
I'm sorry. Will you
have tea or cold drinks?
Lemonade?
Ma'am...
-Some tea for us.
-Yes.
Has Ajit taken you on
a tour of Mumbai yet?
Sudha.
Make six cups of tea
and serve some snacks
in the new bowls.
I was posted here.
Oh! Where were you posted?
Dungarsi Road.
He has started with his stories!
We used to live
in the same area.
Just behind the Opera House.
We moved to Andheri
after we got married.
But Mumbai has changed a lot.
Everything has.
Even Meerut has changed so much.
It's so green now.
Mr. Manoj, your
area is nice too.
It's an old building but
there is greenery around.
Greenery is a luxury in Mumbai.
Like, they say... sea view...
tree view...
Similarly, we have tree views.
It's a good one!
You are a 'Jokey' man.
The word is 'Jovial'.
They are the same.
My sister-in-law's family
speaks highly of you.
Your brother-in-law is married
into that family, right?
They are the reason we are here.
-Do you come to Mumbai often?
-Not really.
Once a year.
But Ajit comes to
Meerut on festivals.
Whenever he gets a break.
Diwali must be
spectacular in Meerut!
-Absolutely! We get new outfits made.
-I see.
-We hold Lakshmi puja...
-We do that too.
And they play cards. It's a
cosmopolitan kind of Diwali!
We have a Ram Leela
performance there.
Ajit had played Ravana once!
He was Ravana!
-He forgot some lines!
-Oh!
He was so nervous.
We will be right back.
Let me show her the house.
-My small flat.
-Sure.
Go ahead.
Do you know?
People talk about it.
Aparna told me that
they have met twice.
Nowadays, things are
finalized at coffee shops.
-Marriages, business deals.
-Right.
Even divorces...
in coffee shops!
-Why are you talking
about divorce?
-Why not? It's a fact of life
We will not get divorced.
Oh, come on!
Never!
They are a good match.
Similar lifestyles and values.
The same profession. It's great.
-But mutual understanding is vital.
-Correct.
-If they want to be together...
-That is very important.
True.
We saw Aparna for the first
time at Mr. Pramod's funeral.
-Were you there?
-Yes.
He was close to us.
He loved Ajit dearly.
He was a good man.
He introduced us to the astrologer.
We really believe in him.
You have faith in him.
We showed him our horoscopes.
-He told us so many things!
-Wow! Here comes the tea!
Please come.
Did you add sugar? One more.
-Let him.
-He has diabetes.
They are a great match.
Their horoscopes are compatible.
Very good. Very good.
Serve them inside.
She makes very good tea.
It is very nice.
People prefer tea
bags these days.
Does she cook?
She does, but not too well.
And do you cook?
-Yes, but not non-veg dishes.
-Are you a vegetarian?
Yes, but Ajit is a carnivore.
So difficult to put
things across to him.
The guy has a small brain!
No, I mean...
#
I mean...
I know.
#
Um.. stop.
Stop?
Okay.
Thank you.
You... wanna share half?
Actually... I don't want this.
Put it there.
So, there's this high protein
diet you were talking about?
Ajit?
Yes.
You were talking about
some high protein diet.
Yeah.
-Mom, should we go?
-Did you show her the house?
What do you think?
Are you ready to
give up chicken?
Congratulations!
-Congratulations to you too!
-Congratulations.
I knew things would work out
today, so I got some sweets.
God bless you!
I will talk to my astrologer
and call you tomorrow.
-Yes, please.
-Definitely.
Ajit!
There is no need!
-We'll meet again.
-Sure.
-Congratulations once again.
-To you too.
-Keep in touch.
-Sure.
Call us, sometime. Okay.
Sudha, Ajit is going
to get married!
We will finalize the date soon.
Congratulations to you too!
Good people. Good family.
Please take some sweets home.
Only one elevator
is working, right?
It's a ten-minute
wait if we miss it.
I was just about to leave and
Ms. Neha gave me some work.
'Dust the painting...'
I did that yesterday. She
wanted me to do it again!
What should I do if someone
is renovating their home?
'Sweep the balcony, water
the plants...' Annoying.
Should I show you something?
Ms. Neha gave it to me.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Pure silk and fully embroidered.
I will fix it or
drape a scarf over it.
It will look perfect.
-Absolutely!
-Isn't it?
I will wear it on my
sister's wedding day.
With this, matching...
Don't know when she
will get married.
Wow!
You're not having one?
Your day also went well.
Help!
Why can't you swim?
My dad wasn't a Gymkhana member.
-How do I look now?
-Like a mother of two.
Tea!
Yes.
I don't look so fat, yaar.
As compared to?
A woman's heart is lighter?
But it beats faster.
There are eleven more differences.
Shall I tell you?
No, no.
The girls didn't even call
me once in the afternoon.
You must have put on
back to back movies?
Not bad, mister.
You are not going to
accept, matashreeji?
We'll live, okay?
Yes. Speak...
Am I disturbing you?
Speak...
Where are you?
I...
Hey Sudhir, where
the hell are you?
I... at the beach house.
I'm coming over.
Salman, where are
you speaking from?
I'm coming.
Now?
We decided that you will
come after the house-warming!
Did you send me an email?
What about?
Salman, bank details,
my black money
my Swiss account numbers,
you know it, yaar.
Where all I stole money from,
I'm sending all
details in an email.
-I will introduce you to Hardik.
-Who is Hardik?
Hardik, my lawyer, yaar.
Salman, what will I
speak with your lawyer?
I'm not getting you.
-Why are you laughing?
-That is the problem, yaar.
Nobody gets me bro.
What I'm saying is...
you will take care of Ankita
and Tapishree after I am gone.
What do you mean,
after you're gone?
Forget it, Sudhir!
Salman!
After I'm gone, you will take
care of Ankita and Tapishree.
Where are you going?
Where are you now?
#
On my balcony, drinking.
I had asked for single malt,
but there is no one in
the house to give me ice.
Where are the girls?
Where are Tapishree and Ankita.
Watching a movie with Rosemary,
I guess. I don't know.
Did they have dinner?
How the hell do I know?
Why don't you ask their mother?
The girls could be starving!
Where is the mother?
Who is she with?
And why is her location
service disabled?
-What are you talking about?
-Sudhir...
Sudhir, Reena is bored of me.
She's looking for excitement.
She's with somebody exciting.
-Got it?
-Salman...
Salman, are you serious?
Am I laughing, Sudhir?
What are you saying. Are
you listening to yourself!
You know what she said to me?
In 13 years of our marriage,
she was happy for
only 11 months.
You want proof?
What? What are you doing?
Sudhir, I want you to be
witness to this moment.
Salman? What are you doing?
I'm calling her. I bet, she
will not answer my call.
-Salman, stop the drama.
-Sudhir, listen... listen to this.
Listen...
See, she's not
picking the phone.
-Salman.
-She will not take the call!
You can bet anything.
Now imagine, what if
I was in an accident?
And I'm dying.
Salman, you've gone mad!
I'm dying Sudhir, listen to me.
I'm calling ICE. 'In case
of Emergency'... my wife.
Let the boring husband die!
Are you listening?
Husband is dying.
There's blood everywhere.
Anyway, enjoy your beach life.
Love you darling. See you. Bye.
You think... he...
Call.
Call him. Find out what's wrong.
Nothing is wrong.
He is pretending.
Reena, he's in the balcony.
He's drinking.
Call him.
Don't tell him I asked you to.
What is it, Salman?
Now what?
Where are you?
You can call Sudhir
up but not me.
He is my buddy.
I have every right!
Where are you?
I'm at Geeta's.
Have you gone nuts?
Assume I have... for a moment.
Tell me this.
When I call Geeta,
why does she tell me...
'I don't know what's going
on between Reena and you?
but Reena is not here.'
Why did she say that?
Reena.
-What?
-Shh.
He knows.
He's spying.
#
He's spying on me.
How?
Geeta told him that
I'm not with her.
-What else has she told him?
-Bitch.
How would I know
what she said to him?
#
I have no idea.
We don't send each other
messages or emails!
We meet once in a while.
Is he following us?
No. He is not.
Otherwise, why
would he call Geeta.
Geeta knows?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
She would have confronted me.
What did you tell Geeta?
I texted her that I was going on
a tour with my HSBC colleague.
#
Because I feel ashamed.
What have I become?
My children are hungry and
my husband is spying on me.
God! The bitch.
Not Geeta, I'm the bitch.
Tell him you are here.
Call him and tell him you
are here to talk to me.
What about?
About your fights.
Okay?
End this Geeta chapter now
or you'll be caught in a lie.
Call him and tell him that you
came to me for advice.
You hung up on me?
Salman, are you spying on me?
Where are you?
-At Sudhir's.
-At Sudhir's?
-At his beach house.
-Beach house?
He's not yet done
the house-warming.
What are you doing there?
-I needed to talk.
-About what?
About us...
Our daily fights.
You're talking to
Sudhir about us?
What's wrong with you?
Salman, I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
Do I go to him and rat on you?
In 12 years of our marriage,
I didn't bore you for 10 months.
Do you know why?
#
He just saw me crying, okay?
-Alright.
-Crying? Where?
In a party.
Which party?
At the Kishore Thadani
one, last week?
Yes.
Reena, Kishore came to our house
and you were doing
drama in front of him?
Drama?
What else?
Kishore Thadani of
Sunrise Capital!
You know him.
He's going to invest 200 crore
rupees in my company!
12 years as a banker and
you have learned nothing!
You know what Kishore
Thaddani means to me?
Of course, I know what
he means to you.
To me? To all of us.
#
Ankita and Tapishree's
education.
Dad's 10 crore rupees
loan and the debt!
Salman, who's doing drama?
What drama?
You or I?
Dad's loan is 2 crores.
Not 10 crores.
Listen, listen. You are
not doing this for us.
You are doing this for yourself.
Sudhir...
#
Me... Kishore... beach house...
you are collecting trophies!
It's all about you, Salman.
Anyways. I'm coming home.
What if I don't?
What?
You said I like to
collect trophies.
What will you do if I
stop collecting them?
I will live my life.
Oh, life?
What is your life about?
Branch Manager, MG Road!
Tell me. What is your life?
Your life is that, Reena...
what I permit it to be.
Is there any other life?
Permit?
Yes.
Tell me. What kind of life
will you have without me?
I'm allowing you... your life?
So there.
please don't lecture.
The girls are hungry. Come home.
Please come home.
Hello.
That's enough.
Come back home.
Reena?
You're dropping me?
Sudhir,
should we tell Salman?
About what?
About us.
You... me.
Reena, start working again.
Half of your problems
will be solved.
What about the remaining 50 percent?
Salman also said the same thing.
I'm giving you 60 percent freedom.
So, what is your problem?
Let's tell him about
it and make it simple.
What's so complex here?
-It's not?
-This is life.
This is an allowance.
You know Salman.
-He talks and forgets about it.
-I don't.
I don't forget.
Anyway...
He will be here soon.
-What?
-I told him to come over.
Who did you call?
You should have told me.
How could you do this?
You've no right, okay?
Is this not about me as well?
-Get dressed!
-I am dressed!
He wasn't supposed to come
here before the house-warming!
Why are you laughing?
Get dressed!
Wear these shoes.
Why should I?
You always wear them at home.
-But here I take them off.
-I don't want him to notice.
Reena...
What has Salman got to
do with our relationship?
Stop being childish!
I knew that you had a
crush on me in college.
Did you ever talk to me?
If Salman didn't make a
scene at Jamshed's party,
would you have dropped me off?
If I wasn't Salman's wife...
would you have kissed me
Do you believe that
if we tell Salman,
we can meet again?
Sudhir,
if he learns the truth...
would he want to be
in this marriage?
Our marriage will end.
Ankita and Tapishree...
have you thought about them?
Whenever I talk to you,
why do the kids always come in?
-Do you feel it is wrong?
-Yes. It is wrong.
They will be raised as children
of divorced parents are.
What?
Sudhir, I'm tired.
I cannot take this anymore.
If you want a divorce,
what is the point
in telling Salman?
If Salman sees us together
after our divorce...
how would he feel?
Us...
us together?
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Forward the email.
Yeah. Cool.
Yes.
It's 12 in the afternoon in New York.
So just call them up.
Okay.
Forward the email to me.
Alright?
Okay then. Bye.
Nice room.
Nice house.
#
Very nice.
Actually, there were
many colours earlier.
I repainted the walls to off-white.
The contractor's dog died.
So the work stalled.
It looks empty, doesn't it?
Empty is good!
We all need space.
Get me a house like this.
Yours is better, pal!
But it should be only mine...
I have no voice there.
Even this house
belonged to a couple.
My wife looks pretty
in your house.
How much did it cost you?
Not much.
It belonged to a couple.
I got it in a distress
sale at the separation.
What does Kishore
Thadani have to say?
He's your friend.
You tell me if he is serious or not.
He is. Keep at it.
She is up to something.
I know it.
Salman, you provoke her.
-I provoke her?
You just know her version.
-You have not heard my version.
-Did you tell Reena?
I had no chance.
She'll give back a bouncer.
'I gave up my career
for you and the kids!
I could have been
anything I wanted!'
Could've been queen, could've
been Chanda Kochchar'.
Could've been Kareena Kapoor,
could've been Mary Kom!'
No matter what, you...
You must not use the word
'allowance' with her.
But why did she lie to me that
she is going to Geeta's house...
So what? She is Reena!
Don't you understand?
'Ice Doll', they used
to call her in college.
No one had the balls
to stand before her.
You were the only one
who talked to her.
Handling marriage issues
is not my cup of tea.
So, I'm telling you...
talk to her lovingly
and take her home.
You also got married,
knowing this.
Don't you know?
You never told me.
After my marriage,
your mom sent me
the invitation card.
I ate veg biryani
at your wedding.
You went away for a year
and then you called
me and said that you
signed papers in the court.
It has been ten years now!
Forget it.
Think about yourself.
Sometimes I feel like...
What did she say to you?
'She doesn't want
to live with me.'
Should I divorce her?
Salman, have you lost it?
I know.
I know, man. I know.
I don't know. I don't know.
Listen.
You will never find a
better package than Reena.
I know.
As a wife, mother, hostess...
I know that.
I know Sudhir. Two kids,
one after the other...
Right?
Yes.
Yes, you do.
-You'll be finished without her.
-But...
Kishore Thadani had come home.
She was crying in front of him?
When did Reena cry in
front of Kishore Thaddani?
You were there!
He's going to invest 200
crores in my company...
And you're crying
in front of him?
How could she?
I'm coming.
Shall we watch a movie tonight... action.
What do you think, Reena?
Sure. We can go to a night show.
It's only a suggestion.
You only suggest the
things you want to do.
The other day you took me to
a movie that you had seen.
I was bored.
But I tolerated two
hours if that movie.
You had decided beforehand
that you will not like it.
Who decided this?
A movie should entertain.
Or it should have a message
of patriotism or love.
You like to leave things
open-ended, and I, black and white.
What's wrong in that?
Salman. Finish your food.
I'm tired!
Actually, both of you are tired.
Eat well. Go home and rest.
Am I an idiot?
I drove all the way here.
You have all the wisdom
and I'm an idiot.
Pure idiot. I am the idiot.
-Why do you keep repeating it?.
-I will say it ten times
Why? Are you Girish...
Remember that guy? He would
repeat everything three times?
-Yes.
He was such an item.
Half fry! Half fry! Half fry!
The waiter got three half fries.
What would he say?
Thapar is going to...
#
-Where is he now?
-He's in Dallas.
He sold his start-up and
is living it up there.
Lucky guy.
Let's plan a reunion.
Start a group.
Good old days.
Those were the days!
Drink coffee and the movies!
Memories, memories, man.
Reena, this guy introduced
me to black coffee.
-I was broke. He took care of me.
-Sudhir...
Can Salman and I talk?
-Here or...
-Yes.
-Is it comfortable here?
-It is comfortable, Sudhir.
Babe, can you just
pass me the water?
Actually, he is right.
Enough of this. Wash your hands.
Let's go home.
Heart Matters. Your
YouTube channel.
Super successful...
But how...
I always wanted to
be an IAS officer.
My father taught in
a Government school.
My initial studies were
in a Government school.
Maybe, that is why my
English accent is...
You hate me?
No.
So you love me?
It's not that simple.
I get irritated with you.
What about?
What did I say?
I feel a strange tightness
in my head, day and night.
You feel a tightness
in your head?
Tell me in one line.
What's the problem?
You need a mother, not a wife.
I can't do it.
Sudhir saw me crying, not
at Kishore Thaddani's party...
but at Jamshed's party.
Sudhir and I
have been together
for three years.
Sudhir Batra? Indiabulls?
My father suffered a
heart attack, and...
We could not afford the treatment.
He passed away.
I think, that was when I
decided to be a heart surgeon.
And...
So, greatness started
with a tragedy.
Let me tell our viewers...
Dr. Sinha is the only cardiologist...
Sudhir?
It is a reversible process.
Take care of it and
you will be fine.
If there are any technical
flaws, we are there to mend them.
But my focus has
has been more on...
Salman wants to talk.
Kishore sent a text.
'Hi Salman.'
'Just finished with the team.
We are going ahead.'
'Option 1. 130 crores, 1st stage...'
'Congrats buddy. Take
good care of my money.'
'Smiley. Let's catch up tomorrow.' Kishore
Congrats, friend.
Reena...
It's good news.
Yes.
#
Great.
But boss...
I'm exhausted.
Don't go. Sleep here.
#
I'll show you the bedroom.
Yeah. I think that's the best option.
What are the plans for Saturday?
You tell me.
Golf?
Okay. Ranjeet was saying,
let's have lunch in
the club after that.
Is he back?
Yes.
How is he doing?
Happy.
Single now.
His profile on Tinder says...
I love adventure sports.
It is another matter, that he
can't even catch a Frisbee.
Shit! I am getting late.
-Salman.
-Thadani's team is visiting today.
I left my sunglasses inside.
Sudhir.
-Sudhir...
-Not now.
We will talk later.
Will I see you again?
Salman knows.
He told me two things.
This must stop.
And he said...
you should not know...
that he knows.
-Did you say anything to him?
-No.
What did I say that
day, at Jamshed's party?
Nothing.
-So you guys were...
-He called me two days later.
I didn't answer it.
Then I called him
back after a week.
Had we fought again?
No.
It was a peaceful day.
Libertina! The fish fry
was outstanding!
Ms. Rekha...
Principal sir...
Is all okay at the library?
It was dusty. I got it cleaned.
-On the books?
-On the fans, sir...
Who reads books these days?
The library is always empty.
If you get bored, come to
my office for a cup of tea.
I have invited
you several times.
I have also told you several times sir.
I don't drink tea.
Is that all?
That's it.
Thank you, sir.
The principal ogles
at me so hard,
his eyes will pop out one day.
So, Meghaji...
Are you happy...
or suffering?
-Ma'am, I can't do it.
-I know.
Come here. Let me do it.
Not every soldier is
capable of firing a bullet.
Ask me.
I am experienced
in such battles.
And now, my dear...
are ready for battle.
Is it too revealing?
I wish it was.
Rekha ma'am. You are too much!
Go! You'll be late!
Good luck, soldier!
Megha Verma?
Yes?
This is my daughter, Sanditi.
Sorry, I'm late for the meeting.
She never told me about it.
No worries. She is an excellent student!
I have no complaints.
But I have some.
Thank God I checked her phone!
Or I would not have known.
Look what she is up to! Look!
-She's eating ice cream.
-I am eating ice cream.
What happened?
Did you not like the flavour?
What is the advantage of sending
her to an all-girls school...
If she is dancing
around with mad boys?
And... she is sending
it by telegram.
It's Instagram, Mom!
Ma'am,
when both school children
participate in debates together,
friendship happens.
Please, Ms. Rekha!
If we let you mind our children,
our culture will be washed out.
You have made
detergents of teachers.
One minute! One minute!
Can you do something
about her school dress?
When she leaves the
house in the morning,
her skirt is in Lucknow.
Slowly it shortens
to reach Kanpur.
Why do you not ask them to
wear salwar-kameez instead?
It will keep their legs covered.
-Sorry for being late, Paras.
-Don't worry. No problem!
I was hanging out
with my friend.
Google.
So... how's you?
Fine.
Should we make small
talk or get to the point?
I've just come.
Let's make some small
talk to start with.
Correct.
It is not cold enough
to use a shawl now.
I feel the cold
more that others.
You are sweating. You can take
off the shawl. No problem.
You can keep it on, if you like.
I'm good.
See...
this is our third meeting...
that too, without our families.
So I want to speak openly.
Yes. Sure.
I'm a shy boy.
I have never asked a
girl for her number.
-No, I did when I took her sari.
-What!
I spilled my Cola on
here in the train.
So, I kept her sari with me.
-You took her sari off on the train?
-Yes!
No, I mean...
The next day, I took
it to get it washed.
I see.
But the Cola stains
are stubborn.
Can I ask you something?
Of course!
Did the Cola spill accidentally,
or did you spill
it intentionally?
Please, Meghaji...
I studied in an all-boys school.
I don't have such courage.
Why? I have heard that
all-boys school students
often treat all-girls school
students to ice creams.
What!
You are smart, Megha.
I know now.
You are trying to
distract me again,
but it won't work this time.
Shall we get to the point?
-No.
-Why not, Megha?
He's a such a good boy!
He has a good job!
He has good values.
He is respectable
and respectful.
Ma, he is a little dark skinned,
but you'll balance that out.
So when everything is
good, what is your problem?
I cannot tell the difference
between good and bad guys.
What do you mean?
You made me study,
not in a coed school,
but an all girls school.
You gave me, neither
freedom, nor an allowance.
Also, I wasn't brave enough,
to hang around with
boys from other schools
and speak with them
or make them buy me ice creams.
That is why I am saying...
get married.
You can have as much
ice cream as you want.
Paras. You made it!
-Who are you searching for?
Normally, friends
show up to play prank.
No one came.
Please come in.
They must have got
drunk and gone home.
-Come on.
-What!
Have a seat.
Sit.
If you could be an animal,
which one would
you prefer to be?
What kind of a question is that?
At work also, we ask
such silly questions.
People enjoy it.
So tell me.
Animal?
A cat.
A cat!
They have nine lives.
Seven lives with me...
and two extra!
Meow!
Okay, you tell me, what
would you prefer to be?
A crocodile.
The sleeping devil.
If he wakes up, he will bite!
Do you know anything
about crocodiles?
No.
I have watched Nat Geo a lot.
The male crocodile blows bubbles
in the water with his breath.
Really!
Why?
To attract the female!
To excite them.
-Do you want some water?
-I'm fine!
Okay, I'll have some.
Congratulations.
Are you drying your hair?
Are you drying clothes?
Are you chopping tomatoes?
No.
If aunties in the colony are
happy, Mom is also happy.
Look, child...
I will be happy
when you deliver two children
quickly, one after one.
Oh, Ma! You do not lose any
opportunity to mention this.
Keep quiet.
This is a discussion
between women.
-What do you say?
-Right.
Okay. You ladies talk, we are
going to go get some air.
Excuse me.
Megha...
listen to us.
Look at my elder
daughter-in-law, Sandhya.
She looks so happy.
She delivered two kids,
one after the other.
She spends all her time
looking after them.
She does not need to
work hard anymore.
Hard work?
Yes, my dear, this is hard work.
Look,
your mother-in-law
squawks all day
and the bed squeaks all night.
Once you have two kids,
all your time will be spent
with their squaks and squeaks.
When desires are fulfilled,
toil will end.
What if desires
are not fulfilled?
How is that possible?
Tell me something,
can a woman desire
anything more than a child?
No.
See.
So...
this is why teacher madam is
upset since morning. I noticed...
you were upset
with what ma said.
Don't listen to ma. We will
have a kids when we have them.
We must make love now.
Lots of love.
You are enjoying
married life a lot.
You are always excited!
Hey!
You are also enjoying very much.
I noticed, understand?
You are happy, too.
Have you ever watched
an adult film?
What?
Adult film?
Have you seen?
Yes.
Back in school... college.
Even till last month... Why?
When the guy says...
Oh baby!
And the girl says...
Oh yeah!
They have a good time together.
Together.
Yes!
I have never understood that!
You either have sex or talk!
Or sit down, relax
and talk or have sex.
What this 'doing
both together' is,
I have never been
able to understand
See, also at work in the office,
I either check the accounts
or type on the computer.
I do not have this funda
of doing both together.
It feels stupid.
Look! Birds!
Take these birds for example.
They either lay eggs or fly.
Have you seen a
flying bird lay eggs?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Megha, the Principal
has called you.
Go.
All the best.
Principal sir, please
tell me what I should do.
Such books are issued
in this school?
What were you thinking
when you issued such books?
-Ma'am, I did not issue the book...
-Hold on.
She did not issue the book.
It was issued by our
librarian, Rekha ma'am.
Oh! I understand now!
She is a divorcee. What
can teach our children?
What is there in this book.
Let me take a look at it.
I see.
What is the story?
-I have not read it, sir.
-Lolita!
Read it and you will understand.
It is about a relationship
between a father and daughter.
So you have read it.
No!
Why should I read
such strange stories of father
and daughter relationships?
She and her father
have read it.
-Call Rekha ma'am, please.
-Okay.
Jaswant!
Yes sir?
Ask Rekha m'am to
come here immediately.
Okay.
Lolita!
Light of my life!
Fire of my loins!
Spelling mistake.
Ma'am, this book
is about animals.
Who knows what is written?
I will correct it.
Where is Rekha ma'am?
Let me find out.
Lion. L-I-O-N.
Nobody has died. All is well.
Why in the library?
I had two fantasies.
Let me tell you.
In a locked airplane toilet...
and the other, in the midst
of books in a library.
That is why I thought,
let me fulfil one fantasy.
Men are selfish.
They cannot make a woman happy.
We have to do it ourselves.
And this useless principal...
took away my happiness
and my husband as well.
Husband?
Yes. It can be
called my husband.
It's always with
me, day and night.
It does not talk.
and keeps me happy.
Can I get a better husband?
Anyway, enough for today.
Shall I go?
What happened?
It's Sunday.
Hello, Grandma.
-Have you seen the TV remote?
-No.
Where is it?
Megha!
Oh shit!
Megha! Come soon. What
has happened to Paras.
Sandhya! Get the First Aid kit!
-Hurry up!
-Does it hurt?
Paras!
-Come Megha. Sit beside me.
-What happened, Paras.
Are you all right?
Forget about her! Tell
me how did you get hurt?
It was my fault, Mom!
I do not know why I felt
that Megha needed me.
I immediately left the office,
took a rickshaw and told
the driver to hurry.
And the driver
drove at full speed
and we collided with a bull.
And the saying came true.
Come bull. Hit me.
I do not know about the bull,
but the rickshaw
toppled, and I fell.
I lost consciousness
for a minute.
As they say 'All people
seek light in the dark'
but I was searching for Megha.
Megha.
Why are you sitting
and looking at him!
Go get him a glass of water!
Go! Look over here.
Why did I not see this before?
-Nothing will happen.
-Just blow on it gently!
Why is this not working?
-Sister, please listen to me...
-Not at all!
Please tell us.
Why should we accept her.
To save your respect...
we'll tell our relatives...
that your daughter...
is epileptic.
Sister,
how can this
marriage break apart?
-I beg you...
-Ma. There is no need to do all this.
Look Sister...
In this family,
we do not want a child from
her womb, in this family.
Ma... enough now.
This is between us.
If it happened in the bedroom,
it was between you both.
But, because it
happened in the open,
it's a family matter!
I have heard enough!
And if you care so much for her,
you also stay here. Understand?
Goodbye.
-Sister, please listen.
-I don't want to listen to anything.
Please listen to me. Sister!
-Sorry, I am late.
-No, no! Sit down.
I always arrive early.
It was the Annual Day at school.
How was it?
Shall we get to the point?
Megha.
Let's forget what happened.
Let's make a new start.
I apologize for what my mom did.
But I cannot divorce you.
-Whatever wrong happened...
-Paras!
I didn't do wrong.
What happened was not wrong.
Where it happened..
I apologize.
Women desire more
than just children.
So,
what have you decided?
What do you want to do?
I don't know what I want to do.
But for now,
I want some ice cream.