[theme music playing]
[theme music concludes]
[family laughing]
[Cheeku] Babi, when we used
to go to shopping,
he would look at the embroidery
instead of the clothes.
He still does it.
[Cheeku] Actually, he thought
he could impress girls with that.
-Look at her.
-[all laugh]
This is too much. [chuckles]
-[Dabbu] Aha! Samosas.
-[upbeat instrumental music playing]
Wow. Looks good.
Arrey, if you do all this,
then I won't
let you both get married.
Arrey, his hands work too.
He can serve himself.
If you start serving him now,
then he will boss you around forever.
[chuckles]
-Arrey yaar. Cheeku?
-[Cheeku] Yes?
-I will help myself.
-Where is Maji?
She'll be here soon.
You know, two hours after sunrise
and two hours before sunset,
even if someone dies,
Maji won't stop her Maataji's prayers.
[all laugh]
Don't say that.
Move away from the samosas.
Put it down. Give it. Leave the samosa.
Uh…
-[sighs] Give it to me.
-That's for you.
You made them, Veda?
[retches]
Did you put sugar in it?
Not sugar, Dadi. I've put sweet potato.
-Hmm.
-It's healthy. You can eat them.
If I can't even eat them,
how will they be good for my health?
Do you hate potatoes, huh?
We don't hate them, Dadi, really.
Anyone who eats potatoes
ends up becoming one.
[all laugh]
They are made for each other.
Arrey, even as a kid, he used to take
the potatoes out of his parathas
and just eat them plain.
By the way, why this new generation
is so obsessed with fitness,
-I just don't understand.
-Ma.
Not only anti-potato.
I guess these two have a lot in common.
Yeah, I mean, three months of talking
and walking together is paying off.
[laughs]
[Cheeku] Babiji, we can never know
what the universe has planned
for all of us.
It's crazy how Dabbu and I
saw each other after 12 years,
and then he convinced me
to come to your place for some chai,
and before we could even finish our chai,
Arjun came home.
Who knew that, instead of vegetables,
I would bring an in-law?
Here I was matching their horoscopes
and they were both busy finding out
every little thing about each other.
Sufi songs, Chinese food,
traveling the world, going on treks,
becoming CEOs. [chuckles]
All the same things.
-Mama, stop it, please.
-Arrey, why stop it?
What's wrong with talking
-about things with the family?
-[Dabbu] Mm!
You know, I really think
that you two are so lucky, that…
you are so compatible together.
[Rina] You better say yes soon, bhaisaab.
If our boy grabs your dear daughter
and runs off with her in a Rajdhani,
then please don't complain to us.
Arrey, I think we should
let them run away.
We will save some money.
[all laugh]
Excuse me, Baba?
-Uh, sorry.
-Have you had sex?
[music fades]
[clock ticking]
Have you done it?
-Tell me.
-Hmm?
Mom!
What is this nonsense?
The reason you were born
is because of this nonsense.
-You all are nonsensical.
-Dadi…
Veda, we are talking
about marriage here, so I asked.
Before you even buy a small car,
you test drive it, right?
[music resumes]
Yeah.
So no test drive before marriage?
[Dadi] This is marriage, beta.
This is what will drive your entire life.
Sorry.
Maji, I think
you're not feeling well. Come.
[Rina] No, no, let her speak.
-Do you think our son can't do it?
-Yes.
-Cheeku, yaar, what is this?
-I'm… I'm…
-Dadi, we are getting married.
-That's why I said all this.
[music concludes]
And you all should also wonder
about my granddaughter.
Forget about us.
They both should wonder
if they are compatible or not
-inside the bedroom.
-[chuckles]
It's really good.
It's really good that they both like
Chinese food, very good.
But for how long will noodles
keep them together?
After working hard to reach
the position of CEO,
what will make them
want each other at home?
To listen to Sufi music?
Or to plan their trekking trip?
[clicks tongue]
No.
Even if their horoscopes
don't match perfectly,
if the sex is satisfying,
then they both will never,
ever leave each other.
[grunts]
[Dadi chanting]
[chants]
[tense music playing]
[train rumbling]
[insects chirping]
[Veda] Dadi…
[Dadi] Hmm. Come, come.
[grunts]
-[Veda] Sorry, did I wake you up?
-No, no, I was just lying down. Come here.
You are so funny, Dadi.
-[chuckles]
-No, no.
I wasn't joking.
Dadi! Like a nuclear attack happened.
You know, one blast rocked two homes.
Forget about Mom and Dad,
poor Dabbu Uncle and Rina Auntie…
You should have seen their faces!
Yes, poor them…
Here.
That's the problem with the world.
-All think poorly.
-[Veda] Hmm.
How is Arjun?
He's fine. He's cool.
He just couldn't stop…
[chuckles] …laughing about it.
Not reaction, Veda.
I'm asking about action.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Veda laughs]
-How's he?
-I'll… I'll find out and let you know.
-Hurry.
Hurry? What's the hurry, Dadi?
So…
you're not in a hurry?
[sighs] This means you both
are not made for each other.
Everything is not about sex, okay?
And I am--
I'm not that inexperienced.
I know. I… I have had boyfriends.
[breathes deeply]
But…
marriage is something else only.
What I'm actually saying to you,
that you should marry the person
with whom the sex is good.
Rather what I want to say is the person
you finally marry…
make sure…
the sex is amazing with him.
[laughs] Fine. Understood!
Understood. But…
why didn't I see
this side of you before?
Dadi, you are so passionate,
you are so sexy.
You're such a rock star, Dadi.
If your dadu hadn't died at such
a young age, you know,
this door would still be locked
from the inside at night.
Wow!
I mean, he was that good?
Not just that he was good, we were good.
[laughs]
Open this. Open the small drawer.
It's the last packet.
Dadi, this…
Even if the chances are low, why take one?
I always kept some here.
Or else, who knows,
maybe you would have grown up
with your little uncle.
Hey, let it be, leave it.
It's expired already,
like your grandfather.
Tell me one thing. Come.
[Dadi grunts]
-You had an arranged marriage, right?
-Yes.
So how did you know
that you both would be compatible?
It was an arranged marriage
for the people who were arranging it,
-no?
-[Veda] Hm.
We went near the river…
[soft romantic music playing]
[Dadi] …the sugarcane fields,
a bogie in the railway yard,
and so many other places
to check our compatibility.
It's so easy… [grunts]
…for you guys these days, right? Huh?
-You can do it.
-[chuckling] D-- Dadi, come on!
-[Dadi] You can do it.
-Dadi, I'm going.
[chuckling] You are so sexy!
["Khelo Khellum" playing]
[Dadi] Good morning, beta.
[male singer vocalizing]
[singing in Hindi]
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Play the game
The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul
Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Let candles of desire ♪
♪ Light up nights in your heart ♪
♪ As creases smile at your sight ♪
♪ Marvel at this maddening delight ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
[all in English] Cheers!
[laughs]
[female singer vocalizing]
-[song ends abruptly]
-[insects chirping]
[Suchi] I'm getting worried now.
We don't have much time.
[Cheeku]
The date is set, it will be all right.
[Dadi] Where did you go, huh?
Arrey, thank God!
That even after everything you said,
Dabbu and my friendship is still alive.
Twenty-eighth of next month
is good date for the wedding.
Everything needs to be good
before the wedding.
Arrey. Mom, have you lost it?
You try to reason with her.
Hey.
Let me tell you, this wedding won't happen
-till Veda and Arjun--
-Hey, Bhagavan!
[tense music playing]
What do you want?
Before every relationship,
she should test every guy?
Chee!
What chee? Huh?
What chee?
I don't want to make
the same mistake again.
Because of your habit
of saying "chee-chee" to these things,
today, Suchi's life has become like this.
What is wrong with my life now?
[scoffs] It's over.
It died right after your marriage.
But I'm happy, Maji.
[scoffs]
One who has not felt happiness for years,
how would she know what happiness means?
When was the last time
you two slept together?
-Ma!
-[shushes]
Don't shout.
Just giving birth to a child
does not prove
that you have a good sex life.
I'm not saying
that there is a problem with you or her.
The problem is your relationship.
You have just turned 52 and she is 48.
Before starting new relationships,
fire up the old ones.
I should have told you both about all this
when her parents
first came to us with the proposal.
[somber music playing]
It's already 1:00 at night
and Veda isn't home yet. [sobs]
[Dabbu] Arjun hasn't come home yet either.
That was a farewell party,
so maybe Veda also went along with him.
Or maybe they went to clear
your maji's doubt.
[laughs] What say?
Yaar, that is your son,
and she is my daughter.
You shouldn't joke
about these things, Dabbu.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, just-- just--
sorry, sorry, sorry.
[rings]
[female voice vocalizing]
-[Dadi] How was it, girl?
-What?
[grunts]
I left God and came here for you.
How was it?
[female voice vocalizing]
[Veda] Dadi… Nice.
"Nice" are those biscuits
with sugar on top.
No, no, no, no, no, we are-- we are--
we are-- We're good. We're good.
We're good.
Did Mount Fuji happen?
What?
It was your dadu's code word.
He used to ask me every time.
You know our bodies,
they are like volcanoes like Mount Fuji.
We are fully satisfied
only when it erupts.
-[laughing]
-[soft music playing]
Mount Fuji.
Dadi.
I really didn't know
you were so wild inside. My God.
I mean, why do you hide this
and we only see you praying all the time?
Praying keeps the mind clear, you know?
Did it erupt?
-It… It did.
-For both?
Hmm.
Dadi, you're just so embarrassing yaar.
This is very embarrassing, Dadi.
Embarrassing is better than depressing.
Okay.
Uh…
Dadi, it was the first time, you know,
and you know guys, they erupt first.
Maybe I'm just too hot for them, you know?
-Too hot.
-Is Arjun not hot enough?
No, he's… he's… he's so hot.
I mean, he's so gorgeous.
Maybe I was tensed.
Performance pressure, na?
And thanks to you, you were in my head,
sitting on the bed.
God!
You know what, Dadi? Um…
I'm happy. I'm good.
It's unnecessary for Mount Fuji
to erupt every time.
It's not you. I'm worried for Arjun.
He is sensitive.
He is not like most other men
who just turn around and sleep,
even if their partners
are left unsatisfied.
He will think it's his fault.
How will he know that I wasn't satisfied?
He thinks I… erupted.
[female voice vocalizing]
[clears throat] Then…
Then your marriage
will definitely be very sad.
[female voice vocalizing]
[sighs]
["Khelo Khellum" playing]
[male singer in Hindi]
♪ Those who seek pearls must dive deep ♪
♪ With drowsy eyes deprived of sleep ♪
♪ Don't stop rowing, says the boat ♪
♪ Keep swimming, stay afloat ♪
♪ Lose all your senses
Let the sun rise in the west ♪
♪ Lose your way
And set in the east ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Let candles of desire ♪
♪ Light up nights in your heart ♪
♪ As creases smile at your sight ♪
♪ Marvel at this maddening delight ♪
[song concludes]
[in English] Come.
What do I say?
Um, that you're here to have tea. Come!
[chanting indistinctly]
Dadi.
Where are you going?
[Veda] Uh, Dadi,
I didn't want to disturb you.
It is not possible to disturb the one
who is already very disturbed.
Uh…
Dadi…
[resumes chanting indistinctly]
[chuckles]
We…
Dadi, we are fi-- fine.
Dadi, we are fully on.
[continues chanting]
We, uh… Dadi, we both…
Everything is great.
[continues chanting]
Dadi…
Dadi, we are in love.
[continues chanting]
Dadi, if you--
Dadi, if you don't wanna
listen to us, then we'll just go.
We…
[chants indistinctly]
We left a 23,000-rupee
suite room to come and talk to you.
Why are you wasting our time, Dadi?
-[chuckles] That… that…
-[soft music playing]
That's all I wanted to hear.
Waste of time. Eh?
Now that you feel
that this is a waste of time
means you were enjoying
doing something so much
that you want to waste
all your precious time doing it.
-Hmm?
-[both chuckle]
I pray to God
that you both always feel this passion.
Look at him. He's blushing so much.
If you would have heard
what all Dadi said to me,
you would have lost it completely!
He's blushing like a squishy tomato.
I just wanna…
Dadi, she fights a lot.
I don't think this relationship
will last more than a year.
Oh! Ouch!
Which hotel were you at?
-Do you have a boyfriend?
-Shh, not so loud.
Or else he will come
at night to haunt me.
[clears throat]
If the bond is strong, you'll be able
to handle each other for years.
Don't ever let this bond get weak.
Don't let it get boring, hmm?
Uh, what do they call people
who take drugs?
-Junkie?
-Oh, no, no, no.
Junkie.
-They're called something else.
-Addict?
-Yes, yes.
-Addict.
You two should be
absolutely addicted to each other.
They'll pull you.
A lot of things will pull you away.
But if the sex between you is great,
then you won't be able to stay away.
The chances are very low.
Even if you grow apart, those memories,
you know, will definitely
bring you back to each other.
Sex is important for love.
-Hmm?
-[female singer vocalizing]
Where are you going for the honeymoon?
Dadi, do we even need a honeymoon?
I do. For you.
Look. [clears throat]
The wedding night's Fuji.
[upbeat music playing]
-Don't laugh, listen carefully.
-Hmm.
The wedding night's Fuji
is more special than any other Fuji
which may have erupted
before or after marriage.
Until that Fuji happens,
the two of you are not going
to step outside this room.
-[laughs] Hey. Wha--
-[music concludes]
What did you say? Outside this room?
Dadi, this Mount Fuji, what is that?
[both laugh]
["Khelo Khellum" playing]
[all cheering, applauding]
Made for each other.
[Dadi]
Now that your job as parents is over,
you go on a honeymoon too.
Make each other… Hmm.
[male singer in Hindi] ♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
♪ Let candles of desire ♪
♪ Light up nights in your heart ♪
♪ As creases smile at your sight ♪
♪ Marvel at this maddening delight ♪
♪ Play the game ♪
♪ The game of love, player ♪
♪ Let your body and soul ♪
♪ Swing by the gates of heaven ♪
["Khelo Khellum" concludes]
-[traffic rumbling]
-[car horns blaring]
[woman retching]
-[clock beeps]
-[footsteps retreating]
[tense music playing]
[breathes deeply]
-[cell phone ringing]
-[gasps]
Hi, Sammy.
[Sameera, over phone] Isheeta,
you won't believe what Rohan has done.
What happened?
[Sameera] He's gone
and applied for that loan.
We talked about it for weeks.
We had decided together
that this is not a good time.
And then this morning,
he casually informs me
that he has applied for it.
I mean, what's the point then?
Should I just ignore it?
It's not a small amount, yeah?
And I don't understand why do we have
to have the latest model of the damn car.
It's so unnecessary.
Ish, I'm so angry, I can't tell you.
[Isheeta] Yeah, I can understand.
[Sameera] It's totally
going to fuck up my finances.
We just bought the house,
and he knows that I have to take care
of Mom's treatment.
-And now, another EMI.
-[car horn honking]
[Sameera] Why are you sounding so low?
Everything okay?
[Isheeta] Sameera, I have migraine.
[Sameera] Oh, no. Again?
Ish, please go to the acupuncture lady.
Just trust me.
-Yeah, I guess so.
-[Sameera] Yeah.
Listen, I've reached home, huh.
[Sameera] Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
You go rest, okay?
-I'll call you later.
-Yeah. Okay. Bye.
[Sameera] Okay. Bye. Bye.
[keys jingling]
[woman panting]
[both moaning]
[door slams shut]
[phone ringing]
-[Sameera] Yeah, Ish?
-Hi. Sammy?
-[Sameera] What?
-You won't believe what's happened.
-I just walked in and Didi is…
Didi is…
[Sameera] What? What? I can't hear you.
-She's having sex inside.
-[upbeat music playing]
[Sameera] Didi? Which Didi?
-Seema Didi.
-[Sameera gasps] What?
-Yeah.
-[Sameera] Inside, meaning in your house?
On my bed.
[Sameera] What the fuck?
Why are you shouting?
[Sameera] What the fuck, Ish?
That is disgusting. That's sick!
I know. I just froze and I ran out.
[Sameera] You ran out?
Are they still in there or what?
Yeah.
[Sameera] And where are you?
On the landing.
[Sameera] Babe, are you mad?
That's your house.
Your maid is in your bed.
You go back inside right now and fire her!
Listen, Sammy, I can't.
I just can't deal with this right now.
I'm like… You know, my head.
My head is… killing me.
[Sameera] Listen, you go inside.
Otherwise, I'm coming there.
And I mean it! Fuck! Seema!
And with whom?
You think she's having an affair or…?
-I don't know.
-[door rattles]
[whispers]
They're coming out. I have to go.
[Sameera whispering] Okay. Okay. Okay.
[crow caws]
[elevator chimes]
[automated voice] Please close the door.
[elevator whirs]
[tense music playing]
-[cell phone vibrates]
-[water trickling]
[moans]
[sobs]
[continues sobbing]
[gas hissing]
[microwave beeping]
-Did--
-[Seema] I've got some fresh brinjal.
-I'll make it today.
-Didi, did you call the plumber, huh?
No. Actually, I forgot I wanted to--
What? Didi, how many times
should I remind you, huh?
I got done late from work yesterday.
But you got home late the day before too.
The tap is like a fountain now.
While washing the dishes, I was fully wet.
Accha, the watchman said
-that on Thursday morning--
-Didi, yesterday--
Wh-- What, Didi?
You left the window open.
[clicks tongue] No.
I shut all the windows
before leaving yesterday.
The bathroom window was open.
Right?
Bathroom?
There were so many mosquitos.
The food was also not nice.
Same thing every day.
Go more asymmetrical.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-Increase the pixel size of this.
-[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
And check the borders.
[Isheeta] Here, simplify the notes.
Okay? And print it in maybe, uh,
like, thick paper, like maybe 300 GSM,
-and show it to me, okay?
-Okay.
[cell phone chimes]
[clock beeps]
[sighs]
[Seema moaning]
[tense instrumental music playing]
[Seema continues moaning]
[moaning fades]
-[student 1] Ma'am?
-[student 2] Ma'am?
-Yeah?
-[telephone ringing]
-Tell me--
-Can you pass that?
-See this?
-Yup.
[whimsical instrumental music plays]
[Seema moaning]
[Seema panting]
[Isheeta moaning]
-[moaning stops]
-[music concludes]
[doorknob rattles]
[door shuts]
[crow caws]
[gasps]
-[dial tone ringing]
-[cell phone ringing nearby]
[cell phone beeps]
[tense music playing]
[Isheeta gasps]
[door creaks]
[music intensifies]
[whimsical instrumental music playing]
[pants]
[Seema moaning]
[gasps]
[moans]
[man snoring]
[baby crying]
[grunts]
Did you pay Saayli's fees?
I did.
I had gone to get the cylinder today.
There was a long queue.
I'll go tomorrow.
What happened to you today?
Hmm?
[chuckles]
[snoring continues in background]
-[birds chirping]
-[indistinct chatter]
[rooster crowing]
[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
[Isheeta] Didi, where are you?
It's 9:30 already.
I have to go to a meeting.
My lunch isn't ready yet.
Please come fast, Didi.
Sorry, Didi.
I'll be there in five minutes.
[upbeat percussive music playing]
Hey, didn't you go to school today?
[button clatters]
[Isheeta screams]
It's up there, Didi, there! See? See?
There's something with me, you know?
Past couple of months,
I've been getting
these pounding headaches
in the afternoon.
Migraines, na?
So, my friend's mother told me
about this amazing acupuncture guy,
uh, who fixed her in just two sessions.
It's very difficult
to get an appointment, you know, from him,
so I have to go again today.
Hmm?
Okay. No worries.
Great.
[Seema moaning]
[moaning]
[clock beeps]
Hello, Didi.
You are home early today?
No.
-[objects rattling]
-Guess what? I got the plumber myself!
Huh, very good.
Actually, I forgot my charger.
I'll just go inside and get it quickly.
[plumber] This is done. Check it once.
[upbeat music continues]
[Kamal snoring]
[waves crashing]
Look at me.
Shave before you come tomorrow.
[Seema moaning]
[screams]
-[Kamal] Someone is there.
-[Seema] There's no one there.
-[Kamal] Let's go. Come on. Come!
-[Seema] Wait. Look, there is no one.
Listen to me. Wait!
-[Kamal] No, I heard a sound.
-Wait, wait. She can't come at this time.
What are you say… [gasps]
What's happening here in my house?
What are you up to?
What do you mean?
What's happening here?
-Huh?
-You…
-So, you were hiding here and watching us?
-Shut up!
Why shut up, huh?
Don't you have any shame?
You are hiding and watching us from here?
Look how her pants are open! Chee!
-You're such a dirty woman. Chee!
-[Isheeta] What?
-Please, Seema. Please, calm down.
-[Isheeta] What bullshit is this?
First you do disgusting things
on my bed with him,
and then you accuse me of being wrong?
Eh? What do you mean disgusting?
Whatever I'm doing,
I'm doing it with my husband.
Not like you,
looking at others and enjoying it.
-God, you are such a dirty woman.
-I'm dirty?
What are you saying?
Have you gone mad?
I'm dirty? Huh?
You are the one lying naked
on my bed and messing around.
-And I'm dirty?
-[Kamal] Sor-- Sor-- Sorry, madam.
-Uh, please--
-You wanna sleep with your man, right?
Then go and do it in your house.
-I trusted you with my house keys.
-[Kamal] Please let it go, madam.
-And you used it to--
-What exactly did I use your keys for?
Did I steal anything from your house?
-[Isheeta] One minute--
-You gave me the keys for work.
Because you can't wake up and open
the bloody door!
-[Isheeta] Keep your voice down.
-[Seema] Why should I?
Can you tell her to keep her voice down?
You gave me the keys
so I could look after your house!
[Isheeta] Stop shouting!
Do you even know
where your things are kept?
I'm the one who washes your underwear.
Seema, what the hell are you saying?
Please.
What do you mean by that? It's her house
so she can say whatever she wants?
You are not bloody working here
for free, okay?
I pay you a salary for it!
And you…
did you ask for my permission
before you came up?
Did you ask me?
You tell me, how do I know
who all she brings to my house, huh?
-I don't know.
-What did you just say?
-Hey! Stop it!
-Have you gone mad, huh?
-Or else I'll call the police, okay?
-You wanna call the police? Call them.
-So-- Sorry, madam. Please.
-Why you say sorry to her?
Did you hear what she said?
That I'm sleeping around with people
and you are saying,
"Sorry, sorry, sorry" to her?
-Huh?
-Just calm down!
She was watching us from there.
She was watching both of us
-from that mirror.
-What?
I will look at you?
-So who are you looking at?
-I will look at you?
Even thinking about it is disgusting!
Disgusting for me.
Huh. Really, Didi?
Now I disgust you? I disgust you?
Food, clothes, dishes, I do everything
and now you are disgusted by me?
You did not feel disgusted
when I cleaned your house
like it was my own.
You did not feel disgusted then.
Can you do a single thing without my help?
You can't even get yourself a man.
Even to cool yourself,
you bloody need me horny!
-Seema!
-Get out!
-[Kamal] Seema, stop this nonsense!
-Get out of my house.
Take whatever I owe you and just leave.
-Get out.
-[Seema] Kamal, wait.
Give me that.
Take your keys back.
I don't want this job.
I don't need your money.
I'll find work at ten other places! Ha!
No one in this building will hire you.
I will tell everyone in the society
how you were naked on my bed
and were fucking around!
Okay, so tell them.
You think I'll keep quiet?
I have seen everything with my own eyes.
How you sneak into the house like a mouse
every day and hide behind the tree
to watch us
and touch yourself every fucking day!
And you think people are
gonna believe you?
You?
Fuck off!
[door slams]
Akkash, take this.
Bring back the change, yeah?
I am leaving now.
Arrey, don't you have
to go to work today?
I will.
[doorbell rings]
Didi, today again, you're late for work?
-Sorry, Didi, there was no water at home.
-[Isheeta] Okay, okay.
Just come inside and wash the dishes,
I'm getting very late for work.
And please don't forget to clean
the fans on Sunday.
Accha, Didi.
Seema was working with you
for a very long time, right?
Why did she leave?
-[sighs]
-[doorbell rings]
-Watchman said you wanted a maid?
-[man] Yes.
Only for the dishes and cooking.
And also, I'm a vegan.
So don't use milk and curd.
-And not too much masala.
-Okay.
Can you come at 9:00 tomorrow?
Sure. I will.
[man] Thank you.
What?
[Sameera] You didn't fire Seema that day?
-Actually, I was, uh--
-[Sameera] Babe!
You know, I've been hearing
all sorts of crazy things.
Meaning?
[Sameera] So your seventh-floor neighbor
was in my Bandra Mom's group, you know?
-She's been saying, like, crazy--
-What's she been saying?
[Sameera] She's been saying
that you've been making your maid
-do stuff and watching and all.
-[Isheeta] What?
[Sameera] Yeah. And then, apparently,
she was asking for money also.
But then you guys
have had some big fight
-and everybody in the building heard.
-What did you say?
[Sameera] Babe, I didn't
even know want to say.
Because I haven't even spoken to you.
You've just ghosted me, and I think--
I mean, did you even fire her?
Sammy, are you nuts?
I fired her and I didn't call you
because I've been busy at work.
[Sameera] You know, Ish,
there's been something on my mind.
And I really wanna ask you.
-So I'm just gonna go ahead and ask you.
-Yeah.
[Sameera] You know
when you and I used to live together
and Rohan used to come over?
You, by any chance,
didn't watch Rohan and me--
No.
-And how can you even ask me this, Sammy?
-[Sameera] Sorry, sorry.
Listen, I have to go now.
I'll talk to you later, okay? Bye.
[elevator chimes]
-[automated voice] Please close the door.
-She's the same one.
The same one with the bai scandal.
[man] This is her?
DESPERATE HAG
[melancholy instrumental music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[music fades]
[man snoring]
[cell phone chimes]
[door closes]
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[chuckles]
-Use the heart filter, no?
-[Saayli] Wait.
Now see how cute you are looking?
-Okay.
-Saayli? What's going on here, huh?
-Arrey!
-What's going on here?
Take your hand off her!
Hands off.
You're touching her, huh?
How dare you touch her?
Shall I go to your mother
and tell her, huh?
Useless kid! And you, what were you--
-Arrey, please listen.
-[Seema] What were you doing?
Hiding the phone, huh? Give me.
-Give me the phone.
-We were discussing the paper…
Open it. What were you looking at?
Tell me.
What did you close when I came here, huh?
-I'll show you now, huh?
-I'm sorry.
-[Seema] What did you close?
-We were discussing the paper.
[Seema] What do you think of yourself?
I'm your mother,
I know what you're doing.
-[Saayli] I am sorry.
-[Seema] Don't act smart, okay?
[sobbing]
[Seema] Nothing happened.
Just go to sleep.
[Kamal] Why did you have to hit her?
So did you expect me to praise her?
No.
But you could have just yelled at her.
When you were that age,
we ran away and got married.
So do you want her to marry that idiot?
You think that boy is right for her?
Is that what I said?
Then?
And you know everything, right? Huh?
What all is right, what is wrong.
Hmm?
Let it be. I don't want to talk to you.
Yeah.
I can see that.
Since the last few days.
You don't even look at me anymore, huh?
Tell me.
Am I really that dirty, huh?
-What have I done? Tell me, huh?
-Leave me.
Did I steal something?
Or have I slept with someone else, huh?
You really think…
you didn't do anything wrong?
And whatever she did,
was that right?
She didn't do anything wrong?
Arrey, those people have money.
It was bloody our fault.
We shouldn't have gone there.
We went once, we went twice.
-But every day?
-There was nothing wrong.
She knew everything about us.
She had no problem.
She really knew everything.
That means she knew everything.
You knew everything.
What about me?
I didn't need to know anything?
She was there every day, but why?
You were enjoying it, na?
Hmm?
She came every day, was watching us.
And you liked it, right?
Hmm?
Tell me now.
You were enjoying it too.
Hmm?
Say something.
Go on.
What are you doing? The girls will see.
So?
Are you feeling shy?
[Seema moans]
[bike bell ringing]
[Isheeta] Didi, how much
is this broccoli for?
Fifty rupees for 100 grams.
Give me half a kilo, please.
Broccoli is 400 rupees a kilo.
Give me half a kilo of bhindi and give me
the fresh ones. These are not good.
Brinjal.
Give me this too.
-How are you doing?
-Saayli's exam, how--
[both chuckle]
Are they over?
Exams are next month.
-But she doesn't study.
-What?
She spends whole day on the phone
with the boys tiki, tiki, tiki, tiki.
That's all she does.
This is the age for it, you know?
So… but, yeah.
How much is it?
[woman] Hundred rupees.
Did you find a new maid?
No.
Did you find a new job?
Yeah, I got two.
Oh.
Actually, you know, I thought about
calling you a number of times.
I even tried to talk to you, you know?
Actually, I should've told you earlier
only that I, um, used to…
watch you…
and your husband.
I knew it long ago.
Why didn't you ever tell me about it?
Because I used to enjoy it too, you know?
[woman] Here you go, tai.
It will be 200.
Okay.
[car horn blaring]
Okay, then.
-[Isheeta] Bye.
-[soft chuckles]
Shall I…
come from tomorrow?
Hmm.
The keys.
[upbeat percussive music playing]
[clock beeps]
["Jab Koi Baat Bigad Jaye"
playing on radio]
[male singer in Hindi]
♪ Whenever something goes wrong ♪
♪ Whenever there's a problem ♪
♪ Stand by me, oh companion ♪
♪ Whenever something goes wrong ♪
[in English] We will finish this
once you get here.
Look. No, Nisha. Come on.
You can't just stop.
[cell phone beeping]
Uh, just a minute.
What's wrong now?
Senior has called
for an emergency AGM.
What? How is this possible?
I'm the CEO. How can they just--
Well, they are doing it.
ED is up our ass, Vijay.
I kept telling you not to make a deal
with the Malaysians, to keep away.
But you wouldn't listen, would you?
Bro, everything I've done till now,
I did it for the company, okay?
Not for myself.
Clearly, Senior doesn't think so.
And after today's board meeting,
maybe the board won't either.
Just get your ass back here.
Where are you right now?
Site visit.
I'll call you back later.
It's been so long.
How much longer will you take?
Yeah, okay.
Nisha, one minute.
[phone ringing]
Papa!
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing?
Reading Famous Five.
But I am not reading it.
Mama is reading. I am hearing.
[Anita] Not hearing, listening.
-Ah, but--
-Papa, when are you coming home?
Soon, soon, buddy.
Okay, give the phone to Mama now.
Okay, Papa.
[Anita] Give.
What is the problem with your dad, huh?
What is this about
an emergency AGM?
I don't know.
Even I got a call an hour ago.
And you're going?
I am a member of the board, Vijay.
I have to go.
Why don't you just remind your father
that the company's successful
only because of me?
It was nothing before that.
How dare he fucking doubt my intentions?
I don't know that.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
[dramatic music playing]
You're getting a lot of calls.
Nisha, I will have to go back now.
What? No way! You promised me.
I know. But there is some important work
to be done.
More important than this?
[bicycle bell ringing]
[man] Hey!
[tires screeching]
If you're blind,
then why are you riding a bike?
Me? Sir, you were driving badly.
[car beeping]
[melancholy music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Sir, my village.
You will get a mechanic here.
Thank you.
Sir, you have a vintage car.
Getting spare parts will be--
Why don't you go and try at least?
Come.
Listen, do you have a landline?
It's been dead for two months.
So then why did…
Fuck it, you go. I'm already late.
Is there a coffee shop around?
Hello.
[choir singing in Hindi]
♪ There isn't anyone, there never was
In my life, apart from you ♪
-♪ Stand by me… ♪
-♪ Oh companion ♪
♪ Stand by me ♪
["Jab Koi Baat Bigad Jaye" plays]
-♪ Whenever something goes wrong ♪
-♪ Whenever there's a problem ♪
-♪ Stand by me, oh companion ♪
-♪ There isn't anyone, there never was ♪
-♪ In my life, apart from you ♪
-♪ Apart from you ♪
-♪ Stand by me, oh companion ♪
-♪ Whenever something goes wrong ♪
-♪Whenever there's a problem ♪
-♪ Whenever there's a problem ♪
-♪ Stand by me, oh companion ♪
-♪ There isn't anyone, there never was ♪
-♪ In my life, apart from you ♪
-♪ Apart from you ♪
-♪ Stand by me ♪
-♪ Oh companion ♪
♪ Oh companion ♪
[song concludes]
[dramatic music playing]
-[in English] Bye.
-Bye.
[Vijay] Excuse me?
Shanti, you're still alive?
It's me, Vijay.
Sorry. I think you must be confused.
Balls, confused.
I'd recognize you anywhere.
You should leave right now.
You're making a mistake.
Mistake?
So what's your name then? Tell me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
[tense music playing]
What happened?
Why are you behaving like this?
[man] What's going on here?
-Is this man bothering you?
-Me? Why--
-Did I speak to you?
-No.
No, right?
Good. So shut up.
Tell me, Shanti, is he bothering you?
-Yes.
-Yes?
No, no.
Yes, because I remembered something.
That kind of yes.
Not yes that I'm bothering her.
Not that yes.
They're both different yeses.
It's okay, Inder. I know this guy.
-He isn't bothering me.
-See?
Sure?
-Hey, she told you, right?
-Didn't I ask you to shut up?
Who are you? What's your name?
Uh, Vijay. Vijay Chauhan.
Vijay Chauhan?
Yes. My full name.
What are you doing in my town?
[scoffs] In your town?
My car broke down.
[sighs]
I'll leave now. See you in the evening.
And you,
please get your car fixed quickly.
And get the hell out of here.
I don't wanna see you in the evening.
Oh, hello.
You can't just talk to me like this.
It's for your own good.
Leave this place.
Look at how he's talking to me.
He's right.
You should leave this place right now.
Okay. I will go.
But could first you explain to me
where did you disappear ten years ago?
-[door slams]
-Do you know I looked for you everywhere?
I was going crazy.
Suddenly, you just vanished.
It's been ten years now, Vijay.
And for those ten years,
I had no idea where my wife was.
How she was. Dead or alive?
And you're here!
Listen.
You owe me an explanation.
Sorry.
Old habits.
I need to change my clothes.
Will you wait?
Yes.
-Do you have coffee?
-Yes.
The kettle is there
and coffee is up there.
And milk?
Since when do you take milk
in your coffee?
Just checking whether you remember or not.
[soft instrumental music plays]
[Shanti] Vijay, can you
shut the tap, please?
There's no water in here.
Don't you think this place
is so much like our old place in Malad?
Only one tap at a time.
[tense music playing]
[water running in shower]
What the fuck?
[music intensifies]
-It's for you.
-I don't drink coffee.
I know. It's tea with milk.
[soft instrumental music playing]
So tell me.
You really should leave.
Otherwise, you'll get late.
I have a meeting, but it can wait.
Vijay Chauhan late for a meeting?
You were never late for anything.
Well, there is always a first time.
Now tell me.
[ominous music playing]
Uh, well, I don't remember it completely.
I was on my way back from the nursing home
when a man came up to me
and he was looking for the nursing home.
In the car,
his pregnant wife was in labor
and she was screaming in pain.
So I went to help her and then…
Then?
I don't remember what happened after that.
I only remember waking up here
in Paraisol.
So why didn't you come back home then?
You didn't even bother to call me once.
I was scared.
Why?
I was scared that someone is
trying to kill me.
Someone wants to kill you?
Why would anybody want to kill you?
I don't know,
but I was really scared that day.
And I thought
that I would give you a call,
but I didn't have the guts.
Listen, nobody wants to kill you.
How could you even think like that?
Nursing home?
You just said you were coming back
from the nursing home.
Why did you go there in the first place?
Were you pregnant?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to give you a surprise.
We were gonna have a baby?
I lost our baby.
It's all my fault.
Why did I ever go to that car?
-It's okay.
-I should have told you.
-[Shanti] It would have all been…
[soft instrumental music playing]
No, no, no. We can't do this.
This is wrong.
What's wrong?
You're my wife, for God's sake.
So you didn't get married again?
To whom?
Anita.
Anita?
Anu?
[scoffs] Our Anu?
Wow. So you got married to Anu?
[Vijay] Everything happened so fast.
After I lost you, I was a mess.
And she was there for me.
Kids?
Two. Boys. Eight and five.
So sweet.
I still remember when you and Anu
had joined that company together.
What was that term?
Graduate management trainees.
The first time that Anu had come home…
I thought she was
the prettiest girl in the world.
Is it…
jealousy?
At first, I was,
but I was sure that you were only mine
and I had a marriage certificate
to prove it too.
You're right.
I have always been only yours.
Nice tea.
And I still am.
Well, I can see you've changed a lot.
What happened to Anu's fiancé?
The one who was gonna take over
the company after their wedding?
Uh… no idea.
I only met him a couple of times.
One of those times we met him together.
Remember?
Then who's running the company now?
Oh, hello.
He's standing right in front of you.
I'm so proud of you.
You've been wanting this
since you were in college.
And now look, you got it.
But it wouldn't
have been possible without you.
You've made so many sacrifices.
-Took care of the house so that I could--
-No.
Taking care of the house was my choice.
It made me happy.
Whatever I am today, it's because of you.
Thank you.
Mmm, Vijay!
You just haven't changed at all.
Jump at the first chance you get.
How does Anu keep up with you?
Very happily.
[Shanti] You should leave now.
You're getting really late.
Yeah, I am getting late.
Listen, you are coming back with me.
Why? No.
Why not?
Do you know how happy Anu
will be when she sees you?
[tense music playing]
She won't be.
Why?
You still haven't realized it, Vijay?
It was Anu.
What was Anu?
She was the one who hired those people.
The couple.
The one I met outside the nursing home.
The one that had tried to kill me.
What the hell are you saying?
Are you out of your mind?
Anu has loved you for a long time.
No. No, Shanti.
The three of us
were the best of friends, man.
The three fucking musketeers.
Anu always wanted you for herself.
She always tried
to keep you distracted from me.
And the day that she found out
I was pregnant, she tried to--
Wh-- wha-- One minute.
How did Anu find out
that you were pregnant, huh?
She never said anything to me about it.
What would she have said anyway?
Do you remember that evening
when we had that party at home
and we were singing
"Jab Koi Baat Bigad Jaye" together?
No, but go on.
I had taken the test that evening,
and by mistake,
I left the test kit in the washroom.
I didn't want anyone to know about it,
so I went right back to get it.
And I saw that Anu
was leaving the washroom.
-[Vijay] So?
-[Shanti] So, Vijay,
I had kept the test kit facing upwards,
and when I went back
it was facing downwards,
which means that Anu saw it
and kept it back the wrong way by mistake.
Yeah. So, even if she did see…
Fuck.
Actually, after you were gone,
Anu didn't even let me
out of her sight for a second.
I thought she was
genuinely concerned, but…
It costs a lot of money
to do something like this.
And Anu had a lot of money.
-We need to do something about this.
-No, we don't.
Sorry?
You're happy, right, Vijay?
With Anu and your lovely kids?
Yes.
Then that's it.
Just go back to your home,
back to your family.
You still have time.
-So please go away from here.
-And just forget about this?
Everything that you've just told me?
You'll have to try.
Or else your life will become hell.
Listen to what I'm saying.
Please go away from here.
I know it was a long time ago,
but do you remember
what that couple looked like?
Yes.
Seriously, even now?
Like it was yesterday.
Super.
If we can find them,
then we can find out what happened.
We will find the truth.
[scoffs] And what will you do
with the truth?
And what if Anu
really was behind all this?
Then she will have to be punished.
And then?
Then maybe…
we can be together again.
I missed you so much.
No, no, we can't.
Will you please leave from here?
-You have a wife now.
-Because of whom, I lost you.
[Shanti] We can't do this.
Please go away.
Listen, I'm with Inder now.
[dramatic music playing]
You were always like this or what?
Will you focus first?
[music continues]
[both gasp]
[both panting]
[grunts]
[grunting]
Vijay, careful. Be careful.
[Vijay groans]
[groans]
[soft instrumental music playing]
-Vijay, did you just--
-Sorry. I couldn't help myself.
Last time that you couldn't help yourself,
you remember I got pregnant?
And then I ended up here.
Don't worry, you won't get pregnant.
How do you know that?
I just know it.
And if you want to be sure,
then try your Red Blue again.
You'll find out yourself.
Same old Vijay.
-"I know everything."
-[chuckles]
Correct.
Red Blue?
How do you know that?
What Red Blue?
[Shanti] The test kit.
The one that Anu saw,
it's called Red Blue.
It's not available anywhere in India.
My friend from Canada bought it for me.
I hadn't told anyone about it.
Then how do you know?
You only must have told me.
No, I did not tell you.
Did Anu tell you?
No, Anu didn't tell me.
That means it was you.
That was you--
-[muffled] Vijay! Vijay!
-[ominous music playing]
[Shanti] Vijay! Mm! Vijay!
I paid those fuckers so much money!
Even then,
they didn't do their job properly!
And on top of that,
you remember their faces too.
Thank you for not coming back
and staying the fuck away.
'Cause whatever I am today
is because of you.
You did sacrifice a lot for me.
Just do this one.
One more thing. Please.
[pants]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Fuck, I'm late.
[metal squeaks, clanks]
-[knocking on door]
-Fuck.
[knocking on door]
[tense music playing]
Shanti?
Shanti? Shanti, are you inside?
[dramatic music playing]
[man 1] I tried a lot to wake him up.
["Jab Koi Baat Bigad Jaye"
looping on radio]
[man 1] It seems
he didn't want to come back.
♪ Whenever something goes… ♪
[man 2] This music system is stuck.
How do I turn it off?
[Shanti] I had warned you, right?
[ominous music playing]
Just leave…
or you'll be really late.
[laughs menacingly]
[screams]
[audio ends abruptly]
[heavy breathing]
[man, in Hindi] Bloody bitch!
[woman whimpering]
[man] Fucking dirty skank!
[man, in English]
Let me show you how it's done, huh?
[crickets chirping]
[somber music playing]
[yelps]
[insect squishes]
[driver] Mehersa, you know a lot
of important people.
Why don't you ask for their help?
Your Mehersa never asks for anything.
I only give orders.
-[goat bleats]
-[driver laughs]
Um, so this time, the tender
will be definitely yours, Mehersa?
Of course I will get it.
The collector's mother used
to pick up cow dung from our place.
[driver] Then please do something
for me too, Mehersa.
I take Yuvraj to tuitions every day.
So, if you could, uh, do something for me?
[laughs] Just wait.
Once I get the contract,
then I'll do something. Huh?
Then the tender should be yours.
Arrey, whose picture have you put up here?
Arrey, Mehersa, it's just something
to look at when I get lonely.
Accha.
Keep your eyes on the road, will you?
Hey, hey!
[goat bleats]
BIJOKPUR RAJWADA
Pranaam, Mehersa.
-Drive safe.
-Pranaam.
Okay. Pranaam. Pranaam.
[humming]
[footsteps approaching]
Huh?
Ankur, listen! You go ahead, I'm coming.
Arrey, Bitari? You're going home
early today? Huh?
Jee, Mehersa. Morhe has a fever, so…
I'll give you medicines for him.
What will I do with this?
My naara is loose. Tie it for me, okay?
-No, no. Mehersa. No, Mehersa.
-Come.
-Mehersa.
-Come on. Come, come. Come, come.
-[Bitari] No. No, Mehersa. Mehersa.
-[Mehersa] Come quickly.
-[Bitari] Please let me go, Mehersa.
-[Mehersa] Come, come.
Let's spend some time. Hmm.
[dramatic music playing]
Eat this. It's hot.
-I don't want it.
-Ah. Put it down.
Don't drink water. Eat your food.
I made your favorite vegetable.
Okay, tell me. How are your studies going?
Okay.
Just okay?
It's going well, right?
No.
What do you mean "no"?
You want to go to England, right?
No, I don't want to go to England.
What do you mean?
I don't want to go.
You are going.
The only thing left here are the goats.
What about you?
How can I leave you?
[melancholy music playing]
Don't worry about me.
Look…
If you go there,
I can come there too, right?
Hmm? Got it?
Your hair is looking dry.
I won't put oil.
Do you know how expensive it is?
Baba went to the city again
today for some tender.
God knows what else he took a loan on.
How do you know?
He is the one telling everyone about it.
[clock chiming]
You don't worry about the money, hmm?
You just concentrate
-and study hard. [laughs]
-Arrey! Don't put oil on my face, Ma!
Ma!
-Ma!
-Tell me you will study or no?
Tell me. Tell me. First tell me, huh?
Come on, tell me quickly.
Come on, tell me.
-[laughing]
-[upbeat music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[Mehersa humming]
[laughs]
[glass shatters]
[footsteps]
Chanda?
Chanda!
[light switch clicks]
Chanda.
[in Hindi] My queen.
Hmm?
[in English] Are you asleep?
Are you asleep?
Today was a good day, you know?
You don't know this, but…
I got a big tender today.
Just like you got last time?
[gasps]
[in Hindi] Bloody bitch.
[in English] You slut.
[in Hindi] Bloody whore!
[in English] Bloody whore! Huh?
[brothel keeper, in Hindi] Bastard! Huh?
[in English] I'll show you.
Get out of here!
Get up! Go! Get up! Get lost from here!
Get up, haramzada!
Who do you think you are?
Do you think this is a fucking
midday meal, huh?
If I see you again,
I will cut you into pieces.
Just get out! Fuck off from here!
Just get lost.
-[in Hindi] Son of a bitch!
-[phone ringing]
[in English] I will…
-[coughs]
-[ringing continues]
Who is this?
[man] Yeah, it's me.
I'll show you, bitch!
Get out from here! Get out, you harami!
-[man] What will you do?
-Should I come? Should I?
Bloody animal!
Haramzada!
-Come on.
-[woman] Come on, let's go back to work.
-Go now.
-[woman] Yeah, yeah, coming.
Oh, yes?
-Oh, tell me.
-What happened?
[coughs]
Oh, the same shit every day.
All the losers of the whole universe
come here only.
[coughing]
Anyway, you tell me, what's the matter?
Are you still not getting better?
[coughing]
There is absolutely nothing left in me.
How are you doing?
[Chanda] I'm okay.
-I'm just missing you.
-[laughs]
Yes. I know exactly.
Why do you miss me now?
Because you were a queen here.
[laughs, coughs]
You became a whore
only when you went there.
[somber music playing]
If my being a whore
can make my son a king then…
I'm fine with that.
Did you go to the doctor?
What will a doctor do? Huh?
When it's someone's time to go…
[coughing]
…then they have to go.
It's actually good
that you left this place.
Just yesterday, I found out that
one of our girls has got the disease.
Don't know which horrible fucker
gave this to her.
Her life is over. So young.
-[water splashing]
-[Mehersa] You fucking asshole!
Bloody dropped me in the water.
Can't you row carefully?
Harami, fuck off!
Mehersa.
What? Tell me what?
What are you doing here?
Mehersa, leaving for tuitions.
[under breath] Fucking tuitions.
Listen, come here.
If my son gets less marks this time,
you are the one who's going to fail.
[Yuvraj] Come.
Teja Singh!
What was he saying?
Asking about the stars.
Told him they're not favorable.
I hope you've studied well.
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
[thunder rumbles]
Uh, those hotel people had come again.
They wanted to talk to you.
[laughs] Come.
This is a king's palace,
not your whorehouse
that can be made into a hotel.
I said it once, I won't repeat myself.
Go.
[tense music playing]
-Go!
-[whimpers]
[thunder rumbles]
[in Hindi] Bitch.
[groans]
[ominous music playing]
[in English] Arrey, Bitari?
Panaam, Mehersa.
Oh, you are not Bitari.
Are you new here?
Yes, I am, Mehersa.
Go get a towel for me.
-Towel?
-Mm-hmm.
One, two,
and that's my piece to the finish.
Yeah.
-Baba?
-[Mehersa] Huh?
I want to go England for further studies.
Why? What's wrong here?
College is better there.
And now, we have got the tender as well.
So, Ma and I can go there for a few years.
Panaam, Mehersa.
Rani Saheba has sent some tea for you.
Listen…
What's your name?
Jee, Rekha.
Wrap it up.
[water splashes]
No black clothes, black shoes,
black shirt, avoid wearing anything black.
You know what? Right now,
your stars are waiting to attack you.
Need to avert them.
This is usually done
at a place in Ujjain.
But can get it done for 1,100 rupees.
Don't worry.
[Yuvraj] And?
First thing every morning,
feed roti to a dog,
vegetables to a crow,
and sugar to five ants.
-Can I feed black ants?
-[Pandit] Absolutely not.
In case of going to England,
red and black are the difference
between heaven and earth.
What I don't get is
what will you do in England?
They don't see the sun for three months.
I wonder who they offer water to then.
[chants]
I will get rich one day.
How rich do you want to be, man? Huh?
More than your father? Huh?
Bhanu says his blood is white,
that's why he's like this.
It's not your father's fault.
Rahu.
Rahu is setting foot in his chart.
This can be fixed in Banaras,
but we can get it done here itself.
Less than 2,100.
Your Shukra is angry too.
As long as you live in this haveli,
no England for you.
So how do I calm down Shukra?
[Pandit] Havan needs to be done.
But for now, smoke this.
Hey!
[Chanda] Rekha?
[Rekha] I'm coming, Rani Sa.
I'll finish washing the clothes.
[Chanda] Okay. Just come here after that.
[water splashing]
[dramatic music playing]
[crow cawing]
Can you iron this kurta?
I have a meeting.
Who is this new girl?
The old one was doing fine.
Why did you fire her?
I didn't fire her. She ran away.
What? We were paying her, right?
What was the problem?
We were paying her only to work
in the kitchen.
Not in the bedroom.
[gasps]
Mind how you talk to me, okay?
Or else I'll send you back
where you came from.
-And again.
-[gasps]
Stop filling Yuvraj's head
with this England crap.
He is a raja's son.
And a raja doesn't work for anyone.
How beautiful are these sarees, Rani Sa?
They must look lovely on you, Rani Sa.
Then take one.
Oh, no, no, Rani Sa,
they won't look good on a girl like me.
Okay, then don't take.
Shall I take this one, Rani Sa?
This color looks good on me.
Wear it.
[Rekha] Rani Sa.
[laughs]
[upbeat instrumental music playing]
[music fades]
[Mehersa, in Hindi] Sons of bitches.
[in English] Leave me! Asshole!
You dare talk back to me, madarchod?
Your mother used to be
a cow dung collector, madarchod!
[in Hindi] You swine.
[grumbling indistinctly]
[in English] Are you asleep?
[light switch flicks]
It's not working again.
Fuck!
Nothing ever works in this house.
Bloody hell!
[in Hindi] Fucking… [grunts]
[door opens]
[humming]
Mehersa?
[in English] He's alive.
[in Hindi] Master?
Mehersa?
[in English] Drunkard.
[door shuts]
[Chanda] Rekha!
Yeah, Rani Sa. Coming!
[dramatic music playing]
[Mehersa groaning]
Hey, choree, you are very good at massage.
Hmm? Where did you learn from?
I didn't learn it, hukum.
When I was a kid, you know,
I used to massage my father's legs.
I see.
You were bright from your childhood. Hmm?
[Rekha] When I was kid,
everyone used to say,
"This girl will make
the whole village proud."
A little higher.
May I ask something, hukum?
Is this palace
more than a hundred years old?
-Such beautiful flowers drawn on the wall.
-A little more.
Oh. I never imagined in my life
that one day I'll get a chance
-to live in a palace this big.
-A little more.
May I ask something, hukum?
Are Rani Sa
and young Mehersa going abroad?
If they leave from here,
the palace will feel so empty,
but I hear
it's very beautiful abroad, huh?
-They even have got--
-Go.
Get lost now.
Hukum, but--
I'm sorry, hukum.
I'm a fool.
I don't think before speaking.
I'm sorry.
Stop gossiping now.
And pay attention here.
Don't you want to live here?
Huh?
Do you drink?
[ominous music playing]
Hmm? [laughs]
Take it. Take it.
Take it.
Look here and drink in front of me.
-[coughs]
-[laughs]
What did you do? [chuckles]
That will spoil your saree, huh?
[chuckles] It's not a problem,
I'll wash it.
Will you do something?
Take it off.
-[chuckles]
-Take it off, take it off. Take it off.
Come on.
Very good.
-[Yuvraj] Baba?
-[music ends abruptly]
Someone has come to meet you.
These fuckers won't leave me alone.
[birds chirping]
I will study very hard.
We will go to England.
We can't stay here.
Just wanted to say that.
[soft instrumental music playing]
All of them are bastards.
I paid such a heavy bribe
and it's all gone.
[in Hindi] All a waste, rascals!
Chanda, that bitch.
[in English] And my son too
wants to leave me and go.
The pandit had told me
that I will die alone. [laughs]
Run away, bastards.
All of you can fuck off! [laughs]
[door opens]
[Rekha giggling]
[Rekha moaning]
[moaning continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[triumphant music playing]
[music intensifies]
[brothel keeper] It's actually good
that you left this place.
Just yesterday, I found out
that one of our girls has got the disease.
I don't know which horrible fucker
gave this to her.
Her life is over. So young.
[Chanda] What is her name?
[brothel keeper] Rekha.
[Rekha moaning]
[Mehersa grunting]
[music stops abruptly]
[Rekha moaning]
[dramatic music playing]
[theme music playing]
[theme music concludes]