Hey, Hey!
Teddy!
Listen to me!
Listen!
I don't want to leave here, allright?
I mean, why wouldn't anybody want to?
We hear things here.
About the outside world.
About atolls,
about H-bomb tests.
You know how
a hydrogen bomb works?
- I know that, with hydrogen, with hydrogen.
- Now that's funny.
- Boss!
Other bombs explode, right?
But not the hydrogen bomb
It's implodes-
Creating an explosion thousandth
a millionth degree.
- Get it?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Do you?
- I get it, I get it.
Go!
No!
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ, Teddy. Jesus!
You got Billings?
What's the fuck's the matter with you guys?
Catch 'em, not kill them!
He jumped us.
You give me a hand with him,
we've got to get him to the infirmary
No, no, not you, not you,
take a walk.
Come on!
Poe's gonna have my goddamn balls for this.
Laeddis ..
Laeddis ....
Ten thousand times the air.....
Please ...
Why kill
Stop me or I'll kill more.
AHH!!
Please, please!
Laeddis ...
You told me I'd be free of
this place.
You promised.
You lied.
Laeddis?
That's pretty damned funny.
Your vioce ...
Don't you recognize it?
After all the talks we've had?
After all the lies
you told me.
Let me see your face.
They say I'm theirs now.
They say I'll never leave here.
Your match is about to go out.
Let me see your goddamn face now!
Why?
So you can lie to me more?
- This isn't about the truth.
- Yes it is.
- It's about exposing the truth.
- It's about you.
And Laeddis.
That's all it's ever been about.
I was incidental.
A way in.
George?
George Noyce?
No, it is not possible,
you can't be here.
Do you like it?
Who did this to you, George?
You did!
What the hell do you mean?
What of your talk
and your fucking talk,
And I'm back in here because of you!
George, I'm gonna get you out of there tomorrow.
However this happened, I'm gonna find a way to fix this
Do you understand me?
I'll never get out now.
I got out once, not twice, never twice.
- Tell me how they got you here?
- They knew!
Don't you get it?
Everything you were up to.
Your whole plan.
This is a game. All of this ...
is for you.
You're not investigating anything.
You're a fucking rat
in a maze.
Georgie ...
you're wrong,
youre wrong
Really?
Been alone much since
you got here?
I've been with my partner.
You've have never worked
with him before, have you?
He's a ...
He's a US Marshall.
You have never worked
with him before, have you?
George, look ...
I know people.
I trust this man.
Then they've already won.
Fuck!
They're going to  ...
take me to the lighthouse.
They're going to
cut into my brain.
And I'm only here because of you!
I'm going to get you out of here.
You're not going to the lighthouse,
Your not.
You can't dig up the truth
and kill Leaddis at the same time.
You gotta make a choice
you understand that, don't you?
I'm not here to kill anyone.
Liar!
- I not gonna kill him! I swear to you, I swear.
She's death.
Let her go ...
Let her go.
Tell him Teddy ..
Tell him why.
You've got to do it
There's no other way.
- Let her go.
- Tell him about the day you brought my locket.
You gotta do it
How I told you my heart was breaking,
and you asked me why?
She's fucking with your head.
And I told you
it was from happiness.
She gonna kill you. she's going to kill you.
You wanna uncover the truth?
You gotta let her go.
- I can't.
- You have to let her go!
I can't!
I can't.
Then you'll never leave
this island.
Dolores?
He's not in this ward.
He was transferred ...
Out of here.
If he's not in ward A
There's only one place he can be.
The lighthouse.
Hey!
God help you.
Boss, we got problems.
McPherson and Cawley are in the building.
They heard an orderly went batshit on a patient,
There lookin all over the place for him.
There on their way to the roof.
Let's get the hell outta here.
This way.
Just keep going,
we belong here.
- What happened to you?
- What do you mean?
Where were you?
After we got that guy to the infirmary,
I took a little detour
to patient records.
Did you ever find Laeddis?
No.
- No. I never found him.
- I got the next best thing,
his intake form.
It's the only thing in his file, there's
no session notes, no incident reports,
no photographs,... just this.
It was weird.
Here, take a look.
I'll look at it later.
What's the matter boss?
I'll look over later,
that's all.
Ashecliff's that way.
I'm not going to Ashecliff.
I'm going to that lighthouse.
I'm going to find out what
the fuck is happening on this island.
There it is.
Damn!
Were too far south
We'll have to double back.
There's no way we can cross those rocks.
There could be a way behind those trees.
Maybe, maybe a path that goes around the rocks
that leads over to the lighthouse... Come on.
What, what are we doing?
We've get the intake form.
It proof there's a 67th patient,
which they've said repeatedly doesn't exist.
I'm getting to that lighthouse,
you understand?
What the hell can I say to you to stop you.
Why would you want to Chuck?
Why?
Because climbing down there
when it's dark is a thin step short of suicide.
That's why.
Ok.
Maybe it's better you sit this one out then.
You brought me into this, boss.
And now I am trapped here, on this rock,
on this island.
With  no one to rely on but each other,
and now you acting like .........
Like what? Like what?
How are my acting?
What the hell happened back there
in those cells, Ted?
- What do you think weather is like in Portland, Chuck?
- I'm from Seattle.
Seattle?
I'll go on... alone.
I'm going with you boss.
I said alone.
Fine.
Damn it!
Oh damn it.
I knew it wouldn't take long,
but I couldn't get to it, the tide was up.
Chuck!
Where are you Chuck!
Who are you?
I am Teddy Daniels.
I'm a cop.
You're the Marshal.
That's right.
Would you mind ...
taken your hand from behind
your back please?
Why?
I wanna make sure what you
holding wont hurt me.
I'm gonna keep this.
If you don't mind.
Fine by me.
You're Rachel Solando.
The real one.
Did you kill your children?
I never had children.
I was never married.
And before I was a patient
at Ashecliff, I worked here.
You were a nurse?
I was a doctor, Marshal.
You think I'm crazy?
- No...No, I
- And if I say I'm not crazy ...
Well that hardly helps, does it?
That's the Kafkaesque genius of it.
People tell the world you're crazy,
and all your protests to the contrary,
just confirm what they're saying.
I'm not following you.
I'm sorry.
Once you are declared insane,
then anything you do is called
part of  that insanity.
Reasonable protests
or denial,
valid fears,
paranoia.
Survival instincts are
defense mechanisms.
You're smarter than you look Marshal,
that's probably not a good thing.
Tell me something ...
Yeah ...
What happened to you?
I started asking about this
large amount of sodium amytal.
- And opium based hallucinogens.
- Psychotropic drugs.
I asked about the surgeries, too.
Ever heard of transorbital lobotomy?
They zap the patient with electroshock,
then go through the eye with an ice pick.....
Pull out some nerve fibres,
makes the patients much more obedient.
Tractable.
It's barbaric.
Unconscionable
Do you know how pain enters the
body Marshal? Do you?
Depends on where you hurt.
No, it has nothing to the flesh.
The brain controls pain.
The brain controls fear, empathy,
sleep, hunger, anger ... everything.
What If you could control it?
The brain?
Recreate a man,
so he doesn't feel pain,
or love, or sympathy.
A man who can't be interrogated
because he has no memories to confess.
You can never take away all a
man's memories,
Never.
Marshal, the North Koreans
used American POWs
during their brainwashing experiments.
They turned soldiers into traitors.
That's what they're doing here.
They're creating ghosts to go out in the world,
and do things, sane man, sane men never would.
To have that kind of ability, that kind of knowledge,
that would take years.
Years of research,
hundreds of patients to experiment on.
For 50 years now,
people will look back
and say here, this place
is where it all began.
The Nazis used the Jews
the Soviets
used prisoners in their own gulags'
and we...
We tested patients,
on Shutter Island.
No, they won't ...
No
You do understand.
That they can't let you leave?
I'm a federal Marshal ...
they can't stop me.
I was an esteemed psychiatrist,
from a respected family.
It didn't matter.
Let me ask you ...
Any past trauma in your life?
Yes, why... why would that matter?
Because they gotta point to
some event in your past
and this is the reason you lost your sanity......
so that when they commit you here,
your friends, and colleagues will say...
cause he cracked.
Who wouldn't,
after what he'd been through.
That could say that about anyone.
- anyone at all.
- The point is they're going to say it about you.
How's your head?
- My head?
- Any funny dreams lately?
Trouble sleeping, headaches ...
I am prone to migraines, yes.
Jesus!
You haven't taken any pills, have you?
- I mean even aspirin?
- The aspirins?
Jesus!
And you, you ate the food in the cafeteria and drank the
coffee they gave you.
You tell me at least that you've been
smoking your own cigarettes.
Not ... no.
No I haven't.
It takes 36 to 48 hours for
neuroleptics narcotics
to reach workable levels in the
blood stream.
Pulse will become first
First the finger tips, then
eventually the whole hand.
Seen any walking nightmares lately,
Marshal, huh?
Tell me what's goes on in that lighthouse?
Tell me.
Brain surgery.
"Now let's open the skull and see
what happens if we pull on this kind"..............
They learned it from the Nazi's kind.
That's where they create the ghost.
Who knows about this?
On the island, I mean. Who?
Everyone.
O'come on, the nurses, the.. the, the orderlies?
- They couldn't possibly know...
- Everyone.
You can't stay here.
They think I'm dead, that I drowned. I'm afraid
if they come looking for you, they might find me.
I'm sorry, but you have to go.
I'm gonna come back for you.
I wont be here. I move during the day,
new places every night.
But I could come get you,
get, get you out of this island.
Haven't you heard a word I've said?
The only way off the island
is a ferry and they control it.
You'll never leave here.
I had a friend.
I was with him yesterday,
but we got seperated.
Have you seen him?
Marshal ...
You have no friends.
There you are.
We were wondering when
you'd show up.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Taking a leisurely stroll? were we?
I was a...
just, just looking around.
Did you enjoy
God's latest gift?
- What?
- God's gift.
The violence.
When I came downstairs in my home
and saw that tree in my living room,
it reached out for me, a divine hand.
God loves violence.
- I, I hadn't noticed.
- Sure you have.
Why else would there be so much of it?
It's in us.
It's what we are.
We wage war, we burn sacrifices,
and pillage and plunder
and tear at the flesh
of our brothers
and why? Because God gave us violence
to wage in his honor.
I thought God gave us moral order.
There is no moral orders
as pure as this storm.
There's no moral order at all.
There's just this-
Can my violence conquer yours?
- I'm not violent.
- Yes you are.
You're as violent as they come.
I know this, because I am as violent as they come.
If the constraints of society
were lifted..............
and I was all that stood between you and the meal, you
would crack my skull with a rock and eat my meaty parts.
Wouldn't ya?
Cawley thinks you're harmless, but you can be
controlled, but I know different.
- You don't know me.
- Oh but I do.
Oh, I know you
We've known each other for centuries.
If I was to sink my teeth into your hide
right now,
would you be able to stop me before I blinded you?
Give it a try.
That's the spirit.
Where have you been?
Wandering, just looking at your island.
Oh I forgot your leaving,
now that Rachel's been found.
Sure.
Big meeting
Oh, yes ...
Apparently there was an unidentified man
in ward C yesterday,
he subdued a highly dangerous patient.
quite handly.
Is that so?.........
It seems he had a long conversation with a
paranoid schizophrenic, George Noyce.
This Noyce,
so you said his name was,
- he's delusional?
- Oh extremely, he can be quite upseting.
In fact, two weeks ago, a patient
got so wound up
by one of Noyce's stories
that he beat him up.
Cigarette?
No, thanks.
I quit.
So, your taking the ferry?
Yes, absolutely ...
I think we've gotten
all we came here for.
"We" Marshal?
Speaking of a which-
- Have you seen him, Doctor?
- Who?
My partner, Chuck.
You don't have a partner, Marshal.
You came here alone.
You know, I've built something valuable here,
but valuable things have a way of
being misunderstood in their own time.
Everyone wants a quick fix,
they always have.
I'm trying to do something that people
your self included don't understand.
And I'm not going to give up
without a fight.
I can see that ...
So tell me again
about your partner.
What partner?
Marshal ...
Going somewhere?
No. Just ... heading out
to the ferry.
I'm afraid, I'm afraid it's the other way.
If you wait a moment,
I'll find you someone that can take you
to the dock.
What's this, Doctor?
Huh, What's this?
It's just a sedative?
- It's a precaution.
- Precaution?
What are you going to do,
kill me?
Do you think you deserve it
For what? Provoking you?
And forgive me
what doesn't provoke you?
Remarks ...
- Words ...
- Nazis
Well that too.
And of course, memories, dreams ...
Did you know that the word "trauma" comes
from the Greek- for wound?
And what is the German word for "dream"
is "traume".
I like traume.
Wounds can create monsters.
And you ...
you are wounded, Marshal.
And wouldn't you agree,
when you see a monster
you must stop it.
- I agree.
- Yes.
What are you doing, baby?
You've gotta get to the ferry.
No, no, ... no.
If the world thinks that Chuck is dead,
then he is perfect for their experiments.
There's only one place they'd take him.
You go there and you'll die.
He's my partner, if they are hurting him, if they're
holding him against his will, I have gotta bring him out.
I can't lose anyone else.
Don't go Teddy, please,
please don 't do this, don't go.
I'm sorry, honey.
I love this thing because
you gave it to me,
but the truth is ...
it's one fucking ugly tie.
No!
Don't move!
Stay where you are.
Are you gonna kill me?
No
I'm not going to kill you.
Why are you all wet, baby?
- What did you say?
- You know exactly what I said.
The rifle's empty by the way.
Have a seat.
For God's sake dry off,
you'll catch cold.
All right.
How badly did you hurt the guard?
I, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, he's here.
Have Dr Sheehan take a look
at your man before you send him up.
So, Dr Sheehan,
came in on the ferry
this morining?
Not exactly.
You blew up my car.
I really loved that car.
Sorry to hear about that.
Tremors are getting pretty bad.
How are the hallucinations?
Proud of you Teddy.
This place is gonna be the end of you ..
- Not bad.
- They'll get worse.
I know.
Dr. Solando,
she told me about neuroleptics.
Did she now?
and when was this?
I found the doctor, in a cave, out by the cliffs.
But you'll never get to her.
I don't doubt it.
Considering she's not real.
But your delusions are
more severe than I thought.
You are not on neuroleptics.
You're not on anything,
as a matter of fact.
Then what the fuck is this?
Huh, what the fuck is this?
Withdrawal.
Withdrawal?
From, from  what? I haven't even had a goddamned
drink since I've been on this island.
Chlorpromazine.
I'm not a fan of pharmacology,
but I have to say in your case.
- Clorpro, chlorproma what?
- Chlorpromazine.
The same thing we've
been giving you for the past 24 months.
So for the past two years
you, you have had somebody slipping
me drugs in Boston, is that it?
Not Boston, here.
You've been here for two years,
a patient of this institution.
After everything I've seen here, Doctor,
you, you really think you can
convince me I'm crazy huh?
Do you know the kind of people I deal with
everyday? I'm a U.S. marshal for God sakes.
You were a U.S. Marshal.
Here's a copy of the intake form.
You broke into ward C for
proof of the 67th patient.
If you'd gotten it to the mainland, then
you could have blown the lid off this place.
- Wait ...wait
- But somehow
you couldn't find time
to look at it yet. read it now
Go ahead.
The patient is highly intelligent,
highly delusional.
Decorated army veteran.
Present for the
liberation of Dachau.
Former US Marshal,
known proclivity for violence.
shown no remorse for his crime because
he denies
the crime ever, ever took place.
Highly developed and fantastical
narratives which preclude facing
the truth of his actions-
I had enough of this bullshit.
Where's my partner huh?
Where's Chuck?
Where is he?
Let's try this another way.
Your wife's maiden name was
"Chanal" am I correct?
- Don't you even talk about her, don't you..
- I'm afraid I have to.
Notice anything these four names have in common?
It's your rule 4.
- Andrew, what do you see?
- If you've done anything
- to my partner, Doctor, that is a violation ...
- Focus, Andrew. What do you see?
The names
have the same letters.
Edward Daniels has exactly same
13 letters
as Andrew Laeddis.
The same as Rachel Solando
and Dolores Chanal. The names
- are anagrams for each other.
- The...the tactics their not gonna
work on me.
You came here for the truth.
Here it is.
Your name is Andrew Laeddis.
The 67th patient at Ashecliff
is you, Andrew.
Bullshit.
You were committed here by
court order 24 months ago.
Your crime is terrible.
One you can't forgive yourself for.
So you invented
another self.
Allright, let's, let's get down to the facts.
You've created a story in which
you're not a murderer, you're a hero,
Still a U.S. Marshal,
only here at Ashecliff
because of a case,
and you've uncovered a conspiracy.
So that anything we tell you about
who you are, what you've done,
you can dismiss as lies, Andrew.
My name is Edward Daniels.
I've been hearing this fantasy
for two years now. I know every detail.
Patient 67, the storm,
Rachel Solando,
your missing partner,
the dreams you have every night.
You were at Dachau,
But you may not have killed any guards.
I wish I could let you just
live in your fantasy world,
I really do.
But you are violent, trained, dangerous.
You're the most dangerous patient we have.
You've injured orderlies, guards,
other patients.
Two weeks ago
you attacked George Noyce.
No, no, I'm fuckin on to you doctor..
- You had Noyce beaten.
- Of course I didn't.
Give me one reason
why I'd even touch him.
Because he called you Laeddis,
and you'd do anything not to be him.
I have a transcript of the conversation
you had with Noyce yesterday.
"This is about you and Laeddis.
That's all it's ever been about."
No, no, he's saying this is about
"me and Laeddis".
When you asked him what happened
to his face,
he said, and here I'm quoting again,
"You did this".
- No, no he meant it was my fault ...
- You almost killed him.
The warden and the board of overseers
are determined that something be done, it's been decided
that unless we can bring you back to sanity
now, right now.
permanent measures will be taken to ensure
you can't hurt anyone ever again.
They lobotomise you, Andrew.
Do you understand?
Yeah, I understand.
I understand just fine.
If , if I don't play along
with your little game here,
Dr Naehring gonna turn me into
one of his ghosts.
What about my partner?
You gonna tell  U.S. Marshals' office
that he's a  defense mechanism?
Hello boss.
What the fuck is going on here?
You, you working for him?
I'm sorry there wasn't any other way.
Someone had to stick with you, keep you safe.
You've been watchin me, huh?
Watching me every minute.
Who ... who are you?
Who are you?
Tell me.
Don't you recognize me, Andrew?
I've been your primary psychiatrist
for the last two years.
I am Lester Sheehan.
I told you, I told you about my wife.
- I know.
- I climbed down a cliff to get you.
I , I trusted you. I, I risked
everything, to come in here after you, everything!
I know boss.
We're running out of time here, Andrew.
I swore before the board of
overseers that I could construct
the most radical, cutting edge role-play
ever attempted in psychiatry and
will bring you back.
I thought if we let you play
this out,
we could get you to see how
untrue, how impossible it is.
You've had the run of the place for two days.
Tell me, where are the Nazi experiments.
The satanic ORs
Andrew, listen to me.
If we fail with you,
then everything we've tried
to do here will be discredited.
Everything.
We are on the front lines of a war here old boy,
and right now,
it all comes down to you.
Don't move!
- Andrew, Andrew, no, no.
- My name is Edward Daniels.
This one is loaded.
I can tell by the weight.
I see and that's your firearm Marshal?
You're sure?
My initials are on the side. There's a dent in
the barrel from when Philip Stacks shot at me.
You're not going to fuck with my mind
on this one doctor.
Then blast away, because that's the
only way you're ever getting off this island.
Andrew, please don't.
My gun ...
What have you done to
my goddamned gun?
It's a toy, Andrew.
We're telling you the truth.
Dolores was insane, manic-depressive.
suicidal.
You drank, stayed away,
ignored what everyone told you.
You moved to that lake house after
she, purposely,
set your city apartment on fire.
- You're lying.
- Andrew... Andrew stop, stop
All you've done is lie.
Your children, Andrew your children.
Streme,
- Henry,
- I have no children.
Your wife drowned them
at the cabin by the lake.
And here, the little girl,
the one you dream of
every night.
I never had a girl.
The one who tells you over and over that
you should saved her,
saved them all.
Your daughter ...
Her name is Rachel. Are you going to deny
that she ever lived?
Andrew, are you?
I'm so sorry, baby.
I told you not to come in here.
I told you ...
This would be the end of you.
I'm back.
we got him,
just outside of Oklahoma.
Must've stopped ten places
in between here and Tulsa.
I could sleep for a week.
Dolores?
Baby ...
Why are you all wet?
I missed you.
I want to go home.
You are home.
Where are the kids?
They're at school.
It's Saturday, honey.
School's not in on Saturday.
My school is.
Oh my God!
Oh my God, no!
Come on!
No please, God, no please, god no.
No!
Put them around the table Andrew.
We'll dry them off,
we'll change their clothes.
They'll be our living dolls.
Tomorrow we can take them on a picnic.
If you ever loved me Dolores-
Please stop talking.
I love you.
Just set me free.
Baby.
We'll give them baths.
- I love you baby.
- I love you too.
- I love you so much.
- I love you so much. I love you.
Andrew?
Andrew, can you hear me?
Rachel!
Rachel, Rachel.
Rachel?
Rachel who?
Rachel Laeddis.
My daughter.
Why you here?
Because I killed my wife.
And why did you do that?
Because she murdered our children.
And she told me to let her go.
- Who's Teddy Daniels?
- He doesn't exist.
Neither does Rachel Solando,
I made them up.
Why?
We need to hear you say it.
After she tried to kill
herself the first time,
Dolores told me she ...,
she has an insect ...
living inside her brain.
She could feel it,
clicking across
her skull ...
pulling the wires,
just for fun.
She told me that.
She told me that, but I didn't listen.
I loved her so much.
Why do you make them up?
Because I can't take knowing
that Dolores killed our children.
And I killed them, because
I didn't get her help.
I killed them.
Here's my fear, Andrew,
we broke through once before,
nine months ago,
and then you regressed.
- I don't remember that.
- I know.
You reset, Andrew,
like a tape,
playing over and over, on an endless loop.
I hope that what we've done will be enough
to stop it from ever happening again.
but I need to know,
you've accepted reality.
You came after me, huh doctor?
You tried to help me when no one else would.
My name is Andrew Laeddis,
and I murdered my wife
in the spring of '52.
How we doing this morning?
Good.
and You?
Can't complain.
So what's our next move?
You tell me.
I've gotta get off this rock,
Chuck.
Get back to the mainland. Whatever the
hell is going on here it's bad.
Don't worry partner,
they're not gonna catch us.
That's right we're too smart for them.
Yeah, we are,
aren't we?
You know this place makes
me wonder.
Yeah? What's that boss?
Which would be worse?
To live as a monster,
or to die as a good man?
Teddy?
subtitled by
Sub Conqueror