Subtitles by
amir_t6262
Get it together Teddy!
Get it together!
It's just water.
It's a lot of water
Come on.
- You okay boss?
-Yeah, i'm just...i just can't
I just can not stand on water.
- You're my new partner?
- that's right.
Not the best way to know you
half head in the toilet.
Doesn't exactly square with
Teddy Daniels: the man of legend, i'll give you that
the Legend?
What the hell are you boys smoking
out there in Portland anyway?
Seatle.
I came from the office in Seatle.
How long have you been with Marshals?
Four years.
So you know how small it is
What about you? got a girl? Married?
I was.
she died.
- Jesus ...Boss, i didn't...
- don't worry .
There was a fire in our apartment
building, while i was out
Four People died.
It was the smoke that got her
not the fire
- That's important.
- I'm sorry.
Where are my goddamn Cigars?
i have. have one of mine
I could swear that I have the clothes
when I boarded.
Government employees, rob you blind
thanks
Have you received any briefing
about the institution befor you left?
All I know is it's a mental hospital
For the criminally insane.
Well, if it was just folks hearing voices
and chasing butterflies, i guess
they wouldn,t need us
- that's where we're headed?
- Yap.
The other side of the island is rock bluffs
all to ended in water
The dock, it's the
only way on, or off
we will casting off again as soon as
you two are ashore
i'd appreciate if you two hurry about it
- Why?
- Storm's coming.
I've never seen a marshal
badge before.
i'm Deputy warden
McPherson, gentlemen.
Welcome to Shutter Island.
I'll be taking you up to Ashecliffe.
Your boys seem a little on edge
Mr McPherson
Right now, Marshal. We all are
"Remember us for we too have
lived, loved and laughed"
Electrified perimeter.
How you know?
I've seen something like it before.
All right. you gentelman will be accorded
all the help we can offer.
But during the stay you will
obey protocol, do you understand?
Absolutely.
The red brick bulding on my right
is ward A, the male ward
Ward B the female ward, is one
on the left
Ward C is that building on the bluffs
The most dangerous patients
are there
Admittance to ward C is forbidden without
the written consent and
physical presence of both myself and Dr.Cawly
Is that understood?
You act like insanity is catching
You are hereby required to surrending
your firearms
Mr McPherson, We are duly apointed
federal marshals
we are required to carry our
firearms at all times
Executive order 319 of the Fedral Code of
Penitentiaries states that
when stays at Penitentiaries
the office head of institutions
has the final authority.
Gentlemen, you will not be allowed
to pass through the gate with your firearms
ok, well that does for the official stuff,
come on boys
What do you say we go find Dr.Cawley?
So when did she escaped? the prisoner?
I'm afraid that Dr. Cawley will have to
fill you in on the situation
Protocol.
Correctional officers at a mental institution
that's a weired sight,
if you don't mind me saying
It's the only pursuit of it's kind in the U.S
Even in the world. We care
only the most periculo and patients.
Most of the other hospitals can not deal.
And all because of Dr. Cawley.
It created something really unique here.
Hospital, people who deal ...
Id's, gentlemen.
Badges, gentlemen.
Dr. Cawley's been consulted
numerous times
- By Scotland Yard, MI 5, OSS ...
- Why?
What do you mean?
Why the intelligence agencies want
to consult a psychatrist about?
i guess you'll have to ask him
-  Marshall Daniels.
- I am Ted.
marshall Aule.
- Thanl you deputy warden, that will be all
- Yes, sir.
pleasure, gentlemen.
He sure had a lot to say about you
McPherson is a good man.
he believe in the work they do here.
And what would that be exactly?
a moral fusion between law and
order and clinical care
Pardon me Dr...
a waht between what and what?
These paintings are quite accurate.
It used to be that kind of patients we
deal with here
shackled and left in their own filth
they were beaten
as they put bloody
drove screws into their brain, and submerged them into icy water to lose their consciousness
Or even drown.
- And now?
- we treat them.
Trying to heal, to cure.
And if this fails, we at least provide them
with a measure of calm in their lives.
these are ...
all violent offenders, right?
they've hurt people.
- murdered them in some cases.
- In almost all cases. Yes.
then personally Doctor, I'd have to
say... screw their sense of calm.
It's my job to treat my patients not theire victims. I'm not here to judge.
- So this female prisoner ...
- Patient.
Excuse me, patient.
one Solando Rachel,
- Escaped sometime in the last 24 hours.
- Last night.
Between 10 and midnight
- Is she considered dangerous?
- You could say that.
She killed all three of her children.
She drowned them in the lake behind the house.
She took them out one by one and held their
head in water until drowned.
Thenshe brought them back inside and
arranged them around the kitchen table
and ate a meal
before a neighbor dropped by.
What about her husband?
He died. On the beaches of Normandy.
she is a poor widow.
She starved herself when first she came here
she insist the children weren't dead
- Sorry Dr wouldn't happen to have some aspirin?
-  Prone to headaches marshal
Sometimes, but today ...
- more prone to seasickness.
-Ah, Dehydration ...
- You allright boss?
- Yes.
In that case you're quite right
Simpler the better.
thank you so much
Rachel still believe
her children are alived.
Also thought that this is her home
of Berckshires.
you are kidding.
in four years acknowldge
that she is in an institution
She believe we're all ...
deliveryman Milkman, postal workers.
to sustain the Illusion that her children never died
she created an elaborate fictional structure
she gives us all parts to play in that fiction
- so you searched the ground yet?
- the warden and his man scoured the island,
not a trace.
What's more disturbing, is that we don't know
how she got out of her room.
it was locked from the outside
and the only window is barred.
it's as if she evaporated straight
through the walls.
Brought her right back here after
group therapy, locked her in
I came back for midnight rounde
and she was gone
Seriously doctor, how is it possible
the truth never gets through her?
Ie, in an institution
mental illness, right?
seems like something you'de
notice from time to time
- How many pairs of shoes get patientsi?
- Two pairs.
Sanity is not a choice, marshal,
You can't just choode to get over it
So ... she left here barefoot?
Come on Doc, she can't get ten
yard in this terrain.
Marshall?
. The law of 4.
Who's 67?.
That's definitely Rachel's
Handwriting
I have no idea what the " law of 4" is, though
- Not a psychiatric term?
I'm afraid not.
Who's 67?
Fuck if I know!
I'de have to say that's quite
close to my clinical conclusion
So you think it's just
random scribblings?
No, not at all. Rachel is smart .
Brilliant in fact.
- This paper that could be important.
- Excuse me Doctor, but ...
- We need to hold onto this.
- of course
The departure had to come through here.
After lights out, the orderlies play
card in here
Last night there were 7 man sitting
at the base of the atairs playing stud poker
And yet somehow, Rachel has managed
to slip by.
Why?
How? She turns invisible?
Doctor, we need access to personal files
of all medical staff
of nurses, guards, orderlies
- Everyone who worked here.
- we take your request under consideration.
This is not a request, Doctor.
This is a federal facility
and a dangerous prisoner ...
- Patient.
- Patient ...
- has escaped now. You can comply ...
- All I can say is that I will see what I can do.
Doctor, we'll need to speak with the staff,
do you understand?
I'll assemble them in the
common room after dinner.
If you have any further questions
feel free to join the dwputy warden in the search
It's 11 miles to the nearest land
and the water is freesing
The current was strong last night.
the tide pushing in
She's have drowned or been crushed on
the rocks, her body would have washed back onshore.
Those caves down ther,
have you checked them?
no way she could get there.
The base of those cliffs are covered
in poison ivy, live oak, sumac
and a thousand plants with thorns
as big as my dick.
You said it yourself marshall,
she's got no shoes
All right, boys!
Let's check the other side!
- What's that tower?
- An old lighthouse.
the quards already searching inside it.
- What's in there? more patients?
- sewage treatment facility.
It will be dark soon.
I'm calling this off for the night
Let's go, boys!
- You were watching the land, right?
- Yes.
Can't no one get in or out of their room
in that corridor without me seeing
All right, Rachel Solando,
who else does she had to pass
to get down here?
Me.
Glen Miga.
- Sir, I saw nothing.
- And you were at your post all night?
Yes. But I saw nothing.
Glen.
Tell me the truth.
I'm really ... went to the bathroom.
- What? You breached protocols? Christ ...
- I was away only one minutes.
All right, I do not know what to expect here.
Let's back up.
Mrs. Solando was put in her room for lights out.
Does anybody knows what did she do
before taht?
Anyone?
come on, anyone. anyone anyone
she was in a group therapy session
Did anything unusual occur?
Defines "unusual".
- Excuse me!
- It's a mental institution, marshall,
for criminally insane.
"Usual", isn't a big part of our day.
I will rephrase.
Did anything happened last night
during and group therapy, that was more...
- let's Say, more memorable than ...
- Normal?
Exactly!
No. I'm sorry.
Did Mrs. Solando said anything
during group therapy?
She was worried about the rain.
And she hates the food here.
Complained constantly.
Last night including
So ... you were there
in the presence of a doctor?
Dr. Sheehan led discuses.
Dr. Sheehan?
Yes. He was running the session.
He's Rachels's "primary"
The psychaiatrist who directly
oversees her care.
We'll need to speak with Dr. Sheehan.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
He left on the ferry in this morning
His vacation was already planned.
He'd putting it off too long
You're in a state of lockdown.
A dangerous patient has escaped
and you let her primary doctor
leave on vacation?
Of course, he's a doctor
Do you have the phone number for
where he's gone?
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
I'm sorry sir, but it all down.
All the lines.
The storm's hitting the
mainland as a hammer.
If you get it working come find me immediately.
the marshalls need to make an important call
Yes, sir.
I'm afraid I have evening rounds in the wards,
But I'll be having drinks and a cigar at
my house around 9
If you like to drop by
Good, we can talk then, right?
We have been talking, marshall.
Gotta say, i'm thinking I went
into the wrong line of public service
It is a little overwhelming.
it was constructed during the civil war
The same time as the military fort
houses, ward C
This building is the original commander's quarters
It cost a fortune when uncle sam got the bill
the commander was courtmartialed
I can see why
Nice music. who's that? Brahms?
No.
It's Mahler.
Quite right, marshall.
Forgive me, gentlemen ...
My colleague, Dr. Jeremiah Naehring.
Quartet for Piano and Strings
in A minor.
-Your poison, gentlemen?
- Rye, if you've got it.
Soda and ice please, thanks
You don't indulge in alcohol?
I am surprised.
Isn't it common for men in your
profession to imbibe?
common enough.
and yours?
- I'm sorry?
- your profession, doctor psychiatry ...
I've always heared it's overrun
with booceys and drunks
Not that i've noticed.
what's it? Cold tea in your glass?
Excellent marshall.
You have outstanding defense mechanism.
You must be quite adapt at interrogation.
Men like you ... are my specialty.
Men of violence.
That's a hell of assumption to make...
No assumption. Not at all. you misunderstand me,
i said you are men of violence
I'm not accusing you of being violent man
It's quite different
Please, please, edify us, Doc.
You both served overseas
Not much of a stretch, Doc. for all you know,
we were both paper pushers over there
No, you were not.
Since the schoolyard, I would bet neither
of you has ever walked away from a physical conflict
Not to suggest you enjoy it
but because retreat wasn't something you considered an option
Wasn't raised to run doc
Ah, yes... Raised
and who raised you, marshall?
Me?
Wolves.
Very impressive defense mechanism.
Do you believe in God, marshall?
I'm quite serious
That's rubbish.
Have you ever seen ... a death camp, Doctor?
I have, I was there, for the liberation of Daqhau
Your English is very good, almost clawless
Your English is very good.
You hit the consonants a tad hard, though
You're German?
-Is legal immigration a crime, marshall?
- Oh I don't know doctor, you to tell us.
Listen, we need the files of Sheehan
and on the rest of staff as well
No such file will be released for you.
Period.
- We gonna need those files.
- out of the question.
bullshit, there is no question.
bullshit.
Anyway, who is in charge here? huh?
Dr Naehring is the liaison to
our board of overseas.
He relayed your request and it's been refused.
Refused? They don't have the authority to refuse. And neither you, sir.
marshall, continues your investigation
and we will do all we can to help.
This investigation is over.
we will file our reports
and handle it over ...
- Hoover's boys.
- Hoover's boys, that's right.
We'll take the ferry back in the morning.
Come on, Chuck
Nice night.
You're bunking in the orderlies quarter.
Hey boss? ... we really gonna pack it in?
Why?
I guess, i dunno, i just...
never quit anything before.
We haven't heared the truth once yet Chuck
Rachel Solando did not slipped out of
a locked room barefoot without any help.
I'm beginning to think alot of help
Maybe Cawley sitting up in his mansion
right now,
rethinking his whole attitudes
- Maybe in the morning...
- You're bluffing?
I didn't said that.
I found a whole stock of these, Teddy.
Jesus, are you ever sober anymore?
I killed alot of people in the war.
Is that why you drink?
Are you real?
No.
She's still here.
Who?
Rachel?
she never left.
Remember when we stayed at the cabin
by the lake ?
we were so happy
She's here.
You can't leave
I'm not gonna leave.
I love you so much.
- I am the bones in a box, Teddy.
- No.
I am
You have to wake up.
I won't go.
You're here.
I'm not.
You have to face that.
But she is
and so is he
Who?
Laeddis.
I have to go.
No! please... don't
-Just a little longer.
- Oh, Teddy ...
Let me go.
I can not.
Ain't gonna be no ferry in this shit
Doctor.
Doctor, Doctor.
we need to interview the patients who
were in Rachel's group therapy that night
I thought your investigation was finished?
It's not like we can take the ferry
and was Rachel recieving any
other treatment for her illnesses?
Do you know what the state of
mental health field in these days, gentelmen?
No. We are not doctors.
War.
The old schools believes in
surgical interventions
Psychosurgery.
The procedures are that the orbital lobotomy.
Some say that patientsi are reasonable,
Other essential say become zombies.
- And the new school?
- Psycho pharmacology.
A new drug has just been approved
of autorities.
That relaxes psychotic patients
some would say tames then
- And which school are you in, Doc?
- I?
I have this radical idea that if you treat a
patient with respect
and listen to him
Trying to understand.
you just might reach him.
- These pacients?
- My point is.
What should be the last resort,
becomes the first response.
Give them a pill and put them in a corner,
and it all goes away.
Rachel Solando was a on a combination of drugs
meant to keep her from becoming violent
and it was only intermittently effective
The greatest obstacle to her recovery was
her refusal to face what she had done
"was."
Is there a reason why you refer to
your patint in the past tense,Doctor?
Look outside, marshall.
Why do you think?
Next one is Peter Breen. Assaulted
his father's nurse with a brocken glass.
Nurse survived, but
her face permaanently disfigured
i can't wait.
She smiles at me.
She was so sweet
But ... I could read in his eyes.
she liked to be naked.
Liked to suck cock
All right, Mr Breen.
And asked me if she can have
a glass of water
Alone in the kitchen?
like that's no big deal?
- Why was that a big deal?
-  It was obvious.
She wanted me to pull out my thing so she
could laugh at it
Mr Breen,
we need to ask you some questions, okay?
When I cut her she screamed
But ...
She scared me.
What did she expect?
Interesting.
But we are here to talk
Rachel Solando, OK?
Rachel Solando ...
Did you know she had drown her own kids?
She drowned her kids
This is a sick fucking world
we live in. i'll tell you that ...
They should be gassed
all of them... the retards, killers
the niggers, kill your own kids?
gas the bitch
Please.. stop that?
- A nurse?
- Please. Stop that.
a nurse maybe. maybe she had kids.
A husband ...
trying to make ends meet,
to have a normal life ...
assisting your father................
You tore her face off, didn't you
Congratulations, no more normal
for her, not ever again
Do you know what she was afraid of?
You.
Could you stop that, please?
Stop that!
Please ... stops!
- You know a patient by the name Andrew Laeddis?
- No! No!
I want to go back.
I'll never get out of here.
I'm not sure I should
Excuse me for saying it,
- Miss Kearns ...
- God.
Mrs. Kearns.
But you seem  ...
quite normal, ...
I mean in comparison
with the other patients here
Well, I have my dark days
I suppose everyone does
Differents is that most people don't kill
their husbands with an axe
Although personally I think if a
man beats you and fuck
half the women he sees
and no one will help you
axing him isn't the least understandable
thing you can do
Maybe you shouldn't get out.
And what would i do if I did?
I don't know the world anymore.
They say there are
bombs that can turn whole
cities to ash
And what do they call "television" ...
voices and faces coming from a box
I hear enough voices already
What can you tell us about rachel?
No much, she... she keep to herself
She believes her kids were alive
She thought she was still living
in Berkshire and we were all neighbours
- milkman, postman
- deliveryman,
Dr Sheehan was there that night?
Yes.
He talked about anger.
Tell me about him ...
What's he like?
I think e. ..
Ok... nice
Not hard on the eyes
just my mother would say
Did he ever come passing you?
No.
No, Dr. Sheehan is a good doctor, he wouldn't ...
Could I have a glass of water, please?
No problem.
Thank you, marshall.
I have just one more question
Mrs. Kearns.
Did you ever meet a patient
named Andrew Laeddis?
No.
Never heard of him.
She was coached
He used the same words as
Cawley's and the nurse.
- It's like she'd been told exactly what to say.
- Who is Andrew Laeddis?
You asked every one of those patients
about him. Who's he?
What the hell, boss, I'm your partner
for the God's sake!
We just met, Chuck.
There are the job long.
You got a duty, a career
and what i'm doing
not exactly by the book.
I don't give a damn about the book, boss
But I need to know what the hell is going on
When this case came over the wires,
- I requested it. Specifically, do you understand?
- Why?
Andrew Laeddis,
was the maintenance man in thr apartment
building where my wife and I lived
Okay.
He was also a firebug.
Andrew Laeddis lit the match,
that caused the fire that killed my wife.
Open the!
What happened with Laeddis?
got away.
Laeddis got away and disappeared.
About a year ago I opened the
newspaper and there he is.
He's an ugly son of a bitch.
He had a new scar in the right temple
down to his left lip.
Eyes different colors.
not a type of face you forget.
He'd burned a schoolhouse. Killed 2 people.
He said voices told him to do that.
First he was sent to prison
and then he was transferred here.
- Then what?
- Then, nothing.
He vanished like he never existed
no records forever
I'm sure he's not in ward B
that leaves ward C.
Or he could be dead.
So could Rachel Solando.
Lots of places to hide a body here
only one place where
no one really knows
the patient , Bridget Kearne,
when she sent me for water,
she said something back to you, didn't she?
No.
Come on boss!
She wrote it.
. Run ..
Boss!
We must get inside. It's turning
into fucking Kansas out here...
All right. Now.
Let's go!
watch out!
Jesus!
Come on! Let's go back!
Jesus Christ!
damn it!
- Are you okay boss?
- Yes. that's all right.
So ... you think Laeddis is here ...
What are you going to do boss?
I'm not here to kill Leaddis.
If it were my wife
I'd kill him twice.
When we got through the gates of Dachau,
the SS guards surrendered.
The commander tried to kill himself
before we got there ...
but he botched it
took him an hour to die
When I went outside,
I saw bodies on the ground.
too many to count
too many to imagine.
so yeah
The guards surrendered, we took,
their guns, lined them up ...
I wasn't warfair,
it was murder.
I'm tired of killing.
That's not why I'm here
So what is it all about?
After Laeddis vanished,
I started doing some checking
on Ashecliffe.
lot of people knew about this place, but no
one wants to talk ...
like they're scared of something
you know this place is funded by
special grants
from the house of
American activities Committee .
Great. And how exactly are we fighting
the countries from an island in Boston Harbor?
by conducting experiments on the mind
at least that's my guess
And you think thats going on in here?
As I said, nobody's talking, right?
Until I found someone
who used to be a patient here.
Guy's name George Noyce.
nice college kid.
Socialist.
He got an offer to get some money for some psych study. Guess what they were testing.
- drug tests.
- He started seeing dragons everywhere.
Almost beat his proffesor to death
End up appearing in Ashecliffe.
Ward C.
They released him after 1 year, right?
What does he do?
Two weeks on a mainland
he walks into a bar and stabs three men to death
His lawyer pleads insanity,
but Noyce ...
stands up in the courtroom and
he begs the judge,
for the electric chair,
anywhere but not a
mental hospital.
Judge give him life in the Dedham prison.
- And you have you found him?
- Yes, I've found him.
he's a mess
But it is pretty clear from what he tells me,
they're experimenting on people here.
I do not know, boss.
- I don not believe a crazy
- That's the beauty of it.
crazy people are a perfect subject.
they talk, but nobody listened.
I stood in Dachau.
we saw what human beings are capable
of doing to each other, right?
for Christ sake we fought a goddamn war
to stop them,
and now find out it may be happening here?
On our land?
No.
What are you really here to do, Teddy?
I'm here to get the proof.
I'm gonna go back and blow
the lid off this place.
That's it
wait a minute.
You started asking around about Ashecliffe.
waiting for a chance to get out here
then suddenly they need a US marshall?
I got lucky. a patient escaped ,
it was the perfect excuse.
No, no, no boss.
Luck doesn't work that way.
The world doesn't work that way.
They got electric fence around a septic facility.
Ward C is inside a Civil War fort?
A chief of staff with ties to the SS
Funding from HUAC?
Jesus Christ! Everything in this place
stinks  "government ops"
-  What If they wanted you here?
- bullshit.
- Ask questions.
- Nonsense.
bullshit? Where is Rachel Soalndo?
Where is one shred of evidence that she even existed?
I had to know where
that will give me any. In any case.............
While you were looking at that neighbourhood,
they're looking at you
All they need to do
is making a fake escape to get you here
And now they have you.
they have us both,here, now.
Marshall, are you here?.
.Please signal us, this is deputy warden McPherson.
marshall!.
How about that? They found us.
It's an island, boss. They'll always find us.
. I know you are in there ...
We get out of this fucking island.
You and me.
Come on!
- Come on!
- Go!
get dry off
Dr. Cawley wants to talk to you. Now!
And hurry up, this thing is transforming
to a goddamn hurricane!
I dopped those suits to be cleaned.
It should be ready by tomorrow.
If we don't all wash away first
speaking of which, I'm afraid your smoke were
pretty much done for
So ...
It's our only choice, right?
that's something really nice in prison already
that ...................
Now that you mention it, it is just fine.
that's why i must repeat my insistence
that all ward C patients
be placed in manual restrains,
If the facility floods, they'll drown
you know that
- That would take a lot of flooding.
- We are on an island,
in the middle of the ocean,
during a hurricane.
A lot of flooding seems like a
distinct possibility
It's a gamble, Steven.
say the power fails
there's a backup generators.
and if htat goes? The cell doors
will open
Where are they to go?
They can't just hop a ferry, scoot over
to the mainland over a weak havoc.
You're right. Probably responsible
recovery right here on us..
If they're manacled to the floor, they die
24 human beings.
you can't live with that, can you?
frankly, if it were up to me
, i'd put all 42 in ward A and B in
manual restrains as well
Excuse me
- marshall.
- I'm sorry, I have one quick question.
Yes, I will be with you in a moment.
When we spoke this morning about Rachel Solando's note
the law of 4, I loved that.
you told me you had no idea what
that second line could refer to
Who's 67?
Yes, I'm afraid I still do not know.
None of us knows.
Nothing comes to mind.
Nothing?
Because I believed i just heard
you say that there are
24 patients in ward C.
And 42 of patients, in wards A and B
which would mean there are
66 patients here in this facility
That's correct, yes.
Then it seems that
Rachel Solando was suggesting
you have a 67th paient, doctor
- But I'm afraid we don't.
- This Is ridiculous.
- What are you doing here?
- We are doing our goddamn job.
Didn't McPherson tell you the good news?
No, what's the good news, doctor?
Rachel has been found.
It's here.
Safe and sound
There is not a mark on her.
Who are these men?
Why are they in my home?
Police officers, Rachel.
They ... have a few questions.
Ma'am.
There's been a sighting of a known
Communist
subversive in this area
passing out literature
Here?
In this neighborhood?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
If you have tell us what you have done yesterday, where you were,
it'll help us narrow  our search.
Yes ...
Well, I ...
I made breakfast for Jim
and the children,
and then I ...
I packed Jim's lunch
and he left.
Then I sent the children off to school.
And then ...
I decided to take a long swim in the lake.
I see...
And after that?
After that ...
I thought of you.
I ... I'm sorry, ma'am.
I do not know what you talking about.
Don't you know how lonely I've been, Jim?
You're gone ...
You're dead.
I cry every night.
How am I supposed to survive?
God.
Rachel ... it will be all right.
I'm so sorry, but ...
everything will be all right? Okay?
I buried you
I buried an empty basket . Your body
was nothing but blood and chunke of....,
eaten by sharks.
My jim is dead,
So who the fuck are you?
who the fuck are you?
Who are you? Who are you?
I'm sorry about that
I didn't wanted to interrupt, I thought
she might trll you something, but ...
we found her down by the lighthouse,
skipping stones.
We have no idea how she get there.
i'm going to ask you both to go down into basement.
We have food, water, and cots .
It's the safest place to be
when the hurricane hits.
are you all right?
You look pale.
I'm fine, it's just ...
Boss, are you okay?
It's so goddamn bright? isn't it?
Photo sensitivity, headaches sometime?
Marshal are you having migraine?
Yeah, right.
Take these, marshall. You'll sleep a couple
of hours, wake up clear as bell.
You have a migraine.
Imagine someone sawed open your head and
filled it with razors then shook it
as hard as they could
Take these pills, marshall.
- No ... not want.
- It'll stop the pain. Take pills.
You'll need to lay down
carefull. All right.
Gonna be okay. Relax.
- Who is that?
- He?
That's the warden.
Do not worry about him, allright?
Looks like ex-military prick.
You know  I can not argue with you onthat.
You should have saved me.
You should have saved all of us.
Hey buddy ...
Laeddis.
Yes.
Hi, buddy.
No hard feelings, right?
No hard feelings.
Little something for later.
I know how much you need it.
clock's ticking, my friend.
Wer're running out of time.
give me a hand here.
I could get in trouble.
I'm dead?
I'm so sorry.
Why did not you saved me?
I tried, I wanted to,
but by the time I got there,
it was too late.
See?
It's not beautiful?
Why are you all wet, baby?
Laeddis isn't dead.
He isn't gone.
He's still here.
I know.
We need to find him, Teddy.
find him and you kill him dead.
It's okay.
. Again!.
Generaytor is faulty
Are you okay boss ?
that goddamn Migraine !
Back up generator failed.
whole places gone crazy.
What do you want to do?
Christ!
No, no, no!
Put it down.
Now! Now!
You think the whole electrical system is fried?
I think that is a good possibility.
All electronic security system ...
fences, gates, doors
Come on.
Nice day for a stroll
don't you think?
to ward C for example.
Maybe you'll find Andrew Leaddis
The guy I told you about, George Noyce?
He told me this is where they keep
the worse ones
The guys in the other wards
are scared of
Noyce did not say anything about the lab?
Not really.
All that he remember was people
scream day and night. There were no windows.
There were bars everywhere.
Jesus Christ!.
first time
on ward C, right?
- Yes, yes ...
- Yes.
- yeah heard stories, but ...
-  Trust me,sons. You haven't heard shit.
we got most of the bugsies locked down now,
But some of them are still loose.
If you see some don't try
to restrain him yourself
These fuckers will kill you.
Clear?
Well get your ass moving, then
c'mon
he's here.
Laeddis.
I can feel him.
Tag! You are it.
ted!.......
Hey, hey!