Hey, hey!
Teddy!
Listen to me!
Listen!
I do not want to leave, all right?
Why wouldn't anyone want that?
I have heard many things here.
About the outside world.
About atolls,
about the hydrogen bomb tests.
You know how
a hydrogen bomb works?
- With ... Hydrogen?
- that's funny.
Other bombs exploding, right?
But not the hydrogen bomb
It's imploding.
An explosion that is hundredth thousand
millionth degree .
- Do you understand?
- Yes, yes ...
- do you?
- I get it!
Go!
No!
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ, Teddy. Jesus!
you got Billings?
What's the matter with you guys?
catch them, not kill them!
He jumped at us.
You give me a hand with him
we've got to get him to the infirmary
No! Not you, not you.
take a walk.
Come on!
. get up thr roof where you belong..
. Laeddis ..
. Laeddis ....
you're dead, we're all dead
this is hell, we're in hell
Please ...
...................
stop me.
Go!
Please, please!
Laeddis ...
you told me i'de be free of
this place
You promised.
You lied.
Laeddis?
Laeddis!?
That's pretty damned funny.
Your vioce ...
Don't you recognize it?
After all the talks we've had?
After all the lies
that you've tell me?
Let me see your face.
They say i'm theirs now
They say i'll never leave.
Your match is about to go out.
Let me see your goddamn face!
Why?
so you can lie me more?
- This isn't about the truth!
-yes it is.
- It's about exposing
- This is about you!
And Laeddis.
That's all it's ever been about.
I was incidental.
a way in
George?
George Noyce?
No, it is not possible,
You can not be here.
do you like it?
Who did this to you, George?
You did!
What do you mean?
What are you talking
all of your fucking talk
And I'm back here because of you!
George, I get you out of here.
I'll find a way to fix this
I'll never get out now.
I got out once, But not twice, never twice
- Tell me how sis they got you here?
-they knew!
Don't you get it?
Everything you were up to.
Your whole plan.
This is a game. All of this ...
is for you.
You're not investigating anything.
You're a fucking rat
in a maze.
George ...
you're wrong.
Really?
Been alone much since
you got here?
I'm with my partner.
You have never worked
with him before, right.....?
He's a ...
US Marshall from Seattle.
You have never worked
with him before, have you?
George, look ...
I know people.
I trust this man.
Then, they've already won.
fuck!
they're going to  ...
tale mr to the lighthouse.
they're going to
cut into my brain.
And I'm only here because of you!
George, I'm going to get you out of here.
You're not going to the lighthouse.
You can't kill Leaddis and expose
the truth at the same time
You have to make a choice
you understand that, don't you?
I'm not here to kill anyone.
- Liar!
- I won't kill him! I swear to you ...
She's death.
Let her go ...
Let her go.
. Tell him Teddy ..
. Tell him ..
You've got to do it
There's no other way.
- Let her go.
- The time you brought me these flowers ...
You have to do!
And I told you and you broke my heart.
And you asked me why?
Play with your mind.
And then i told you
it broke from happiness
she kill you. she's going to kill you.
You want to uncover the truth?
then you have to let her go ...
I can't.
- You have to let her go!
I can't!
I can't.
Then you'll never leave
this island.
Dolores?
He's not in this ward.
He was transferred ...
Out of here.
If he's not in ward A
There's only one place he can be
The lighthouse.
Hey!
God help you.
Boss, we have problems.
Cawley and McPherson are in the building.
Cawley heard an orderly went batshit on a patient,
then got sent up to the roof.
He went up to look for him
Let's get the hell out of here.
This way
Just keep going.
we belong here
- What happened to you?
- What do you mean?
Where were you?
after we got that guy to the infirmary,
I took a little detect
to patient records.
did you find Laeddis?
No.
- I didn't find him.
- I find next best thing.
in his intake form.
that's all that was in his file
no session note, no incident reports
no photograph... just this.
It was weired
here, take a look.
I'll take a look later.
What's the matter boss?
I'll look at it later,
that's all.
Ashecliffe's that way.
I'm not going to Ashecliffe.
I'm going to the lighthouse.
I'm going to find out what
the fuck is hapening in thid island.
Here it is.
Damn!
too far north
We'll have to double back
There's no way to cros those rocks
there could be a way behind those trees
maybe a path that goes around the rocks
to the lighthouse
what are we doing here?
we've get the intake form
It proofs ther's a 67th patient...
who they've said repeatedly he doesn't exist
I'm getting to that lighthouse
do you understand?
What can I say to you stop.
why would you want to?
Because climbing down there
when it's dark ......... suicide
okay.
maybe it's better you sit this one out
you brought me into this, boss.
And now I am trapped on this rock.
On the island.
Without anyone we know.
And now you acting like .........
Like what?
How my acting?
What the hell happened
in those cells, Ted?
- What do you think weather is like in Portland, Chuck?
- I'm from Seattle.
Seattle?
I'll go alone... alone
Come with you, partner.
I said alone
Fine.
Damn it!
I knew it will take long.
but I couldn't get there because tide is on
Chuck!
Come on!
Where are you, chuck!
Chuck!
Who are you?
I am Teddy Daniels.
I'm a cop.
You're a marshal.
that's right.
would you mind ...
take your hands from behind
your back?
Why?
To make sure what you
have hold there does not hurt me
I'm gonna keep this...
If you do not mind.
fine with me.
You're Rachel Solando.
the real one.
did you kill your children?
I never had children.
I was never married.
before I be a patient
in Ashecliff, I worked here.
You were a nurse?
I was a doctor, marshall.
you think i'm crazy?
- No, I ...
- And if I say I'm not crazy ...
well that hardly helps, does it?
That's the Kafkaesque genius of it.
people always tell you you're crazy
and protested, on the contrary,
confirm what they say.
I do not following you.
I'm sorry.
Once you are declared insane,
then anything you do is called
as a part of insanity.
Your reasonable protests
or denial .
valid fears,
paranoia.
survival Instincts
As defense mechanisms.
You're smarter than you look marshall
that's probably not a good thing
Tell me something ...
Yes ...
What happened to you?
I started asking about shipping this
this large amount of sodium .
- And the sodium-based hallucinogens.
- Psychotropic drugs.
And I began to ask about the surgeries, too
Ever heard of transorbital lobotomy?
they cap the patient with electroshocks,
then go through the eye with an ice pick
and pull out some nerve fibers
Makes the patient more obedient.
Tractable
It's barbaric.
Unconscionable
Do you know how pain enters the
body marshal? do you?
Depends on where you hurt.
No, it has nothing to the flesh
The brain controls pain.
The brain controls fear, empathy,
sleep, anger, hunger ... everything.
what If you could control it?
the brain?
To re-create a man,
so he doesn't feel pain
Or love. Or sympathy.
A man who can't be interrogated
because he has no memories to confess
They can never takes
all men memories
Never.
And you know the North Koreans
use american POWs
during brainwashing experiments
they turns soldiers into traitors.
that's what they are doing here.
Creates ghosts and give way in the world.
And do things sane man never do.
that kind of ability, that kind of knowledge
It would take years.
Years of research,
experiments on hundreds of patients.
For 50 years now,
people will look back
and they say ... this place
is where it all began.
The Nazis used the Jews
the Soviets
used prisoners in their own gulags
and we...
We tested patients,
on Shutter Island.
No, they won't ...
no
you do understand
That they can't let you leave?
I'm a federal marshall ...
they can't stop me.
I was a esteemed psychiatrist,
from a respected family.
It did not matter.
let me ask you ...
any past trauma in your life?
yes, why... why that matter?
If a particular event is past
the reason you lost your sanity......
so when they commit you in here
your friends, colleagues will say...
he has cracked.
And who would do it,
after what happened.
That could be said of anyone
- anyone at all.
- The point is they're going to say it about you.
How's your head?
- My head?
- You had funny dreams?
trouble Sleeping, headaches ...
I'm prone to migraine
Jesus!
you haven't taken any pills, no?
- Not even aspire?
- I get a aspirin.
Jesus!
And you ate in the canteen and of drinking
coffee that gave it.
Tell me that even
Smoking Cigars of you.
Not ... no.
I haven't.
It takes between 36 and 48 hours for
neuroleptics narcotics ...
To reach sufficient blood
that you-and take effect.
pulse will become first
Fingers first and then
shall include all labor.
seen any waking nightmares lately,
marshall?
Tell me what's going on in that lighthouse?
Tell me.
brain surgery.
Like, "to open the skull to see
What if we pull on this kind. "..............
that's not different with Nazi's kind
And then they created the ghosts.
Who knows about this?
on the islandm i mean. Who?
Everyone.
Come on, the nurses, the orderlies?
- it's not possible ...
- Everybody.
you can't stay here.
They think i'm dead, that I drowned.
If they come looking for you, they might finf me
I'm sorry, but you have to go.
I'm gonna come back for you.
I will not be here. I move during the day.
new places every night.
but I could come get you
take you out of the island.
Haven't you heard a word I've said?
The only way off the island
is ferry and they control it
You'll never leave here.
I had a friend.
he was with me yesterday,
but we got seperated.
Have you seen him?
marshall ...
You have no friends.
subtitle by
Amir_T6262
There you are.
We've been wondering when
you'd show up
Take a seat.
Come on.
Taking a leisurely stroll? were we?
I just...
just looking around.
Did you enjoy
God's latest gift?
- What?
- The God's gifts.
the violence.
when I came downstaires in my home
and saw a tree in my living room
it reached for me like a divine hand.
God loves violence.
- I hadn't noticed.
- sure you have.
Why else would there be so much of it?
It's in us.
what we are.
we wage war, we burn sacrifices
we pillage and plunder
and treat at the flesh
of our brothers
and why? Because God gave us violence
to wage in his honor.
I thought God gave us moral orders.
There is no moral orders
as pure as this storm.
There's no moral order at all.
there's just this:
can my violence conquer yours?
- I'm not violent.
- You are.
You're violent as they come.
I know, because I am as violent as they come.
From constructred society
we were lifted..............
If I always stood between you and my meal you
would crack my skull with rock and steal my meal
Poor you
Cawley thinks you're harmless, you can be
controled, but I know are different.
- You don't know me.
- Oh but I do.
We've known each other for centuries.
If I am to send my teeth to sank into your eye
right now,
could you stop me before I blinded you?
Give it a try.
That's the spirit.
Where have you been?
Wandering, just looking at your island.
You'll be leaving,
Now that Rachel has been found.
sure.
big meeting
Oh, yes ...
Apparently there was an unidentified man
in ward C yesterday
He subdued a very dangerous patient.
quite handly.
Even so?.........
It seems he had a long concersation with a
paranoid schizophrenic, George Noyce.
This Noyce,
so you said his name was,
- he's delusional, right?
- oh extremely. he can be quite upseting
In fact, two weeks ago, a patient
was so worked up
over one of Noyce's stories
that he beat him up.
Cigarette?
No, thanks.
I quit.
So, you'll taking the ferry?
Absolutely ...
I think we've gotten
all we came here for
"We" Marshall?
Speaking of a ..............
- You've seen him, Doctor?
- Who?
My partner, Chuck.
You don't have a partner, Marshall.
You came here alone.
You know, I've built something valuable here
But valuable things have a way of
being misunderstood in their own time
Everyone wants a quick fix,
they always have
I'm trying to do something that people
that even you don't undersyand
And I'm not going to give up
without a fight
I can see that ...
so tell me again
about your partner.
What partner?
Marshall ...
Going somewhere?
No. Just ... take my way
to ferry.
I'm afraid it's the other side.
If you wait a moment,
I find someone to take you
to the port.
What is this, Doctor?
it's just a sedative?
- It's for precaution.
- precaution?
What are you going to do?
To kill me?
you think you deserve it
for what?
for provoking you?
and forgive me
what doesn't provoke you?
remarks ...
- Words ...
- Nazi !
And that too
And of course, memories, dreams ...
did you knew that the word "trauma" comes
from a Greek word of wound?
And what's the German word for "dream"
is "traumen.
. Traumen......... "
a dream-.
Wounds can creates monsters.
And you ...
you are wounded, Marshall.
I think you're agree,
when you see a monster
you must stop it.
- I agree.
- Yes ...
What are you doing, baby?
You've got to get to the ferry.
No. Not ... no.
If the world thinks that Chuck is dead,
then he is perfect for their experiments.
Only one place they'd take him
You go there and you'll die.
He's my partner. if they're hurting him
holding him against his will, I have to bring him out
I can not lose anyone else.
Do not go there.
Please don 't do this Teddy.
I'm sorry, honey.
I love this because
you gave it to me
But the truth is ...
it's one fucking ugly tie.
No!
Do not move!
Stay where you are.
Are you going to kill me?
No.
I will not kill you.
Why are you all wet, baby?
- What did you say?
- You know exactly what I said.
The rifle's empty by the way.
have a seat
For god's sake dry off
you're going to catch cold
all right.
How badly did you hurt the guard?
I do not know what
are you talking about.
Yes. he's here.
Have Dr.Sheehan take a good look
at your man before you send him up
So, Dr. Shehan ...
He came on the ferry
this morining.
Not exactly.
You blew up my car.
I really loved that car.
sorry to hear about that.
Tremors are getting pretty bad.
How are the hallucinations?
. Go away, Teddy ....................
. this place is gonna be the end of you ..
- Not bad.
- they'll get worse.
I know.
Dr. Solando ...
she told me about neuroleptics.
did she now?
and when was this?
I found her doctor,in a cave on the cliffs.
But you won't get her.
I don't doubt it.
considerations are not real.
But your hallucinations are
more severe than I thought.
You are not on neuroleptics.
You are not on neuroleptics
as a matter of fact
Then what the fuck is this?
Huh, what the fuck is this?
Withdrawal.
Withdrawal?
From what? I haven't even had a goddamned
drink since we got on this island.
Chlorpromazine
I'm not a fan of pharmacology
but I have to see in your case ...
- Clorpro ... like you said?
- Chlorpromazine.
the same thing we've
been giving you for the last 24 months.
So in the past two years
you have had somebody in Boston
who gave me drugs.........
Not Boston.
Here.
You've been here for two years.
a patient of this institutions.
After everythings I see here, Doctor,
You really thinks you can
convince me I'm crazy?
You know what kind of people we are dealing?
I'm U.S. marshal
You were a U.S. marshal
Here's a copy of your intake form
you broke into ward C for.
Proof of the 67th patient
If you'd gotten to the mainland,
you could have blown the lid off this place.
- wait ...wait
- But somehow
and yet you couldn't find time
to look at it yet. read it
Go ahead
The patient is highly intelligent
highly delusional.
Decorated army veteran.
prisoned for the
liberation of Dachav.
Former U.S. marshal
known proclivity for violence.
shown no remorse for his crime because
his denial is such
that no crime ever took place
highly developed and fantastical
narratives which preclude facing
the truth of his actions...
I am tired of this bullshits.
Where's my partner?
Where's Chuck?
Where is he?
Let's try this in another way.
your wife's maiden name was
"Chana" am I correct?
- Not even talk about her!
- I'm afraid I have to.
Notice anything these four names have in common?
the rule 4.
- Andrew, what do you see?
- If you done anything
- to my partner, Doctor, It is a violation ...
- Focus, Andrew. What do you see?
the names ...
have the same letters.
Edward Daniels has exactly same
13 letters
As Andrew Laeddis.
the same as Rachel and Solando
and Dolore Chan. All names
- Are anagrams of each other.
- Tactics of intimidation........
it doesn't work on me.
You came here for the truth.
Here it is.
Your name is Andrew Laeddis.
the 67th patient at Ashecliffe
is you, Andrew.
Bullshit
You were committed here by
court order 24 months ago.
your crime's terrible.
One you can't forgieve yourself.
So you invented
another self.
Let us return to the facts.
And have created a story in which
you're not a murderer, you are hearless.......
you are a U.S marshal.
only here in Ashkliff
because of a case
and you've uncovered conspiracy
So that anything we tell you about
who you are, what you've done
you can dismiss as lies, Andrew
My name is Edward Daniels.
I've been hearing this fantasy
for two years. I know every details.
Patient 67. Storm.
Rachel Solando.
your missing partner
Dreams you have every night.
You were at Dachave,
But it could not have killed any guards.
I wish i could let you just
live in your fantasy world
I really do.
But are violent, trained, dangerous.
You're the most dangerous patient we have.
You've injured all of the guards
Other patients.
Two weeks ago
you attacked George Noyce.
I did so something!.............................
- You have ............
- off course I didn't.
Give me one reason
why i even touch him.
Because he called you Laeddis
and you do anything not to be him
I have a transcript of that conversation
you had with Noyce yesterday .
This is about you and Laeddis
That's all it's ever been about
This says it's about
"me and Laeddis".
When you've asked him what happened
to his face,
said, and I quote again,
"You did it".
- he meant it was my fault he ...
- you almost killed him.
The warden and the board of overseas
are determined that something be done it's been decided
nevertheles we can bring you back in sanity now
right now
Permanent measures will be taken to ensure
you can't hurt anyone ever again
they lobotomine you, Andrew.
do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I understand just fine
If , if I don't play along
with your little game here
Dr. Naehring will turn me into
one of his ghosts.
What about my partner?
you mean a U.S. marshal
is a  defense mechanism?
Hey, boss .
What the fuck is going on here?
you're working for him?
I'm sorry about that
someone had to stay with you, keep you safe
You've been watch me, right?
watch me every minute.
Who ... who are you?
Who are you?
Tell me.
don't you recognize me, Andrew?
I've been you primary psychiatrist
for the last two years.
I am Lester Sheehan.
And I told you about my wife ...
- I know.
- I climbed a cliff to save you.
I trusted you. I risked
everything, after you. Everything!
I know, boss `.
we're running out of time here, Andrew,
I swore before the entire board of
overseas that I could construct
The most radical, role-play
ever in history of psychiatry and
that will bring you back.
I thought if we let you play
this out
we could get you to see how
untrue how impossible it is
we've had to tun of the place for two days
Tell me, where are the Nazi experiments
The satanic O.R.'s
Andrew, listen to me.
If we fail on you
then everything we've tried
to do here will be discredited.
Everything.
We are on the first line of a war, Andrew
and right now, in this place
it comes down to you
Do not move!
- Andrew, no!
- My name is Teddy Daniels.
This one is loaded.
I can tell from the weight.
I see. and that's your firearm marshall
You're sure?
There's a dent in the barrel from
the day Philip Stacks shot at me.........
and the bullet ricocheted. You're not going to mind-fuck me out of this doc
Then blast away, because that's the
only way you're ever getting off this island
Andrew, please don't.
My gun ...
What have you done to
my goddamned gun.
It's a toy, Andrew.
we're telling you the truth.
Dolores was insane. Manic-depressive.
suicidal.
You drank. stay away.
ignored what everyone told you.
You moved in that lake house after
she, purposely,
set your city apartment on fire
Andrew... Andrew
stop it
you're lying...
These are your children.
Serena ...
- Henry ...
- I have no children.
Your wife drowned them
in the cabin by the lake.
And here, the little girl,
you dream about
every night.
I never had a daughter.
the one who tells you over and over that
you should saved her
save them all
Your daughter ...
Her name is Rachel. are you going to deny
that she ever lived?
Andrew, are you?
I'm so sorry, honey ..
I told you not to coming here.
I told you ...
this would be the end of you.
I came back.
we got him
just out of Oklahoma.
must stopped ten places
between here and Tulsa
I could sleep for a week
Dolores?
Honey ...
Why are you all wet?
I missed you.
I want to go home.
You're home!
Where are the kids?
they're in school.
It's Saturday, honey.
school's not in on Saturday
my school is
Oh my God!
My God!
God!
Oh, Good God, no!
Come on!
Please, God, no.
No!
Let put them in the kitchen.
let's dry them off ...
change their clothes ...
They'll be our living dolls
Tomorrow we can take them on a picnic.
If you ever loved me , Dolores ...
Please stop talking
I need you to love me.
I need you to free me!
Honey ...
We'll give them baths...
- I love you so much Dolores
- And I love you. I love you.
Andrew ...
Andrew, can you hear me?
Rachel!
Rachel, Rachel ...
Rachel.
Rachel who?
Rachel Laeddis ...
My daughter.
Why are you here?
Because I killed my wife.
and why did you do that?
she murdered our children.
And she told me to let her go.
- Who is Teddy Daniels?
- he doesn't exist.
Neither Rachel Solando.
I made them up.
Why?
we need to hear you say it.
After she trie to kill
her for the first time,
Dolores told me that ...
she has an insect ...
living inside her brain.
she could feel it ...
walking cross
her skull ...
pulling the wires,
just for fun.
she told me that.
she told me but i didn't listen
I loved her so much.
Why did you make them up?
Because I can not take knowing
that Dolores killed our children.
I killed them, because
i didn't get her some help.
I killed them...
Here's my theory, Andrew.
we broke through once before,
nine months ago,
and then you regressed.
- I do not remember that.
- I know.
you reset, Andrew.
like a tape
playing over and over on an endless loop
I hope that what we've done will be enough
to stop it from happening again
I need to know ...
that you have accepted the reality.
You came after me, Doctor?
You tried to help me when no one else would
My name is Andrew Laeddis ...
And I murdered my wife
in the spring of 1952.
how we doing this morning?
good.
and You?
can't complain.
So what's our next move?
You tell me.
We've gotta get off this rock,
Chuck.
Back to the mainland. Whatever the
hell is going on here is bad.
Do not worry, partner.
I'm gonna catch this
that............ is too small for them.
Yes, we are.
aren't we?
You know this place makes
me wonder
Yeah? What's that boss?
which would be worse?
To live as a monster ...
or to die as a good man.
Teddy?
subtitle by
Amir_T6262