Subtitles by
Sub Conqueror
Pull yourself together Teddy.
Pull yourself together.
It's just water.
It's alotta water.
Come on.
- You okay boss?
- Yeah, fine, Im just...I just can't-
I just can't stomach the water.
- You're my new partner?
- That's right.
Not the best way to meet with
my head half way down the toilet.
Doesn't exactly square with
Teddy Daniels, the man, the legend, I'll give you that.
The legend?
What the hell are you boys smoking
over there in Portland, anyway?
Seattle.
I came from the office in Seattle.
How long you been with Marshals?
Four years.
- So you know how small it is?
- Sure.
What about you? Got a girl? Married?
I was.
She died.
- Jesus ..., I didn't...
- Don't worry about it.
There was a fire at the apartment
building, while I was at work.
Four People died.
It was the smoke that got her,
not the fire.
- That's important.
-  Sorry boss.
Where are my goddamn cigarettes?
Here, have one of mine.
I could swear that they were in my jacket
before I...
Government employees, they'll rob you blind.
Thanks.
Give you a briefing
about the institution before you left?
All I know is it's a mental hospital.
For the criminally insane.
Well, if it was just folks running around hearing voices
and chasing after butterflies,
they wouldn't need us.
- Yeah
- That's where were headed?
- Yep.
The other side of the island is rock bluffs,
all the way down to the edge of the water.
The dock, it's the
only way on, or off.
We will be casting off as soon as
you two are ashore.
I'd appreciate it if ya hurry up about it
- Why?
- Storm's coming.
Never seen a Marshals'
badge before.
I'm Deputy Warden
McPherson gentlemen.
Welcome to Shutter Island.
I'll be the one taking you up to Ashecliff.
Your boys seem a little on edge,
Mr McPherson.
Right now Marshal, we all are.
Electrified perimeter.
How can you tell?
I've seen something like it before.
All right, you gentlemen will be accorded
all the help we can give.
But during your stay you will
obey protocol, is that understood?
Absolutely.
The red brick building on my right
is ward A, the male ward.
Ward B, the female ward, is the one
on your left.
Ward C, is that building on the bluffs,
an old civil war fort, the most dangerous patients
are housed there.
Admittance to ward C is forbidden without
the written consent and
physical presence of both myself and Dr Cawley.
Is that understood?
You act like insanity is catching.
You are hereby required to surrender
your firearms.
Mr McPherson, we are duly appointed
federal Marshals,
we are required to carry our
firearms with us at all times.
Executive order 319 of the Federal Code of
Penitentiaries states that
When inside the penitentiary,
the officers of that institution
have the final authority.
Gentlemen, you will not get through this
gate with your firearms.
Ok, now the official stuff is done,
come on boys.
What do you say we go find Dr Cawley?
- So when did she escape?
- This prisoner?
I'm afraid Dr Cawley will have to
fill you in on the situation.
Protocol.
Correctional officers at a mental institution,
that's a weired sight,
if you don't mind me saying.
It's the only facility of it's kind in the U.S.
Even in the world. We take only the most dangerous,
damaged patients.
Ones no other hospitals can manage.
And it's all due to Dr Cawley.
He's created something really unique here.
It's a hospital, for people in society who normally ...
IDs gentlemen.
Show your badges, gentlemen.
Dr Cawley's been consulted
numerous times.
- By Scotland Yard, MI 5, the OSS ...
- Why?
What do you mean?
What would intelligence agencies want
to consult a psychatrist about?
I guess you'll have to ask him.
- Marshal Daniels.
- Doctor.
Marshal Aule.
- Thank you deputy warden, that will be all.
- Yes, sir.
Pleasure, gentlemen.
He had a lot to say about you.
McPherson is a good man,
he believes in the work we do here.
And what would that be exactly?
A moral fusion between law and
order and clinical care.
Pardon me Doc,
a what between what and what?
Those paintings are quite accurate.
It used to be the kind of patients we
deal with here, were
shackled and left in their own filth,
they were beaten,
as if whipping them bloody would drive the psychosis out.
We drove screws into their brains, we
submerged them in icy water until they lost consciousness,
or...even drowned.
- And now?
- We treat them.
Trying to heal, try to cure
And if that fails, at least we provide them
with a measure of comfort in their lives, calm.
These are all...
violent offenders, right?
I mean, they've hurt people,
- murdered them in some cases.
- In almost all cases. Yes.
Then personally Doctor, I'd have to
say... screw their sense of calm.
It's my job to treat my patients, not their victims. I'm not here to judge.
- So this female prisoner ...
- Patient.
Excuse me, patient,
one Rachel Solando.
- Escaped sometime in the last 24 hours.
- Last night.
Between 10 and midnight.
- Is she considered dangerous?
- You could say that.
She killed all three of her children.
She drowned them in the lake, behind the house.
She took them out one by one and held their
heads under till they died.
Then she brought them back inside and
arranged them around the kitchen table.
She ate a meal there
before a neighbour dropped by.
And what about the husband?
He died on the beaches of Normandy,
she's a war widow.
She starved herself when first she came here,
she insisted the children weren't dead.
- Sorry doctor, you don't happen to have an aspirin, do you?
- Prone to headaches Marshal?
Sometimes, but today I'm a...
- little more prone to seasickness.
-Ah, dehydration ...
- You allright boss?
- Yeh.
In that case you're quite right,
the simpler the better.
Ah, thanks so much.
Rachel, still believes
the children are alive.
She also believes this place is her home
in the Berkshires.
You're kidding me.
She never once in two years acknowledged
that she is in an institution.
She believes we're all ...
deliverymen, milkmen, postal workers.
To sustain the illusion that her children never died
she created an elaborate fictional structure,
she gives us all parts to play in that fiction.
- So have you, you searched the grounds yet?
- The warden and his men scoured the island.
Not a trace.
What's more disturbing, is that we don't know
how she got out of her room.
It was locked from the outside.
and the only window's barred.
It's as if she evaporated straight
through the walls.
Brought her right back here after
group therapy, locked her in,
I came back for midnight rounds,
she was gone.
Seriously doctor, how is it possible that
the truth never gets through to her?
I mean she's in a mental institution, right?
Seems like something you'd
notice from time to time.
- How many pairs of shoes do the patients get?
- Two pairs.
Sanity is not a choice, Marshal.
You can't just choose to get over it.
So ... she left here barefoot?
Come on doc, she can't get ten
yards in that terrain.
Marshal?
That is definitely Rachel's
handwriting.
- I have no idea what the " law of 4" is though.
- Not a psychiatric term?
I'm afraid not.
Who is 67?
Fuck if I know.
I'd have to say that's quite
close to my clinical conclusion.
So you think it's just
random scribblings?
No, not at all. Rachel is smart,
brilliant in fact.
- This paper could be important.
- Excuse me Doctor, but ...
- were gonna have to hold onto this.
- Of course.
And you say she had to come through here.
After lights out, the orderlies play
cards in here.
Last night there were 7 men sitting
at the base of those stairs playing stud poker.
And yet somehow, Rachel managed
to slip past them.
Why?
How? She turns invisible?
Doctor, we gonna need access to the personal files
of all the medical staff-
The nurses, the guards, the orderlies and,
- anyone who was working here that night.
- We take your request under consideration.
This is not a request, Doctor.
This is a federal facility
and a dangerous prisoner ...
- Patient.
- Has escaped now. You will comply or....
- All I can say is that I will see what I can do.
Doctor, were gonna need to speak with the staff,
do you understand?
I'll assemble them in the
common room after dinner.
If you have any further questions
feel free to join the deputy warden in the search.
It's 11 miles to the nearest land
and the water is freezing.
The current was strong last night
the tide pushin in.
She'd have drowned or been crushed on
the rocks and her body would have washed back up on shore.
What about those caves down there
have you checked them?
No way she could get there.
The base of those cliffs are covered
in poison ivy, live oak, sumac
and a thousand plants with thorns
as big as my dick.
You said yourself Marshal,
she's got no shoes.
All right,
let's check the other side!
- What's that tower?
- It's an old lighthouse.
The guards already searched inside it.
- What's in there? more patients?
- Sewage treatment facility.
It's gettin dark soon.
I'm calling this off for the night.
Let's go, boys!
- You were on watch on the landing, huh?
- Yes.
Could nobody get in or out of their room
on that corridor without me seeing.
Ok Rachel Solando.
Who else does she have to pass
to get down here?
Me.
Glen Miga.
- Sir, I aint seen nothing.
- And you were at your post all night?
Yeh. But I didn't see a thing.
Glen?
Tell me the truth.
I .. I.. maybe went to the bathroom.
- What? You breached protocol? Christ ...
- I wasn't gone longer than a minute.
All right, let's back up here,
let's all just back up.
Mrs Solando was put in her room for lights out.
Does anybody here know what she did
before that?
Anyone?
Come on, anyone. anyone anyone.
She was in a group therapy session.
Oh.. Did anything unusual occur?
Define "unusual".
- Excuse me.
- It's a mental institution, Marshal,
for the criminally insane.
"Usual"  isn't a big part of our day.
I will rephrase.
Did anything happen last night
during group therapy, that was more...
- let's say, I don't know- memorable than ...
- Normal?
Exactly!
No, sorry.
Did Mrs. Solando say anything
during group therapy?
She was worried about the rain.
And she hated the food here.
Complained constantly,
last night included.
So ... you were there,
was there a doctor present?
Yes, Dr Sheehan led the discussion.
Dr Sheehan?
Yes, he was running the session.
He's Rachel's "primary".
The psychaiatrist who directly
oversees her care.
Were gonna need to speak with Dr Sheehan.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
He left on the ferry this morning.
His vacation was already planned.
He'd been putting it off too long.
You're in a state of lockdown.
A dangerous patient has escaped,
and you let her primary doctor
leave on vacation?
Of course, he's a doctor.
Do you have the phone number for
where he's gone?
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Anybody there?
I'm sorry sir, but it's all down,
all the lines.
The storm's hitting the
mainland like a hammer.
If you get it working come find me immediately.
The marshal's need to make an important call.
Yes sir.
I'm afraid I have evening rounds, in the wards.
But I'll be having drinks and a cigar at
my house, around 9.
If you care to drop by.
Good, we can talk then, right?
We have been talking, Marshal.
Gotta say, I'm thinking I got
into the wrong line of public service.
It is a little overwhelming.
It was constructed during the civil war.
The same time as the military fort
housing ward C.
This is the original commander's quarters
when uncle sam got the bill.
The commander was courtmartialled.
I can see why.
Nice music. who is that? Brahms?
No.
It's Mahler.
Quite right, Marshal.
Forgive me, gentlemen,
My colleague, Dr Jeremiah Naehring.
Quartet for Piano and Strings,
in A minor.
- Your poison, gentlemen?
- Right, if you've got it.
Soda and ice please, thanks.
Oh, you don't indulge in alcohol?
I am surprised.
Isn't it common for men in your
profession to imbibe?.
Common enough, and
and yours?
- I'm sorry?
- Your profession, doctor, psychiatry ...
I've always heared it's overrun
with boozers and drunks.
Not that I've noticed.
What's that? Icetea in your glass there?
Excellent Marshal.
You have outstanding defense mechanisms.
You must be quite adapt at the interrogations. Humm
Men like you ... are my specialty.
Men of violence.
Now that's a hell of assumption to make...
No assumption. Not at all. You misunderstand me,
I said - you are men of violence.
I'm not accusing you of being, violent men,
that's quite different.
Please, please, edify us Doctor.
You both served overseas, huh?
Not much of a stretch Doc, for all you know
we were both paper pushers over there.
No, you were not.
Since the schoolyard, neither
of you has ever walked away from a physical conflict.
No, not cause you enjoyed it,
but because retreat isn't something you considered an option.
We weren't raised to run Doc.
Ah, yes... raised,
and who raised you, Marshal?
Me?
Wolves.
Ah, ha, very impressive defense mechanisms.
Do you believe in God, Marshal?
No I'm quite serious.
Speaks German
Have you ever um seen ... a death camp, Doctor? (speaks German)
(translation) I have, I was there, at the liberation of Dachau
(Trans) His English is very good, almost flawless.
His english, really is very good.
You hit the consonants a tad hard, though.
You're a German?
- Is legal immigration a crime, Marshal?
- Oh I don't know doctor, you tell us.
Now listen, we gonna need those files on Sheehan
and the rest of staff as well.
No personal files will be released to you
Period.
- We gonna need those files.
- Out of the question.
Bullshit, out of the question,
bullshit.
Who the hells is in charge here anyway? huh?
Dr Naehring acts as liaison to
our board of overseers.
He relayed your request and it's been refused.
Refused? They don't have the authority to refuse.
And neither do you, sir.
Marshal, continue your investigation
and we will do all we can to help.
This investigation is over.
Were gonna file our reports
and were gonna hand it over to...
- Hoover's boys.
- Hoover's boys, that's right.
Were taken the ferry back in the morning.
Come on Chuck.
Nice night.
You'll be bunking in the orderlies quarters.
Hey boss? ... We're really packin it in?
Why?
I guess, I dunno, I just...
never really quit anything before.
We haven't heard the truth once yet Chuck.
Listen, Rachel Solando did not slip out of
a locked cell barefoot without any help.
I think she had alot of help.
Maybe Cawley sitting up in his mansion
right now,
rethinking his whole attitude.
- Maybe in the morning...
- You're bluffing?
I didn't say that.
I found a whole stock of these, Teddy.
Jesus, are you ever sober anymore?
I killed alot of people in the war.
Is that why you drink?
Are you real?
No.
She's still here.
Who?
Rachel?
She never left.
Remember when we stayed in the cabin
in the summer Teddy?
We were so happy.
She's here.
You can't leave.
I'm not gonna leave.
I love you so much.
- I'm just bones in a box, Teddy.
- No.
I am.
You have to wake up.
I won't go.
You're here.
I'm not.
You have to face that.
But she is,
and so is he.
Who?
Laeddis.
I have to go.
No, no please...please, let me hold onto you.
- Just a little bit longer please.
- Oh, Teddy ...you have to.
Let me go.
I can't.
Ain't gonna be no ferry in this shit.
Doctor.
Doctor, Doctor.
We need to interview the patients who
were in Rachel's group therapy session.
I thought your investigation was finished?
It's not like we can take the ferry.
And now was Rachel recieving any
other treatment for her illnesses?
Do you know the state of
mental health field these days, gentlemen?
No, not a clue doctor.
War.
The old school believes in
surgical intervention.
Psychosurgery.
Procedures like the transorbital lobotomy.
Some say that the patients become reasonable,
docile, others say they become zombies.
- And the new school?
- Psycho-pharmacology.
A new drug has just been approved-
Proflorazine.
That relaxes psychotic patients.
You could say tames them.
- And which school are you, Doc?
- Me?
I have this radical idea that if you treat a
patient with respect,
listen to him.
Try and understand,
you just might reach him.
- These patients?
- Even these.
What should be a last resort,
is becoming a first response.
Give them a pill and put them in a corner,
and it all goes away.
Rachel Solando was a on a combination of drugs,
meant to keep her from becoming violent
and it was only intermittently effective.
The greatest obstacle to her recovery was
her refusal to face what she had done.
"Was"
Is there a reason you keep referring to
your patient in the past tense, Doctor?
Look outside, Marshal.
Why do you think?
Next up is Peter Breene. Assaulted
his father's nurse with broken glass.
Nurse survived, but
her face was permanently disfigured.
Can't wait.
She'd smile at me.
She's so sweet.
But ... you could see it in her eyes,
she liked to be naked.
To...to suck cock.
Ok Mr Breene.
And then she asked me if she can have
a glass of water.
Alone in the kitchen?
Like that's no big deal?
- Why was that a big deal?
-  It was obvious.
She wanted me to pull out my thing so she
could laugh at it.
Mr Breene,
we need to ask you some questions, ok?
When I cut her she screamed.
But ...
She scared me.
What did she expect?
Interesting.
But we are here to talk
Rachel Solando, OK?
Rachel Solando ...
Did you know she drowned her own kids?
She drowned her kids.
This is, this a sick fucking world
we live in. I'll tell you that ...
They should be gassed,
all of them... the retards, the killers,
the niggers,  you kill your own kid-
gas the bitch.
Could you.. stop that?
- That nurse?
- Please. Stop that.
That nurse, that nurse maybe,
maybe she had kids, huh?
A husband,
just trying to make ends meet,
to have a normal life ...
and it says in your file, that
you tore her face off, didn't you?
Congratulations, no more normal
for her, not ever again, no.
Do you know what she was afraid of?
You.
Could you stop that, please?
Stop that!
Please ... stop!
- You know a patient by the name Andrew Laeddis?
- No! No!
I want to go back.
Well I'll never get out of here.
I'm not sure that I should.
Excuse me for saying this.
- Miss Kearns
- Mrs
Mrs Kearns.
But you seem,
quite quite normal,
I mean compared
with the other patients here.
Well, I have my dark days,
I suppose everybody does.
The difference is that most people don't kill
their husbands with an axe.
Although personally I think if a
man beats you and fucks
half the women he sees
and no one will help you,
axing him isn't the least understandable
thing you could do.
Maybe you shouldn't get out.
And what would I do if I did?
I don't know the world anymore
They say there are
bombs that can reduce whole
cities to ash
And ah, what do they call "televisions",
voices and faces coming from a box.
I hear enough voices already.
What can you tell us about Rachel?
Umm not much, she... she keeps to herself.
She believed her kids were alive.
She thought she was still living
in the Berkshires and we were all her neighbours,
- the, the, the milkmen, postmen.
- Deliverymen
And Dr Sheehan was there that night?
Yes, um,
he talked about anger.
Tell me about him.
What's he like?
He is a . ..
Ok... nice.
Not hard on the eyes as my mother would say
Did he ever make a pass at you?
No
No, Dr. Sheehan is a good doctor, he wouldn't ...
Um, could I, could I have a glass of water, please?
No problem.
Thank you, Marshal.
I have just one more question for you
Mrs Kearns.
Did you ever meet a patient
named Andrew Laeddis?
No.
Never heard of him.
She was coached.
She used practically the same words as
Cawley and the nurse.
- It's like she'd been told exactly what to say.
- Who's Andrew Laeddis?
You asked every one of those patients back there
about him. Who is he?
What the hell, boss, I'm your partner
for the Christ's sake!
We just met, Chuck.
Been on the beat for a long time.
You got a duty, you got a career
and what I'm doing,
it's not exactly by the book.
I don't, I don't give a damn about by the book, boss
I just what to know what the hell is going on.
When this case came over the wires,
- I requested it, specifically, do you understand?
- Why?
Andrew Laeddis,
was the maintenance man in the apartment
building where my wife and I lived.
Ok.
He was also a firebug.
Andrew Laeddis lit the match,
that caused the fire that killed my wife.
Let em out.
What happened to Laeddis?
Got away with it. Laeddis got away it
and then he disappeared.
About a year ago I opened up the
paper and there he is.
Ugly looking son of a bitch.
Huge scar from his right temple
down to his left lip.
Eyes different colours,
not the type of face you'd forget.
He'd burned down a schoolhouse,
killed 2 people.
He said voices told him to do it.
First he went to prison
and then he got transferred here.
- Then what?
- Then nothing.
He vanished like he never existed,
no record whatsoever.
Pretty sure he's not in ward B,
that leaves ward C.
Or he could be dead.
So could Rachel Solando for that matter.
Lot of places to hide a body here.
Only one place
no one would really notice.
That patient, Bridget Kearne,
when she sent me for water,
she said something to you back there, didn't she?
No.
Come on boss!
She wrote it.
Boss!
We gotta get in there, it's turning
into fucking Kansas out here.
All right. Now
Let's go!
Watch out!
Jesus!
Come on! Go there.
- God.
- Jesus Christ,........ dammit.
- Are you okay boss?
- Yeh. that's all right.
So if Laeddis is here,
What are you going to about it?
I'm not here to kill Leaddis.
If it were my wife
I'd kill him...twice.
When we got through the gates of Dachau,
the SS guards surrendered.
The Commandant tried to kill himself
before we got there,
but he..he botched it.
Took him an hour to die.
When I went outside
I saw all the bodies on the ground.
Too many to count.
Too many to imagine.
So yeah, then
the guards surrendered, we took
their guns and we lined them up.
It wasn't warfare it was, .....
it was murder.
I've had enough of killing.
That's not why I'm here.
So what is this all about?
After Laeddis vanished,
I started doing some checking
on Ashecliff,
lot of people know about this place, but no
one wants to talk, you know, it's like,
it's like they're scared of something.
You know this place is funded by a
special grant,
from the House on
American Activities Committee.
HOUAC? And how exactly are we fighting
the commies from an island in Boston Harbor?
By conducting experiments on the mind.
At least that's my guess.
And you think thats going on here?
Like I said, no one would talk, right?
Until I found somebody
who used to be a patient here.
The guy's name is George Noyce.
Nice college kid,
socialist.
He got offerred some money for some psych study.
Guess what they were testing?
- Toothpaste
- So he starts seeing dragons everywhere.
He almost beats his professor to death,
ends up here in Ashecliff.
Ward C.
They release him after 1 year, right?
What does he do?
Two weeks on the mainland
he walks into a bar,... stabs three men to death.
His lawyer pleads insanity
but Noyce ...Noyce he
stands up in the courtroom and
he he begs the judge,
for the electric chair.
Anywhere but a
mental hospital.
Judge gives him life in Dedham Prison.
- And you found him?
- Yeh, I've found him.
Well,  ...  he's... he's a mess.
- But it is pretty clear from what he tells me.
- What?
They're experimenting on people here.
I don't know boss.
- How do you believe a crazy guy.
- That's the beauty of it.
Crazy people are a perfect subject.
they talk, but nobody listens.
I stood in Dachau.
We saw what human beings are capable
of doing to each other, right?
For Christ sake we fought a goddam war
to stop them,
and now I find out it may be happening here...
On our soil,
No
So what are you really here to do, Ted?
I'm going to get the proof.
I'm gonna go back and I'm gonna blow
the lid off this place.
That's it.
Wait a minute.
You started asking around about Ashecliff.
Waiting for a chance to get out here
then suddenly they need a US marshal?
I got lucky, there was a patient escape
it was the perfect excuse.
No, no, no boss
Luck doesn't work that way.
The world doesn't work that way.
They got electrified fence around a septic facility.
Ward C is inside a Civil War fort?
A chief of staff with ties to the OSS
Funding from HOUAC?
I mean Jesus Christ! Everything about this place
stinks of  government arse.
- What If they wanted you here?
- Bullshit.
- You were asking questions.
Bullshit, we came here for Rachel Solando?
Where..where is one shred of evidence that she even existed?
There is no way they could have known
I would be assigned to this case, there's no way.
What if you were looking into them and
they were looking into you.
All they had to do
is a fake an escape to get you here.
And now they have you and now.
they have us both, here, now.
Marshal, are you over here?
This is Deputy Warden McPherson.
Marshal!
How about that They found us huh?
It's an island boss There always gonna find us.
I know you're in there.
Were gettin off of this godddam island,
you and me.
Come on!
- Come on!
- Go!
Get dryed off,
Dr Cawley wants to talk to you. Now!
And hurry up, this thing is turning into
to a goddam hurricane.
I dropped those suits off to be cleaned.
It should be ready by tomorrow.
That is if we all haven't washed away first.
Speaking of which, well I'm afraid your... a smokes were
pretty much done for.
So ...
It's our only choice, huh?
I have something really nice in prison grey,
that don't work for you?
Now that you mention it, these are just fine.
That's why I must repeat my insistence
that all ward C patients
be placed in manual restraints.
If the facility floods, they'll drown,
you know that.
- That would take a lot of flooding.
- We are on an island,
in the middle of the ocean,
during a hurricane,
a lot of flooding seems like a
distinct possibility.
It's a gamble Steven,
say the power fails
There's a backup generator.
And if that goes? The cell doors
will open.
Where are they going to go?
They can't just hop a ferry, scoot over
to the mainland and wreak havoc.
You're quite right. There far more
likely to wreak havoc right here on us.
If they're manacled to the floor, they'll die.
24 human beings.
And you can live with that, can you?
Frankly, if it were up to me,
I'd put all 42 in ward A and B in
manual restraints as well.
Excuse me.
- Marshal.
- I'm sorry doctor, I just have one quick question.
Yes, I will be with you in a moment.
We spoke this morning about Rachel Solando's note,
The law of 4, I loved that.
You said you had no idea what
that second line could refer to, correct?
Who is 67?
Yes, I'm afraid I still don't,
None of us do.
- Ah huh,
nothing comes to mind.
Nothing?
Because I believed I just heard
you say that there are
24 patients in ward C
and 42 patients in wards A and B.
Which means there's a total of what,
66 patients at this facility.
That is correct, yes.
So it seems that
Rachel Solando was suggesting
that you have a 67th patient doctor.
- But I'm afraid we don't.
- This is ridiculous.
- What are you doing here?
- We are doing our goddam job.
Didn't McPherson tell you the good news?
No, what's the good news, doctor?
Rachel's been found.
She's here.
Safe and sound.
There's not a mark on her.
Who are these men?
Why are they in my house?
Police officers Rachel.
They ... have a few questions.
Ma'am.
There has been a sighting of a known
communist,
subversive in this area
passing out literature.
Here?
In this neighbourhood?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Now if you could tell us what you did yesterday,
where you were,
it would really help us narrow down our search.
Yes.
Well, I ...
I made breakfast for Jim
and the children,
and then I ...
packed Jim's lunch
and he left.
Then I sent the children off to school.
And then ...
I decided to take a long swim in the lake.
I see.
And after that?
After that...
I thought of you.
I ... I'm sorry ma'am,
I..I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't you know how lonely I've been Jim?
You're gone.
You're dead.
I cry everyday.
How am I supposed to survive?
God.
Rachel ... it'll be all right.
I'm so sorry but ...
Everything will be all right? Okay?
I buried you.
I buried an empty casket. Your body
rained down lots of flesh, splashing into the sea.
Eaten by sharks.
My Jim's dead,
so who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you? Who are you?
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't want to interrupt, I thought
she might tell you something, but ...
we found her down by the lighthouse,
skipping stones.
We've no idea how she got out there.
I'm going to have to ask you to go down into the basement.
There's food, water, and cots
It's the safest place to be-
when the hurricane hits.
Are you all right?
You look pale.
I'm fine, it's just a...
Boss, are you okay?
It's so goddam bright? isn't it?
Photo-sensitivity, headache sometimes?
Marshal, are you having a migraine?
I'll be allright.
What's wrong with him?
- Take these, Marshal. Couple
of hours, you'll be as clear as a bell.
What's wrong with him?
- He's having a migraine.
Imagine someone sawed open your head and
filled it with razors then shook it
as hard as they could.
Take these pills, Marshal.
- I...I don't  want.
- It'll stop the pain. Take the pills.
He's going to need to lie down.
- Careful.
- Allright.
Gonna be ok, relax.
- Who is that?
- Him?
That's the Warden.
Don't you worry about him, allright?
Looks like an ex-military prick.
You know what,
I aint even gonna argue with you on that one.
You should have saved me.
You should have saved all of us.
Hey buddy, ......... hey.
Laeddis.
Yes.
Hi, buddy.
No hard feelings, right?
No hard feelings.
A little something for later.
Cause I know how much you need it.
Clock's ticking my friend.
Were running out of time.
Give me a hand here.
I could get into trouble.
Am I dead?
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you save me?
I tried, I wanted to
but by the time I got there,
it was too late.
See?
Aren't they beautiful?
Why are you all wet.....baby?
Laeddis isn't dead.
He isn't gone.
He's still here.
I know.
You need to find him Teddy.
You need to find him and you kill him dead.
It's ok.
Ward A
I got it
The generator rooms' flooded.
Are you okay boss?
That goddam migraine.
Back up generators' failed,
whole place is gone crazy.
What do you want to do?
Christ!
No no no
Put it down.
Now.
Do you think the whole electrical system is fried?
I'd say it's is a good possibility.
All the electronic security ...
The fences, the gates, the doors.
Nice day for a stroll
don't you think?
To ward C for example.
Maybe well run into Andrew Leaddis.
The guy I told you about, George Noyce?
He told me this is where they keep
the worst ones.
The guys even the other inmates
are scared of.
Did Noyce give you anything on the layout?
Not really.
All he remembered was people
screamin day and night, no windows,
and iron bars everywhere.
Jesus Christ!
First time
on Ward C huh?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yeah we heard stories, but ...
-  Trust me, son you haven't heard shit.
We got most of the bugsies locked down now.
But some of them are still loose.
If you see one don't try
to restrain 'em yourselves.
These fuckers'll kill you.
Clear?
Get your asses moving then,
go on.
He's here.
Laeddis.
I can feel him.
Tag! You're in!
Ted!
Hey! Hey!