Smoking causes cancer. Smoking kills.
Consumption of alcohol
is injurious to health.
Be safe. Don't drink and drive.
Drug usage is injurious to health
and is a criminal offense.
The paintings you drew
Are etched in my heart
Even the rain cannot wash them away
A day filled with laughter
And joy with you
There is no happiness
That can surpass that, oh dear!
Even the mirror looks at you
To see its beauty
The breeze will sing to you what I can't
Your words bring life to me
The amethyst flower and our native music
Fill me with happiness when I sing
To my dear love, my girl…
Girl! Sing a song with "girl" in it.
Hey there, my chubby girl
Can't you see my eyes
Are calling out to you?
Did my mustache prick you
Oh, diamond rose?
Does she lovingly call you Tom?
-Tom!
Now, Maharaja will sing a song
with the word "Tom" in it.
Go ahead, sing. "Tom."
Tom…
-Yes, Tom.
-Tom…
Yes. The word is "Tom."
-Tom.
-Tom?
-Yes.
-Tom…
-Tomorrow, I want a day off.
-What?
-You want a day off?
-Yes.
-There is no such song.
Have you heard any such song?
Of course, but it goes,
"I want a day off today."
I need a day off today
-I need a--
-Hey, I'll break your jaws!
Is this how you talk to your boss?
-Are you both mocking me?
-I wasn't mocking.
My wife wanted
to go shopping for our baby.
-Hence…
-No, I don't get it.
I really don't get it.
You talk as if
you're the only one with a family.
Do you think we don't have families too?
You always run off
to fulfill your wife and kid's needs.
If everyone took time off,
who would attend to our customers?
Customers? Yeah, right!
You talk as if there's a queue
24 hours a day to get haircuts.
To attract customers,
we need to sport a smiling face.
If you keep a face like an old,
smothered brush,
not even a dog will come to our shop.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, it was just a figure of speech.
We don't cut hair for dogs.
Sir, I'm not here for him but for myself.
I take Max to a pet spa for grooming.
For you?
Maharaja will attend to you.
Please come in.
What are you looking at?
You wanted a day off, right?
Well, you will attend to all the customers
that come in today.
Sir, please take a seat. Come.
-Got rejected at home?
-Yes.
Fine, find another one.
-She said okay to this.
-Give it.
-Bill this one as well.
-Listen,
get approval for this one as well.
What if she rejects it?
She will love it.
I am Jothi.
I'm studying in the tenth grade.
To be honest,
I'm a bit weak in my studies.
But I am very much interested in sports.
I spend more time on the field
than in the classroom.
And that's why none
of the teachers like me.
Waste!
Except one.
Ms. Asifa, our P.E. teacher.
-Oh, sorry. Ma'am…
-Please come, ma'am.
After all, it's P.E. period, right?
I have to finish the syllabus.
Let me have it.
What do you mean by
"After all, it's P.E. period"?
"Sound body, sound soul."
Haven't you heard?
She's very straightforward
and very friendly.
I'm her favorite.
She helps me with other subjects as well.
Right now, she's training me
for the 100-meter zonal competition.
And our house?
Here, this is our house.
This is my father, Maharaja.
We are a family of three.
Myself, Dad, and Lakshmi.
Who's Lakshmi? Your mom?
My mother passed away when I was a baby.
Oh, sorry! So, who's Lakshmi?
A dustbin named Lakshmi?
So, you guys named a dustbin?
When I was a baby, the house
I was in was destroyed in an accident.
Lakshmi fell upon me,
covered me, and saved my life.
Since then,
Lakshmi has been a part of our family.
Every Friday, Dad and I bathe Lakshmi,
apply holy ash and vermilion to it,
and pray together.
Dear, it's getting late.
You should have woken me up early!
She keeps snoozing when I wake her up
and then blames me for being late!
What have you prepared?
Lemon rice and egg.
Every day!
O, my daughter, you are my world
You are like the pointing finger
That shows me the right direction
Even your cry is a melody to my ears
Even if you hurt me
I will still love you with all my heart
A daughter is every father's world
This grandpa is Mr. Gopal.
So, tell me something.
Who named you Maharaja?
The apt name for you
is Mr. "Long Face" King.
A smile on your face makes you look good.
Instead, if you keep a long face,
no dog will ever step into our shop!
Well, thanks to kind-hearted people
like him, our shop keeps running.
Please turn your head.
Don't give the money to me.
Pay it to the owner.
He is the owner, and I am the laborer
for this "good for nothing" shop.
See, my father works under him
despite being the owner of the shop.
This is doctor uncle,
a friend of my dad's.
Why did you come all the way here?
I could have come to your shop.
It would have been
a good walking exercise for me.
I am talking to you!
Once a month, he takes a day off,
and we roam around.
Not to exotic destinations
but to the shopping street and the beach.
You switch the spoon of salt with sugar
and the spoon of sugar with chili powder!
I've told you a thousand times
to scrub the cloth before washing.
It's still dirty!
Haven't I told you to bathe before
entering the kitchen after salon work?
Look at all these hairs.
His shop and our home,
that's my dad's world.
Mom came as my daughter
Came to take care
Of the father's mental health
My dad never gives up on me,
no matter what.
Let me explain what happened one day.
Here's your daughter's transfer
certificate and sports certificate.
Take them and leave!
Sir, let me speak.
-To hell with your "Sir"!
-Sir--
Your daughter mixed alcohol
in the chief guest's welcome drink!
He was an IAS officer!
I had my school
ranked among the top ten! Top ten!
It's all gone now!
-She wouldn't have done it, sir.
-Come again! She wouldn't have done it?
The alcohol bottle was found
in your daughter's bag!
Are the witnesses lying,
or do you think I'm lying?
I don't care about that, sir.
My daughter wouldn't have done it.
Your daughter, my foot!
You and your daughter better leave!
Or else, just one phone call,
and you will be in prison! Shall I?
Now, watch me!
Sir!
Now, you're going to tell me he did it,
and she's innocent. Am I right?
All I'm saying is, please investigate
such sensitive issues thoroughly.
Don't any of you have any sense?
Is this how you accuse someone
without conducting a proper inquiry?
I was embarrassed in front
of the IAS officer then,
and now I'm embarrassed
by all of you again in front of him!
You! Come here!
I said, come here!
Sir, what are you doing?
Principal, his father
must be here tomorrow. Got it?
Don't think you got away.
If I catch you doing something wrong,
I'll throw you out of here!
There won't be any hearings like this.
Got it?
You all may leave.
Hey! I said, leave!
I said, out!
You! Do you need special instruction?
-Get lost.
-Jothi.
Didn't I tell you
she wouldn't have done it, sir?
-You rushed to judgment and scolded her.
-So what?
Apologize to my daughter, sir.
-Come again.
-Sir…
My daughter is innocent. Right, sir?
-Dad, let's go.
-Yet you scolded her.
Wasn't that wrong?
Apologize to my daughter, sir.
-Dad, let's go.
-Hey!
Do you know whom you're talking to?
-I own many schools and colleges!
-Dad, let's go.
-Let him apologize.
-You want me to apologize?
That too to your daughter?
-Even if I--
-I don't care about that.
Wasn't it wrong of you to scold her?
She'd be hurt, right?
-Apologize to her, and I'll leave, sir.
-Hey!
-Out! Get out!
-Dad, let's go.
-Wait, we'll go.
-Security! Come here!
-Throw him out!
-Apologize to my daughter, sir.
-Drag him away and throw him out!
-Sir, it was wrong of you to scold her.
-Apologize.
-Drag him away!
-Dad, let's go. Please.
-Sir, apologize…
-Dad, please! Let's go.
-Sir…
-Apologize to her, sir. She is innocent.
-Dad, please. Let's leave.
-Throw him out!
-Sir, apologize!
Teacher, my daughter's innocent.
Ask him to apologize.
-Dad, please. Let's leave.
-Stop listening to him!
-Throw him out!
-Sir, apologize to her.
Sir, you're being unfair.
Ask them to leave him.
-I don't want him here! Throw him out!
-Sir…
Sir, you were wrong to scold her.
-Sir, you were wrong to scold her.
-Get out of here, you rascal!
-Sir…
-You better leave!
-Apologize to her!
-Sir, please listen to me.
-Dad…
-Sir, let go of him. Please.
-Apologize to her!
-Jothi…
-Throw him out! Now!
-Sir…
-Don't spare him!
Sir, he won't let go of that grip
until you apologize to me.
Please apologize to me, sir.
You're being so unfair!
Apologize to her, sir!
Please listen to me, sir.
Sir, please apologize to me.
-He isn't listening to us, sir.
-Apologize to my her, sir.
Apologize to my daughter, sir!
Apologize to her!
Sir, please apologize to my daughter!
-Hey! Let go of him.
-Apologize to her.
Just let go of him!
I said, let go of him!
-Apologize to her, sir.
-Let go of him. Leave him.
Let go of him!
Look, dear.
I was wrong to scold you.
It was an honest mistake, dear.
Forgive me.
That's my dad for you.
I am going out of town
to attend a sports camp.
For the first time, my dad
will be away from me for a week.
Since I won’t be here, don’t be careless
and leave the main door open.
-Fine.
-Eat on time, Dad.
Also, sleep on time.
I am going to a camp,
so I won’t be in school.
Don’t forget that
and end up going to school.
Okay?
Yes, an important thing.
Keep Lakshmi clean.
I’ll make video calls often and check!
And I will call when I'm free.
Understood?
-Good morning, Miss.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
-Hi, Jothi.
Dad, bye.
-See you.
-Take care.
Yes, sir? What happened?
Have you watched the movie
Parvai Ondre Podhume?
Parvai Ondre Podhume…
No, sir.
The gentle breeze and a beautiful flower
-They fell in love--
-I've not watched it, sir.
-No? Really?
-No. I don't know.
-You didn't watch it?
-No, sir.
I left my car here for service,
and you stole the sunglasses
that were in it?
-Where are my Kunal sunglasses?
-It hurts, sir.
-Where are my hero's sunglasses?
-Sir!
-Where are the Kunal sunglasses?
-Sir…
Where are they?
-Where are they? Tell me!
-Sir, please.
-Brother…
-Get lost.
If you come near me,
I’ll rip you all apart!
-Where are my hero’s sunglasses?
-Sir, I didn't take it. I swear.
-I don't know, sir.
-Get up!
-Tell me! Move!
-Sir…
-Tell me! Today, all of you are finished!
-I don't know, sir.
-Where are my hero’s sunglasses?
-Tell me, or else I’ll chop you down!
-Sir, let me speak. Wait.
-Tell me! Now!
-Sir…
Sir…
Sir, that guy is the one
who delivered your car.
Sir, let me check with him. Please.
Hey! Where are the Kunal sunglasses?
Kunal sunglasses?
Why are you asking me?
You're the one who serviced his car
and delivered it last evening.
If not you,
who else could have taken them?
Are you accusing me of stealing
just because I delivered the car?
-Mind your job!
-You're the thief!
-You're crossing the line!
-You thief!
You just got released from prison!
-I showed pity on you
-These guys!
and you steal from the customer?
Why should I get the beatings
for your crime?
You delivered the car this morning
instead of last evening!
-Sir…
-My house is just three kilometers away!
Did you travel the whole night
to reach my home?
-Sir…
-Where are my sunglasses? Answer me!
Hands off me! Today, I will…
Speak! Where is it?
-Answer me!
-Sir! Please, no!
-Leave him. I'll buy you a new one.
-A new one?
-Damn it, my hero Kunal gifted it to me!
-Sir…
There's no replacement for it.
I want that back!
I want those sunglasses back!
Listen, if I don’t get
my sunglasses back by tomorrow,
I'll burn down the whole garage.
Understood? Hands off me!
Get lost! I'll kill both of you.
Understand?
You shouldn't have let him go so easily.
You should've beaten him up
even more. Frauds!
-Brother, bring me a drink.
-In a similar case, a guy in Kerala
bought a second-hand Benz.
Only when he left his car
for service did he find out
it wasn't a Benz but a cheap car.
See how they trick people,
just like in the movies!
Buddy, you shouldn't have settled for
just beating him up.
You should have burned down his garage.
I'll finish you off today!
You roam around in my car,
and on top of that, you beat me up?
I won't spare you.
Mr. Police.
-Mr. Police.
-Sir…
Come here.
Sir…
Sir?
"Mala, how are you, Mala?"
I'm good.
Sir, please wrap it up quickly.
I have a lot of work to do.
I have to go.
Wait, turn around.
-What's this?
-Master key, sir.
Why are you wearing it as a necklace?
So that nobody will steal it.
From you?
-Yeah, right!
-Sir, how do you want me to stand?
However you wish.
Oh, mother! Oh, my God!
Oh, father!
G. SURENDAR
Oh, mother! Oh, father!
You must not take a dump for ten days!
Hey, stop!
Where are you running? Stop!
Hey!
You'll steal mopeds?
-Come here!
-Sir…
-Is this your in-laws house?
-You want to leave immediately?
-Sir…
Oh, God!
No! Things don't work here
as per your wish.
-You thief!
-Sir!
Oh, God!
I'll finish you off, jerk.
Hey.
-Who are you?
-Sir, my name is Maharaja.
There was a theft in my house.
I want to file a police report.
You want to file a police report?
Why don't you also start
the investigation?
First, tell us what was stolen.
I will decide if a police report
is needed.
A police report straight away? My foot!
Quenched your thirst?
Your proper introduction
and tell me what exactly was stolen.
Provide a clear explanation.
Sir, my name is Maharaja.
I run a salon in K.K. Nagar.
Yes, sir.
I reside at Bharathi Nagar, Pallikaranai.
Last night, around ten o'clock,
I returned home after closing my shop.
I always keep the house key
under a flower vase outside.
Okay.
Yesterday, upon reaching home,
I retrieved the key,
unlocked the door, and entered the house.
I switched on the living room light.
Then, I removed the bag
from my shoulder and placed it down.
-Then I went inside the room to change.
-Okay.
Suddenly, I heard a noise from behind.
I turned around.
There were two of them,
wearing masks.
What are you saying?
One of them advanced toward me.
I screamed, "Who are you?"
He quickly covered my mouth
with his hand and restrained me.
-God!
-Then I bit his hand, sir.
Suddenly, a third guy…
I think he was hiding in the living room.
He rushed toward me
and struck me with an iron rod.
I lost my senses, sir.
My vision blurred,
and everything went blank.
-All three of them started hitting me.
-Wait!
So they broke into your house
even before you arrived?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Continue.
They beat me up,
stole my Lakshmi, and ran off.
Please help me find my Lakshmi, sir.
It'll be a bit difficult.
So, how many grams?
Sir, not jewels.
-Then, money?
-Not money either, sir.
Then Lakshmi must be…
-Your wife?
-She passed away long ago.
-I'm sorry.
-I live with my daughter.
She's on a school camping trip.
You're confusing me, man!
You say it's not your daughter,
wife, or sister.
Then who is Lakshmi?
Sir… Lakshmi, sir…
What does this mean?
-Who is Lakshmi?
-Sir… Lakshmi, sir.
Sir, wait. Hold on.
Here, sir. Look at this.
This is you.
-And that's my daughter.
-I can see that.
Where's Lakshmi?
Lakshmi, sir.
-The dustbin?
-That's Lakshmi, sir.
The dustbin?
That's Lakshmi?
I'm much better than him.
Earlier, when you said
you wanted to file a police report,
it was for this missing dustbin?
-Sir, that's Lakshmi.
-You!
-A dustbin, right?
-Sir, Lakshmi.
I'll break your jaws!
Fine.
Answer my questions clearly.
Was there any jewelry
or money in the dustbin?
No, sir.
-Any important documents?
-No, sir.
-There was nothing in it?
-Not even garbage?
-No, sir.
-Not even any garbage in the dustbin?
Fine.
Was that dustbin
-made of gold?
-Lakshmi is made of iron, sir.
-Iron?
-Yes, sir.
-How much did it cost?
-Well…
back then, it was worth
about 350 to 400 rupees, sir.
And those three broke in to steal
that 350-rupee dustbin?
Yes, sir.
-They attacked you and took it!
-Yes, sir.
-But the dustbin is empty.
Do I look like a fool to you?
Or does this police station look
like a mental asylum?
Sir, it was Lakshmi who saved
my daughter’s life.
-So please help me find her.
-Hey!
Look, I'm already quite upset!
Stop irritating me and leave!
Missing dustbin, my foot!
Please find my Lakshmi
before my daughter returns, sir.
Or else, I will…
How dare you point your finger?
Or else what? What will you do?!
Say it! What will you do?
What will you do?
What the hell can you do?
What will you do? Tell me!
I will…
file a complaint against you
with higher officials.
You'll complain to my superiors?
Go ahead! Do it, I say!
Go and complain to the IG!
I'll face it!
-Where are you running?
-Please leave me. Please.
Sir, why aren't you taking my complaint?
-Sir… My Lakshmi…
-Let go of me! Leave me!
Don't hit him, sir.
Sir!
-Why are you hitting him?
-Shut up!
Sir…
Sir, he seems to be a madman.
This could become an issue.
Don't listen to him. I'm not crazy.
Please find my Lakshmi, sir.
-You think he's crazy?
-Sir…
-He's driving us crazy! Throw him out!
-Sir, please find my Lakshmi.
-Thrown him out! Now!
-Sir, my Lakshmi…
-Sir, my Lakshmi.
-Throw him out!
-Come on, throw him out.
-Please find my Lakshmi, sir.
-Pull him! Come on!
-Sir, please. Find my Lakshmi.
-Sir, my Lakshmi…
-Bite him!
Sir, my Lakshmi…
Sir! Please find my Lakshmi, sir!
Please find my Lakshmi, sir!
I won't let go of the grip, sir!
-It's about to break!
-Please find my Lakshmi, sir.
Hey!
Snake!
A snake! Run!
Get out!
Sir!
Run! Everybody run!
Let's go!
-Come!
-Run…
Move!
Put it down! It might bite you!
Put it down. It's a snake!
Put the snake down!
-Are you crazy? Put it down!
-Put the snake down!
Let the inspector come,
and we'll discuss your case.
Put it down!
So the key was placed there?
-Sir?
-I asked, was the key placed there?
Yes, sir.
I just searched,
and all the keys were here.
-You!
-Dad, no.
-You steal in my house and--
-Sir, hold on. Sir…
If he gets hurt,
we'll have to answer to the magistrate.
Was going to Tirupathi temple a mistake?
He has robbed us completely!
Was it the Tirupathi God's order
to leave the keys on top of the cupboard?
It's your house,
and you must safeguard it.
Come on, sir! 680 grams of gold, sir!
Didn't we recover it?
Calm down, sir.
Here you go, sir.
Check it.
Sir, this is an awesome house
that you've built.
It must have cost you 30 million, right?
Which era are you living in, sir?
Including the grand interior decoration,
it cost me 70 million.
My house steals the show
in this whole locality.
-Keep it inside…
-Sir…
Sir, I was told
that you work in the RTO department.
So your salary, after deductions,
must be 60,000 per month.
Then how did you build such a grand…
What did you say?
Who are you to question that, sir?
Are you from the Income Tax department?
Why are you bothered about my earnings?
Let the IT department come!
I have the correct documents
and will present them.
-Where should I sign?
-Here, sir.
You may leave, sir.
Blame it all on fate!
-Sir!
-That's true.
Sir, the jewels you handed over to us
are all fake gold!
-You wasted our time on fake gold?
-No, sir!
Our jewels are pure gold.
The ones you handed over to us are fake.
The designs are a perfect match,
and that's what we retrieved for you.
Sir, the designs look the same,
but this is fake gold,
whereas ours was pure gold.
Bring him here.
Hey, come.
Where are the jewels?
-Sir, I handed them over to you.
-He claims that it's all fake gold.
-Where's the gold?
-Sir, I stole only these.
-You stole these? Where's the gold?
-Sir!
-Where are they?
-Where are the original jewels?
-Sir, it hurts. Please, sir.
Sir!
Hey, 680 grams of gold jewels were stolen,
and the recovered amount is 696 grams?
Can't you duplicate it properly?
Sir, what if the owner finds out?
-We'll manage.
-It hurts!
It hurts? My foot!
-Where are the gold jewels?
-He told me it's gold.
-But now he's saying otherwise.
-He's lying, sir!
-Are you both cheating the government?
-No, sir.
-No, sir. Not at all.
-Sait, you jerk!
Didn't you ask why we are bothered
about your earnings?
So this is how you earned it all?
-No, sir.
-No?
-No…
-Then how?
-Sir, leave it. Sir…
-Leave what?
-Go inside. Now!
-Just leave it, sir.
Do you need
special instructions, ma'am? Go!
"Seventy million! I have the documents!
Steals the show in this whole locality!"
I'll tear you apart!
Here you go.
If you need anything,
come home and inform my wife. Okay?
Amudha, take care of yourself
and the baby.
I'll be out of prison soon.
-Sir!
Sir, please change your shirt.
Wear this one.
A dustbin story has turned
the police station into a dustbin.
Sir is here.
Sir…
What happened?
Did some political party
hold a conference in our police station?
Greetings, sir.
So tell me, Maharaja,
what's the issue in your kingdom
under your reign?
Sir, my name is Maharaja.
I run a salon in K.K. Nagar.
I reside at Bharathi Nagar, Pallikaranai.
Last night, around ten o'clock,
-I returned home after closing my shop.
-There he goes again.
I unlocked the door
and entered the house.
-Got a cigarette?
-I switched on the living room light.
Then, I removed the bag
from my shoulder and placed it down.
Then I went inside the room to change.
Suddenly, I heard a noise from behind.
I turned around.
There were two of them, wearing masks.
A third guy…
I think he was hiding in the living room.
-He rushed toward me--
-Wait.
So they broke into your house
even before you arrived?
-Oh, come on! Move.
-Yes, sir.
Sir, he's telling you
the exact same story he told me.
-A dustbin is missing from his house.
-What? A dustbin?
Yes, sir. A dustbin worth 300 rupees.
Three unidentified thieves
broke into his house to steal it.
They attacked him and stole it.
He wants to file a police report,
it seems.
Look!
People get no justice here
even when their lives are in danger,
and here you are,
creating a ruckus over losing a dustbin.
Here!
Buy yourself a new dustbin
and never show your face here again.
Sir, I don't want a new one.
I want my Lakshmi back.
-Lakshmi?
-That's the dustbin's name, sir.
-A dustbin with a name?
-They don't understand, sir.
Lakshmi saved my daughter's life.
-That is our--
-How can a dustbin save a life?
Sir, Lakshmi is made of iron.
When the house collapsed,
it fell on my daughter,
covered her, and saved her.
Just tell me, what do you want?
Lakshmi is the deity
that resides in our home.
My daughter will ask for Lakshmi
as soon as she returns from camp.
Please help me find Lakshmi, sir.
Fine, we'll find it.
Just answer my questions properly.
Usually, criminals leave clues.
Did you find any?
-No, sir.
-Okay.
They must have talked to each other
while stealing your dustbin.
Did they speak Tamil
or some other language?
Can you identify them?
Sir, all three had masks on.
-Hey!
-Right!
Obviously! They won't come naked
to rob a house!
Apart from the dustbin,
what else did they steal?
-Nothing else, sir.
-Nothing?
He's been telling the same story
since morning, and it's driving me crazy.
-Sir, just throw him out.
-Sir…
I'd honestly tell you
if something else was stolen.
Hey!
One slap and your head will roll!
You say they stole an empty dustbin
and nothing else?
Were they indeed thieves or madmen?
Look, your story doesn't sound believable.
Tell me one thing that's believable,
and I will take up this case.
Otherwise, I'll put you in prison
for creating a ruckus here
and break your knees.
Sir, I noticed something
peculiar about one of them.
What was it?
-When the three of them were hitting me,
-Yes…
I pushed them away, asking them to stop.
During the fight, one of the guy's shirts
got hooked on a nail and tore.
I saw his back, sir.
On his back…
-On his back…
-On his back?
On his back…
there was an ear protruding out.
-An ear on the back?
-Yes, sir.
Now, this is interesting.
I saw it with my own eyes, sir.
An ear on the back…
Sir, I have a doubt.
If we cover his two ears,
can he still hear
with the ear in his back?
-Please ask him.
-Who's that fellow?
Police, sir.
-Police?
-No, sir.
That's his name, but he's a thief.
He steals TVS 50 mopeds.
So far, he has stolen 27 TVS 50s.
He even stole my father-in-law's TVS 50.
I was inquiring about it.
There are millions of costly bikes,
so why steal
the TVS 50 brand in particular?
-Sir, I don't ride bikes with gears.
-Oh, really?
-Shall I teach you?
-Sir…
-Sir, how do you want me to stand?
-However you wish.
Sir, move. I have to get beatings.
-Did he come prepared for this?
-Ready, sir.
How dare you steal?
Stealing only TVS 50s, my foot!
-These people are a pain in the head!
-Rascal!
Oh, God!
You have questions?
And how dare you steal?
-You want to trouble the cops?
-Don't go there.
-Sir…
-Oh, God!
Sir…
Sir, if you cannot take up my case,
at least recommend
moving Lakshmi's case to CBI.
-CBI?
-He's going to die today.
-Don't leave him.
-Come on, lift him.
Hold him.
-Look, he's kicking his leg.
-Hold his leg.
Sir… Sir, my Lakshmi!
Sir, please find my Lakshmi.
Grab him!
He's trying to hold something.
Don't let him!
Sir, Lakshmi…
Sir, please help me find my Lakshmi.
Sir!
Hey!
Take one step forward,
and I'll shoot you down!
I dare you!
Hey!
Leave! I said, leave!
I shouldn't see you around. Leave.
Leave! Now!
You heard me! Leave!
Are you all blind?
Don't you know there's a gun here?
-If you had taken it and pointed at him,
-Sir…
-he would have run for his life.
See how he ran away?
Do you think he'll dare to come back?
People must fear the police.
There are so many of you here,
yet you couldn't throw a madman out?
Don't call yourselves police!
Aren't you ashamed?
Hey!
-Why are you feeling bad? Are you police?
-Sir?
-Are you police?
-Sir, please! Not the gun.
Please use the baton.
Don't change your habits, sir.
Sir, I'm ready.
-You're so used to beatings
-Sir,
-that you have no fear at all.
-pass him the baton.
-I'll shoot you right there!
-Sir…
-Sir, not the gun. Please.
-No, don't.
-Sir…
It's me, sir.
Sir,
keep this 40,000 rupees as an advance.
Please find my Lakshmi, sir.
I'll pay you five hundred thousand, sir.
Five hundred thousand for a dustbin?
How dare you try to bribe me!
Do you have any sense?
Who accepts bribes in front of people?
Have some respect for the inspector.
Hereafter, deal with me regarding money.
Understood?
Sir, I turned on this switch.
I kept the key over there.
-I placed my bag here.
-Hey! Wait!
-Lakshmi was here.
-Look!
-Don't start again. I'll become furious!
-Sir, Lakshmi…
-Look here, we can't find your dustbin!
You move the case to CBI.
Just leave me alone! God!
He keeps flapping his gums.
Sir!
They broke in from here.
There is nothing here.
Sir, this shop
would be better off without him.
He can't even perform his job properly.
Even now, he took two days off
without notifying anyone.
He's simply a waste, sir.
-Sir…
-What is it?
Come here.
He has one and a half million rupees
in his savings account.
Dad, this is the TT court.
I don't play this game, but my friends do.
Look, there's Sumathi.
Sumathi, say hi to my dad.
-Hi, Uncle.
-By the way, today's Friday.
Did you clean Lakshmi?
Click a photo and send it to me.
A few days ago, a land revenue officer
had stuffed the bribe he got
into a grinder, mixer, and utensils.
Yes, that guy from Salem.
Sir, just like that,
there's a major illegal stash
in this house.
They must have stolen it.
This guy is hiding something from us.
Sir, based on my calculations,
there's something very valuable
in that dustbin.
If we squash him,
we won't have to work
for small change anymore.
We could make a lot of money.
I don't smoke, sir.
So, is this your own house?
Yes, sir. We moved in here
after my wife passed away.
Do you suspect anyone?
Those who work in nearby fields
or guests who visit you regularly.
No, sir.
Look, I'll be working in this police
station until I retire from service.
Don't be afraid of anyone.
Nobody can harm you while I'm here.
When it comes to thieves,
there are various types.
Chain snatchers,
jewel robbers, vehicle thieves.
They all have a modus operandi.
Now, if we knew
what was really inside the dustbin,
we could find the thief,
their whereabouts,
and where they'll sell it.
Otherwise, we'll have to waste time
roaming around.
-Before your daughter returns--
-Sir, don't beat around the bush.
Not 500,000, I'll add another two
and pay you 700,000.
Please find my Lakshmi
before my daughter returns at any cost.
Where are the onions?
Onions.
Check in the refrigerator.
Who keeps onions in the refrigerator?
They don't?
Sorry, man.
Where are the onions?
In the loft?
In a box?
They're in a box in the loft.
Add some curd to the chicken.
There's no curd in the refrigerator.
You don't have curd at home?
Oh, come on, you don't have curd
in such a huge household?
I wonder how you guys run the family.
Fine, forget it.
The food has come out delicious today!
Five minutes.
Selvam, the food's ready.
Selvam, wait.
Looks like she has something to say.
Let's hear it out.
Speak.
Sir, you took everything you wanted.
Please spare our lives
and leave our house.
Look at that! Even in this situation,
she's telling us what to do.
Sir, no, sir. Not at all.
I didn't mean it that way.
Sir, please, sir.
You are only thinking about yourself.
Spare a thought for us, too.
Please, sir.
So far, wherever we've robbed,
we've never spared anyone
who saw our faces.
-Please, sir.
-But you? Like some daring warrior,
you jumped across,
pulled our masks off, and saw our faces.
-Sir…
-If we spare your lives,
-you'll go to the police.
-No, sir. I won't, sir.
-The police will…
-No…
-No, sir. I won't go to the police.
-I have no choice.
No, sir. We won't go to the police.
We won't utter a word, sir.
Fine, imagine I spare your lives.
What's in it for us?
Sir, didn't you take so many jewels?
You even snatched my nuptial necklace.
Still not enough.
Sir, over there,
in front of the God's portrait,
is my mother-in-law's nuptial necklace.
See that, she's opening up one by one!
Still not enough.
I've kept 20,000 rupees
in the kitchen to pay my daughter's fee.
-Sir, that's all.
-Not enough.
I gave you everything I had.
I swear I don't have anything else, sir.
Really?
I promise I don't have anything else.
You don't have anything?
No, sir.
You've nothing left?
No, sir! No!
-Sir, please get out.
-Hey.
Do you think
you're in a position to refuse?
Sir, please.
She's my child! Please, no, sir.
-Please, sir!
-Selvam?
Please, leave her alone, sir. Sir!
Sir! Please don't!
My child!
Please ask him to leave her!
Sir! Please, sir!
Sir!
Oh, my God!
My child! Please, sir!
Abhi! Dear Abhi!
Abhi! Please, sir!
Abhi!
Abhi…
Oh, my.
Her screaming is so nagging.
It's so irritating.
Fine, what do we do with her?
Give it to me.
Who's that?
Where's Ammu?
Hey, catch her. Catch her.
Be careful.
Darling.
Ammu, look what daddy got for you.
Why? You don't want it?
No…
You don't want it?
Excuse me! Come here.
They won't find your dustbin.
Don't waste your money.
The inspector promised me he would
form two special units to look for it.
They will find it soon.
As if this is some Veerappan case
that needs special forces to search!
Look, they won't do anything about it.
They will leave you stranded
until you're stripped bare.
I want a dustbin exactly like this one.
Is this a dustbin?
It looks like a rice cooker.
Sir, this is a new model.
-Not this one, ma'am.
-It's a new model, sir.
Sir…
If it's gold that was stolen,
it can't be sold without my knowledge.
I can guarantee you that.
Sir, he refuses to go home.
He says he'll stay here
until we find the dustbin.
Once the duplicate dustbin is here,
he'll leave.
Mr. Dustbin! You garbage.
Come here.
Five biryanis and a pack of cigarettes.
Sir,
-my name is not Dustbin, it's Maharaja.
-I know.
37TH STATE LEVEL ATHLETIC COACHING CAMP
& SELECTION TRIALS - 2023
Okay.
-Anything else?
-That's all.
KOKHILA ELECTRICALS
Hello.
Which area?
Get lost! Look at him and his ugly face!
Make it fast. How long will you take?
It's okay. It will heal soon.
Sir,
-did you want to install a cupboard?
-I informed you three days ago.
Well, sir, I had a lot of pending work.
Fine, the work's in the kitchen.
-Dear, make it fast.
-Coming.
What happened to the baby?
What's with the bandage?
I had some old stuff up in the loft.
When I was taking it down,
it slipped and fell on her.
Oh.
Almost done.
It'll heal in no time, okay?
Call me without fail
after you watch this video.
I called you twice yesterday,
and you didn't answer.
Where are you?
I asked for Lakshmi's photo,
and you haven't sent it yet.
Excuse me, you must've bought this
for only 50 rupees.
But you're selling it for 90 rupees?
Sir, how can we sell it
for the same price we bought it?
Such a huge utensils shop,
-and you don't have this?
-No, we don't!
-Sir, we have many other things here.
-Don't raise your voice at the customer!
Sir, this is a utensils shop!
You're asking for a dustbin here?
And it's an ancient model!
-Where else will I ask? Call the owner!
-Kuzhanthai…
Nallasivam, what are you doing here?
Why are you yelling?
Don't ask me. Give that!
The inspector asked me to buy
a dustbin exactly like this for a case.
And everywhere I go, they keep saying
they don't have it!
We'll say no if we don't have it.
-I'm getting pissed off!
-Sir, please tell him.
He's creating a scene here for a dustbin.
He orders me to call the owner.
-I've been here for ten years--
-But what's the use?
-Kuzhanthai.
-They don't even have a dustbin--
The inspector is calling.
-Sir.
-Kuzhanthai,
which temple's bell are you ringing?
I'm not ringing any bell, sir.
I'm searching for the dustbin.
Somehow, I just can't believe
you're actually working.
Sir, I swear!
Even now, I'm in a shop looking for it.
I met Nallasivam here.
Talk to him if you don't believe me.
-Nallasivam?
-Yes.
What's he doing there?
Give the phone to him.
I'll give it, sir.
-What is it?
-He wants to talk to you.
Sir, tell me.
Nallasivam, what are you doing there?
No work today?
No, sir. Today is my day off.
I need a dustbin for a case.
-Did Kuzhanthai tell you?
-He did show me. I saw it.
I need an exact replica of that one.
A used one.
Find me one.
A used one, sir?
Kuzhanthai is looking for a brand-new one.
I knew he'd mess up like this.
-Stay with him and get this done.
-Definitely, sir.
-Okay.
-Okay, sir.
I need the last 20 days of
incoming and outgoing call details
for this number.
Also, I need the locations it's been in.
T-18 station?
Inspector Varadhan, right?
Yes, sir.
With the last case, he bought a car.
Is he going to buy an apartment
with this one?
Sir, we are dealing with this legally.
I know how well you deal
with things legally. Wait for a moment.
We have to toil hard
for them to make a fortune.
The dustbin that I showed you
in the photo,
how much do you think it costs?
It must cost around 500 to 600 rupees.
But a guy is ready to pay us
700,000 if we find it for him.
Your thoughts on that?
If someone's paying a bribe
in the hundreds of thousands,
then he's hiding something
worth tens of millions.
Don't let go of him. He's got something
really big that he's hiding.
Mr. Dustbin!
You garbage!
-Sir.
-Come here.
Never enter the control room, even if
anyone from here calls you. Got it?
Then why did you enter now?
You called me.
I told you! Don't enter even if anyone
from here calls you. Get lost!
The number's not reachable.
-I don't know his whereabouts, sir.
-Did you inquire around?
I did, sir, but nobody knows.
-Name?
-Prabhu, sir.
I mean, the name of your friend
who's missing?
Dhana, sir.
-He works with me in the garage--
-Stop!
You can give all those details inside.
The writer has stepped out to smoke.
He'll be back.
-Do you have his photo and details?
-Yes, on my mobile.
Everything's on mobile these days.
Do you have a hard copy of his photo?
A friend is bringing it.
I told you this would be a headache.
But you didn't listen to me.
Looks like Karunakaran is on his way
with his lawyer.
Move!
THOSE WHO LIVE BY RIGHTEOUSNESS
DO NOT FALL INTO DISGRACE,
KNOWING THE HARM CAUSED
BY UNRIGHTEOUSNESS.
Tell me, sir.
The white colored car parked outside,
-whose car is it?
-The Fortuner?
It belongs to our councilor. There he is.
Pour some more water.
What do you want?
I am Maharaja.
Maharaja?
King of which kingdom?
Go ahead, tell me.
Your car that's parked outside, TN10AT…
So you were the one who inquired
at my home this afternoon?
Did those car robbers take you for a ride?
I told you, Karna!
They roamed all over the place last night.
I don't care if they took my car,
but they stole my hero Kunal's sunglasses!
I've given him a day's time, or else
tomorrow morning, I'll rip him apart!
He doesn't know whom he's messing with.
Sir, the guy who took your car last night,
any idea where he is now?
Here. Get lost!
Who in the hell is he?
You shouldn't have let him go so easily.
You should've beaten him up even more.
In a similar case, a guy in Kerala
bought a second-hand Benz.
Only when he left his car
for service did he find out
it wasn't a Benz but a cheap car.
See how they trick people,
just like in the movies!
I'll finish you off today!
Hey!
You roam around in my car,
and on top of that, you beat me up?
I won't spare you.
Bro, wait!
Mr. Barber.
What's up? All good?
I should have killed you
when I broke into your house.
I show you pity,
and you're tailing me?
Do you love me so much?
Dhana, who is he?
Where did you find him?
Well, he's a nobody.
Instead of eating
and sleeping like a common man,
-how dare you disturb us?
-No, wait!
Don't finish him off so quickly.
Chop his arms and legs one by one.
I need some entertainment
to go with my booze.
Or else I would have already killed him.
Hey.
Stretch his hand out.
Move.
I said, stretch his hand out!
Stop shaking and hold it properly.
I only want to kill him.
I'm sure you all have families.
So forget what happened here and leave.
Leave!
I said, leave!
Hey, give me that.
Did I feed you biscuits?
Why are you tailing me like a dog?
Hey!
You are one of the three
who broke into my house.
Who are the other two?
Tell me!
Whether I reveal who they are or not,
you'll kill me anyway.
So why should I tell you?
Tell me…
I'll tell you…
One of them is
at the police station in your locality.
Find out who he is if you can.
Go, find out. Okay?
Find out if you can!
Hey!
I'll go to the police station!
I'll chop his head off,
just like I chopped yours!
Whose photo is that, sir?
Your friend?
A friend?
He dragged me
into huge trouble and escaped.
He's been missing for three days now.
I have no idea where he is
or what happened to him! No idea at all.
It's frustrating, sir.
Don't worry. You'll find him.
I'm also here
because something of mine is missing.
What is that?
Well…
-Lakshmi--
-Hey!
Do you not have any connections
at the police station?
Anyone who knows both you and your friend.
Why don't you ask them?
Nope, I don't know anybody here.
This mongrel is the one who's always
going back and forth
to the police station and prison!
I mortgaged my house
and lent him one million.
If not repaid on time,
then my head is on the line.
Put your trust in God.
You'll find him.
Oh, God.
Listen, Mr. Lawyer,
-speak clearly and bring this to a close.
-Okay, sir.
Sir, it's true that
I caused an issue at his service station.
That guy broke the sunglasses
that my hero Kunal gave me.
Wouldn't that make anyone furious?
So I just roughed him up.
They are here for such a silly matter.
See that, sir? He confessed.
Arrest him and investigate.
Arrest me? You fool.
-Fool? I'd have bashed you the other day.
-Stop it. Look!
You had a feud with him last.
Tell us what you did to him.
If I find out the truth, I won't care that
you're a politician. I'll beat you up!
Look at me. Like a poet,
I'm always gazing at the sky and talking.
That kid beat me up really bad at the bar.
So badly that my neck has gone stiff.
How can I talk about it in public?
It'll be so embarrassing for me.
You know that very well, sir.
Remember anything else from that night?
Anything else?
Yes, sir. Before that guy came to the bar,
another fellow came to me
asking about him.
-Who was that?
-He told me his name.
His name is…
A very nice name. It's almost
on the tip of my tongue but…
NO RECOMMENDATION IS REQUIRED
TO MEET THE POLICE INSPECTOR
What did he say his name was?
-His name…
-Hey!
Leave! Tell me when you recollect it. Go!
Okay, sir. See you.
-Thanks, sir.
-Move!
Niranjan, these guys look suspicious.
If we dig deep into the issue,
we might strike gold.
Excuse me, brother.
Move over a little bit.
Oh, God.
God.
His name…
What did he say it was?
Inquire about Dhana.
-Trace details using his number.
-Okay, sir.
Otherwise, they will mess things up,
and we'll have to run around.
His name…
Sir! His name is…
-Sir, I got his name!
-What is his name?
Illayaraja.
Get lost! Look at him
and his hairstyle, jerk!
I guess he is a Rahman fan.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Watching a man getting dressed!
Your cigarettes, sir.
K. KALIMUTHU
-Tell me, dear.
-We're leaving home.
We'll take a rickshaw.
Will you come directly to the shop?
Listen, an important thing.
Your daughter will keep asking
for things at the shop.
Do not buy everything she asks for.
Just buy what we can afford.
-Got it?
-Okay, dear.
It's too hot outside.
Take care of Ammu.
"Palani Engine-err Works."
He couldn't even write that properly!
Will he do a good job?
Kuzhanthai, these days,
it's the uneducated who do a neat job.
-Fine, come.
-Let's go and meet that "Engine-err."
-I hope he'll do a neat job.
-I'll do it, sir.
It's 1.5 by 1.5 in size.
-Come back the day after tomorrow.
-The day after tomorrow?
The inspector said it's urgent,
and he's saying come back in two days.
-Please…
-This is not magic.
I've got to get the pattern right.
It'll take time.
I promise to do a neat job.
Fine, ask how much?
-How much will it cost?
-2,500 rupees, sir.
2,500 rupees?
You told me it'd cost 500 to 600 rupees.
-Look, I am a cop.
-That's why I'm offering a lower price.
-Okay, do a neat job.
-Don't worry. It'll be perfect.
Check this model, madam.
This is the current trend.
-Dad, this one.
-How about this one?
-What?
-These are the latest models, sir.
I don't want these models.
It's for my kid's birthday.
-So, show me some new and unique models.
-Okay, sir.
-One moment.
-These look good.
Why don't you choose one of these?
Wait, dear.
-Madam.
-That one.
-That one? Look at this.
-Check out these ones.
Look.
This looks good, right?
How is this one?
Wow!
Superb.
-I knew it.
-Do you like this one?
-I want this one.
-Shall we buy it?
It's good.
-You'll wear it on your birthday, okay?
-This one.
Good choice, madam.
It has a rare red diamond.
A classic design, madam.
They say it has a red diamond.
It might be costly.
-Let's not buy it.
-Why do you worry about that?
We don't have that much money.
Look, don't borrow money for this.
-Daddy.
-Fine, don't worry about it.
She likes this. Please bill it.
Sir, we have to pre-order and make it.
Her birthday is in two days.
If it will be very late,
let us know right now.
It won't take that long.
I'll give it in two days.
-Will I get it in two days?
-Definitely, sir.
-It'll look awesome.
-To hell with dad and his daughter.
Manju, come here.
Tell me.
With whose permission
did you take my shoes?
Well, the other day, my shoe ripped.
-I needed a pair, so I took yours--
-What did I ask?
Did you ask for my permission?
Don't you know you must ask for
permission before taking someone's things?
Fine, leave it. Shall we go and eat?
Not sleepy?
Was it necessary to spend
so much on that necklace?
We must buy only according to our status.
To hell with status.
Everything depends on our needs.
Well, that's what I'm asking.
What's the need
to buy a diamond necklace for her?
My daughter's happiness is all I need.
Everything she wishes under the sky
must be hers.
Money should never be a hindrance to that.
Doctor, Collector, Engineer,
let her become whatever she wishes for.
No matter how much it costs.
I'll take care of it.
She must live the life she wants.
You talk as if our fathers run a bank.
-What are you looking at?
-Nothing.
Missing your dad's cooking?
Not just Dad's cooking,
but I miss Dad, Lakshmi, and home.
You are so emotional here,
but at home,
you dominate your dad. Why is that?
Miss, he likes it.
When I scold him
or teach him something,
he feels so proud
that his daughter knows everything.
Where is he looking at?
Forget 500,000, just pay me 400,000.
I'll help you find your dustbin.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm also Police.
Ask anyone here.
Fine, pay me 300,000.
I'll get it done.
Are you going to tell on me?
I'll break your neck.
The third time you made that noise,
it didn't sound like a cat's meow.
Niranjan!
-What are you doing here?
-Sir!
What are you doing here, sir?
Maharaja's case.
I'm here for Illayaraja's case.
-Tell me, dear.
-Got the necklace?
I'm at the shop. I'll collect it now.
Do check the weight.
Don't let them cheat you.
It's a reputed shop. They won't.
-Happy birthday, Ammu.
-Listen,
-Bye.
-did you buy the things for the ritual?
-I'll buy them on my way.
-Okay.
I'm forgetting something.
I had given my blouse for stitching.
Along with the ready-made one,
collect that as well.
-Okay.
-Also,
we're expecting many guests, dear.
So, go to a good salon
and shave your beard.
I'll look bad without the beard.
-At least trim it.
-Ma'am.
-Ma'am!
-Yes?
-I'll talk to you later. Bye.
-Okay.
-Yes, what is it?
-Where do we place these benches?
Everybody, listen up.
Today is my daughter's birthday.
We have a function at our home.
So, don't cook or eat outside.
-Ms. Jaya, especially you.
-Yes.
Be at my house in half an hour.
-Or else, no more ties with you.
-Okay.
Shall we get ready
before your dad arrives?
Hello. Is it delivered?
No?
The function is at three o'clock.
When will you deliver?
Where are you now?
Keep going straight.
The house in the
street next to Vetri Medicals.
-Thanks.
-You can see a decorated house.
They'll be waiting. Make it fast!
Please come.
Take care of things here.
I'll go have a tea and come.
-Shall I join?
-Come.
-Cutting or shaving, sir?
-Trimming.
Okay.
Any function at home, sir?
Well, I heard you talking on the phone.
Yes, my child's birthday.
Son or daughter, sir?
-Daughter.
-I, too, have a daughter, sir.
What's her name, sir?
Will you trim only if I tell you her name,
place, horoscope, and all the details?
Just mind your business.
Okay, sir.
What happened? Battery's dead?
Yes, sir. I'll trim it with scissors.
Will you trim one by one?
Go and buy the battery.
Please wait. I'll be back, sir.
-Tell me, Sabari.
-Where are you?
In a salon. What's the matter?
Step out. I want to have a word.
I'm all alone here. Tell me.
Our robberies are in the newspaper.
Saw it?
Is it? What's written?
They have not just written
about our last robbery,
but they have written about
each and every robbery of ours.
Wait a minute. Let me check.
Brother, I need five meters of this wire.
I'm talking to you. I need this wire.
Please leave!
What a jerk.
Shouldn't have come to your shop.
Not only that,
but they've also mentioned it as if
it was done by guys from another state.
How long will the police
keep the case file open?
They will obviously try to
frame somebody and close the case.
Well, Selvam,
if they have got so much detail,
then don't you think
that by now they know it's us?
They print such news
so that we'll react and get caught.
Don't beat yourself
thinking about this. Got it?
Be on time for the function.
BURGLARS TARGETING ISOLATED HOMES
THE POLICE ARE ON ALERT
Just 20 rupees.
No tips, please.
Sister, why are you doing these chores?
-It's okay. You attend to the guests.
-Okay.
Come, dear.
-Please serve the juice to everybody.
-Bye.
-Bye. Okay.
-The glasses are over there.
Waving bye to her?
Hey.
What happened?
What happened, dear?
Why do you look dull?
You've been dull
since you arrived home.
-Are you not feeling well?
-I'm tired after driving for a long time.
You look so sharp after trimming.
Now sport a smile, come on.
Smile now.
Ask your daddy to smile.
Tell him, "Smile, Daddy."
Come on, let me see that.
Selvam.
Here.
-Come here.
-What happened?
Sabari, remember our call earlier?
The guy at the salon heard it.
Hey, look, your mom's calling.
Please take him.
You said you were all alone.
Then how?
I was alone when you called.
But after the call, I turned
and saw him standing there.
Okay, we'll follow him.
We'll find the right time
and finish him off.
Should we move the money
and jewels elsewhere?
Let's split it
and stash it in different places.
-That'll be safe.
-Dear…
Dear…
Where's the necklace?
-Check in the bag.
-I did, but it's not there.
-It's not there?
-No.
Fine, you carry on with the work.
Leave it. After searching everywhere,
he'll finally come here.
-We'll give it to him then.
-I feel bad for him.
He told me his daughter's
birthday function was at 3 p.m.
If it bothers you so much,
then go and give it to him yourself.
Okay, boss.
So you want a day off
today as well, right?
Poor guy, boss.
Go. Get lost.
It's not there.
-Tell me everywhere you went.
-I was…
One minute…
Sabari…
-Sabari…
-I got work here.
-Just come!
-Take care of it.
Selvam, why is the police here?
Doesn't look like
they are here for us. Be quiet.
No, they are here for us.
He ratted us out. Jerk!
Sabari, leave. Just leave.
Damn it! You thief!
How long have we been searching for you?
Finally, gotcha!
You thief! You rascal!
You decorate your house
with all the money you stole
-and you're celebrating here?
-Sir…
-Sir.
-Do you take police for fools?
Understood our power now?
-Arrest him! Walk!
-Sir…
-Please move.
-Stop acting innocent!
Leave! Move!
-Don't come near! Move!
-Hands off him!
-I said, hands off him!
-Walk!
Stop! Stop it!
I said stop it,
and you're manhandling my husband?
He widowed, raped, and killed many women!
-You live with him without knowing that?
-Who told you all this?
Are you shocked by just this?
A few days ago,
your husband and that fellow
burned a woman and her daughter alive.
Do you know all that?
Rascal, tell her!
Tell her!
-I said, tell her! You heard me!
-Stop hitting him.
Let me talk to him.
Dear, what is he blabbing?
-Is he your "dear"?
-Does the police have the
-He is a murderer!
-license to say anything?
How dare he accuse you?
Tell him you're innocent.
Don't I know about my darling?
You're a nice man,
and you run a shop, right?
-Tell me.
-What are you guys doing there?
-Aren't they framing you
-Let's smash both
-instead of finding the real culprit?
-these culprits today.
-Tell them you're innocent, dear.
-Say it, if you can!
-Say it, dear.
-Hey, move aside!
-Tell them you're innocent.
-Move!
-Don't let him escape! Catch him!
Hey, Sabari!
Oh, God!
-No! Put the gun down!
-Sabari, what did you just do?
Put the gun down.
You're again making a mistake!
-Don't come near me!
-Put the gun down!
-Selvam, run!
-Sabari, listen to me. No!
-You run! I'll manage them.
-No, Sabari.
Sabari, we are caught!
We'll handle it later.
-I'll shoot you if you come near me.
-Sabari…
-Put the gun down!
Hey, his gun might be loaded.
Everyone, move aside.
-Move aside, man! Move!
-Sabari, no.
-Surrender the gun.
-Leave!
-Listen to me!
-Sabari.
-I'll kill you all! Selvam, I got this!
-Sabari, no! Surrender the gun.
Hey!
-Kokhila, I'll explain it to you later.
-Hey, listen to me.
-Selvam, you escape!
-Just surrender the gun.
Listen to me.
This is for your own good.
You better put the gun down.
-I'll shoot!
-Listen to me…
Sabari!
Hey, Sab…
Hey, Sabari?
Sabari?
Sabari!
No! Sabari…
Sabari…
Kokhila…
Walk!
Daddy!
-Daddy!
-Sir.
Ammu.
-Ammu!
-Hey!
-Sir, let me talk to my daughter once.
-Mummy!
-No! No!
-One last time, sir.
-No way!
-Just once, sir.
-Ammu!
-I won't give you my child.
Ammu…
He must not even lay a finger on my child.
Take him away! Arrest him.
I cut ties with my family
and married you.
How could you cheat me?
I curse you!
-You've insulted me in front of the world.
-Ammu…
-My life is ruined! Where will I go now?
-Daddy.
-The only thing I can do is end my life.
Don't show up even if I die.
Don't come to my funeral either!
-Take him away, sir.
-Enough of your drama! Walk!
Daddy!
Don't cry, dear. Take him away.
All of you move.
-Did you take the police for fools?
-Move!
Move!
Walk!
Don't cry, dear.
Did you take all your belongings?
Get in, let's go.
What are you discussing there?
It's getting late. Let's go.
Dad, we are heading back.
I'll reach home tonight.
My new shoes got torn
while I was jogging this morning.
Buy me the same red-colored new pair.
I have practice tomorrow on the ground.
I've sent you the photo.
Don't forget to buy it, okay?
DAD
Buy me the same red-colored new pair.
I have practice tomorrow on the ground.
I've sent you the photo.
Don't forget to buy it, okay?
So…
Looks like they found the culprit.
-You'll get the dustbin tomorrow.
-Thank you, sir.
Do you think I was waiting
for your thanks?
Nallasivam, check it properly.
-Here.
-Rushing things is never good.
Touch and feel it.
-It's as smooth as a young girl's skin.
-You and your comparisons!
How is it, sir?
-It looks exactly like that one.
-Yes, it does.
-Yes, sir. It wasn't an easy task--
-Nallasivam, you're a skilled worker.
-Thanks, sir.
-Sir!
You're good at wasting time, too.
Now, dent it and make it dirty,
exactly like in this photo.
Consider it done, sir.
-Give me that.
-Here.
Look carefully. This is the spot.
This spot.
Rub it nicely.
Sir, he has done it. Look.
Here.
-Nallasivam, you beauty!
-Sir.
You've made it look exactly the same!
You've proved
that you're indeed a skilled worker.
Apply holy ash and vermilion,
and it'll be ready.
-Superb!
-Sir, I have a doubt.
What if he finds out
this is a duplicate dustbin?
Let him find out!
That's what we want.
-I don't get it.
-Look,
if he's really looking for the dustbin,
then he'll accept this,
pay us the balance, and leave.
But if there's something big behind this,
he'll ask us who stole it,
where it was, and other details.
We'll point to some accused and end it.
Sir, he will pay
the remaining balance to us
and follow the accused we showed him,
believing he's the real thief.
He'll fall into the trap,
and we'll know what's inside it.
-Correct! Spot on, Nallasivam.
-Sir, this is like taking the long route.
-Do you have a better idea?
-No, sir.
No, right?
Then, shut up and follow my orders.
Okay, sir. As you wish.
Enough.
-Keep it here.
-Okay.
-Tell me, sir.
-Can you turn yourself in for stealing?
For stealing what, sir?
If you want, I'll steal it for real.
We've got back the stolen item.
You just turn yourself in.
I'll handle the rest.
Okay, sir. What's the stolen item?
-Nothing but just an ordinary dustbin.
-A dustbin?
-Yes, a dustbin.
-What was inside it, sir?
Nothing. Just an empty dustbin.
Sir, do you think I'm a fool to turn in
for stealing an empty dustbin?
-Hang up the call, sir!
-Hey…
Kumar, where are you?
Sir, it's me, Kumar's wife.
Is he not home?
I need a favor from him.
Last week, Inspector Pallavaram
needed a favor, and now he's in prison.
Let him come out, sir.
I'll tell him that you need a favor.
-Don't worry. He'll do it, sir.
-Okay.
Rajamanickam, Inspector Varadhan here.
Tell me, sir. Hope you're fine.
I'm good. How about you?
-I'm doing great.
-Great.
-I need your help.
-What help, sir?
Well, we've got the stolen item back.
Just turn yourself in for stealing it.
No worries, sir. I'll take the blame.
So, what's the item, sir?
Come in person. I'll show it to you.
Sir, if you tell me what is it,
I'll rehearse well and do a neat job.
Well, it's a…
It's a dustbin.
Hello?
Rajamanickam!
I know you're on the line.
You! Hey!
Kuzhanthai, you'll cross that
traffic signal on your way back, right?
Drop me at that signal.
I'll take a rickshaw
from there and go home.
Let's meet the inspector before we leave.
Is it? Fine, I'll take care of it.
Sir, now that's a lot of cigarettes.
Looks like you'll spend
that 700,000 rupees on cigarettes.
700,000, my foot!
To get that money, we need a thief.
But what happened?
I called everyone on this list,
and none of them are ready to come.
Is it such a shame
to play a dustbin thief?
Who said it's a shame, sir?
Call Rajamanickam, sir.
Don't even utter his name.
If I catch hold of him, I'll slap him!
-Kuzhanthai…
-Sir?
I don't know what we are going to do,
but by tomorrow morning, I need a thief.
Sir, before morning? Impossible.
Earlier, I said 30,000,
but I'm ready to pay 50,000.
-Money is fine, but before morning--
-Sir…
-50,000 rupees, sir?
-Yes.
Do you know anybody
who can turn themselves in?
If so, tell us. We'll pay you as well.
Kuzhanthai, if we get anything
from the dustbin, we'll share that, too.
Sir, that's too much.
-It's okay if we can get anyone.
-Sir… Kuzhanthai sir…
You're going to find a thief
who will turn himself in anyway.
Why ask me to find someone I know?
I shall play that part, sir.
Nallasivam,
-can you act?
-Sir,
during childhood,
I acted in school plays.
Just tell me what I must do, sir.
-Sir…
-I'll nail it, sir.
Wait, I have an idea. Hold on.
Thank God. You're a savior!
Mom.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye, ma'am.
-Hello, tell me, sir.
-Shanmugan,
is Mr. Dustbin still there?
He's here more than any of us, sir.
Ask him to repeat that story,
but don't let him know I'm on the call.
Sir, please. I can't hear
or bear that story once again.
Last week,
my child got admitted to a school.
-Which school?
-CS Public School, sir.
Hey, that school is so costly.
How are you going to manage it?
If you want, I'll narrate the story.
Why don't you try RDE School?
-Three robbers broke into--
-Listen, wait!
Except for him,
nobody can narrate it properly.
It's urgent. Ask him to narrate it.
Mr. Dustbin,
where to? Come to my table.
You heard me. Sit down.
Look, we can't file a police report
for a missing dustbin.
I'll at least file a CSR.
So tell me, in detail, what exactly
happened, and I'll note it down.
Sir, everybody knows my story.
I must go home now.
I'll narrate it tomorrow.
Do you want your dustbin or not?
If yes, then narrate it now.
Otherwise, you may leave.
-May I drink some water?
-Yes.
-Kuzhanthai, record it.
-It's already recording.
Sir, my name is Maharaja.
I run a salon in K.K. Nagar.
I reside at Bharathi Nagar, Pallikaranai.
On that day, around ten o'clock,
I closed my shop
and headed home on my bike.
I took the usual route.
I reached home, sir.
-Bye, ma'am.
-Bye, Jothi.
-Bye.
I always keep the house key
under a flower vase outside.
I retrieved the key,
unlocked the door, and entered the house.
I switched on the living room light.
Then…
I removed the bag
from my shoulder and placed it down.
Then…
I went inside the room to change.
When I was changing…
Who is it?
That was unfortunate, Selvam.
If he had been here when we broke in,
we could've killed him,
disposed of his body, and left.
Now, she's an obstacle.
Damn it. On top of that, she's beautiful.
What's with that look?
As if we haven't done it before.
Don't give me that look.
My wife has been out of town
for quite a while now.
Say something, Selvam.
Do you want the exact same model of shoes?
How about a different model?
-I want this exact one.
-The stock has run out.
My daughter's coming back from her tour.
She'll be expecting me to have bought it.
If it's urgent, please wait.
We have a warehouse three kilometers away.
I'll have my assistant fetch it.
You said he'd be home by 10:15 p.m.
Why isn't he home yet?
Bad spying!
If I was bad at spying, how could I have
been a police informer for seven years?
Selvam, for a whole month,
I closely monitored him.
Let me tell you that!
Typically, he closes his shop
around 9:30 p.m.,
heads straight home,
and should arrive by 10:15 p.m.
I wonder what happened today.
Clearly, not every day
is the same, Selvam.
This girl?
This brat wasn't in town for a week,
and now she's home,
complicating things for us.
Selvam, no matter how long it takes,
let's wait and finish him off.
What do you say?
Wait, Dhana!
-Where are you going?
-Should I wait for him?
First, let me slit her throat.
Then we'll take care of him.
Hey.
Anyway, we're going to kill her.
Before that, shall I do it again?
Selvam?
Hey.
I lost my senses, sir.
Those three were so huge,
I couldn't fight them alone.
I almost died, sir.
They beat me up,
stole my Lakshmi, and ran off.
Please, somehow,
find my Lakshmi, sir.
Are you done? Move.
Dhana.
We'll do it later.
Let's go.
What do you mean?
Weren't you waiting 13 years for this?
Back in prison,
you desperately wanted to kill him.
What's stopping you now?
Are you crazy?
Let's finish her off.
Let's go.
Now, come on!
Look, I have written down
everything you said.
The office assistant is not here.
The inspector will come in the morning.
I'll get his signature as soon
as he arrives and file a CSR.
-Okay, sir.
-You come and collect it in person.
Brother…
Maharaja.
I am sure of one thing.
You're not here for the dustbin.
Lakshmi, sir.
Nallasivam,
I hope everything is okay.
Hey, sir is talking to you.
I hope you understood everything clearly.
When you act it out there,
don't repeat exactly what he said.
Change the story a bit
so he won't doubt us.
Now, what's so funny?
Well, sir,
acting as a thief who stole a dustbin
will be very embarrassing.
This is what I was thinking.
If my friends find out about it,
-they will tease me--
-Hey!
One slap and your jaw will be
lying on the floor!
Rascal! You know me very well.
Sir,
why are you getting so angry
over such a silly matter?
Of course, I will.
Sir, I never said that I wouldn't do it.
Well, I am going to play a dustbin thief.
I was just telling you the consequences.
Sir, I'll do it. We'll make it work!
What do you say?
Wait a moment.
Let me make a call to my wife, sir.
-Go ahead.
-Come.
Oh, come on now, sir.
I've nobody to call my own.
I'll be a loner even in death.
For now, with the help of some locals,
I'm taking up electrical contracts
in major apartments.
Let's see.
-Tell me, Nallasivam.
-Selvam,
we’re caught!
The salon owner
filed a missing dustbin complaint.
After running in circles,
they ended up
calling me to play the thief.
-They don’t know we’re behind it.
-Okay, fine!
-Call Dhana. He'll help you.
-His number hasn’t been reachable
for the past three days.
I don’t know where he is.
And where the hell are you?
I came to Salem for some important work.
We’ll deal with him
once I’m back in Chennai. Don’t panic.
Don't panic, my foot!
You postponed the plan to kill him,
and now look!
Hey.
I'll be exposed anyway.
So, I’ll tell them
I’ll come directly tomorrow morning
-and escape.
-Don't do that. Listen to me.
-That will get you caught--
-Leave it! Now, hang up!
Hang up.
Nallasivam, done talking to your wife?
Yes, sir. I spoke to her.
Just let me know when
and where to come tomorrow.
I’ll come directly in the morning.
-See you, sir. See you, Kuzhanthai.
-No need. Stay here.
Sir, just tell me the time and place,
and I'll be there on time.
What's the big deal?
-Why are you--
-Your house is 20 kilometers away.
Escorting you will be a headache.
Shut up and sleep here.
-Kuzhanthai, tell him--
-You heard me! Sleep here.
-Kuzhanthai, you sleep here as well.
-Sir.
We’ve got booze.
If you want some, have it.
What else do you need?
Have a few drinks
and rehearse for tomorrow.
-I'll stay, sir.
-Go.
-What's the big deal?
-Then come along.
Jothi,
you warned me, but now
you’ve carelessly left the door open.
Did you wash your hands
in the plate from which you ate?
The footwear shop guy made me wait.
I didn’t get the color you asked for.
Check this color.
-See if you like it…
-Dad…
Dad…
Oh, my God!
-Doctor, save my child.
-Maharaja, get up.
Get up. First, get up.
Hey.
Why didn't you inform me?
My heart aches to see this.
Hey.
If I were your age,
I would find those mongrels,
no matter where they are,
and stab them to death.
You’re a waste.
Fine, shall we sleep?
Oh, my!
Dad…
-Dear?
-Dad…
Dad…
Who were they, Dad?
Why did they do this to me?
What's my fault, Dad?
Tell me, Dad.
Dad…
You’ve never refused me anything
I’ve ever asked for, right?
Can you do something for me, Dad?
I want to meet the one responsible
for my current plight.
I want to have a word with him.
Please take me to him, Dad.
Will you take me to him, Dad?
I want to have a word with him.
Take me to him, Dad.
-Kuzhanthai…
-Sir?
Did you give him
all the details about Maharaja?
Yes, sir. He memorized them.
Isn't that right? Tell him.
We might get angry and raise our hands
at you in front of Maharaja.
Don't mind it.
Come on, sir.
Nallasivam is one of us.
He won't mind it.
Oh, my.
Nallasivam…
Hey!
Get down. Come.
Walk!
Maharaja, he's the one
who stole your dustbin.
There are a lot of valuable things
here to steal.
I asked him why he stole it,
and he said it was beautiful. Here.
What was so beautiful about it?
Check it properly.
Maharaja, what are you thinking?
I hope you brought the balance payment.
I have, sir.
Go stand over there.
You come here.
Act it out.
Act out the whole robbery scene
that you and your friends committed.
Why are you quiet?
So, where are the other two?
He said they escaped to North India.
We caught him, and we'll catch them, too.
Sir, everyone is telling
their own stories,
and you're believing them?
You act it out. Go ahead.
Well, somehow,
we thought we'd find
something valuable here,
so my friends
and I decided to rob this house.
From there…
We broke in through this door.
What weak construction.
Two blows, and it opened up.
We found nothing in the kitchen.
Then, we all headed to the living room.
We realized there's nothing
valuable here to steal.
So, realizing
there was nothing worth stealing,
we decided to leave.
That's when
we heard the main door open.
Out of curiosity,
we hid to find out who was entering.
It was him, sir.
He opened the door, came in,
and switched on the light.
He put the keys aside
and then placed his bag down.
After he placed his bag down…
Since he runs a salon,
I was sure he'd go take a shower.
We thought we'd escape
when he went for a shower,
but instead, he started walking toward us.
He walked toward us.
Oh, God!
As he came closer,
we came in here, split up, and hid.
He came in…
He started changing.
I kept looking.
Just my luck,
something fell behind me.
He turned around at once!
He yelled,
"Who are you? Tell me! Who are you?"
I got confused, rushed…
and covered his mouth.
Dad…
There were three of them, Dad.
One of them had a bump on his back.
Out of nowhere, he bit my hand!
I immediately slapped him.
Didn't I?
Forgive me.
As soon as you hit me,
-I fainted and fell on you, right?
-Yes.
Sorry for hitting you.
Please forgive me.
There was nothing worth stealing,
so I stole the dustbin.
Why create such a fuss
over this trivial matter?
Right?
Maharaja,
we found the thief
as well as your dustbin.
Can you honor
what you promised us? It's getting late.
I want to talk to him, sir.
With him?
Go ahead.
Come, let's wait outside.
What do you want to talk about?
What is it?
How old are you?
Fifty… Fifty-four.
At this age…
-Isn't that wrong?
-What does age have to do with it?
It looked beautiful. Isn't that enough?
Let it go. Okay?
Just forget it.
-Don't you think it's wrong?
-Look,
I had no intentions of breaking in here.
My friend was insistent
on breaking in here,
so I tagged along.
Got it?
"It hurts…
Please let go of me. Please!"
Listen,
if I wanted to,
I could have
crushed that dustbin and thrown it away.
Did I?
I didn't.
I obeyed the inspector
and returned the dustbin.
Look, you're here, I'm here,
and so is the dustbin.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Hey, do you understand?
Hey!
Threatening him at his own house?
How dare you!
Well, sir,
even if I go to prison for this,
I'll get released
after three months anyway.
He must know
what I might do to him, right?
That's what I was explaining.
-Are you threatening him?
-No, sir. Why would I--
I'll smash you!
Maharaja,
what do you want to do with him?
-Forgive and let him go.
-What? Forgive and let him go?
Are you kidding?
You've spent hundreds of thousands
on this case.
He even broke your door,
stole your dustbin, and harmed you.
Just tell me,
how do you want him punished?
-Let him go, sir.
-I'll file a police report.
-So that's your conclusion?
Forgive him for everything he did?
-Yes, sir. Let him go.
-Forgive him for "all" his crimes?
Sir,
let him go.
Even if he had raped your daughter?
Sir!
Sir! Sir, what's going on?
Sir…
-What? This is shocking!
-Yes, sir.
-I just can't believe it.
-Nallasivam, sir.
Sir, please don't.
Sir, what's going on?
Sir…
Sir. Inspector, please don't.
Sir, please don't do this.
-Here, kill him!
-Sir, please don't.
-Sir, no. Please.
-Butcher him!
-Listen to me, sir!
-Slash him!
-Slash him! Take it!
-Sir! Please, no!
-Listen to me!
-Hey!
Come here!
-Perumal…
-Take it!
-Please tell him, Perumal.
-Slash him!
-Either you do it, or I'll do it!
-Perumal, I came here because of you.
-Do it!
-Perumal, please tell him.
-Take it!
-Sir, no. Please, no.
Don't give him the machete, sir!
Perumal, no. Please tell him.
Isn't this the guy
with an ear on the back?
Weren't you looking for him?
One slash and his head must roll!
No, leave me! Kuzhanthai, please.
At least you tell them.
Save me, Kuzhanthai.
You're going to die anyway.
You better die now!
Please, don't. Sir, no.
Sir!
Sir, we gave him the machete,
what if we land in trouble in the future?
We'll handle it.
Would we stay quiet
if this had happened to our daughter?
-Let him die.
-Yes, sir.
Brother…
Please forgive me, brother.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
Oh, God!
Sir!
Sir! Sir, open the door, please!
Perumal…
-Did you find the third guy's whereabouts?
-Yes, sir.
-Hello.
-Brother!
Someone's beating us up,
asking for you! Hey!
Do you remember me?
Do you remember?
Fifteen years ago,
you sent me to prison!
Do you remember?
I lost my child because of you!
I lost my wife!
My whole life is ruined!
Tell me, do you remember?
Or did you forget it?
Did you forget all that?
Hey, maybe you've forgotten,
but I haven't!
I haven't!
In prison, all I thought about
was getting revenge on you.
After you sent me there,
both you and your daughter
lived a happy life, right?
Does it hurt now? Does it?
Does it hurt, you mongrel?!
I am used to this pain.
It'll eventually fade away.
But…
the pain that I inflicted on you
will last forever.
You will cry every time
you think about your daughter's plight.
And that is what I want.
That's all I want.
Why are you quiet?
Speak.
Dad…
Dear…
You don't have to see him.
Let's go.
-Dad, leave me.
-Listen to me, dear.
-I want to have a word with him.
-Teacher,
-please tell her not to.
-I want to have a word with him.
-Jothi, listen to your dad.
-Dad, leave me.
-No, dear. Let's go.
-No need. Please listen to me.
-Leave me. Dad!
I must have a word with him.
Teacher, please wait here.
Dad, please wait outside.
You talk. I'll wait here.
Just wait outside for a minute.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I came here expecting to see
the most despicable person in the world.
And I'm looking at him.
You came for this, right?
Here, take it.
Don't think you've achieved
something great by doing this to me.
I won't break down.
I will move on from this.
If you have a daughter like me,
then go and ask her
how many filthy dogs like you
we encounter every day.
If I had known you'd talk so much,
I would've killed you back then.
If I hadn't come here,
my dad would've killed you by now.
Remember, you didn't show mercy to me.
I'm showing mercy to you
and sparing your life.
You may live.
Dad.
Wow!
-Do you like this one?
-I want this one.
-Shall we buy it?
-Yes.
One guy came to your house
with his wife and kid.
On your daughter's birthday,
your husband went to his salon.
He forgot the necklace there.
By the time he could return it
to your home, a lot had happened.
We even went to your house a few times.
But it was locked.
We looked everywhere
and finally found you in this house.
Hey.
Hand it over.
Please. I don't want
that piece of jewelry.
I wonder how many families
he killed and robbed to buy this.
Please donate it to some temple.
I wish that even a small gift
my daughter receives
must come from hard-earned money.
Hey.
Go to the shop across the road
and buy her a doll.
In that accident,
only one child survived,
and they took her to the hospital.
But I heard that the kid succumbed
to the injuries and died.
Ammu!
Nothing. Let's leave.
Come.
Ammu!
-Ammu!
-You guys keep walking. I'll be back.
Ammu!
Hey…
That's my daughter, isn't she?
Isn't she my daughter? Tell me.
Ammu!
Oh God! Please forgive me, O my deity!
Hey…
She's my daughter, isn't she?
Please tell me!
Let me talk to her once.
Just once! Please!
I promise I won't tell her
that I'm her father.
Ammu!
Please call her. I beg you.
Please call her. Please call my daughter.
Please call my daughter.
Please!
Please bring her here.
Let me ask for forgiveness. Call her.
She's my daughter, isn't she?
Tell me!
Bring her here.
She's my daughter.
Ammu!
Ammu…