(MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Tie it off, come on!
(THUDS)
(GASPS)
Hey, guys! Guys,
I think we should turn back.
And lose good money?
Not a chance.
Stay close.
Here we are.
Get on his back.
(GRUNTS)
(MAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL WHIMPERING)
Hurry up.
Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
-(GRUNTING)
- MAN: Ow!
Whoa! (GROANS)
(BOTH GASP)
MAN 2: There he is.
Go get him.
Oh, you'll pay for that.
(PANTING)
(WHIMPERING)
-(GRUNTING)
-(CREATURE YELPING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
No. No, please.
Please, no.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Hold it there.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREATURE MUTTERING)
I only got one...
but he's a fine specimen.
(LICKSPITTLE GROANS)
- That's all?
- LICKSPITTLE: Yeah.
That shroom bit me twice.
LICKSPITTLE: Huh.
Tomb Bloom.
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
NARRATOR: Once upon a time...
or perhaps twice upon a time,
for you may
remember this story...
there was a powerful Fey
named Maleficent.
For some reason,
the mistress of evil
and protector of the Moors...
was still hated
after all this time.
True, she had cursed
the princess, Aurora...
but that was before
she found light
in the heart
of a human child...
and raised the girl
as her own.
After all,
it was Maleficent's love
which broke
that very same curse.
But that detail was somehow
mysteriously forgotten.
For as the tale was told
over and again
throughout the kingdom...
Maleficent became the villain
once more.
(CREATURES CHITTERING)
(FROG CROAKING)
(YAWNS)
KNOTGRASS: It's time, guys.
Come on. Let's get everyone.
THISTLEWIT: It's the big day!
FLITTLE: Come on.
THISTLEWIT: Let's go!
FLITTLE: Wake up. Wake up.
(FAIRIES CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
KNOTGRASS: Come on.
(FAIRIES COOING)
(YAWNING)
(FAIRY CHATTERING)
Hurry up, wallerbogs!
It's time!
(WALLERBOGS GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
Do you both remember
the secret plan?
I've got it all right here.
When do I tell the queen
the secret?
You must be patient,
Thistlewit.
Do you think Queen Aurora's
awake yet?
Well, she's not
"Sleeping Beauty" anymore.
-(LAUGHING)
- I see what you did there.
(GIGGLES)
(FAIRIES CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
AURORA: Next item of business,
the missing fairies.
I've sent more sprites
to search
the Tomb Bloom field.
They'll report back to me
at nightfall.
We will keep searching
until we find them.
(MUTTERING)
AURORA: Please don't raise
your roots at me, Lief.
Crushing humans with branches
is not going to help.
(CAWING)
Diaval, you're supposed to be
on my side.
-(GRUNTS)
(AURORA SIGHS)
Well, I'm Queen of the Moors,
and I am a human.
(MUTTERS)
AURORA: We must all learn
a little kindness.
KNOTGRASS: Coming through.
Excuse us.
Official pixie business.
FLITTLE: A word, Your Majesty.
- Maybe two.
- AURORA: Aunties...
you need to wait your turn
like everyone else.
- THISTLEWIT: No!
- This can't wait, Your Grace.
Not for a moment.
Or I might burst.
Truly, I might.
Is that...?
(CHITTERS)
Pinto!
She's come bearing gifts.
The first sap
from the warming trees.
- It's for the big day!
-(BOTH GASP)
Quiet, Thistlewit.
What big day?
(PINTO CHITTERING)
AURORA: Hey! My crown!
I'm not in the mood for this.
Pinto!
Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Come on.
Where are you going, aunties?
(ALL GROAN)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
PINTO: Whoa!
AURORA: I don't have time
for games, Pinto.
(PINTO CHATTERING)
(BRANCH CREAKING)
-(BRANCH SNAPS)
-(GASPS)
(YELPS)
(ALL GASP)
(PANTING)
What's gotten into all of you?
(CREATURES MUMBLING)
Oh. Uh-oh!
(GRUNTING)
There she goes, Your Majesty.
(PINTO CHITTERING)
AURORA: Come back here.
Pinto. I've had enough
of your games for today.
Look at me.
(GASPS) Oh.
Philip.
What are you doing here?
I was looking for you.
- Oh, well, hello.
- Hello.
I'm really sorry,
I can't talk right now.
The Moors have turned
to madness.
I've got a castle
full of complaints.
- Know how busy you are.
- Oh!!
I wanted to ask you something.
Yes.
Do you think there
could be a union
between Ulstead and the Moors?
A union?
To connect both lands.
To bring harmony and peace.
I've been imagining a bridge.
Oh, a bridge.
Yes, a bridge.
A union's a wonderful idea...
if both sides are willing.
(SIGHS) Well, I'm working
on that part.
He's going to blow it.
Give him time.
He's warming up.
Wait.
That's your formal coat.
You're in on all of this,
aren't you?
If you're busy,
I could always come back.
No. No, no.
I'm not busy at all.
No, because I'd hate to...
Really. All ears.
What did you
want to talk about?
You're right.
He's blowing it.
Five years ago,
I thought I lost you forever.
I've decided to reclaim
this day for us.
I've loved you
since the moment I met you
and every day since.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
If love has a truth,
here is mine.
There is No magic nor curse
that could ever tear me away
from you, Aurora.
Are you sure
this is a good time?
Oh, Philip.
Oh, he's on his knee.
He took his sweet time
about it.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Yes! Yes, just stand up.
Kiss me.
(CREATURES CHEERING)
(AURORA GIGGLING HAPPILY)
KNOTGRASS:
We're having a wedding!
A secret surprise wedding.
(GIGGLES)
(FAIRIES GIGGLING)
Of course,
we have to tell our parents.
Do we?
(CAWING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(PHILIP URGES HORSE)
(CAWING INSISTENTLY)
(SCREECHES)
(PANTS)
Mistress.
MALEFICENT: What?
DIAVAL:
I have a little bit of news.
MALEFICENT: Well, on with it.
It's nothing
of any real consequence...
and it's certainly
no reason to overreact.
It's just that...
Prince Philip has, um...
MALEFICENT: Disappeared?
(CHUCKLES) No.
No. Philip has...
Yellow fever? No, wait!
Leprosy!
No, Mistress.
Prince Philip has asked Aurora
if she'll become his...
MALEFICENT: Don't...
ruin my morning.
DIAVAL: Mistress, please.
Stay calm!
PERCIVAL: So, tell me, sire...
am I to be a best man,
or did you choose a creature
from the Moors?
General, if that's your way
of asking me
if she said yes, then I, uh...
I know she said yes, sire.
What human wouldn't want
to leave that place?
What do you have against
Moor folk, Percival?
"Moor folk"? Is that what
we're calling them now?
Winged beasts,
murderous trees.
Guard your tongue, General.
You know nothing about them.
I know that Maleficent
is a killer of men...
destroyer of armies.
Or so the story goes.
She's not like that.
It's my job to protect
this kingdom.
And I will do so,
old friend...
without hesitation.
Walk on. (URGES HORSE)
Open the gates!
(CAT YOWLING)
Your Majesty,
spoils from the annexation
of the Midlands have arrived.
Weapons.
No. We have no need of arms.
Our days of war are over.
(MEOWING)
KING JOHN: Ingrith...
you see where
I've had you placed.
Right behind me.
QUEEN INGRITH: And that's
where I'll always be.
KING JOHN: Ingrith, I said
we had no need of arms.
One can never be too careful.
Your Majesty, it's cocked.
Is it, now?
(TRUMPETS PLAYING FANFARE)
- Father, Mother.
- Well?
What did she say?
She said yes.
Yes! (LAUGHS)
That is wonderful news. Oh!
Two kingdoms united at last.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOFTLY) Yes.
Yes.
Perhaps I've been selfish...
looking at this the wrong way.
You've made your choice.
Now is a time to celebrate.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm glad you finally approve.
QUEEN INGRITH:
Much more than that.
I am ready to welcome
your fiancée with open arms.
(CHUCKLING)
QUEEN INGRITH:
She shall come to dinner.
That would be incredible.
Under one condition.
She will bring her godmother.
Your Majesty, I strongly...
We will meet the one
who raised her
right here in this castle.
KING JOHN: Yes.
The queen is right.
PHILIP: I'm not sure
her godmother will...
-(SHUSHES)
- No, but I insist.
After all,
we will soon be family.
Well, let it be known
throughout the kingdom...
that my son
is to marry Aurora.
(LAUGHS)
And Maleficent
is coming to dinner.
I shall
send word straightaway.
(SIGHS)
(CHITTERING)
Oh!
(GASPS AND MUTTERS)
Incoming.
FLITTLE:
Hold on to your petticoats!
(YELPING)
Well, well.
So?
So.
Godmother...
Philip asked me to marry him.
Poor thing.
He'll recover.
My answer was yes.
- No.
- Yes.
No.
I wasn't really asking.
Nor was I.
What's next?
You'll turn him into a goat?
Hmm.
Stop.
Why don't you like Philip?
Well, for one thing,
he's human.
I'm a human.
And I have never
held that against you.
Until I fell in love.
Love doesn't always
end well, Beasty.
FLITTLE: I'll have you know
Prince Philip is a prince.
A very handsome
and charming prince.
(ALL SCREAMING)
I'm just asking you
to trust me.
Please give him a chance.
Let us prove you wrong.
Philip is thoughtful...
he's very kind...
Kind of what?
The king and queen
are celebrating tonight...
and they have invited
both of us to the castle.
You want me
to meet his parents?
It's just a dinner.
They don't want me in Ulstead.
Why on earth would I go?
Because his mother
wishes to meet mine.
Please.
KING JOHN: Philip.
I want you
to wear this tonight.
Your sword?
Because of you,
Ulstead and the Moors
will be united at last.
(SIGHS)
Father, my love for Aurora
has nothing to do
with politics.
Yes, but your love...
will ensure peace
for generations.
Now take it. And wear it...
to know that
you will never have to use it.
Oh, my son.
(INHALES)
I've never been more proud.
PHILIP: And what about Mother?
Is she okay with this?
Your mother will learn
to love who you love.
(RUMBLING)
(METAL CLANGING)
(MEN CHATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Onh.
Tomb Bloom. Tomb Bloom.
(GRUNTS)
(MUTTERING)
LICKSPITTLE: Oh.
-(QUEEN INGRITH SNEEZES)
-(LICKSPITTLE GASPS)
I'm losing my patience.
Your Majesty.
You need to move faster,
Lickspittle.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(WHIMPERING)
QUEEN INGRITH:
Aurora said yes.
It's all coming together...
perfectly.
MALEFICENT: Hello.
Hello.
Try it with
a little less fang.
How's this?
Try the greeting.
How kind of you
to invite me this evening.
Remember, it's not a threat.
So very kind of you
to invite me this evening.
- Yeah. Better.
- Oh.
Try it with a curtsy.
We can skip that part.
(MALEFICENT SIGHS)
She really loves that boy,
you know.
You're doing her
a great kindness.
Kindness?
Mistress...
(SIGHS)
Doesn't she look lovely?
I have something for you.
Hmm?
AURORA: For your horns.
I just thought it might make
Philip's family
feel more comfortable.
And you, as well.
Maybe it's a bad idea.
No, it's...
It's all right.
I'm so excited. (CHUCKLES)
Mmm...
It's more than I can bear.
(DIAVAL SCOFFS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
-(THUDS)
-(RUMBLING)
- WOMAN:: It's Maleficent!
-(TOWNSPEOPLE CLAMORING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Pitchforks?
- Humans are hilarious.
- DIAVAL: Mmm-hmm.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
- It's getting better.
- MALEFICENT: Hmm.
(TOWNSPEOPLE CLAMORING)
PERCIVAL: Anyone leaves
their post gets hung.
GUARD: Yes, sir.
(TRUMPETS PLAYING FANFARE)
They're here.
Have you ever considered
turning me into a bear?
I think I'd make
quite an impressive one.
Look at their claws.
They're so strong.
Why are we
talking about bears?
Presenting Queen Aurora
of the Moors.
(PLAYING COURTLY TUNE)
-(DOORS CLOSE)
- AURORA: Thank you.
PHILIP: You look wonderful.
AURORA: I'm so happy
to be here.
Aurora, this is
truly an honor.
Welcome to Ulstead.
Such a beautiful girl.
I can see how you stole
Philip's heart.
- Your Majesty.
-(SNIFFS)
(GRUNTS)
The flowers in your hair.
I'm allergic.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no. No, no.
It's all right.
They're beautiful.
Presenting Maleficent.
(CLATTERING)
(GROWLING)
Maleficent, it's wonderful
to see you again.
(DOORS CLOSE)
This is my father,
King John of Ulstead.
And my mother, Queen Ingrith.
Welcome to our home.
It's so very kind of you
to invite me this evening.
(QUIETLY) Don't smile.
And, um, I would like
to introduce you to Diaval.
I trust you had no trouble
finding the castle.
Why would I have trouble?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Shoo!
He's making small talk.
I'll explain it later.
No trouble at all.
Your Majesties,
ladies and gentlemen,
dinner is served.
Please, make yourselves
at home.
(MUSICIANS PLAYING
COURTLY MUSIC)
(CHAIRS SCRAPING)
MALEFICENT: Hmm.
Bird.
Delicious.
(DIAVAL CLEARS THROAT)
Is there a problem?
It's iron.
Majesty, as you are
sensitive to flowers,
she is averse to iron.
I had no idea.
Take it away at once.
I trust you'll be comfortable
using your hands?
(CLEARS THROAT) Such a warm
spell of weather, isn't it?
It certainly is.
(MEOWS)
Shoo!
Well, we have a small gift
for Philip and Aurora...
to celebrate their
glorious future together. Hmm?
QUEEN INGRITH:
Oh, I simply can't wait
to have a little one running
through the castle again.
This castle?
Yes, of course.
This will be their home.
I hear Aurora has
a castle of her own.
AURORA: Yes, sir, I do.
Yes...
I'm curious. How did Aurora
become Queen of the Moors?
MALEFICENT: I made her queen.
PHILIP: Her castle is
quite stunning.
You must see it.
Yes, but in fact,
she has another castle.
Does she not?
PHILIP: Mother...
One in the Moors,
and one left behind
by her father.
King Stefan, was it not?
That castle was never my home.
It was given to the people.
So, you're also
a true princess.
Even though Stefan died.
Was killed?
Remind me,
did he die or was he killed?
Both.
Yes, you're right,
it is very warm recently.
Because I remember
the story of a baby.
A baby cursed to sleep...
and never wake up.
KING JOHN: Really?
Who would do
such a terrible thing
to an innocent child?
Well, there are many who prey
on the innocent.
I'm sure
your kind would agree.
What do you mean, my kind?
She means humans.
There are fairies missing
from the Moors.
What I'm missing is some wine.
Stolen by human poachers.
That's the first
I've heard of it.
Someone gave the order.
It sounds as if
you're accusing the king.
No, she never said that.
Wait... Sorry,
who would steal a fairy?
Your Majesty, I must report
that two peasants
were found dead...
just outside the Moors.
They'd been missing
for several days.
I see.
- Yes, we all see.
-(GROWLING)
The borders are open,
but humans are not welcome.
Isn't that right?
(HISSES)
What exactly are you implying,
Your Majesty?
Innocent men are being
slaughtered on the Moors...
and she's talking
about fairies.
(SCREECHING)
Contain your animal.
Or I will,
(SWORD UNSHEATHES)
(CAT WHINING)
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were
making a threat.
Well, do you?
- Do I what?
- Know better?
Enough.
(WHISPERS) Put her down.
Please, put her down.
-(CAT YOWLS)
- We're here to celebrate.
Forgive me, he's right.
Let's not forget
why we're here.
The start of a new life
for Aurora.
- Cheers.
- AURORA AND PHILIP: Cheers.
You have done
an admirable job,
Maleficent...
going against your own nature
to raise this child.
But now...
Aurora will finally get...
the love of a real family.
A real mother.
Because the one thing
I regret...
is never having a daughter
of my own.
But tonight changes that.
Tonight,
I consider Aurora my own.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Guards!
We have opened our home
to a witch!
(GUARD YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Stop!
There is no union.
There will be no wedding.
- Maleficent!
- We must protect the king!
Maleficent, please, stop now.
John, I'm so frightened.
Ah!
What has she done to me?
(GROANS)
PHILIP: Father!
(GROANING)
QUEEN INGRITH: John!
We go home.
It's a curse.
It's a curse!
Maleficent has cursed
the king!
What have you done?
I've done nothing.
Aurora, we go home now.
Auroral
Wake him!
Wake him, please.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(CAWING)
(GASPS)
(SHATTERING)
(CAWING)
(YELLING)
GUARD: Stand aside!
To the bedroom!
DOCTOR: This magic, we have
no tools to reverse it.
There must be a lesion.
Proof of her witchery.
QUEEN INGRITH: Please,
leave His Majesty his dignity.
We all saw
what Maleficent did to him.
(QUIETLY) I'm so sorry.
A curse upon our king
is a curse upon this kingdom.
All he wanted was peace.
This is all my fault.
You have nothing
to apologize for, my dear.
Maleficent is a threat
to everyone.
Especially you.
We'll do our best
to protect you.
There must be a way
to reverse this.
Mother,
could you try kissing him?
True love and all that.
(SCOFFS)
I doubt that would work.
AURORA: It could save him.
- A Kiss is just a kiss.
- Please, Mother.
Very well.
(WHISPERING)
You wanted peace...
now rest in peace forever.
I told you.
This is no fairy tale.
I have to return to the Moors.
It's the only way.
Wait, wait. Come here.
I have to find her.
It's the middle of the night.
She will break the curse.
I know she will.
Okay, well,
let me come with you.
No. You should stay
with your family.
You are my family.
QUEEN INGRITH:
Let her go, Philip.
Maybe she can save him.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Maleficent!
(CREATURES CHATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
Godmother!
(PINTO CHITTERING)
Please come back.
DIAVAL:
She's not in the Moors.
Diaval.
No one's seen her.
I'm so happy to see you.
She's nowhere to be found.
What if she never comes back?
I could be stuck
as a human forever.
I have to find her.
She's the only one
who can break the curse.
(CHITTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(BABY AURORA CRYING)
Tell me she's dead.
The iron pierced her flesh.
She fell into the river
and went over the falls.
Then where is her head?
There was something else.
Another creature.
It pulled her
from the depths of the sea.
What did it look like?
Her.
It carried her
up into the sky.
Hmm. A wounded animal
lashes out
and now she's not alone.
We must be ready for war.
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
GUARD: Maleficent has
cursed the king!
(METAL CLANGING)
(TOWNSPEOPLE CLAMORING)
GUARD 2: Stay inside!
GUARD 3: Maleficent has
cursed the king!
(GASPING)
(FAINT RUMBLING)
(WINGS WHOOSHING)
(VOICES ECHOING)
(RUSTLING)
(WINGS WHOOSHING)
(VOICES GROWING LOUDER)
(GRUNTS)
(VOICES CONTINUE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BORRA: If Conall hadn't
found her, she would be dead.
They tried to kill her
with this.
(IRON HISSING)
Do you hear it?
Huh?
It's a message
from the humans.
I hear it loud and clear.
Time for us to die.
CONALL: Humans have used iron
against us for centuries.
And we are almost extinct
because of it.
CONALL: Killing peasants
on the Moors
will only lead
to more conflict, Borra.
They've pulled the iron
from the earth...
made their swords and shields,
drove us underground.
But this...
This will finish us.
CONALL: Our people are safe
here for now.
BORRA: But for how long?
The humans will find us.
They will not stop.
I call for war.
(ALL GRUNTING IN AGREEMENT)
BORRA: I call for war!
Right now!
(ALL GRUNT IN AGREEMENT)
CONALL: There are
too many humans.
(CLATTERS)
Too many kingdoms.
BORRA: Conall,
they will keep finding
new ways to destroy us.
We can't win.
We can't win!
Not this way.
No. You're wrong, Conall.
We have something
they didn't plan on.
We have her.
She holds powers
none of us possess.
She is wounded, Borra.
Who are you?
(GRUNTS)
(SNIFFING)
Hmm.
(CONTINUES SNIFFING)
You reek of human.
Maybe I was wrong about you.
Or maybe Conall should have
left you for dead
at the bottom of the sea.
No.
It's there, isn't it?
It's inside you.
Mmm.
(LAUGHING)
-(HISSES)
_Ahhh!
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
You see?
You see what's inside her?
(ALL MUTTERING IN AGREEMENT)
That is what will save us all.
(ALL CLAMORING)
You saved me.
Come.
Let me show you who we are.
(WHOOSHING)
(GROANS)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
We're Dark Fey.
Same as you.
(BABY CRYING)
CONALL: We're all that remain.
Unseen here,
far away from mankind.
Look!
(CHILD GIGGLING)
CONALL: As more
human kingdoms emerged,
we went into hiding...
from every corner
of the earth...
doing what we had to,
to survive.
But many were lost.
(DARK FEY CHANTING)
CONALL: Only a few
generations ago...
our kind roamed
every part of the world.
The tundra.
The forest.
The jungle.
The desert.
Now,
our only refuge is here...
in this cave.
Our nest of origin.
(DARK FEY WHISPERING)
UDO: Listen. Play in the wind.
Go!
(GRUNTS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(CHILD GIGGLING)
(MALEFICENT LAUGHS)
CONALL: Those children
should be soaring
over the trees and rivers.
Instead,
they are raised in exile.
I could protect them.
How? By waging war
against the humans?
I've been at war with them
my whole life.
Not all of them.
There was one you raised
as your own.
Maybe we don't have to hide
from the humans.
Maybe we can exist
without fear...
and war.
Find a way together.
That will never happen.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
-(EXHALES)
-(WIND WHISTLING)
(GASPS AND MUTTERS)
(PANTING)
(CHITTERS)
Whoa. (GASPS)
-(CAT YOWLS)
-(WHIMPERS)
(GROWLS)
Whoa!
(PINTO SCREAMING)
-(GRUNTING)
-(CAT MEOWS)
(WHIMPERING AND GRUNTING)
(YELPING)
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
Ow! Oh.
LICKSPITTLE: Huh?
-(PINTO GRUNTS)
-(GASPS)
LICKSPITTLE: Gotcha!
(PINTO CHITTERING)
-(YELLS)
- Welcome to your new home.
(PINTO CHITTERS)
(CHITTERS)
(EXCLAIMS)
We've been worried
about you, dear.
AURORA: Your Majesty.
I couldn't find her.
My heart breaks for you.
She has brought
a cloud of darkness
upon your happiness.
I know she was
against this marriage.
Never trusted your instincts
as a queen.
When I saw her at dinner...
with her horns covered...
bent cowering...
(SIGHS)
Well, it's no wonder
that she lashed out.
I just don't know what to do.
You do truly love him,
don't you?
My son.
Deeply.
It is love that will heal you.
It's what heals us all.
Let's move forward together...
as a family.
(TRUMPETS PLAYING FANFARE)
To all who live
on the Moors...
(ECHOING)
- What is that noise?
-(SHUSHING)
GERDA: ...and kingdoms
far and wide,
the king and queen
invite you...
to attend the wedding...
of their son Philip to Aurora
in three days' time.
All are welcome.
Huh?
And all are expected!
Did you hear that?
We're invited to the castle!
I knew Aurora
wouldn't abandon us!
I always knew I'd be invited.
Just glad you two
made the cut.
FAIRY: Who's getting married?
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Aurora, we don't have to think
about the wedding right now.
AURORA: The queen is right.
We owe it to everyone...
especially the king.
What about Maleficent?
She's gone.
CONALL: The Phoenix.
It is said the Dark Fey
began with her...
evolved over centuries.
You are the last
of her descendants.
Her blood is your own.
You are her.
In your hands, you hold
the power of life and death...
destruction and rebirth.
But nature's greatest power
is the power
of true transformation.
You transformed
when you raised Aurora.
When you found love...
in the middle of your pain.
I'm asking you
to take all of your fury...
all of your pain...
and not use it.
Help us broker peace
with the humans.
Because peace...
could be the Dark Fey's
final transformation.
The Moors are
our last true nature on earth.
And yet you named
a human as queen.
A daughter you cared for.
I have no daughter.
She has chosen her side.
We've just heard.
There's going to be a wedding
at the castle in three days.
Humans will come
from all over.
That's when we attack.
We'll kill the king and queen
of Ulstead...
and their young prince.
Their kingdom will fall.
And the Fey will rise again.
-(BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE)
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(GIGGLES)
The fairies made it.
I wore it
when I married the king.
I'm sure it's perfect.
Soam I
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Your Majesty,
she's absolutely lovely.
NOBLEWOMAN: Considering
how she was raised.
By the same evil witch
who cursed her.
It's a miracle Prince Philip
came along.
NOBLEWOMAN 2: It's a miracle
the poor child is alive
at all.
Thank you so much.
It's exquisite.
(CHATTERING CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHTER)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
AURORA: When I'm older...
I'm going to live here,
in the Moors, with you.
Then we can
look after each other.
(WAVES CRASHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
- Tell me what's troubling you.
- AURORA: (SIGHS) It's nothing.
Aurora,
I know you better than that.
This jewelry...
my hair...
all these rules.
(STAMMERS) I can't breathe.
I feel like I'm not
Queen of the Moors anymore.
I feel like
a different person.
Listen...
I fell in love with a girl
in the forest and only her.
You don't have to change.
I don't want you to change.
I should have never asked her
to wear that scarf.
(AURORA EXHALES DEEPLY)
Ah, yes.
- QUEEN INGRITH: Well...
-(GASPS)
Does it work?
LICKSPITTLE:
I only have a handful
of fairy specimens
to work with...
and the extraction process
is painstaking.
Extraction from what?
LICKSPITTLE:
Tomb Bloom flowers.
They grow from
a fairy's grave,
contain their very essence.
When you mix the pollen
with iron powder...
the resulting dust
ends a fairy's life.
We will need thousands more.
Show me.
LICKSPITTLE: Very well.
(FAIRY WHIMPERING)
LICKSPITTLE: So...
-(CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
-(PINTO CHITTERS)
(GASPS)
(FAIRY GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERING)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHITTERING)
(EXHALES)
Finally,
the Moors will be mine.
No more fairies.
(CHITTERS IN FEAR)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-(CHANTING)
(DRUMS BEATING)
PERCIVAL: Stay alert, men.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
CHILD: Wow!
PEASANT: This is where
I found them.
PERCIVAL: Excellent.
But what if
the winged one returns?
Don't you worry about that.
We'll be ready.
Take the Tomb Blooms.
Get to work!
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
GUARD: Sentries, stay alert!
PERCIVAL:
Keep your weapons on hand.
(INDISTINCT SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
GUARD: Move it!
CONALL: Maleficent...
(SIGHS)
MALEFICENT: This is where
we bury our dead.
They've destroyed it.
This is what the humans do.
They're nothing but locusts
that swarm the earth.
We have to stop them.
You spent years
caring for a human...
now it's time
to care for your own.
SOLDIER: Fire!
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
- SOLDIER: Reload! We go again!
-(MALEFICENT PANTING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
SOLDIER: Fire!
SOLDIER 2: Reload!
There's another one!
(GROANS)
(ALL GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING
AND GROANING)
(SCREAMING ECHOES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE)
(ALL CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
Everyone, stay together!
We're about to leave
the Moors.
Grab the hand or the wing...
or the tail of whoever
is closest to you.
(YELPS)
(BELLS TOLLING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(FAIRIES GIGGLING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
Hey, over here!
Yeah, over here!
Hold formation, guards.
Hold formation.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Stop right there.
I'm with the bride.
We've been told
to let the, uh, other kind
find their seats first.
But I'm not a human.
- I'm a raven.
- What?
A raven. The black bird.
Mmm. This rice is delicious.
FLITTLE: You're supposed
to throw it
at the bride and groom.
What? And waste good rice?
NOBLEWOMAN 1:
What's the hold up?
(CLAMORING)
NOBLEWOMAN 2: Let me in!
Why can't humans come in, too?
NOBLEMAN:
Why can't we come in?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
PHILIP:
I know it's bad luck...
but I had to see you.
For you.
A Tomb Bloom?
Where did you get this?
From my mother.
The sun's up.
It's our wedding day.
PHILIP: (ECHOING)
From my mother.
(CREAKS)
(THUD)
-(RUMBLING)
(AURORA GASPS)
(GASPING)
(DARK FEY CHANTING)
(SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(ALL GIGGLING)
(GRUNTING)
(FAIRIES CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
THISTLEWIT:
Where should we sit, Flittle?
FLITTLE: On the left.
We're with the bride.
KNOTGRASS: Yes, we are.
But the groom's lovely, too.
Mmm. Yes, he is.
I'm with both.
Huh? (SCOFFS)
(SNORTS)
(WHISTLING)
LICKSPITTLE: (GRUNTS) Now.
(GASPS AND CHITTERS)
(BOTH CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
What's this?
Nobody is allowed in here
except me.
And I'm already here,
SO go away!
(AURORA BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(KING JOHN SCREAMS)
-(GASPS)
Maleficent, please stop.
(GASPING)
(WHISPERS) Maleficent.
She didn't do it.
(COOS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Get out!
Before I call the guards!
(FAIRIES WHIMPERING)
The missing fairies.
I said get out.
Did you hear me?
- What have you done?
-(WHIMPERING)
-(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
-(RIPS)
You're a pixie.
How dare you call me that?
I'm Lickspittle,
the nobleman...
and I serve the queen.
She took your wings.
We have to release them.
They belong on the Moors.
QUEEN INGRITH:
As you do, Aurora.
(BOTH GASP)
A human who has betrayed
her kind.
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
You put the curse on the king.
Oh, dear.
You may be queen...
but you are very young.
Ruling humans
is a bit more complicated...
than running around barefoot
with flowers in your hair.
When I was young...
my family's kingdom
bordered the Moors.
And one
particularly harsh winter...
our crops died...
and the people
began to suffer.
And as we looked
over our walls...
we could see
the fairies thriving.
My brother and I believed we
should take what we needed...
while my father, the king,
sought their kindness.
Choosing peace
over our people,
he sent my brother
to do his bidding.
He never came back.
Those savages...
creatures who could
barely grunt,
let alone engage in talks,
Killed him.
I don't believe that.
Our people became fearful.
They overthrew my father.
The land fell into chaos.
I was cast out.
Forced by fate into marriage
with King John of Ulstead.
Another weak king
speaking of
tolerance and civility.
And now, my own son...
corrupted with visions
of harmony.
But peace
will not be our downfall.
(GASPS AND MUTTERS)
Now lock her up.
A war is coming.
(GRUNTING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
No! No!
(BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE)
I wish you could be here
with me.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
Conall wanted peace...
and they filled him with iron.
Now, we will have our war.
Our fight begins now!
-(ALL GRUNT IN AGREEMENT)
- We will rise together!
- We fight together.
And we will show them
no mercy!
(ALL GRUNTING)
DARK FEY WARRIOR: Come on! Go!
- Go! Go!
-(GRUNTING)
Go! Go! Go!
(ALL CHITTERING EXCITEDLY)
THISTLEWIT:
Where are all Philip's guests?
- Humans are poor timekeepers.
- Mmm.
Start the music.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
(CREATURES CHITTERING)
-(ORGAN PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
-(GASPS)
(GASPS)
-(PANTING)
- GUARD: Come on! Come on!
(GUARDS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ORGAN CONTINUES PLAYING)
(HISSING)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING)
(POWDER HISSING)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
-(BANGING ON DOOR)
-(AURORA SCREAMS)
(OBJECT SHATTERS)
GUARD: She's gone.
Hey!
(PLAYS NOTE)
(ALL SCREAMING)
It's a trap! Get down!
(ALL WHIMPERING)
-(CONTINUES PLAYING ORGAN)
-(CREATURES SCREAMING)
(HORN BLOWS IN DISTANCE)
Your Majesty...
they're coming from the sea.
-(BANGING ON DOOR)
-(GUARD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
She escaped!
(PANTING)
Down this way, come on!
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Your Highness.
Upon my command.
(PANTING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
GUARD 1: Check every room!
(GUARD 2
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
GUARD 3: She can't be far!
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(SHRIEKS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
QUEEN INGRITH: Wait.
Wait.
(SOLDIERS MURMURING)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
What's going on?
Now.
PERCIVAL: (SHOUTS) Fire!
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
- DARK FEY WARRIOR: No!
-(DARK FEY WARRIORS SCREAMING)
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(SCREAMS)
-(PANTING)
-(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE)
They look just like her.
(DARK FEY WARRIORS GROANING)
Withdraw!
SHRIKE: Pull back!
Maleficent's starting a war.
First my father, and now this.
Philip! She didn't curse him.
- Maleficent.
- What?
She never cursed him.
It was your mother.
What are you saying?
It was the spindle.
The curse is still in it.
Your mother used it
against your father.
Look.
It's the same.
She's locked the Moor folk
in the chapel.
This isn't a wedding.
It's a trap.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
Remember where you came from.
Remember who you are.
I've made my choice.
You'll have to make yours.
(CONALL GASPING)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Stay low!
Divide!
Follow me!
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
Attack!
(DARK FEY WARRIORS SHOUTING)
- Ignite!
- PERCIVAL: (SHOUTS) Ignite!
(YELLING)
(DARK FEY WARRIORS YELLING)
-(GROANS)
-(SCREAMS) No!
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
(ALL CLAMORING)
-(GRUNTS)
-(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING, YELLING)
(AURORA PANTING)
(CREATURES SCREAMING)
AURORA: Aunties! Aunties!
It's too heavy!
Auroral
Diaval! You're here.
FLITTLE: Oh, what's happening?
(CONTINUES PLAYING ORGAN)
(FAIRIES WHIMPERING)
(ALL GASP)
Weapon change!
Weapon change! Go!
(DARK FEY WARRIOR SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(TOWNSPEOPLE SCREAMING)
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
Mother!
You have to stop this.
We are at war.
This isn't a war.
It's a massacre.
Philip, you don't understand.
These creatures stand
between us...
and everything
we need to survive.
PHILIP: You're wrong.
We can stand together.
Well, you're a fool
to believe that.
You don't know what it takes
to fight for our kind.
You lied to me.
I am protecting the kingdom...
and your throne.
What about Father?
Were you protecting him, too?
The prince
is not feeling well.
See him to his chambers.
Now.
Sire, stop!
(PHILIP GRUNTS)
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
Yield! Yield!
My mother cursed the king
so she could destroy
the Moor folk.
Your men
are paying heavily for it.
(YELLING)
We have to do something!
(FAIRIES CHITTERING)
Goodbye, girls.
(GRUNTING)
THISTLEWIT: No, come back!
Flittle! No!
(CONTINUES PLAYING ORGAN)
(ORGAN STOPS PLAYING)
(FAILED NOTES)
BOTH: (SCREAMING) No!
Hey, you, stay with your own!
Run, Aurora, run!
Let him go!
(FAIRIES SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
No! No!
(RUMBLES)
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
Godmother.
(RUMBLING)
(GROANING)
(ALL GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
THISTLEWIT: For Flittle!
(FAIRIES GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
- SOLDIER: We've got her!
-(GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
(GRUNTING)
Huh?
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(CREATURES CLAMORING)
Go! Go!
This way! This way!
Go!
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Stand down!
This is not my fight.
My mother wanted a war,
and you're giving it to her.
I won't allow her hatred
to ruin my kingdom or yours.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
There will be no Fey blood
on my hands.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(YELLS)
This way!
(CREATURES CHITTERING)
Maleficent's back!
She's going for the queen.
Yield! Yield!
Stand down!
Lower your weapons!
There's the evil
that I promised them.
Your kind is more predictable
than humans.
(GRUNTS)
AURORA: Stop!
Stop!
Well, almost.
Stop.
I'm sorry I doubted you,
but this isn't you.
-(SNARLS)
- There's another way.
I know who you are.
I Know you.
You do not.
(SOBS)
Yes, I do.
You're my mother.
(GASPING)
(AURORA SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(SCREAMING) No!
(SOBBING)
Do you know what
makes a great leader, Aurora?
The ability to instill fear
in your subjects...
and then use that fear...
SOLDIER: Your Majesty.
...against your enemies.
(BREATHES DEEPLY) So...
I spread the story
of the evil witch...
and the princess she cursed.
It didn't matter
who woke Sleeping Beauty.
They were all terrified.
And the story became legend.
(YELLING)
I know you think
I'm a monster.
But what I did to the king,
to Maleficent, to my son...
I did for Ulstead.
You are a traitor
to your kind,
and you will pay for it.
Maleficent is dead!
We will never again
live in fear!
- SOLDIER: Get back here!
-(AURORA SCREAMING)
Ulstead is free at last!
AURORA: (GRUNTING) Let me go!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
What's happening?
(ROARING)
(GASPS)
(TOWNSPEOPLE CLAMORING)
(ROARS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(GASPING)
-(GRUNTS)
(AURORA SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMING)
(MALEFICENT SCREECHING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
Well, well.
Hello, Beasty.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SNIFFLES)
(PANTING)
I missed you.
Did you bump your head, then?
I did.
(CHUCKLES)
MALEFICENT: Philip.
Yes?
Do you love my daughter?
With everything I have.
Good.
(MUTTERING)
I believe this belongs to you.
Curses don't end.
They're broken.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
It ends.
There will be
no more fighting.
Ulstead will never attack
the Moors again.
And from this day on...
we move forward...
and find our way...
in peace.
Together.
Today,
there will be a wedding.
Not just a union
of two people...
but a union of two kingdoms.
And all are invited...
all are safe...
and all are welcome.
(ALL MURMURING)
- KING JOHN: Hello, there.
-(CO0S)
(LAUGHS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(QUEEN INGRITH SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS, SNEEZES)
(SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPITS)
We cannot live
amongst monsters...
(BLEATING)
Someone should
really cover those horns.
If only Conall could see you.
Borra...
it's time to come home.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Hello.
Can you come here?
MALEFICENT: Yes?
Will you give me away?
Never.
(CHUCKLES) No.
Will you walk me
down the aisle?
(STAMMERS) Ah.
Yes.
(FAIRIES CHITTERING)
(AURORA GIGGLING)
(GROWLS, CHUCKLES)
Apologies to anyone
I might have mauled today.
(GOAT BLEATING)
(LAUGHTER)
(WHISPERS) Is that...?
She can change her back.
I suppose.
- Only if we wanted to.
-(ALL GASP AND APPLAUD)
- Father.
-(KING JOHN CHUCKLES)
(ALL CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
I'm so glad to see you.
I've dreamed of this moment.
Two kingdoms united at last.
And it's because of you.
I'm so proud of you. So proud.
(ALL CHEERING)
(MUTTERING)
She looks better in green.
Pink, you mean.
No, in green.
KNOTGRASS: Pink.
THISTLEWIT: Green.
(GASPS)
Flittle!
It's perfect. (CHUCKLES)
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNIFFLES)
Let her go.
-(MALEFICENT SIGHS)
-(SNIFFLES)
- Pull yourself together.
PRIEST: We are here to join
two kingdoms...
divided by fear.
Today, you teach us
we are not defined
by where we are from...
but by whom we love.
The bands, please.
(CHITTERING)
PRIEST: Do you, Philip,
take Aurora...
I do.
PRIEST: And do you,
Aurora, take...
I do.
Then I pronounce you
husband and wife.
-(ALL CHEERING)
- You may kiss the bride.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
(WHOOPS)
(GRUNTING)
You're smiling.
(CHUCKLES)
(PHILIP BREATHES DEEPLY)
It's a new day.
It Is.
Morning.
Will you stay awhile?
MALEFICENT: A little while.
But don't worry...
I'll see you
at the christening.
(PINTO MUTTERING)
PINTO: Hmm.
PINTO: Hmm. (GIGGLES)
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh
They tryna shoot down angels
They tryna pull
their wings off
So they can't fly
And, oh
But she's so brave, though
Just like a tornado
She's taking us by storm
You can't stop the girl
from going
You can't stop the world
from knowing
The truth will set you free
Oh
You can't stop the girl
from going
You can't stop the world
from knowing
The truth will set you free
Oh
You can't stop the girl
They tryna take our voices
They tryna make our choices
So we scream loud, loud, loud
And, oh
I know you feel the lightnin'
And it's so excitin'
So, here we come
You can't stop the girl
from going
You can't stop the world
from knowing
The truth will set you free
Oh
You can't stop the girl
from going
You can't stop the world
from knowing
The truth will set you free
Oh
You can't stop the girl
No, you can't stop the girl
Oh
I know you feel the lightnin'
And it's so excitin'
So, here we come
(SWEEPING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
PLAYING)