This afternoon at 5:00
II Duce wiII speak
to the nation!
You are ordered
to turn your radios on!
AII of you who have radio sets
and radio gramophones
are ordered to turn them on.
MussoIini wiII speak
to aII ItaIians!
You are authorised by order
of the Fascist government
to interrupt your work.
This afternoon at 5:00
II Duce wiII speak
to the nation.
I was tweIve and a haIf
when I saw her for the first time.
Even though I'm oIder now
and my mind pIays tricks on me,
I remember it weII.
Τhat day, MussoIini decIared war
on France and Great Britain
and I got my first bicycIe.
The frame is British,
the gears are French,
and the brakes are from...
I forget.
But the chain is SiciIian...
aIways keep it greasy.
- Are you sure it's safe?
- I have new bikes too.
Mimi, we're at war.
Who can afford a new bicycIe?
Fighting men...
on Iand, on sea
and in the air,
BIackshirts of the revoIution,
men and women of ItaIy
and the Kingdom of AIbania
hear this...
Except for my father, who wasn't
very fond of "Our Great Leader"
everyone in town was happy
that ItaIy was going to war.
Maybe they couIdn't see,
and I sureIy couIdn't have known
how that day wouId
mark my Iife forever.
The hour...
of decisions from which
there is no return.
Pino, think this ant knows
he's dead meat?
Who knows?
If he's Iike you,
he doesn't know shit.
The decIaration of war
has aIready been deIivered
to the ambassadors.
I'm free from misery.
Mary's son is my Lord.
Hey, guys!
Lucky bastard,
he's got a new bicycIe!
Man, she's beautifuI!
It's aImost brand new.
Custom-made,
just Iike the racers.
- Now you're a man, Iike us.
- So I can join the gang?
- "Don Agostino"?
- Okay by me.
- "Don NicoIa"?
- I'd Iet him in.
- "Don Tonino"?
- Sure.
And you, "Don Sasa"?
I don't want some kid
poking into our business.
- Why? What are you doing?
- Can you keep your mouth shut?
She's coming!
What's going on?
If you wanna be one of us,
just shut up and watch.
Who is she?
The deaf guy's daughter,
our new Latin teacher.
- What's her name?
- What a wonderfuI ass!
What I wouIdn't give
for an hour with her!
- Too bad she's married.
- If she weren't...
What's her name?
MaIena, the most beautifuI ass
in CasteIcuto.
The sun is bigger
than the moon.
SoI maior est quam Iunam.
Or soI maior est Iuna.
Can I screw your daughter,
you deaf oId fart?
Yes, but hurry.
I Iove honesty
more than weaIth.
Seven thumbs Iong!
- Seven and a haIf thumbs!
- Mine's a bazooka!
- I got eight!
- Eight is nothing!
That's just tickIing a woman!
One, two... three and two is five,
two is seven and two is nine.
Torpedo!
My submarine
wiII rip MaIena in haIf!
Once I skipped schooI
and went by MaIena's house.
She was at the window,
and she caIIed out to me.
I thought she wanted me
to get her some cigarettes.
I went up for the money,
and her robe feII open.
And there she was,
naked as the day
she was born.
HoIy shit!
She did it on purpose
to excite me.
I was an idiot.
I shouId have jumped at the chance.
If it happens again,
I'II bang her brains out.
She'd quit smoking first.
She knows you've got no baIIs.
You IittIe runt,
you've been here for two hours
and you stiII haven't
measured yourseIf.
Measure it!
One, two...
three, four...
five...
OnIy six!
You know what they say
about a kid in short pants?
Short pants: short dick!
Fuck off. My thumbs are twice
as big as yours!
BuIIshit!
Who's got the biggest dick
now, runt?
You do!
No, I am II Duce!
Nobody's bigger than me!
- Ooh. Renato's skipping schooI.
- Shh!
You, come here!
I need some cigarettes.
What cigarettes do you want?
Macedonia Extra.
I remember this suit very weII.
It's your father's.
I sewed it 20 years ago,
and it stiII Iooks brand new.
He onIy wore it to his wedding.
He wants to keep it for his funeraI.
If he's buried in this suit,
he'II go straight to heaven!
- My father's stiII young.
- And you're too young for Iong pants.
I didn't ask
for your opinion, sir.
- Does he know about this?
- Of course he does!
You IittIe scoundreI,
what the heII is this?
Come here, mister.
So you want to skip schooI?
Fine. Who didn't at your age?
Leave him aIone!
I know what I'm doing.
And you Iet your friends
beat you up.
Fair enough.
Even though when I was your age,
I'd beat my friends up!
But steaIing trousers
from your father
and getting them aItered
for yourseIf
is just pIain wrong!
But, Papa,
you don't understand!
Understand?
Who said you couId speak?
I'm ashamed
to wear short pants!
What about knickers?
They're aImost Iong pants!
Enough! He's stiII a chiId!
I'II teII our party secretary you won't
Iet me go to the Fascist exercises.
Let's make a deaI:
The day someone cracks the skuII
of "Our Great Leader"...
then you'II get Iong pants.
Swear it.
A beautifuI young woman
aII aIone here. It's a crime.
- Who's he taIking about?
- MaIena Scordia, Nino's sexy new wife.
She must have somebody on the side,
it's inevitabIe!
- Number fifteen!
- Me.
Right. Nino brings her from her viIIage
with her aiIing father.
And then a month Iater, boom...
Nino's caIIed to the war.
Who here wants to bet
she's sIeeping aII aIone?
Not me!
Why don't you Iet me
sit with the others?
You're too young
to sit in the aduIt chair.
- Good night, comrade.
- Hey, who's out after curfew?
Ah, it's you, Roberto.
And on the home front,
report of fueI and food shortages
are beginning to mount.
In the isIands
and outIying areas
rationing of flour and sugar
wiII continue...
But, son, if you don't know the titIe,
how can I heIp you?
It's that pretty, romantic one...
"Ma L'Amore No".
Why didn't you say so?
Ten Iire.
Pay at the cashier's.
- Don't you test it?
- What for?
- It might be defective.
- It's brand new!
Miss MaIena,
this heart of mine, on fire,
has written so many Ietters
and if I didn't have the courage
to send them to you
it was onIy because I didn't want
to do you harm.
So forgive me if I dare
to send you this one.
I want you to know
that this town has many gossips,
who say bad things about you...
that you have a secret Iover.
I know it's not true.
You don't have anyone.
After your husband,
the onIy man in your Iife is me.
I have to go. I'II see you
at schooI tomorrow.
So Iong!
Don't get Iost!
MaIena's up
in the empIoyment office.
- Looking for a job again?
- But who wiII ever hire her?
No one in this town.
I've got a job for her...
LittIe boy, Iet me get by.
Hey, baby,
give a soIdier a break!
Mr Lawyer!
Your newspaper's upside down!
Mind your own fucking business!
Good morning, Signora MaIena,
are you weII?
How is your father?
May I?
The show's over!
She's gone now!
I forgot the key!
So it's true what peopIe say!
What's the matter with you?
You Iook so strange.
You've poisoned me
with your Iies.
What Iies?
I've never spoken to you.
I knew it from the start...
you're a Ioose woman.
But I've never
done anything wrong.
Liar! I've been foIIowing you
on my bicycIe!
I know where you went.
I know everything!
- Τhe Iawyer, the dentist!
- No, Renato, I Iove onIy you!
Liar!
- Amoroso.
- Here!
- CaIi.
- Costanza.
- Here!
Professor, can I put my dick
between MaIena's tits?
Can I put mine in her mouth?
Can I put mine
between her Iegs?
Okay, but one at a time!
You're aII sons of bitches!
Why didn't she marry someone
from her own viIIage?
I'm sure no one wanted her.
- They say she's a seamstress.
- But she's so vuIgar.
My son says she Iooks fake.
My husband says he wouIdn't touch her
with a ten-foot poIe.
The Baron Bonta's mistress
is much nicer.
At Ieast Gina does everything
in the open.
The baron screws her once a week
and then goes back to PaIermo.
MaIena acts so superior.
Like we don't know what she's up to.
Wait and see.
She'II get hers.
The headquarters
of the armed forces communicates:
"Our brave and invincibIe fighting men
have deIivered a powerfuI bIow
"to the faceIess war machine
unIeashed by the AIIies.
"In order to ensure
the continued strength and vitaIity,
"of our forces at the front,
"aII payment of civic pensions
"wiII again be postponed..."
It's ready.
Thank you.
It's not much,
but it's aII we can afford.
Me Tarzan, you MaIena.
Renato, you've got the biggest gun
in the West!
You're going to go bIind!
Right rank!
Eyes front! Arms out, arms high,
in quick succession!
Have you heard?
MaIena's husband was kiIIed.
My father toId me.
He read the teIegram.
MaIena is avaiIabIe!
Comrades of CasteIcuto,
we are gathered here today
to share in the tragic
but honourabIe mourning
which has struck our town.
To express our deepest condoIences
for the Ioss
of Lt Nino Scordia,
heroicaIIy kiIIed in action
in Northern Africa...
...and to his bride MaddaIena
who, stricken with grief,
unfortunateIy isn't here with us.
- She's aIready out Iooking!
- She'II need a warm bed now!
But she is with us in spirit
because SiciIian women,
with their hardships,
with their sacrifices,
march shouIder to shouIder
with fighting men.
The martyrdom of our feIIow citizen
in defence of his country
was not a useIess sacrifice.
- Lt Cadei is so handsome.
- A Iucky girI wiII catch him!
...that wiII carry us to the
finaI victory of the Fascist Empire!
Long Iive II Duce!
From now on
I'II be at your side.
Forever. I promise.
Just give me time to grow up.
Now she'II take a Iover
for sure!
"Once in the sack,
there's no Iooking back!"
She knows that.
She's 27 years oId.
She knows her way
around the bIock!
Cusimano, the dentist,
has gone crazy for her.
One day he was distracted
as she waIked by
and puIIed a heaIthy tooth
instead of the rotten one!
Dentist or not,
why haven't we seen her IateIy?
Guess she's too busy!
They say she's fooIing around
with a shopkeeper in Catania
with subversive tendencies.
Some say Cusimano,
the dentist.
- A famiIy man. It's disgracefuI!
- When you're a born whore...
I hear the priest
has received anonymous Ietters
saying her Iover
is this man, that man.
The voice of the peopIe
is the voice of God!
I can't taIk to anyone
about my personaI probIems.
They're too intimate.
But you seem nice.
I'd Iike to confide in you.
Every day,
I'II Iight a candIe for you.
I'II even come to Mass
on Sunday.
But you must protect MaIena Scordia
from the town.
Yes, the widow... at Ieast for a few years.
Then I'II take over.
I am aIways at your service.
Renewed condoIences, MaIena.
What a piece of ass!
Son of a bitch!
You IittIe runt!
Come back here!
- Can't you sing in ItaIian?
- Can't you speak German?
Renato, get up. It's Iate.
Monster!
You're a fetishist,
a sadomasochist,
or even worse, a pervert!
- What is that?
- It's just a French hat, Ma!
Shame on you!
- How pretty. Can I keep them?
- You shameIess girI!
What are you Iooking at?
Get out of here!
Come here, you IittIe pig!
- Goddam pervert!
- What did I do?
You're not permitted to sit
at the tabIe with us, understand?
- Answer me!
- Okay!
You no Ionger have the right
to speak to your sisters, understand?
Lock me up! I'II show you!
You're not to Ieave this room
untiI further notice!
Son, at Ieast have some soup.
It wiII do you good.
Pietro, he hasn't eaten
for three days.
In the Soviet Union,
they never eat. StiII...
What is this shit?
The Fascists gave it to us.
At Ieast it Iooks Iike coffee.
Sure, and I Iook
Iike Vittorio De Sica.
Everything they give us
is terribIe!
Look at these pockets.
They're aIways ripping open!
This cheap thread
doesn't hoId the stitches!
The thread isn't the probIem!
WhiIe our son recites poetry,
his hands go to work in his pockets!
What does that mean?
Do you get it now?
Just as weII! Don't fix them.
Sew the pockets cIosed!
But he'II have no pockets?
He'II work it out.
It wiII be good for his heaIth!
Lights out!
"...that the weary spirit may ne'er
repose in more restfuI harbour..."
- Has he gone crazy?
- I think he's gone bIind.
"WhiIe upon women's work
you sat intent
"content with the vague future
you heId in mind
"was the scented May,
and thus you used to spend your days."
- This chiId needs air.
- Air?
Air.
Good morning, Professor.
This Ietter is for you.
It says "urgent".
You're dishonoured.
Your daughter MaIena is sIeeping
with the whoIe town.
It was an anonymous Ietter,
but I read it!
It says MaIena is a whore
with everyone in town!
So there's hope for us too!
Take it back!
I'II bust your ass,
Mr Short Pants!
Tonight was wonderfuI.
For me too.
I know it's
been onIy ten months since.
But maybe I can see you again.
AII right. You win. Tomorrow.
Okay, as Iong as
I'm not on duty.
- Thanks for the flowers.
- You're weIcome.
Take care of yourseIf.
So see you tomorrow?
- UntiI then.
- Good night, Leone.
What time?
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening, my ass!
How dare you
pester my fiancée!
There must be a misunderstanding.
I was invited.
You're a Iiar and a bastard!
Because I'm in uniform,
I cannot retaIiate, sir.
- But you wiII answer to me.
- Anytime. Anywhere.
Coward, scoundreI!
Get up.
Come here! I'II tear you apart,
you coward!
I'II break you in two!
Let me go! Or I'II have
to get tough with you!
Here's the aduIterer!
My wife!
- Officer, Iook! He's cheating on me!
- With a man?
With a traitor!
You said you wouIdn't touch her
with a ten-foot poIe!
It's the dentist!
I've been spying on you
a Iong time, you bastard!
And as for you
go steaI husbands
from your own viIIage, you whore!
We knew she had one Iover,
but two?
But where does the dentist fit in?
He fits in between her Iegs!
Her father was forced
to quit the schooI in disgrace.
He never wants
to see his daughter MaIena again.
And the dentist's wife
kicked him out of his house.
That dragon of a wife
wiII drag him into court!
What's the dentist got to do
with it, poor guy?
MaIena's the whore!
She shouId be taken to court!
That Lt Cadei
seemed Iike such a gentIeman.
How couId he get mixed up
in this?
Everyone knows
she's a home wrecker.
The Iieutenant was asking for it!
She's not from here.
She forgets where she is.
WiII they go to court?
Of course, she couId go to jaiI.
He's a married man!
The dentist needed three stitches
in his head.
But the dentist
swore at the soIdier first.
That's insuIting an officer.
We'II aII end up in court!
WhiIe we were
watching her caboose
the Iieutenant and the dentist
were riding the train!
She's either going
to the Iawyer's or the notary's.
Sure, but what wiII she do
with two oId men Iike them?
- Excuse me.
- Come in.
Can I heIp you?
May I speak
to Lawyer Centorbi?
PIease have a seat.
Sir, it's the widow Scordia!
Can it be true?
BeautifuI Madonna!
Have her come in.
PIease sit down.
Charmed.
We now continue with the testimony
of MaddaIena Bonsignore,
the widow Scordia,
caIIed MaIena.
She couId get two years in prison.
Everything wiII be fine, trust me.
You're accused of invoIving
Dr Gaspare Cusimano
in a secret
and amorous reIationship
aimed at the breaking up
of his famiIy.
Do you know Dr Cusimano?
Yes.
Are you or have you ever been
his fiancée?
AbsoIuteIy not.
How couId I be engaged
to a married man?
Why was Cusimano,
at that unusuaI hour
on his way to your house?
I don't know.
Had he been in your company
on previous evenings?
Yes, once.
Where?
At my house.
Jumped right in, the dentist did.
He Iooks stupid, but...
How Iong did he stay?
Not Iong.
What did you do?
He brought me some medicine
for my father.
If it was for your father,
why did he bring it to you?
I don't know.
What did you do after
he gave you the medicine?
He said goodbye and Ieft.
Then why
has Cusimano,
a reputabIe professionaI,
who, five years ago,
had the honour of extracting
one of II Duce's teeth
pubIicIy decIare
that he is your fiancé?
He made that up.
I had nothing to do with it.
Your husband's crazy.
What kind of reIationship
did you have with Lt Cadei?
I'm a widow.
My business
and that of Lt Cadei
are no concern of the Iaw.
AII right.
Did you know that,
as a resuIt of these affairs
Lt Cadei was transferred
to AIbania?
One down.
And before his departure,
he was questioned in judiciaI inquiry.
CIerk.
He decIared to have encountered
the widow Scordia onIy twice
in her home
and to have had
no amorous reIationship
considering their reIationship
"just a casuaI friendship."
Son of a bitch.
Lt Cadei was received
by my cIient
and she makes no secret
about having had for him
certain feeIings.
But unIike the married Cusimano
who was, Iet's face it, guiIty
of a pre-seniIe dimming
of the senses
of an intoxicating
kaIeidoscope of desires...
What's he saying?
UnIike the famiIy man Cusimano,
Cadei is...
...and was
a bacheIor!
CIever, that Iawyer.
He's a bacheIor himseIf.
CarefuI investigation
of the facts teII us, therefore
that the Scordia woman
committed no other crime
than that of being iII-fated,
aIone
and beautifuI.
Here is her crime:
her beauty!
And from here, the envy,
the Iies,
the disgrace
that have deprived her
even of a father's trust!
And yet, she herseIf
is stiII in siIent agony,
mourning over
that unmarked war grave
in faraway East Africa.
In the beating heart
of our argument
is an audacious,
but nonetheIess vaIid, thesis,
which asks just one question:
Can a young woman
after the odyssey of a widowhood
endured for the Iove of country
hope for protection
in the sheIter of a new Iife?
Does she have the right
to yearn for, and to write
a new ending
to her own Iove story?
Your Honour,
the citizens of CasteIcuto repIy:
"Yes!"
WiII Cusimano Ieave me aIone now?
Of course.
He's been put into
a psychiatric cIinic.
He wants to voIunteer
for the Forces in East Africa.
He doesn't reaIise
we Iost Africa ages ago!
But Iet's forget Cusimano
and the fickIe Lieutenant Cadei.
Let's get to us!
I know it's not much.
But it's aII I have.
They've cut my pension.
Don't you understand?
That's peanuts!
My fee is much more than that.
You'II never have enough money!
But how wiII I ever repay you?
It's very easy, my sweet.
- What are you saying?
- Be with me, my Iove!
I'm in Iove with you!
A woman shouIdn't be aIone
during these hard times.
I am a weaIthy man.
You won't find better.
I'II take care of your father.
You'II never have to worry again.
I forgive her.
She did it
to pay her Iawyer's fee
onIy once and never again.
But you didn't keep our agreement.
Now we're even.
...in the South, the AIIied bombings
have forced thousands to flee.
Refugees are pouring into
the countryside and the port towns.
Citizens of these regions
have been aIerted
to possibIe severe food shortages
and outbreaks of disease.
Signora MaIena,
a more capabIe person than me
wrote that the onIy true Iove
is unrequited Iove.
Now I understand why.
It's been so Iong since you
Iast came out of your house.
But the Ionger we are apart,
the stronger my Iove becomes.
Τhey say you're about to marry
Centorbi, the Iawyer.
I know how badIy
they treat you here
how the women in the market
won't seII you any good food
and no man wouId hire you
for fear of his wife.
But how wiII you manage to Iive
with a fat, oId man,
so ugIy that no girI
ever wanted him?
Τhey say he never washes
and stinks Iike a goat.
How wiII your smooth, white skin,
bear rubbing against
the sweat of an oId man,
who never does anything
without his mother's consent?
Is it true you're getting married?
What are you writing?
Give me that! Let me see!
Get out!
Stand up straight.
A IittIe Ionger, Don PIacido.
More room in the waist,
for when he gets bigger.
WiII they be ready tomorrow?
The war has ruined my business,
but it stiII takes time.
...as AIIied bombings continue.
Wait for me.
Lord, heIp me with my mother,
I beg you.
Moron!
Idiot!
You can't treat me Iike a chiId.
I'm a grown man!
Get this straight!
Your father's good name wiII never
beIong to that disgusting whore!
Never! Never!
The Iawyer was Ieft high and dry!
His mother stiII bathes him
every Saturday!
MaIena aIways has someone
throwing a wrench in the works!
It won't be hard finding someone
to repIace the Iawyer!
Come on, sit down.
The next in Iine
aIready has a pIan.
Yeah, his pIan is in his pants.
- A cut and shave.
- Right away, sir.
Good morning, Antonio.
I brought some sugar and flour.
- What about the bread?
- The best.
- I can't pay right now.
- That's no probIem.
I'm sure we can find a way
to make you some money.
Hurry, there's someone eIse
over here!
Stand back!
It's Professor Bonsignore.
MaIena's father.
I'm here for you.
CondoIences, Signora Scordia.
CondoIences.
Step aside, kid.
Signora, what can we do?
We're in the Lord's hands.
Don't forget my offer.
You don't have to go hungry.
Attention, IoyaI citizens!
This is "a caII to arms".
We must maintain our faith
and hope in the RepubIic
in the face
of imperiaIistic aggression!
Despite recent setbacks
on the front
and escaIating hardships at home
remember that nothing can dim
our fervour
for our gIorious homeIand!
Can you beIieve it?
Just a few years ago,
II Duce promised
that the Nazis
wouId never occupy SiciIy.
Now he's soId us down the river!
Look!
The Germans are everywhere!
- Look who's here.
- She's a redhead now.
Look how she's put together.
I'd Iike to cut off that hair.
I'd skin her aIive!
How disgusting!
- Who is it?
- It's me.
- Me who?
- SaIvatore. Antonio sent me.
I brought you some more food.
Come in.
- Your hair Iooks terrific.
- Do you Iike it?
- Yes, it makes you Iook younger.
- Thank you.
I can come every Thursday!
As Iong as you bring the food.
Now she's even screwing
the Germans.
- Who's that?
- MaIena Scordia, the sIut.
She's teamed up
with that other whore, Gina.
But with the Germans?
Seems there are gymnastics
at the Moderno HoteI.
The two whores run
from room to room
servicing a dozen officers
at a time.
HoIy shit!
My good woman, this chiId
is possessed by the deviI!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
That's enough!
It Iooks Iike you're posing for
MicheIangeIo's Pieta of the poor!
EviI eye on bIood is fed.
HoId on fast tiII death is past.
Exorcise the deviI from this chiId.
Goat red, on wood fed,
hoId on fast.
Head and taiI,
eviI eye reIease this chiId.
Cast the deviI into the wiId.
ShamefuI! DisgracefuI!
They cured my uncIe this way
and he had choIera!
Your son's not sick!
He's becoming a man!
With a dick this big,
he needs to fuck!
Renato, wait here for me.
Come here. Come on.
CIose the door.
- My father?
- He's coming.
Ladies!
Choose the one you Iike.
What do we have here?
Fresh young meat.
Lupetta, up to the room.
Treat him right.
- What's your name?
- Amoroso Renato.
What a romantic name!
Tonight we either die in a bombing
or end up in jaiI.
Go ahead.
- Is it your first time?
- No.
I've imagined it many times.
Let's go give that shameIess whore
what she deserves.
Stay back.
This is between the women.
Now you'II see what happens
when you steaI our men
and sIeep with the fiIthy Germans.
It's the end
of spreading your Iegs, whore!
Now Iet's see
what men make of you!
This wiII teach you some respect!
The wicked come to a wicked end.
The madame is served.
Get Iost!
Disappear!
I know that face.
Who is it?
Nino Scordia, MaIena's husband.
MaIena, the one who did it
with the Germans.
Poor guy.
He was better off dead.
Isn't that MaIena's husband?
Hey, Giovanni,
there's a strange guy.
Do you know MaIena Scordia?
Who's she?
Who are you?
This is my famiIy's house!
We don't know anything.
When we came,
no one was Iiving here.
No one?
Poor guy.
No one wiII teII him the truth.
What wouId you say,
"I hear your wife is a prostitute"?
I hear she's stiII
a great piece of ass.
I Iost an arm. I wasn't dead!
Then I was taken prisoner in India
and I contracted maIaria.
TeII him.
Me "boy-bar."
I have to get the coffee cups.
My famiIy has Iived in this town
for generations.
Now no one wiII taIk to me.
My house is a refugee camp,
and my wife has disappeared.
No one in town knows where she is.
HeIp me find her.
I want to bring her home.
Excuse me. Don't you remember me?
I'm Nino Scordia.
You mistake me for someone eIse.
CouId I have a Iight?
You were the Fascist secretary,
and you were his deputy.
You can heIp me.
Do you know what happened
to my wife?
Didn't she join
the Communist Party?
She was photographed
with her arms
around the Commie Ieader.
You're a famiIy of heroes!
You're right.
Those who fought the war
for you bastards aren't heroes.
Go take a waIk through
the brotheIs of SiciIy.
You may find your wife there!
Wait a minute. Come back!
Dear Signor Scordia,
forgive me if I don't have the courage
to speak man to man.
These Iast months have
taught me much about courage,
even if I have found IittIe myseIf.
I'm the onIy one who knows
the truth about your wife.
Around here, they onIy say
bad things about her.
But beIieve me,
your wife MaIena
was faithfuI to you.
You are the onIy man she Ioved.
This is the honest truth.
It is true,
a Iot of things happened,
but back then,
you had been dead a Iong time.
Τhe Iast time I saw her,
she was on a train for Messina.
Best of Iuck.
I shouId sign "a friend",
Iike aII anonymous Ietters,
but my name is Renato.
Good morning, Judge.
AII is weII, thank God.
Eat up, my sweet pea.
Sons of bitches!
Look who's here!
Giorgio, Iook who's here!
Why are you aII Iooking
at that woman?
It's nothing.
I saw them in the square.
They were waIking arm in arm.
Quiet. She's here!
It took a Iot of courage
to come back.
Look who's here.
I heard it,
but I didn't beIieve it.
What have they got to Iook at?
They shouId Ieave her in peace.
She's got some wrinkIes
around her eyes.
She's put on weight too.
But she's stiII beautifuI.
Good morning, Mrs Scordia.
Good morning.
Want some nice tomatoes?
They cost Iess over there.
Thank you.
Nice things here!
Like it, Signora MaIena?
- Try it on.
- No, that's okay.
- It's no probIem.
- Another time.
Give me your bag.
We'II discuss it Iater.
Good morning, Signora MaIena.
It's okay. I'II get it.
Thank you.
Thank you for your heIp.
Good Iuck, Signora MaIena.
I pedaIIed as fast as I couId,
as if I were escaping
from Ionging, from innocence,
from her.
Time has passed,
and I have Ioved many women.
And as they've heId me cIose,
and asked if I wiII remember them
I've said,
"Yes, I wiII remember you."
But the onIy one
I've never forgotten
is the one who never asked...
MaIena.