~Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick~
Let us tell an old story a new.
And we will see
how well you know it.
Once upon a time
there were two kingdoms
that were the worst of neighbors.
So vast the discord between them
that is was said only a great hero
or a terrible villain might
bring them together.
In one kingdom lived folk
like you and me
with a vain and greedy king
to rule over them.
They were forever discontent
and envious
of the wealth and beauty
of their neighbors.
For in the other kingdom, the Moors
lived every manner of strange
and wonderful creature.
And they needed neither
king nor queen
but trusted in one another.
In a great tree
on a great cliff in the Moors
lived one such spirit.
You might take her for a girl.
But she was not just any girl.
She was a fairy.
There you go.
And her name was Maleficent.
Good morning, Mr. Shantuwell.
I love your car.
No! No! Don't do it!
Ha, you missed me!
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Love your walk, girls.
What's all the fuss about?
- The border guards...
Why'd you get to tell her?
I want to tell her!
There are rules, Flittle.
I tell this time, you tell next time.
The border guards...
- No, you told last time.
So I should tell this time
and Thistletwit next time.
Tell me what?
Fine!
- Ah, thank you.
Maleficent, the border guards...
The border guards have found
a human thief at the Pool of Jewels!
I'm sorry.
She's always in a hurry
with her big wings.
Humans, here.
I hope this isn't another war.
I'm not afraid.
Besides, I've never seen
a human up close.
Come out!
No! They mean to kill me.
And besides, they're hideous
to look at.
That's extremely rude!
Don't listen to him, Balthazar.
You're classically handsome.
It's not right to steal,
but we don't kill people for it.
Come out! Come out
this instant!
Are you fully grown?
No.
I believe he's just a boy.
And you're just a girl, I think.
Who are you?
I'm called Stefan.
I'm Maleficent.
Yes, right.
You have to give it back.
Give what back?
If I knew you would throw it away,
I would have kept it.
I didn't throw it away.
I delivered it home,
as I'm going to do for you.
Someday, you know, I'll live there.
In the castle.
Where do you live now?
In a barn.
So, your parents are farmers then?
My parents are dead.
Mine too.
We'll see each other again.
You really shouldn't come back here,
you know.
It's not safe.
And If I made that choice?
if I came back, would you be here?
Perhaps.
What's wrong?
Your ring! Iron burns fairies.
I'm sorry.
I like your wings.
Maleficent thought of how Stefan
cast away his ring.
He, who had so little in the world
so that their hands
might touch again.
And her heart was moved.
Thus did the young thief who
had hoped to steal a jewel
steal something far more precious.
Maleficent!
After all these weeks,
look who came back.
I thought it worth the risk.
So, what do you do for fun?
Stefan and Maleficent became
the most unlikely of friends.
And for a time,
it seemed as if - in them at least
the old hatred between man
and fairy had been forgotten.
As it will friendship slowly
turned into something else.
And on her 16th birthday
Stefan gave Maleficent a gift.
He told her it was true love's kiss.
But it was not to be.
As the years passed
Stefan's ambition called him away
from Maleficent
and towards the temptations
of the human kingdom.
While Maleficent, the strongest
of the fairies
rose to become the protector of the Moors.
Maleficent often wandered
alone
and sometimes wondered
where Stefan might be.
For she had never understood
the greed and envy of men.
But she was to learn.
For the human king had heard
of a growing power in the Moors.
And he sought to strike it down.
Guards, hold!
There they are!
The mysterious Moors
and no one dares to venture
for fear of the magical creatures
that lurk within.
Well, I say:
Crush them!
Go no further!
A king does not take orders
from a winged elf.
You are no king to me!
Bring me her head.
Battalion!
Attack!
Arise and stand with me!
Hold the line!
It's the dark creatures!
Charge!
You!
To the king!
You will not have the Moors.
Not now, nor ever!
You...
When I ascended to the throne
I promised the people
one day
we would take the Moors
and it's treasures.
Each of you swore
allegiance to me
and to that cause...
Your Majesty.
Defeated in battle.
Is this to be my legacy?
I see you're waiting
for me to die.
It won't be long,
but what then?
I will choose a successor
to take the throne and
care for my daughter.
Who among you is worthy?
Kill the winged creature!
Avenge me!
And upon my death
you will take the crown.
Maleficent.
Maleficent!
So, how is life
with the humans?
Maleficent, I've come
to warn you.
They mean to kill you.
King Henry will stop
at nothing.
Please, you have to trust me.
They spoke of many things
and the years faded away.
And she forgave Stefan,
his folly and his ambition.
And all was as it happened
long ago.
Are you thirsty?
Maleficent?
What is this?
I have avenged you, Sire.
She is vanquished?
Ah, you have done well,
my son.
You have done
what others failed to do.
You will be rewarded.
I shall do my best
to be a worthy successor.
Your Majesty.
I got you!
Wicked bird!
- Into a man.
It's a demon!
What have you done
to my beautiful south?
Would you rather I let them
beat you to death?
I'm not certain.
- Stop complaining.
I saved your life.
Forgive me.
What do I call?
- Diaval.
And in return for saving my life
I am your servant.
Whatever you need.
Wings.
I need you to be my wings.
I present to you
the first of his line:
His Royal Highness,
King Stefan.
He did this to me
so he would be king.
Now what, mistress?
She!
Her wings!
It's a girl!
O, my God, it's a girl!
- It's a girl!
Well?
- Well, I saw nothing.
But there's been a...
- What?
child.
King Stefan and the Queen
have had a child.
There'll be a christening.
They say it's to be
a grand celebration.
A grand celebration...
for a baby.
How wonderful!
All manner of folk
came to the christening.
Even three of the fairies
who sought
to foster peace and
good will.
Look, there's the baby!
- Love baby!
Concentrate, please!
I'm not telling you again.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I am Knotgrass
of the Moorland fair folk.
I am Flittle, Your Kingship.
And I am Thistletwit, Your Royals...
They bring gifts for our daughter.
These are not just any old gifts.
For you see, we are magic!
And very good with children.
Very well.
Sweet Aurora.
I wish for you
the gift of beauty.
My wish is that you'll
never be blue.
Only happy,
all the days of your life.
Sweet baby.
My wish for you is that
you'll find...
Maleficent!
Well, well.
What a glittering assemblage,
King Stefan.
Royalty, nobility
the gentry and...
How quaint.
Even the rabble.
I must say I really felt
quite distressed.
of not receiving an invitation.
You're not welcome here.
Oh, dear.
What an awkward situation.
You're not offended?
Why no.
And to show I bear
no ill-will
I too shall bestow
a gift on the child.
No! We don't want your gift!
Stay away from the princess!
- Yes, stay away!
Listen well, all of you.
The princess shall indeed
grow in grace and beauty.
Beloved by all
who meet her.
That's a lovely gift.
Don't do this.
But...
Before the sun sets on
her 16th birthday
she will prick her finger on
the spindle of a spinning wheel
and fall into a sleep
like death!
A sleep from which
she will never awaken!
Maleficent, please don't do this.
I'm begging you.
I like you begging.
Do it again.
I beg you.
Alright.
The princess can
be woken from her
death sleep.
But only by...
true love's kiss.
This curse will last
until the end of time!
No power on earth
can change it!
King Stefan ordered his men
to seize every spinning wheel
in the kingdom.
The wheels were broken
and burned
that they might never be used
and thrown in the deepest dungeon
in the castle.
Secretly he entrusted
the safety of the child
to the magic of the pixies
who would take her to
a remote hideaway
for sixteen years and a day.
Stefan shut himself behind
the walls of his castle
while his soldiers rode
far and wide
to hunt Maleficent down.
But she made walls
of her own
that the Moors might
never again
suffered the touch
of any human.
And she revelled
in the sorrow
that her curse
had brought.
The fairies began their charge
to raise Aurora in a snug
little cottage in the woods.
Oh, no! What is it?
Looks dreadful.
Come on.
We need a smaller baby.
Or a bigger body.
No, what we need is
a proper disguise.
What do you mean?
Well, we have to blend in,
don't we?
We have to be big enough
to look after this baby.
So, gather around, ladies.
Get ready.
One, two, three.
Grow!
Oh, that went quite well.
That's very nice.
Now, there'll be no questions asked.
We are no longer fairies.
We are three peasant women,
raising our orphan child
in the woods.
So, no more flying.
No flying?
- No, no.
And no magic.
- No magic?
Yes, you've heard.
- But we in the middle of nowhere.
No one is going to find
us here.
There you are.
Why are you always hiding?
Come on. Here you go.
It's so ugly you could almost
feel sorry for it.
I hate you.
Beastie.
The fairies were perhaps
unequal to their task.
Why is she crying?
Maybe she might be hungry.
Then feed her!
It's gonna to starve with
those three looking after it.
What?
- You're cheating.
I saw that.
- We're starting again.
Suit yourself.
Greedy, bloated goat!
Bloated goat!
Stop doing that.
I'm not doing anything.
Well, someone is.
- It's not me.
You two are having a go at me
and I will not tolerate...
Stop it!
This is all your fault!
Oh, come on! That's funny!
As the days went on,
Stefan darkened...
further consumed by
paranoia and vengeance.
Pull down!
- The torch!
Flame!
Make ready!
Release!
You failed me.
The wall cannot be burned.
It is indestructible.
Nothing is indestructible!
Not a wall, not Maleficent!
Not even her curse!
Bring me the iron workers.
Oh, look! The little beast is about
to fall off the cliff.
What?
Hello.
Go away.
Go.
I don't like children.
Up, up.
Go on. Go, go, go.
As Maleficent had said
Aurora did grow
in grace and beauty.
Pretty bird.
Far away from the lofty palace
that she remembered not.
And as the seasons changed
and the flowers grew
so did she.
Hello.
That's it.
She wondered at the world
about her
and at what lay beyond
the fearsome wall of thorns.
Curious little beastie.
She was not the only one
who wished to get through.
Is that her?
Is that Maleficent?
I don't know.
Bring her to me.
Ah, it's just
a silly peasant girl.
It's her!
- It's her!
How could you do that to me?
- You said, anything I need!
Yeah, but not a dog!
It was a wolf, not a dog.
- It's the same thing!
They are dirty, vicious
and they hunt birds!
Fine, next time I'll turn you
into a mealy worm.
Well, I'll be a mealy worm gladly!
Anything but a filthy, stinking...
I wonder...
I know you're there.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Then come out.
Then you will be afraid.
No, I won't.
I know who you are.
Do you?
You're my fairy godmother.
What?
- Fairy godmother.
You've been watching over me
my whole life.
I've always known
you were close by.
How?
Your shadow. It's been following me
ever since I was small.
Wherever I went,
your shadow is always with me.
I remember you...
pretty bird.
This is Diaval.
Hello, Aurora.
I've known you
since you were a little one.
It's everything I imagined
it would be.
Oh, it's just so beautiful!
I've always wanted to come...
Goodnight, beastie.
You mock me.
I know what you're doing.
I know exactly...
what you're doing.
Sire, your presence has been
requested by the Queen.
Leave me.
Sire, she is not well.
The nurses are fearful that
she won't make it through the night.
Can you not see
we're having a conversation?
When the curse fails,
Maleficent will come for me.
And on that day...
I will be ready.
They're so beautiful.
I revoke the curse.
Let it be no more.
I revoke my curse!
Let it be no more!
This curse will last
until the end of times
No power on earth
can change it.
Do all the fair people have wings?
Most do.
Then, why don't you?
All the other fairies fly.
I had wings once.
They were stolen from me.
That's all I wish
to say about it.
What color were they?
Were they big?
So big they dragged behind me
when I walked.
And they were strong.
They could carry me above the clouds
and into the headwinds.
And they never faltered.
Not even once.
I could trust them.
She's coming.
Where are your workers?
In their beds, Majesty.
Get them back to work
without delay.
They're exhausted, Sire.
But I'll have them back
to work at first light.
I need them back to work now.
It's the wee hours.
Aye.
It is... the wee hours.
So, wake them up.
Sire?
So, wake them up!
And get them back
to work now!
We're running out of time!
Go on!
Aurora!
Come here.
Sit.
There is something
I need to tell you.
What is it?
There is an evil in this world.
And I cannot keep
you from it.
I'm almost 16, godmother.
I can take care of myself.
I understand.
That's not what I have to say to you..
- I have a plan.
When I grow up, I'm going
to live here in the Moors with you.
Then we can look after each other.
You don't have to wait
until you're older.
You could live here now.
Then I will!
I'll sleep in a tree and
eat berries and black nuts.
And all the fair people
will be my friends.
I'll be happy here
for the rest of my life.
I'm going to tell
my aunties tomorrow.
Until tomorrow.
Oh, I'm so excited!
Aunties.
I'm almost 16.
I need a life of my own.
No, I love you very much.
But it's time to say goodbye.
You've been very good to me.
Except the time
you accidentally fed me spiders.
Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you
but I'm on my way to King Stefan's
castle
and I've become... hopelessly lost.
Can you help me?
I'm sorry, that was my fault.
I rushed into...
Forgive me.
It's that way.
The castle.
What's your name?
- It's Phillip.
Hello, Phillip.
What's yours?
- Aurora.
Hello, Aurora.
Well, it was nice meeting you
and once again my apologies
for being such a clumsy fool.
You're forgiven.
- That's good.
Well, I'll best be off then.
Goodbye.
Will you be back this way?
Nothing could stop me.
Then I'll see you soon.
- Very soon.
Goodbye, Phillip.
Goodbye... for now.
Stop doing that.
Well?
That boy is the answer!
No, Diaval.
- Yes!
True love's kiss, remember?
It can break the spell.
True love's kiss?
Have you not
worked it out yet?
I cursed her that way,
because there is no such thing.
Well, that might be how you feel.
But... what about Aurora?
That boy could be her only chance.
It's her fate, anyway.
Go ahead.
Turn me into whatever you want.
A bird, a worm.
I don't care anymore.
I'm so happy
we're leaving tomorrow.
You're not leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Aurora's 16th birthday.
And Stefan told us to take her back
the day after her birthday.
No, he said,
on her birthday.
No, after her birthday.
On.
- After.
On, on, on!
- After, after!
On, on!
Stop it!
What?
How could you?
I need to talk to you
about something.
O yes, sweetie, what is it?
I'm sorry to have
to tell you this.
But I'll be 16 tomorrow.
Oh, yes, quick,
put it here.
I'm leaving home.
See here, young lady.
I did not spend 16 years
in this miserable hovel
with these two imbeciles... Hush!
So that you could ruin it
on the last day!
We are taking you back
to your father without...
My father?
You told me
my parents were dead.
I think you better come
and sit down.
Fairy godmother!
I'm here.
When were you going to tell me
that I'm cursed?
Is it true?
It is.
My aunts said
it was an evil fairy.
I... I can't remember her name.
They said...
that is was...
Maleficent.
Is that you?
Are you Maleficent?
No! Don't touch me.
You're the evilest in the world.
it's you!
Find the boy!
...all the men to the east wing now!
There should be no guards at the gate.
I want her to walk in...
Sorry to disturb, Your Majesty.
We found this girl at the gate.
She claims to be the princess.
Father, it's me, Aurora!
You look just like your mother.
They brought you back a day too soon.
I told those three idiots!
Lock her up in her room.
Go.
Prepare the net.
Maleficent is coming.
It's so good to be small again!
Look at my feet!
I love my tiny little feet!
Pay attention!
We have to find Aurora!
Oh, the king will have our heads!
Wait!
Princess.
I'm looking for a girl.
- Of course you are.
I need a horse.
Come on, Diaval!
Faster, Diaval!
Faster!
It's done.
They pulled the guards.
He's waiting for you in there.
If we go inside those walls,
we'll never come out alive.
Then don't come.
It's not your fight.
Well, thank you very much.
I need you, Diaval.
I can't do this
without you, Diaval.
I can hear you.
Look at her.
Look at what you've done.
She's only sleeping.
She's only sleeping, you say?
She's only sleeping forever!
What about the kiss?
Yes, true love's kiss.
True love does not exist.
But it's her only chance,
Your Majesty.
Mistress.
What are we going to do?
Well, we can't give up, can we?
Come on, girls!
But we don't even know
where to start!
True love doesn't just
fall from trees, you know.
Pardon me.
I'm embarrassed to say
that I don't know where I am.
In King Stefan's castle.
This is where I was meant to be.
Although I can't recall
how I got here.
Why have you come?
- My father sent me to see the king.
Who is your father?
- King John of Ofsted.
A prince!
Aurora.
He knows her.
Why is she sleeping?
She's trapped in an enchantment.
Isn't she beautiful?
The most beautiful girl
I have ever seen.
Do you want to kiss her?
Very much.
Just go on then.
I'm not sure about it. I barely know her.
We've only met once.
Haven't you ever heard of love
at first sight? Kiss her! Go on.
An enchantment, you say?
Kiss her!
You didn't do it properly!
It's supposed to be true love's kiss!
I was certain he was the one!
- What are you doing?
We have to keep looking.
I told you.
I will not ask your forgiveness.
Because what I have done to you
is unforgivable.
I was so lost
in hatred and revenge.
Sweet Aurora.
You stole what was left of my heart.
And now I have lost you forever.
I swear, no harm will come
to you
as long as I live.
And not a day shall pass
that I don't miss your smile.
Hello, godmother.
Hello, beastie.
No true love.
She's here, Sire.
Are we going back
to the Moors now?
If that is what you wish.
Stop!
- Get back!
Into a dragon.
Run, Aurora!
Enough!
How does it feel?
To be a fairy creature
without wings?
In a world
where you don't belong!
Kill her!
Shoot her!
It's over.
Maleficent brought down
her wall of thorns
and took off her crown
And she invited Aurora to see
how the Moors had been once.
Long ago when Maleficent was
but a child
and her heart was bright.
For now, it was again.
But that was not all.
Over there she is.
Hurry up, they're waiting!
Wait for me!
We present this crown
to our little Aurora
for whom we have sacrificed
the best years of our...
Never mind.
Our kingdoms have been unified.
You have your Queen!
So you see, the story is not quite
as you were told.
And I should know.
For I was the one
they called Sleeping Beauty.
In the end,
my kingdom was united.
Not by a hero or a villain
as legend had predicted.
But one who was both
hero and villain.
And her name was
Maleficent.
~Hope it helped ->bozxphd~