Tie it off, come on!
Hey, guys!
Guys, I think we should turn back.
And lose good money?
Not a chance.
Stay close.
Here we are.
Get on his back.
Hurry up.
There he is. Go get him.
You'll pay for that.
No. No, please.
Please, no.
Hold it there.
I only got one...
but he's a fine specimen.
-That's all?
-Yeah.
That shroom bit me twice.
Tomb Bloom.
Once upon a time...
or perhaps twice upon a time,
for you may remember this story...
there was a powerful Fey
named Maleficent.
For some reason, the mistress of evil
and protector of the Moors...
was still hated after all this time.
True, she had cursed the princess,
Aurora...
but that was before she found light
in the heart of a human child...
and raised the girl as her own.
After all, it was Maleficent's love
which broke that very same curse.
But that detail was somehow
mysteriously forgotten.
For as the tale was told
over and again throughout the kingdom...
Maleficent became the villain once more.
It's time, guys.
Come on. Let's get everyone.
-It's the big day! Let's go!
-Come on.
Wake up. Wake up.
Come on.
Hurry up, wallerbogs! It's time!
Do you both remember the secret plan?
I've got it all right here.
When do I tell the queen the secret?
You must be patient, Thistlewit.
Do you think Queen Aurora's awake yet?
Well, she's not "Sleeping Beauty" anymore.
I see what you did there.
Next item of business, the missing fairies.
I've sent more sprites
to search the Tomb Bloom field.
They'll report back to me at nightfall.
We will keep searching until we find them.
Please don't raise your roots at me, Lief.
Crushing humans with branches
is not going to help.
Diaval, you're supposed to be on my side.
Well, I'm Queen of the Moors,
and I am a human.
We must all learn a little kindness.
Coming through.
Excuse us.
Official pixie business.
A word, Your Majesty.
-Maybe two.
-Aunties...
you need to wait your turn
like everyone else.
-No!
-This can't wait, Your Grace.
Not for a moment.
Or I might burst.
Truly, I might.
Is that...?
Pinto!
She's come bearing gifts.
The first sap from the warming trees.
It's for the big day!
Quiet, Thistlewit.
What big day?
Hey! My crown!
I'm not in the mood for this.
Pinto!
Come on.
Where are you going, aunties?
I don't have time for games, Pinto.
What's gotten into all of you?
There she goes, Your Majesty.
Come back here.
Pinto. I've had enough
of your games for today.
Look at me.
Philip. What are you doing here?
I was looking for you.
-Well, hello.
-Hello.
I'm really sorry, I can't talk right now.
The Moors have turned to madness.
I've got a castle full of complaints.
I know how busy you are.
-I wanted to ask you something.
-Yes.
Do you think there could be a union
between Ulstead and the Moors?
A union?
To connect both lands.
To bring harmony and peace.
I've been imagining a bridge.
A bridge.
Yes, a bridge.
A union's a wonderful idea...
if both sides are willing.
Well, I'm working on that part.
He's going to blow it.
Give him time. He's warming up.
Wait.
That's your formal coat.
You're in on all of this, aren't you?
If you're busy, I could always come back.
No. No, no.
I'm not busy at all.
No, because I'd hate to...
Really. All ears.
What did you want to talk about?
You're right.
He's blowing it.
Five years ago,
I thought I lost you forever.
I've decided to reclaim this day for us.
I've loved you since the moment I met you
and every day since.
If love has a truth, here is mine.
There is no magic nor curse that could
ever tear me away from you, Aurora.
-Are you sure this is a good time?
-Philip.
He's on his knee.
He took his sweet time about it.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
-Yes?
-Yes.
Yes!
Yes, just stand up. Kiss me.
We're having a wedding!
A secret surprise wedding.
Of course, we have to tell our parents.
Do we?
Mistress.
What?
I have a little bit of news.
Well, on with it.
It's nothing of any real consequence...
and it's certainly no reason to overreact.
It's just that...
Prince Philip has...
Disappeared?
No. No. Philip has...
Yellow fever? No, wait!
Leprosy!
No, Mistress.
Prince Philip has asked Aurora
if she'll become his...
Don't...
ruin my morning.
Mistress, please.
Stay calm!
So, tell me, sire...
am I to be a best man,
or did you choose a creature from the Moors?
General, if that's your way of asking me
if she said yes, then I...
I know she said yes, sire.
What human wouldn't want to leave that place?
What do you have against Moor folk, Percival?
"Moor folk"?
Is that what we're calling them now?
Winged beasts, murderous trees.
Guard your tongue, General.
You know nothing about them.
I know that Maleficent is a killer of men...
destroyer of armies.
Or so the story goes.
She's not like that.
It's my job to protect this kingdom.
And I will do so, old friend...
without hesitation.
Walk on.
Open the gates!
Your Majesty, spoils from the annexation
of the Midlands have arrived.
Weapons.
No. We have no need of arms.
Our days of war are over.
Ingrith...
you see where I've had you placed.
Right behind me.
And that's where I'll always be.
Ingrith, I said we had no need of arms.
One can never be too careful.
Your Majesty, it's cocked.
Is it, now?
-Father, Mother.
-Well?
What did she say?
She said yes.
Yes!
That is wonderful news.
Two kingdoms united at last.
Yes.
Perhaps I've been selfish...
looking at this the wrong way.
You've made your choice.
Now is a time to celebrate.
I'm glad you finally approve.
Much more than that.
I am ready to welcome your fiancée
with open arms.
She shall come to dinner.
That would be incredible.
Under one condition.
She will bring her godmother.
Your Majesty, I strongly...
We will meet the one who raised her
right here in this castle.
Yes. The queen is right.
I'm not sure her godmother will...
No, but I insist.
After all, we will soon be family.
Well, let it be known
throughout the kingdom...
that my son is to marry Aurora.
And Maleficent is coming to dinner.
I shall send word straightaway.
Incoming.
Hold on to your petticoats!
Well, well.
So?
So.
Godmother...
Philip asked me to marry him.
Poor thing.
He'll recover.
My answer was yes.
No.
Yes.
I wasn't really asking.
Nor was I.
What's next?
You'll turn him into a goat?
Stop.
Why don't you like Philip?
Well, for one thing, he's human.
I'm a human.
And I have never held that against you.
Until I fell in love.
Love doesn't always end well, Beasty.
I'll have you know
Prince Philip is a prince.
A very handsome and charming prince.
I'm just asking you to trust me.
Please give him a chance.
Let us prove you wrong.
Philip is thoughtful...
he's very kind...
Kind of what?
The king and queen are celebrating tonight...
and they have invited both of us
to the castle.
You want me to meet his parents?
It's just a dinner.
They don't want me in Ulstead.
Why on earth would I go?
Because his mother wishes to meet mine.
Please.
Philip.
I want you to wear this tonight.
Your sword?
Because of you,
Ulstead and the Moors will be united at last.
Father, my love for Aurora
has nothing to do with politics.
Yes, but your love...
will ensure peace for generations.
Now take it. And wear it...
to know that you will never have to use it.
My son.
I've never been more proud.
And what about Mother?
Is she okay with this?
Your mother will learn
to love who you love.
Tomb Bloom.
I'm losing my patience.
Your Majesty.
You need to move faster, Lickspittle.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Aurora said yes.
It's all coming together...
perfectly.
Hello.
Try it with a little less fang.
How's this?
Try the greeting.
How kind of you to invite me this evening.
Remember, it's not a threat.
So very kind of you
to invite me this evening.
Yeah. Better.
Try it with a curtsy.
We can skip that part.
She really loves that boy, you know.
You're doing her a great kindness.
Kindness?
Mistress...
Doesn't she look lovely?
I have something for you.
For your horns.
I just thought it might make Philip's family
feel more comfortable.
And you, as well.
Maybe it's a bad idea.
No, it's...
It's all right.
I'm so excited.
It's more than I can bear.
It's Maleficent!
Pitchforks?
Humans are hilarious.
It's getting better.
-Anyone leaves their post gets hung.
-Yes, sir.
They're here.
Have you ever considered
turning me into a bear?
I think I'd make quite an impressive one.
Look at their claws.
They're so strong.
Why are we talking about bears?
Presenting Queen Aurora of the Moors.
Thank you.
-You look wonderful.
-I'm so happy to be here.
Aurora, this is truly an honor.
Welcome to Ulstead.
Such a beautiful girl.
I can see how you stole Philip's heart.
Your Majesty.
The flowers in your hair. I'm allergic.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no. No, no. It's all right.
They're beautiful.
Presenting Maleficent.
Maleficent, it's wonderful to see you again.
This is my father, King John of Ulstead.
And my mother, Queen Ingrith.
Welcome to our home.
It's so very kind of you to invite me
this evening.
Don't smile.
And I would like to introduce you to Diaval.
I trust you had no trouble
finding the castle.
Why would I have trouble?
He's making small talk.
I'll explain it later.
No trouble at all.
Your Majesties, ladies and gentlemen,
dinner is served.
Please, make yourselves at home.
Bird.
Delicious.
Is there a problem?
It's iron.
Majesty, as you are sensitive to flowers,
she is averse to iron.
I had no idea.
Take it away at once.
I trust you'll be comfortable
using your hands?
Such a warm spell of weather, isn't it?
It certainly is.
Well, we have a small gift
for Philip and Aurora...
to celebrate their
glorious future together.
I simply can't wait to have a little one
running through the castle again.
This castle?
Yes, of course.
This will be their home.
I hear Aurora has a castle of her own.
Yes, sir, I do.
Yes...
I'm curious. How did Aurora
become Queen of the Moors?
I made her queen.
Her castle is quite stunning.
You must see it.
Yes, but in fact, she has another castle.
Does she not?
Mother...
One in the Moors,
and one left behind by her father.
King Stefan, was it not?
That castle was never my home.
It was given to the people.
So, you're also a true princess.
Even though Stefan died.
Was killed?
Remind me, did he die or was he killed?
Both.
Yes, you're right, it is very warm recently.
Because I remember
the story of a baby.
A baby cursed to sleep...
and never wake up.
Really?
Who would do such a terrible thing
to an innocent child?
Well, there are many who prey
on the innocent.
I'm sure your kind would agree.
What do you mean, my kind?
She means humans.
There are fairies missing from the Moors.
What I'm missing is some wine.
Stolen by human poachers.
That's the first I've heard of it.
Someone gave the order.
It sounds as if you're accusing the king.
No, she never said that.
Wait...
Sorry, who would steal a fairy?
Your Majesty, I must report
that two peasants were found dead...
just outside the Moors.
They'd been missing for several days.
I see.
Yes, we all see.
The borders are open, but humans
are not welcome. Isn't that right?
What exactly are you implying, Your Majesty?
Innocent men are being slaughtered
on the Moors...
and she's talking about fairies.
Contain your animal.
Or I will.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were making a threat.
Well, do you?
Do I what?
Know better?
Enough.
Put her down.
Please, put her down.
We're here to celebrate.
Forgive me, he's right.
Let's not forget why we're here.
The start of a new life for Aurora.
-Cheers.
You have done an admirable job, Maleficent...
going against your own nature
to raise this child.
But now...
Aurora will finally get...
the love of a real family.
A real mother.
Because the one thing I regret...
is never having a daughter of my own.
But tonight changes that.
Tonight, I consider Aurora my own.
Guards!
We have opened our home to a witch!
Stop!
There is no union.
There will be no wedding.
-Maleficent!
-We must protect the king!
Maleficent, please, stop now.
John, I'm so frightened.
What has she done to me?
Father!
John!
We go home.
It's a curse.
It's a curse!
Maleficent has cursed the king!
What have you done?
I've done nothing.
Aurora, we go home now.
Aurora!
Wake him!
Wake him, please.
Stand aside!
To the bedroom!
This magic, we have no tools to reverse it.
There must be a lesion.
Proof of her witchery.
Please, leave His Majesty his dignity.
We all saw what Maleficent did to him.
I'm so sorry.
A curse upon our king
is a curse upon this kingdom.
All he wanted was peace.
This is all my fault.
You have nothing to apologize for, my dear.
Maleficent is a threat to everyone.
Especially you.
We'll do our best to protect you.
There must be a way to reverse this.
Mother, could you try kissing him?
True love and all that.
I doubt that would work.
It could save him.
-A kiss is just a kiss.
-Please, Mother.
Very well.
You wanted peace...
now rest in peace forever.
I told you.
This is no fairy tale.
I have to return to the Moors.
It's the only way.
Wait, wait. Come here.
I have to find her.
It's the middle of the night.
She will break the curse.
I know she will.
Okay, well,
let me come with you.
No. You should stay with your family.
You are my family.
Let her go, Philip.
Maybe she can save him.
Maleficent!
Godmother!
Please come back.
She's not in the Moors.
Diaval.
No one's seen her.
I'm so happy to see you.
She's nowhere to be found.
What if she never comes back?
I could be stuck as a human forever.
I have to find her.
She's the only one who can break the curse.
Tell me she's dead.
The iron pierced her flesh.
She fell into the river
and went over the falls.
Then where is her head?
There was something else.
Another creature.
It pulled her from the depths of the sea.
What did it look like?
Her.
It carried her up into the sky.
A wounded animal lashes out
and now she's not alone.
We must be ready for war.
Maleficent has cursed the king!
Stay inside!
If Conall hadn't found her,
she would be dead.
They tried to kill her with this.
Do you hear it?
It's a message from the humans.
I hear it loud and clear.
Time for us to die.
Humans have used iron
against us for centuries.
And we are almost extinct because of it.
Killing peasants on the Moors
will only lead to more conflict, Borra.
They've pulled the iron from the earth...
made their swords and shields,
drove us underground.
But this...
This will finish us.
Our people are safe here for now.
But for how long?
The humans will find us.
They will not stop.
I call for war.
I call for war!
Right now!
There are too many humans.
Too many kingdoms.
Conall, they will keep finding
new ways to destroy us.
We can't win.
We can't win!
Not this way.
No. You're wrong, Conall.
We have something they didn't plan on.
We have her.
She holds powers none of us possess.
She is wounded, Borra.
Who are you?
You reek of human.
Maybe I was wrong about you.
Or maybe Conall should have left you
for dead at the bottom of the sea.
No.
It's there, isn't it?
It's inside you.
You see?
You see what's inside her?
That is what will save us all.
You saved me.
Come.
Let me show you who we are.
We're Dark Fey.
Same as you.
We're all that remain.
Unseen here, far away from mankind.
Look!
As more human kingdoms emerged,
we went into hiding...
from every corner of the earth...
doing what we had to, to survive.
But many were lost.
Only a few generations ago...
our kind roamed every part of the world.
The tundra.
The forest.
The jungle.
The desert.
Now, our only refuge is here...
in this cave.
Our nest of origin.
Listen. Play in the wind.
Go!
Those children should be soaring
over the trees and rivers.
Instead, they are raised in exile.
I could protect them.
How? By waging war against the humans?
I've been at war with them my whole life.
Not all of them.
There was one you raised as your own.
Maybe we don't have to hide from the humans.
Maybe we can exist without fear...
and war.
Find a way together.
That will never happen.
Gotcha!
Welcome to your new home.
We've been worried about you, dear.
Your Majesty.
I couldn't find her.
My heart breaks for you.
She has brought a cloud of darkness
upon your happiness.
I know she was against this marriage.
Never trusted your instincts as a queen.
When I saw her at dinner...
with her horns covered...
bent cowering...
Well, it's no wonder that she lashed out.
I just don't know what to do.
You do truly love him, don't you?
My son.
Deeply.
It is love that will heal you.
It's what heals us all.
Let's move forward together...
as a family.
To all who live on the Moors...
What is that noise?
...and kingdoms far and wide,
the king and queen invite you...
to attend the wedding...
of their son Philip to Aurora
in three days' time.
All are welcome.
And all are expected!
Did you hear that?
We're invited to the castle!
I knew Aurora wouldn't abandon us!
I always knew I'd be invited.
Just glad you two made the cut.
Who's getting married?
Aurora, we don't have to think
about the wedding right now.
The queen is right.
We owe it to everyone...
especially the king.
What about Maleficent?
She's gone.
The Phoenix.
It is said the Dark Fey began with her...
evolved over centuries.
You are the last of her descendants.
Her blood is your own.
You are her.
In your hands,
you hold the power of life and death...
destruction and rebirth.
But nature's greatest power
is the power of true transformation.
You transformed when you raised Aurora.
When you found love...
in the middle of your pain.
I'm asking you to take all of your fury...
all of your pain...
and not use it.
Help us broker peace with the humans.
Because peace...
could be the Dark Fey's
final transformation.
The Moors are our last true nature on earth.
And yet you named a human as queen.
A daughter you cared for.
I have no daughter.
She has chosen her side.
We've just heard.
There's going to be a wedding
at the castle in three days.
Humans will come from all over.
That's when we attack.
We'll kill the king and queen of Ulstead...
and their young prince.
Their kingdom will fall.
And the Fey will rise again.
The fairies made it.
I wore it when I married the king.
I'm sure it's perfect.
So am I.
Your Majesty, she's absolutely lovely.
Considering how she was raised.
By the same evil witch who cursed her.
It's a miracle Prince Philip came along.
It's a miracle
the poor child is alive at all.
Thank you so much.
It's exquisite.
When I'm older...
I'm going to live here,
in the Moors, with you.
Then we can look after each other.
-Tell me what's troubling you.
-It's nothing.
Aurora, I know you better than that.
This jewelry...
my hair...
all these rules.
I can't breathe.
I feel like
I'm not Queen of the Moors anymore.
I feel like a different person.
Listen...
I fell in love with a girl in the forest
and only her.
You don't have to change.
I don't want you to change.
I should have never asked her
to wear that scarf.
Ah, yes.
Well...
Does it work?
I only have a handful of fairy specimens
to work with...
and the extraction process is painstaking.
Extraction from what?
Tomb Bloom flowers.
They grow from a fairy's grave,
contain their very essence.
When you mix the pollen
with iron powder...
the resulting dust ends a fairy's life.
We will need thousands more.
Show me.
Very well.
So...
Finally, the Moors will be mine.
No more fairies.
Stay alert, men.
This is where I found them.
Excellent.
But what if the winged one returns?
Don't you worry about that.
We'll be ready.
Take the Tomb Blooms.
Get to work!
Sentries, stay alert!
Keep your weapons on hand.
Move it!
Maleficent...
This is where we bury our dead.
They've destroyed it.
This is what the humans do.
They're nothing but locusts
that swarm the earth.
We have to stop them.
You spent years caring for a human...
now it's time to care for your own.
Fire!
Reload! We go again!
Reload! There's another one!
Everyone, stay together!
We're about to leave the Moors.
Grab the hand or the wing...
or the tail of whoever is closest to you.
Hey, over here! Yeah, over here!
Hold formation, guards. Hold formation.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Stop right there.
I'm with the bride.
We've been told to let the other kind
find their seats first.
But I'm not a human.
-I'm a raven.
-What?
A raven. The black bird.
This rice is delicious.
You're supposed to throw it
at the bride and groom.
What? And waste good rice?
What's the hold up?
Let me in!
Why can't humans come in, too?
Why can't we come in?
I know it's bad luck...
but I had to see you.
For you.
A Tomb Bloom?
Where did you get this?
From my mother.
The sun's up.
It's our wedding day.
From my mother.
Where should we sit, Flittle?
On the left.
We're with the bride.
Yes, we are.
But the groom's lovely, too.
Yes, he is.
I'm with both.
Now.
What's this?
Nobody is allowed in here except me.
And I'm already here, so go away!
Maleficent, please stop.
Maleficent.
She didn't do it.
Get out!
Before I call the guards!
The missing fairies.
I said get out. Did you hear me?
What have you done?
You're a pixie.
How dare you call me that?
I'm Lickspittle, the nobleman...
and I serve the queen.
She took your wings.
We have to release them.
They belong on the Moors.
As you do, Aurora.
A human who has betrayed her kind.
You put the curse on the king.
Oh, dear.
You may be queen...
but you are very young.
Ruling humans is a bit more complicated...
than running around barefoot
with flowers in your hair.
When I was young...
my family's kingdom bordered the Moors.
And one particularly harsh winter...
our crops died...
and the people began to suffer.
And as we looked over our walls...
we could see the fairies thriving.
My brother and I believed we
should take what we needed...
while my father, the king,
sought their kindness.
Choosing peace over our people,
he sent my brother to do his bidding.
He never came back.
Those savages...
creatures who could barely grunt,
let alone engage in talks, killed him.
I don't believe that.
Our people became fearful.
They overthrew my father.
The land fell into chaos.
I was cast out.
Forced by fate into marriage
with King John of Ulstead.
Another weak king
speaking of tolerance and civility.
And now, my own son...
corrupted with visions of harmony.
But peace will not be our downfall.
Now lock her up.
A war is coming.
No! No!
I wish you could be here with me.
Conall wanted peace...
and they filled him with iron.
Now, we will have our war.
Our fight begins now!
We will rise together!
We fight together.
And we will show them no mercy!
Come on! Go!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Where are all Philip's guests?
Humans are poor timekeepers.
Start the music.
Come on! Come on!
She's gone.
Hey!
It's a trap! Get down!
Your Majesty...
they're coming from the sea.
She escaped!
Down this way, come on!
Your Highness.
Upon my command.
Check every room!
She can't be far!
Wait.
What's going on?
Now.
Fire!
No!
They look just like her.
Withdraw!
Pull back!
Maleficent's starting a war.
First my father, and now this.
Philip! She didn't curse him.
-Maleficent.
-What?
She never cursed him.
It was your mother.
What are you saying?
It was the spindle.
The curse is still in it.
Your mother used it against your father.
Look.
It's the same.
She's locked the Moor folk in the chapel.
This isn't a wedding.
It's a trap.
Remember where you came from.
Remember who you are.
I've made my choice.
You'll have to make yours.
Stay low!
Divide!
Follow me!
Attack!
-Ignite!
No!
Aunties!
It's too heavy!
Aurora!
Diaval! You're here.
What's happening?
Weapon change!
Weapon change! Go!
Mother!
You have to stop this.
We are at war.
This isn't a war. It's a massacre.
Philip, you don't understand.
These creatures stand between us...
and everything we need to survive.
You're wrong.
We can stand together.
Well, you're a fool to believe that.
You don't know what it takes
to fight for our kind.
You lied to me.
I am protecting the kingdom...
and your throne.
What about Father?
Were you protecting him, too?
The prince is not feeling well.
See him to his chambers.
Now.
Sire, stop!
Yield! Yield!
My mother cursed the king
so she could destroy the Moor folk.
Your men are paying heavily for it.
We have to do something!
Goodbye, girls.
No, come back!
Flittle! No!
No!
Hey, you, stay with your own!
Run, Aurora, run!
Let him go!
No! No!
Godmother.
For Flittle!
We've got her!
Go! Go!
This way! This way!
Go!
Stand down!
This is not my fight.
My mother wanted a war,
and you're giving it to her.
I won't allow her hatred
to ruin my kingdom or yours.
There will be no Fey blood on my hands.
This way!
Maleficent's back!
She's going for the queen.
Yield! Yield!
Stand down!
Lower your weapons!
There's the evil that I promised them.
Your kind is more predictable than humans.
Stop!
Well, almost.
Stop.
I'm sorry I doubted you,
but this isn't you.
There's another way.
I know who you are.
I know you.
You do not.
Yes, I do.
You're my mother.
No!
Do you know what
makes a great leader, Aurora?
The ability to instill fear
in your subjects...
and then use that fear...
Your Majesty.
...against your enemies.
So...
I spread the story of the evil witch...
and the princess she cursed.
It didn't matter who woke Sleeping Beauty.
They were all terrified.
And the story became legend.
I know you think I'm a monster.
But what I did to the king,
to Maleficent, to my son...
I did for Ulstead.
You are a traitor to your kind,
and you will pay for it.
Maleficent is dead!
We will never again live in fear!
Get back here!
Ulstead is free at last!
Let me go!
What's happening?
Well, well.
Hello, Beasty.
I missed you.
Did you bump your head, then?
I did.
Philip.
Yes?
Do you love my daughter?
With everything I have.
Good.
I believe this belongs to you.
Curses don't end.
They're broken.
It ends.
There will be no more fighting.
Ulstead will never attack
the Moors again.
And from this day on...
we move forward...
and find our way...
in peace.
Together.
Today, there will be a wedding.
Not just a union of two people...
but a union of two kingdoms.
And all are invited...
all are safe...
and all are welcome.
Hello, there.
We cannot live amongst monsters...
Someone should really cover those horns.
If only Conall could see you.
Borra...
it's time to come home.
Hello.
Can you come here?
Yes?
Will you give me away?
Never.
No.
Will you walk me down the aisle?
Yes.
Apologies to anyone
I might have mauled today.
Is that...?
She can change her back.
I suppose.
Only if we wanted to.
Father.
I'm so glad to see you.
I've dreamed of this moment.
Two kingdoms united at last.
And it's because of you.
I'm so proud of you. So proud.
She looks better in green.
Pink, you mean.
No, in green.
Pink.
-Green.
-Pink.
Flittle!
It's perfect.
Let her go.
Pull yourself together.
We are here to join
two kingdoms...
divided by fear.
Today, you teach us
we are not defined by where we are from...
but by whom we love.
The bands, please.
-Do you, Philip, take Aurora...
-I do.
-And do you, Aurora, take...
Then I pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
You're smiling.
It's a new day.
It is.
Morning.
Will you stay awhile?
A little while.
But don't worry...
I'll see you at the christening.