Subtitles by explosiveskull
Ja-James, what are you doing?
Something that I should have
done a long time ago.
Top university, tenure
position, fully-furnished house.
Who cares where it is?
One plus one?
Two.
You're a genius.
No wonder they hired you
to teach math.
I thought it was because
of my incredible charm...
and my devilish handsome,
good looks.
Unh-unh, that's why I married
you and let you knock me up.
So how is little "Adam Jr."
dealing with the big move...
leaving the city?
Little "Lisa Jr." is doing
just fine.
It's her daddy I'm worried
about.
Me?
Yes, you hate the country.
I do not.
Wow, would you look at that?
I'm looking. Oh, the house
isn't bad, either.
- Professor Pierce?
- Yes?
Hi, I'm David.
Nice to meet you.
I think I'm gonna be in your
linear algebra class.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. And you must be
Mrs. Pierce.
Oh, Mrs. Pierce makes me sound
like my mother-in-law.
Please, call me Lisa.
Sure thing, Lisa.
Mrs. Pierce is fine.
Oh, hey, let me help you
with that.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
So what brings you out here,
David?
Class doesn't start till Monday.
I've got your keys, professor.
Yeah, they give them to all
their students.
Nah, I'm just kidding. It's a...
it's a work study program.
The university pays me to keep
up some of the properties.
Yours included.
Here you go, professor.
Thank you.
Door's already open, though.
We don't really keep 'em locked
around here.
Oh, is that safe?
Well, in my experience most
people's problems...
happen behind closed doors.
Oh, yeah, professor,
uh, someone sent you a gift.
I put it inside.
Gift?
Come on, "Professor."
Let's see your new home.
Wow, this place must
really need a math teacher.
- Wow.
- Yes.
Still missing the city?
Not anymore.
I think this table alone is
bigger than our old apartment.
It's from your sister.
Do I dare ask how it got here
before we did?
Be nice. I gave her the address.
The last time we saw your
sister, she almost burned...
down our apartment with candles
and incense.
It's a house-warming gift.
She's not so bad.
As long as she doesn't pop out
of here, I'll agree with you.
That's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Your sister sent us a box
that doesn't open.
"This fertility box will keep
you company...
"until I come to visit. See you
soon."
She's coming to visit already?
Shush. She's not here now.
No, she's not.
So let's go create some problems
behind closed doors.
Yes, ma'am. After you,
Mrs. Pierce, come on, come on.
Don't.
Oh, for the love of everything.
No, no, slow down.
Our room...
And this is Adam Jr.'s room.
Lisa Jr.'s gonna love it here.
Her dad's gonna love it here,
too.
Oh, this looks kinda heavy.
Guess I have my first
after-school project.
What is it? What's wrong?
What if I'm not a good mom?
You're gonna be a great mom.
How do you know?
You're loving, you're kind,
and you're loyal.
Go on.
And nurturing...
What about protective?
And protective. And you're
beautiful, and sexy.
You really wanna do this here?
I don't care where.
Just now.
All right.
First day of school.
How do I look?
All you need's a pipe.
No.
It's perfect.
Please be careful today.
No heavy lifting.
I'm pregnant, not breakable,
remember?
Walking, even jogging is
healthy.
Walking, please.
Okay, fine.
Or maybe I'll just
put together the crib then.
No, no, no, don't do that.
I promise I'll do it when
I get home.
Good, because pretty soon, one
plus one is gonna equal three.
I love your logic.
Go get 'em, professor.
A box that doesn't open...
Huh.
Just remember, no matter how
complicated the problem...
the solution is always logical.
Math, and life for that matter,
are very reliable in that way.
All you have to do is logically
work through the problem...
and the solution will appear.
Numbers are always rational...
except, of course...
when they're being irrational.
Thank you, everyone, and don't
forget to read chapter one...
in your books before our
next meeting.
Good first class, professor.
Thank you, David.
Glad to see you in a shirt
today.
Hello.
"All of math's and life's problems
can be solved using logic?"
You wouldn't agree?
One plus one doesn't always
equal two.
You sound like my wife.
Smart lady you have there.
Adam Pierce. We haven't met yet.
Ronald Clark.
As in Dr. Clark, head of the
Math Department?
I also teach a
course in parapsychology.
That's an interesting
combination of subjects.
Logic by day, superstition
by night.
Mm. "There are more things in
the heaven and earth, Horatio...
"than are dreamt of in your
philosophy."
Yeah, I guess I'm more of a
science and logic kind of guy.
Oh, me, too.
Being blind, though, has a way
of opening your eyes...
to what's really going on
in the world.
Sorry. I didn't mean to offend.
Oh, don't apologize, professor.
I'm sitting in your class,
not you in mine.
I'm not complaining, but do you
have any idea why...
the university offered me such
a good package to teach here?
We have a shortage of qualified
math teachers.
Evidently, my superstition class
scares off...
some of the more qualified
academics.
And the school still lets you
teach it?
The students love it.
Consequently, their parents'
checkbooks love it.
And I suppose that the administrators
don't want to tempt fate.
Excuse me?
Miss? Are you okay?
I, I lost my baby.
Oh, my God. We have
to get you to a hospital.
I'm not well...
No, w-we need to get you
some help.
You're not well, either.
I'm sorry?
You're afraid of me?
Soon, everyone will be afraid
of you.
I don't mean-mean to bother you.
I don't want any trouble.
Then don't care for it.
Don't love it. Don't protect it.
It's not yours anymore.
Hey, babe, how was your walk,
not run?
Actually, I just got a little
spooked out in the forest.
Yeah? What happened?
I ran into this creepy woman out
there, covered in blood.
What? What happened?
Are you all right?
I'm fine, I just...
She just really freaked me out.
I thought she needed help,
but then maybe she didn't.
And she started saying these
really crazy things.
Was she playing a banjo?
Missing some teeth?
No... but she was really dirty.
Are you gonna be all right?
You need me to come home?
No. No, don't be silly.
I'm fine.
I just wanted to hear
your voice.
All right, I love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, my God.
Lisa, I'm home.
Glad to see we're locking
the doors again.
Hey.
Lisa?
Lisa, you sleepin'?
Lisa!
Yes? How is she?
It was touch and go there
for a moment...
but your wife's going to be
okay.
Thank you.
She suffered a miscarriage,
and then she hemorrhaged.
She must've been lifting
something heavy...
lucky you found her when
you did.
She was exercising, stretching,
walking, maybe jogging.
No, that all sounds pretty
healthy.
It had to be something else.
The amount of trauma that I saw
internally was pretty extensive.
Can I see her?
Yes, but there's something else.
Your wife won't be able to have
children anymore.
I'm sorry.
How are you, darling?
Terrible.
I was so worried about you...
but the doctor says you're gonna
be okay.
No, I'm not. I lost the baby.
I can't have children.
How am I gonna be okay?
We still have each other.
We're gonna get through this,
I promise you.
The crib...
It was too heavy? You were
trying to put it together?
No, it wasn't... I heard crying.
Adam... I saw our daughter.
I held Lisa Jr. in my arms.
And then I woke up here.
Babe? I don't understand.
I don't...
There's my big sister.
Hi. Don't worry, Becky's here
to take care of you.
Hey.
How are you, Becky?
I'm good, Adam.
Hey, do you wanna give us a few
minutes of some girl time?
Thank you.
Sugar, salt, gluten. There's
nothing healthy in here at all.
How is she doing?
She's resting now.
She'll probably sleep through
the night.
Do you need me to drop you
off at the house...
so you can get settled
or anything?
Oh, no, I'm staying here
with my sister.
I'll leave when she does.
I'm not going to deal with your
shit, Becky. Not this time.
Welcome home, Lisa.
Thank you, David.
Hi, I'm Becky, I'm Lisa's
sister.
Pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
The pleasure's all mine.
Can I get your bag?
Yes, please.
Here you go.
Thanks. I'll be seeing you
around.
See ya.
He's cute.
Easy, he's one of my students.
Just being friendly.
Guest room is right over there.
No incense, please.
You need anything?
I need a shower.
Hey, honey, you remember the box
that wouldn't open?
Hm.
It opens.
I know. I opened it.
You did? When?
When you were at school.
Can you please put it back in the
living room where you found it?
I found it in the nursery.
What? What was it doing
in there?
I don't know. I just assumed
you put it there.
No, I put it above the
fireplace.
Adam, please.
I see you guys got my
house-warming gift.
Yep.
Actually, it got here
before we did.
Where'd you get it anyway?
It's pretty cool, right?
I actually found it at an estate
sale on my way down here.
Lucky us.
When do you go back to work?
Tomorrow. I can't take anymore
time off.
Lucky us.
Lisa... you scared me. What are
you doing down here?
The painting is different.
What do you mean?
The children are all staring
at the mother.
They weren't doing that before.
Looks the same to me.
What are you saying?
That I'm making it up?
No.
I'm saying you're going through
a really difficult time...
and maybe your mind is just
trying to sort it all out.
I know you're gonna
be all right.
E equals MC, squared.
I know this isn't physics class,
but I bring this up to remind...
you that just like matter can be
neither created nor destroyed...
the same can be true for the
equations here in this class.
They must equal out in the end,
and if they don't...
then the equation was false
to begin with.
Thank you.
Dr. Clark, if I keep
seeing you in here...
I'm gonna have to start
grading you.
If you do, I warn you,
I'm pretty good at this stuff.
And now you're teaching
Einstein, ha, ha, watch out.
What can I do for you?
I stopped by to offer my
condolences.
I was sorry to hear
about your loss.
Thank you.
How's your wife?
It's been tough on her. She's
gonna get through it, though.
That's good to hear.
As long as she's still giving
you a hard time...
about the answer to basic
equations.
More than ever. She's even
starting to believe...
in some of the same stuff
that you do.
Ooh, that bad. Hoo-hoo.
And her sister's even worse.
She believes in everything.
Someone who believes
in everything scares me...
even more than somebody who
believes in nothing.
Close your eyes.
Breathe in. Breathe out.
You're sitting on a beach.
It's beautiful.
Quiet. It's very peaceful...
It's just you.
The sun.
And the calming waves.
You're very relaxed.
Becky, can you hear that?
Hear what?
I'll go and check the kitchen.
What am I looking for?
Is there anyone up here?
Mommy...
Becky! There's a little girl
lying in the crib.
What?
There's nobody here.
That's impossible.
She was right here. There was a
little girl lying right here!
- I don't see anyone.
- I'm not crazy.
What did she look like?
She looked like this.
Well, whoever she was, she's
gone now. We're safe.
Are we?
- Hey.
Didn't think you'd still be up.
Something's happening, Adam.
What is it?
I saw something in the
nursery again.
There was a little girl lying
in the crib.
Was Becky with you?
Becky didn't see her. I saw her.
I've been seeing and
hearing other things, too.
Are you hearing things now?
No, not now. I'm serious, Adam.
I am, too.
We'll talk to your doctor.
And no more nursery.
I'll get rid of that crib.
It isn't the crib, Adam.
I told you that I'd put it
together when I got home.
If you had only waited for me...
If I'd have waited... what?
I wouldn't have lost the baby?
I never said that.
It sounded like that.
I'll be right back, Mrs. Pierce.
How is she?
Physically, your wife is fine.
Emotionally, she's been through
a very traumatic experience...
and it's going to take some
time to heal.
Her hormones are still all over
the place...
as her body tries to figure out
it's no longer pregnant.
What about everything that
she's hearing and seeing?
It's her way of going through
the grieving process.
I prescribed her some medication
so she can relax...
and as long as she doesn't
become a danger to herself...
she should be okay.
But if that changes, you bring
her right back to me.
Of course, of course.
Thank you so much, doctor.
I think that's the last of it.
That sounds good. It's supposed
to rain later.
A country boy with a horse,
can't beat that.
What can we do for you, Becky?
You forgot the doll.
I'll take that.
Thanks.
The nursery won't be bothering
your sister anymore, ma'am.
Not with you here, it won't.
Mommy.
Shhhh.
Adam, wake up.
Lisa...
Wake up, wake up.
There's someone in the house.
What?
She just walked down the
hallway.
She? Was it Becky?
No. No.
- Stay here.
- Be careful.
Becky?
What? You think you saw me
fucking your student?
When I get home, we need
to talk...
about how long your sister's
gonna be staying.
Did you know that your
university...
offers a degree
in parapsychology?
Mm-hm, oh, it's not a degree,
is a certificate.
Guy who runs it's the
Head of the Math Department.
- Dr. Clark?
- Mm-hm.
It says here that he's one
of the most respected...
paranormal researchers
in the country.
I want you to talk to him about
what's been going on here.
What's been going on?
What's with the poker?
It's made of cast iron.
Supposedly good against this
sort of thing.
You read that in the catalog?
I'm asking you to do this
for me.
Will you please just
speak to him? Please.
You know, we do get offices,
professor.
Yes, but I find the classroom...
to be way more conducive
to learning.
Agreed.
I got a message you wanted
to see me.
I'm guessing this isn't
about a math problem.
No, this is about your other
area of expertise.
Ah.
It seems that my wife has been
seeing things...
since her miscarriage and, uh,
thanks to her sister...
she now thinks our house
is haunted.
Haunted? The faculty house?
Mm-hm.
You know, I've been here
a long time...
and I've never heard anything
like that.
It'd mean a lot if you'd come
over and talk to her anyway.
Make her feel better.
Let her know everything
is gonna be okay.
You mean, I'd actually get
a chance to help...
keep one of our math professors,
as opposed to chasing them away?
Yes.
How does tomorrow sound?
Perfect.
Hey, Lisa, did you borrow
my make-up?
Lisa, are you in here?
Found your pom-poms.
♪ Bulldogs sure are number one ♪
What the hell?
Becky?
Is that you?
I'm in the bathroom.
Hey, what happened?
Eh, just a little clumsy,
I'll be out in a minute.
Let me in.
Shh.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Okay, well, call me if you
need anything.
Thanks, I love you.
You're fine.
Lisa?
What's wrong?
Becky's gone. She didn't even
say good-bye.
Babe, I'm so sorry.
She always does this.
She comes in here out
of nowhere, creates chaos...
and then she leaves the same
way she came.
I know. I just thought this time
would be different.
She's my sister.
She's the only one who
understands.
I'm here.
And I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
I'm so scared, Adam.
I talked to Dr. Clark and he's
gonna come and see you tomorrow.
- Yeah...
- Thank you.
Of course, of course.
Hey... it's gonna be alright.
You want me to get your door
for you?
Dr. Clark, welcome.
One plus one doesn't always
equal two and I heard...
there's a beautiful woman living
here who agrees with me on that.
I like him already.
Oh, this is going to be fun.
Doctor, I'd like you to meet
my wife, Lisa.
Lisa. Pleasure to meet you,
ma'am.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you for coming.
Hi, professor, Mrs. Pierce.
You seem to be getting around
a lot lately.
Well, he's not just your
student, professor...
he's mine also.
Well, today it's your class,
doctor.
Alright, then.
The university didn't give me a
house. Let's investigate yours.
Somehow, I feel like this all...
has to do with me losing
the baby.
On a cellular level...
yourself and the baby are still
connected.
It doesn't matter whether you
miscarried or gave birth.
In fact, there are recent
studies that show...
that fetal cells from
a pregnancy...
they stay with the mother
for the rest of her life.
What do the cells do?
Well, one theory is that since
they are foreign cells...
they do harm to the mother,
which is why women...
have higher rates of autoimmune
diseases such as lupus.
Oh, that's comforting.
But, there's another theory...
one to which I personally
subscribe and that is...
that the cells actually help
protect the mother...
by assisting in the healing
process.
That's why women live longer.
I like that idea much better.
Agreed.
Mrs. Pierce, I'm gonna be
honest with you.
I don't think there's anything
wrong with your house.
How can you be so sure?
I sense things that other people
usually don't.
You can call it my gift
or my curse...
depending on your point of view.
So what, everything's in my
head, like hormones gone wild?
No, don't misunderstand me.
I believe you 100%, Mrs. Pierce.
But you just said..
I said the house isn't the
problem...
which means something else is.
Then what?
What's behind me right now?
The fireplace.
What's this?
That's my sister's house-warming
gift.
A box that couldn't be opened,
until it was.
- David.
- Yes, sir.
Who opened it?
I did.
Well... I think we found
your problem.
An empty box?
No... what was in it.
What are you talking about?
You said, professor, that you
were not able to open this box...
but your wife could.
So?
So, I believe that when your
wife opened this box...
it killed your baby.
Oh, my God!
All right, that's enough,
it's time to go.
This is not one of our
intellectual...
"Science versus Superstition"
debates, professor.
No, it isn't.
- This is very real.
- Mm-hmm.
Adam, listen to him,
he's trying to help.
Please, Adam, hey, hey.
I brought you here to make my
wife feel better...
not to scare her.
Life isn't logical or rational,
professor.
Yourself and your wife are
in a very real danger.
From a house-warming gift?
You know, it's no wonder that
your department...
has a shortage of math teachers,
because you're nuts.
And I don't want to see you
around here anymore, either.
My sister-in-law is gone,
so the meat market is closed.
Why did you do that?
Why? Because he thinks a box
caused your miscarriage.
I believe him.
You think this is the problem?
There, problem solved. Can I
have my wife back now?
Ad... Adam?
Adam?
Are you seeing things, too?
A girl?
A woman. It was two of them,
actually.
You didn't try to hurt them,
did you?
What?
I don't know why I said that.
Pack your things, we're gonna
go now.
- Where?
- Anywhere.
You heard Dr. Clark.
It's not the house.
We need to make things right.
I thought you'd be happy to go.
We can't leave.
The Aztecs referred to it
as a fertility box...
because only a pregnant woman
is capable of opening it.
The box itself, it's not evil.
It's more like a prison...
to keep a malicious entity
trapped inside.
So we're very fortunate,
professor...
that when you decided to throw
it away...
you did so from your front
porch...
rather than the middle of the
ocean somewhere.
And now, we have to get whatever
it is that got out, back in.
How do we do that?
First we have to find out what
it is, what it wants.
And why it killed my baby.
Especially that.
I did some research.
You see that a man named James
Harper claimed...
that a fertility box that caused
his wife Emily's miscarriage...
just a few years back.
I've seen her before.
You've seen her before? When?
The day I had my miscarriage.
Remember that creepy woman who
scared me in the forest?
That was her.
Mrs. Pierce, Emily Harper is
dead.
Her husband, James, killed her
two years ago.
He's been in state prison
ever since.
That's not possible.
I-I saw her, I spoke to her.
Maybe it was somebody
that looked like her.
No, it was her. I'm sure of it.
Believe me, that's a day
I'll never forget.
Mrs. Pierce, I believe
everything you've said.
Now I need you all
to believe in me.
Okay, doctor, every room
is covered.
All the ambiance levels have
been set.
So if there's a sound that
doesn't belong, we'll know it.
People would only listen more...
they could see so much better
with their ears...
than they ever could with
their eyes.
And we're also going to be
recording...
on both a hard drive and mag
tape.
Isn't mag tape a little
old school?
The world we're trying to hear
is very old school, professor.
Is everybody ready?
- Yeah.
- Good, then let's begin.
David, what's happening?
I'm not sure, but there's something
definitely going on in the nursery.
Playback what's recording
directly from the mag, please.
Mom, mother. Mommy, mama.
Madre, mama. Madre?
Who's saying that?
Mom, mother. Mommy, mama.
Madre, mama. Madre.
Record again, David.
There's somebody up there.
What does it want?
Stop.
Rewind and playback
just what happened.
What does it want?
Life. Death.
David, record.
Who are you?
Stop. Rewind.
Stop. Playback.
Who are you?
Lisa... Jr.
I take it we're all
in the dark now.
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah.
That was fast.
Doctor, why did it say its name
was Lisa Jr.?
I was hoping you could tell me
that.
That's what I used to call
my baby.
David, start recording.
And playback directly
from the mag.
Mom, mother. Mommy, mama.
No! No.
Mama...
David, switch off playback,
keep recording.
Lisa Jr., you got out of your
box. How do I get you back in?
You don't.
- She's gone!
- Who was that?
That's-that's the girl.
That's the little girl.
Mrs. Pierce...
I see you.
I see you, too.
Doctor Clark, are you okay?
Hey.
I think so. Yeah.
We weren't sure
there for a moment.
- Who did you see?
- What?
You said, "I see you."
The entity.
It killed your unborn
daughter...
possessed her spirit
and then took her place.
How do we get rid of it? How do
we get it back in the box?
I don't know. But I know
it's getting stronger.
I need to get him to a hospital.
You two just get out of here.
Go somewhere safe.
No, no, no, there is no
safe place.
Mrs. Pierce, this thing
is connected to you.
It is a part of you.
There's no place that you can go
it will not follow.
There has to be something
that we can do.
James and Emily Harper got it
back in the box.
How did they do it?
I don't know.
And Emily Harper's dead.
Well, then we're just going
to have to ask James.
I haven't had many visitors
since I killed my wife.
So who are you again?
I met your wife, Emily,
out in the forest, recently.
Really?
People think that I'm crazy?
I was pregnant
and she threatened me.
Obviously, I think we all know
that...
it couldn't have been Emily.
We found your fertility box.
Where?
Apparently, when someone
kills their wife...
their landlord has an estate
sale.
Did you open it?
Yeah.
Who have you seen so far?
I've seen a baby, a little girl,
and a teenager and...
I've seen a young woman,
and an old woman.
As I'm sure you already know,
it kills unborn babies...
possesses who they were going
to be.
Has it made physical contact?
Yeah. It kissed me
in the shower.
You made out with your own
possessed ghost daughter?
I mean, I may have killed
my wife...
but that is some twisted shit.
I'm glad you find this all
amusing. What does it mean?
It means that you're almost
out of time.
When it's young, only the mother
can see it.
But as it gets older,
it gets stronger.
Pretty soon, it won't be kissing
you, it'll be killing you...
and everyone else, until there
is no one else.
You stopped it somehow.
How did you do it?
You're the one that needs to be
stopped, before you start...
loving it, and protecting it,
as if it was your own child.
You're not well anymore.
How do we get it back
in the box, James?
Look around you. Isn't it
obvious?
I killed my wife.
I don't understand.
You're its-its mother. It's
connected to you.
But it, it goes both ways.
It can't hurt you, but you
can hurt it.
When you die, it's got nowhere
to go, but back in the box.
No, there's gotta be
another way.
There's gotta be another way.
I wake up every morning wishing
that there was another way.
Kill your wife, everyone lives.
Don't, everyone dies.
We're gonna figure this out.
Every problem has a solution...
or the equation is false
to begin with.
He gave you the solution,
you just didn't like it.
One answer is not the only
answer.
He's right. I'm not well.
What are you talking about?
He's a crazy man that killed
his wife.
What if I started loving Lisa
Jr. and wanted to protect her?
Would you kill me?
Of course, I wouldn't.
Because this not a "her",
it is an "it".
An evil "it" that killed our
baby, and now wants to kill us.
No, not us. You, she wants
to kill you.
You're starting to scare me.
Yeah, that's what Emily said out
in the forest that day.
She said that pretty soon,
everybody would be scared of me.
Tell me, Adam, can one plus one
equal anything other than two?
You taught me that it could.
Let's just keep going...
and don't look back.
Let's go back to the city.
Go back to our apartment.
Hell, we could go anywhere.
You heard what Dr. Clark said.
She's a part of me now. She'll
follow me where ever we go.
I don't see her anywhere now.
I do.
Lisa?
Lisa!
Lisa, are you in here?
David?
Lisa
Jr., you got out of your box.
How do I put you back in?
You don't.
What are you doing here?
You gave us that box.
You're gonna answer for that.
I didn't know what it was.
I still don't.
Where's Lisa?
Upstairs.
I'll deal with you later.
You'll deal with me now!
Was it good for you, Daddy?
You weren't supposed to tell
Mommy about us.
Lisa!
Lisa, what happened?
I know why I saw Emily Harper
out in the forest that day.
A part of her was trapped in the
box, and when I opened it...
she tried to warn me...
about everything.
They're all looking at us.
Do you believe me now?
Yeah.
And do you believe we're gonna
live happily ever after?
We're gonna find a way to stop
this, I promise you.
You said I was gonna be
a great mom.
The best.
You remember the reasons
you told me?
'Cause you're loving, and kind,
and loyal, and nurturing.
And protective.
She's my daughter. I have to
take care of her and love her.
And protect her.
It's not Lisa Jr.
You're just jealous, because you
wanted a boy.
You wanted an Adam Jr and you're
taking it out on our daughter.
No, darlin', our baby's dead,
and something...
something terrible took its
place. But we can beat it.
By killing me?
No.
I won't let you hurt her.
I won't let you hurt me.
Look behind you.
Daddy, are you trying
to kill Mommy?
Lisa...
Adam.
No.
I'm so sorry...
I didn't... I didn't know it was
you. I didn't mean to...
I know, it's okay.
I'm going to get you out
of here. Come on.
No, you have to finish this.
...before it's too late.
I'm not giving up on you.
Please... do it for our real
daughter.
I love you.
I love you, too, professor.
Don't do it, Daddy.
Oh, God, forgive me.
Dr. Clark, surprised to see
you here.
Why's that?
Because when I was sitting
exactly where you are now...
James told me that nobody came
to visit him...
after he killed his wife,
everyone thought he went crazy.
Didn't he?
Didn't I?
They say that I killed Lisa...
because I found her sleeping
with one of my students.
They say I killed David.
That would be a logical
and rational conclusion.
You know, I tried talking
to the police, but even...
in the country, superstition
is something that only...
happens behind closed doors.
You and I both know the truth.
I know "a truth", but "the
truth"?
Adam... why did you kill Lisa?
Is it because James Harper
told you to?
Mm-mm.
It was the only way to save
her... and our little baby.
And you really believe that?
A wise person once said that
one plus one...
doesn't always equal two.
What, what happened to the box,
Adam?
The police couldn't find it, not
that they were looking for it.
But we couldn't find it, either.
I took care of it.
I sent it back to where
it came from.
Subtitles by explosiveskull