1
00:00:39,379 --> 00:00:41,293
This afternoon at 5:00,

2
00:00:41,379 --> 00:00:44,424
Il Duce (Benito Mussolini)
will speak to the nation!

3
00:00:44,554 --> 00:00:46,425
You are ordered to turn your radios on!

4
00:00:46,598 --> 00:00:52,469
All of you who have radio
sets and radio gramophones...

5
00:00:52,600 --> 00:00:55,861
are ordered to turn them on.

6
00:00:55,992 --> 00:00:59,776
Mussolini will speak to...

7
00:00:59,906 --> 00:01:02,559
all Italians!

8
00:01:02,820 --> 00:01:07,343
You are authorized by order of the
Fascist government...

9
00:01:07,430 --> 00:01:11,648
to interrupt your work. This afternoon at 5:00,
Il Duce will speak to the nation.

10
00:01:11,996 --> 00:01:17,041
<i>I was twelve and a half when I
saw her for the first time.</i>

11
00:01:17,215 --> 00:01:19,607
<i>And my mind plays tricks on me,
I remember it well.</i>

12
00:01:20,260 --> 00:01:23,870
<i>That day, Mussolini declared war
on France and Great Britain...</i>

13
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:27,913
<i>and I got my first bicycle.</i>

14
00:01:28,087 --> 00:01:31,480
The frame is British, the gears are German,

15
00:01:31,611 --> 00:01:34,480
the pedals are French,

16
00:01:34,568 --> 00:01:38,569
and the brakes are from... I forget.

17
00:01:38,699 --> 00:01:42,004
But the chain is Sicilian...
always keep it greasy.

18
00:01:42,135 --> 00:01:43,568
Are you sure it's safe?

19
00:01:43,569 --> 00:01:45,352
I have new bikes too.

20
00:01:45,961 --> 00:01:49,963
Mimi, we're at war.
Who can afford a new bicycle?

21
00:01:51,963 --> 00:01:53,399
Fighting men,

22
00:01:55,225 --> 00:01:58,486
on land, on sea and in the air,

23
00:01:59,400 --> 00:02:02,575
Black shirts of the revolution,

24
00:02:03,010 --> 00:02:04,967
men and women of Italy...

25
00:02:05,141 --> 00:02:08,315
and the Kingdom of Albania, hearth is...

26
00:02:35,714 --> 00:02:37,019
The hour...

27
00:02:39,106 --> 00:02:40,368
of decisions from which

28
00:02:41,150 --> 00:02:44,716
there is no return.

29
00:02:45,282 --> 00:02:48,587
Pino, think this ant knows he's dead meat?

30
00:02:48,674 --> 00:02:49,674
Who knows?

31
00:02:49,892 --> 00:02:52,675
If he's like you, he doesn't know shit.

32
00:02:53,066 --> 00:02:55,806
The declaration of war...

33
00:02:56,329 --> 00:03:00,721
has already been delivered to the ambassadors.

34
00:03:17,377 --> 00:03:19,943
I'm free from misery. Mary's son is my Lord.

35
00:03:20,117 --> 00:03:22,813
I'm free from misery. Mary's son is my Lord.

36
00:03:24,248 --> 00:03:27,163
Hey, guys!

37
00:03:31,598 --> 00:03:33,295
Lucky bastard.

38
00:03:33,904 --> 00:03:37,426
- He got a new bicycle!
- Man, she's beautiful!

39
00:03:38,470 --> 00:03:41,166
Custom-made, just like the racers.

40
00:03:41,514 --> 00:03:45,123
- Now you're a man, like us.
- So I can join the gang?

41
00:03:45,167 --> 00:03:47,341
- "Don Agostino"?
- Okay by me.

42
00:03:47,473 --> 00:03:50,169
- "Don Nicola"?
- I'd let him in.

43
00:03:50,516 --> 00:03:52,430
- "Don Tonino"?
- Sure.

44
00:03:52,560 --> 00:03:57,606
- And you, "Don Sasa"?
- I don't want some kid poking into our business.

45
00:03:57,692 --> 00:04:00,606
- Why? What are you doing?
- Can you keep your mouth shut?

46
00:04:06,825 --> 00:04:07,608
She's coming!

47
00:04:12,174 --> 00:04:13,523
What's going on?

48
00:04:14,436 --> 00:04:18,611
If you wanna be one of us,
just shut up and watch.

49
00:05:10,146 --> 00:05:13,016
- Who is she?
- The deaf guy's daughter, our new Latin teacher.

50
00:05:13,365 --> 00:05:16,582
- What's her name?
- What a wonderful ass!

51
00:06:19,686 --> 00:06:21,730
What I wouldn't give for an hour with her!

52
00:06:21,904 --> 00:06:25,818
- Too bad she's married.
- If she weren't...

53
00:06:26,427 --> 00:06:27,514
What's her name?

54
00:06:27,558 --> 00:06:31,646
Malèna, the most beautiful ass in Castelcuto.

55
00:06:37,909 --> 00:06:40,517
The sun is bigger than the moon.

56
00:06:44,476 --> 00:06:48,000
Or "Sol maior est quam lunam."

57
00:06:48,693 --> 00:06:51,043
Can I screw your daughter, you deaf old fart?

58
00:06:51,520 --> 00:06:52,782
Yes, but hurry.

59
00:06:53,869 --> 00:06:57,740
I love honesty more than wealth.

60
00:06:58,293 --> 00:07:03,006
"Magis diligo onestatem quam divitias."

61
00:07:03,173 --> 00:07:07,636
Or "Magis diligo onestatem divitiis."

62
00:07:40,620 --> 00:07:42,621
- Seven thumbs long!
- Seven and a half thumbs!

63
00:07:42,708 --> 00:07:44,839
- Mine's a bazooka!
- I got eight!

64
00:07:44,969 --> 00:07:48,883
Eight is nothing!
That's just tickling a woman.

65
00:07:48,884 --> 00:07:52,536
One, two... three and two is five,
two is seven and two is nine.

66
00:07:52,667 --> 00:07:54,102
Torpedo!

67
00:07:54,277 --> 00:07:57,320
My submarine will rip Malèna in half!

68
00:07:59,538 --> 00:08:01,495
Once I skipped school and went
by Malèna's house.

69
00:08:01,669 --> 00:08:05,714
She was at the window,
and she called out to me.

70
00:08:05,888 --> 00:08:09,889
I thought she wanted me
to get her some cigarettes.

71
00:08:10,410 --> 00:08:12,890
I went up for the money,
and her robe fell open.

72
00:08:13,194 --> 00:08:17,500
And there she was...
naked as the day she was born.

73
00:08:17,586 --> 00:08:19,500
Holy shit! She did it on purpose to excite me.

74
00:08:19,674 --> 00:08:24,414
I was an idiot.
I should have jumped at the chance.

75
00:08:24,415 --> 00:08:27,850
If it happens again,
I'll bang her brains out.

76
00:08:28,024 --> 00:08:31,677
She'd quit smoking first.
She knows you've got no balls.

77
00:08:31,678 --> 00:08:35,939
You little runt, you've been here for two hours...

78
00:08:36,244 --> 00:08:37,984
and you still haven't measured yourself.

79
00:08:38,287 --> 00:08:40,288
Measure it!

80
00:08:41,593 --> 00:08:43,203
One, two,

81
00:08:43,680 --> 00:08:46,551
three, four, five...

82
00:08:46,681 --> 00:08:48,029
Only six!

83
00:08:49,595 --> 00:08:51,900
You know what they say about a kid in short pants?

84
00:08:52,030 --> 00:08:53,857
Short pants: Short dick!

85
00:08:55,205 --> 00:08:56,814
Fuck off. My thumbs are twice as big as yours!

86
00:08:56,815 --> 00:08:58,032
Bullshit!

87
00:09:02,120 --> 00:09:04,643
- Who's got the biggest dick now, runt?
- You do!

88
00:09:04,903 --> 00:09:06,861
No, I am II Duce!
Nobody's bigger than me!

89
00:09:13,602 --> 00:09:15,732
- Ooh. Renato's skipping school. - Shh!

90
00:10:11,399 --> 00:10:15,053
You, come here! I need some cigarettes.

91
00:10:25,621 --> 00:10:27,186
What cigarettes do you want?

92
00:10:28,708 --> 00:10:30,274
Macedonia Extra.

93
00:10:48,930 --> 00:10:52,889
I remember this suit very well.
It's your father's.

94
00:10:53,149 --> 00:10:56,977
I sewed it 20 years ago,
and it still looks brand-new.

95
00:10:57,107 --> 00:11:01,021
He only wore it to his wedding.
He wants to keep it for his funeral.

96
00:11:01,108 --> 00:11:05,588
If he's buried in this suit,
he'll go straight to heaven!

97
00:11:05,674 --> 00:11:07,022
My father's still young.

98
00:11:07,066 --> 00:11:10,414
And you're too young for long pants.

99
00:11:10,589 --> 00:11:12,720
I didn't ask for your opinion, sir.

100
00:11:12,937 --> 00:11:15,198
- Does he know about this? - Of course he does!

101
00:11:15,807 --> 00:11:18,852
You little scoundrel, what the hell is this?

102
00:11:18,982 --> 00:11:23,939
Come here, mister.
So you want to skip school?

103
00:11:23,940 --> 00:11:26,419
Fine. Who didn't at your age?

104
00:11:27,723 --> 00:11:29,420
- Leave him alone!
- I know what I'm doing.

105
00:11:31,942 --> 00:11:35,552
And you let your friends beat you up.

106
00:11:35,682 --> 00:11:40,162
Even though when I was your age,
I'd beat my friends up!

107
00:11:40,597 --> 00:11:44,772
But stealing trousers from your father...

108
00:11:44,946 --> 00:11:49,165
and getting them altered for yourself
is just plain wrong.

109
00:11:49,295 --> 00:11:50,643
But, Papa, you don't understand!

110
00:11:51,034 --> 00:11:53,774
Understand? Who said you could speak?

111
00:11:54,122 --> 00:11:56,297
I'm ashamed to wear short pants!

112
00:11:56,427 --> 00:11:58,515
What about knickers? They're almost long pants!

113
00:11:58,645 --> 00:12:00,428
Enough! He's still a child!

114
00:12:00,558 --> 00:12:05,256
I'll tell our party secretary you won't let me go to the Fascist exercises!

115
00:12:11,214 --> 00:12:13,040
Let's make a deal.

116
00:12:14,127 --> 00:12:18,432
The day someone cracks the skull
of "Our Great Leader,"

117
00:12:19,868 --> 00:12:22,477
then you'll get long pants.

118
00:12:22,695 --> 00:12:23,869
Swear it.

119
00:15:00,476 --> 00:15:04,259
A beautiful young woman all alone here.
It's a crime.

120
00:15:05,477 --> 00:15:08,391
- Who's he talking about?
- Malèna Scordia, Nino's sexy new wife.

121
00:15:08,477 --> 00:15:11,478
She must have somebody on the side...
it's inevitable!

122
00:15:11,609 --> 00:15:13,610
- Number fifteen! - Me.

123
00:15:14,087 --> 00:15:17,306
Right. Nino brings her from her village
with her ailing father.

124
00:15:17,393 --> 00:15:21,437
And then a month later... boom...
Nino's called to the war.

125
00:15:21,525 --> 00:15:24,134
Who here wants to bet she's sleeping all alone?

126
00:15:24,264 --> 00:15:26,135
Not me!

127
00:15:29,353 --> 00:15:31,396
Why don't you let me sit with the others?

128
00:15:31,484 --> 00:15:35,528
You're too young to sit in the adult chair.

129
00:17:45,600 --> 00:17:47,300
♪ But love, no, ♪

130
00:17:47,400 --> 00:17:49,800
♪ My love cannot... ♪

131
00:17:49,900 --> 00:17:53,900
♪ ...dissolve itself in the wind with the roses. ♪

132
00:17:54,000 --> 00:18:00,800
♪ So strong that it will not surrender. ♪

133
00:18:03,300 --> 00:18:05,300
♪ I will watch over it, ♪

134
00:18:05,400 --> 00:18:07,500
♪ I will defend it... ♪

135
00:18:07,600 --> 00:18:11,500
♪ ...from all those poisoned hidden dangers... ♪

136
00:18:11,600 --> 00:18:15,300
♪ ...that would want to rip from the heart. ♪

137
00:18:15,500 --> 00:18:19,000
♪ Poor love! ♪

138
00:18:20,800 --> 00:18:22,700
♪ Maybe you will go, ♪

139
00:18:22,800 --> 00:18:26,500
♪ to look for other women's caress. ♪

140
00:18:26,900 --> 00:18:28,600
♪ Poor me! ♪

141
00:18:29,500 --> 00:18:31,100
♪ And if you come back... ♪

142
00:18:31,200 --> 00:18:37,600
♪ you will find every beauty already faded in me.♪

143
00:18:38,400 --> 00:18:40,100
♪ But love, no, ♪

144
00:18:40,200 --> 00:18:46,500
♪ My love cannot fade away like the gold in my hair. ♪

145
00:18:46,600 --> 00:18:50,000
♪ Until I die it will be alive in me. ♪

146
00:18:50,100 --> 00:18:52,200
♪ Only for you. ♪

147
00:18:52,363 --> 00:18:55,059
But, son, if you don't know the title,
how can I help you?

148
00:18:55,146 --> 00:18:57,364
It's that pretty, romantic one...

149
00:19:01,148 --> 00:19:04,191
Ma L'Amore No. Why didn't you say so?

150
00:19:07,715 --> 00:19:09,410
Ten lire. Pay at the cashier's.

151
00:19:09,584 --> 00:19:10,932
- Don't you test it?
- What for?

152
00:19:11,063 --> 00:19:14,107
- It might be defective.
- It's brand-new!

153
00:21:37,710 --> 00:21:40,972
<i>Miss Malèna, this heart of mine, on fire,
has written so many letters,</i>

154
00:21:41,102 --> 00:21:45,408
<i>and if I didn't have the courage to send them to you,</i>

155
00:21:45,582 --> 00:21:48,322
<i>it was only because I didn't want to do you harm.</i>

156
00:21:49,018 --> 00:21:52,541
<i>So forgive me if I dare to send you this one.</i>

157
00:21:52,584 --> 00:21:55,715
<i>I want you to know that this town has many gossips...</i>

158
00:21:55,803 --> 00:22:00,498
<i>who say bad things about you...
that you have a secret lover.</i>

159
00:22:00,499 --> 00:22:03,978
<i>I know it's not true.
You don't have anyone.</i>

160
00:22:04,065 --> 00:22:08,023
<i>After your husband,
the only man in your life is me.</i>

161
00:22:44,720 --> 00:22:47,640
I have to go.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.

162
00:22:47,860 --> 00:22:48,860
So long!

163
00:22:49,180 --> 00:22:50,860
Don't get lost!

164
00:24:15,960 --> 00:24:17,640
Mr. Lawyer! Your newspaper's upside down!

165
00:24:17,900 --> 00:24:20,000
Mind your own fucking business!

166
00:24:32,278 --> 00:24:36,627
Good morning, Signora Malèna.
Are you well? How is your father?

167
00:25:08,462 --> 00:25:12,593
The show's over! She's gone now!

168
00:26:08,304 --> 00:26:09,608
I forgot the key.

169
00:26:25,874 --> 00:26:28,831
So it's true what people say!

170
00:26:28,961 --> 00:26:31,092
What's the matter with you?
You look so strange.

171
00:26:31,267 --> 00:26:32,483
You've poisoned me with your lies.

172
00:26:32,614 --> 00:26:35,745
What lies? I've never spoken to you.

173
00:26:36,137 --> 00:26:41,312
I knew it from the start...
you're a loose woman.

174
00:26:41,530 --> 00:26:44,487
But I've never done anything wrong.

175
00:26:44,661 --> 00:26:47,618
Liar! I've been following you on my bicycle!

176
00:26:47,792 --> 00:26:50,010
- I know where you went. I know everything!
- No!

177
00:26:50,750 --> 00:26:53,358
- The lawyer, the dentist!
- No, Renato, I love only you!

178
00:26:53,576 --> 00:26:55,011
Liar!

179
00:26:59,795 --> 00:27:01,666
- Amoroso.
- Here!

180
00:27:01,796 --> 00:27:02,796
- Cali.
- Here!

181
00:27:03,449 --> 00:27:04,579
- Costanza.
- Here!

182
00:27:05,710 --> 00:27:08,624
Professor, can I put my dick between Malèna's tits?

183
00:27:08,754 --> 00:27:11,059
Can I put mine in her mouth?

184
00:27:11,190 --> 00:27:13,190
Can I put mine between her legs?

185
00:27:14,103 --> 00:27:15,974
Okay, but one at a time!

186
00:27:24,643 --> 00:27:26,520
Do you spit instead of oiling it?

187
00:27:26,603 --> 00:27:31,149
No. I use cooking oil.

188
00:27:31,275 --> 00:27:32,651
If you come, I will give it to you.

189
00:27:32,734 --> 00:27:35,904
Used machine needs oil, fool.
Or grease, which is better.

190
00:27:35,988 --> 00:27:38,782
Do you know grease?
Keep over the chain slippery!

191
00:27:49,591 --> 00:27:52,592
Why didn't she marry someone
from her own village?

192
00:27:52,679 --> 00:27:54,244
I'm sure no one wanted her.

193
00:28:00,333 --> 00:28:02,159
They say she's a seamstress.

194
00:28:02,290 --> 00:28:04,334
But she's so vulgar.

195
00:28:13,597 --> 00:28:15,468
My son says she looks fake.

196
00:28:15,642 --> 00:28:17,468
My husband says he wouldn't touch her
with a ten-foot pole.

197
00:28:17,555 --> 00:28:22,209
The Baron Bonta's mistress is much nicer.

198
00:28:22,600 --> 00:28:24,686
At least Gina does everything in the open.

199
00:28:24,687 --> 00:28:28,471
The baron screws her once a week
and then goes back to Palermo.

200
00:28:28,862 --> 00:28:32,428
Malèna acts so superior.
Like we don't know what she's up to.

201
00:28:32,559 --> 00:28:34,472
Wait and see. She'll get hers.

202
00:29:24,399 --> 00:29:27,791
The headquarters of the armed forces
communicates...

203
00:29:27,921 --> 00:29:30,487
Our brave and invincible
Fighting men have delivered a powerful blow...

204
00:29:30,618 --> 00:29:34,619
to the faceless war machine
unleashed by the Allies.

205
00:29:34,793 --> 00:29:38,968
In order to ensure the continued strength
and vitality...

206
00:29:39,142 --> 00:29:44,187
of our forces at the front,

207
00:29:44,361 --> 00:29:49,884
all payment of civic pensions...
will again be postponed...

208
00:29:57,190 --> 00:29:58,886
- It's ready. - Thank you.

209
00:31:11,119 --> 00:31:15,957
You will go blind!

210
00:31:24,561 --> 00:31:25,561
Malèna.

211
00:31:25,779 --> 00:31:27,909
Right rank! Eyes front!

212
00:31:28,039 --> 00:31:31,171
Arms out, arms high, in quick succession!

213
00:31:31,345 --> 00:31:34,606
One, two! One, two!

214
00:31:34,824 --> 00:31:39,348
Have you heard? Malèna's husband was killed.

215
00:31:39,478 --> 00:31:41,435
Malèna is available!

216
00:32:11,356 --> 00:32:13,748
Comrades of Castelcuto,

217
00:32:13,922 --> 00:32:16,399
we are gathered here today...

218
00:32:16,400 --> 00:32:20,749
to share in the tragic but honorable mourning...

219
00:32:20,923 --> 00:32:23,272
which has struck our town.

220
00:32:23,620 --> 00:32:26,837
To express our deepest condolences...

221
00:32:26,838 --> 00:32:29,578
for the loss of Lt. Nino Scordia...

222
00:32:29,882 --> 00:32:34,579
heroically killed in action...
in Northern Africa...

223
00:32:35,797 --> 00:32:37,928
and to his bride Maddalena,

224
00:32:38,145 --> 00:32:42,493
who, stricken with grief,
unfortunately isn't here with us.

225
00:32:42,494 --> 00:32:47,148
- She's already out looking!
- She'll need a warm bed now!

226
00:32:47,452 --> 00:32:51,541
But she is with us in spirit,
because Sicilian women...

227
00:32:51,932 --> 00:32:54,672
with their hardships, with their sacrifices,

228
00:32:54,845 --> 00:32:57,064
march shoulder to shoulder with Fighting men!

229
00:33:02,674 --> 00:33:06,761
Of our fellow citizen in defense
of his country was not a useless

230
00:33:07,023 --> 00:33:09,632
Lt. Cadei is so handsome.

231
00:33:11,981 --> 00:33:14,111
A lucky girl will catch him!

232
00:33:14,285 --> 00:33:17,634
That will carry us to the final victory of the Fascist Empire!

233
00:33:27,071 --> 00:33:28,898
For Victory!

234
00:33:28,941 --> 00:33:29,941
Long live II Duce!

235
00:34:55,659 --> 00:34:58,400
From now on I'll be at your side.

236
00:34:58,486 --> 00:35:01,183
Forever. I promise.

237
00:35:01,270 --> 00:35:03,531
Just give me time to grow up.

238
00:35:58,719 --> 00:36:00,372
Now she'll take a lover for sure.

239
00:36:00,460 --> 00:36:03,503
Once in the sack, there's no looking back!

240
00:36:03,591 --> 00:36:06,504
She knows that. She's 27 years old.

241
00:36:06,678 --> 00:36:08,636
She knows her way around the block!

242
00:36:08,766 --> 00:36:11,506
Cusimano, the dentist, has gone crazy for her.

243
00:36:11,593 --> 00:36:13,724
One day he was distracted as he walked by...

244
00:36:13,898 --> 00:36:17,855
and pulled a healthy tooth instead
of the rotten one!

245
00:36:18,769 --> 00:36:22,074
Dentist or not, why haven't we seen her lately?

246
00:36:22,204 --> 00:36:25,336
Guess she's too busy!

247
00:36:28,119 --> 00:36:31,423
They say she's fooling around with
a shopkeeper in Catania...

248
00:36:31,424 --> 00:36:32,946
with subversive tendencies.

249
00:36:33,033 --> 00:36:36,338
Some say Cusimano, the dentist.

250
00:36:36,469 --> 00:36:40,862
- A family man. It's disgraceful!
- When you're a born whore...

251
00:36:40,992 --> 00:36:45,820
I hear the priest has received anonymous letters...

252
00:36:45,993 --> 00:36:48,385
saying her lover is this man, that man.

253
00:36:48,559 --> 00:36:50,255
The voice of the people is the voice of God!

254
00:37:23,960 --> 00:37:26,742
I can't talk to anyone about my personal problems.

255
00:37:26,743 --> 00:37:28,744
They're too intimate.

256
00:37:28,787 --> 00:37:31,962
But you seem nice.
I'd like to confide in you.

257
00:37:32,092 --> 00:37:33,919
Every day, I'll light a candle for you.

258
00:37:40,051 --> 00:37:45,574
I'll even come to Mass on Sunday.

259
00:37:45,704 --> 00:37:49,880
But you must protect Malèna Scordia
from the town.

260
00:37:50,010 --> 00:37:53,663
Yes, the widow... at least for a few years.
Then I'll take over.

261
00:38:17,337 --> 00:38:19,839


262
00:38:45,894 --> 00:38:50,026
I am always at your service.

263
00:38:50,243 --> 00:38:52,244
- Renewed condolences, Malèna
- Condolences.

264
00:39:01,638 --> 00:39:03,899
What a piece of ass!

265
00:39:05,857 --> 00:39:06,900
Son of a bitch!

266
00:39:10,118 --> 00:39:11,206
You little runt! Come back here!

267
00:39:30,340 --> 00:39:34,255
- Can't you sing in Italian?
- Can't you speak German?

268
00:42:04,381 --> 00:42:06,468
Renato, It's late.

269
00:42:06,643 --> 00:42:08,818
Renato, get up.

270
00:42:17,210 --> 00:42:18,646
Monster!

271
00:42:18,820 --> 00:42:20,908
You're a fetishist,

272
00:42:21,038 --> 00:42:23,343
a sadomasochist, or even worse, a pervert!

273
00:42:25,560 --> 00:42:28,301
- What is that?
- It's just a French hat, Ma!

274
00:42:31,345 --> 00:42:32,389
Shame on you!

275
00:42:34,960 --> 00:42:37,860
- Can I keep them?
- You shameless girl.

276
00:42:38,912 --> 00:42:43,174
What are you looking at? Get out of here!

277
00:42:43,304 --> 00:42:45,001
Come here, you little pig!

278
00:42:46,435 --> 00:42:48,350
- Goddamn pervert!
- What did I do?

279
00:42:50,263 --> 00:42:54,873
You're not permitted to sit
at the table with us, understand?

280
00:42:55,352 --> 00:42:57,569
- Answer me!
- Okay!

281
00:43:00,918 --> 00:43:04,702
You no longer have the right to speak
to your sisters, understand?

282
00:43:04,788 --> 00:43:08,398
Lock me up! I'll show you!

283
00:43:09,311 --> 00:43:12,529
You're not to leave this room until further notice!

284
00:43:13,269 --> 00:43:17,357
Son, at least have some soup.
It will do you good.

285
00:43:17,748 --> 00:43:20,532
Pietro, he hasn't eaten for three days.

286
00:43:20,662 --> 00:43:24,446
In the Soviet Union, they never eat.

287
00:43:25,533 --> 00:43:26,664
Still... What is this shit?

288
00:43:26,795 --> 00:43:30,926
The Fascists gave it to us.
At least it looks like coffee.

289
00:43:31,100 --> 00:43:32,883
Sure, and I look like Vittorio De Sica.

290
00:43:33,057 --> 00:43:35,883
Everything they give us is terrible!

291
00:43:35,884 --> 00:43:39,059
Look at these pockets. They're always ripping open!

292
00:43:39,232 --> 00:43:41,624
This cheap thread doesn't hold the stitches!

293
00:43:41,754 --> 00:43:43,669
The thread isn't the problem!

294
00:43:43,711 --> 00:43:46,973
While our son recites poetry, his hands go to work in his pockets!

295
00:43:47,017 --> 00:43:49,931
What does that mean?

296
00:43:50,671 --> 00:43:52,628
Do you get it now?

297
00:43:53,105 --> 00:43:55,759
Just as well! Don't fix them.
Sew the pockets closed!

298
00:43:55,932 --> 00:43:58,845
But he'll have no pockets.

299
00:43:58,846 --> 00:44:01,455
He'll work it out. It will be good for his health!

300
00:44:03,108 --> 00:44:05,848
Lights out!

301
00:44:06,327 --> 00:44:11,502
That the weary spirit may never repose in more restful harbor...

302
00:44:11,676 --> 00:44:14,763
- Has he gone crazy?
- I think he's gone blind.

303
00:44:20,852 --> 00:44:23,780
While upon womens work you sat intent,

304
00:44:23,896 --> 00:44:27,000
content with the vague future you held in mind...

305
00:44:27,114 --> 00:44:31,600
was the scented May, and thus you used to spend your days.

306
00:44:31,898 --> 00:44:34,420
This child needs air.

307
00:44:34,421 --> 00:44:36,638
- Air?
- Air.

308
00:45:05,733 --> 00:45:07,169
Good morning, Professor.

309
00:45:20,259 --> 00:45:22,347
This letter is for you.

310
00:45:23,608 --> 00:45:25,869
It says "urgent."

311
00:45:35,950 --> 00:45:40,000
You're dishonored. Your daughter Malèna
is sleeping with the whole town.

312
00:45:59,531 --> 00:46:01,574
It was an anonymous letter,
but I read it!

313
00:46:01,661 --> 00:46:04,357
It says Malèna is a whore with everyone in town!

314
00:46:04,531 --> 00:46:06,793
So there's hope for us too!

315
00:46:08,794 --> 00:46:10,446
Take it back!

316
00:46:10,533 --> 00:46:14,143
I'll bust your ass, Mr. Short Pants!

317
00:46:56,024 --> 00:46:57,589
Tonight was wonderful.

318
00:46:59,067 --> 00:47:03,069
- For me too.
- I know it's been only ten months since.

319
00:47:03,242 --> 00:47:07,026
- But maybe I can see you again.
- All right. You win.

320
00:47:07,157 --> 00:47:10,462
- Tomorrow.
- Okay, as long as I'm not on duty.

321
00:47:10,636 --> 00:47:12,201
- Thanks for the flowers.
- You're welcome.

322
00:47:25,118 --> 00:47:26,858
Take care of yourself.

323
00:47:34,208 --> 00:47:37,642
So see you tomorrow?

324
00:47:37,643 --> 00:47:38,774
Yes.

325
00:47:40,426 --> 00:47:42,514
- Until then.
- Good night, Leone.

326
00:47:44,862 --> 00:47:46,907
What time?

327
00:47:49,125 --> 00:47:51,777
- Good evening, sir.
- Good evening, my ass!

328
00:47:51,908 --> 00:47:56,169
How dare you pester my fiancee!

329
00:47:56,301 --> 00:47:59,432
There must be a misunderstanding.
I was invited.

330
00:47:59,562 --> 00:48:01,606
You're a liar and a bastard!

331
00:48:02,259 --> 00:48:05,128
Because I'm in uniform, I can not retaliate, sir.

332
00:48:05,259 --> 00:48:08,391
- But you will answer to me.
- Anytime.

333
00:48:09,782 --> 00:48:14,609
- Coward, scoundrel!
- Get up.

334
00:48:14,740 --> 00:48:16,783
Come here! I'll tear you apart, you coward!

335
00:48:16,958 --> 00:48:20,045
I'll break you in two!

336
00:48:21,351 --> 00:48:24,351
Let me go! Or I'll have to get tough with you!

337
00:48:26,830 --> 00:48:30,831
- Here's the adulterer!
- My wife!

338
00:48:30,917 --> 00:48:34,180
- Officer, look! He's cheating on me!
- With a man?

339
00:48:34,397 --> 00:48:37,572
With a traitor!

340
00:48:37,616 --> 00:48:40,225
You said you wouldn't touch her with a ten-foot pole!

341
00:48:40,399 --> 00:48:41,355
It's the dentist.

342
00:48:44,443 --> 00:48:47,052
I've been spying on you a long time,
you bastard!

343
00:48:47,270 --> 00:48:49,444
And as for you,

344
00:48:49,575 --> 00:48:53,010
go steal husbands from your own village, you whore!

345
00:49:04,319 --> 00:49:06,884
We knew she had one lover, but two?

346
00:49:07,058 --> 00:49:10,059
But where does the dentist fit in?

347
00:49:10,145 --> 00:49:11,537
He fits in between her legs!

348
00:49:11,625 --> 00:49:15,626
Her father was forced to quit the school in disgrace.

349
00:49:15,756 --> 00:49:18,627
He never wants to see his daughter Malèna again.

350
00:49:18,757 --> 00:49:21,975
And the dentist's wife kicked him out of his house.

351
00:49:22,062 --> 00:49:27,627
That dragon of a wife will drag him into court!

352
00:49:27,628 --> 00:49:30,934
What's the dentist got to do with it, poor guy?

353
00:49:31,064 --> 00:49:34,283
Malèna's the whore!
She should be taken to court!

354
00:49:34,456 --> 00:49:37,283
That Lt. Cadei seemed like such a gentleman.

355
00:49:37,370 --> 00:49:39,632
How could he get mixed up in this?

356
00:49:39,762 --> 00:49:43,154
Everyone knows she's a home wrecker.

357
00:49:43,285 --> 00:49:45,460
The lieutenant was asking for it!

358
00:49:45,546 --> 00:49:48,677
- She's not from here. She forgets where she is.
- Will they go to court?

359
00:49:48,808 --> 00:49:54,765
Of course, she could go to jail.
He's a married man!

360
00:49:54,766 --> 00:49:59,333
The dentist needed three stitches in his head.

361
00:49:59,506 --> 00:50:02,899
But the dentist swore at the soldier first.

362
00:50:02,986 --> 00:50:05,029
That's insulting an officer.

363
00:50:05,291 --> 00:50:07,421
We'll all end up in court!

364
00:50:07,813 --> 00:50:10,509
While we were watching her caboose,

365
00:50:10,510 --> 00:50:13,858
the lieutenant and the dentist were riding the train!

366
00:51:25,225 --> 00:51:27,008
She's either going to the lawyer's or the notary's.

367
00:51:27,138 --> 00:51:30,009
Sure, but what will she do with two old men like them?

368
00:51:31,922 --> 00:51:33,966
- Excuse me.
- Come in.

369
00:51:35,663 --> 00:51:36,923
Can I help you?

370
00:51:37,011 --> 00:51:39,707
May I speak to Lawyer Centorbi?

371
00:51:40,185 --> 00:51:41,621
Please have a seat.

372
00:51:44,664 --> 00:51:46,970
Sir, it's the widow Scordia!

373
00:51:47,100 --> 00:51:51,014
Can it be true? Beautiful Madonna!

374
00:52:02,191 --> 00:52:03,539
Have her come in.

375
00:52:04,191 --> 00:52:05,627
- Go in.
- Thank you.

376
00:52:06,627 --> 00:52:08,628
Please sit down.

377
00:52:09,019 --> 00:52:10,584
Charmed.

378
00:52:16,021 --> 00:52:19,846
We now continue with the testimony of Maddalena Bonsignore,

379
00:52:19,847 --> 00:52:23,153
the widow Scordia called Malèna.

380
00:52:24,719 --> 00:52:26,589
She could get two years in prison.

381
00:52:28,850 --> 00:52:31,024
Everything will be fine, trust me.

382
00:52:38,114 --> 00:52:39,288
Sit down.

383
00:52:47,638 --> 00:52:51,552
You're accused of involving Dr. Gaspare Cusimano...

384
00:52:51,682 --> 00:52:55,466
in a secret and amorous relationship...

385
00:52:55,553 --> 00:52:57,771
aimed at the breaking up of his family.

386
00:52:57,945 --> 00:53:00,815
Do you know Dr. Cusimano?

387
00:53:02,120 --> 00:53:02,989
Yes.

388
00:53:03,164 --> 00:53:07,991
Are you or have you ever...
been his fiancee?

389
00:53:08,295 --> 00:53:10,556
Absolutely not.

390
00:53:10,731 --> 00:53:13,210
How could I be engaged to a married man?

391
00:53:13,297 --> 00:53:17,037
Why was Cusimano, at that unusual hour...

392
00:53:17,123 --> 00:53:19,168
on his way to your house?

393
00:53:19,255 --> 00:53:20,385
I don't know.

394
00:53:20,603 --> 00:53:24,691
Had he been in your company
on previous evenings?

395
00:53:40,869 --> 00:53:42,566
Yes, once.

396
00:53:47,871 --> 00:53:50,219
- Where? - At my house.

397
00:53:57,439 --> 00:54:00,091
Jumped right in, the dentist did. He looks stupid, but...

398
00:54:00,266 --> 00:54:05,745
- How long did he stay? - Not long.

399
00:54:05,919 --> 00:54:06,919
What did you do?

400
00:54:08,920 --> 00:54:11,486
He brought me some medicine for my father.

401
00:54:13,616 --> 00:54:17,400
If it was for your father, why did he bring it to you?

402
00:54:17,879 --> 00:54:18,835
I don't know.

403
00:54:20,183 --> 00:54:24,098
What did you do after he gave you the medicine?

404
00:54:24,228 --> 00:54:26,403
He said good-bye and left.

405
00:54:30,752 --> 00:54:34,753
Then why has Cusimano,
are put able professional,

406
00:54:34,927 --> 00:54:36,752
who, five years ago...

407
00:54:36,753 --> 00:54:40,798
had the honor of extracting one of II Duce's teeth...

408
00:54:40,928 --> 00:54:43,103
publicly declare that he is your fiance?

409
00:54:43,277 --> 00:54:47,669
He made that up. I had nothing to do with it.

410
00:54:47,930 --> 00:54:49,583
Your husband's crazy.

411
00:54:49,800 --> 00:54:54,627
What kind of relationship did you
have with Lt. Cadei?

412
00:54:57,455 --> 00:55:02,717
I'm a widow. My business and that of Lt. Cadei...

413
00:55:02,847 --> 00:55:05,022
are no concern of the law.

414
00:55:07,022 --> 00:55:10,719
All right. Did you know that,

415
00:55:11,110 --> 00:55:14,763
as a result of these affairs,
Lt. Cadei was transferred to Albania?

416
00:55:14,851 --> 00:55:15,502
One down.

417
00:55:15,720 --> 00:55:19,417
And before his departure,
he was questioned in judicial inquiry.

418
00:55:19,895 --> 00:55:20,678
Clerk.

419
00:55:20,852 --> 00:55:23,287
He declared to have encountered

420
00:55:23,417 --> 00:55:27,810
the widow Scordia only twice...
in her home,

421
00:55:27,897 --> 00:55:32,290
and to have had no amorous relationship...

422
00:55:32,420 --> 00:55:36,813
considering their relationship "just a casual friendship."

423
00:55:40,596 --> 00:55:41,814
Son of a bitch.

424
00:55:41,944 --> 00:55:45,989
Lt. Cadei was received by my client...

425
00:55:46,119 --> 00:55:50,686
and she makes no secret about having had for him...

426
00:55:50,859 --> 00:55:53,382
certain feelings.

427
00:55:53,469 --> 00:55:56,992
But unlike the married Cusimano,

428
00:55:57,384 --> 00:56:02,124
who was, let's face it, guilty...

429
00:56:02,341 --> 00:56:04,994
of a pre-senile dimming of the senses...

430
00:56:05,734 --> 00:56:08,038
of an intoxicating kaleidoscope of desires...

431
00:56:08,082 --> 00:56:13,649
Unlike the family man Cusimano, But...

432
00:56:13,735 --> 00:56:15,867
Cadei is...

433
00:56:16,084 --> 00:56:20,085
and was...

434
00:56:20,346 --> 00:56:21,564
a bachelor... a bachelor!

435
00:56:21,737 --> 00:56:23,738
Clever, that lawyer.

436
00:56:24,260 --> 00:56:25,782
He's a bachelor himself.

437
00:56:26,347 --> 00:56:31,131
Careful investigation of the facts tell us, therefore...

438
00:56:31,393 --> 00:56:34,567
that the Scordia woman committed no other crime...

439
00:56:34,697 --> 00:56:37,307
than that of being ill-fated,

440
00:56:37,568 --> 00:56:41,221
alone and beautiful.

441
00:56:41,568 --> 00:56:44,900
Here is her crime: Her beauty!

442
00:56:45,000 --> 00:56:46,800
And from here, the envy,

443
00:56:46,900 --> 00:56:48,000
the lies, the disgrace,

444
00:56:48,093 --> 00:56:51,223
that have deprived her even of a father's trust!

445
00:56:51,224 --> 00:56:55,877
And yet, she herself is still in silent agony...

446
00:56:56,747 --> 00:56:59,747
mourning over that unmarked war grave...

447
00:57:00,704 --> 00:57:06,097
in faraway East Africa.

448
00:57:07,141 --> 00:57:10,489
In the beating heart of our argument...

449
00:57:10,663 --> 00:57:15,273
is an audacious, but nonetheless valid, thesis...

450
00:57:15,577 --> 00:57:17,490
which asks just one question:

451
00:57:17,491 --> 00:57:19,666
Can a young woman...

452
00:57:19,753 --> 00:57:24,623
after the odyssey of a widowhood endured for the love of country...

453
00:57:24,624 --> 00:57:29,886
hope for protection in the shelter of a new life?

454
00:57:30,016 --> 00:57:33,365
Does she have the right to yearn for, and to write...

455
00:57:33,539 --> 00:57:36,627
a new ending to her own love story?

456
00:57:37,454 --> 00:57:39,411
Your Honor,

457
00:57:39,584 --> 00:57:41,802
the citizens of Castelcuto reply: "Yes!"

458
00:57:53,240 --> 00:57:55,502
Will Cusimano leave me alone now?

459
00:57:55,675 --> 00:58:00,416
Of course. He's been put into a psychiatric clinic.

460
00:58:00,633 --> 00:58:03,634
He wants to volunteer for the Forces in East Africa.

461
00:58:04,287 --> 00:58:08,592
He doesn't realize we lost Africa ages ago!

462
00:58:08,679 --> 00:58:12,637
But let's forget Cusimano
and the fickle Lt. Cadei.

463
00:58:12,941 --> 00:58:15,029
Let's get to us!

464
00:58:18,030 --> 00:58:21,117
I know it's not much.

465
00:58:21,204 --> 00:58:24,857
But it's all I have. They've cut my pension.

466
00:58:25,248 --> 00:58:27,292
Don't you understand?

467
00:58:27,466 --> 00:58:30,076
That's peanuts!

468
00:58:30,685 --> 00:58:32,947
My fee is much more than that.

469
00:58:33,250 --> 00:58:36,904
You'll never have enough money!

470
00:58:36,990 --> 00:58:40,035
But how will I ever repay you?

471
00:58:40,121 --> 00:58:43,036
It's very easy, my sweet.

472
00:58:43,122 --> 00:58:47,471
- What are you saying?
- Be with me, my love!

473
00:58:47,732 --> 00:58:49,385
I'm in love with you!

474
00:58:54,691 --> 00:58:56,735
A woman shouldn't be alone during these hard times.

475
00:58:57,518 --> 00:59:00,127
I am a wealthy man.
You won't find better.

476
00:59:02,823 --> 00:59:05,085
I'll take care of your father. You'll never have to worry again.

477
00:59:29,352 --> 00:59:33,831
I forgive her. She did it to pay her lawyer's fees

478
00:59:33,919 --> 00:59:35,528
only once and never again.

479
00:59:35,614 --> 00:59:37,832
But you didn't keep our agreement.

480
00:59:39,789 --> 00:59:41,530
Now we're even.

481
01:01:52,477 --> 01:01:55,434
<i>Signora Malèna, a more capable person than me...</i>

482
01:01:55,609 --> 01:01:59,392
<i>wrote that the only truelove is unrequited love.</i>

483
01:01:59,479 --> 01:02:01,262
<i>Now I understand why.</i>

484
01:02:01,567 --> 01:02:04,480
<i>It's been so long since you last came out of your house.</i>

485
01:02:04,654 --> 01:02:08,176
<i>But the longer we are apart,
the stronger my love becomes.</i>

486
01:02:08,699 --> 01:02:12,874
<i>They say you're about to marry Centorbi, the lawyer.</i>

487
01:02:13,004 --> 01:02:15,048
<i>I know how badly they treat you here,</i>

488
01:02:15,135 --> 01:02:18,614
<i>how the women in the market won't sell you any good food...</i>

489
01:02:18,788 --> 01:02:21,136
<i>and no man would hire you for fear of his wife.</i>

490
01:02:21,267 --> 01:02:25,529
<i>But how will you manage to live with a fat, old man...</i>

491
01:02:25,746 --> 01:02:28,835
<i>so ugly that no girl ever wanted him?</i>

492
01:02:29,095 --> 01:02:33,879
<i>They say he never washes and stinks like a goat.</i>

493
01:02:34,140 --> 01:02:37,097
<i>How will your smooth, white skin... bear rubbing against</i>

494
01:02:37,227 --> 01:02:39,272
<i>the sweat of an old man...</i>

495
01:02:39,533 --> 01:02:43,273
<i>who never does anything without
his mother's consent?</i>

496
01:03:09,236 --> 01:03:11,410
Is it true you're getting married?

497
01:03:12,368 --> 01:03:14,760
What are you writing?

498
01:03:14,846 --> 01:03:17,891
Give me that! Let me see!

499
01:03:18,456 --> 01:03:20,021
Get out!

500
01:03:42,985 --> 01:03:44,941
Stand up straight.

501
01:03:45,072 --> 01:03:47,116
A little longer, Don Placido.

502
01:03:47,202 --> 01:03:51,203
More room in the waist,
for when he gets bigger.

503
01:03:51,335 --> 01:03:52,465
Will they be ready tomorrow?

504
01:03:52,552 --> 01:03:56,336
The war has ruined my business, but it still takes time.

505
01:03:56,553 --> 01:03:58,728
As Allied bombings continue.

506
01:04:05,773 --> 01:04:06,729
Wait for me.

507
01:04:10,035 --> 01:04:12,992
Lord, help me with my mother, I beg you.

508
01:04:19,212 --> 01:04:21,386
Moron! Idiot!

509
01:04:21,604 --> 01:04:22,734
Idiot!

510
01:04:22,908 --> 01:04:24,908
You can't treat me like a child. I'm a grown man!

511
01:04:25,256 --> 01:04:26,822
Get this straight. Your father's good name...

512
01:04:26,909 --> 01:04:31,214
will never belong to that disgusting whore!

513
01:04:31,302 --> 01:04:33,606
Never! Never!

514
01:04:33,693 --> 01:04:37,911
Never!

515
01:05:02,222 --> 01:05:04,136
The lawyer was left high and dry!

516
01:05:04,223 --> 01:05:07,702
His mother still bathes him every Saturday!

517
01:05:08,224 --> 01:05:11,137
Malèna always has someone throwing
a wrench in the works!

518
01:05:11,269 --> 01:05:14,921
It won't be hard finding someone to replace the lawyer!

519
01:05:15,226 --> 01:05:20,663
- Come on, sit down.
- The next in line already has a plan.

520
01:05:20,749 --> 01:05:23,185
Yeah, his plan is in his pants.

521
01:05:24,011 --> 01:05:26,272
- A cut and shave.
- Right away, sir.

522
01:06:51,686 --> 01:06:52,730
Good morning, Antonio.

523
01:06:53,643 --> 01:06:55,687
I brought some sugar and flour.

524
01:06:55,861 --> 01:06:58,036
- What about the bread?
- The best.

525
01:07:02,863 --> 01:07:06,082
- I can't pay right now.
- That's no problem.

526
01:07:06,168 --> 01:07:09,256
I'm sure we can find a way to make you some money.

527
01:08:16,099 --> 01:08:18,622
Hurry, there's someone else over here!

528
01:08:40,236 --> 01:08:42,324
It's Professor Bonsignore.

529
01:08:43,585 --> 01:08:45,629
Malèna's father.

530
01:09:51,429 --> 01:09:53,126
I'm here for you.

531
01:09:56,126 --> 01:09:57,822
Condolences, Signora Scordia.

532
01:10:00,040 --> 01:10:02,084
Condolences.

533
01:10:06,911 --> 01:10:08,737
Step aside, kid.

534
01:10:08,738 --> 01:10:11,434
Signora, what can we do?
We're in the Lord's hands.

535
01:10:11,435 --> 01:10:12,478
Don't forget my offer.

536
01:12:59,174 --> 01:13:01,522
- Who is it?
- It's me.

537
01:13:01,740 --> 01:13:03,219
- Me who?
- Salvatore. Antonio sent me.

538
01:13:03,305 --> 01:13:06,046
I brought you some more food.

539
01:13:07,306 --> 01:13:08,524
Come in.

540
01:13:23,137 --> 01:13:25,486
- Your hair looks terrific.
- Do you like it?

541
01:13:25,616 --> 01:13:29,487
- Yes, it makes you look younger.
- Thank you.

542
01:13:44,186 --> 01:13:46,057
I can come every Thursday!

543
01:13:46,273 --> 01:13:47,882
As long as you bring the food.

544
01:14:21,761 --> 01:14:25,545
Never before in our history have we been
called upon to band together.

545
01:14:25,632 --> 01:14:28,546
Just a few years ago, Il Duce promised

546
01:14:28,676 --> 01:14:32,285
that the Nazis would never occupy Sicily.

547
01:14:32,286 --> 01:14:34,156
Look! The Germans are everywhere!

548
01:14:35,460 --> 01:14:37,331
Look who's here.

549
01:15:00,075 --> 01:15:01,511
She's a redhead now.

550
01:15:02,293 --> 01:15:04,381
Look how she's put together.

551
01:15:04,555 --> 01:15:06,816
I'd like to cut off that hair.

552
01:15:18,689 --> 01:15:20,167
How disgusting!

553
01:17:12,894 --> 01:17:14,677
Now she's even screwing the Germans.

554
01:17:14,850 --> 01:17:18,763
- Who's that?
- Malèna Scordia, the slut.

555
01:17:18,764 --> 01:17:21,983
She's teamed up with that other whore, Gina.

556
01:17:22,156 --> 01:17:24,896
But with the Germans?

557
01:17:25,114 --> 01:17:28,506
Seems there are gymnastics
at the Moderno Hotel.

558
01:17:29,071 --> 01:17:31,811
The two whores run from room to room...

559
01:17:32,333 --> 01:17:35,682
servicing a dozen officers at a time.

560
01:17:35,856 --> 01:17:37,639
Holy shit!

561
01:18:09,082 --> 01:18:12,300
My good woman,
this child is possessed by the devil!

562
01:18:13,518 --> 01:18:14,648
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!

563
01:18:23,911 --> 01:18:24,651
Rosa!

564
01:18:28,086 --> 01:18:29,565
Come here!

565
01:18:31,087 --> 01:18:32,784
That's enough!

566
01:18:33,132 --> 01:18:36,089
It looks like you're posing for
Michelangelo's Pieta of the poor!

567
01:18:36,698 --> 01:18:37,437
No.

568
01:18:38,220 --> 01:18:41,308
Evil eye on blood is fed.
Hold on fast till death is past.

569
01:18:41,482 --> 01:18:44,744
Exorcise the devil from this child.

570
01:18:44,918 --> 01:18:46,657
Goat red, on wood fed, hold on fast.

571
01:18:46,787 --> 01:18:49,354
Head and tail, evil eye release this child.

572
01:18:49,745 --> 01:18:51,876
Cast the devil into the wild.

573
01:18:53,137 --> 01:18:54,572
Shameful!

574
01:18:54,703 --> 01:18:58,269
Disgraceful!

575
01:18:58,355 --> 01:19:03,357
They cured my uncle this way... and he had cholera!

576
01:19:03,444 --> 01:19:06,228
Your son's not sick! He's becoming a man!

577
01:19:06,314 --> 01:19:09,532
With a dick this big, he needs to fuck!

578
01:19:18,839 --> 01:19:19,970
Renato!

579
01:19:26,494 --> 01:19:28,407
Renato, wait here for me.

580
01:19:35,930 --> 01:19:38,714
Come here. Come on.
Close the door.

581
01:19:38,889 --> 01:19:41,280
- My father?
- He's coming.

582
01:19:41,888 --> 01:19:44,106
Ladies!

583
01:19:44,107 --> 01:19:45,977
Choose the one you like.

584
01:19:46,107 --> 01:19:49,152
Ladies!

585
01:19:49,238 --> 01:19:51,109
What do we have here?

586
01:19:51,239 --> 01:19:53,197
Fresh young meat.

587
01:20:59,562 --> 01:21:01,866
Lupetta, up to the room.

588
01:21:05,258 --> 01:21:06,650
Treat him right.

589
01:21:14,914 --> 01:21:17,218
- What's your name?
- Amoroso Renato.

590
01:21:17,306 --> 01:21:19,263
Amoroso. What a romantic name!

591
01:21:19,480 --> 01:21:23,959
Tonight we either die in a bombing
or end up in jail.

592
01:21:28,657 --> 01:21:29,831
Go ahead.

593
01:23:14,553 --> 01:23:17,163
- Is it your first time?
- No.

594
01:23:18,946 --> 01:23:20,903
I've imagined it many times.

595
01:24:42,490 --> 01:24:46,056
Let's go give that shameless whore
what she deserves.

596
01:24:51,275 --> 01:24:54,058
Stay back. This is between the women.

597
01:26:22,995 --> 01:26:26,126
Now you'll see what happens when you steal our men...

598
01:26:36,563 --> 01:26:38,738
and sleep with the filthy Germans.

599
01:26:41,478 --> 01:26:43,391
It's the end of spreading your legs, whore!

600
01:27:00,744 --> 01:27:02,439
Now let's see what men make of you!

601
01:27:08,746 --> 01:27:11,138
The madame is served.

602
01:28:20,504 --> 01:28:21,765
Get lost!

603
01:28:22,678 --> 01:28:24,765
Disappear!

604
01:32:19,045 --> 01:32:21,871
- I know that face.
- Who is it?

605
01:32:24,698 --> 01:32:27,047
Nino Scordia, Malèna's husband.

606
01:32:27,264 --> 01:32:30,439
Malèna, the one who did it with the Germans.

607
01:32:36,658 --> 01:32:40,616
Poor guy. He was better off dead.

608
01:32:47,095 --> 01:32:48,748
Isn't that Malèna's husband?

609
01:33:15,842 --> 01:33:19,147
Hey, Giovanni, there's a strange guy.

610
01:33:28,498 --> 01:33:30,107
Do you know Malèna Scordia?

611
01:33:30,933 --> 01:33:32,064
Who's she?

612
01:33:32,237 --> 01:33:34,672
Who are you? This is my family's house!

613
01:33:34,673 --> 01:33:36,587
We don't know anything.

614
01:33:36,761 --> 01:33:39,413
When we came, no one was living here.

615
01:33:39,545 --> 01:33:41,066
No one?

616
01:33:56,506 --> 01:33:59,202
Poor guy. No one will tell him the truth.

617
01:33:59,288 --> 01:34:03,203
What would you say,
"I hear your wife is a prostitute"?

618
01:34:03,289 --> 01:34:06,986
I hear she's still a great piece of ass.

619
01:34:07,160 --> 01:34:10,553
I lost an arm. I wasn't dead!

620
01:34:10,683 --> 01:34:15,075
Then I was taken prisoner in India
and I contracted malaria. Tell him.

621
01:34:15,249 --> 01:34:17,728
Sir, he lost his arm...

622
01:34:17,902 --> 01:34:20,164
Hey, kid, what are you doing here?
Go away.

623
01:34:20,772 --> 01:34:22,034
Me "boy-bar." Coffee.

624
01:34:22,207 --> 01:34:26,077
I have to get the coffee cups. Understand?

625
01:34:26,078 --> 01:34:27,253
Okay, alright.

626
01:34:28,297 --> 01:34:31,297
My family has lived in this town
for generations.

627
01:34:31,471 --> 01:34:33,602
Now no one will talk to me.

628
01:34:33,689 --> 01:34:35,168
My house is a refugee camp,
and my wife has disappeared.

629
01:34:35,255 --> 01:34:38,256
No one in town knows where she is.

630
01:34:39,690 --> 01:34:42,256
His wife was the woman

631
01:34:42,300 --> 01:34:44,997
we saw beaten up on the day we arrived here.

632
01:34:45,170 --> 01:34:47,954
Everybody says she's a prostitute in a whorehouse.

633
01:34:48,171 --> 01:34:50,346
Help me find her. I want to bring her home.

634
01:35:13,351 --> 01:35:18,223
Excuse me. Don't you remember me? I'm Nino Scordia.

635
01:35:18,440 --> 01:35:22,180
- You mistake me for someone else.
- Could I have a light?

636
01:35:22,310 --> 01:35:26,573
You were the Fascist secretary, and you were his deputy.

637
01:35:27,268 --> 01:35:28,530
You can help me. Do you know what happened to my wife?

638
01:35:28,704 --> 01:35:31,008
Didn't she join the Communist Party?

639
01:35:32,617 --> 01:35:36,749
She was photographed with her arms
around the Commie leader.

640
01:35:39,445 --> 01:35:42,011
You're a family of heroes!

641
01:35:44,056 --> 01:35:45,708
You're right.

642
01:35:46,230 --> 01:35:50,318
Those who fought the war for you
bastards aren't heroes.

643
01:35:51,709 --> 01:35:54,798
Go take a walk through the brothels of Sicily.

644
01:35:54,971 --> 01:35:58,537
You may find your wife there!

645
01:36:59,118 --> 01:37:03,033
Wait a minute. Come back!

646
01:37:09,209 --> 01:37:10,861
<i>Dear Signor Scordia,</i>

647
01:37:10,992 --> 01:37:14,862
<i>forgive me if I don't have the courage
to speak man to man.</i>

648
01:37:15,167 --> 01:37:20,211
<i>These last months have taught me much about courage,
even if I have found little myself.</i>

649
01:37:20,559 --> 01:37:23,343
<i>I'm the only one who knows
the truth about your wife.</i>

650
01:37:23,517 --> 01:37:27,778
<i>Around here, they only say
bad things about her.</i>

651
01:37:27,996 --> 01:37:31,997
<i>But believe me,
your wife Malèna was faithful to you.</i>

652
01:37:32,127 --> 01:37:35,911
<i>You are the only man she loved.
This is the honest truth.</i>

653
01:37:36,302 --> 01:37:38,910
<i>It is true, a lot of things happened,</i>

654
01:37:38,911 --> 01:37:42,304
<i>but back then, you had been dead along time.</i>

655
01:37:42,609 --> 01:37:47,349
<i>The last time I saw her, she was on a train for Messina.</i>

656
01:37:47,653 --> 01:37:51,828
<i>I should sign "a friend," like all anonymous letters,</i>

657
01:37:52,002 --> 01:37:53,872
<i>but my name is Renato.</i>

658
01:38:26,240 --> 01:38:28,720
{\an8}One Year Later

659
01:38:33,318 --> 01:38:36,057
Good morning, Judge.

660
01:38:38,058 --> 01:38:39,536
All is well, thank God.

661
01:38:41,580 --> 01:38:43,103
Eat up, my sweet pea.

662
01:38:56,585 --> 01:38:58,585
- Sons of bitches! - Look who's here!

663
01:38:59,542 --> 01:39:01,499
Giorgio, look who's here!

664
01:40:03,255 --> 01:40:06,038
Why are you all looking at that woman?

665
01:40:06,168 --> 01:40:07,646
It's nothing.

666
01:40:35,828 --> 01:40:38,655
I saw them in the square. They were walking arm in arm.

667
01:40:38,742 --> 01:40:40,786
Quiet. She's here!

668
01:40:42,221 --> 01:40:45,309
It took a lot of courage to come back.

669
01:40:46,179 --> 01:40:47,788
Look who's here.

670
01:40:50,180 --> 01:40:51,963
I heard it, but I didn't believe it.

671
01:40:52,049 --> 01:40:54,964
- What have they got to look at?
- They should leave her in peace.

672
01:40:57,921 --> 01:41:00,443
She's got some wrinkles around her eyes.

673
01:41:00,573 --> 01:41:02,226
She's put on weight, too.

674
01:41:04,792 --> 01:41:06,662
But she's still beautiful.

675
01:41:07,054 --> 01:41:09,184
Good morning, Mrs. Scordia.

676
01:41:25,275 --> 01:41:26,537
Good morning.

677
01:41:28,755 --> 01:41:31,886
Want some nice tomatoes?
They cost less over there.

678
01:41:31,973 --> 01:41:34,365
- Good morning.
- Thank you.

679
01:41:37,453 --> 01:41:39,453
Nice things here!

680
01:41:40,280 --> 01:41:43,193
- Like it, Signora Malèna?
- Yes.

681
01:41:43,323 --> 01:41:45,759
- Try it on.
- No, that's okay.

682
01:41:45,847 --> 01:41:47,890
- It's no problem.
- Another time.

683
01:41:48,456 --> 01:41:52,240
Give me your bag.
We'll discuss it later.

684
01:41:52,370 --> 01:41:55,197
- Thank you.
- Good day.

685
01:42:55,300 --> 01:42:56,778
It's okay. I'll get it.

686
01:43:01,474 --> 01:43:02,866
Thank you.

687
01:43:05,998 --> 01:43:07,172
Thank you for your help.

688
01:43:13,522 --> 01:43:15,566
Good luck, Signora Malèna.

689
01:43:45,704 --> 01:43:49,270
<i>I pedaled as fast as I could</i>

690
01:43:49,444 --> 01:43:51,488
<i>as if I were escaping...</i>

691
01:43:51,618 --> 01:43:54,663
<i>from longing, from innocence, from her.</i>

692
01:43:54,793 --> 01:43:57,272
<i>Time has passed,
and I have loved many women.</i>

693
01:43:57,576 --> 01:44:00,447
<i>And as they've held me close...</i>

694
01:44:00,795 --> 01:44:05,100
<i>and asked if I will remember them,</i>

695
01:44:05,101 --> 01:44:10,406
<i>I've said, "Yes, I will remember you."</i>

696
01:44:10,580 --> 01:44:14,451
<i>But the only one I've never forgotten
is the one who never asked...</i>

697
01:44:14,581 --> 01:44:15,755
<i>Malèna.</i>

