******cc******
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You don't understand.
Krypton's core is collapsing.
We may only
have matter of weeks.
I warned you,
harvesting the core was suicide.
As it accelerated
the process of implosion.
Our resources were exhausted,
what would you have us do Kal?
Look to the stars.
Like our ancestors did.
There are habitable worlds within reach.
We can begin by using the old outpost.
Are seriously suggesting that
we evacuate the entire planet.
No, everybody here
is already dead.
Give me the control of the codex,
I will ensure survival of our race.
There is still hope,
I have held that hope in my hand.
- This council has been disband.
- On whose authority?
Mine.
The rest of you will be trialled
and punished accordingly.
What are you doing Zod,
this is madness.
What I should done years ago,
these lawmakers with their endless debates.
Had led krypton to ruin.
You be the leader of nothing.
Then join me, help me
save our race we start new.
That the degenerate bloodlines
that led us to this state.
And who decide which
bloodlines survives, Zod.
You?
Don't be the reason out, the last
thing I want is us to be enemy's.
You have abandon the principles
that bind us together,
you have taken up a sword
against your own people.
I will honer the man you once were, Zod
not this monster that you become.
Take him away.
**sir, is everything all-right?**
- Out of the way! I said..
Behind you!
Lara, you have to rise the launch,
I will be with you soon as I can.
- Have you seen the codex?
**its just beneath central house, sir.**
**but I'm compelled to warn you, reaching
the chambers is class B crime punishable**
Nobody cares any more achilles
the world is about coming to end.
Jor-el, by the authority of General zod,
surrender the codex.
Easy now.
Did you find the world?
We have.
**orbiting major stellar star**
**just as you say it would.**
his cells will init its radiation.
Its have seeming less
intelligent population.
He will be a outcast, a freak.
They kill him.
No...
he will be a god to them.
What if the ship wont make it.
He will die out there.
Alone.
I can't do it.
I thought I could, but.
Krypton is doomed.
Its our only chance, now.
Its our people only hope.
What is it Achilles.
**citadels deferences**
**are scanned by android**
no, wait.
Just, let me look at him.
I never get to see him walk.
Never hear him our names.
Out there among the stars...
he will live.
Goodbye my son.
Concentrate fire on the main door.
**launch control coming on-line**
- Proceed to ignition.
We have identified the
in the citadel.
Advance.
Hold this platform commander.
I know you stole the codex Jor-el
surrendered it and I let you live.
This is a second change for all of krypton,
not just the bloodlines you deem worthy.
What have you done?
We had a child Zod.
A boy child.
Krypton's first natural
birth in centuries.
And he will be free.
Free to forge its own destiny.
Heresy!
Destroyed it!
Lara listen to me.
Codex is krypton's future.
Abort the launch.
Your son Lara,
where have you sent him.
His name is Kal.
Son of El.
And he is beyond your reach.
Bring that ship down.
**target locked**
Lay down your weapons,
your forces are surrounded.
General Zod, for the crimes
of murder and high treason.
The council sentences you
and your fellow accomplishes.
To 300 hundred cycles of
semantic recondition.
Do you have any last words?
You wont kill us yourself.
You wouldn't filthy your hands,
but you damn us to
black hole for eternity.
Jor-El, was right
you are pack of fools,
every last one of you!
And you...
and you believe
your son is safe.
I will find him.
I will re claim, what
you have taken from us.
I will find him.
I will find him Lara.
I Will Find Him!
**Lara, shouldn't we find refuge**
There is no refuge Achilles.
Jor-El was right,
this is the end.
Build a better world
than ours Kal.
Watch yourself, keep your eyes open
or you are going to be squash.
Where hell they find you, greenhorn.
Gentlemen secure the deck, we just got
a distress call from a rig due west of us.
Secure the deck!
Also all involved stand clear, sub sea
valves failed, the rig is about to explode.
Roger coast guard.
- What about the men left inside, over.
- Forget them, they are dead,
greenhorn, fetch me my binoculars.
Greenhorn.
I don't know how much
longer we can hold out!
This is coast guard 65-10.
We are going to make one last pass
then we are getting out of here.
Wait, we got guys on the heli-pad!
- Where is that guy going, we have to got go!
- Hey lets go!, what are you doing!
When Kansas become
are you listening Clark?
Are you aright Clark?
- Clark, get out of there.
- Leave me alone.
Clark I have called your mother.
Clark honey, what's wrong?
- How can I help you honey.
- The world is too big, mom.
Focus on mine voice.
Pretend there is a Island.
Out in the ocean.
Can you see it.
I see it.
Then swim towards it honey.
Whats wrong with me mom.
Hey, azzwipe.
What did you think of the game.
Leave him alone Pete.
I want hear what he has to say.
Come on, dick splash.
My son was there, he was in the bus.
He saw what Clark did.
I know he didn't.
Was act of god Jonathan.
Well, I think you are blowing
little out of the proportion.
No, I'm not.
Lana saw it too and the Forny boy.
And this isn't the first time
Clark done something like this.
- I just wanted to help.
- I know you did, but we talked about this,
Right.
Right, we talked about this,
you have...
Clark, you have keep
this side of yourself a secret.
What was I appose to do,
just let them die.
Maybe.
There are more at stake here than just our
lives Clark, there are lives around us.
When a world...
when, world finds out what you can do
its going to change everything.
Our believes, our knowlidge.
what it means to be human, everything.
You saw how Pete's mom,
was reacting, right. she was scared, Clark.
Why?
People are afraid what
they don't understand.
Is she right.
Did god gave this to me?
Tell me.
We found you in this.
We were sure that the government
going to show on our doorstep.
No one ever came.
This was in the chamber with you.
I took it to an Metallurgist,
in Kansas state.
He said, what ever it was made did even,
did even exist on periodic-table.
Its another way saying
its not from this world, Clark.
And neither are you.
You are the answer to Something.
you are the answer to
all we alone in universe.
I don't want to be.
And I don't blame you son.
Be huge burden for anybody to bare,
but you are not just anybody, Clark.
And I have to believe that you were,
you were send for an reason.
All these changes that
you going through one day,
one day you are thinking
them as a blessing.
When that day comes,
you have to make a choice,
choice of whether to stand proud
in front of human race or not..
Can I just keep pretending i'm, your son.
You are my son.
But some where out there, you
have another father too.
Who gave you another name.
And he send here for a reason, Clark.
And even if it take you rest of your life, you own
it to yourself to find out what that reason is.
They did find something strange in...
I know, its grazy right.
the americans are there too.
Lots of them.
they are calling it anonmylous object,
what ever that means.
back off rebel, I'm serious.
Oh come on Chrissy.
Knock it of, let me go.
Hey, leave her alone man.
Or what tough guy?
Or going to have ask you to leave.
I think probably just leave
when I'm good and ready.
O, there he is.
Its not worth sweety.
Hey, azzhole don't forget your tip.
Thanks,
hi.
Miss Lane, how are you doing?
- Jed Eubanks Arctic cargo.
- How far to the station?
Camp is just over the rise,
I Walk you over. - great.
- Help her out.
- Careful with those they are heavy.
I got to confess miss Lane,
I'm not fan of the daily planet.
But those you pieces you wrote.
Well, they were pretty impressive.
Well, what can I say, I get writers
block if I'm not wearing a flat jacket.
Miss, Lane!
Hardy US north-com, dr Emil Hamilton.
You are early, we were
excepting you tomorrow.
Which I why show up today.
Look, lets get one thing
straight, guys okay.
The only reason why I'm here,
because we are on Canadian soil,
and appeals court overruled your
injunction to keep me away.
So, if we are done
measuring dicks,
can you have your people
show me what you got.
NASA cci satellites ping the anomaly first
the ice shelf's plates echo.
But, there is definitely
something down there.
- A submarine, maybe from soviet era?
- Doubtful that's 300m,
considerably larger than
anything they build back then.
But, here is the spooky part.
The ice surrounding the object,
its nearly 20.000 years old...
miss Lane, do not wanderer.
Temperatures drops to
- 40 at night round here.
We couldn't find your
body until after spring.
there you go.
- What if I needed to pee.
- There is bucket in the corner.
Where to hell you are going.
Its aright, Its aright..
You are haemorrhaging internally
and if I don't Cauterize you bleed.
I can do things other people cant,
now hold my hand.
This is going to hurt.
For general Hardy and his team
dismay a soviet era submarine,
was actually something much more exotic.
Isotopic analysis of the
surrounding ice bores,
suggest that an object had
been trapped in glacier over,
18,000 years.
As for my rescue, he disappeared
during objects departure,
a background check revealed that his, work
history and identity had been falsified.
The question raised by my rescues
existence are frighten to contemplate.
but I also know what I saw.
And they arrived at inescapable conclusion
that the object and its occupant,
did not originate on earth..
I cant print this Lois, you may
have hallucinated half of it.
What about civilian contractors
who collaborated my story.
Pentagon is denying that
there where was a ship.
Of course they are that's what
they appose to do, its the pentagon.
Harry come on, its me we are talking about,
I'm Pulitzer winning reporter.
- Then act like it.
- Print it or I walk.
You cant, you are under contract.
I'm not running a story about
aliens, walking among us...
Never going to happen.
That's a Scots straight up for the lady.
I'm sending you the original article,
my editor wont printed.
but, if it happened leak to on line...
but, didn't you once describe my site as a,
- creeping cancer of false woods.
- I stand by my words Woodburn.
- But, I want this story out there.
- Why?
Because I want my mystery man
to know I know the truth.
****precoursic diagnostic complete
guidance process authenticated***
***all systems operational***
to see you standing there
and grown to an adult.
- Only Lara could witness this.
- Who are you?
I'm your father Kal.
Or at least a shadow of it, its conscience.
My name is Jor-El.
And Kal?
Its my name.
Kal-El, it is.
I have so many questions.
Where do I come from?,
why did you send me here?
You came from krypton.
A world with much harsher
environment than the earth's.
A long a go,
in era of expansion.
Our race spread out through the stars.
Seeking new worlds to settle upon.
This scout ship was one of thousands
launched at to the void.
We build outpost on other planets,
using great machines to reshape
environments to our needs.
For 100.000 years
our civilization flourished.
- Accomplishing wonders.
- What happened?
Artificial population control established.
The outpost on space
exploration was abandoned,
we exhausted natural
resources, as result...
our planets core became unstable.
Eventually our military
leader, General Zod,
attempted a cue
by then it was to late.
your mother and I,
for saw the coming calamity,
and we took some steps
to insure your survival.
This is a genesis chamber.
All krypton's is conceived
in chambers such as this,
every child was desired to fulfill
pre detainment role in our society,
as worker, a Warrior, a Leader.
Your mother and I, believed that
krypton lost something precocious,
the element of choice, of chance.
What if a child dreamed become other than
what society intended he wonder...
and what if a child spotted
to something greater.
You were embodiment of that believe Kal,
krypton's first natural birth in centuries.
That's why we risked
so much save you.
Why didn't you come with me.
We couldn't Kal.
No matter how we wanted to.
And how much we loved you.
Your mother Lara and I were products
of failures of our world as much zod was.
So, I'm alone.
You are much as a child of earth
now as you are of krypton.
You can embodied best of both worlds.
A dream your mother and I
dedicated our lives to preserve.
People of earth are different
than us, its true.
But ultimately I believe
that is a good thing.
They will not necessary make
same mistake a we did.
And if you guide them, Kal.
And if give them hope.
That is what this symbol means.
The symbol of house of EL means hope.
Embodied in within that help
is fundamental believe,
the potential of every person
to be a force for good.
that's what you can bring them.
Why I'm so difference from them?
Earth's sun is younger and
brighter than Kryptons was.
your cells grown in radiation.
Strengthen your muscles, skin, senses.
Earth gravity is weaker,
yet, its atmosphere is more nourishing,
you have grown stronger
here than I ever could imagine.
The only way to know how strong,
is to keep testing your limits.
You will give the people of earth
an ideal strafe towards.
they will rest behind you, they
will stumble, they will fall.
And in time...
they will join you when the sun come.
In time, you help them
accomplish wonders.
How, do you find someone who has
spent a lifetime covering his tracks.
You start with urban legends
that have sprung in his wake.
All the friends of the friends
who claim to have see him.
For some he was a guardian angel.
For others a cypher,
a ghost who never quite fit in.
As you work your way back in time.
The story's begin to form a pattern.
Pete Ross, do you know him? yes, he
works in I-hop, you go down to road.
I like to talk to you about an accident
that occur when you were younger,
a school bus that went in to the river.
Mrs Kent, I'm Lois Lane from daily planet.
I'm from daily planet and would
like to talk about your son.
Where are you from?, what are you
doing here, let me tell your story.
- What if I don't want my story told.
- Its going to come out eventually.
Somebody going to get a photo
or figures out where you live.
Then I disappear again.
The only way you can disappear for good,
is to stop helping people all together,
and that's not option for you.
My father believed.
If the world found
out, who I really was.
They reject me, of fear.
I'm tired of safe!
I just want do something
useful with my life.
So, farming isn't useful.
I didn't say that.
Our family has been farming for
5 generations Clark. -your family.
Not mine.
I dot know even why I'm listening to you,
you are not my dad,
you are just some guy who
found me in the field.
Clark!
That's all-right Martha.
He is right, Clark has a point.
We are not your parents.
But we have been doing best we can,
and we have making it up as we go along,
so maybe, maybe our best
isn't good enough any more.
Look.
Dad please. -hold on.
Go for the overpass.
Take cover!, take cover!
Over there just! follow them!
She's stuck!
You guys follow me.
The dog in the car!
I get him!
Get your mom to the overpass.
Jonathan!
Ma, stay here.
I let my father die,
because I trusted him.
Because he was convinced,
that I have to wait.
That the world is not ready.
What do you think?
You better watch out Lois.
Hey, Perry got it in for you, he knows
you are Woodburns anonymous source...
I told you not to run with this.
You let Woodburn just shotgun,
it all over the internet.
Now, the publishers want me to sue you.
Well, if its make a difference,
I'm dropping it. - wow just like that?
- What happened to your leads?
- They didn't pan out.
Or perhaps it just didn't get
the attraction you hope it would.
2 weeks leave, no pay
that's your appendence.
You try something like
this again your done here.
No, lets make it 3 weeks, since you
are so willing to agreed with me.
- Perry!
- Don't.
I believe you saw something Lois,
but not for a moment do I believe
that your lead just went cold,
so what ever your reason
are for dropping it...
I think you are doing a right thing.
Why?
Can you imagine how people
on this planet would react...
If...
they knew that there was
someone like this out there.
Go get him!
Well look at you!
A reporter came by here.
She is a friend, don't worry.
Mom.
What.
- I found them.
- Whom?
My parents.
My people.
I know where I come from now.
Wow...
That's wonderful.
I'm so happy for you.
- What?
- Its nothing.
When you were a baby,
I use to lay by your Cradle.
Listen to you breath.
It was hard for you.
You struggled.
- I worried all the time. - you worried
that the truth could come out.
No, the truth about you...
We saw that, the moment we lay eyes on you.
We knew that one day,
the whole world would see that.
I just.
I worried they take you away from me.
I'm not going anywhere mom.
I promise.
- General Swanwick sir.
- What are I'm looking at, doc.
Comet?, asteroid?
Comets don't make course
corrections, General.
I want you see this before some amateur
with a telescope creates a blueprint..
The ships appears to have inserted
itself to lunar synchronous orbit.
I have No idea why.
Have you tried
communicated with it?
Well, they haven't
responded as it yet.
I'm just speculating,
but, I think who ever is on helm of that thing
is looking to make a dramatic entrance.
Does anybody know where,
we keep toner cartridges
- what's going on?
- Its all over the news.
You got to see this.
Yeah, coming.
Yo*are* no* AL**0
**you are not alone**
its coming over rr feeds.
its on my phone too.
My name is general Zod.
I come from a world far from yours.
I have journeyed crossed a ocean
star systems to reach you.
For Sometime your world has
sheltered one of my citizens.
I request that you return
this individual.
To my custody.
For reasons unknown he has chosen
to keep his existence a secret from you.
He had made efforts to blend in.
He will look like you.
But, he is not one of you.
To those of you who may
know his current location.
The faith of your planet
rest in your hands.
To kal-el I say this.
Surrender within 24 hours.
Or watch this world
suffer the consequences
If he truly means us no harm
he should turn himself to his people,
and face the consequences
and if he wont do that,
then maybe we should.
The daily planets Lois Lane
knows who this guys is.
And I think shes the one
we should question.
Hold-on, you are saying
Lois Lane knows who this guy is.
Are you watching this crap?
Been running all morning.
For once I actually I agree with
woodburn now have you seen him?
No, even I did I wouldn't say.
The Entire world is being threaten here.
This not time for you to fallback
on journalistic integrity.
This is serious Lois, fbi is here
upping words like treason.
I got to go.
Its the fbi, hands up
drop the bag now!
Come on kent.
come on, Fight back.
Getup kent.
Is that it?
is that all you got.
Come on!
Did they hurt you?
they cant.
It was what I meant,
are you all-right?
I wanted to hit that kid.
And I know you did, I mean.
Part of me even wanted
you to but then what,
make you feel any better.
You must decide what kind of
man you really want grow up to be clark.
Because...
whatever that man has a
good character or bad, he is.
He is going to change the world.
Whats on your mind.
I don't where to start.
Where ever you want.
That ship that appeared last night.
I'm the one they are looking for.
Do you know why they want you.
With this general zod, even if I surrender
there's no grantee he keeps his word.
There is chance I can safe
earth by turning myself in.
Shouldn't I take it.
What's your gut tell you.
Zod cant be trusted.
Problem is... I'm not sure
people of earth can be either.
Sometimes you have to take
a leap of faith first,
the trust part comes later.
Al-right, you got our attention.
- What it is you want?
- I would like to speak to Lois Lane.
What makes you think he is here.
Don't play games with me general,
I surrender.
Only if you grantee Lois freedom.
Why are you surrendering to Zod.
I surrendering to mankind,
there is a difference.
You let the man handgun you.
Would not be much of
a surrender if I resisted.
And makes them feel more secure,
then all the better for it.
What's the S stand for.
Its not an a S,
on my world its meant hope.
Well, here its an S.
How about...
sir, hi
- my name is doctor..
- Emil hamilton, I know.
I can see your id tag
in your breast pocket,
along with half eaten roll
of pastrami sandwich.
I can also see tranquillize needle
you wont need it.
Sir, you can not except
to not take preconceptions,
you could be carrying
some kind alien pathogen.
I been here for 33 years doctor,
haven't infected anyone yet.
That you know of.
We have legitimize
security concerns,
as you revealed your identity
to miss Lane over there.
Why would you do same with us?
Lets put our cards to table general.
You are scared of me,
because you cant control me.
You don't and you never will.
But that doesn't mean I'm your enemy.
And who is? Zod?
- That's what I'm worried about.
- Be as it may,
I been given orders
hand you over to him.
Do, what you have to do general.
Thank you.
For what?
For believing in me.
Didn't make much
difference in the end.
It did to me.
They are coming.
Go, Lois.
Kal-El, I'm sub commander Faora-Ul.
On behalf of general Zod
I extend you his greetings.
- Are you the ranking officer here?
- I am.
General Zod, would like this
woman to accompany me.
you asked for the alien.
You didn't say anything about our own.
Shall, I tell the general,
you are unwilling to comply.
I don't care what you tell him.
I'll go.
The atmosphere composition in our
ship is not compatible with humans.
You will need wear
a breather beyond this point.
Kal-El.
You don't have no idea how long
we been searching for you.
I take you are zod.
General Zod, our Commander!
You can forgive Kal any
lapses in our quorum..
He is stranger to our ways.
This should be cause for celebration.
Not conflict.
I, feel strange.
- What's happening to him?
- He is rejecting our ships atmospherics.
Spend a lifetime adapting to earth's
ecology but never adapted to ours.
Help him!
I cant what ever is happening
its better running its course.
Hello Kal.
Or do you prefer Clark.
That's the name they
gave you, isn't it.
I was krypton's military leader,
your father our foremost scientist.
The only thing we agreed on
was that krypton was dying.
In return for my evidence
to protect our civilization.
And save our planet.
I and my fellow officers
was sentenced to the phantom zone.
And then destruction of our world...
freed us.
We were adrift.
Destinyed float amongst the ruins
of our planet until we starved.
how did you find a way to earth?
We manage to retro fit the phantom
projector into hyper drive.
Your father made similar modification,
to the craft that brought your here.
So the instrument of our damnation..
Became our salvage.
We seek through old colonial outposts.
Looking for signs of life.
But all we found was death.
Cut of from krypton these
outpost wither and died long ago.
We salvage what we could
armour, weapons.
Even a world-engine.
For 32 years we prepared,
until finally we detected
a distress beacon.
Which you triggered when
you accessed ancient scout ship.
You lead us here, Kal.
And now it is in within your power
to safe what remains of your race.
On krypton, the genetic of
every being yet to be born,
is encoded in
the register of citizens.
Your father stole the registers codex and
stored in the capsule that brought you here.
For what purpose?
So, that krypton can live again,
on earth.
Where is the codex Kal.
If krypton lives again,
what happens to earth?
A foundation has to be build on something.
Even your father recognized that.
No, Zod.
I cant be part of this.
Then what can you be part of.
Stop!
Your father acquitted
himself with honor Kal.
- You killed him?
- I did.
And not a day goes by
when its doesn't haunt me.
But if I do it again, I would.
I have a duty to my people.
And I will not allow anyone
to prevent me to carrying it out.
2 bogeys launching from the alien ship.
Put it out. - yes, sir. - there it is.
Re task skycam 4 give me
a closer look. - yes, sir.
Command, word of the day is trident.
- We have 2 alien craft on aggressive
approach. - icom 4 coming on line.
- Air speed? - 380 knots they are
not responding to our hails.
You are wasting your efforts.
For your exposure to earths sun......
You are not as weak as a human.
- Where did you come from?
- The command key Kal send.
Thanks to you I'm uploaded
to the ships main frame.
- Who are you.
- I'm kals father.
- Can you help us?
- I designed this ship.
I can modify its atmospheric
composition to human compatibility.
We can stop them, we can send
them back to the phantom zone.
- How?
- I can teach you.
And in return you can teach Kal.
Will you help me.
You will be safe here.
- Are you all-right?
- Oh yeah.
I'm sorry.
I didn't meant to tell any thing about you,
but they did something to me...
they did same thing to me.
The craft he arrived in,
where is it.
Go to hell.
There.
Where has he hidden it.
I don't know.
Where Is The Codex!
You been frighten my mother!
What have you done to me?
My parents taught me
to home my senses, Zod.
To focus.
On just what I want to see and without
your helmet, you are getting everything.
And its hurts, doesn't it.
Get inside, its not safe.
All clear, this is guardian
I have previously encounter beings
we are about to engage close proximity,
they are extremely dangerous
we are authorize to use deadly force.
Guardian advanced to target.
Requesting immediately attack
eject!, eject!
I have a bogey incoming!
You are weak, son of El.
The fact, that you posses sense
of morality and we do not.
Gives us evolutionary advantaged.
And history has proven,
it is that the evolution always wins.
I need you engage the targets.
Guardian, this is battle 01,
what about that guy in blue?
I say make all the targets.
Are you okay?
We are going in hard.
Break for impact!
Guardian is down,
I repeat guardian is down.
Guardian, guardian do you read?
This is guardian, I want you to put down every thing
you got at my position, this will be danger close.
Copy, danger close.
Good luck, sir.
A good death is its own reward.
You will not win,
for ever you safe
we kill million more.
I dot think they are
interested sharing this world.
I know how to stop them.
- What happened down there?
- He exposed a temporary weakness.
It is of little inconvenience,
because I have located the codex.
It was never in the capsule.
Jor-el, took the codex,
a DNA of an billion people..
And he bonded it with
his sons individual cells,
all krypton's heirs,
Living in one refugees body.
Does Kal-el need to be alive, for us
to extract the codex from his cells.
No.
Released the world-engine.
What did just happened.
The ships just split in 2,
track 1 is heading east,
track 2 is deploying towards
southern hemisphere.
- How fast is that bogey moving?
- Approaching Mach 24 and accelerating.
Looks like its going to impact
somewhere in south Indian-ocean.
- Rest of the ship is descending.
- Put it on board now.
O.M.G
bring the phantom drive on-line.
We are now sled to the world edge.
Initiated.
What can they hit us with?
Looks like some kind of gravity weapon,
its working in tandem with their ship.
Some how they are increasing earth mass,
clouding the atmosphere with particulates.
O.M.G.
they are Terra-forming.
What's that?
Planetary engineering modifying
earth's atmosphere and topography.
And turning Earth in to krypton.
- But what happen to us?
- Based on these readings,
there wont be an us.
General Swanwick, sir.
I'm on with the control tower, general hardy
is on his way in and he got superman in tow.
Superman?
The alien, sir that what
they call him, superman.
- We have a plan general.
- Is that what I think it is?
Its the ship he arrived in.
This ship is run by something
called phantom-drive.
Its bends space.
Zod ship use the same technology if we
can make 2 drives collide with one other.
- Singularity could be created,
- Like a black hole.
Theoretically they should
be pulled back in.
So, you want us bomb them with that?
General, if that craft max out
17000 pounds we drop it from a c-17.
Its revival the plan.
And if I don't stop that
machine over the Indian-ocean,
the gravity field
will continue to expand.
If that thing is making earth
more like in krypton,
would you be weaker around it?
Maybe, I'm not going let that
stuff stop me trying.
You may want step back a little bit.
Maybe, a little bit more.
- Take command.
- Yes sir
I need to secure the Genesis chamber,
pay my respects to an old friend.
Guardian in route to the metropolis.
**command key accepted**
**genesis chamber coming on-line, sir.**
stop this zoo, while there still time.
Haven't giving up lecturing me
have you, even in death.
I will not let you use
the codex like this.
You don't have
the power to stop me.
The command key I have entered
is revoking your authority,
this ship is now under my control.
North com lightning requesting
permission unleash the hell.
North com lightning 1,
you are clear to engage.
Send battle damage
assessment when able, out.
All right everybody! we are leaving,
leaving the building now.
Get back!, everybody keep
moving, keep moving.
Our people can co exist.
So we can suffer through years of
pain trying to adapt like your son has?
You are talking about genocide.
Yes, and I'm arguing
its merits with a ghost.
We are both ghost Zoid,
cant you see that.
The krypton you cling
on is gone.
- I'm tired about this debate.
- Silencing me wont change anything.
My son, is twice the man you are.
He will finish what we started.
I can promise you that.
Tell me, you have Jor-Els
memory's, his conscience.
Can you experience his pain.
I will harvest the codex
from your son's corps.
And I will re-build krypton,
on top of his bones.
Jenny, where are you!
I'm here! -hold on, hold on.
I can't get free, I'm stuck.
We get you out there, all-right.
Just sit tight.
No, no please! don't leave me.
Robert, get your azz over here and help me.
Try this.
Come on push!
This is guardian, are we
clear to make the drop.
Negative guardian.
He did it.
North-com, this is guardian,
we are god to go.
godspeed guardian on the package.
You are cleared out.
We are lining in for
the final run.
Its up to you and
Hamilton, now.
Load master is it packege on.
- are we ready to drop.
- Negative.
There is something wrong,
its not pose to this.
What is it appose to do?
Its appose to go in all the way.
Let me take a look.
Co-pilot the aircraft.
Whats the hold up!
Target that air craft.
**target locked**
if destroy this ship..
You destroy krypton.
Krypton has its chance.
Are they gone? - I think so.
He saved us.
You know they say its
down hill after the first kiss.
I'm pretty sure, nobody cares
if I'm kissing a human.
Look at this...
we could build a new krypton in here.
But you chose humans over us.
I exist only to protect Krypton...
that is soul purpose which I was born,
and every action I take,
no matter how violent,
or how cruel,
is for the greater good.
Of my people...
and now I have no people.
My soul...
that is what you have taken from me!
I'm going to make them suffer Kal,
these humans you adopted.
- I will take them all from you, one by one.
- You are a monster Zod.
I'm going to stop you.
There is only one way this end Kal
either you die or I do!
I was bred to be a warrior Kal,
trained my entire life,
to master my senses,
where did you trained, on a farm!
Are you F-ing stupid.
That one of your
surveillance drones.
That's a 12 million $
piece of hardware. -it was.
I know you are trying to find out,
where I hang my cape, you won't.
Then I ask the obvious question,
how do we know you wont one day
act against Americas interest.
I grow up in Kansas general,
I'm about American as its gets.
Look, I'm here to help, but its
has to be with my own terms.
- You have to convince Washington of that.
- Even if was willing to try.
- What makes you think they listen.
- I don't know general.
Guess I just have to trust you...
- what are you smiling about captain.
- Nothing sir.
I just think he is kind of hot.
- Get in the car captain.
- Yes sir.
He always believed you were meant for
greater things, and when the day came,
your shoulders will be
able to bare the weight.
So, he could be around
to see who I really I'm.
He saw it Clark, believe me.
What are you going to do, when
you are not saving the world.
Have you given any though to that.
I have actually.
I'm going to find a job, where I can
keep my ear to the ground.
Where people move twice,
when I want go somewhere dangerous,
start asking questions.
Come on Lois, when are you
going to throw me a bone.
Court side seats to the game
tonight, what do you say?
I say, you should go back to trolling the
intern pool you probably have more luck.
sorry.
courtside?
Lombardi, Lane.
Want you to meet our new stringer,
want you to show him the ropes.
this is Clark Kent, good luck kid.
Hey, steve nice to meet you.
Lois Lane, welcome to PIAnEt.
Glad to be here, Lois.)
*****cc*****
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player