Hurry!
Do you not understand?
Krypton's core is collapsing.
We may only have a matter
of weeks. I warned you.
Harvesting the core was
suicide. It has accelerated...
- the process of implosion.
- Our energy reserves...
were exhausted. What
would you have us do, El?
Look to the stars,
like our ancestors did.
There are habitable worlds within reach.
We can begin by using the old outposts.
Are you seriously suggesting
that we evacuate the entire planet?
No. Everybody
here is already dead.
Give me control of the Codex. I
will ensure the survival of our race.
There is still hope.
I have held that
hope in my hands.
This council has been disbanded.
On whose authority?
Mine.
The rest of you will be tried
and punished accordingly.
- What are you doing, Zod? This is madness.
- What I should have done...
years ago.
These lawmakers...
with their endless debates...
have lead Krypton to ruin.
And if your forces prevail...
- you'll be the leader of nothing.
- Then join me.
Help me save our
race. We'll start anew.
We'll sever...
the degenerative bloodlines
that led us to this state.
And who will decide which
bloodlines survive, Zod?
You?
Don't do this, El.
The last thing I want
is for us to be enemies.
You have abandoned the
principles that bound us together.
You've taken up the sword...
against your own people.
I will honor the man
you once were, Zod...
not this monster you've become.
Take him away.
Sir? Is everything all right?
Out of the way.
I said...
Get me Lara.
Jor. Behind you.
Lara, you have to
ready the launch.
I'll be with you
as soon as I can.
H'Raka!
Hyah!
- Can you see the Codex?
- It's just beneath the central hub.
But I'm compelled to warn you.
Breaching the genesis
chamber is a Class-B crime...
Nobody cares anymore, Kelex.
The world is about to come to an end.
Jar-El, by the authority
of General Zed...
surrender the Codex.
Unh!
Ahh!
Easy, H'Raka.
Did you find a world?
- We have.
- Orbiting a main sequence yellow star...
Just as you said it would.
A young star.
His cells will
drink its radiation.
It's a seemingly
intelligent population.
He'll be an outcast.
A freak.
They'll kill him.
How?
He'll be a God to them.
What if the ship
doesn't make it?
He'll die out there...
alone.
I can't do it.
I thought I could, but...
- Lara.
- now that he's here...
Krypton is doomed.
It's his only chance now.
It's our people's only hope.
What is it, Kelex?
Five attack ships
converging from the east.
Citadel's defenses are
being scanned and evaluated.
I'll upload the Codex.
No, wait.
Lara.
Just let me look at him.
We'll never get to see him walk.
Never hear him say our names.
But out there...
amongst the stars...
he will live.
Goodbye, my son.
Our hopes and
dreams travel with you.
Concentrate fire
on the main doors.
Lady Lara.
- The phantom drives are coming online.
- Proceed to ignition.
General.
We have identified an engine
ignition within the citadel.
A launch.
Hold this platform, commander.
I know you stole
the Codex, Jor-El.
Surrender it...
and I'll let you live.
This is a second
chance for all of Krypton...
not just the bloodlines
you deem worthy.
What have you done?
We've had a child, Zod.
A boy child.
Krypton's first natural
birth in centuries.
And he will be free.
Free to forge his own destiny.
Heresy.
Destroy it.
Ah!
Lara...
listen to me.
The Codex is Krypton's future.
Abort the launch.
No!
Your son, Lara...
where have you sent him?
His name...
is Kal...
son of El.
And he's beyond your reach.
Bring that ship down.
Target locked.
Lay down your weapons.
Your forces are surrounded.
General Zod...
for the crimes of murder
and high treason...
the Council has sentenced
you and your fellow insurgents...
to three hundred cycles
of somatic reconditioning.
Do you have any last words?
You won't kill us yourself!
You wouldn't sully your
hands! But you'll damn us...
to a black hole for eternity!
Jor-El was right.
You're a pack of fools,
every last one of you.
And you.
You believe your son is safe?
I will find him.
I will reclaim what
you have taken from us.
I will find him.
I will find him, Lara.
I will find him!
Argh!
Lady Lara, shouldn't
you find refuge?
There is no refuge, Kelor.
Jor-El was right.
This is the end.
Make a better
world than ours, Kal.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Watch it, dumb-ass!
Keep your eyes open or
you're gonna get squashed.
Where the hell did they
find you, greenhorn?
Let's get this trap in the air.
Gentlemen, secure the deck.
We just got a distress call
from a rig due west of us.
Secure the deck.
All civilian boats, stand clear.
The sub-sea valves failed
and the rig is about to explode.
Roger, Coast Guard. What
about the men left inside?
- Forget them. They're dead.
- Greenhorn...
fetch me my binoculars.
Greenhorn.
This is the last of the oxygen. I don't
know how much longer we can hold out.
This is Coast Guard 6510. We'll
make one more pass then get out.
Wait, wait. I got some
guys on the helipad.
Right here!
Come on, come
on! Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go!
Get that last guy loaded.
We have got to go.
Hey, let's go. What
are you doing?
Go! Go!
Argh!
When Kansas became a territory?
Clark.
Are you listening, Clark?
I asked if you could
tell me who first...
settled Kansas.
Are you all right, Clark?
Clark.
Clark!
Clark, come out of there.
Leave me alone.
Clark, I have
called your mother.
Clark?
Ah!
I'm here.
Clark, honey, it's Mom.
Will you open the door?
- What's wrong with him?
- He's such a freak.
Crybaby.
His parents won't even
let him play with other kids.
I know.
Sweetie.
How can I help you
if you won't let me in?
The world's too big, Mom.
Then make it small.
Just, um...
focus on my voice.
Pretend it's an island...
out in the ocean.
Can you see it?
I see it.
Then swim towards it, honey.
What's wrong with me, Mom?
Clark.
- Did you get everything I need?
- Yep.
Hold it, hold it.
Hey, ass-wipe.
What do you think?
You see the game?
- Leave him alone, Pete.
- What are you, his girlfriend?
I wanna hear what he has to say.
Come on...
dick-splash.
My son was there.
He was in the bus.
- He saw what Clark did.
- I know he did.
- I'm sure what he thought he saw was...
- Was an act of God, Jonathan.
This was providence.
I think you're blowing
it out of proportion.
No, I'm not. Lana saw it too.
And the Fordham boy.
This isn't the first time...
Clark's done
something like this.
I just wanted to help.
I know you did, but
we talked about this.
Right?
Right? We talked
about this. You have...
Clark, you have to keep
this side of yourself a secret.
What was I supposed
to do? Just let them die?
Maybe.
There's more at
stake here than just our
lives, Clark, or the
lives of those around us.
When the world...
When the world finds out what you can
do it's gonna change everything. Our...
Our beliefs, our notions of...
what it means to be
human. Everything.
You saw how Pete's
mom reacted, right?
She was scared, Clark.
Why?
People are afraid of what
they don't understand.
Is she right?
Did God do this to me?
Tell me.
We found you in this.
We were sure the government
was gonna show up on our doorstep...
but no one ever came.
This was in that
chamber with you.
I took it to a metallurgist...
at Kansas State.
He said whatever it was
made from didn't even...
Didn't even exist
on the periodic table.
That's another way of saying...
that it's not from
this world, Clark.
And neither are you.
You're the answer, son.
You're the answer to "Are
we alone in the universe?"
I don't wanna be.
And I don't blame you, son.
It'd be a huge burden
for anyone to bear.
But you're not just anyone, Clark,
and I have to believe that you were...
That you were sent
here for a reason.
All these changes that you're
going through, one day...
One day you're gonna
think of them as a blessing.
When that day comes...
you have to make a choice.
A choice of whether to stand proud
in front of the human race or not.
Can't I just keep
pretending I'm your son?
You are my son.
But somewhere
out there you've...
You have another father too,
who gave you another name.
And he sent you here...
for a reason, Clark.
And even if it takes you the rest
of your life, you owe it to yourself...
to find out what that reason is.
Bound by wild desire
I fell into a ring of fire.
Wait a second. Aren't
you here fer the exercise?
No, there was a
change in the plans.
Somebody found something
strange on Ellesmere.
- Aircom's making runs out there all week.
- That rat hole?
- You gotta be kidding me.
- I know. It's crazy.
The Americans are
there too, lots of them.
- Anything else?
- They're calling it an anomalous object.
- Whatever that means.
- Back off, Ludlow. I'm serious.
- Oh, come on, Chrissy.
- Knock it off.
- Sit down.
- Let me go.
Hey. Leave her alone, man.
Or what, tough guy?
Or I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
I think I'll probably just leave
when I'm good and ready.
Ooh.
Oh, there he is.
It's not worth it, sweetie.
Hey, asshole,
don't forget your tip.
Strike.
Thanks.
Hi.
Miss Lane. How you doing?
- Good.
- Jed Eubanks, Arctic Cargo.
How far to the station?
- Camp's just over the rise.
- I'll walk you over. - Great.
Joe can take your bags. Joe.
Help her out.
Careful with those.
They're heavy.
I gotta confess, Miss Lane...
I'm not a fan of
the Daily Planet.
But those pieces you wrote when you
were embedded with the 1st Division were...
Well, they were
pretty impressive.
Well, what can I say? I get writer's
block if I'm not wearing a flak jacket.
Miss Lane.
I'm Colonel Hardy, U.S.
Northcom. Dr. Emil Hamilton...
from DARPA.
- You're early.
- Hi.
We were expecting you tomorrow.
Which is why I showed up today.
Look, let's get one thing
straight, guys, okay?
The only reason I'm here is
because we're on Canadian soil...
and the appellate court overruled
your injunction to keep me away.
So if we're done
measuring dicks...
can you have your people
show me what you found?
NASA's EOS satellites...
pinged the anomaly first.
The ice shelf plays hell
on the echo soundings.
- But there's something there.
- A submarine, maybe?
Soviet-era?
Doubtful. That's 300 meters.
Considerably larger than anything
we know they built back then.
But here's the spooky part.
The ice surrounding
the object...
it's nearly twenty
thousand years old.
Miss Lane?
Try not to wander.
Temperatures drop to
minus 40 at night around here.
Wouldn't find your
body till after spring.
And there you go.
What if I need to tinkle?
There's a bucket in the corner.
Where the hell are you going?
Hello?
It's all right, it's all right,
it's all right. It's all right.
You're hemorrhaging
internally...
and if I don't
cauterize this bleed...
How can I?
I can do things that
other people can't.
Now hold my hand.
This is gonna hurt.
What Colonel Hardy
and his team surmised...
was a Soviet-era submarine...
was actually something
much more exotic.
An isotope analysis of the surrounding
ice bores suggests that an object...
had been trapped in the
glacier for over 18,000 years.
As for my rescuer?
He disappeared during
the object's departure.
A background check
revealed that his work history...
and identity had been falsified.
The questions raised
by my rescuer's...
existence are
frightening to contemplate.
But I also know what I saw.
And I have arrived at the
inescapable conclusion...
that the object
and its occupant...
did not originate on Earth.
I can't print this, Lois. You
might have hallucinated half of it.
What about the civilian
contractors who corroborated...
my story?
The Pentagon is denying
that there was a ship.
Of course they are.
They're supposed to.
It's the Pentagon.
Perry, it's me
we're talking about.
- I'm a Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter.
- Then act like it.
- Print it or I walk.
- You can't.
You're under contract.
I'm not running a story about
aliens walking among us.
Never gonna happen.
That's a Scotch,
straight-up, for the lady.
I'm sending you the article.
My editor won't print it,
but if it leaked online...
Got it.
But didn't you once
describe my site...
as a creeping
cancer of falsehoods?
I stand by my words,
Woodburn, but I want this story...
- out there.
- Why?
Because I want my mystery
man to know I know the truth.
Recursive diagnostics complete.
Guiding presence authenticated.
All systems operational.
To see you standing there
having grown into an adult...
If only Lara could
have witnessed this.
Who are you?
I am your father, Kal.
Or at least a shadow of him.
His consciousness.
My name was Jor-El.
And Kal?
That's my name.
It is.
I have so many questions.
Where do I come from?
Why did you send me here?
You came from Krypton.
A world with a much harsher
environment than Earths.
Long ago...
in an era of expansion...
our race spread out
through the stars...
seeking new
worlds to settle upon.
This scout ship was one of
thousands launched into the void.
We built outposts
on other planets...
musing great machines to
reshape environments to our needs.
For 100,000 years, our
civilization flourished...
accomplishing wonders.
What happened?
Artificial population
control was established.
The outposts on space
exploration were abandoned.
We exhausted our
natural resources.
As a result, our planet's
core became unstable.
Eventually, our
military leader...
General Zod, attempted a coup.
But by then it was too late.
Your mother and I foresaw
the coming calamity...
and we took certain steps
to ensure your survival.
This is a genesis chamber.
All Kryptonians were conceived
in chambers such as this.
Every child was designed to fulfill a
pare-determined role in our society...
as a worker...
a warrior, a leader and so on.
Your mother and I believed
Krypton lost something precious.
The element of
choice, of chance.
What if a child dreamed
of becoming something...
other than what society
had intended for him or her?
What if a child aspired
to something greater?
You were the embodiment
of that belief, Kal.
Krypton's first natural
birth in centuries.
That's why we risked
so much to save you.
Why didn't you come with me?
We couldn't, Kal.
No matter how much...
we wanted to.
No matter how much we loved you.
Your mother, Lara, and I...
were a product of the failures of
our world as much as Zod was...
tied to its fate.
- So I'm alone.
- No.
You're as much a child of
Earth now as you are of Krypton.
You can embody the
best of both worlds.
A dream your mother and I
dedicated our lives to preserve.
The people of Earth are
different from us, it's true.
But, ultimately, I believe
that's a good thing.
They won't necessarily make
the same mistakes we did.
Not if you guide them, Kal.
Not if you give them hope.
That's what this symbol means.
The symbol of the
house of El means hope.
Embodied within that hope
is the fundamental belief...
in the potential of every
person to be a force for good.
That's what you can bring them.
Why am I so different from them?
Earth's sun is younger and
brighter than Krypton's was.
Your cells have
drunken its radiation...
strengthening your muscles,
your skin, your senses.
Earth's gravity is weaker, yet its
atmosphere is more nourishing.
You've grown stronger here
than I ever could have imagined.
The only way to
know how strong...
is to keep testing your limits.
Unh!
Uh... Oh.
Whoa!
You will give the people of
Earth an ideal to strive towards.
They'll race behind you.
They will stumble.
They will fall.
But in time...
they will join you
in the sun, Kal.
In time...
you will help them
accomplish wonders.
How do you find someone who has
spent a lifetime covering his tracks?
You start with the
urban legends...
- that have sprung up in his wake.
- That's Joe.
The friends of a friend...
- who have seen him.
- He worked here.
For some he was a guardian
angel. For others, a cipher...
a ghost who never quite fit in.
Well, I was saying we were...
coming towards the oil rig.
As you work your way back in
time, the stories form a pattern.
I'm looking for a Pete
Ross. Do you know him?
Yeah, he works at the IHOP.
If you go down the road...
Pete Ross?
I'd like to talk to you about an
accident when you were younger.
A school bus that
went into the river.
Dusty. Shh-shh-shh.
Mrs. Kent?
I'm Lois Lane. I'm
from the Daily Planet.
Quiet.
I'm from the Daily Planet and I'd
like to talk to you about your son.
I figured if I turned over enough
stones you'd eventually find me.
Where are you from?
What are you doing here?
Let me tell your story.
What if I don't
want my story told?
It's going to come
out eventually.
Somebody's going to get a
photograph or figure out where you live.
- Then I'll disappear again.
- The only way you could disappear...
is to stop helping people altogether,
and I sense that's not an option for you.
My father believed that if the
world found out who I really was...
they'd reject me...
out of fear.
I'm tired of safe.
I just wanna do something
useful with my life.
So farming, feeding
people. That's not useful?
I didn't say that.
Our family's been farming
for five generations.
Your family, not mine.
I don't even know why I'm
listening to you. You're not my dad.
You're just some guy
who found me in a field.
Clark.
It's all right, Martha.
He's right. Clark has a point.
We're not your parents.
But we've been
doing the best we can.
And we've been making this
up as we go along, so maybe...
Maybe our best isn't
good enough anymore.
Look, Dad...
Hold on.
Go for the overpass.
Go for the overpass!
Take cover! Take cover!
- Over there. Just follow them.
- Take cover.
She's stuck.
Hank's still in the car.
Hank's in the car.
- I'll get him, I'll get him.
- No, no.
Get your mom to the overpass.
Hank! Hank! Come!
- Jonathan!
- Mom, it's okay.
- Mom, stay here.
Dad!
I let my father die
because I trusted him.
Because he was
convinced that I had to wait.
That the world was not ready.
What do you think?
You better watch out, Lois.
Hey, Perry's gunning for you.
He knows you're Wood burns anonymous source
and cannot wait to rip you a new one.
Oh, look at her. Ha, ha, ha.
I told you not to run with
this, and what do you do?
You let Wood burn just
shotgun it all over the Internet.
Now the publishers
want me to sue you.
Well, if it makes a
difference, I'm dropping it.
Whoa, just like that?
Yep.
What happened to your leads?
They didn't pan out.
The story is smoke.
Or it didn't get the
traction you hoped?
Two weeks leave...
no pay, that's your penance.
You try something
like this again...
- you're done here.
- Fine.
Let's make it three weeks
since you're so willing to agree.
- Perry.
- No, no. Don't. Don't.
I believe you saw
something, Lois.
But not for a moment do I believe
that your leads just went cold.
So whatever your
reasons are for dropping it...
I think you're
doing the right thing.
Why?
Can you imagine how people
on this planet would react...
if they knew there was
someone like this out there?
Go get him.
Well, look at you.
A reporter came by here.
She's a friend. Don't worry.
Oh.
Mom.
- Heh, heh, heh.
- What?
- I found them.
- Who?
My parents.
My People.
I know where I come from now.
Wow.
That's wonderful.
I'm so happy for you, Clark.
- What?
- It's nothing.
When you were a baby I used
to lay by your crib at night...
listening to you breathe.
It was hard for you.
You struggled.
And I worried all the time.
You worried the
truth would come out.
No.
The truth about
you is beautiful.
We saw that the moment
we laid eyes on you.
We knew that one day, the
whole world would see that.
I'm just...
I'm worried they'll
take you away from me.
I'm not going anywhere, Mom.
I promise.
General Swan wick, sir.
What am I looking at,
doc? Comet? Asteroid?
Comets don't make
course corrections, general.
Wanted you to see this
before some amateur
with a telescope creates
a worldwide panic.
The ship appears to have...
inserted itself into a
lunar synchronous orbit...
though I have no idea why.
Have you tried...
communicating with it?
Well, they haven't
responded as of yet.
I'm just speculating, but I think
whoever? At the helm of that thing...
is looking to make
a dramatic entrance.
Anybody know where
we keep the toner?
- What's going on?
- It's all over the news.
You gotta see this.
Clark.
Yeah?
Coming.
This is a breaking
news. An unidentified...
You are not alone.
It's coming in on the RSS feeds.
It's on my phone too.
My name is General Zod.
I come from a
world far from yours.
I have journeyed across an
ocean of stars to reach you.
For some time, your world
has sheltered one of my citizens.
I request that you
return this individual...
to my custody.
For reasons unknown, he has
chosen to keep his existence...
a secret from you.
He will have made
efforts to blend in.
He will look like you.
But he is not one of you.
To those of you who may know...
of his current location...
...fate of your planet...
rests in your hands.
To Kal-El, I say this:
Surrender within 24 hours...
or watch this world
suffer the consequences.
Ah!
We hardly know anything
about him, isn't that right?
If he truly means us no harm...
he'll turn himself in and
face the consequences.
And if he won't do that...
then maybe we should.
The Daily Planet's Lois
Lane knows who this guy is.
And I think that she's the
one we should be questioning.
- Hold on. You're saying Lois Lane...
- Hello?
Are you watching this crap?
Been running all morning.
For once I agree with
Woodburn. Have you seen him?
- Do you know where he is?
- No. Even if I did, I wouldn't say.
The entire world is
being threatened here.
This is not time
for you to fall...
back on journalistic integrity.
This is serious, Lois.
The FBI is here. They're throwing
around words like "treason".
I gotta go.
FBI. Hands up.
Drop the bag. Now.
Regarding the visitors
themselves we know...
very little. According
to government officials...
the visitors do not
represent a threat...
despite the ominous
tone of their message.
Then of course there's the
question on everyone's mind:
"Who is this Kal-El person?
Does he actually exist?
How could he have remained
hidden from us for so long?"
Come on, Kent.
Come on. Fight back.
Get up, Kent.
So is that it?
Is that all you've got?
Come on, Kent.
Come on!
Did they hurt you?
You know they can't.
That's not what I meant.
I meant, are you all right?
I wanted to hit that kid. I
wanted to hit him so bad.
I know you did. I mean...
part of me even wanted
you to, but then what?
Make you feel any better?
You just have to decide what kind of
man you want to grow up to be, Clark.
Because whoever that man
is, good character or bad, he's...
He's gonna change the world.
What's on your mind?
I don't know where to start.
Wherever you want.
That ship that
appeared last night.
I'm the one they're looking for.
Do you know...
why they want you?
No. But this General Zod...
even if I surrender, there's no
guarantee he'll keep his word, but...
if there's a chance I can save
Earth by turning myself in...
shouldn't I take it?
What does your gut tell you?
Zod can't be trusted.
The problem is...
I'm not sure the people
of Earth can be either.
Sometimes you have to
take a leap of faith first.
The trust part comes later.
All right. You've
got our attention.
What is it you want?
I would like to
speak to Lois Lane.
What makes you think she's here?
Don't play games
with me, general.
I'll surrender, but only if you
guarantee Lois's freedom.
Why are you surrendering to Zod?
I'm surrendering to
mankind. There's a difference.
You let them handcuff you?
Wouldn't be much of
a surrender if I resisted.
And if it makes them
feel more secure...
then all the better for it.
What's the S stand for?
It's not an S.
On my world it means hope.
Well, here, it's an S.
How about...
Super...
Sir?
- Hi, my name is Dr. E...
- Emil Hamilton.
I know, I can see your ID
tag in your breast pocket.
Along with a half-eaten
roll of Lifesavers.
I can also see the
soldiers in the next room...
preparing that
tranquilizing agent of yours.
You won't need it.
Sir, you can't expect us
to not take precautions.
You could be carrying
some kind of alien pathogen.
Been here for 33 years, doctor.
- Haven't infected anyone yet.
- That you know of. We have legitimate...
security concerns. You revealed
your identity to Miss Lane over there.
Why won't you do
the same with us?
Let's put our cards on
the table here, general.
You're scared because
you can't control me.
You don't, and you never will.
But that doesn't
mean I'm your enemy.
Then who is?
Zod?
That's what I'm worried about.
Be that as it may...
I've been given orders
to hand you over to him.
Do what you have to do, general.
Thank you.
For what?
For believing in me.
Didn't make much
difference in the end.
It did to me.
They're coming.
You should leave now.
Go, Lois.
Kal-El.
I'm sub-commander Faora-Ul.
On behalf of General Zod,
I extend you his greetings.
- Are you the ranking officer here?
- I am.
General Zod would
like this woman...
to accompany me.
You asked for the alien.
You didn't say anything
about one of our own.
Shall I tell the general
you're unwilling to comply?
I don't care what you tell him.
It's all right.
I'll go.
The atmospheric composition on
our ship is not compatible with humans.
You need to wear a breather...
beyond this point.
Kal-El.
You have no idea how long...
we've been searching for you.
I take it you're Zod?
General Zod.
- Our commander.
- It's all right, Faora.
We can forgive Kal
any lapses in decorum.
He's a stranger to our ways.
This should be 'cause...
for celebration, not conflict.
- Unh.
- Not conflict.
I...
feel strange.
Weak.
What's happening to him?
He's rejecting our
ship's atmospherics.
Clark.
You've spent a lifetime
adapting to Earth's ecology...
but never adapted to ours.
Help him.
I can't. Whatever's happening...
- has to run its course.
- Clark.
Help him.
Hello, Kal.
Or do you prefer Clark?
That's the name they gave you.
Isn't it?
I was Krypton's
military leader...
your father our
foremost scientist.
The only thing we agreed on...
was that Krypton was
dying. In return for my efforts...
to protect our civilization...
and save our planet...
I and my fellow officers were
sentenced to the Phantom Zone.
And then the
destruction of our world...
freed us.
We were adrift,
destined to float...
amongst the ruins
of our planet...
Until we starved.
How did you find
your way to Earth?
We managed to retrofit the
phantom projector into a hyper drive.
Your father made a similar modification
to the craft that brought you here.
And so the instrument
of our damnation...
became our salvation.
We sought out the
old colonial outposts...
looking for signs of life.
But all we found was death.
Cut off from Krypton,
these outposts...
mwithered and died long ago.
We salvaged what we could...
armour, weapons...
even a world engine.
For 33 years we prepared...
until finally we detected
a distress beacon...
which you triggered...
when you accessed
the ancient scout ship.
You led us here, Kal.
And now it's
within your power...
to save what
remains of your race.
On Krypton...
the genetic template for
every being yet to be born...
is encoded in the
registry of citizens.
Your father stole
the registry's Codex...
and stored it in the capsule
that brought you here.
For what purpose?
So that Krypton
can live again...
on Earth.
Where is the Codex, Kal?
If Krypton lives again...
what happens to Earth?
The foundation has to
be built on something.
Even your father
recognized that.
No, Zod.
I can't be a part of this.
Then what can you be a part of?
No!
Zod!
Your father acquitted...
himself with honor, Kal.
You killed him?
I did.
And not a day goes by
where it doesn't haunt me.
But if I had to do
it again, I would.
I have a duty to my people...
and I will not allow anyone to
prevent me from carrying it out.
What's the sit-rep, major?
DSP pinged two bogeys
launching from the alien ship.
- Put it up.
- Yes, sir.
There it is.
Re-task lkon-4...
- and get me a closer look.
- Yes, sir.
Command, the word...
of the day is trident.
We have two alien craft
on aggressive approach.
Ikon-4 coming online.
Air speed?
380 knots, entering Kansas...
airspace. Not
responding to our hails.
You're wasting your efforts.
The strength you derived
from the Earth's sun...
has been neutralized
aboard our ship.
Here...
in this environment...
you are as weak as a human.
Unh!
Where did you come from?
The command key, Miss Lane.
Thanks to you, I'm uploading
to the ship's mainframe.
Who are you?
I am Kal's father.
Can you help us?
I designed this ship.
I can modify its
atmospheric composition...
to human compatibility.
We can stop them.
We can send them back
to the Phantom Zone.
How?
I can teach you.
And in turn, you can teach Kal.
Will you help me?
The ship's crew are alerted.
We need to move quickly.
Retrieve the command key.
- Did you do that?
- Yes. Pick up her sidearm.
What's happening?
To your right.
Fire.
Behind you.
Secure yourself
inside the open pod.
Safe travels, Miss
Lane. It's unlikely...
we'll see each other again.
Remember, the phantom drives
are essential in stopping them.
Move your head to the left.
Is it true what Zod
said about the Codex?
Strike that panel.
We wanted you to learn...
what it meant to
be human first...
so that one day, when the time
was right, you could be the bridge...
between two peoples.
Look.
Lois.
You can save her, Kal.
You can save all of them.
You'll be safe here.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I didn't wanna tell them anything,
but they did something to me.
- They looked inside my mind...
- It's okay, Lois.
They did the same thing to me.
Clark!
The craft he arrived in...
where is it?
Go to hell.
There.
Unh!
The Codex is not here.
Argh!
Ah!
Where has he hidden it?
I don't know.
Where is the Codex?!
Ahh!
You think you can
threaten my mother?!
Ah!
What have you done to me?
My parents taught me to hone...
my senses, Zod.
Focus...
on just what I wanted to see.
Without your helmet...
you're getting everything.
Unh!
And it hurts...
doesn't it?
Argh!
Get away from the window.
Get inside. It's not safe.
Ail players, this is Guardian. I
am airborne mission commander.
I have previously
encountered and observed...
the beings we're
about to engage.
They are extremely dangerous
and we have been authorized...
to use deadly force.
Roger, Guardian, we
are inbound to target.
Cleared hot. Weapons free.
Copy, 11. Weapons free.
Thunder 11...
tally three targets.
Unh!
Thunder 11...
good hit. Request
immediate re-attack.
Roger, Guardian. We'll
make a second gun run...
on a heading of 212 degrees.
Thunder 11, eject!
Eject!
I have a bogey incoming!
Oh, shit.
Argh!
You are weak...
son of El.
Unsure of yourself.
The fact that you possess
a sense of morality...
and we do not...
gives us an
evolutionary advantage.
And if history has
proven anything...
it is that evolution
always wins.
Ragh!
Unh!
CCT, we're approaching...
LZ Jay hawk. Get down in five.
Let's go. Go to the LZ.
Roger, sarge. Let's go!
All rangers, I need you...
to engage the targets.
Guardian, this is Badger 01.
What about the guy in blue?
I said engage...
all targets.
Contact. Contact.
Ah!
You Okay?
We're auto-rotating,
going in hard.
Brace for impact.
We're going in hard!
Fallen angel. Fallen
angel. Guardian is down.
I repeat, Guardian is down.
Guardian, do you read?
Thunder 12, calling Guardian.
- Do you read?
- Thunder 12...
this is Guardian.
Put down everything you've
got north of my position.
- This will be danger-close.
- Copy, danger-close.
Good luck, sir.
A good death is its own reward.
You will not win.
For every human you save...
we will kill a
million more. Unh!
Do we have an all clear?
Alpha team, sit-rep. Alpha team.
Do you copy? Alpha team.
This man is not our enemy.
Thank you, colonel.
Mom?
I'm all right.
Nice suit, son.
I'm so sorry.
It's only stuff, Clark.
It can always be replaced.
But you can't be.
Mom, Zod said this Codex...
he's looking for can
bring my people back.
Isn't that a good thing?
I don't think they're
interested in sharing this world.
Clark.
I know how to stop them.
What happened down there?
He exposed a temporary weakness.
It is of little consequence...
because I have
located the Codex.
It was never in the capsule.
Jor-el took the Codex...
the DNA of a billion
people, then he bonded it...
within his son's individual...
cells.
All of Krypton's heirs...
living hidden in
one refugee's body.
Does Kal-EI need to be alive...
for us to extract the
Codex from his cells?
No.
Release the world engine.
What just happened?
The ship just split in mo.
Track one is heading east, track
two to the southern hemisphere.
- How fast is that bogey moving?
- Approaching...
Mach 24 and accelerating.
It's gonna impact somewhere
in the Indian Ocean.
The rest of the
ship is descending.
Put it on the board now.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
Bring the phantom drive online.
We are now slave
to the world engine.
Initiate.
- What have they hit us with?
- Looks like some kind of gravity...
weapon. It's working in
tandem with their ship.
Somehow they're
increasing the Earth's mass...
clouding the atmosphere
with particulates.
Oh, my God.
They're terraforming.
What's that?
Planetary engineering...
modifying the Earth's
atmosphere and topography.
Turning Earth into Krypton.
- But what happens to us?
- Based on these readings...
there won't be an "us".
General Swan wick, sir.
I'm on with the control tower.
Colonel Hardy's on his way
and he's got Superman in tow.
Superman?
The alien, sir.
That's what they're
calling him. Superman.
We have a plan, general.
Is that what I think it is?
It's the ship he arrived in.
This ship is powered by
something called a phantom drive.
It bends space.
Zod's ship uses the same technology, and
if we can make the two drives collide...
A singularity can be created.
- Like a black hole.
- Yes.
So if we open up this doorway...
they should be pulled back in.
So you want us to
bomb them with that?
General, that craft maxes out...
17,000 pounds, we
can drop it from a C-17.
It's a viable plan.
If I don't stop that machine
over the Indian Ocean...
the gravity field
will continue...
to expand.
If that thing is making
Earth more like Krypton...
won't you be weaker around it?
Maybe.
I'm not about to let
that stop me from trying.
You might want to
step back a little bit.
Maybe a little bit more.
Faora.
Take command.
- Yes, sir.
- I need to secure the genesis chamber...
and pay my respects
to an old friend.
Guardian en route
to Metropolis...
package in tow.
Be advised, F-35s
inbound to rendezvous point.
You should have
visual contact now.
Command key accepted.
Genesis chamber coming online, sir.
Stop this, Zod...
while there's still time.
Haven't given up lecturing
me, have you, even in death?
I will not let you use
the Codex like this.
You don't have the
power to stop me.
The command key I have
entered is revoking your authority.
This ship is now
under my control.
Norlhcom,
Lightning 1, request...
- permission to unleash the hounds.
- Lightning 1...
you are clear to engage. Send battle
damage assessment when able. Out.
Avionics are going
haywire. The gravity field...
is pulling our missiles
down. We gotta get closer.
All right, everybody...
we're leaving. We're
leaving the building now.
I just lost my wingman.
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
Everybody, this way! Come on!
Everybody, come on!
Keep moving, keep moving.
Jenny!
Oh, my God.
Perry!
Go! There! Go!
Our people can co-exist.
So we can suffer through years of
pain trying to adapt like your son has?
- You're talking about genocide.
- Yes.
And I'm arguing its
merits with a ghost.
We're both ghosts, Zod.
Can't you see that? The Krypton
you're clinging onto is gone.
Ship, have you managed to
quarantine this invasive intelligence?
- You'll fail.
- I have.
Then prepare to terminate it.
- I'm tired of this debate.
- Silencing me...
won't change anything.
My son...
is twice the man you were.
And he will finish
what we started.
I can promise you that.
Tell me...
you have Jor-El's
memories, his conscience.
Can you experience...
his pain?
I will harvest the Codex
from your son's corpse...
and I will rebuild Krypton...
atop his bones.
Argh!
Jenny.
- Jenny. Jenny, where are you?
- I'm here!
- I'm here. Here.
- Jenny.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm stuck.
- I can't get free. I'm stuck.
- Okay.
We'll get you out of there,
all right? Just sit tight.
No, no, no!
- Don't leave me.
- We're not gonna leave you.
- Okay.
- Lombard!
- Get your ass over here and help me.
- Damn it.
- We just gotta move this.
- Here.
Slide that in. You
push, I'll pull, okay?
Go.
- Push!
- Oh, my God.
It's getting closer!
Come on, push!
Northcom, this is
Guardian. Are we cleared?
Negative, Guardian.
Come on! Push!
Ahh!
Argh!
He did it.
Northcom, this is Guardian.
We're passing through
phase line red. Good to go.
Godspeed, Guardian.
Arm the package.
You are cleared hot.
We're lining up
for the final run.
It's up to you and Hamilton now.
You gotta be kidding me.
Loadmaster, is the package...
ready to drop?
Negative, Guardian.
There's something wrong.
It's not supposed to do this.
What's it supposed to do?
- It's supposed to go in all the way.
- Let me take a look.
Co-pilot's aircraft.
We are lined up for the
drop. What's the hold up?
We've had a setback.
Target that aircraft.
Target locked.
Stop!
If you destroy this ship...
you destroy Krypton!
Krypton had its chance.
Argh!
Miss Lane! It's
not safe for you...
over there!
Miss Lane!
Ah!
Move now! Go!
A good death...
is its own reward.
Ah!
Argh!
Are they gone?
I think so.
He saved us.
You know, they say it's all
downhill after the first kiss.
I'm pretty sure that only counts
when you're kissing a human.
Look at this.
We could have
built a new Krypton...
in this squalor.
But you chose the
humans over us.
I exist...
only to protect Krypton.
That is the sole purpose
for which I was born.
And every action I take...
no matter how violent...
or how cruel...
is for the greater good...
of my people.
And now...
I have no people.
My soul...
that is what you have taken...
from me.
I'm going to make
them suffer, Kal.
These humans you've adopted,
I will take them all from you...
- one by one.
- You're a monster, Zod...
and I'm gonna stop you.
Argh!
There's only...
one way this ends, Kal.
Either you die...
or I do.
Unh!
I was bred to be a warrior, Kal.
Trained my entire life...
to master my senses.
Where did you train? On a farm?
Argh!
If you love...
these people so much...
you can mourn for them.
Don't do this!
Stop!
Never.
Ahh!
Are you effing stupid?
It's one of your
surveillance drones.
That's a $12,000,000
piece of hardware.
It was.
I know you're trying to find
out where I hang my cape.
- You won't.
- Then I'll ask...
the obvious question:
How do we know you won't one
day act against America's interests?
I grew up in Kansas, general.
I'm about as
American as it gets.
Look...
I'm here to help...
but it has to be
on my own terms.
You have to convince
Washington of that.
Even if I were willing to try, what
makes you think they'd listen?
I don't know, general.
Guess I'll just
have to trust you.
What are you smiling about?
Nothing, sir.
I just think he's kind of hot.
- Get in the car, captain.
- Mm-hm. Yes, sir.
He always believed you
were meant for greater things.
And that when the day came...
your shoulders would
be able to bear the weight.
Yeah, I just wish he could have
been here to see it finally happen.
He saw it, Clark, believe me.
What are you going to do
when you're not saving the world?
- Have you given any thought to that?
- I have, actually. Heh, heh.
I gotta find a job where I can
keep my ear to the ground.
Where people won't look twice...
when I want to go somewhere
dangerous and start asking questions.
Come on, Lois. When are
you gonna throw me a bone?
Courtside seats
to the game tonight.
- What do you say?
- I say...
you should go back to
trolling the intern pool.
You'll probably have
more luck. Sorry.
Courtside?
- Don't. Ha, ha, ha.
- No.
Lombard, Lane, I want
you to meet our new stringer.
I want you to show him
the ropes. This is Clark Kent.
Good luck, kid.
Hey. Steve.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
Hi.
Lois Lane.
Welcome to the Planet.
Glad to be here, Lois.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)