(BACK IN BLACK PLAYING)
♪ Back in black
I hit the sack
♪ I've been too long
I'm glad to be back
♪ Yes, I'm let loose
from the noose
♪ That's kept me
hanging around
♪ I've been looking at the sky
and it's gettin' me high
♪ Forget the hearse
'cause I never die ♪
I feel like you're driving me
to a court-martial.
This is crazy.
What did I do?
I feel like you're
going to pull over
and snuff me.
What, you're not
allowed to talk?
Hey, Forrest!
We can talk, sir.
Oh, I see.
So it's personal?
No, you intimidate them.
Good God, you're a woman.
I honestly...
I couldn't have called that.
I mean, I'd apologize,
but isn't that what
we're going for here?
I thought of you
as a soldier first.
I'm an airman.
You have,
actually, excellent
bone structure, there.
I'm kind of having
a hard time not
looking at you now.
Is that weird?
Come on, it's okay, laugh.
Sir, I have
a question to ask.
Yes, please.
Is it true you went
12 for 12 with last year's
Maxim cover models?
That is an
excellent question.
Yes and no.
March and I had
a scheduling conflict,
but fortunately,
the Christmas cover
was twins.
Anything else?
You're kidding me
with the hand up, right?
Is it cool if I take
a picture with you?
Yes. It's very cool.
All right.
I don't want to see this
on your MySpace page.
Please, no gang signs.
No, throw it up.
I'm kidding.
Yeah, peace.
I love peace.
I'd be out of
a job with peace.
Come on. Hurry up.
Just click it. Don't change
any settings. Just click it.
(ALL SCREAMING)
What's going on?
WOMAN: Contact left!
What have we got?
(GUNS FIRING)
Jimmy, stay with Stark!
Stay down!
Yeah.
(GROANING)
Son of a bitch!
Wait, wait, wait!
Give me a gun!
Stay here!
(GROANING)
(POWERING UP)
Whoa!
(MAN SPEAKING IN URDU)
NARRATOR: Tony Stark.
Visionary. Genius.
American patriot.
Even from an early age,
the son of legendary
weapons developer
Howard Stark
quickly stole the spotlight
with his brilliant
and unique mind.
At age four, he built
his first circuit board.
At age six, his first engine.
And at 17, he graduated
summa cum laude from MIT.
Then, the passing of a titan.
Howard Stark's
lifelong friend and ally,
Obadiah Stane,
steps in to help fill the gap
left by the legendary founder,
until, at age 21,
the prodigal son returns
and is anointed the new CEO
of Stark Industries.
With the keys to the kingdom,
Tony ushers in a new era
for his father's legacy,
creating smarter weapons,
advanced robotics,
satellite targeting.
Today, Tony Stark
has changed the face
of the weapons industry
by ensuring freedom
and protecting America
and her interests
around the globe.
As liaison to
Stark Industries,
I've had the
unique privilege of
serving with a real patriot.
He is my friend
and he is my great mentor.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my honor
to present this
year's Apogee Award
to Mr. Tony Stark.
Tony?
Thank you, Colonel.
Thanks for the save.
This is beautiful. Thank you.
Thank you all very much.
This is wonderful.
Well, I'm not Tony Stark.
(ALL LAUGHING)
But if I were Tony,
I would tell you
how honored I feel
and what a joy it is
to receive this
very prestigious award.
Tony, you know...
The best thing about Tony
is also the worst thing.
He's always working.
(ALL WHOOPING)
Work it! Come on!
We should just
stay till the morning.
You are unbelievable.
Oh, no! Did they
rope you into this?
Nobody roped me
into anything!
I'm so sorry.
But they told me that
if I presented
you with an award,
you'd be deeply honored.
Of course I'd be
deeply honored.
And it's you, that's great.
So when do we do it?
It's right here.
Here you go.
There it is.
That was easy.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, it's okay.
Wow! Would you look at that?
That's something else.
I don't have any of those
floating around.
We're gonna let it ride!
Give me a hand, will you?
Give me a little
something-something.
Okay, you, too.
I don't blow on a man's dice.
Come on, honey bear.
There it is.
Lieutenant Colonel
Rhodes rolls! And...
DEALER: Two craps.
Line away.
That's what happens.
Worse things have happened.
I think we're gonna be fine.
Color me up, will you?
This is where I exit.
All right.
Tomorrow, don't be late.
Yeah, you can count on it.
I'm serious!
I know, I know.
Render unto Caesar
that which is Caesar's.
There you go.
Mr. Stark!
Excuse me,
Christine Everhart,
Vanity Fair magazine.
Can I ask you
a couple of questions?
She's cute.
She's all right?
Hi.
Yeah. Okay, go.
It's okay?
You've been called
the da Vinci of our time.
What do you say to that?
Absolutely ridiculous.
I don't paint.
And what do you say
to your other nickname?
"The Merchant of Death"?
That's not bad.
Let me guess. Berkeley?
Brown, actually.
Well, Ms. Brown,
it's an imperfect world, but
it's the only one we've got.
I guarantee you,
the day weapons are no longer
needed to keep the peace,
I'll start making
bricks and beams
for baby hospitals.
Rehearse that much?
Every night in
front of the mirror
before bedtime.
I can see that.
I'd like to show
you first-hand.
All I want is
a serious answer.
Okay, here's serious.
My old man
had a philosophy,
"Peace means
having a bigger stick
than the other guy."
That's a great line
coming from the guy
selling the sticks.
My father helped
defeat the Nazis.
He worked on
the Manhattan Project.
A lot of people,
including your
professors at Brown,
would call that
being a hero.
And a lot of people
would also call that
war profiteering.
Tell me,
do you plan to report
on the millions we've saved
by advancing
medical technology
or kept from starvation
with our intelli-crops?
All those breakthroughs,
military funding, honey.
You ever lose
an hour of sleep
your whole life?
I'd be prepared to
lose a few with you.
(CHRISTINE EXCLAIMS)
(TONY LAUGHING)
JARVIS ON SPEAKER:
Good morning. It's 7:00 a.m.
The weather in Malibu
is 72 degrees with
scattered clouds.
The surf conditions are fair
with waist-to-shoulder
high lines.
High tide will
be at 10:52 a.m.
MALIBU, CALIFORNIA
Tony?
Hey, Tony?
(BEEPING)
JARVIS: You are not authorized
to access this area.
Jesus.
That's Jarvis.
He runs the house.
I've got your clothes here.
They've been
dry-cleaned and pressed,
and there's a car
waiting for you outside
that will take you anywhere
you'd like to go.
You must be
the famous
Pepper Potts.
Indeed I am.
After all these years,
Tony still has you
picking up the dry-cleaning.
I do anything and everything
that Mr. Stark requires,
including, occasionally,
taking out the trash.
Will that be all?
(INSTITUTIONALIZED PLAYING)
Sometimes I try to do things
but it just doesn't work out
the way I want it to,
and I get real frustrated
and then, like,
I try hard to do it
and I, like, take my time
but it just doesn't work out
the way I want it to.
It's like I concentrate
on it real hard
but it just doesn't work out.
Give me an exploded view.
JARVIS: The compression
in cylinder three
appears to be low.
Log that.
(MUSIC STOPS)
I'm gonna try again,
right now.
Please don't
turn down my music.
I'll keep you posted.
You are supposed to be
halfway around
the world right now.
How'd she take it?
Like a champ.
Why are you
trying to hustle me
out of here?
Your flight was
scheduled to leave
an hour and a half ago.
That's funny,
I thought with it being
my plane and all,
that it would
just wait for me
to get there.
Tony,
I need to speak to you
about a couple things
before I get you
out of the door.
Doesn't it kind of defeat
the whole purpose
of having your own plane
if it departs
before you arrive?
Larry called. He's got
another buyer for the
Jackson Pollock in the wings.
Do you want it?
Yes or no.
Is it a good representation
of his spring period?
No. The Springs was actually
the neighborhood
in East Hampton
where he lived and worked,
not "spring" like the season.
So?
I think it's a fair example.
I think it's
incredibly overpriced.
I need it.
Buy it. Store it.
Okay. The MIT
commencement speech...
Is in June. Please, don't
harangue me about stuff
that's way, way, down...
They're haranguing me,
so I'm gonna say yes.
Deflect it and absorb it.
Don't transmit it back to me.
I need you to sign this
before you get on the plane.
What are you trying
to get rid of me for?
What, you got plans?
As a matter of fact, I do.
I don't like it
when you have plans.
I'm allowed to have plans
on my birthday.
It's your birthday?
Yes.
I knew that. Already?
Yeah. Isn't that strange?
It's the same day
as last year.
Get yourself
something nice from me.
I already did.
And?
Oh, it was very nice.
Yeah.
Very tasteful.
Thank you, Mr. Stark.
You're welcome,
Miss Potts.
Okay.
You're good. Oh, I thought
I lost you back there.
You did, sir.
I had to cut
across Mulholland.
I got you.
RHODES: What's wrong with you?
What?
Three hours.
I got caught doing a piece
for Vanity Fair.
For three hours.
For three hours
you got me standing here.
Waiting on you now.
Let's go. Come on.
Wheels up!
Rock and roll!
What you reading, platypus?
Nothing.
Come on, sour patch.
Don't be mad.
I told you, I'm not mad.
I'm indifferent, okay?
I said I was sorry.
Good morning, Mr. Stark.
You don't need to
apologize to me.
I'm your man.
Hi. I told him
I was sorry, but he...
I'm just
indifferent right now.
Hot towel?
You don't respect yourself,
so I know you
don't respect me.
I respect you.
I'm just your babysitter.
So, when you need
your diaper changed...
Thank you.
Let me know and
I'll get you a bottle, okay?
Hey! Heat up the sake,
will you?
Thanks for reminding me.
No, I'm not talking...
We're not drinking.
We're working right now.
You can't have
sashimi without sake.
You are constitutionally
incapable of
being responsible.
It would be
irresponsible not to drink.
I'm just talking
about a nightcap.
Hot sake?
Yes, two, please.
No.
I'm not drinking.
I don't want any.
That's what I'm
talking about.
When I get up in the morning
and I'm putting on my uniform,
you know what I recognize?
I see in that mirror that
every person that's got this
uniform on got my back!
Hey, you know what?
I'm not like you.
I'm not cut out...
No, no. You don't
have to be like me!
But you're more
than what you are.
Can you excuse me if
I'm a bit distracted here?
No! You can't be
distracted right now!
Listen to me!
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
General.
Welcome, Mr. Stark.
We look forward to
your weapons presentation.
Thanks.
(CHATTERING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Is it better to be
feared or respected?
I say, is it too
much to ask for both?
With that in mind,
I humbly present
the crown jewel
of Stark Industries'
Freedom Line.
It's the first
missile system
to incorporate
our proprietary
repulsor technology.
They say the best weapon
is one you never have to fire.
I respectfully disagree.
I prefer the weapon
you only have to fire once.
That's how Dad did it.
That's how America does it.
And it's worked out
pretty well so far.
Find an excuse
to let one of these
off the chain,
and I personally guarantee you
the bad guys won't even want
to come out of their caves.
For your consideration,
the Jericho.
I'll be throwing
one of these in
with every purchase
of 500 million or more.
To peace!
Tony.
Obie, what are you doing up?
I couldn't sleep till
I found out how it went.
How'd it go?
It went great.
Looks like it's gonna be
an early Christmas.
Hey! Way to go, my boy!
I'll see you tomorrow, yeah?
Why aren't you wearing
those pajamas I got you?
Good night, Tony.
(SIGHS)
Hey, Tony.
I'm sorry,
this is the "fun-vee."
The "hum-drum-vee"
is back there.
Nice job.
See you back at base.
(BACK IN BLACK PLAYING)
(SCREAMING ECHOING)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
(VESSEL CLATTERING)
(COUGHING)
(HUMMING)
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
(GROANS)
(WHISTLING)
What the hell
did you do to me?
(CHUCKLES)
What I did?
What I did is to
save your life.
I removed all
the shrapnel I could,
but there's a lot left,
and it's headed into
your atrial septum.
Here, want to see?
I have a souvenir.
Take a look.
I've seen many
wounds like that
in my village.
We call them
the walking dead
because it takes about
a week for the barbs to
reach the vital organs.
What is this?
That is an electromagnet,
hooked up to
a car battery,
and it's keeping
the shrapnel from
entering your heart. Hmm?
That's right. Smile.
We met once, you know,
at a technical
conference in Bern.
I don't remember.
No, you wouldn't.
If I had been that drunk,
I wouldn't have
been able to stand,
much less give a lecture
on integrated circuits.
Where are we?
(MAN SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
(SOFTLY) Come on,
stand up. Stand up!
Just do as I do.
Come on,
put your hands up.
Those are my guns.
How did they
get my guns?
Do you understand me?
Do as I do.
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
He says,
"Welcome, Tony Stark,
the most famous mass murderer
"in the history of America."
He is honored.
He wants you to
build the missile.
The Jericho missile
that you demonstrated.
This one.
I refuse.
(GROANING)
PEPPER: Tony!
(CLAMORING)
He wants to know
what you think.
I think you got
a lot of my weapons.
He says they have
everything you need
to build the Jericho missile.
He wants you to make
the list of materials.
He says for you
to start working immediately,
and when you're done,
he will set you free.
No, he won't.
I'm sure they're
looking for you, Stark.
But they will never find you
in these mountains.
Look, what you just saw,
that is your legacy, Stark.
Your life's work,
in the hands of
those murderers.
Is that how you
want to go out?
Is this the last
act of defiance
of the great Tony Stark?
Or are you going to
do something about it?
Why should I do anything?
They're going to kill me,
you, either way.
And if they don't,
I'll probably be
dead in a week.
Well, then,
this is a very
important week for you,
isn't it?
Hmm?
TONY: If this is going to be
my work station,
(YINSEN TRANSLATING)
I want it well-lit.
I want these up.
I need welding gear.
I don't care if it's
acetylene or propane.
I need a soldering station.
I need helmets.
I'm gonna need goggles.
I would like
a smelting cup.
I need two sets
of precision tools.
How many languages
do you speak?
A lot.
But apparently,
not enough for this place.
They speak Arabic, Urdu,
Dari, Pashto, Mongolian,
Farsi, Russian.
Who are these people?
They are your
loyal customers, sir.
They call
themselves the Ten Rings.
(CHATTERING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
You know,
we might be more productive
if you include me
in the planning process.
Uh-huh.
Okay, we don't need this.
What is that?
That's palladium,
0.15 grams.
We need at least 1.6,
so why don't you go
break down the other 11?
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
WHAT'S HE DOING?
(SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
WORKING.
Careful. Careful,
we only get one shot at this.
Relax. I have steady hands.
Why do you think
you're still alive? Huh?
What do I call you?
My name is Yinsen.
Yinsen.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
(EXCLAIMS)
That doesn't look
like a Jericho missile.
That's because
it's a miniaturized
arc reactor.
I got a big one
powering my factory
at home.
It should keep
the shrapnel
out of my heart.
But what could
it generate?
If my math is right,
and it always is,
three gigajoules per second.
That could run your heart
for 50 lifetimes.
Yeah. Or something
big for 15 minutes.
This is our
ticket out of here.
What is it?
Flatten them out and look.
Oh, wow.
Impressive.
(SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
YINSEN: (CHUCKLING) Good.
Good roll.
You still haven't told me
where you're from.
I'm from a small
town called Gulmira.
It's actually a nice place.
Got a family?
Yes, and I will see them
when I leave here.
And you, Stark?
No.
No?
So you're a man
who has everything
and nothing.
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
IT DOESN'T LOOK ANYTHING LIKE THE
PICTURE.
MAYBE IT'S BEEN MODIFIED.
THE TAIL IS WRONG.
IT'S JUST BACKWARDS.
(SHOUTS IN ARABIC)
Relax.
The bow and arrow
once was the pinnacle
of weapons technology.
It allowed the great
Genghis Khan
to rule from
the Pacific to
the Ukraine.
An empire twice the size
of Alexander the Great
and four times
the size of the
Roman Empire.
But today,
whoever holds
the latest Stark weapons
rules these lands.
And soon,
it will be my turn.
(SPEAKING IN URDU)
WHY HAVE YOU FAILED ME?
WE'RE WORKING.
DILIGENTLY.
I LET YOU LIVE.
THIS IS HOW YOU REPAY ME?
IT'S VERY COMPLEX.
HE'S TRYING VERY HARD.
ON HIS KNEES.
(CHUCKLING)
YOU THINK I'M A FOOL?
I'LL GET THE TRUTH.
WE'RE BOTH WORKING.
OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
What does he want?
YOU THINK I'M A FOOL?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
HE'S BUILDING YOUR JERICHO.
What do you want?
A delivery date?
I need him.
Good assistant.
You have till tomorrow
to assemble my missile.
(RAZA SPEAKING IN URDU)
Okay? Can you move?
Okay, say it again.
41 steps straight ahead.
Then 16 steps,
that's from the door,
fork right,
33 steps, turn right.
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
WHERE IS STARK?
HE WAS HERE A MOMENT AGO.
GO LOOK FOR HIM.
Yinsen! Yinsen! Stark!
Say something.
Say something back to him.
He's speaking Hungarian.
I don't...
Then speak Hungarian.
Okay. I know.
What do you know?
(SPEAKING IN HUNGARIAN)
(MAN SHOUTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
How'd that work?
Oh, my goodness.
It worked all right.
That's what I do.
Let me finish this.
Initialize the power sequence.
Okay.
Now!
Tell me.
Function 11.
Tell me when you
see a progress bar.
It should be up right now.
Yes.
Talk to me.
Tell me when
you see it.
I have it.
Press Control "I".
"I." Got it.
"I." "Enter."
"I" and "Enter."
Come over here
and button me up.
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
Okay. All right.
Every other hex bolt.
They're coming!
Nothing pretty,
just get it done.
Just get it done.
They're coming.
Make sure the checkpoints
are clear before you
follow me out, okay?
We need more time.
Hey,
I'm gonna go
buy you some time.
Stick to the plan!
Yinsen!
(CLAMORING)
(SCREAMING)
(GUNS COCKING)
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
(SUIT CLATTERING)
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
(SCREAMING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING STOPS)
(MAN SHOUTS IN URDU)
(COUGHING)
Yinsen!
Watch out!
Stark.
Come on.
We got to go.
Move for me, come on.
We got a plan.
We're gonna stick to it.
This was always
the plan, Stark.
Come on, you're gonna go
see your family. Get up.
My family is dead.
I'm going to see
them now, Stark.
It's okay.
I want this.
(SIGHS)
Thank you for saving me.
Don't waste it.
Don't waste your life.
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
My turn.
(CLAMORING)
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
Not bad.
Hey!
(EXCLAIMING)
How was the "fun-vee"?
Next time,
you ride with me, okay?
Watch it,
coming up here.
TONY: Are you
kidding me with this?
Get rid of them.
Hmm.
Your eyes are red.
A few tears for
your long-lost boss?
Tears of joy.
I hate job hunting.
Yeah, vacation's over.
Where to, sir?
Take us to the hospital,
please, Happy.
No.
No? Tony, you have to
go to the hospital.
No is a complete answer.
The doctor has
to look at you.
I don't have to do anything.
I've been in captivity
for three months.
There are two things
I want to do. I want
an American cheeseburger,
and the other...
That's enough of that.
...is not what you think.
I want you to call for
a press conference now.
Call for a press conference?
Yeah.
What on earth for?
Hogan, drive.
Cheeseburger first.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Look at this!
Tony.
We were going to
meet at the hospital.
No, I'm fine.
Look at you!
You had to have
a burger, yeah?
Well, come on.
You get me
one of those?
There's only one left.
I need it.
Hey, look
who's here! Yeah!
Miss Potts?
Yes.
Can I speak to
you for a moment?
I'm not part of
the press conference,
but it's about to
begin right now.
I'm not a reporter.
I'm Agent Phil Coulson,
with the Strategic Homeland
Intervention, Enforcement
and Logistics Division.
That's quite a mouthful.
I know.
We're working on it.
You know, we've been
approached already by
the DOD, the FBI, the CIA...
We're a separate division
with a more specific focus.
We need to debrief Mr. Stark
about the circumstances
of his escape.
I'll put something
in the book, shall I?
Thank you.
Uh...
Hey, would it be all right
if everyone sat down?
Why don't you just sit down?
That way you can
see me, and I can...
A little less formal and...
What's up with the love-in?
Don't look at me.
I don't know
what he's up to.
Good to see you.
I never got to say
goodbye to Dad.
goodbye to my father.
There's questions
that I would
have asked him.
I would have asked him
how he felt about
what this company did.
If he was conflicted,
if he ever had doubts.
Or maybe he was
every inch the man we all
remember from the newsreels.
I saw young
Americans killed
by the very weapons
I created to defend them
and protect them.
And I saw
that I had become part of
a system that is comfortable
with zero accountability.
Mr. Stark!
Hey, Ben.
What happened over there?
I had my eyes opened.
I came to realize
that I have more
to offer this world
than just making
things that blow up.
And that is why,
effective immediately,
I am shutting down
the weapons
manufacturing division
of Stark International
until such a time as I can
decide what the future
of the company will be.
I think we're
gonna be selling
a lot of newspapers.
What direction
it should take, one
that I'm comfortable with
and is consistent
with the highest good
for this country, as well.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
What we should
take away from this
is that Tony's back!
And he's healthier
than ever.
We're going to have
a little internal discussion
and we'll get back to you
with the follow-up.
Where is he?
He's inside.
Well, that...
That went well.
Did I just paint a target
on the back of my head?
Your head?
What about my head?
What do you think the
over-under on the stock drop
is gonna be tomorrow?
TONY: Uh, optimistically,
40 points.
At minimum.
Yep.
Tony, we're
a weapons manufacturer.
Obie, I just don't
want a body count
to be our only legacy.
That's what we do.
We're iron mongers.
We make weapons.
It's my name
on the side
of the building.
And what we do
keeps the world from
falling into chaos.
Not based on
what I saw.
We're not doing
a good enough job.
We can do better.
We're gonna do
something else.
Like what?
You want us to
make baby bottles?
I think we should take
another look into
arc reactor technology.
Ah, come on.
The arc reactor,
that's a publicity stunt!
Tony, come on.
We built that thing
to shut the hippies up!
It works.
Yeah, as a science project.
The arc was
never cost effective.
We knew that
before we built it.
Arc reactor technology,
that's a dead end, right?
Maybe.
Huh? Am I right?
We haven't had a breakthrough
in that in what?
30 years.
That's what they say.
Could you have
a lousier poker face?
Just tell me, who told you?
Never mind who told me.
Show me.
It's Rhodey or Pepper.
I want to see it.
Okay, Rhodey.
Okay.
Okay?
It works.
Listen to me, Tony.
We're a team.
Do you understand?
There's nothing we can't do
if we stick together,
like your father and I.
I'm sorry I didn't give you
a heads-up, okay?
But if I had...
Tony.
Tony, no more of this
"ready, fire, aim" business.
You understand me?
That was Dad's line.
You gotta let me
handle this.
We're gonna have to play
a whole different
kind of ball now.
We're going to have
to take a lot of heat.
I want you to promise me
that you're gonna lay low.
Stark Industries!
I've got one recommendation!
Ready? Ready?
Sell, sell, sell!
Abandon ship!
Does the Hindenburg
ring any bells?
(SCREAMING ON TV)
Let me show you the
new Stark Industries
business plan!
Look,
that's a weapons company
that doesn't make weapons!
(TOY GUN FIRING)
TONY: Pepper.
How big are your hands?
What?
I don't understand why...
Get down here. I need you.
Hey.
Let's see them.
Show me your hands.
Oh, wow. They are small.
Very petite, indeed.
I just need your
help for a sec.
Oh, my God, is that the thing
that's keeping you alive?
It was.
It is now an antique.
This is what will
be keeping me alive
for the foreseeable future.
I'm swapping it up
for an upgraded unit,
and I just ran into
a little speed bump.
Speed bump,
what does that mean?
It's nothing.
It's just a little snag.
There's an exposed wire
under this device.
And it's contacting the
socket wall and causing
a little bit of a short.
It's fine.
What do you want me to do?
Put that on
the table over there.
That is irrelevant.
Oh, my God!
I want you to reach in,
and you're just gonna
gently lift the wire out.
Is it safe?
Yeah, it should be fine.
It's like Operation.
You just don't let it touch
the socket wall
or it goes "beep."
What do you mean,
"Operation"?
It's just a game,
never mind.
Just gently lift the wire.
Okay? Great.
Okay.
You know,
I don't think that I'm
qualified to do this.
No, you're fine.
You're the most capable,
qualified,
trustworthy person
I've ever met.
You're gonna do great.
Is it too much of
a problem to ask?
'Cause I'm...
Okay, okay.
I really need your help here.
Okay.
Oh, there's pus!
It's not pus.
It's an inorganic plasmic
discharge from the device,
not from my body.
It smells!
Yeah, it does.
The copper wire.
The copper wire,
you got it?
Okay, I got it! I got it!
Okay, you got it?
Now, don't let it
(BUZZING)
touch the sides when
you're coming out!
I'm sorry.
That's what
I was trying to
tell you before.
Okay, now make sure
that when you pull
it out, you don't...
There's a magnet
at the end of it!
That was it.
(RAPID BEEPING)
You just pulled it out.
Oh, God!
Okay, I was not expecting...
Don't put it back in!
Okay, what do I do?
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just going into
cardiac arrest 'cause you
yanked it out like a trout...
What? You said it was safe!
We gotta hurry.
Take this. Take this.
You gotta switch
it out really quick.
Okay. Okay.
Tony? It's going to be okay.
What?
Is it?
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna make this okay.
Let's hope.
Okay, you're gonna attach
that to the base plate.
Make sure you...
(SCREAMS)
Was that so hard?
That was fun, right?
Here, I got it.
I got it. Here.
Nice.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I feel great.
You okay?
(LAUGHING)
Don't ever, ever, ever,
ever ask me to do
anything like that
ever again.
I don't have
anyone but you.
Anyway...
What do you want me
to do with this?
That?
Destroy it.
Incinerate it.
You don't want to keep it?
Pepper, I've been called
many things. "Nostalgic"
is not one of them.
Will that be all,
Mr. Stark?
That will be all,
Miss Potts.
Hey, Butterfingers,
come here.
What's all this stuff
doing on top of my desk?
That's my phone,
that's a picture
of me and my dad.
Right there.
In the garbage.
All that stuff.
RHODES:
The future of air combat.
Is it manned or unmanned?
I'll tell you,
in my experience,
no unmanned aerial vehicle
will ever trump
a pilot's instinct,
his insight,
that ability to look
into a situation
beyond the obvious
and discern its outcome,
or a pilot's judgment.
Colonel?
Why not a pilot
without the plane?
Look who fell
out of the sky.
Mr. Tony Stark.
Hello, sir.
Speaking of
manned or unmanned,
you gotta get him
to tell you about the
time he guessed wrong
at spring break.
Just remember that,
spring break, 1987.
That lovely lady
you woke up with.
Don't do that!
What was his name?
Don't do that.
Was it Ivan?
They'll believe it.
Don't do that.
Okay.
Pleasure meeting you.
Give us a couple minutes,
you guys.
(CHATTERING)
I'm surprised.
Why?
I swear,
I didn't expect to see you
walking around so soon.
I'm doing a little
better than walking.
Really?
Yeah.
Rhodey, I'm working on
something big.
I came to talk to you.
I want you to be a part of it.
You're about to make
a whole lot of people
around here real happy,
'cause that little stunt
at the press conference,
that was a doozy.
This is not for the military.
I'm not... It's different.
What? You're
a humanitarian now
or something?
I need you to listen to me.
No.
What you need is time
to get your mind right.
I'm serious.
Okay.
It's nice seeing you, Tony.
Thanks.
Jarvis, you up?
For you, sir, always.
I'd like to open
a new project file,
index as Mark II.
Shall I store this on
the Stark Industries
Central Database?
Actually, I don't know
who to trust right now.
Till further notice,
why don't we just
keep everything
on my private server?
Working on
a secret project,
are we, sir?
I don't want this winding up
in the wrong hands.
Maybe in mine,
it can actually
do some good.
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Next. Up.
Not in the boot, Dummy.
Right here. You got me?
Stay put. Nice.
You're of no benefit at all.
Move down to the toe.
I got this.
Okay, I'm sorry,
am I in your way?
Up.
Screw it. Don't even move.
You are a tragedy.
Okay, let's do this right.
Start mark, half a meter,
and back and center.
Dummy, look alive.
You're on standby
for fire safety.
You, roll it.
Okay. Activate
hand controls.
(POWERING UP)
We're gonna start
off nice and easy.
We're gonna see if
10% thrust capacity
achieves lift.
And three,
two,
one.
(GROANING)
Up two.
All right, set that.
I've been buzzing you.
Did you hear the intercom?
Yeah, everything's... What?
Obadiah's upstairs.
Great!
What would you
like me to tell him?
Great. I'll be right up.
Okay.
I thought you said
you were done making weapons.
It is.
This is a flight stabilizer.
It's completely harmless.
I didn't expect that.
(OBADIAH PLAYING PIANO)
How'd it go?
It went that bad, huh?
Just because I brought
pizza back from New York
doesn't mean it went bad.
Uh-huh. Sure doesn't. Oh, boy.
It would have gone better
if you were there.
Uh-uh.
You told me to lay low.
That's what I've been doing.
I lay low, and you
take care of all...
Hey, come on.
In public.
The press.
This was a board of
directors meeting.
directors meeting?
The board is claiming
you have posttraumatic stress.
They're filing an injunction.
A what?
They want to lock you out.
Why, 'cause the stocks
dipped 40 points?
We knew that
was gonna happen.
Fifty-six and a half.
It doesn't matter.
We own the
controlling interest
in the company.
Tony, the board
has rights, too.
They're making
the case that you
and your new direction
isn't in the company's
best interest.
I'm being responsible!
That's a new
direction for me,
for the company.
I mean, me on the company's
behalf being responsible
for the way that...
This is great.
Oh, come on.
Tony. Tony.
I'll be in the shop.
Hey, hey!
Hey, Tony. Listen.
I'm trying to turn this
thing around, but you
gotta give me something.
Something to pitch them.
Let me have
the engineers analyze that.
You know, draw up some specs.
No. No, absolutely not.
It'll give me
a bone to throw the boys
in New York!
This one stays with me.
That's it, Obie.
Forget it.
All right, well,
this stays with me, then.
Go on, here,
you can have a piece.
Take two.
Thank you.
You mind if I come down there
and see what you're doing?
Good night, Obie.
Day 11,
test 37, configuration 2.0.
For lack of a better option,
Dummy is still on fire safety.
If you douse me again,
and I'm not on fire,
I'm donating you
to a city college.
All right,
nice and easy.
Seriously,
just gonna start off
with 1% thrust capacity.
And three, two, one.
Okay.
Please don't
follow me around
with it, either,
'cause I feel like I'm gonna
catch on fire spontaneously.
Just stand down!
If something happens,
then come in.
And again,
let's bring it up to 2.5.
Three, two, one.
(GRUNTING)
Okay, this is where
I don't want to be!
Oh, not the car,
not the car!
(EXCLAIMS)
Table!
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
Could be worse!
We're fine! Okay.
No! Uh-uh! Uh-uh! Uh!
Yeah, I can fly.
Jarvis, are you there?
At your service, sir.
Engage Heads Up Display.
Check.
Import all preferences
from home interface.
Will do, sir.
All right,
what do you say?
I have indeed
been uploaded, sir.
We're online and ready.
Can we start
the virtual walk-around?
Importing preferences
and calibrating
virtual environment.
Do a check on
control surfaces.
As you wish.
Test complete.
Preparing to power down
and begin diagnostics.
Uh, yeah. Tell you what.
Do a weather and ATC check.
Start listening in
on ground control.
Sir, there are
still terabytes
of calculations needed
before an actual flight is...
Jarvis!
Sometimes you got to run
before you can walk.
Ready? In three, two, one.
(EXCLAIMING)
(WHOOPING)
Handles like a dream.
All right, let's see what
this thing can do.
What's SR-71's record?
The altitude record
for fixed wing flight
is 85,000 feet, sir.
Records are made
to be broken! Come on!
Sir, there is
a potentially fatal
buildup of ice occurring.
Keep going!
Higher!
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
We iced up, Jarvis!
Deploy flaps! Jarvis!
Come on,
we got to break the ice!
(HONKING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Kill power.
(CHATTERING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Notes. Main transducer
feels sluggish at
plus 40 altitude.
Hull pressurization
is problematic.
I'm thinking icing
is the probable factor.
JARVIS: A very astute
observation, sir.
Perhaps, if you intend
to visit other planets,
we should improve
the exosystems.
Connect to the sys. co.
Have it reconfigure
the shell metals.
Use the gold titanium alloy
from the seraphim
tactical satellite.
That should ensure
a fuselage integrity
while maintaining
power-to-weight ratio.
Got it?
Yes.
Shall I render using
proposed specifications?
Thrill me.
REPORTER ON TV:
Tonight's red-hot red carpet
is right here at
the Disney Concert Hall,
where Tony Stark's
third annual benefit
for the Firefighter's
Family Fund
has become the place to be
for L.A.'s high society.
Jarvis, we get an
invite for that?
JARVIS: I have no record
of an invitation, sir.
WOMAN ON TV:
...hasn't been seen
in public
since his bizarre
and highly controversial
press conference.
Some claim he's suffering
from posttraumatic stress
and has been
bedridden for weeks.
Whatever the case may be,
no one expects
an appearance
from him tonight.
JARVIS:
The render is complete.
A little ostentatious,
don't you think?
What was I thinking?
You're usually so discreet.
Tell you what.
Throw a little
hot-rod red in there.
Yes, that should help you
keep a low profile.
The render is complete.
Hey, I like it.
Fabricate it. Paint it.
Commencing
automated assembly.
Estimated completion
time is five hours.
Don't wait up for me, honey.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Weapons manufacturing
is only one small part of
what Stark Industries
is all about,
and our partnership
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
with the fire and
rescue community...
Hey, Tony,
remember me?
Sure don't.
You look great, Hef.
We're going to
have a great quarter.
What's the world coming to
when a guy's got to
crash his own party?
Look at you.
Hey, what a surprise.
I'll see you inside.
Hey. Listen,
take it slow,
all right?
I think I got the board
right where we want them.
You got it.
Just cabin fever.
I'll just be a minute.
Give me a Scotch.
I'm starving.
Mr. Stark?
Yeah?
Agent Coulson.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The guy from the...
Strategic Homeland
Intervention, Enforcement
and Logistics Division.
(SIGHS) God, you need
a new name for that.
Yeah, I hear that a lot.
Listen, I know this must be
a trying time for you,
but we need to debrief you.
There's still a lot of
unanswered questions,
and time can be a factor
with these things.
Let's just put
something on the books.
How about
the 24th at 7:00 p.m.
at Stark Industries?
Tell you what. You got it.
You're absolutely right.
Well, I'm going to
go to my assistant,
and we'll make a date.
You look fantastic!
I didn't recognize you.
What are you doing here?
Just avoiding
government agents.
Are you by yourself?
Yes. Where'd you
get that dress?
Oh, it was
a birthday present.
That's great.
From you, actually.
Well, I got great taste.
Yes.
You want to dance?
Oh, no.
All right, come on.
Thank you. No.
Am I making you
uncomfortable?
No. No. I always forget
to wear deodorant and
dance with my boss
in front of
everyone that I work with
in a dress with no back.
You look great
and you smell great.
Oh, God.
But I could fire
you if that would
take the edge off.
I actually don't think
that you could tie
your shoes without me.
I'd make it a week. Sure.
Really?
What's your
Social Security number?
Five.
Five?
Right.
You're missing just
a couple of digits there.
The other eight?
So I got you for
the other eight.
How about a little air?
Yes, I need some air.
(CLEARS THROAT)
That was totally weird.
Totally harmless.
It was totally
not harmless,
by the way.
We're dancing.
No one's even watching.
Everybody who I work with...
No, you know why?
I think you lost objectivity.
I think they just...
People... We just danced.
No, it was not just a dance.
You don't understand
because you're you.
And everybody knows
exactly who you are
and how you are with girls
and all of that,
which is completely fine.
But, you know,
then me, you're my boss,
and I'm dancing with you.
I don't think it
was taken that way.
Because it makes me look like
the one who's trying to...
I just think
you're overstating it.
You know, and we're here,
and then I'm wearing
this ridiculous
dress, and then we were
dancing like that and...
I would like a drink, please.
Got it, okay.
I would like
a vodka martini, please.
Okay.
Very dry with olives,
a lot of olives.
Like, at least three olives.
Two vodka martinis,
extra dry, extra olives,
extra fast.
Make one of them dirty,
will you?
Wow. Tony Stark.
Oh, hey.
Fancy seeing you here.
Carrie.
Christine.
That's right.
You have a lot of nerve
showing up here tonight.
Can I at least get
a reaction from you?
Panic. I would say
panic is my reaction.
'Cause I was referring
to your company's
involvement in
this latest atrocity.
Yeah. They just put my name
on the invitation.
I don't know
what to tell you.
I actually almost bought it,
hook, line and sinker.
I was out of town
for a couple months,
in case you didn't hear.
Is this what you
call accountability?
It's a town
called Gulmira.
Heard of it?
When were these taken?
Yesterday.
I didn't approve
any shipment.
Well, your company did.
Well, I'm not my company.
Please, do you mind?
Have you seen
these pictures? Huh?
What's going on in Gulmira?
Tony, Tony.
You can't afford
to be this naive.
You know what?
I was naive before,
when they said,
"Here's the line.
We don't cross it.
"This is how
we do business."
If we're double-dealing
under the table... Are we?
MAN: Tony,
your picture, please!
Let's take a picture.
Come on. Picture time!
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Tony. Who do you think
locked you out?
I was the one who filed
the injunction against you.
It was the only way
I could protect you.
No. No.
The 15-mile hike to
the outskirts of Gulmira
can only be described
as a descent into hell,
into a modern day
Heart of Darkness.
Simple farmers and herders
from peaceful villages
have been driven
from their homes,
displaced from their lands
by warlords
emboldened by
a new-found power.
Villagers have been forced
to take shelter in
whatever crude dwellings
they can find in the ruins
of other villages,
or here in the remnants
of an old Soviet
smelting plant.
Recent violence has been
attributed to a group of
foreign fighters
referred to by locals
as the Ten Rings.
As you can see,
these men are heavily armed
and on a mission.
A mission that could
prove fatal to anyone
who stands in their way.
With no political will
or international pressure,
there's very little hope
for these refugees.
Around me, a woman begging
for news on her husband,
who was kidnapped
by insurgents,
either forced to
join their militia...
Desperate refugees clutch
yellowed photographs,
holding them up to anyone
who will stop.
A child's simple question,
"Where are
my mother and father?"
There's very little hope
for these refugees,
refugees who can
only wonder who,
if anyone, will help.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING IN ARABIC)
HURRY IT UP.
PUT THE WOMEN IN THE TRUCKS.
STACK THE WEAPONS HERE.
CLEAR ALL THE HOUSES.
THAT ONE THERE.
FASTER. FASTER.
GRAB THAT DOG.
PUT HIM WITH THE OTHERS.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
SHOOT THIS DOG.
YOU'RE ALL INCOMPETENT.
TURN YOUR HEAD!
(SHOUTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(RUMBLING)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
He's all yours.
What the hell was that?
Were we cleared
to go in there?
EDWARDS AIR FORCE BASE,
CALIFORNIA
No, they were
using human shields.
We never got the green light.
Put me through to State.
They're going to
be all over this.
MAN 1: Get those monitors up!
We got a bogey!
MAN 2: Wasn't Air Force!
We got the CIA on the line?
I've got Langley on the line.
They want to know if it's us.
No, it definitely
is not us, sir!
It wasn't Navy.
Wasn't Marines.
I need answers!
Can I please get
eyes on target?
MAN 3: Negative, negative.
MAN 4: Cannot identify.
Get me Colonel Rhodes
from Weapons Development
down here now!
We ran an ID check
and cross-referenced
with all known databases.
We have nothing.
Any high altitude
surveillance
in the region?
We got an AWAC
and a Global Hawk
in the area.
So this thing just
appeared out of nowhere?
How come it didn't
show up on the radar?
Got a minimal radar
cross-section, sir.
Is it stealth?
No, sir, it's tiny.
We think it's an unmanned
aerial vehicle.
Colonel, what are
we dealing with here?
Let me make a call.
Sergeant, clear a hole.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Tony?
Who's this?
It's Rhodes.
Sorry, hello?
I said it's Rhodes.
Speak up, please.
What in the hell
is that noise?
Oh, yeah, I'm driving
with the top down.
Yeah, well,
I need your help right now.
It's funny how
that works, huh?
Yeah. Speaking of funny,
we've got a weapons depot
that was just blown up
a few clicks from where
you were being held captive.
Well, that's a hot spot.
Sounds like someone
stepped in and did
your job for you, huh?
Why do you sound
out of breath, Tony?
I'm not, I was just
jogging in the canyon.
I thought you were driving.
Right, I was driving
to the canyon,
where I'm going to jog.
You sure you don't have
any tech in that area
I should know about?
Nope!
MAN: Bogey spotted!
MAJOR ALLEN:
Whiplash, come in hot.
Okay, good,
'cause I'm staring at one
right now,
and it's about to be
blown to kingdom come.
That's my exit.
Ballroom, this is
Whiplash One. I've got
the bogey in my sights.
Whiplash One,
what is it?
I've got no idea.
MAJOR ALLEN:
You have radio contact?
Non responsive, sir.
Then you are
clear to engage.
TONY: Hit it.
That bogey just
went supersonic.
I got a lock!
JARVIS: Inbound missile.
TONY: Flares!
Wait a second.
Bogey deployed flares!
(EXCLAIMS)
(SHOUTS)
(GRUNTING)
Deploy flaps!
Holy!
That thing just
jumped off the radar, sir.
The sat visual
has been lost.
No way that's a UAV.
What is it?
I can't see anything.
Whatever it was,
it just bought the farm.
I think bogey's
been handled, sir.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
TONY: Hi, Rhodey, it's me.
It's who?
I'm sorry, it is me.
You asked.
What you were
asking about is me.
No, see,
this isn't a game.
You do not send
civilian equipment
into my active war zone.
You understand that?
This is not
a piece of equipment.
I'm in it.
It's a suit.
It's me!
Rhodey, you got
anything for me?
MAJOR ALLEN:
Mark your position
and return to base.
Roger that, Ballroom.
On your belly!
It looks like a man!
Shake him off!
Roll! Roll!
I'm hit! I'm hit!
MAN 4: It's confirmed.
He has been hit.
WHIPLASH TWO:
Punch out! Punch out!
Whiplash One down.
Whiplash Two,
do you see a chute?
Negative! No chute, no chute!
(WHIPLASH ONE GROANING)
My chute's jammed!
Sir, I've got
a visual on the bogey.
Whiplash Two, reengage.
If you get a clear shot,
you take it.
Major, we don't even know
what we're shooting at.
Call off the Raptors.
That thing just
took out an F-22
inside a legal no fly zone!
Whiplash Two, if you have
a clear shot, take it!
JARVIS: You've been reengaged.
Execute evasive maneuver.
Keep going!
WHIPLASH ONE:
Good chute! Good chute!
(ALL CHEERING)
Tony, you still there?
Hey, thanks.
Oh, my God,
you crazy son of a bitch.
You owe me a plane.
You know that, right?
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah, well,
technically, he hit me.
Now are you going to come by
and see what I'm working on?
No, no, no, no, no, no,
the less I know, the better.
Now, what am I supposed
to tell the press?
TONY: Training exercise.
Isn't that the usual BS?
RHODES: It's not that simple.
An unfortunate
training exercise
involving an F-22 Raptor
occurred yesterday.
I am pleased to report
that the pilot
was not injured.
As for the unexpected
turn of events on the
ground in Gulmira,
it is still unclear
who or what intervened,
but I can assure you that
the United States government
was not involved.
TONY: Hey!
(GROANING)
JARVIS:
It is a tight fit, sir.
Sir, the more you struggle,
the more this
is going to hurt.
Be gentle.
This is my first time.
I designed this to
come off, so...
(GROANS) Hey.
I really should be
able to...
JARVIS: Please,
try not to move, sir.
What's going on here?
Let's face it.
This is not the worst thing
you've caught me doing.
Are those bullet holes?
(CHATTERING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Welcome.
Compliments of Tony Stark.
If you'd killed him
when you were supposed to,
you'd still have a face.
You paid us trinkets
to kill a prince.
Show me the weapon.
Come. Leave your
guards outside.
His escape bore
unexpected fruit.
So this is
how he did it.
This is only a first,
crude effort.
Stark has
perfected his design.
He has made
a masterpiece of death.
A man with a dozen of these
can rule all of Asia.
And you dream of
Stark's throne.
We have a common enemy.
If we are still
in business,
I will give you
these designs
as a gift.
And in turn,
I hope you'll repay me with
a gift of iron soldiers.
(HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING)
(GASPING)
(SPEAKING IN URDU)
THIS IS THE ONLY GIFT
YOU SHALL RECEIVE.
Technology.
It's always been
your Achilles' heel
in this part of the world.
Don't worry.
It'll only last
for 15 minutes.
That's the least
of your problems.
Crate up the armor
and the rest of it.
All right,
let's finish up here.
(GUNS FIRING)
Set up Sector 16
underneath the arc reactor,
and I'm going to
want this data masked.
Recruit our top engineers.
I want a prototype
right away.
Hey. You busy?
You mind if I send
you on an errand?
I need you to
go to my office.
You're going to hack
into the mainframe and
you're going to retrieve all
the recent
shipping manifests.
This is a lock chip.
This'll get you in.
It's probably
under Executive Files.
If not,
they put it on a ghost drive,
in which case you need
to look for the lowest
numeric heading.
And what do you plan to
do with this information
if I bring it back here?
Same drill.
They've been
dealing under the table,
and I'm going to stop them.
I'm going to find my weapons
and destroy them.
Tony,
you know that
I would help you
with anything,
but I cannot help you
if you're going to start
all of this again.
There is nothing except this.
There's no art opening.
There is no benefit.
There is nothing to sign.
There is the next mission
and nothing else.
Is that so?
Well, then, I quit.
You stood by my side
all these years
while I reaped
the benefits
of destruction.
And now that I'm trying
to protect the people
that I put in harm's way,
you're going to walk out?
You're going to
kill yourself, Tony.
I'm not going
to be a part of it.
I shouldn't be alive,
unless it was
for a reason.
I'm not crazy,
Pepper.
I just finally know
what I have to do.
And I know in my heart
that it's right.
(EXHALES)
You're all I have,
too, you know.
Sector 16?
What are you
up to, Obadiah?
(SPEAKING IN URDU)
You did not tell us that
the target you paid us to kill
was the great Tony Stark.
As you can see,
Obadiah Stane...
Oh, my God.
...your deception and lies
will cost you dearly.
The price to kill Tony Stark
has just gone up.
So, what are we
going to do about this?
Hmm?
I know what you're
going through, Pepper.
Tony. He always
gets the good stuff,
doesn't he?
I was so happy
when he came home.
It was like
we got him back
from the dead.
Now I realize,
well, Tony never really did
come home, did he?
He left a part of
himself in that cave.
Breaks my heart.
Well, he's
a complicated person.
He's been through a lot.
I think he'll be all right.
You are a very rare woman.
Tony doesn't know
how lucky he is.
Thank you. Thanks.
I'd better get
back there.
Is that today's paper?
Yes.
Do you mind?
Not at all.
Puzzle.
Of course.
Take care.
(EXCLAIMS)
Ms. Potts?
We had an appointment.
Did you forget
about our appointment?
Nope, right now.
Come with me.
Right now?
We're going to
have it right now.
Yeah, walk with me.
Okay.
I'm going to
give you the meeting
of your life. Your office.
Yeah, we've been working
our best to do it.
Absolutely, we're...
I'm going to have
to call you back.
Mr. Stane?
Sir, we've explored
what you've asked us,
and it seems as though
there's a little hiccup.
Actually...
A hiccup?
Yes, to power the suit, sir,
the technology
actually doesn't exist.
So it's...
Wait, wait, wait.
The technology?
William, here is
the technology.
I've asked you to
simply make it smaller.
Okay, sir, and that's what
we're trying to do, but
honestly, it's impossible.
Tony Stark was able to
build this in a cave!
With a box of scraps!
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm not Tony Stark.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING)
PEPPER: Tony?
Tony, are you there?
Hello?
Breathe.
Easy, easy.
You remember
this one, right?
It's a shame the government
didn't approve it.
There's so many
applications for causing
short-term paralysis.
Ah, Tony.
When I ordered
the hit on you,
I worried that I was
killing the golden goose.
But, you see, it was just
(GASPING)
fate that you survived that.
You had one last
golden egg to give.
Do you really think
that just because you have
an idea, it belongs to you?
Your father,
he helped give us
the atomic bomb.
Now, what kind of world
would it be today if he
was as selfish as you?
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, Tony,
this is your
Ninth Symphony.
Ah. What a masterpiece.
Look at that.
This is your legacy.
A new generation of weapons
with this at its heart.
Weapons that will
help steer the world
back on course,
put the balance of
power in our hands.
The right hands.
I wish you could
see my prototype.
It's not as...
Well, not as
conservative as yours.
Too bad you had to
involve Pepper in this.
I would have preferred
that she lived.
What do you mean,
he paid to have
Tony killed?
Pepper, slow down.
Why would Obadiah...
Okay, where's Tony now?
I don't know.
He's not answering his phone.
Please go over there
and make sure
everything's okay.
Thank you, Rhodey.
I know a shortcut.
(HEART BEATING RHYTHMICALLY)
(DUMMY APPROACHING)
Good boy.
Tony?
Tony!
Tony! You okay?
Where's Pepper?
She's fine.
She's with five agents.
They're about to
arrest Obadiah.
That's not
going to be enough.
Section 16.
There it is.
(BEEPS)
My key's not working.
It's not opening the door.
Oh, wow! What's that?
It's, like, a little device?
It's, like, a thing
that's going to
pick the lock?
You might want to take
a few steps back.
That's the coolest
thing I've ever seen.
Not bad, huh?
Let's do it.
You need me to
do anything else?
Keep the skies clear.
Damn!
Next time, baby.
Looks like you were right.
He was building a suit.
I thought it'd be bigger.
(JINGLING)
(SCREAMS)
AGENT: Take him out!
How do you think the
Mark I chest piece
is going to hold up?
JARVIS: The suit's at 48%
power and falling, sir.
That chest piece
was never designed
for sustained flight.
Keep me posted.
TONY: Pepper!
Tony! Tony,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
How are...
Obadiah, he's gone insane!
I know.
Listen, you'd
better get out of there.
He built a suit.
(RUMBLING)
Get out of there right now!
Where do you think
you're going?
(SHOUTS)
Your services are
no longer required.
TONY: Stane!
(SCREAMING)
(HONKS)
I love this suit!
Put them down!
Collateral damage, Tony.
Divert power
to chest RT.
JARVIS: Power reduced to 19%.
Lady!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
For 30 years,
I've been holding you up!
I built this company
from nothing!
Nothing is going
to stand in my way.
Least of all you!
Impressive!
You've upgraded
your armor!
I've made some
upgrades of my own!
JARVIS: Sir, it appears
that his suit can fly.
Duly noted. Take me
to maximum altitude.
JARVIS: With only 15% power,
the odds of reaching that...
TONY: I know the math! Do it!
Sir, you're not
going to believe this.
That thing is back.
Get me Major Allen.
Scramble the jets!
Not necessary, people.
Just a training exercise.
Yes, sir.
JARVIS: Thirteen percent
power, sir.
Climb!
Eleven percent.
Keep going!
Seven percent power.
Just leave it on the screen!
Stop telling me!
You had a great idea,
Tony, but my suit is
more advanced in every way!
How'd you solve
the icing problem?
Icing problem?
Might want to
look into it.
JARVIS: Two percent.
We are now running
on emergency backup power.
Whoa!
Potts!
Tony! Oh, my God,
are you okay?
I'm almost out of power.
I've got to get out of this
thing. I'll be right there.
Nice try!
(GRUNTS)
TONY: Weapons status?
JARVIS:
Repulsors offline.
Missiles offline.
Flares!
(GROANING)
Very clever, Tony.
Potts?
Tony!
This isn't working.
We're going to have to
overload the reactor
and blast the roof.
Well, how are you
going to do that?
You're going to do it.
Go to the central console,
open up all the circuits.
When I get clear of the roof,
I'll let you know.
You're going to hit
the master bypass button.
It's going to fry
everything up here.
Okay. I'm going in now.
Make sure you wait
till I clear the roof.
I'll buy you some time.
TONY: This looks important!
I never had a taste
for this sort of thing,
but I must admit,
I'm deeply enjoying the suit!
You finally
outdid yourself, Tony!
You'd have made
your father proud!
It's ready, Tony!
Get off the roof!
(GROANING)
(SCREAMS)
PEPPER: Tony!
How ironic, Tony!
Trying to rid
the world of weapons,
you gave it
its best one ever!
Pepper!
And now I'm going
to kill you with it!
You ripped out my
targeting system!
Time to hit the button!
You told me not to!
Hold still,
you little prick!
Just do it!
You'll die!
Push it!
(SCREAMING)
PEPPER: Tony!
You've all received
the official statement
of what occurred
at Stark Industries
last night.
There have been unconfirmed
reports that a robotic
prototype malfunctioned
and caused damage
to the arc reactor.
Fortunately, a member
of Tony Stark's
personal security staff...
"Iron Man."
That's kind of catchy.
It's got a nice ring to it.
I mean, it's not
technically accurate.
The suit's
a gold-titanium alloy,
but it's kind of evocative,
the imagery, anyway.
Here's your alibi.
Okay.
You were on your yacht.
Yeah.
We have port papers
that put you in
Avalon all night,
and sworn statements
from 50 of your guests.
See, I was thinking
maybe we should say
it was just Pepper and me
alone on the island.
That's what happened.
All right.
Just read it,
word for word.
There's nothing
about Stane here.
That's being handled.
He's on vacation.
Small aircraft have such
a poor safety record.
But what about
the whole cover story
that it's a bodyguard?
He's my... I mean, is that...
That's kind of flimsy,
don't you think?
This isn't
my first rodeo,
Mr. Stark.
Just stick to
the official statement,
and soon,
this will all
be behind you.
You've got 90 seconds.
Oh, Agent Coulson?
I just wanted to say
thank you very much
for all of your help.
That's what we do.
You'll be hearing from us.
From the Strategic Homeland...
Just call us S.H.I.E.L.D.
Right.
Let's get this
show on the road.
You know,
it's actually
not that bad.
Even I don't think
I'm Iron Man.
You're not Iron Man.
Am so.
You're not.
All right,
suit yourself.
You know, if I were Iron Man,
I'd have this girlfriend
who knew my true identity.
She'd be a wreck,
'cause she'd always
be worrying
that I was going to die,
yet so proud of
the man I'd become.
She'd be wildly conflicted,
which would only make her more
(CLEARS THROAT)
crazy about me.
Tell me you never
think about that night.
What night?
You know.
Are you talking about
the night that we danced
and went up on the roof,
and then you went downstairs
to get me a drink,
and you left me there,
by myself?
Is that the night
you're talking about?
Mmm-hmm.
Thought so.
Will that be all, Mr. Stark?
Yes, that will be all,
Miss Potts.
And now, Mr. Stark has
prepared a statement.
He will not be
taking any questions.
Thank you.
Been a while since
I was in front of you.
I figure I'll stick
to the cards this time.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
There's been speculation
that I was involved in
the events that occurred
on the freeway
and the rooftop...
I'm sorry, Mr. Stark,
but do you honestly
expect us to believe that
that was a bodyguard
in a suit that
conveniently appeared,
despite the fact that you...
I know that it's confusing.
It is one thing to question
the official story,
and another thing entirely
to make wild accusations,
or insinuate
that I'm a superhero.
I never said
you were a superhero.
Didn't?
Mmm-mmm.
Well, good,
because that would be
outlandish and fantastic.
(TONY SIGHS)
I'm just not
the hero type.
Clearly.
With this laundry list
of character defects,
all the mistakes I've made,
largely public.
(SOFTLY) Just stick to
the cards, man.
Yeah, okay. Yeah.
The truth is
I am Iron Man.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Jarvis!
Welcome home, sir.
"I am Iron Man."
You think you're the only
superhero in the world?
Mr. Stark,
you've become part
of a bigger universe.
You just don't
know it yet.
Who the hell are you?
Nick Fury,
Director of S.H.I.E.L.D.
Ah.
I'm here
to talk to you about
the Avenger Initiative.