THE OTHER:
The Tesseract has awakened.
It is on a little world,
a human world.
They would wield its power,
but our ally
knows its workings
as they never will.
He is ready to lead
and our force,
our Chitauri,
will follow.
A world will be his.
The universe, yours.
And the humans,
what can they do but burn?
AGENT ON PA: All personnel,
the evacuation order
has been confirmed.
[CONTINUES
GIVING INSTRUCTIONS]
[DIRECTING AGENTS]
How bad is it?
That's the problem, sir.
We don't know.
Dr. Selvig read
an energy surge
from the Tesseract
four hours ago.
NASA didn't authorize Selvig
to go to test phase.
He wasn't testing it.
He wasn't even in the room.
Spontaneous event.
It just turned itself on?
Where are
the energy levels now?
Climbing. When Selvig
couldn't shut it down,
we ordered evac.
How long to get
everyone out?
Campus should be clear
in the next half-hour.
Do better.
HILL:
Sir, evacuation
may be futile.
FURY: We should tell them
to go back to sleep?
HILL: If we can't control
the Tesseract's energy,
there may not be
a minimum safe distance.
I need you to make sure
the Phase 2 prototypes
are shipped out.
Sir, is that really
a priority right now?
Until such time
as the world ends,
we will act as though
it intends to spin on.
Clear out the tech below.
Every piece of Phase 2
on a truck and gone.
Yes, sir.
With me.
Talk to me, Doctor.
Director.
FURY: Is there anything
we know for certain?
SELVIG:
The Tesseract is misbehaving.
Is that supposed to be funny?
No, it's not funny at all.
The Tesseract is not only
active, she's...behaving.
FURY:
I assume you pulled the plug.
SELVIG:
She's an energy source.
We turn off the power,
she turns it back on.
If she reaches peak level...
We prepared for this, Doctor.
Harnessing energy from space.
But we don't
have the harness.
My calculations
are far from complete.
And she's throwing off
interference, radiation.
Nothing harmful,
low levels of
gamma radiation.
That can be harmful.
Where's Agent Barton?
[SCOFFS] The Hawk?
Up in his nest, as usual.
FURY ON RADIO:
Agent Barton, report.
I gave you this detail
so you could keep
a close eye on things.
Well, I see better
from a distance.
Have you seen
anything that might
set this thing off?
Doctor, it's spiking again.
BARTON:
No one's come or gone.
And Selvig's clean.
No contacts, no IMs.
If there was any tampering,sir, it wasn't at this end.
"At this end"?
Yeah, the Cube is
a doorway to the other
end of space, right?
Doors open from both sides.
Not yet.
[ENERGY CRACKLING]
[RUMBLING]
Sir, please put down
the spear.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
You have heart.
[GROANING]
LOKI: Please don't.
I still need that.
This doesn't have
to get any messier.
LOKI: Of course it does.
I've come too far
for anything else.
I am Loki, of Asgard,
and I am burdened with
glorious purpose.
Loki,
brother of Thor.
We have no quarrel
with your people.
An ant has no quarrel
with a boot.
Are you planning
to step on us?
I come with glad tidings
of a world made free.
Free from what?
Freedom.
Freedom is life's
great lie.
Once you accept that,
in your heart,
[GASPS]
you will know peace.
Yeah, you say "peace,"
I kind of think
you mean the other thing.
Sir, Director Fury
is stalling.
This place is about to blow
and drop a hundred feet
of rock on us.
He means to bury us.
Like the pharaohs of old.
SELVIG: He's right.
The portal is
collapsing in on itself.
We've got maybe two minutes
before this goes critical.
Well, then.
[GROANS]
I need these vehicles.
Who's that?
BARTON: They didn't tell me.
FURY ON RADIO: Hill!
Do you copy?
Barton has turned.
[GRUNTS]
They have the Tesseract!
Shut them down!
[ALL GROANING]
Okay, let's go.
No, leave it. Go!
We're clear upstairs, sir.
You need to go.
[ALL GRUNT]
[GRUNTS]
COULSON ON RADIO:
Director?
Director Fury,
do you copy?
The Tesseract is with
a hostile force.
I have men down. Hill?
A lot of men still under.
I don't know
how many survivors.
FURY: Sound a general call.
I want every living soul
not working rescue
looking for that briefcase.
Roger that.
Coulson, get back to base.
This is a Level Seven.
As of right now,
we are at war.
What do we do?
[GROANS]
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
...you may have
to write it down.
[GROANS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[ANSWERS IN RUSSIAN]
COULSON: You're at 1-14
Silensky Plaza, 3rd floor.
We have an F-22
exactly eight miles out.
Put the woman on the phone,  or I will blow up the block
before you can make the lobby.
We need you to come in.
Are you kidding? I'm working.
This takes precedence.
I'm in the middle of
an interrogation.
This moron
is giving me everything.
I don't...give everything.
Look, you can't pull me
out of this right now.
Natasha,
Barton's been compromised.
Let me put you on hold.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[SOUNDS OF GROANING ON PHONE]
[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[CRIES OUT IN PAIN]
ROMANOFF:
Where is Barton now?
We don't know.
But he's alive?
We think so.
I'll brief you on everything
when you get back.
But first, we need you
to talk to the big guy.
Coulson, you know that
Stark trusts me
about as far as
he can throw me.
Oh, I've got Stark.
You get the big guy.
[EXCLAIMS IN RUSSIAN]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[MAN EXCLAIMS IN HINDI]
[SPEAKING HINDI]
You're a doctor.
[CONTINUES IN HINDI]
[SICK CHILD COUGHING]
Please.
[MEN SPEAKING HINDI]
You should've got paid
up front, Banner.
ROMANOFF:
You know, for a man
who's supposed to be
avoiding stress,
you picked
a hell of a place
to settle.
Avoiding stress
isn't the secret.
Then what is it? Yoga?
You brought me
to the edge of
the city. Smart.
I assume the whole place
is surrounded.
Just you and me.
And your actress buddy?
Is she a spy, too?
They start that young?
I did.
Who are you?
Natasha Romanoff.
Are you here to kill me,
Ms. Romanoff?
Because that's not going
to work out for everyone.
No, of course not.
I'm here on behalf
of S.H.I.E.L.D.
S.H.I.E.L.D.
How did they find me?
We never lost you, Doctor.
We've kept our distance.
Even helped keep some
other interested parties
off your scent.
Why?
Nick Fury
seems to trust you.
But now we need you
to come in.
What if I say no?
I'll persuade you.
And what if
the other guy says no?
You've been
more than a year
without an incident.
I don't think you want
to break that streak.
Well, I don't every time
get what I want.
Doctor, we're facing
a potential
global catastrophe.
[CHUCKLES] Well,
those I actively
try to avoid.
This
is the Tesseract.
It has the potential energy
to wipe out the planet.
What does Fury
want me to do,
swallow it?
He wants you to find it.
It's been taken.
It emits a gamma signature
that's too weak
for us to trace.
There's no one that
knows gamma radiation
like you do.
If there was,
that's where I'd be.
So, Fury isn't after
the monster?
Not that he's told me.
And he tells you everything?
Talk to Fury.
He needs you on this.
He needs me in a cage?
No one's going to
put you in a...
Stop lying to me!
[COCKS GUN]
I'm sorry.
That was mean.
I just wanted to see
what you'd do.
Why don't we do this
the easy way
where you don't use that
and the other guy
doesn't make a mess.
Okay?
Natasha?
Stand down.
We're good here.
"Just you and me."
This is out of line,
Director.
You're dealing
with forces
you can't control.
You ever been
in a war, Councilman?
In a firefight?
Did you feel
an overabundance
of control?
You're saying
that this Asgard
is declaring war
on our planet?
Not Asgard. Loki.
He can't be working alone.
What about the other one?
His brother.
Our intelligence says
Thor is not a hostile,
but he's worlds away.
We can't depend on him
to help, either.
It's up to us.
Which is why you
should be focusing
on Phase 2.
It was designed
for exactly this...
Phase 2 isn't ready.
Our enemy is.
We need a response team.
The Avengers Initiative
was shut down.
This isn't about the Avengers.
We've seen the list.
You're running
the world's greatest
covert security network,
and you're going to leave
the fate of the human race
to a handful of freaks.
I'm not leaving anything
to anyone.
We need a response team.
These people
may be isolated,
unbalanced even,
but I believe
with the right push
they can be exactly
what we need.
You believe?
War isn't won by
sentiment, Director.
No, it's won by soldiers.
[GRUNTING]
ROGERS:
There's not enough time.
I got to put her
in the water!
PEGGY: You won't be alone.
DOCTOR: Oh, my God.
This guy is still alive!
[PANTING]
Trouble sleeping?
I slept for 70 years, sir.
I think I've had my fill.
Then you should be out,
celebrating, seeing the world.
When I went under,
the world was at war.
I wake up,
they say we won.
They didn't say what we lost.
We've made some mistakes
along the way.
Some, very recently.
Are you here
with a mission, sir?
I am.
Trying to get me back
in the world?
Trying to save it.
ROGERS: HYDRA's secret weapon.
FURY: Howard Stark
fished that out of the ocean
when he was looking for you.
He thought what we think.
The Tesseract
could be the key
to unlimited
sustainable energy.
That's something
the world sorely needs.
Who took it from you?
He's called Loki.
He's not from around here.
There's a lot we'll have to
bring you up to speed on
if you're in.
The world has gotten
even stranger
than you already know.
At this point, I doubt
anything would surprise me.
Ten bucks says you're wrong.
There's a debriefing packet
waiting for you back
at your apartment.
Is there anything you can
tell us about the Tesseract
that we ought
to know now?
You should have left it
in the ocean.
[BUBBLING]
[MECHANICAL BREATHING]
Good to go on this end.
The rest is up to you.
PEPPER: You disconnected
the transmission lines?
Are we off the grid?
Stark Tower is about
to become a beacon
of self-sustaining
clean energy.
PEPPER: Well, assuming
the arc reactor takes over
and it actually works.
STARK: I assume.
Light her up.
PEPPER: How does it look?
Like Christmas,
but with more me.
We've got to go wider
on the public
awareness campaign.
You need to do some press.
I'm in DC tomorrow,
I'm working on the zoning
for the next three buildings.
STARK: Pepper,
you're killing me.
The moment, remember?
Enjoy the moment.
PEPPER:
Get in here and I will.
JARVIS: Sir, Agent Coulson of
S.H.I.E.L.D. is on the line.
STARK: I'm not in.
I'm actually out.
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
JARVIS: Sir, I'm afraid
he's insisting.
Grow a spine, Jarvis.
I got a date.
Levels are holding
steady, I think.
Of course they are.
I was directly involved.
Which brings me to
my next question.
How does it feel
to be a genius?
Well, I really
wouldn't know,
now would I?
What do you mean?
All this came from you.
No, all this
came from that.
Give yourself
some credit. Please.
Stark Tower is your baby.
Give yourself
12% of the credit.
12%?
An argument can
be made for 15.
12%? My baby?
Well, I did do
all the heavy lifting.
Literally,
I lifted the heavy things.
And, sorry,
but the security snafu?
That was on you.
Oh.
My private elevator...
You mean our elevator?
...it was teeming with
sweaty workmen.
I'm going to pay for that
comment about percentages
in some subtle way later,
aren't I?
It's not going to be
that subtle.
I'll tell you what.
The next building is gonna
say "Potts" on the tower.
On the lease.
Call your mom.
Can you bunk over?
JARVIS:
Sir, the telephone.
I'm afraid my protocols
are being overridden.
COULSON: Mr. Stark,
we need to talk.
You have reached the life
model decoy of Tony Stark.
Please leave a message.
This is urgent.
Then leave it urgently.
Security breach.
It's on you.
Mr. Stark.
Phil! Come in.
"Phil"?
I can't stay.
His first name is "Agent."
PEPPER: Come on in.
We're celebrating.
Which is why
he can't stay.
We need you
to look this over as
soon as possible.
I don't like
being handed things.
That's fine, because
I love to be handed things.
So, let's trade.
Thank you.
Official consulting hours
are between 8 and 5
every other Thursday.
This isn't a consultation.
PEPPER: Is this
about the Avengers?
Which I know
nothing about.
STARK: The Avengers
Initiative was
scrapped, I thought.
And I didn't even qualify.
I didn't know that either.
Apparently I'm volatile,
self-obsessed,
don't play well with others.
That I did know.
This isn't
about personality
profiles anymore.
Whatever.
Ms. Potts, got a second?
Half a mo.
You know, I thought we were
having a moment.
I was having
12% of a moment.
This seems serious.
Phil's pretty shaken.
How would you know if it's...
Why is he "Phil"?
What is all this?
This is
this.
[OVERLAPPING AUDIO FROM FILES]
I'm going to take
the jet to DC tonight.
Tomorrow.
You have homework.
You have a lot of homework.
Well, what if I didn't?
If you didn't?
Yeah.
You mean when
you've finished?
Well, um, then...
Square deal. Fly safe.
Work hard.
So, any chance
you're driving by LaGuardia?
COULSON: I can drop you.
Fantastic.
I want to hear
about the cellist.
Is that still a thing?
COULSON:
She moved back to Portland.
PEPPER: What? Boo!
PILOT: We're about 40 minutes
out from home base, sir.
So, this Dr. Banner
was trying
to replicate the serum
they used on me?
A lot of people were.
You were the world's
first superhero.
Banner thought
gamma radiation
might hold the key
to unlocking
Erskine's original formula.
Didn't really go his way,
did it?
Not so much.
When he's not
that thing, though,
the guy's like
a Stephen Hawking.
He's like a smart person.
I gotta say,
it's an honor
to meet you
officially.
I've sort of
met you. I mean,
I watched you
while you were sleeping.
I mean, I was present
while you were
unconscious from the ice.
You know, it's really
just a huge honor
to have you on board this...
I hope I'm the man
for the job.
Oh, you are.
Absolutely.
We made some modifications
to the uniform.
I had a little
design input.
The uniform?
Aren't the stars
and stripes a little
old-fashioned?
With everything
that's happening,
and the things that are
about to come to light,
people might just need
a little old-fashioned.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
The Chitauri grow restless.
LOKI: Let them
gird themselves.
I will lead them
in the glorious battle.
Battle?
Against the meager
might of Earth?
Glorious, not lengthy.
If your force is as
formidable as you claim.
You question us?
You question him,
he who put the scepter
in your hand?
Who gave you
ancient knowledge
and new purpose
when you were
cast out, defeated?
I was a king!
The rightful king
of Asgard,
betrayed.
Your ambition is little
and born of childish need.
We look beyond the Earth
to the greater worlds
the Tesseract will unveil.
You don't have
the Tesseract yet.
I don't threaten.
But until
I open the doors,
until your force
is mine to command,
you are but words.
You will have
your war, Asgardian.
If you fail,
if the Tesseract
is kept from us,
there will be no realm,
no barren moon,
no crevice
where he cannot find you.
You think you know pain?
He will make you long
for something sweet as pain.
[GROANS]
COULSON:
Stow the captain's gear.
CREWMAN: Yes, sir.
Agent Romanoff,
Captain Rogers.
Ma'am.
Hi.
They need you
on the bridge.
They're starting
the face-trace.
See you there.
It was quite
the buzz around here,
finding you in the ice.
I thought Coulson
was gonna swoon.
Did he ask you to sign
his Captain America
trading cards yet?
Trading cards?
They're vintage.
He's very proud.
ROGERS: Dr. Banner.
Yeah, hi.
They told me
you would be coming.
Word is,
you can find the Cube.
Is that the only
word on me?
Only word I care about.
It must be strange
for you, all of this.
Well, this is
actually kind of familiar.
Gentlemen, you might want
to step inside in a minute.
It's going to get
a little hard to breathe.
AGENT ON PA:
Flight crew,
secure the deck.
Is this a submarine?
Really?
They want me in a submerged,
pressurized, metal container?
[TURBINES POWERING UP]
No, no,
this is much worse.
[AGENTS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
Hover power check complete.
Position cyclic.
Increase collective
to 8.0%.
AGENT:
Preparing for maximum
performance takeoff.
Increase output to capacity.
Power plant performing
at capacity.
We are clear.
HILL: All engines operating.
S.H.I.E.L.D. Emergency
Protocol 193.6 in effect.
We are at level, sir.
Good.
Let's vanish.
HILL: Engage
retro-reflection panels.
BRIDGE TECH:
Reflection panels engaged.
FURY: Gentlemen.
Doctor,
thank you for coming.
Thanks for asking nicely.
So, how long am I staying?
Once we get our hands
on the Tesseract,
you're in the wind.
Where are you with that?
We're sweeping every
wirelessly accessible
camera on the planet.
Cell phones, laptops...
If it's connected
to a satellite,
it's eyes and ears for us.
That's still not gonna
find them in time.
BANNER: You have to
narrow your field.
How many spectrometers
do you have access to?
How many are there?
Call every lab you know.
Tell them to put
the spectrometers
on the roof
and calibrate them
for gamma rays.
I'll rough out
a tracking algorithm,
basic cluster recognition.
At least we could rule out
a few places.
Do you have somewhere
for me to work?
Agent Romanoff,
could you show Dr. Banner
to his laboratory, please?
You're gonna love it, Doc.
We got all the toys.
Put it over there.
[SCIENTISTS
TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
Where did you find
all these people?
S.H.I.E.L.D.
has no shortage
of enemies, Doctor.
Is this the stuff you need?
Yeah, iridium.
It's found in meteorites.
It forms anti-protons.
It's very hard
to get hold of.
Especially if S.H.I.E.L.D.
knows you need it.
Well, I didn't know.
Hey!
The Tesseract
has shown me so much.
It's more than knowledge.
It's truth.
LOKI: I know.
What did it show you,
Agent Barton?
My next target.
LOKI: Tell me what you need.
I need a distraction.
And an eyeball.
I mean, if it's not
too much trouble.
No, no. It's fine.
It's a vintage set.
It took me
a couple of years
to collect them all.
Near mint.
Slight foxing
around the edges, but...
We got a hit.
A 67% match.
Wait. Cross match, 79%.
COULSON: Location?
AGENT: Stuttgart, Germany.
28 Konigstrasse.
He's not exactly hiding.
FURY: Captain,
you're up.
[VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
[PATRONS
CHATTING INDISTINCTLY]
[ARROW STRIKING]
[CURATOR SPEAKING GERMAN]
[CONTINUES IN GERMAN]
[ALL GASPING]
[WHIRRING]
[ALL CLAMORING]
[PANICKED SCREAMING]
[PANICKED SCREAMING
AND SHOUTING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[CROWD CRIES OUT]
LOKI: Kneel before me.
I said
[CROWD SCREAMS]
kneel!
Is not this simpler?
Is this not
your natural state?
It's the unspoken
truth of humanity,
that you crave subjugation.
The bright lure of freedom
diminishes your life's joy
in a mad scramble for power,
for identity.
You were made to be ruled.
In the end,
you will always kneel.
Not to men like you.
There are no men like me.
There are always
men like you.
Look to your elder, people.
Let him be an example.
[GROANS]
You know, the last time
I was in Germany,
and saw a man standing
above everybody else,
we ended up disagreeing.
The soldier.
The man out of time.
I'm not the one
who's out of time.
ROMANOFF ON PA:
Loki, drop the weapon
and stand down.
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
Kneel.
Not today!
[GROANS]
The guy's all
over the place.
[GROANING]
STARK:
Agent Romanoff.
You miss me?
[PA SYSTEM PLAYING ROCK MUSIC]
[GROANS]
Make your move,
Reindeer Games.
Good move.
Mr. Stark.
Captain.
FURY ON RADIO:
Is he saying anything?
Not a word.
Just get him here.
We're low on time.
I don't like it.
STARK: What, Rock of Ages
giving up so easily?
I don't remember it
being that easy.
This guy packs a wallop.
Still, you are pretty spry
for an older fellow.
What's your thing,
Pilates?
What?
It's like calisthenics.
You might have missed
a couple of things
doing time as a Capsicle.
Fury didn't tell me
he was calling you in.
Yeah,
there's a lot of things
Fury doesn't tell you.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Where's this coming from?
What's the matter?
Are you scared
of a little lightning?
I'm not overly fond
of what follows.
[REAR HATCH OPENING]
ROGERS: What are you doing?
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
And now there's that guy.
Another Asgardian?
That guy's a friendly?
STARK: Doesn't matter.
If he frees Loki
or kills him,
the Tesseract's lost.
Stark, we need
a plan of attack!
I have a plan. Attack.
I'd sit this one out, Cap.
I don't see how I can.
These guys come from legend.
They're basically gods.
There's only one God, ma'am.
And I'm pretty sure
he doesn't dress like that.
[GROANING]
[LAUGHING]
Where is the Tesseract?
I missed you, too.
Do I look to be
in a gaming mood?
You should thank me.
With the Bifrost gone,
how much dark energy
did the Allfather
have to muster to
conjure you here
to your precious Earth?
[GROWLS]
I thought you dead.
Did you mourn?
We all did. Our father...
Your father.
He did tell you
my true parentage,
did he not?
We were raised together.
We played together,
we fought together.
Do you remember
none of that?
I remember a shadow.
Living in the shade
of your greatness.
I remember you tossing me
into an abyss.
I, who was,
and should be, king!
So you take
the world I love
as a recompense
for your imagined slights?
No. The Earth is under
my protection, Loki.
[LOKI LAUGHING]
And you're doing
a marvelous job
with that.
The humans slaughter
each other in droves
while you idly fret.
I mean to rule them,
as why should I not?
You think yourself
above them?
Well, yes.
Then you miss the truth
of ruling, brother.
A throne would suit you ill.
I've seen worlds
you've never known about!
I have grown, Odinson,
in my exile.
I have seen
the true power
of the Tesseract,
and when I wield it...
Who showed you this power?
Who controls
the would-be king?
I am a king!
Not here!
You give up
the Tesseract!
this poisonous dream!
You come home.
I don't have it.
You need the Cube
to bring me home.
But I've sent it off,
I know not where.
You listen well, brother.
[GRUNTS]
I'm listening.
[GROANS]
Do not touch me again.
Then don't take my stuff.
You have no idea
what you're dealing with.
Shakespeare in the Park?
Doth Mother know
you wear-eth her drapes?
This is beyond you,
metal man.
Loki will face
Asgardian justice.
He gives up the Cube,
he's all yours. Until then,
stay out of the way.
Tourist.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Okay.
[GRUNTS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
JARVIS: Power at
400% capacity.
How about that?
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[METAL CRUNCHING]
[SENSORS BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
ROGERS: Hey!
That's enough.
Now, I don't know
what you plan on doing here.
I've come here
to put an end
to Loki's schemes.
Then prove it.
Put that hammer down.
Yeah... No.
Bad call.
He loves his hammer.
[GROANS]
You want me to put
the hammer down?
[GROANS]
Are we done, here?
[LOCK ENGAGING]
[COMPARTMENT PRESSURIZING]
In case it's unclear,
if you try to escape,
if you so much as
scratch that glass,
[AIR WHOOSHING]
it's 30,000 feet
straight down
in a steel trap.
You get how that works?
Ant, boot.
[LOKI CHUCKLING]
It's an impressive cage.
Not built, I think,
for me.
Built for something
a lot stronger than you.
Oh, I've heard.
A mindless beast.
Makes play
he's still a man.
How desperate are you,
that you call on
such lost creatures
to defend you?
FURY: How desperate am I?
You threaten
my world with war.
You steal a force
you can't hope to control.
You talk about peace,
and you kill because it's fun.
You have made me
very desperate.
You might not be glad
that you did.
Ooh.
It burns you
to have come so close.
To have the Tesseract,
to have power,
unlimited power.
And for what?
A warm light
for all mankind to share.
And then to be reminded
what real power is.
Well, let me know
if "real power"
wants a magazine
or something.
He really grows on you,
doesn't he?
Loki's gonna drag this out.
So, Thor, what's his play?
He has an army
called the Chitauri.
They're not of Asgard,
nor any world known.
He means to lead them
against your people.
They will win him
the Earth,
in return, I suspect,
for the Tesseract.
An army
from outer space.
So, he's building
another portal.
That's what he needs
Erik Selvig for.
Selvig?
He's an astrophysicist.
He's a friend.
Loki has him under
some kind of spell,
along with one of ours.
I want to know why
Loki let us take him.
He's not leading
an army from here.
I don't think
we should be
focusing on Loki.
That guy's brain
is a bag full of cats.
You could smell
crazy on him.
Have care
how you speak.
Loki is beyond reason,
but he is of Asgard.
And he is my brother.
He killed 80 people
in two days.
He's adopted.
I think it's about
the mechanics.
Iridium... What do they
need the iridium for?
It's a stabilizing agent.
I'm just saying,
pick a weekend.
I'll fly you to Portland.
Keep love alive.
It means the portal
won't collapse on itself
like it did at S.H.I.E.L.D.
No hard feelings, Point Break.
You've got a mean swing.
Also, it means the portal
can open as wide
and stay open as long,
as Loki wants.
Raise the mizzenmast.
Jib the topsails.
That man is playing Galaga.
He thought
we wouldn't notice,
but we did.
How does Fury
even see these?
He turns.
Sounds exhausting.
The rest
of the raw materials,
Agent Barton can get
his hands on pretty easily.
The only major component
he still needs
is a power source
of high-energy density.
Something to kick-start
the Cube.
When did you become
an expert in thermonuclear
astrophysics?
Last night.
The packet, Selvig's notes,
the extraction theory papers.
Am I the only one
who did the reading?
Does Loki need
any particular kind
of power source?
He would have
to heat the Cube to
120-million Kelvin
just to break through
the Coulomb barrier.
Unless Selvig
has figured out
how to stabilize
the quantum tunneling effect.
BANNER: Well,
if he could do that,
he could achieve
heavy ion fusion
at any reactor
on the planet.
Finally, someone
who speaks English.
Is that what
just happened?
It's good to meet you,
Dr. Banner.
Your work on antielectron
collisions is unparalleled.
And I'm a huge fan
of the way
you lose control
and turn into an enormous
green rage-monster.
Thanks.
Dr. Banner is only here
to track the Cube.
I was hoping
you might join him.
ROGERS: I would start
with that stick of his.
It may be magical,
but it works an awful lot
like a HYDRA weapon.
I don't know about that,
but it is powered by the Cube.
And I would like to know
how Loki used it
to turn two
of the sharpest men I know
into his personal
flying monkeys.
Monkeys?
I do not understand.
I do.
I understood that reference.
Shall we play, Doctor?
This way, sir.
The gamma readings
are definitely consistent
with Selvig's reports
of the Tesseract.
But it's going to take
weeks to process.
If we bypass
their mainframe
and direct route
to the Homer cluster
we can clock this
at around 600 teraflops.
All I packed
was a toothbrush.
You know, you should come by
Stark Tower sometime.
Top ten floors, all R&amp;D.
You'd love it.
It's Candy Land.
Thanks, but the last time
I was in New York,
I kind of broke Harlem.
Well, I promise
a stress-free environment.
No tension, no surprises.
[ELECTRIC DISCHARGE]
Ow!
ROGERS: Hey!
Nothing?
Are you nuts?
Jury's out.
You really have got
a lid on it, haven't you?
What's your secret?
Mellow jazz, bongo drums,
huge bag of weed?
Is everything
a joke to you?
Funny things are.
Threatening the safety
of everyone on this ship
isn't funny.
No offense, Doc.
It's all right,
I wouldn't have
come aboard
if I couldn't handle
pointy things.
You're tip-toeing, big man.
You need to strut.
And you need to focus
on the problem, Mr. Stark.
STARK: Do you think I'm not?
Why did Fury call us in?
Why now? Why not before?
What isn't he telling us?
I can't do the equation unless
I have all the variables.
You think Fury's
hiding something?
He's a spy.
Captain, he's "the" spy.
His secrets have secrets.
It's bugging him, too.
Isn't it?
Uh...
I just want to finish
my work here, and...
Doctor?
"A warm light
for all mankind."
Loki's jab at Fury
about the Cube.
I heard it.
I think that
was meant for you.
Even if Barton
didn't tell Loki
about the tower,
it was still
all over the news.
The Stark Tower?
That big, ugly
building in New York?
It's powered
by an arc reactor,
a self-sustaining
energy source.
That building
will run itself for,
what, a year?
It's just the prototype.
I'm kind of the only name
in clean energy right now.
That's what
he's getting at.
So, why didn't S.H.I.E.L.D.
bring him in
on the Tesseract project?
What are they doing
in the energy business
in the first place?
STARK: I should probably
look into that
once my decryption program
finishes breaking into all of
S.H.I.E.L.D.'s secure files.
I'm sorry.
Did you say...
Jarvis has been running it
since I hit the bridge.
In a few hours,
I'll know every
dirty secret
S.H.I.E.L.D. has ever
tried to hide.
Blueberry?
Yet you're confused
about why they didn't
want you around.
An intelligence organization
that fears intelligence?
Historically,
not awesome.
I think Loki's trying
to wind us up.
This is a man
who means to start a war,
and if we don't stay focused,
he'll succeed.
We have orders.
We should follow them.
Following's not really
my style.
And you're all about style,
aren't you?
Of the people
in this room,
which one is,
A, wearing a spangly outfit,
and, B, not of use?
Steve, tell me none
of this smells
a little funky to you.
Just find the Cube.
[AGENTS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
STARK: That's the guy
my dad never shut up about?
I'm wondering if
they shouldn't have
kept him on ice.
Huh.
The guy's not wrong
about Loki.
He does have
the jump on us.
What he's got
is an Acme dynamite kit.
It's going to blow up
in his face.
And I'm going to be there
when it does.
Yeah.
I'll read all about it.
Uh-huh. Or you'll be
suiting up with
the rest of us.
[CHUCKLES]
You see, I don't get
a suit of armor.
I'm exposed.
Like a nerve.
It's a nightmare.
I've got a cluster
of shrapnel trying
every second
to crawl its way
into my heart.
This stops it.
This little circle of light,
it's part of me now,
not just armor.
It's a terrible privilege.
But you can control it.
Because I learned how.
It's different.
Hey, I read all about
your accident.
That much gamma exposure
should have killed you.
So you're saying
that the Hulk...
The other guy
saved my life?
That's nice.
It's a nice sentiment.
Saved it for what?
I guess we'll find out.
You may not enjoy that.
And you just might.
[METAL STRAINING]
[METAL BREAKING]
[AGENTS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
COULSON: As soon as
Loki took the doctor,
we moved Jane Foster.
They've got an excellent
observatory in Tromso.
She was asked to consult there
very suddenly yesterday.
Handsome fee,
private plane,
very remote.
She'll be safe.
Thank you.
It's no accident,
Loki taking Erik Selvig.
I dread what
he plans for him
once he's done.
Erik is a good man.
He talks about you a lot.
You changed his life.
You changed
everything around here.
They were better
as they were.
We pretend on Asgard
that we're more advanced,
but we come here,
battling like bilge snipe.
Like what?
Bilge snipe.
You know, huge,
scaly, big antlers.
You don't have those?
I don't think so.
Well, they are repulsive.
And they trample everything
in their path.
When I first
came to Earth,
Loki's rage
followed me here,
and your people
paid the price.
And now, again.
In my youth,
I courted war.
FURY: War hasn't started yet.
You think you could
make Loki tell us
where the Tesseract is?
I do not know.
Loki's mind is far afield.
It's not just power he craves,
it's vengeance, upon me.
There's no pain
would prise his need
from him.
A lot of guys think that,
until the pain starts.
What are you
asking me to do?
I'm asking,
what are you
prepared to do?
Loki is a prisoner.
Then why do I feel like
he's the only person
on this boat
that wants to be here?
There's not many people
who can sneak up on me.
But you figured
I'd come.
After.
After whatever tortures
Fury can concoct,
you would appear
as a friend, as a balm.
And I would cooperate.
I want to know
what you've done
to Agent Barton.
I would say
I've expanded his mind.
And once you've won,
once you're
king of the mountain,
what happens
to his mind?
Oh...
Is this love,
Agent Romanoff?
Love is for children.
I owe him a debt.
Tell me.
Before I worked
for S.H.I.E.L.D.,
I, uh...
Well, I made
a name for myself.
I have a very
specific skill set.
I didn't care
who I used it for, or on.
I got on S.H.I.E.L.D.'s
radar in a bad way.
Agent Barton
was sent to kill me.
He made a different call.
And what will you do
if I vow to spare him?
Not let you out.
No, but I like this.
Your world in the balance,
and you bargain for one man.
Regimes fall every day.
I tend not
to weep over that.
I'm Russian.
Or I was.
And what are you now?
It's really
not that complicated.
I got red in my ledger,
I'd like to wipe it out.
Can you?
Can you wipe out
that much red?
Dreykov's daughter,
Sao Paulo,
the hospital fire?
Barton told me everything.
Your ledger is dripping.
It's gushing red,
and you think saving a man
no more virtuous
than yourself
will change anything?
This is the basest
sentimentality.
This is a child at prayer.
Pathetic!
You lie and kill
in the service
of liars and killers.
You pretend to be separate,
to have your own code,
something that makes up
for the horrors.
But they are part of you.
And they will never go away.
I won't touch Barton,
not until I make him kill you.
Slowly, intimately,
in every way
he knows you fear.
And then he'll wake
just long enough to
see his good work,
and when he screams,
I'll split his skull.
This is my bargain,
you mewling quim.
[SNIFFLING]
You're a monster.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, no.
You brought the monster.
So, Banner.
That's your play.
What?
Loki means
to unleash the Hulk.
Keep Banner in the lab.
I'm on my way.
Send Thor as well.
Thank you
for your cooperation.
What are you doing,
Mr. Stark?
Uh, kind of been wondering
the same thing about you.
You're supposed
to be locating
the Tesseract.
BANNER: We are.
The model's locked
and we're sweeping
for the signature now.
When we get a hit,
we'll have the location
within half a mile.
Yeah, then you get
your Cube back.
No muss, no fuss.
What is "Phase 2"?
Phase 2 is S.H.I.E.L.D. uses
the Cube to make weapons.
Sorry, computer was moving
a little slow for me.
Rogers, we gathered
everything related
to the Tesseract.
This does not mean
that we're making...
STARK: I'm sorry, Nick.
What were you lying?
I was wrong, Director.
The world
hasn't changed a bit.
Did you know about this?
You want to think about
removing yourself
from this environment,
Doctor?
I was in Calcutta.
I was pretty well removed.
Loki is manipulating you.
And you've been
doing what, exactly?
You didn't come here
because I bat my
eyelashes at you.
Yes, and I'm not leaving
because suddenly
you get a little twitchy.
I'd like to know
why S.H.I.E.L.D.
is using the Tesseract
to build weapons
of mass destruction.
Because of him.
Me?
Last year,
Earth had a visitor
from another planet
who had a grudge match
that leveled a small town.
We learned that
not only are we not alone,
but we are hopelessly,
hilariously, outgunned.
My people want nothing
but peace with your planet.
But you're not
the only people out
there, are you?
And you're not
the only threat.
The world's filling up
with people who can't
be matched,
that can't be controlled.
Like you controlled the Cube?
Your work with
the Tesseract
is what drew Loki to it,
and his allies.
It is a signal
to all the realms
that the Earth is ready
for a higher form of war.
A higher form?
You forced our hand.
We had to come up
with something.
A nuclear deterrent.
Because that always
calms everything
right down.
Remind me again
how you made
your fortune, Stark.
I'm sure if he still
made weapons,
Stark would be neck-deep...
Hold on. How is this
now about me?
I'm sorry,
isn't everything?
I thought humans were
more evolved than this.
Excuse me, did we
come to your planet
and blow stuff up?
You treat your champions
with such mistrust.
Are you boys
really that naive?
S.H.I.E.L.D. monitors
potential threats.
Captain America's
on threat watch?
ROMANOFF: We all are.
STARK: Wait,
you're on that list?
Are you above
or below angry bees?
ROGERS: Stark,
so help me God,
if you make
one more wisecrack...
STARK: Threat!
Verbal threat.
I feel threatened.
ROGERS: Show some respect.
STARK: Respect what?
[ALL ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
FEMALE AGENT ON RADIO:
Transport Six-Six-Bravo,
please relay confirm codes.
I've got you on the computer,
but not on the day log.
What is your haul? Over.
PILOT:
Arms and
ammunition. Over.
You speak of control,
yet you court chaos.
BANNER:
That's his M.O., isn't it?
I mean, what are we, a team?
No, we're a chemical mixture
that makes chaos.
We're a time bomb.
You need to step away.
Why shouldn't the guy
let off a little steam?
You know damn well why.
Back off!
I'm starting to want you
to make me.
Yeah. Big man
in a suit of armor.
Take that off,
what are you?
Genius, billionaire,
playboy, philanthropist.
I know guys
with none of that
worth ten of you.
I've seen the footage.
The only thing you really
fight for is yourself.
You're not the guy
to make the sacrifice play,
to lay down on a wire
and let the other guy
crawl over you.
I think I would just
cut the wire.
Always a way out.
You may not be a threat,
but you better
stop pretending
to be a hero.
A hero? Like you?
You're a laboratory
experiment, Rogers.
Everything special
about you came out
of a bottle.
[BEEPING]
Put on the suit.
Let's go a few rounds.
[THOR LAUGHING]
You people are so petty,
and tiny.
BANNER: Yeah,
this is a team.
FURY: Agent Romanoff,
would you escort
Dr. Banner back to his...
Where?
You rented my room.
The cell was
just in case...
In case you
needed to kill me.
But you can't.
I know, I tried.
I got low.
I didn't see an end.
So, I put a bullet
in my mouth,
and the other guy
spit it out.
So I moved on.
I focused on
helping other people.
I was good.
Until you dragged me back
into this freak show
and put everyone
here at risk.
You want to know my secret,
Agent Romanoff?
You want to know
how I stay calm?
ROGERS: Dr. Banner,
put down the scepter.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Got it.
Sorry, kids,
you don't get to see
my party trick after all.
You located
the Tesseract?
STARK: I could
get there fastest.
The Tesseract
belongs on Asgard.
No human is
a match for it.
You're not going alone.
You're gonna stop me?
Put on the suit,
let's find out.
I'm not afraid
to hit an old man.
Put on the suit.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Oh, my God.
[BOTH GRUNT]
Put on the suit.
Yeah.
[ALL CLAMORING]
AGENT ON PA:
All hands to stations.
[PANTING]
Hill!
HILL: External detonation.
Number three
engine is down.
AGENT: We've been hit.
Can they get it running?
AGENT: Fire in engine three!
Talk to me.
Turbine looks
mostly intact,
but it's impossible
to get out there
to make repairs
while we're in the air.
If we lose one more
engine, we won't be.
Somebody's got to
get outside and
patch that engine.
Stark, you copy that?
STARK: I'm on it.
FURY: Coulson, initiate
defensive lockdown
in the detention section,
then get to the armory.
Romanoff?
[GRUNTING]
We're okay.
[STRAINED PANTING]
We're okay, right?
Keep that engine down!
Yes, sir.
Detention,
wait for cameras
to go dark.
Got it.
Stay close.
AGENT: Let's go, Level 4.
Engine three.
I'll meet you there.
[POWERING UP]
[BANNER GROANING]
ROMANOFF: Doctor?
[BANNER GROANS LOUDLY]
Bruce?
You got to fight it.
This is just
what Loki wants.
We're going to be okay.
Listen to me.
Are you hurt?
We're going to be okay.
All right?
I swear on my life,
I will get you out of this.
You will walk away
and never ever...
[IN MONSTROUS VOICE]
Your life?
[PANTING]
[GROANING]
[GROANING LOUDLY]
Bruce.
[INHUMAN GROANING]
[ROARING]
[STRAINING]
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLS]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[HULK ROARING]
Bring the carrier about
to a 1-8-0, heading south!
Take us to the water!
We're flying blind.
Navigation's recalibrating
after the engine failure.
Is the sun coming up?
Yes, sir.
Then put it on the left.
Get us over water.
One more turbine goes
down, and we drop.
[AGENTS YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
Thanks.
Stark!
Stark, I'm here!
STARK: Good.
Let's see what we've got.
I got to get this
superconducting
coolant system
back online
before I can
access the rotors,
work on dislodging
the debris.
I need you to get to that
engine control panel
and tell me which relays
are in overload position.
[GRUNTING]
What does it
look like in there?
It seems to run
on some form
of electricity.
Well, you're not wrong.
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
[ROARING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[SNORTING]
[ROARING]
[SNARLS]
We are not
your enemies, Banner.
Try to think!
[SCOFFS]
[REPULSOR RAYS FIRING]
ROGERS:
Okay, the relays are intact.
What's our next move?
STARK:
Even if I clear the rotors,
this thing won't
re-engage without a jump.
I'm going to have to
get in there and push.
If that thing
gets up to speed,
you'll get shredded.
That stator control unit
can reverse the polarity
long enough to disengage
maglev and that could...
Speak English!
You see that red lever?
It will slow the rotors
down long enough
for me to get out.
Stand by it.
Wait for my word.
[GRUNTING]
[HULK ROARING]
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
[YELLS]
We need full evac
on the lower hangar bay.
Grenade!
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
AGENT ON PA:
We've got a perimeter breach!
Hostiles are in
S.H.I.E.L.D. gear.
Call-outs at every junction.
[HULK SNARLS]
We have the Hulk and Thor
on Research Level 4.
Levels 2 and 3 are dark.
Sir, the Hulk will
tear this place apart!
Get his attention.
Escort 6-0, proceed
to Wishbone and
engage hostile.
Don't get too close.
PILOT: Copy.
Target acquired.
[HULK SNARLING]
[THOR GROANING]
Target engaged.
[ROARING]
Target angry,
target angry!
[HULK GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[MACHINE GUN FIRING]
[GROANS]
They're not getting
through here,
so what the hell...
[SCREAMING]
[AGENTS CLAMORING]
[POWERING DOWN]
AGENT ON PA: Engine one
is now in shut-down.
[AGENTS CLAMORING]
AGENT 1: We are in
an uncontrolled descent.
AGENT 2: Sir, we've lost
all power in engine one.
FURY: It's Barton.
He took out our systems.
He's headed
for the detention level.
Does anybody copy?
This is Agent Romanoff.
I copy.
FURY: Stark,
we're losing altitude.
Yeah, I noticed.
[GRUNTS]
No!
Are you ever not
going to fall for that?
[AGENTS CLAMORING IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
The humans
think us immortal.
Should we test that?
[GUARD GRUNTING]
Move away, please.
You like this?
We started working
on the prototype
after you sent
the Destroyer.
Even I don't know
what it does.
[POWERING UP]
Do you want to find out?
[GROANS]
No!
[AIR WHOOSHING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
[BOTH STRAINING]
[YELLING]
[GROANING]
Natasha?
[YELLS]
[GROANING]
COULSON:
You're going to lose.
Am I?
It's in your nature.
Hmm.
Your heroes are scattered.
Your floating fortress
falls from the sky.
Where is my disadvantage?
You lack conviction.
I don't think I'm...
[CRIES OUT]
So, that's what it does.
[AGENTS CLAMORING]
AGENT ON PA:
All hands to crash
stations immediately.
[YELLING]
Cap, hit the lever.
ROGERS:
I need a minute here!
Lever,
now!
Uh-oh.
Help!
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
[SIGHS]
Sorry, boss.
The god rabbited.
Just stay awake.
Eyes on me.
No, I'm clocking out here.
Not an option.
It's okay, boss.
This was never
gonna work
if they didn't
have something
to...
FURY:
Agent Coulson is down.
AGENT:
A medical team is on
its way to your location.
FURY: They're here.
They called it.
These were in
Phil Coulson's jacket.
I guess he never did
get you to sign them.
We're dead in
the air up here.
Our communications,
the location of the Cube,
Banner, Thor...
I got nothing for you.
I lost my one good eye.
Maybe I had that coming.
Yes,
we were going
to build an arsenal
with the Tesseract.
I never put all my chips
on that number, though,
because I was playing
something even riskier.
There was an idea,
Stark knows this,
called
the Avengers Initiative.
The idea was to bring
together a group
of remarkable people,
to see if they could
become something more.
To see if they
could work together
when we needed them to,
to fight the battles
that we never could.
Phil Coulson died
still believing in that idea.
In heroes.
Well,
it's an old-fashioned notion.
SECURITY GUARD:
You fell out of the sky.
[GROANS]
Did I hurt anybody?
There's nobody
around here to get hurt.
You did scare
the hell out of some
pigeons, though.
Lucky.
Or just good aim.
You were awake
when you fell.
You saw?
The whole thing.
Right through the ceiling.
Big and green
and buck-ass nude.
Here.
Didn't think those
would fit you until
you shrunk down
to a regular-size feller.
Thank you.
Are you an alien?
What?
From outer space,
an alien.
No.
Well, then, son,
you've got a condition.
[GROANS]
Clint. You're going
to be all right.
You know that?
[CHUCKLES]
Is that what you know?
I've got no window.
I have to flush him out.
ROMANOFF:
You got to level out.
It's gonna take time.
You don't understand.
Have you ever had someone
take your brain and play?
Pull you out and stuff
something else in?
Do you know what
it's like to be unmade?
You know that I do.
Why am I back?
How'd you get him out?
Cognitive recalibration.
I hit you really hard
on the head.
Thanks.
Natasha...
How many agents did I...
Don't.
Don't do that
to yourself, Clint.
This is Loki.
This is
monsters and magic,
and nothing
we were ever trained for.
Loki, did he get away?
Yeah.
I don't suppose
you know where.
I didn't need to know.
I didn't ask.
He's gonna make
his play soon, though.
Today.
We got to stop him.
Yeah? Who's "we"?
I don't know.
Whoever's left.
Well,
if I put an arrow
through Loki's eye socket,
I'd sleep better,
I suppose.
Now you sound like you.
But you don't.
You're a spy,
not a soldier.
Now you want to
wade into a war. Why?
What did Loki do to you?
He didn't. I just...
Natasha.
I've been compromised.
I got red in my ledger.
I'd like to wipe it out.
Was he married?
No.
There was a cellist,
I think.
I'm sorry.
He seemed
like a good man.
He was an idiot.
Why? For believing?
For taking on Loki alone.
He was doing his job.
[SCOFFS]
He was out of his league.
He should have waited.
He should have...
Sometimes there isn't
a way out, Tony.
Right, I've heard
that before.
Is this the first time
you lost a soldier?
We are not soldiers.
I'm not marching
to Fury's fife.
Neither am I.
He's got the same
blood on his hands
that Loki does.
But right now,
we got to put
that behind us
and get this done.
Loki needs
a power source.
If we can
put together a list...
He made it personal.
That's not the point.
That is the point.
That's Loki's point.
He hit us all
right where we live. Why?
To tear us apart.
Yeah, divide and conquer
is great,
but he knows he has to
take us out to win, right?
That's what he wants.
He wants to beat us,
he wants to be seen doing it.
He wants an audience.
Right. I caught
his act in Stuttgart.
Yeah, that's just previews.
This is opening night.
And Loki, he's a
full-tilt diva, right?
He wants flowers,
he wants parades.
He wants a monument
built to the skies
with his name plastered...
Son of a bitch.
Time to go.
Go where?
I'll tell you on the way.
Can you fly
one of those jets?
I can.
You got a suit?
Yeah.
Then suit up.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[POWERING UP]
Hey, you guys aren't
authorized to be in here.
Son, just don't.
Sir.
Agent Hill.
Those cards,
they were
in Coulson's locker,
not in his jacket.
They needed the push.
AGENT ON PA: We have
an unauthorized departure
from Bay 6.
FURY: They found him.
Get our communications
back up,
whatever you have to do.
I want eyes on everything.
Yes, sir.
[ENERGY CRACKLING]
JARVIS:
Sir, I've turned off
the arc reactor
but the device
is already self-sustaining.
STARK: Shut it down,
Dr. Selvig.
It's too late!
She can't stop now.
She wants to
show us something!
A new universe.
Okay.
[CROWD GASPING]
JARVIS: The barrier
is pure energy.
It's unbreachable.
STARK: Yeah, I got that.
Plan B.
JARVIS: Sir, the Mark 7
is not ready for deployment.
Then skip the spinning rims.
We're on the clock.
Please tell me
you're going to appeal
to my humanity.
Actually, I'm planning
to threaten you.
You should have left
your armor on for that.
Yeah.
It's seen a bit of mileage,
and you've got
the glow stick of destiny.
Would you like a drink?
Stalling me
won't change anything.
No, no. Threatening.
No drink?
Are you sure?
I'm having one.
The Chitauri are coming.
Nothing will change that.
What have I to fear?
The Avengers.
That's what we call ourselves.
We're sort of like a team.
"Earth's mightiest heroes"
-type thing.
Yes, I've met them.
Yeah.
It takes us a while
to get any traction,
I'll give you that one.
But let's do
a head count, here.
Your brother,
the demigod,
a super soldier,
a living legend
who kind of lives up
to the legend.
A man with breathtaking
anger-management issues,
a couple of
master assassins,
and you, big fella,
you've managed to piss off
every single one of them.
That was the plan.
Not a great plan.
When they come,
and they will,
they'll come for you.
I have an army.
We have a Hulk.
I thought the beast
had wandered off.
You're missing the point.
There is no throne.
There is no version of this
where you come out on top.
Maybe your army comes
and maybe
it's too much for us,
but it's all on you.
Because if we can't
protect the Earth,
you can be damn well sure
we'll avenge it.
How will your friends
have time for me
when they are
so busy fighting you?
This usually works.
Well, performance issues,
it's not uncommon.
One out of five...
[GRUNTS]
Jarvis, anytime now.
You will all
fall before me.
Deploy!
[SCREAMS]
[THRUSTERS FIRING]
[CROWD GASPING]
STARK:
And there's one other
person you pissed off.
His name was Phil.
[GROANING]
Right.
Army.
[SCREECHING]
[CROWD GASPING
IN ASTONISHMENT]
[CROWD CLAMORING]
[PANICKED SCREAMING]
[LASERS FIRING]
[PANTING]
Loki!
Turn off the Tesseract,
or I'll destroy it.
You can't.
There is no stopping it.
There is only
the war.
So be it.
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
ROMANOFF:
Stark, we're on your three,
headed northeast.
What? Did you
stop for drive-through?
Swing up Park. I'm gonna
lay 'em out for you.
[GRUNTS]
[RAIL GUN FIRING]
JARVIS:
Sir, we have more incoming.
Fine.
Let's keep them occupied.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Nat?
I see him.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[CIVILIANS CLAMORING]
ROGERS: We got
to get back up there.
[LOUD MECHANICAL GROWL]
[ROARING]
[WORKERS CLAMORING]
Stark, are you
seeing this?
STARK: Seeing.
Still working on believing.
Where's Banner?
Has he shown up yet?
ROGERS: Banner?
Just keep me posted.
Jarvis, find me a soft spot.
Look at this!
Look around you!
You think this madness
will end with your rule?
It's too late.
It's too late to stop it.
No. We can, together.
[GROANS]
Sentiment.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
We've got civilians
still trapped up here.
ROGERS: Loki.
[SCREAMING]
They're fish in a barrel
down there.
We got this.
It's good. Go.
Do you think
you can hold them off?
Captain,
it would be
my genuine pleasure.
[CIVILIANS CLAMORING]
[PANICKED SCREAMING]
Just like Budapest
all over again.
You and I
remember Budapest
very differently.
It's going to be an hour
before they can
scramble the National Guard.
National Guard?
Does the army know
what's happening here?
Do we?
You need men
in these buildings.
There are people inside and
they're going to be running
right into the line of fire.
You take them
to the basements
or through the subway.
You keep them
off the streets.
I need a perimeter
as far back as 39th.
Why the hell
should I take
orders from you?
I need men
in those buildings.
Lead the people down
and away from the streets.
We're going to
set up a perimeter
all the way
down to 39th Street.
[CLAMORING]
Well, we got its attention.
What the hell
was step two?
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLING]
[GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
What's the story upstairs?
The power
surrounding the Cube
is impenetrable.
STARK: Thor's right.
We got to deal
with these guys.
How do we do this?
As a team.
I have unfinished business
with Loki.
Yeah?
Well, get in line.
ROGERS: Save it.
Loki's going to keep
this fight focused on us,
and that's what we need.
Without him,
these things could run wild.
We got Stark up top.
He's going to need us to...
[MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING]
So, this all
seems horrible.
I've seen worse.
Sorry.
No, we could
use a little worse.
ROGERS: Stark, we got him.
STARK: Banner?
Just like you said.
Then tell him to suit up.
I'm bringing the party to you.
[SNARLS]
I don't see
how that's a party.
ROGERS: Dr. Banner.
Now might be a really good
time for you to get angry.
That's my secret, Captain.
I'm always angry.
Hold on!
[SCREECHING]
[SNARLING]
[ROARS]
Send the rest.
Guys.
STARK: Call it, Captain.
All right, listen up.
Until we can
close that portal,
our priority
is containment.
Barton,
I want you on that roof.
Eyes on everything.
Call out patterns and strays.
Stark, you got
the perimeter.
Anything gets
more than three blocks out,
you turn it back
or you turn it to ash.
Can you give me a lift?
Right.
Better clench up, Legolas.
Thor, you got to try
and bottleneck that portal.
Slow them down.
You got the lightning.
Light the bastards up.
You and me,
we stay here on the ground.
We keep the fighting here.
And Hulk...
[SNARLS]
Smash.
[ROARS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[YELLS]
[CHATTER FROM
NEWS REPORTS OVERLAPPING]
Sir.
The Council is on.
Stark,
you got a lot of strays
sniffing your tail.
I'm just trying
to keep them
off the streets.
Well, they can't bank
worth a damn.
So find a tight corner.
I will roger that.
Oh, boy.
Nice call.
What else you got?
BARTON: Thor is taking on
a squadron down on Sixth.
And he didn't invite me.
[WORKERS GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
[WORKERS SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Captain, none of this
is going to mean a damn thing
if we don't
close that portal.
ROGERS: Our biggest guns
couldn't touch it.
Well, maybe
it's not about guns.
If you want to get up there,
you're going to need a ride.
I got a ride.
I could use a boost, though.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah. It's gonna be fun.
[GRUNTING]
Okay, turn, turn.
Less! Less!
[THOR GRUNTING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[CIVILIANS SCREAMING]
[SOLDIERS DIRECTING CIVILIANS]
[GRUNTING]
BARTON: Captain, the bank
on 42nd past Madison.
They've cornered
a lot of civilians in there.
I'm on it.
[PANICKED WHISPERING]
[ACTIVATES]
[BEEPING]
[ALL GASP]
Everyone! Clear out!
[STRAINING]
[BEEPING INCREASES TEMPO]
COUNCILWOMAN:
Director Fury,
the Council
has made a decision.
I recognize the Council
But given that
it's a stupid-ass decision,
I have elected to ignore it.
Director, you're closer
than any of our subs.
You scramble that jet...
That is the island
of Manhattan, Councilman.
Until I'm certain
my team can't hold it,
I will not order
a nuclear strike
against a civilian population.
If we don't hold them here,
we lose everything.
If I send that bird out,
we already have.
Oh, you.
Hawkeye!
Nat, what are you doing?
A little help?
I got him.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[GROANS]
Enough!
You are, all of you,
beneath me!
I am a god,
you dull creature.
And I will not
be bullied by...
Puny god.
[WHIMPERS]
SELVIG: The scepter...
Doctor.
Loki's scepter.
The energy.
The Tesseract can't fight,
but you can't
protect against yourself.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know
what you were doing.
Actually, I think I did.
I built in a safety
to cut their power source.
Loki's scepter.
It may be able
to close the portal.
And I'm looking
right at it.
[GRUNTING]
JARVIS: Sir,
we will lose power
before we penetrate
that shell.
Jarvis, you ever hear
the tale of Jonah?
JARVIS: I wouldn't
consider him a role model.
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[CRIES OUT IN PAIN]
[GROWLS]
[ROARING]
COUNCILWOMAN:
Director Fury is no
longer in command.
Override order 7-Alpha-1-1.
PILOT:
7-Alpha-1-1, confirmed.
We're go for takeoff.
Sir, we have
a bird in motion!
Anyone on the deck,
we have a rogue bird.
We need to shut it down!
Repeat,
takeoff is not authorized.
Stark, do you hear me?
You have a missile
headed straight for the city.
STARK: How long?
FURY: Three minutes, max.
The payload
will wipe out Midtown.
Jarvis, put everything we got
into the thrusters.
JARVIS: I just did.
PILOT: Package is sent.
Detonation in
2 minutes, 30 seconds, mark.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[HAMMER CLANGING]
Are you ready
for another bout?
What, are you
getting sleepy?
Right at the crown!
I can close it.
Can anybody copy?
I can shut the portal down.
Do it!
STARK: No, wait.
Stark, these things
are still coming.
I got a nuke coming in.
It's gonna blow
in less than a minute.
And I know
just where to put it.
ROGERS: Stark, you know
that's a one-way trip.
Save the rest
for the turn, J.
JARVIS: Sir,
shall I try Miss Potts?
Might as well.
REPORTER:
The streets of New York City
have become a battleground.
The Army is here trying
to contain the violence
but clearly, it is outmatched.[PHONE VIBRATING]
And I have to say,
in all my years
of reporting,
I have never seen
anything like this.
We have limited information
on the team,
but we do know that
billionaire Tony Stark's
Iron Man...
[EXERTIVE GRUNT]
[ALL CHEERING]
[JARVIS POWERING DOWN]
[CHITAURI POWERING DOWN]
Come on, Stark.
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
Close it.
Son of a gun.
He's not slowing down.
Is he breathing?
[ROARS]
[GASPS]
What the hell?
What just happened?
Please tell me
nobody kissed me.
We won.
[SIGHS]
All right, yay!
Hurray. Good job, guys.
Let's just not
come in tomorrow.
Let's just take a day.
Have you ever
tried shawarma?
There's a shawarma joint
about two blocks from here.
I don't know what it is,
but I want to try it.
We're not finished yet.
And then shawarma after.
[GROANING]
If it's all the same to you,
I'll have that drink now.
Despite the devastation
of what has been confirmed
as an
extraterrestrial attack,
the extraordinary heroics
of the group known
as the Avengers
has been to many a cause
not only for comfort,
but for celebration.
It's just really
great knowing
they're out there.
That someone
is watching over us.
I love you, Thor!
And then these guys were
like...[MIMICS LASERS]
And then the air goes...
[MIMICS EXPLOSION]
And this green guy walks up
and he goes...[ROARS]
I don't know.
I don't exactly feel safer
with those things out there.
It just seems that
there's a lot they're
not telling us.
Superheroes in New York?
Give me a break.
These so-called "heroes"
have to be held
responsible
for the destruction
done to this city.
This was their fight.
Where are they now?
REPORTER: Tough questions
are being asked
about the Avengers themselves.
Their sudden appearance
and equally sudden
disappearance...
WOMAN: What, this is all
somehow their fault?
Captain America
saved my life.
Wherever he is, and
wherever any of them are,
I would just...
I would want to say thank you.
Where are the Avengers?
I'm not currently
tracking their whereabouts.
I'd say they've earned
a leave of absence.
COUNCILWOMAN:
And the Tesseract?
FURY: The Tesseract
is where it belongs.
Out of our reach.
COUNCILMAN 1:
That's not your call.
I didn't make it.
I just didn't argue
with the god that did.
COUNCILMAN 1:
So, you let him take it
and the war criminal, Loki,
who should be
answering for his crime.
FURY: Oh,
I think he will be.
COUNCILWOMAN:
I don't think you understand
what you've started,
letting the Avengers
loose on this world.
They're dangerous.
FURY: They surely are,
and the whole world knows it.
Every world knows it.
Was that the point
of all this?
A statement?
FURY: A promise.
HILL: Sir,
how does it work now?
They've gone
their separate ways.
Some, pretty extremely far.
If we get into a situation
like this again,
what happens then?
They'll come back.
HILL: Are you really
sure about that?
FURY: I am.
Why?
Because we'll need them to.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING]
THE OTHER: Humans.
They are not
the cowering wretches
we were promised.
They stand.
They are unruly,and therefore cannot be ruled.
To challenge them
is to court death.