TONY: Been a while since
I was up here in front of you.
Maybe I'll do us all a favor
and just stick to the cards.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
There's been speculation
that I was involved in
the events that occurred
on the freeway
and the rooftop...
CHRISTINE: Sorry, Mr. Stark,
do you honestly expect us
to believe that
that was a bodyguard
in a suit that
conveniently appeared,
despite the fact that you
sorely despise bodyguards?
Yes.
And this mysterious
bodyguard
was somehow equipped
with an undisclosed
Stark high-tech
powered battle...
Moscow
I know that
it's confusing.
It is one thing to question
the official story,
and another thing entirely
to make wild accusations,
or insinuate
that I'm a superhero.
I mean, let's face it,
I'm not the heroic type.
(MAN TRANSLATING
SIMULTANEOUSLY IN RUSSIAN)
A laundry list
of character defects,
all the mistakes I've made,
largely public.
The truth is
I am Iron Man.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ANTON CALLING OUT WEAKLY)
Ivan...
Ivan.
Vanya.
(ANTON COUGHING)
(ANTON GASPING)
(TV ANNOUNCER
CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN)
(IN RUSSIAN)
That should be you.
Don't listen to that crap.
I'm sorry.
All I can give you
is my knowledge.
(ANTON COUGHS)
(ANTON EXHALES)
(ROARING)
(POWER SURGING)
(SQUAWKS)
(CHUCKLING)
MAN: (ON RADIO)
270 at 30 knots.
Holding steady
at 15,000 feet.
You are clear
for exfiltration
over the drop zone.
♪ All you women
who want a man of the street
♪ But you don't know
which way you wanna turn
♪ Just keep a coming
and put your hand out to me
♪ 'Cause I'm the one
who's gonna make you burn
♪ I'm gonna take you down
Down, down, down
♪ So don't you fool around
♪ I'm gonna pull it
Pull it, pull the trigger
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(LOUD ROCK
PLAYING IN THE STADIUM)
♪ Too many women
with too many pills
♪ Shoot to thrill
Play to kill
Stark Expo - Flushing,
New York
♪ I got my gun at the ready
Gonna fire at will, yeah
♪ Shoot you, shoot you
Shoot you, shoot you down
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
♪ I'm gonna shoot to thrill
♪ Play to kill
♪ Shoot to thrill
♪ Yeah, ooh, yeah ♪
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Tony! Tony! Tony! Tony!
Oh! It's good
to be back.
You missed me?
MAN: Blow something up!
I missed you, too.
Blow something up?
I already did that.
(PEOPLE CHUCKLING)
I'm not saying that
the world is enjoying
its longest period
of uninterrupted peace
in years because of me.
(CROWD CHEERING)
I'm not saying that from
the ashes of captivity,
never has a greater phoenix
metaphor been personified
in human history.
I'm not saying that
Uncle Sam can kick back
on a lawn chair,
sipping on an iced tea
because I haven't
come across anyone
who's man enough
to go toe-to-toe
with me on my best day.
(CHEERING LOUDLY)
WOMAN:
I love you, Tony!
Please, it's not about me.
It's not about you.
It's not even about us.
It's about legacy.
It's about what we
choose to leave behind
for future generations.
And that's why
for the next year
and for the first
time since 1974,
the best and
brightest men
and women
of nations
and corporations
the world over
will pool their resources,
share their collective vision,
to leave behind
a brighter future.
(CHEERING)
It's not about us.
Therefore, what I'm saying,
if I'm saying anything,
is welcome back
to the Stark Expo.
And now, making
a special guest appearance
from the great beyond
to tell you what
it's all about,
please welcome
my father, Howard.
Everything is achievable
through technology.
Better living, robust health,
and for the first time
in human history,
the possibility
of world peace.
So, from all of us here
at Stark Industries,
I would like to personally
introduce you to the
City of the Future.
Technology holds
infinite possibilities
for mankind,
and will one day rid
society of all its ills.
Soon, technology
will affect the way you
live your life every day.
No more tedious work,
leaving more time
for leisure activities
and enjoying the sweet life.
The Stark Expo. Welcome.
(CROWD CHEERING)
We are coming to you
live from the kickoff
of the Stark Expo,
where Tony Stark
has just walked offstage.
Don't worry
if you can't make it
down here tonight
because this Expo
goes on all year long.
And I'm gonna be here
checking out
all the attractions
and the pavilions
and the inventions
from all around the world.
Make sure you join me...
All right, it's a zoo
out there, watch out.
Open up, let's go.
TONY: Hey!
Nice to see you.
All right. Thank you.
I remember you.
WOMAN: Tony, Tony...
TONY: Hey, hey...
Call me.
HAPPY: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on, come on.
TONY: Hello.
It would be a pleasure.
HAPPY: Okay.
TONY: See you, buddy.
This is Larry.
TONY: Hey,
the oracle of Oracle.
What a pleasure.
Nice to see you.
Call me. Call me.
HAPPY: Larry King.
TONY: Larry!
Ah, yes,
my people, my people.
Come on, Tony.
There we go.
Very mellow.
That wasn't so bad.
No, it was perfect.
Look what we got here,
the new model.
Hey, does she come
with the car?
I certainly hope so.
Hi.
And you are?
Marshal.
Irish. I like it.
Pleased to
meet you, Tony.
I'm on the wheel.
Do you mind?
Where you from?
Bedford.
What are you
doing here?
Looking for you.
Yeah? You found me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What are you
up to later?
Serving subpoenas.
Yikes.
He doesn't like
to be handed things.
Yeah, I have a peeve.
I got it.
You are hereby
ordered to appear
before the Senate
Armed Services Committee
tomorrow morning
at 9:00 a.m.
Can I see a badge?
You wanna see
the badge?
He likes the badge.
You still like it?
Yep.
How far are we
from D.C.?
D.C.? 250 miles.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GAVEL BANGING)
Washington, D.C.
STERN: Mr. Stark,
could we pick up now
where we left off?
(BANGING GAVEL)
Mr. Stark. Please.
Yes, dear?
Can I have
your attention?
Absolutely.
Do you
or do you not possess
a specialized weapon?
I do not.
You do not?
I do not. Well, it depends
on how you define
the word "weapon."
The Iron Man weapon.
My device does not
fit that description.
Well... How would
you describe it?
I would describe it
by defining it as
what it is, Senator.
As?
It's a high-tech
prosthesis.
(ALL LAUGHING)
That is... That is...
That's actually
the most apt description
I can make of it.
It's a weapon.
It's a weapon,
Mr. Stark.
Please, if your priority
was actually the well-being
of the American citizen...
My priority is to get
the Iron Man weapon
turned over to the people
of the United
States of America.
Well, you can forget it.
I am Iron Man.
The suit and I are one.
To turn over the Iron Man suit
would be to turn over myself,
which is tantamount
to indentured servitude
or prostitution,
depending on what
state you're in.
You can't have it.
Look, I'm no expert...
In prostitution?
Of course not.
You're a senator. Come on.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I'm no expert
in weapons.
We have somebody here
who is an expert on weapons.
I'd now like to call
Justin Hammer,
our current primary
weapons contractor.
Let the record reflect that
I observed Mr. Hammer
entering the chamber,
and I am wondering
if and when any actual expert
will also be in attendance.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(LAUGHS)
Absolutely. I'm no expert.
I defer to you, Anthony.
You're the wonder boy.
Senator, if I may.
I may well not be an expert,
but you know who
was the expert?
Your dad. Howard Stark.
Really a father
to us all, and to the
military-industrial age.
Let's just be clear.
He was no flower child.
He was a lion.
We all know why we're here.
In the last six months,
Anthony Stark
has created a sword
with untold possibilities.
And yet he insists
it's a shield.
He asks us to trust him
as we cower behind it.
I wish I were comforted,
Anthony, I really do.
I'd love to leave
my door unlocked
when I leave the house,
but this ain't Canada.
You know,
we live in a world
of grave threats,
threats that Mr. Stark
will not always
be able to foresee.
Thank you.
God bless Iron Man.
God bless America.
That is well said,
Mr. Hammer.
The committee would
now like to invite
Lieutenant Colonel
James Rhodes
to the chamber.
Rhodey? What?
Hey, buddy.
I didn't expect
to see you here.
Look, it's me, I'm here.
Deal with it. Let's move on.
I just...
Drop it.
All right,
I'll drop it.
STERN: I have before me
a complete report on
the Iron Man weapon,
compiled by Colonel Rhodes.
And, Colonel, for the record,
can you please
read page 57,
paragraph four?
You're requesting
that I read
specific selections
from my report, Senator?
Yes, sir.
It was my understanding
that I was going
to be testifying
in a much more comprehensive
and detailed manner.
I understand.
A lot of things
have changed today.
So if you could
just read...
You do understand
that reading
a single paragraph out of
context does not reflect
the summary of my final...
Just read it, Colonel.
I do. Thank you.
Very well.
"As he does not operate
within any definable
branch of government,
"Iron Man presents
a potential threat
"to the security
of both the nation
"and to her interests."
I did, however,
go on to summarize that
the benefits of Iron Man
far outweigh
the liabilities.
Uh... Uh... Uh...
And that it would
be in our interest...
That's enough, Colonel.
...to fold Mr. Stark...
That's enough.
...into the existing
chain of command, Senator.
I'm not a joiner,
but I'll consider
Secretary of Defense,
if you ask nice.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
We can amend
the hours a little bit.
I'd like to go on
and show, if I may,
the imagery
that's connected
to your report.
I believe it is
somewhat premature
to reveal these images
to the general
public at this time.
STERN: With all
due respect,
Colonel, I understand.
And if you could
just narrate those for us,
we'd be very grateful.
Let's have the images.
Intelligence suggests
that the devices seen
in these photos
are, in fact,
attempts at making
manned copies of
Mr. Stark's suit.
This has been corroborated
by our allies and local
intelligence on the ground,
indicating that these suits
are quite possibly,
at this moment, operational.
Hold on one second, buddy.
Let me see something here.
Oh! Boy, I'm good.
I commandeered your screens.
I need them.
Time for a little
transparency.
Now, let's see
what's really going on.
What is he doing?
If you will
direct your attention
to said screens...
I believe
that's North Korea.
(MAN CHATTERING ON TV)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING ON TV)
Can you turn that off?
Take it off.
Iran.
(MAN SHOUTING ON TV)
No grave immediate
threat here.
Is that Justin Hammer?
How did Hammer
get in the game?
Justin, you're on TV.
Focus up.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
HAMMER: Okay,
give me a left twist.
Left's good.
Turn to the right.
(MAN SCREAMING ON TV)
HAMMER: Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
TONY: Wow.
Yeah, I'd say
most countries,
five, 10 years away.
Hammer Industries, 20.
I'd like to point out that
that test pilot survived.
STERN: I think we're done,
is the point that he's making.
(STUTTERS) I don't think
there's any reason...
The point is,
you're welcome, I guess.
STERN: For what?
Because I'm your
nuclear deterrent.
It's working. We're safe.
America is secure.
You want my property?
You can't have it.
But I did you
a big favor.
I've successfully
privatized world peace.
What more do you want?
For now!
I tried to play ball
with these ass-clowns.
(BLEEP) you, Mr. Stark.
(BLEEP) you, buddy.
We're adjourned.
We're adjourned
for today.
Okay.
You've been a delight.
(MAN ON TV
TRANSLATING IN RUSSIAN)
My bond is
with the people.
And I will serve
this great nation
at the pleasure of myself.
If there's one
thing I've proven
it's that you can count
on me to pleasure myself.
(POWER SURGING)
Malibu, California
(ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO)
Wake up.
Daddy's home.
JARVIS: Welcome home, sir.
Congratulations on
the opening ceremonies.
They were such a success,
as was your Senate hearing.
And may I say how
refreshing it is
to finally see you in a video
with your clothing on, sir.
(CHUCKLES)
You!
I swear to God
I'll dismantle you.
I'll soak your motherboard.
I'll turn you
into a wine rack.
(POWERING DOWN)
How many ounces a day
of this gobbledegook
am I supposed to drink?
We are up to 80 ounces
a day to counteract
the symptoms, sir.
Check palladium levels.
Blood toxicity, 24%.
It appears that
the continued use
of the Iron Man suit
is accelerating
your condition.
Another core
has been depleted.
God, they're
running out quick.
I have run simulations
on every known element,
and none can serve
as a viable replacement
for the palladium core.
You are running
out of both time
and options.
(EXHALES)
Unfortunately, the device
that's keeping you alive
is also killing you.
Miss Potts is approaching.
I recommend that
you inform her...
TONY: Mute.
Uh-uh.
Is this a joke?
What are you thinking?
What?
(ANGRILY)
What are you thinking?
Hey, I'm thinking
I'm busy.
And you're angry
about something.
Do you have the sniffles?
I don't wanna get sick.
Did you just donate...
Keep your business.
...our entire modern art
collection to the...
Boy Scouts of America.
...Boy Scouts of America?
Yes. It is
a worthwhile
organization.
I didn't physically
check the crates but,
basically, yes.
And it's not
"our" collection,
it's my collection.
No offense.
No, you know what?
I think I'm actually
entitled
to say "our" collection
considering the time
that I put in,
over 10 years,
curating that.
It was a tax write-off.
I needed that.
You know, there's only
about 8,011 things
that I really need
to talk to you about.
Dummy. Hey,
stop spacing out.
The Bridgeport's
already machining
that part.
The Expo is a gigantic
waste of time.
I need you to wear
a surgical mask until
you're feeling better.
Is that okay?
That's rude.
There's nothing
more important to me
than the Expo.
It's my primary
point of concern.
I don't know
why you're...
The Expo is your
ego gone crazy.
Wow. Look at that.
That's modern art.
That's going up.
Oh, you've got
to be kidding.
I'm gonna put
this up right now.
This is vital.
Stark is in
complete disarray.
You understand that?
No. Our stocks have
never been higher.
Yes, from
a managerial
standpoint.
You are...
Well, if it's messy,
then let's double back.
Let me give you an example.
Let's move on to
another subject.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You are not taking down
the Barnett Newman
and hanging that up!
I'm not taking it down.
I'm just replacing
it with this.
Let's see what
I can get going here.
Okay, fine.
My point is,
we have already
awarded contracts
to the wind farm people.
Yeah.
Don't say "wind farm."
I'm already
feeling gassy.
And to the plastic
plantation tree,
which was your idea,
by the way.
Those people
are on payroll...
Everything was my idea.
...and you won't
make a decision.
I don't care
about the liberal
agenda anymore.
It's boring. Boring.
I'm giving you
a boring alert.
You do it.
I do what?
Excellent idea.
I just figured this out.
You run the company.
Yeah, I'm trying
to run the company.
Pepper, I need you
Well, stop trying
to do it and do it.
You will not
give me
the information...
I'm not asking you to try...
...in order to...
I'm asking you
to physically do it.
I need you to do it.
I am trying to do it.
Pepper, you're not
listening to me!
No, you are not
listening to me.
I'm trying to make you CEO.
Why won't you let me?
Have you been drinking?
Chlorophyll.
I hereby irrevocably
appoint you chairman
and CEO of Stark Industries,
effective immediately.
Yeah, done deal. Okay?
I've actually given this
a fair amount of thought,
believe it or not.
Doing a bit of headhunting,
so to speak,
trying to figure out
who a worthy successor
would be.
And then I realized
it's you.
It's always been you.
I thought there'd
be a legal issue,
but actually I'm capable
of appointing my successor.
My successor being you.
Congratulations?
Take it, just take it.
I don't know what to think.
Don't think. Drink.
(LAUGHING IN SHOCK)
There you go.
(MAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(TONY CHATTERING)
PEPPER: The notary's here!
Can you please come sign
the transfer paperwork?
TONY: I'm on happy time.
(GROANS)
Sorry.
What the hell was that?
It's called
mixed martial arts.
It's been around
for three weeks.
It's called dirty boxing.
There's nothing new about it.
TONY: All right,
put them up. Come on.
I promise you this is the
only time I will ask you
to sign over your company.
I need you to
initial each box.
Lesson one.
Never take your eye off...
(GRUNTING)
(BELL RINGS)
HAPPY: That's it.
I'm done.
What's your name, lady?
Rushman. Natalie Rushman.
Front and center.
Come into the church.
No. You're seriously
not gonna ask...
TONY: If it pleases
the court, which it does.
It's no problem.
I'm sorry.
He's very eccentric.
What?
Can you give her
a lesson?
No problem.
(WHISPERING) Pepper.
What?
Who is she?
She is from legal.
And she is potentially
a very expensive sexual
harassment lawsuit
if you keep
ogling her like that.
I need a new
assistant, boss.
Yes, and I've got
three excellent
potential candidates.
They're lined up
and ready to meet you.
I don't have time to meet.
I need someone now.
I feel like it's her.
No, it's not.
You ever boxed before?
I have, yes.
What, like, the Tae Bo?
Booty Boot Camp? Crunch?
Something like that?
(CLEARS THROAT)
How do I spell
your name, Natalie?
R-U-S-H-M-A-N.
PEPPER: What,
are you gonna
google her now?
TONY: Hmm? I thought
I was ogling her.
Oh, wow. Very, very
impressive individual.
PEPPER:
You're so predictable,
you know that?
She's fluent in
French, Italian,
Russian, Latin.
Who speaks Latin?
No one speaks Latin.
It's a dead language.
No one speaks Latin?
You can read Latin
or you can write Latin,
but you can't speak Latin...
Did you model in Tokyo?
'Cause she
modeled in Tokyo.
Well...
TONY: I need her.
She's got everything
that I need.
Rule number one,
never take your eye
off your opponent.
(CRACKING)
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
(GRUNTING HAPPILY)
PEPPER: Happy!
That's what
I'm talking about.
I just slipped.
You did?
Yeah.
(RINGING BELL)
Looks like a TKO to me.
Just...
I need your impression.
You have a quiet reserve.
I don't know,
you have an old soul.
I meant your fingerprint.
Right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, how are we doing?
Great.
Just wrapping up. Hey.
You're the boss.
Will that be all,
Mr. Stark?
No.
Yes, that will be all,
Ms. Rushman.
Thank you very much.
I want one.
No.
(TV ANNOUNCER
SPEAKING FRENCH)
You know, it's Europe.
Whatever happens
the next 20 minutes,
just go with it.
Go with it?
Go with what?
NATALIE: Mr. Stark?
Hey.
Hello.
How was your flight?
It was excellent.
Boy, it's nice to see you.
We have one photographer
from the ACM,
if you don't mind.
Okay?
Mmm-hmm.
When did
this happen?
What?
You made me do it.
I made you do what?
You quit. Smile.
Look right there.
Stop acting
constipated.
Don't flare your nostrils.
You are so predictable.
That's the amazing thing.
Right this way.
You look fantastic.
Why, thank you very much.
But that's unprofessional.
What's on the docket?
You have a 9:30 dinner.
Perfect. I'll be
there at 11:00.
Absolutely.
Is this us?
It can be.
Great. Make it us.
Okay.
Mr. Musk.
How are you?
Hi, Pepper.
Congratulations
on the promotion.
Thank you very much.
Elon, how's it going?
Those Merlin engines
are fantastic.
Thank you.
Yeah, I've got an idea
for an electric jet.
You do?
Yeah.
Then we'll
make it work.
You want a massage?
(SIGHING) Oh, God.
No, I don't want a massage.
I'll have Natalie make an...
I don't want
Natalie to do...
Don't want you tense.
By the way, I didn't mean
to spring this on you.
PEPPER: Thank you very much.
Green is not
your best color.
PEPPER: Oh, please.
Anthony! Is that you?
Hey, pal.
My least favorite
person on Earth.
Justin Hammer.
How you doing?
You're not the only
rich guy here
with a fancy car.
You know Christine Everhart
from Vanity Fair.
You guys know
each other?
Hi.
CHRISTINE: Yes.
Yes!
Yes, roughly.
CHRISTINE: We do.
BTW, big story. The new
CEO of Stark Industries.
Congratulations.
I know. I know.
My editor will kill me
if I don't grab
a quote for our
Powerful Women issue.
Can I?
Oh! Sure.
She's actually doing
a big spread on me
for Vanity Fair.
I thought I'd throw
her a bone, you know.
Right.
HAMMER: Right?
CHRISTINE: Yes.
Well, she did
quite a spread on
Tony last year.
And she wrote
a story as well.
PEPPER: It was
very impressive.
TONY: That was good.
PEPPER: Very well done.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go wash.
Don't leave me.
Hey, buddy.
How you doing?
I'm all right.
Looking gorgeous.
Please, this is tough.
Can I ask you...
Is this the first time...
Fromage.
Say, "Brie."
...that you guys
have seen each other?
God, that's so awful.
(LAUGHS)
Listen, is it the first time
you've seen each other since
the Senate?
Since he got his
contract revoked...
Actually,
it's on hold.
...when you were
attempting to...
That's not what I heard.
What's the difference
between "hold"
and "canceled"?
The truth?
Yes, what is?
No. The truth is...
Why don't we put that away?
The truth is, I'm actually
hoping to present something
at your Expo.
Well, if you invent
something that works,
I'll make sure
I get you a slot.
Mr. Stark,
your corner table
is ready.
Yes?
I actually have a slot
this year. Yes, I do.
Hammer needs a slot,
Christine.
HAMMER: (LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
We kid, yeah.
We kid. We're kidders.
(SIGHS)
Got any other bad ideas?
(FANS CLAMORING)
(RACING CAR ENGINES REVVING)
Tony!
Tony and I... Tony...
I love Tony Stark.
Tony loves me.
We're not competitors.
Him being out of
the picture created
tremendous opportunities
for Hammer Industries,
you know?
(STUTTERING)
Everything that
Tony and I do...
Well, what's the use
of having...
...is a healthy...
...and owning
a race car...
...competition.
...if you
don't drive it?
(FANS CHEERING)
Is he driving?
(TV ANNOUNCER
SPEAKING FRENCH)
Natalie. Natalie!
Yes, Miss Potts?
Did you know
about this?
This is the first that
I have known of it.
(SIGHS) This...
This cannot happen.
NATALIE: Absolutely.
I understand.
How can I help you?
Where's Happy?
He's waiting outside.
Okay, get him.
I need Happy.
Right away.
Tony's... You know, he...
We're not competitive.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know,
can you excuse me
just one second?
Just read me
what you wrote.
I will.
I will, after.
Just read it back to me.
But I have to make
one quick phone call.
Where are you going?
This is great.
I've got some
caviar coming.
This is great stuff.
I'll be right back.
WOMAN: Look!
MAN: That's Stark.
(ENGINES REVVING)
(REVVING ENGINE)
(RACE COMMENTATOR
CHATTERING OVER TANNOY)
(WOMAN ON TV
CHATTERING IN FRENCH)
(POWERING UP)
(MALE TV COMMENTATOR
EXCLAIMING IN FRENCH)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Go, go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hang on.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING IN ALARM)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Give me the case.
Here. Take it.
Where's the key?
It's in my pocket.
PEPPER: Car!
(GROANS)
PEPPER: Oh, my God!
(CAR HORN BLARING)
HAPPY: Are you okay?
Yeah.
Were you heading
for me or him?
I was trying
to scare him.
'Cause I can't tell!
Are you out of your mind?
Better security.
Get in the car right now!
I was attacked!
We need better security.
Get in the car!
TONY: You're CEO.
Better security measures.
God, it's embarrassing.
First vacation
in two years.
(PEPPER AND HAPPY SCREAMING)
PEPPER: Oh, my God!
I got him!
TONY: Hit him again.
Hit him again.
Football.
I got him!
Take the case! Take it!
Take the case!
HAPPY: Give him the case!
PEPPER: Stop
banging the car!
(PEPPER SCREAMING)
TONY: Calm down.
God! God!
Give me the case!
Please! Come on!
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICITY SURGING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(LAUGHS) You...
(IN RUSSIAN ACCENT) You lose.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
You lose. You lose, Stark.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
We ran his prints.
We got nothing back,
not even a name.
Where are we going?
Over there.
We're not even sure
he speaks English.
He hasn't said a word
since he got here.
Five minutes.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Pretty decent tech.
Cycles per second
were a little low.
You could have
doubled up
your rotations.
You focused the repulsor
energy through
ionized plasma channels.
It's effective.
Not very efficient.
But it's a passable
knock-off.
I don't get it.
A little fine tuning,
you could have made
a solid paycheck.
You could have sold it
to North Korea, China, Iran,
or gone right to
the black market.
You look like you got
friends in low places.
You come from a family
of thieves and butchers.
And now,
like all guilty men,
you try to rewrite
your own history.
And you forget
all the lives the Stark
family has destroyed.
Speaking of thieves,
where did you get
this design?
My father. Anton Vanko.
Well, I never
heard of him.
My father is the reason
you're alive.
The reason I'm alive
is 'cause you had a shot,
you took it, you missed.
Did I?
If you can make
God bleed,
the people will cease
to believe in him.
And there will be
blood in the water.
And the sharks will come.
The truth,
all I have to do is
sit here and watch
as the world
will consume you.
Where will you be watching
the world consume me from?
That's right. A prison cell.
I'll send you a bar of soap.
Hey, Tony.
Before you go,
palladium in the chest,
painful way to die.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
It's just unbelievable.
It proves that the genie
is out of the bottle
and this man has no idea
what he's doing.
He thinks of the Iron Man
weapon as a toy.
I was at a hearing
where Mr. Stark,
in fact, was adamant
that these suits can't
exist anywhere else,
don't exist anywhere
else, never will
exist anywhere else,
at least for five
to 10 years,
and here we are in
Monaco realizing,
"Uh-oh.
These suits exist now."
TONY: Mute.
He should be
giving me a medal.
That's the truth.
What is that?
This is your
in-flight meal.
Did you just make that?
Yeah. Where do you
think I've been
for three hours?
Tony,
what are you
not telling me?
I don't want
to go home.
At all.
Let's cancel my
birthday party and...
We're in Europe.
Let's go to Venice,
Cipriani.
Remember?
Oh, yes.
It's a great place to
be healthy.
I don't think this
is the right time.
We're in kind of a mess.
Yeah, but maybe that's
why it's the best time.
'Cause then we...
Well, I think as the CEO,
I need to show up.
As CEO, you are
entitled to a leave.
A leave?
A company retreat.
A retreat?
During a time like this?
Just a ride.
Well, I'm just saying,
to recharge our batteries
and figure it all out.
Not everybody runs
on batteries, Tony.
"Enjoy the potatoes."
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(TIMER BEEPING)
(ORDERING IN FRENCH)
(QUESTIONING IN FRENCH)
(NECK SNAPPING)
(SIREN BLARING)
(GUARDS SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(SOFT CLASSICAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, there he is.
There he is.
What an absolute
pleasure. Welcome.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Can we get the handcuffs
off my friend here?
Forgive me, I'm sorry.
I'm such a huge fan of yours.
I didn't want to make
a first impression like this.
He's not an animal.
Come on.
He's a human being.
Thank you.
(GUARD AND HAMMER
SPEAKING FRENCH)
(DISMISSIVELY) Oui, oui.
We're fine.
My name is
Justin Hammer.
I'd like to do some
business with you.
Please sit.
Dig in. What do we
have today, Jack?
We have some
salmon carpaccio.
HAMMER:
Salmon carpaccio.
Mmm-mmm.
Anything you want
here, we got it.
I like my dessert first.
I had this flown in
from San Francisco.
It's Italian, though.
Organic ice cream.
I got a sweet tooth.
Apparently you do,
too, for Tony Stark.
What I saw you
do to Tony Stark
on that track,
how you stepped up
to him in front of
God and everybody,
that was... Wow!
You spoke to me
with what you did.
And I know that you knew
that I'd be listening.
This is why I couldn't bear
to have you shipped off
to God knows where.
It would have been
such a waste of talent.
But if I might
make a suggestion,
you know,
you don't just go and
try and kill the guy.
I think, if I may,
you go after his legacy.
That's what you kill.
You and me,
we are a lot alike
in a lot of ways.
The only difference
between you and I is
that I have resources.
I think, if I may,
you need my resources.
Someone behind you,
a benefactor.
I'd like to be that guy.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Okay. Do you
speak English?
Because I can
get a translator.
I don't know. Have you
been understanding
everything I'm saying?
Very good, man.
(LAUGHING) Very good, man.
Hey! Huh?
Hey.
Yes?
I want my bird.
A bird? You want a bird?
I can get you a bird.
I can get you 10 birds.
(POUNDS TABLE)
I want my bird.
Well, okay.
Nothing's impossible.
I could...
Are we talking about...
Is this a bird
back in Russia?
Yes, but the fundamentals
of the company are still
very, very strong
despite the events
in Monaco.
Yes, of course.
The AP wants a quote.
(WHISPERS) Don't tell him.
Fax them...
Where is he?
He doesn't want
to be disturbed.
He's downstairs.
...what happened
in Monaco?
PEPPER: Yes, but...
But his continuing
erratic behavior
may lead many people
to ask themselves,
"Can this man
still protect us?"
PEPPER: Iron Man never
stopped protecting us.
The events in
Monaco proved that.
JARVIS: Query complete, sir.
Anton Vanko was
a Soviet physicist
who defected to
the United States
in 1963.
However,
he was accused of espionage
and was deported in 1967.
His son, Ivan,
who is also a physicist,
was convicted of
selling Soviet-era
weapons-grade
plutonium to Pakistan,
and served 15 years
in Kopeisk prison.
No further records exist.
Tony, you gotta
get upstairs
and get on top of this
situation right now.
Listen. I've been
on the phone with
the National Guard all day,
trying to talk them out
of rolling tanks up the PCH,
knocking down
your front door
and taking these.
They're gonna take
your suits, Tony, okay?
They're sick of the games.
You said nobody else
would possess this
technology for 20 years.
Well, guess what?
Somebody else
had it yesterday.
It's not
theoretical
anymore.
Are you
listening to me?
Are you okay?
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Let's go.
(GASPS)
Hey, man.
Hey, hey!
You all right?
Yeah, I should
get to my desk.
(GASPS)
See that cigar box?
Yeah.
It's palladium.
(TONY GROANING)
Is that supposed
to be smoking?
If you must know,
it's neutron damage.
It's from the reactor wall.
You had this
in your body?
And how about
the high-tech crossword
puzzle on your neck?
Road rash.
Thank you.
(SIGHING)
What are you
looking at?
I'm looking at you.
You wanna do
this whole lone
gunslinger act
and it's unnecessary.
You don't have
to do this alone.
You know, I wish
I could believe that.
I really do.
But you've gotta trust me.
Contrary to popular belief,
I know exactly
what I'm doing.
(SNORTS SOFTLY)
This is where we do it.
This is my humble abode.
You can work in
absolute peace.
Must be fun to
be dead, right?
No pressure.
Here they are.
I'm very excited.
They're combat-ready.
I may have done
a few miscalculations
and rushed the prototype
into production.
(CHUCKLING) Sue me,
I'm enthusiastic.
Go ahead,
take a look around.
(STAMMERING)
Oh, you don't
wanna do that.
You'll be able
to access that
as soon as we generate
some encrypted pass codes.
Can we generate
some encrypted
pass codes?
Get some of those
encrypted pass codes, Jack.
Never mind, I...
Wow. Okay. Good stuff.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
Sorry?
Software shit.
Uh-huh?
Well... (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
You're good. You really
blasted in past
the firewall there. Uh...
Let me show you where
you're gonna be
working primarily.
Go ahead, take a look.
Get a good look at that.
That's something, isn't it?
You know,
those are really just
for show and tell.
They're $125.7 million
a pop, so... Wait!
Oh, gosh. Uh...
(WHISPERS) Jesus Christ.
Get somebody up here.
Um, that's where
the pilot goes.
I'm having a tough time
finding volunteers. (LAUGHS)
I'll take care of that,
just leave it.
What you want them do?
Well, long term,
I want them to put me
in the Pentagon
for the next 25 years.
I want to make Iron Man
look like an antique.
I wanna go to
that Stark Expo,
I wanna take a dump
in Tony's front yard.
You know what
I'm talking about?
(CHUCKLES)
I can do that.
No problem.
Yeah?
Hey, fabulous! I love it.
Hey, this is our guy.
Didn't I tell you?
I had a feeling.
Do you know which watch
you'd like to wear
tonight, Mr. Stark?
I'll give
them a look.
I should cancel
the party, huh?
Probably.
Yeah. Cause it's, um...
Ill-timed.
Right, sends
the wrong message.
Inappropriate.
Is that dirty
enough for you?
Gold face, brown band.
The Jaeger.
I'll give that a look.
Bring them over here.
I'll take that.
Why don't you...
I gotta say it.
It's hard to get
a read on you.
Where are you from?
Legal.
Can I ask you a question,
hypothetically?
Bit odd.
If this was
your last birthday party
you were ever gonna have,
how would you
celebrate it?
I'd do whatever
I wanted to do
with whoever
it with.
(SIGHING)
(SCRATCHING)
♪ California
Knows how to party
VALET: Good evening.
MAN: Good evening.
Yes, sir, I understand.
No. No, sir, that will
not be necessary.
I'll handle it.
Sir, I personally guarantee
that within 24 hours,
Iron Man will be
back on watch.
♪ We keep it rockin'
We keep it rockin' ♪
Hey, Pepper.
I'm... I'm going
to go get some air.
What's wrong?
I don't know
what to do.
You gotta be kidding me.
(PEOPLE WHOOPING)
(CRASHING)
(TONY LAUGHING DRUNKENLY)
That's it. I'm making...
No, no, no.
Don't call anyone.
Pepper. This is ridiculous.
I just stuck
my neck out for this guy.
I know. I know.
I get it.
I'm gonna handle it, okay?
Just let me handle it.
Handle it.
Or I'm gonna have to.
You know, the question
I get asked most often is,
"Tony, how do you go
to the bathroom in the suit?"
Just like that.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(TONY GIGGLING DRUNKENLY)
Does this guy know how
to throw a party or what?
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
I love you.
Unbelievable!
Thank you so much.
Tony, we all thank you so much
for such a wonderful night.
And we're gonna
say good night now,
(GUESTS GROANING)
and thank you
all for coming.
No, no, no, we can't...
Wait, wait, wait.
We didn't have the cake.
We didn't blow
out the candles.
You're out of control, okay?
Trust me on this one, okay?
You're out of control,
gorgeous.
It's time to go to bed.
It's time.
Give me another smooch.
You're not going to be
happy about this.
Come on,
you know you want to.
(ENUNCIATING)
You just peed the suit.
I know. It has
a filtration system.
It's not sexy.
You could
drink that water.
Just send
everybody home, okay?
It's time to...
If you say so.
Okay.
I'll take this,
you take that.
Pepper Potts.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
She's right.
The party's over.
Then again,
the party was over for me,
like, an hour and a half ago.
The after-party
starts in 15 minutes!
(GUESTS CHEERING WILDLY)
And if anybody, Pepper,
doesn't like it,
there's the door.
(ENERGY BOLT FIRES)
Yeah!
Hit!
Pull!
(EXCLAIMING)
(CHEERING)
TONY: I think she
wants the Gallagher!
RHODES: I'm only
gonna say this once.
Get out.
You don't deserve
to wear one of these.
Shut it down!
Goldstein.
Yes, Mr. Stark?
(GIGGLING)
Give me a phat beat
to beat my buddy's ass to.
(BASS LINE PLAYING)
I told you
to shut it down.
TONY: Now, put that thing
back where you found it
before someone gets hurt.
Really?
Sorry, pal,
but Iron Man doesn't
have a sidekick.
Sidekick this!
Had enough?
PEPPER: Natalie!
Miss Potts.
Don't you "Miss Potts" me!
I'm on to you.
You know what?
Ever since you came here...
(SHRIEKS)
HAPPY: Pepper!
Get out of here.
TONY: You want it?
Take it!
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ROARS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Put your hand down.
You think you
got what it takes
to wear that suit?
We don't have
to do this, Tony.
You wanna be
the War Machine,
take your shot.
Put it down!
You gonna take a shot?
No!
Drop it, Tony!
Take it!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(BEEPING)
(SYSTEMS POWERING UP)
(ON RADIO) Edwards Tower,
this is Lieutenant
Colonel James Rhodes,
inbound from
three miles east
at 5,000 feet...
(MEN CHATTERING)
(RUMBLING APPROACHING)
(WINDOWS RATTLING)
Colonel.
Major.
Wow.
Yeah.
Let's take it inside.
MAJOR: Clear the area.
Sir!
I'm gonna have to ask you
to exit the donut.
I told you I don't wanna join
your super-secret boy band.
(CHUCKLES) No, no, no.
See, I remember, you do
everything yourself.
How's that
working out for you?
It's... It's... It's...
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna get off
on the wrong foot.
Do I look at the patch
or the eye?
Honestly,
I'm a bit hung over.
I'm not sure if you're real
or if I'm having...
I am very real.
I'm the realest person
you're ever gonna meet.
Just my luck.
Where's the staff here?
That's not
looking so good.
TONY: I've been worse.
NATALIE: We've secured
the perimeter,
but I don't think we should
hold it for too much longer.
TONY: Huh!
You're...fired.
That's not up to you.
Tony, I want you
to meet Agent Romanoff.
Hi.
I'm a S.H.I.E.L.D. shadow.
Once we knew you
were ill, I was tasked
to you by Director Fury.
I suggest you apologize.
You've been very busy.
You made your girl
your CEO, you're giving
away all your stuff.
You let your friend
fly away with your suit.
Now, if I didn't
know better...
You don't know better.
I didn't give it to him.
He took it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He took it?
You're Iron Man
and he just took it?
The little brother walked
in there, kicked your ass
and took your suit?
Is that possible?
Well, according to Mr. Stark's
database security guidelines,
there are redundancies
to prevent unauthorized
usage.
(SNORTS SOFTLY)
What do you want from me?
What do we want
from you? Uh-uh.
(STRESSING)
What do you
want from me?
You have become
a problem, a problem
I have to deal with.
Contrary to your belief,
you are not the center
of my universe.
I have bigger
problems than you
in the southwest
region to deal with.
Hit him.
(GROANS) Oh, God,
are you gonna steal
my kidney and sell it?
Could you please
not do anything awful
for five seconds?
What did she
just do to me?
What did we
just do for you?
That's lithium dioxide.
It's gonna take the edge off.
We're trying to get
you back to work.
Give me a couple
of boxes of that.
I'll be right as rain.
It's not a cure,
it just abates
the symptoms.
Doesn't look like
it's gonna be an easy fix.
Trust me, I know.
I'm good at this stuff.
I've been looking
for a suitable
replacement for palladium.
I've tried every combination,
every permutation of
every known element.
Well, I'm here to tell you,
you haven't tried them all.
Hey, hey, hey.
Special delivery.
Candygram.
HAMMER: I brought you
something. Oh, yeah.
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
(CHUCKLING)
We got you
the bird, pal!
This is not my bird.
What do you mean?
That's the bird.
This is the bird. Yeah!
Pulled a lot of strings
to get this bird.
This is a great bird.
It's a beautiful bird.
We got this all the way
from Russia.
(POUNDS TABLE)
Hey, man,
this not my bird.
Well, listen,
even if it's not the bird,
I mean, this is
a gorgeous bird.
I mean, you know,
look, don't get so attached
to things. Learn to let go.
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
Wait a minute.
Jack, what is that?
Is that...
That's not a helmet.
What is that?
Um...
Ivan...
What's this? Jack.
Is that a helmet?
It doesn't look
like a helmet to me.
How... How are you supposed
to get a head in there?
Jack, could you put
your head in there?
No.
Try to put your
head in there.
Go ahead. Try to put
your head in there.
See, Ivan? He can't put his
head in there. That's...
That's not a helmet.
It's a head. I need
to put a guy in there.
I need to fit
a person in that suit.
You understand?
Drone better.
What? Drone better?
Why is drone better?
People make problem.
Trust me. Drone better.
Ivan, you know, I like you.
I got you the bird.
You said, "No problem."
That's what you said to me.
Now I need suits.
The government wants suits.
Like Iron Man.
You understand?
That's what the people want.
That's what's gonna
make them happy.
Hey, man.
Don't get too
attached to things.
Learn to let go.
These drones better
steal the show, Ivan.
You understand?
Better rock my world, Ivan.
Unbelievable.
This ought to get
the Senate off my ass.
It's functional?
Fully mission-capable.
Good.
Get Hammer down here
to weaponize it.
Sir?
Justin Hammer's
making a weapons
presentation at the Expo.
We'd like this
to introduce it.
Sir, I don't believe
that the Expo...
Colonel, the world needs
to see this fast.
We've got to make
this happen.
Yes, General,
but...
It's also an order.
Yes, sir.
Good work, Colonel.
You've made
your country proud.
Thank you, sir.
That thing in your
chest is based on
unfinished technology.
No, it was finished.
It has never been
particularly effective
until I miniaturized
it and put it in my...
No. Howard said
the arc reactor
was the stepping stone
to something greater.
He was about to kick off
an energy race that was
gonna dwarf the arms race.
He was on to something big,
something so big
that it was gonna make
the nuclear reactor
look like a triple-A battery.
Just him,
or was Anton Vanko
in on this, too?
Anton Vanko is the
other side of that coin.
Anton saw it as
a way to get rich.
When your father found out,
he had him deported.
When the Russians
found out
he couldn't deliver,
they shipped his
ass off to Siberia
and he spent the next 20 years
in a vodka-fuelled rage.
Not quite the environment
you want to raise a kid in,
the son you had the
misfortune of crossing
paths with in Monaco.
You told me I hadn't
tried everything.
What do you mean
I haven't tried everything?
What haven't I tried?
He said that
you were the only person
with the means and knowledge
to finish what he started.
He said that?
Mmm.
Are you that guy?
Hmm? Are you?
'Cause if you are,
then you can solve
the riddle of your heart.
I don't know
where you get
your information,
but he wasn't
my biggest fan.
What do you remember
about your dad?
He was cold,
he was calculating.
He never told me
he loved me.
He never even
told me he liked me,
so it's a little
tough for me to digest
when you're telling me
he said the whole future
was riding on me
and he's passing it down.
I don't get that.
You're talking about a guy
whose happiest day
was when he shipped me off
to boarding school.
That's not true.
Well, then, clearly
you knew my dad
better than I did.
As a matter of fact, I did.
He was one of the founding
members of S.H.I.E.L.D.
What?
I got a 2:00.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's this?
Okay,
you're good, right?
No, I'm not good.
You got this?
Right? Right?
Got what? I don't even know
what I'm supposed to get.
Natasha will remain
a floater at Stark
with her cover intact.
You remember
Agent Coulson, right?
Yeah.
Oh, and Tony,
remember,
I got my eye on you.
We've disabled
all communications.
No contact with
the outside world.
Good luck.
Please.
First thing, I need
a little bodywork.
I'll put in a little
time at the lab.
If we could send
one of your goon squad
down to The Coffee Bean,
Cross Creek,
for a Starbucks run,
or something like that,
that'd be nice.
I'm not here for that.
I've been authorized
by Director Fury
to use any means necessary
to keep you on premises.
If you attempt to leave
or play any games,
I will tase you
and watch Supernanny
while you drool
into the carpet.
Okay?
I think I got it, yeah.
Enjoy your evening's
entertainment.
Think this is
the power source?
Major, this is not
a scientific exercise.
Let's just focus on
arming it, all right?
Yes, sir.
HAMMER: Oh, yes!
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Is it my birthday?
You got it.
What did you do?
(SIGHING REVERENTLY) Oh!
Is this what
I think it is?
Yes, it is.
Hammer,
I want to know what
you're gonna do for us.
What am I going
to do for you?
Well, the first thing
I'm gonna do for you
is I'm gonna upgrade
your software.
And then, second,
I think I should...
That's not what
I'm talking about.
I'm talking
about firepower.
Well, you're talking
to the right guy.
(CRUNCHING)
Claridge Hi-Tec,
semi-automatic, 9mm pistol.
Too downtown? I agree.
M24 shotgun, pump action.
Five-round magazine.
You know what?
You're not a hunter.
What am I talking about?
I'm getting rid of it.
This is the FN-2000
from Belgium.
They do make something
better than waffles.
It's beautiful,
but I can tell this isn't
disco enough for you,
so I'm gonna
put it right here.
You're looking at
a Milkor 40mm
grenade launcher.
Tear gas, smoke.
Hippie control.
You're tough.
Let me tell you something.
Size does matter.
Don't let anyone
tell you different.
This is an M134
7.62 Minigun.
Six individual barrels.
The torso taker, powder maker.
Our boys in uniform
call it Uncle Gazpacho,
or Puff the Magic Dragon.
Okay.
These are the Cubans, baby.
This is the Cohibas,
the Montecristos.
This is a kinetic-kill,
side-winder vehicle
with a secondary
cyclotrimethylenetrinitramine
RDX burst.
It's capable of busting
the bunker under the
bunker you just busted.
If it were any smarter,
it would write a book.
A book that would make
Ulysses  look like
it was written in crayon.
It would read it to you.
This is my Eiffel Tower.
This is my
Rachmaninoff's Third.
My Pieta.
It's completely elegant.
It's bafflingly beautiful.
It's capable of reducing
the population of any
standing structure to zero.
I call it the Ex-Wife.
That's the best I got.
Are we gonna do this?
Give me something here.
You're like a sphinx.
I can't read you.
I think I'll take it.
Which one?
All of it.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
Everything is achievable
through technology.
Better living,
robust health
and for the first time
in human history,
the possibility
of world peace.
I'm Howard Stark,
and everything
you'll need for the future
can be found right here.
City of the Future?
City of Tomorrow? City of...
I'm Howard Stark,
and everything
you'll need in the future
can be found right here.
So, from all of us
at Stark Industries,
I would like
to personally...
Tony, what are you
doing back there?
What is that? Put that back.
(FIRMLY) Put it back
where you got it from.
Where's your mother? Maria?
Go on. Go, go, go, go.
All right,
I think we got...
I'll... I'll...
I'll come in and...
Are you waiting on me?
So, from all of us
at Stark Industries,
I'd like to
personally show you
my ass.
I'd like to...
I can't... This is...
I can't...
We have this, don't we?
This is a ridiculous way...
Everything
is achievable
through technology.
Tony?
You're too young
to understand this right now,
so I thought I would
put it on film for you.
I built this for you.
And someday
you'll realize that it
represents a whole lot more
than just people's inventions.
It represents my life's work.
This is the key
to the future.
I'm limited by the technology
of my time, but one day
you'll figure this out.
And when you do,
you will change the world.
What is and always will be
my greatest creation
is you.
(POWERFUL ENGINE REVVING)
(BOTH SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
$6. Six.
I don't have
any dough.
Here.
No, sir,
that's too much.
No, it's fine.
Take that.
It's fine.
No, senor.
Take it. Take it.
I don't like people
handing me things.
If you just
drop that there,
that'd be great.
Are you Iron Man?
Sometimes.
We believe in you!
It was an illegal seizure
of trademark property.
Miss Potts?
TONY: Relax.
SECRETARY: Mr. Stark...
TONY: Is here.
He refuses...
I don't. It's fine.
I'll just be a second.
Listen, it's our position
that Stark has
and continues to maintain
proprietary ownership
of the Mark II platform.
MAN ON TV:
When Mr. Stark announced
he was indeed Iron Man,
he was making
a promise to America.
PEPPER: No, the suit
belongs to us.
We trusted that he
would look out for us.
Yeah, but you're not...
Burt...
He obviously did not.
And now we learn
that his secretary...
Yes, it does.
...a woman named
Virginia "Pepper" Potts,
has been appointed
as CEO of Stark Industries.
What are her qualifications?
(FIRMLY) No.
Ms. Potts is doing nothing
to manage this terrible...
TONY: Mute.
PEPPER: No...
Burt... Burt...
Burt, listen to me.
Don't tell me that
we have the best patent
lawyers in the country
and then not
let me pursue this.
I'll get this
stuff out of here.
Well, then,
tell the President
to sign an order.
(SIGHS) We'll talk
about it at the Expo.
Hammer's giving
some presentation
tomorrow evening.
Will Tony Stark
be there?
Will I?
No, he will not. Bye.
I would like to be.
Got a minute?
No.
Come on,
you just got off the phone.
You're fine, 30 seconds.
Twenty-nine. Twenty-eight.
Okay, I, um...
I was just
driving over here,
and I thought I was coming
to basically apologize,
but I'm not.
Oh, you didn't come
here to apologize?
Look, that goes
without saying,
and I'm working on that.
But I haven't been
entirely upfront with you,
and I just want
to try to make good.
Can I move this?
This is crazy.
It's like
a Ferris wheel going.
I'm trying to get some...
No.
(TONY CLEARS THROAT)
Do you know
how short life is?
And if I never
got to express...
And by the way,
this is somewhat
revelatory to me.
And I don't care...
I mean, I care.
It would be nice.
I'm not expecting you to...
Look, here's what
I'm trying to say.
I'm just gonna say it.
Let me stop you
right here, okay?
Because if you say
"I" one more time,
I'm gonna
actually hurl something
at your head, I think.
I am trying
to run a company.
Do you have any idea
what that entails?
Yes.
People are relying
on you to be Iron Man
and you've disappeared,
and all I'm doing
is putting out your fires
and taking the heat for it.
I am trying to do the job
that you were meant to do.
Did you bring me
strawberries?
Did you know that there's
only one thing on Earth
that I'm allergic to?
Allergic to strawberries.
Mmm-hmm.
This is progress, Pepper.
I knew
there was a correlation
between you and this.
I need you...
I need you, too.
That's what
I'm trying to...
...to leave now.
Ms. Potts?
Hi, come on in.
Wheels up in 25 minutes.
Thank you.
Anything else, boss?
I'm good, Hap.
No, I'll be
just...another minute.
I lost both the kids
in the divorce.
(LAUGHS)
No.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Are you blending in
well here, Natalie?
Here at Stark Enterprises?
Your name is Natalie,
isn't it?
I thought you two
didn't get along.
No. That's not so.
It's just me
you don't care for.
No? Nothing?
PEPPER: Actually,
while you're here,
maybe you and Natalie
could discuss the matter
of the personal belongings.
Absolutely.
I'm surprised you can
keep your mouth shut.
Boy, you're good. You are
mind-blowingly duplicitous.
How do you do it?
You just tear things...
You're a triple impostor.
I've never seen
anything like you.
Is there anything
real about you?
Do you even
speak Latin?
(SPEAKING LATIN)
Which means? Wait. What?
What did you just say?
It means you can either
drive yourself home or
I can have you collected.
You're good!
(SIGHS)
(BLOWS)
Jarvis, could you
kindly Vac-U-Form
a digital wire frame?
I need a manipulatable
projection.
JARVIS: 1974 Stark Expo
model scan complete, sir.
How many buildings
are there?
Am I to include the
Belgian waffle stands?
That was rhetorical.
Just show me.
Uh-huh. Um...
What does that look
like to you, Jarvis?
Not unlike an atom.
In which case
the nucleus would be here.
Highlight the unisphere.
Lose the footpaths.
Get rid of them.
What is it you're
trying to achieve, sir?
I'm discovering...
Correction.
I'm rediscovering
a new element, I believe.
Lose the landscaping,
the shrubbery, the trees.
Parking lots,
exits, entrances.
Structure the protons
and the neutrons using
the pavilions as a framework.
Dad.
Dead for almost 20 years,
and still taking me to school.
The proposed element
should serve as a viable
replacement for palladium.
Thanks, Dad.
Unfortunately,
it is impossible
to synthesize.
TONY: Uh-huh.
Get ready
for a major remodel, fellas!
We're back in hardware mode.
(GRUNTS)
(JACKHAMMER RATTLING)
(RATCHET CLICKING)
I heard you broke
the perimeter.
Uh, yeah.
That was, like,
three years ago.
Where you been?
I was doing
some stuff.
Yeah, well, me, too,
and it worked.
Hey, I'm playing for
the home team, Coulson,
you and all your
Fabulous Furry
Freak Brothers.
Now, are you gonna let me
work or break my balls?
What's this
doing here?
That's it.
Bring that to me.
You know what this is?
It's exactly what I need
to make this work.
Lift the coil.
Go, go.
Put your knees into it.
There you go. And...
Drop it. Drop it.
Perfectly level.
(SNORTS) I'm busy.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Goodbye.
I've been reassigned.
Huh.
Director Fury
wants me in New Mexico.
Fantastic.
Land of Enchantment.
So I'm told.
Secret stuff?
Something like that.
Good luck.
Bye.
Thanks.
We need you.
Yeah, more than you know.
Not that much.
JARVIS: Initializing
prismatic accelerator.
(WHIRRING)
Approaching
maximum power.
(RUMBLING)
(SCREECHING)
Whoops!
That was easy.
JARVIS:
Congratulations, sir.
You have created
a new element.
(BEEPING)
Sir, the reactor
has accepted
the modified core.
I will begin
running diagnostics.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Ivan.
I got Senator Stern here.
Thought we'd swing over
and look at some of
the drone designs.
The drone is not
going to be ready.
Not ready?
What do you mean?
I can make presentation,
not demonstration.
(LAUGHING) What the hell
is the difference?
Presentation.
No fly. No shoot.
Well, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. (SIGHS)
What can you make them do?
I mean, this is a weapons
demonstration.
I can make salute.
You can make salute?
What do you mean,
"make salute"?
What the hell
does that mean, Ivan?
This is not what
we agreed to, okay?
You promised me
suits and then you
promised me drones.
Hey, man,
everything will be okay.
This is not
what I wanted.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
Hey, there he is.
It's the bird man.
Now you like the bird.
Is that right?
Is that your bird?
I'm confused.
You said it wasn't,
but now it looks like
you're best of pals.
You love that bird,
don't you?
You know what?
Take the bird.
(SQUAWKING)
Hey!
Take his pillows, too.
Both of them.
And his shoes.
Take his shoes.
I took your stuff.
How does that make you feel?
Do you feel bad? Good.
(SHOUTING) 'Cause
that's how I feel!
We had a contract!
I saved your life
and you give me suits.
That was our deal.
And you did not deliver.
I don't know if you're
a genius or a fraud.
I don't know what you are.
Something really,
really great
fell into my lap.
And if it hadn't,
I'd be at your
mercy tonight.
Now I have
a piece of Stark tech
that I pimped out myself.
And now your
overpriced
paperweights
are gonna look
like a backdrop
to my demonstration.
Do you dig what
I'm getting at here?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(CHUCKLING)
I don't know
if you know this,
(SHOUTING) but I
don't speak Russian!
I'm gonna leave now.
I'm gonna go to the Expo.
Maybe I'll even get laid.
You see these guys?
They're your babysitters.
They are not
to be trifled with.
When I get back,
we're gonna renegotiate
the terms of our agreement.
And you're gonna make
good on our arrangement
because if you don't,
you're gonna be
exactly what you were
when I found you,
a dead man.
You got that?
Maybe you can
watch me on TV.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SCOFFS)
TONY: Dummy, you,
can we clean up this mess?
You're killing me.
You know I don't...
(PHONE RINGING)
JARVIS: Incoming call
with a blocked number, sir.
My phone privilege
is reinstated. Lovely.
Coulson.
How's the Land
of Enchantment?
IVAN: Hey, Tony,
how you doing?  (LAUGHS)
I double cycle.
You what?
You told me double
cycle's more power.
Good advice.
You sound pretty sprightly
for a dead guy.
You, too.  (LAUGHS)
Trace him.
JARVIS: Sir.
Now, the true history
of Stark name will be written.
Jarvis, where is he?
Accessing the Oracle grid.
Eastern Seaboard.
What your father
did to my family
over 40 years,
I will do to you
in 40 minutes.
Sounds good. Let's get
together and hash it out.
JARVIS: Tri-State area.
Manhattan and outlying
boroughs.
I hope you're ready.
(DIALING TONE DRONING)
JARVIS: Call trace
incomplete.
(SIGHS)
JARVIS: Sir...
You want to run
some tests, run them.
And assemble the suit
while you're at it.
Put it together now.
We are unclear
as to the effects...
I don't want to
hear it, Jarvis.
(COUGHS)
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
That tastes like coconut.
And metal.
Oh, wow, yeah!
(ANNOUNCER CHATTERING OVER PA)
I'll keep the car
down here, all right?
Thank you, Happy.
ANNOUNCER:
...Justin Hammer.
His presentation
will begin shortly
in the main pavilion.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(PICK UP THE PIECES
PLAYING OVER PA)
Yeah!
That's what
I'm talking about.
Thanks for coming.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for far too long,
this country has had
to place its brave men
and women in harm's way,
but then the
Iron Man arrived,
and we thought
the days of losing lives
were behind us.
Sadly, that technology
was kept out of reach.
That's not fair.
That's not right.
And it's just too bad.
(SIGHING) Oh, Lord.
Regardless, it was
an impressive innovation,
one that grabbed
headlines the world over.
Well, today, my friends,
the press
is faced with quite
a different problem.
They are about
to run out of ink.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
(SOFTLY) Get that
out of here.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Ladies and gentlemen,
today I present to you
the new face of the
United States military.
The Hammer drone!
(THE CAISSONS GO
ROLLING ALONG  PLAYING)
HAMMER: Army!
Navy!
(ANCHORS AWEIGH  PLAYING)
(THE U.S. AIR FORCE  PLAYING)
Air Force!
Marines!
(THE MARINES' HYMN  PLAYING)
HAMMER: Yeah! Yeah! Whoo!
That's a hell of a lot better
than some cheerleaders,
let me tell you.
But as revolutionary
as this technology is,
there will always
be a need for man
to be present
in the theater of war.
Ladies and gentlemen,
today I am proud
to present to you
the very first prototype
in the Variable Threat
Response Battle Suit
and its pilot,
Air Force Lieutenant
Colonel James Rhodes.
What?
For America and its allies,
Hammer Industries
is reporting for...
(RUMBLING APPROACHING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING LOUDLY)
We got trouble.
RHODES:
Tony, there are
civilians present.
I'm here on orders.
Let's not do this right now.
TONY: Give them a wave.
HAMMER: Hey,
all right! Yeah!
TONY: All these people
are in danger.
We gotta get them
out of here.
You gotta trust me
for the next five minutes.
Yeah, I tried that.
I got tossed around
your house, remember?
Listen, I think
he's working with Vanko.
Vanko's alive?
HAMMER: Huh? Yeah!
Where is he?
What?
Where's Vanko?
Who?
Tell me.
What are you
doing here, man?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is that you?
RHODES:
No, I'm not doing that.
That's not me.
I can't move.
I'm locked up.
I'm locked up!
Get out of here.
Go! This whole
system's been compromised.
TONY: Let's take it outside.
(PEOPLE SHRIEKING)
No. No!
Jarvis, break in.
I need to own him.
Yes, sir.
Tony, Tony, I'm locked on.
I have target lock.
On what?
On you!
RHODES: Tony, on your six!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
What's going on?
What's happening?
The software's
been overridden.
What? What do you mean
it's been overridden?
What does that mean?
I think he slaved the drones.
That's impossible.
Call the guards.
All the phones
are down, sir.
HAMMER:
Well, then call their...
Call their cells.
Their cell phones
are not working,
either, sir.
He's locked us out
of the mainframe.
Who's locked you
out of the mainframe?
Please, please,
go away. Go away.
I've got this handled.
Have you now?
Yes, I do.
In fact,
if your guy hadn't showed up,
this wouldn't be happening.
So please,
now go away.
Thank you.
Listen, we got to get
these bitches out of here.
HAMMER: What?
(NATALIE EXCLAIMS)
You tell me
who's behind this.
Who's behind this?
(GROANING)
Ivan. Ivan Vanko.
Where is he?
He's at my facility.
I need NYPD, please.
No, no, no!
Command Central.
No, no, honey.
Don't call the authorities.
Okay. Right away.
Right away.
Step aside.
Tell me everything
you know. Go.
How are we doing, Jarvis?
Remote reboot
unsuccessful.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
SECURITY GUARD: This way.
Nobody's answering the phone.
What's going on?
Get in the car.
Take me to Hammer Industries.
I'm not taking
you anywhere.
Fine. You want
me to drive?
No, I'm driving.
Get in the car.
Nice work, kid.
RHODES: You got multiples
coming in on you.
Let's get this away
from the Expo.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
When we arrive,
I need you to watch
the perimeter.
I'm gonna enter the facility
and take down the target.
(CAR HORNS BLARING)
Watch the road.
I got it. I got it.
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
(MULTIPLE CAR ALARMS BLARING)
Listen, listen.
A pack just peeled off.
They're headed
back to the Expo.
Got it.
RHODES:
I'm closing on you.
Ordnance coming in
hot, Tony. Watch it.
NATALIE: Stay in the car.
I'm not staying
in the car.
I said,
stay in the car.
What are you wearing?
Look, I'm not
letting you go
in there alone.
(DOOR PANEL BEEPING)
You want to help?
Keep the car running.
Okay.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Hey, hey, hey.
You can't come in here.
SECURITY GUARD:
Hold on. Hey!
(SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
TECHNICIAN:
Each set of drones
is communicating
in its own
unique language.
Well, choose one
and focus on that.
Have you tried Russian?
Why don't you try Russian?
(GRUNTING)
MAN: (OVER RADIO) Attention.
We have intrusion on Grid W.
SECURITY GUARD:
We got it.
We're on our way.
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING) I got him!
(GRUNTING)
Rhodey,
you still locked on?
Yeah.
Drop your socks
and grab your Crocs.
We're about to get
wet on this ride.
Wait, wait, wait!
(GUNS COCKING)
He's gone.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Had to thin out the herd.
What's your 20?
(EXCLAIMING)
What are you doing?
I'm rebooting
Rhodey's suit.
(GRUNTING)
Tony!
(POWERING DOWN)
(TONY PANTING)
Reboot complete.
You got your
best friend back.
Thank you very much,
Agent Romanoff.
Well done with
the new chest piece.
I am reading
significantly
higher output
and your vitals
all look promising.
Yes, for the moment,
I'm not dying. Thank you.
What do you mean
you're not dying?
Did you just say
you're dying?
TONY: Is that you?
No, I'm not. Not anymore.
What's going on?
I was going to tell you.
I didn't want to alarm you.
You were gonna tell me?
You really were dying?
You didn't let me.
Why didn't you tell me that?
I was gonna make
you an omelet
and tell you.
Hey, hey.
Save it for the honeymoon.
You got incoming, Tony.
Looks like the fight's
coming to you.
Great. Pepper?
PEPPER: Are you okay now?
I am fine.
Don't be mad.
I will formally apologize...
I am mad!
...when I'm not fending off
a Hammeroid attack.
Fine.
We could have
been in Venice.
Oh, please.
(DISTORTED) Rhodes?
Snap out of it, buddy.
I need you.
They're coming.
Come on, let's roll.
(KNOCKING ON HELMET)
Get up.
Oh, man. You can
have your suit back.
You okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Tony, look,
I'm sorry, okay?
Don't be.
No. I should have
trusted you more.
I'm the one who put
you in this position.
Forget it.
No. It's your fault.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry.
Thank you. That's all
I wanted to hear.
Partner.
They're coming
in hot, any second.
What's the play?
Well, we want to take
the high ground, okay?
So let's put the biggest
gun up on that ridge.
Got you.
Where do you want to be?
Where are you going?
What're you talking about?
I meant me.
You have a big gun.
You are not the big gun.
Tony, don't be jealous.
No. It's subtle,
all the bells
and whistles.
Yeah. It's called
being a badass.
Fine.
All right.
You go up top.
I'll draw them in.
Don't stay down here.
This is the worst
place to be.
Okay, you got a spot.
Where's mine?
It's the kill box,
Tony. Okay? This is
where you go to die.
(ROARING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(WEAPON COCKS)
See that?
Yeah, yeah, nice.
Rhodey?
Get down.
Wow. I think you should
lead with that next time.
Yeah. Sorry, boss.
I can only use it once.
It's a one-off.
I told you that
five minutes ago.
That's your guy here.
Excuse me?
COP: You're being
placed under arrest.
Are you kidding me?
Hands behind your back, sir.
I'm trying to help here.
(LAUGHS) I get it.
I see what you're doing.
You're trying
to pin this on me, huh?
That's good. That's good.
You're starting
to think like a CEO,
taking out
the competition.
I like that.
You think you're making
a problem for me?
I'm gonna make
a problem for you.
I'm gonna be seeing
you again real soon.
When they get here,
I think you should
station them
at the south, east
and both west exits.
COP: We shut down
the 7 train in and out
of Willets Point already.
PEPPER: Well, have
city buses there to ferry
people to operating lines.
Yeah. Are you
coming with us?
No, I'm gonna stay
till the park is clear.
Okay.
NATALIE: Heads up.
You got one more
drone incoming.
This one looks different.
The repulsor signature
is significantly higher.
Good to be back.
Oh, this ain't
gonna be good.
I got something
special for this guy.
I'm gonna
bust his bunker
with the Ex-Wife.
With the what?
(WHIRRING)
(SOFT POP)
Hammer tech?
Yeah.
I got this.
(GRUNTING)
(TONY BELLOWING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
TONY: Rhodes. I got an idea.
You want to be a hero?
What?
I could really
use a sidekick.
Put your hand up.
RHODES: This is your idea?
Yep.
RHODES:
I'm ready. I'm ready!
Go, go, go!
TONY: Take it!
(PANTING)
(WEAKLY) You lose.
(BEEPING)
(BEEPING ACCELERATING)
All these drones
are rigged to blow.
We gotta get
out of here, man.
Pepper?
(BEEPING)
(PEPPER SCREAMS)
(SHRIEKS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, my God!
I can't take this anymore.
You can't? Look at me!
I can't take this.
My body, literally,
cannot handle the stress.
I never know if
you're gonna kill yourself
or wreck the whole company.
I think I did okay.
I quit. I'm resigning.
That's it.
What did you just say?
You're done?
That's surprising.
No, it's not surprising.
I get it.
You don't have to
make any excuses.
I'm... I'm...
I'm not making any excuses.
You actually were
just making excuses.
But you don't have to.
No, I wasn't
making an excuse.
I'm actually
very justified.
Listen. Hey, hey.
You deserve better.
Well...
You've taken such
good care of me.
I've been in a tough spot,
but you got me
through it, so...
Right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you
for understanding.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's talk clean-up.
I'll handle
the transition.
It'll be smooth.
Okay.
What about the press?
Because you only had
the job for a week.
That's gonna seem...
Well, with you
it's like dog years.
I know.
I mean, it's like
the Presidency...
Weird.
(SOFTLY) No,
it's not weird.
It's okay, right?
Yeah.
Run that by me again.
RHODES: I think
it was weird.
You guys
look like two seals
fighting over a grape.
I had just quit,
actually.
Yeah, so we're not...
You don't have to do that.
I heard the whole thing.
You should get lost.
I was here first.
Get a roof.
(TONY CHUCKLES)
I thought you were
out of one-liners.
That's the last one.
You kicked ass
back there,
by the way.
Thank you. You, too.
Listen,
my car got taken out
in the explosion,
so I'm gonna have to
hang on to your suit
for a minute, okay?
Not okay.
Not okay with that.
It wasn't a question.
How are you
gonna resign
if I don't accept?
(LAUGHS)
Hmm?
I don't think I want
you looking at that.
I'm not sure it pertains
to you anymore.
Now this, on the other hand,
is Agent Romanoff's
assessment of you.
Read it.
Uh...
"Personality overview.
Mr. Stark displays
compulsive behavior."
In my own defense,
that was last week.
"Prone to self-destructive
tendencies." I was dying.
I mean, please.
And aren't we all?
"Textbook narcissism"?
Agreed.
Okay, here it is. Uh...
"Recruitment assessment
for Avenger Initiative.
Iron Man? Yes."
I gotta think about it.
Read on.
"Tony Stark not...
"Not recommended"?
That doesn't
make any sense.
How can you approve me
but not approve me?
I got a new ticker.
(STAMMERING)
I'm trying to do
right by Pepper.
I'm in a stable-ish
relationship.
Which leads us
to believe
at this juncture
we'd only like to use
you as a consultant.
You can't afford me.
Then again, I will waive
my customary retainer
in exchange
for a small favor.
Rhodey and I are being
honored in Washington
and we need a presenter.
I'll see what I can do.
It is my honor
to be here today
to present these
distinguished awards
to Lieutenant Colonel
James Rhodes
and Mr. Tony Stark,
who is, of course,
a national treasure.
Thank you,
Lieutenant Colonel,
for such an exceptionally
distinguished performance.
You deserve this.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Stark. Thank you
for such an exceptionally
distinguished performance.
You deserve this.
Ow!
Oh, sorry.
Funny how annoying
a little prick
can be, isn't it?
Let's get a photo.
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
♪ Living easy, living free
♪ Season ticket
on a one-way ride
♪ Asking nothing
Leave me be
♪ Taking everything
in my stride
♪ Don't need reason
Don't need rhyme
♪ Ain't nothing
I would rather do
♪ Going down, party time
♪ My friends
are gonna be there, too
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ On the highway to hell
♪ Highway to hell
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ No stop signs, speed limit
♪ Nobody's gonna slow me down
♪ Like a wheel, gonna spin it
♪ Nobody's gonna mess me round
♪ Hey, Satan, payed my dues
♪ Playing in a rocking band
♪ Hey, Mama, look at me
♪ I'm on my way
to the promised land
♪ Whoo!
I'm on the highway to hell
♪ Highway to hell
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ Don't stop me
♪ Highway to hell
♪ And I'm going down
♪ All the way down
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ Oh, a bright new
morning is dawning
♪ Make way for tomorrow today
♪ Yes, a new tomorrow
is upon me
♪ To light up a brave new day
♪ Oh, the future's
brimming with promise
♪ And the promise
is heading our way
♪ So you can rise
on that shining horizon
♪ Make way for tomorrow today
♪ Daring new devices
will help us to succeed
♪ Better tools for living
will meet our every need
♪ Incredible inventions
through new technology
♪ Extending life's dimensions
for all humanity
♪ Modern marvels
rising around us
♪ Bringing progress
and dazzling display
♪ So we will rise
on that shining horizon
♪ Make way for tomorrow today
♪ Make way for tomorrow
♪ Today ♪
Sir, we've found it.