(BEEPING)
Wait for it.
Can I turn on the radio?
No.
ERIK: Jane,
you can't keep doing this.
The last 17 occurrences
have been predictable
to the second.
ERIK: Jane,
you're an astrophysicist,
not some storm chaser.
JANE: I'm telling you,
there's a connection
between these
atmospheric disturbances
and my research.
Erik, I wouldn't
have asked you
to fly out here if
I wasn't absolutely sure.
DARCY: Jane?
I think you want
to see this.
JANE: What is that?
ERIK: I thought you said
it was a subtle aurora!
Go!
Get closer.
Right. Good one.
Go!
(LAUGHING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
What are you doing?
I am not dying for
six college credits!
(DARCY EXCLAIMING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(DARCY AND JANE EXCLAIMING)
(GASPS)
DARCY: I think that was
legally your fault.
JANE: Get the first aid kit.
Do me a favor
and don't be dead.
Please.
Where did he come from?
ODIN: Once,
mankind accepted
a simple truth,
that they were not alone
in this universe.
Some worlds man believed
to be home to their gods.
Others, they knew to fear.
From a realm of
cold and darkness
came the Frost Giants,
(SCREAMS)
threatening to
plunge the mortal world
into a new ice age.
(ROARS)
But humanity would
not face this threat alone.
(YELLING)
Our armies drove
the Frost Giants
back into the heart
of their own world.
The cost was great.
In the end,
their king fell.
And the source
of their power
was taken from them.
With the last
great war ended,
we withdrew from
the other worlds
and returned home
to the Realm Eternal,
Asgard.
Here we remain
as a beacon of hope,
shining out across the stars.
And though we have fallen
into man's myths and legends,
it was Asgard
and its warriors
that brought peace
to the universe.
But the day will come
when one of you
will have to
defend that peace.
Do the Frost Giants
still live?
When I'm king,
I'll hunt the monsters down
and slay them all!
Just as you did, Father.
A wise king
never seeks out war.
But he must always
be ready for it.
I'm ready, Father.
So am I.
Only one of you
can ascend to the throne.
But both of you
were born to be kings.
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, please.
(SPEAR THUDDING)
Thor Odinson,
my heir,
my firstborn.
So long entrusted with
the mighty hammer Mjolnir,
forged in the heart
of a dying star,
its power has no equal,
as a weapon to destroy
or as a tool to build.
'Tis a fit companion
for a king.
I have defended Asgard
and the lives of the innocent
across the Nine Realms
from the time of
the great beginning.
Though the day has come...
Do you swear to guard
the Nine Realms?
I swear.
And do you swear
to preserve the peace?
I swear.
Do you swear
to cast aside
all selfish ambition
and to pledge yourself only
to the good of the Realms?
I swear!
Then, on this day,
I, Odin Allfather,
proclaim you...
The Frost Giants!
(SPEAR THUDDING)
THOR: The Jotuns must pay
for what they've done!
They have paid,
with their lives.
The Destroyer did its work,
the Casket is safe,
and all is well.
All is well?
They broke into
the weapons vault!
If the Frost Giants
had stolen even one
of these relics...
They didn't.
Well, I want to know why!
I have a truce with Laufey,
King of the Jotuns.
He just broke your truce!
They know you are vulnerable!
What action
would you take?
March into Jotunheim
as you once did.
Teach them a lesson.
Break their spirits
so they'll never dare
try to cross
our borders again.
You're thinking
only as a warrior.
This was an act of war!
It was the act of but a few,
doomed to fail.
Look how far they got!
We will find
the breach in our defenses
and it will be sealed.
As King of Asgard...
But you're not king!
Not yet.
(ROARING)
It's unwise
to be in my company
right now, Brother.
This was to be
my day of triumph.
It'll come.
In time.
What's this?
If it's any consolation,
I think you're right.
About the Frost Giants,
about Laufey,
about everything.
If they found
a way to penetrate
Asgard's defenses once,
who's to say they
won't try again?
Next time with an army.
Exactly.
There's nothing you can do
without defying Father.
No, no, no.
I know that look.
That's the only way
to ensure the safety
of our borders.
Thor, it's madness.
Madness?
What sort of madness?
We're going to Jotunheim.
VOLSTAGG: What?
This isn't like
a journey to Earth
where you summon
a little lightning
and thunder,
and the mortals
worship you as a god.
This is Jotunheim.
My father fought
his way into Jotunheim,
defeated their armies
and took their Casket.
We would just be
looking for answers.
It is forbidden!
(CHUCKLES)
My friends,
have you forgotten all that
we have done together?
Fandral, Hogun.
Who led you
into the most
glorious of battles?
You did.
And Volstagg,
to delicacies so succulent,
you thought you'd died
and gone to Valhalla?
(LAUGHS)
You did.
Yes!
And who proved wrong
all who scoffed at the idea
that a young maiden could be
one of the fiercest warriors
this realm has ever known?
I did.
True, but I
supported you, Sif.
My friends,
we're going to Jotunheim.
You leave this to me.
Good Heimdall...
You're not
dressed warmly enough.
I'm sorry?
Do you think that
you can deceive me?
(LAUGHS) You must
be mistaken...
THOR: Enough!
Heimdall, may we pass?
Never has an enemy
slipped my watch
until this day.
I wish to know
how that happened.
Then tell no one
where we have gone
until we've returned.
Understand?
What happened?
Silver tongue turn to lead?
(ALL LAUGHING)
HEIMDALL: Be warned.
I will honor my sworn oath
to protect this realm
as its Gatekeeper.
If your return threatens
the safety of Asgard,
Bifrost will
remain closed to you
and you'll be left to die
in the cold waste
of Jotunheim.
VOLSTAGG:
Couldn't you just leave
the bridge open for us?
HEIMDALL:
To leave the bridge open
would unleash
the full power
of the Bifrost
and destroy Jotunheim
with you upon it.
I have no plans
to die today.
None do.
We shouldn't be here.
Let's move.
Where are they?
Hiding,
as cowards always do.
LAUFEY: You've come
a long way to die,
Asgardians.
I am Thor Odinson!
LAUFEY: We know who you are.
How did your people
get into Asgard?
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
The House of Odin
is full of traitors.
Do not dishonor
my father's name
with your lies!
Your father is
a murderer and a thief!
And why have you come here?
To make peace?
You long for battle.
You crave it.
You're nothing but a boy
trying to prove
himself a man.
THOR: Well, this "boy"
has grown tired
of your mockery.
Thor, stop and think.
Look around you,
we're outnumbered.
Know your place, Brother.
You know not what your
actions would unleash.
I do.
Go now,
while I still allow it.
We will accept your
most gracious offer.
(GRUNTS)
Come on, Brother.
FROST GIANT:
Run back home,
little princess.
Damn.
Next?
(LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
At least make it
a challenge for me!
(ROARING)
That's more like it.
(GROANS)
Don't let them touch you!
(SCREAMS)
Thor!
We must go!
Then go!
Run!
Thor!
(ROARS)
(LAUGHING)
Heimdall!
Open the bridge!
(ROARING)
(HORSE WHINNYING)
Father! We'll finish
them together!
Silence!
Allfather.
You look weary.
Laufey,
end this now.
Your boy sought this out.
You're right.
And these are
the actions of a boy,
treat them as such.
You and I can end
this here and now,
before there's
further bloodshed.
We are beyond
diplomacy now, Allfather.
He'll get what he came for.
War
and death.
So be it.
THOR: Why did
you bring us back?
ODIN: Do you realize
what you've done?
What you've started?
THOR: I was
protecting my home.
You cannot even
protect your friends!
How can you hope
to protect a kingdom?
Get him to
the healing room! Now!
THOR: There won't be
a kingdom to protect
if you're afraid to act.
The Jotuns must
learn to fear me,
just as they once
feared you.
ODIN: That's pride
and vanity talking,
not leadership.
You've forgotten
everything I taught you
about a warrior's patience.
While you wait
and be patient,
the Nine Realms
laugh at us.
The old ways are done.
You'd stand giving speeches
while Asgard falls.
You are a vain,
greedy, cruel boy!
And you are
an old man and a fool!
Yes.
I was a fool
to think you were ready.
Father...
(ODIN SHOUTS)
Thor Odinson,
you have betrayed
the express command
of your king.
Through your
arrogance and stupidity,
you've opened
these peaceful realms
and innocent lives
to the horror and
desolation of war!
You are unworthy
of these realms!
You're unworthy
of your title!
of the loved ones
you have betrayed.
I now take from
you your power!
In the name of my father
and his father before,
I, Odin Allfather,
cast you out!
Whosoever holds this hammer,
if he be worthy,
shall possess
the power of Thor.
(DARCY AND JANE SCREAMING)
DARCY: I think that was
legally your fault.
JANE: Get the first aid kit.
Do me a favor
and don't be dead.
(GASPS)
Whoa. Does he need CPR?
Because I totally know CPR.
(GROANS)
Where did he come from?
You all right?
Hammer?
Yeah, we can
tell you're hammered.
It's pretty obvious.
(GASPS) Oh, my God.
Erik, look at this!
We have to move quickly
before this all changes.
Jane, we have to take him
to the hospital.
Father!
JANE: He's fine,
look at him.
Heimdall!
I know you can hear me!
Open the Bifrost!
JANE: Hospital.
You go, I'll stay.
You. What realm is this?
Alfheim? Nornheim?
New Mexico?
You dare threaten me, Thor,
with so puny a weapon?
(FIRES TASER GUN)
(SHUDDERING)
What? He was
freaking me out!
Next time you decide
to taser somebody,
make sure he's already
in the car, okay?
Jane! Come on.
NURSE: Name?
He said it was Thor?
T-H-O-R.
And your
relationship to him?
I've never met him before.
Until she hit him with a car.
I grazed him,
but she tasered him.
Yes, I did.
Hi.
Just taking a little blood.
How dare you attack
the son of Odin?
MALE NURSE:
I need some help!
Call security!
MAN: Security to
ER 3, stat!
You're no match
for the Mighty...
Huh.
ERIK: You don't think
this was just
a magnetic storm, do you?
Look, the lensing
around these edges
is characteristic
of an Einstein-Rosen Bridge.
A what?
I thought you were
a science major?
Political science.
She was
the only applicant.
An Einstein-Rosen Bridge
is a theoretical connection
between two
different points
of space-time.
It's a wormhole.
Erik, look.
What do you see?
Stars.
Yeah, but not our stars.
See, this is
the star alignment
for our quadrant
this time of year,
and unless Ursa Minor
decided to take
a day off,
these are someone
else's constellations.
Hey! Check this out.
No, it can't be.
I think I left something
at the hospital.
It's not possible!
(PANTING)
He was on
drugs or something.
He just went nuts.
DARCY: Oh, my God.
I just lost
my most important
piece of evidence.
Typical.
So now what?
We find him.
Did you see what
he did in there?
I'm not sure finding
him is the best idea.
Well, our data can't
tell us what it was like
to be inside that event,
and he can.
So, we're gonna find him.
DARCY: Okay.
So we're gonna look
all over New Mexico, right?
Exactly.
JANE: What?
I'm so sorry.
I swear I'm not doing
this on purpose.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
I got it, I got it.
MAN: Come on,
kick it in now!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Did it work?
(LAUGHING)
Sir, we found it.
You know, for a crazy
homeless person,
he's pretty cut.
Hey, sorry I tased you!
Excuse me, excuse me!
What is this?
Oh.
My ex.
Good with patients
and bad with relationships.
They're the only clothes
I had that would fit you.
They will suffice.
You're welcome.
THOR: This mortal form
has grown weak.
I need sustenance.
We should never
have let him go.
There was no stopping him.
FANDRAL: Well, at least
he's only banished, not dead.
Which is what we'd all be
if that guard
hadn't told Odin
where we'd gone.
How did the guard
even know?
I told him.
What?
I told him to go to Odin
after we'd left.
He should be flogged
for taking so long.
We should never have
reached Jotunheim.
You told the guard?
I saved our lives.
And Thor's.
I had no idea
Father would banish him
for what he did.
Loki.
You must go to the Allfather
and convince him to change
his mind.
And if I do, then what?
I love Thor more
dearly than any of you,
but you know what he is.
He's arrogant.
He's reckless.
He's dangerous.
You saw how he was today.
Is that what Asgard
needs from its king?
He may speak
of the good of Asgard,
but he's always
been jealous of Thor.
We should be
grateful to him,
he saved our lives.
Laufey said
there were traitors
in the House of Odin.
A master of magic
could bring three
Jotuns into Asgard.
FANDRAL:
Loki's always been
one for mischief,
but you're talking
about something
else entirely.
ODIN: Stop!
LOKI: Am I cursed?
ODIN: No.
What am I?
You're my son.
What more than that?
The Casket
wasn't the only thing
you took from
Jotunheim that day,
was it?
No.
In the aftermath
of the battle,
I went into the temple
and I found a baby.
(CRYING)
Small for
a giant's offspring.
Abandoned, suffering,
left to die.
Laufey's son.
Yes.
Why?
You were
knee-deep in Jotun blood,
why would you take me?
You were an innocent child.
No. You took me
for a purpose.
What was it?
(SHOUTING) Tell me!
I thought
we could unite our
kingdoms one day.
Bring about an alliance,
bring about permanent peace.
Through you.
What?
But those plans
no longer matter.
So I am no more
than another stolen relic,
locked up here
until you might
have use of me.
Why do you twist my words?
You could have
told me what I was
from the beginning,
why didn't you?
You're my son.
I wanted only to protect you
from the truth.
Because I'm the monster
parents tell
their children about
at night?
No, no.
You know,
it all makes sense now!
Why you favored Thor
all these years!
Because no matter how much
you claim to love me,
you could never
have a Frost Giant
sitting on
the throne of Asgard!
Guards!
Guards, please, help!
JANE: How'd you get
inside that cloud?
DARCY: Also, how could
you eat an entire box
of Pop-Tarts
and still be this hungry?
This drink, I like it.
I know. It's great, right?
Another!
JANE: Sorry, Izzy.
Little accident.
What was that?
It was delicious.
I want another.
Well, you could
have just said so.
I just did.
No, I mean, ask nicely.
I meant no disrespect.
All right.
Well, no more smashing.
Deal?
You have my word.
Good.
MAN 1:
The usual, please, Izzy.
MAN 2: You missed
all the excitement
out at the crater.
MAN 1: They're saying
some kind of satellite
landed out in the desert.
MAN 2: Yeah, we were having
a good time with it
until the Feds showed up.
JANE: Excuse me.
Did you say there
was a satellite crash?
MAN 2: Yeah.
Oh, my God. This is
going on Facebook. Smile.
What did it look like,
the satellite?
I don't know
anything about satellites,
but it was heavy.
I mean, nobody could lift it.
They said it was radioactive.
I had my hands all over it.
Which way?
Fifty miles west of here.
MAN 1: Well,
I wouldn't waste my time!
Looked like the whole Army
was coming when we left.
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(HONKING)
DRIVER: Dumbass!
Where are you going?
Fifty miles west of here.
Why?
To get what belongs to me.
Oh, so you own
a satellite now?
It's not what
they say it is.
Well, whatever it is,
the government seems
to think it's theirs.
So, you just intend
to go in there
and take it?
Yes.
If you take me there now,
I'll tell you everything
you wish to know.
Everything?
Yes.
All the answers
you seek will be yours
once I reclaim Mjolnir.
Myeu-muh?
What's Myeu-muh?
Can I have a word, Jane?
Please don't do this.
(SOFTLY) You saw
what I saw last night.
This is no coincidence.
We have to find out
what's in that crater.
But I'm not
talking about the crater,
I'm talking about him.
But he's promising us
the answers.
He's delusional.
Listen to what he's saying.
He's talking about Mjolnir
and Thor and Bifrost.
It's the stories
I grew up with as a child.
I'm just going to
drive him. That's it.
He's dangerous, Jane.
I'm sorry,
but I can't take you.
Then this is
where we say goodbye.
(GIGGLES)
Um...
Thank you?
Jane Foster,
Erik Selvig,
Darcy,
farewell.
All right.
Back to work.
(TRUCK HONKING)
Hey!
That's my stuff!
What the hell
is going on here?
Ms. Foster,
I'm Agent Coulson
with S.H.I.E.L.D.
Is that supposed
to mean something
to me?
You can't do this!
Jane!
Jane, this is
a lot more serious than
you realize. Let it go.
Let it go? This is my life.
We're investigating
a security threat.
We need to appropriate
your records and all
your atmospheric data.
By "appropriate,"
do you mean steal?
Here, this should
more than compensate you
for your trouble.
I can't just buy
replacements at Radio Shack,
I made most of
this equipment myself!
Then I'm sure
you can do it again.
And I'm sure I can
sue you for violating
my constitutional rights!
I'm sorry, Ms. Foster,
but we're the good guys.
So are we!
I'm on the verge
of understanding
something extraordinary.
And everything I know
about this phenomenon
is either in this
lab or in this book.
And you can't just
take this away... Hey!
Jane! Easy! Easy. Jane...
Thank you for
your cooperation.
Years of research,
gone.
DARCY: They even
took my iPod.
ERIK: What about
the backups?
JANE: They took our backups.
They took
the backups of our backups.
They were extremely thorough.
I just downloaded, like,
30 songs onto there.
Could you please
stop with your iPod?
Who are these people?
I knew this scientist.
The pioneer in
gamma radiation.
S.H.I.E.L.D. showed up
and he wasn't
heard from again.
They're not gonna
do that to us.
I'm gonna get
everything back.
Come on, please.
Let me contact one
of my colleagues.
He's had some dealings
with these people before.
I'll e-mail him and
maybe he can help.
They took your laptop, too.
Allfather, we must speak
with you urgently.
My friends.
Where's Odin?
Father has fallen
into the Odinsleep.
Mother fears
he may never awaken again.
We would speak with her.
She has refused to leave
my father's bedside.
You can bring your
urgent matter to me.
(SPEAR THUDDING)
Your king.
My King, we would ask
that you end
Thor's banishment.
(CHUCKLES)
My first command
cannot be to undo
the Allfather's last.
We're on the brink of war
with Jotunheim.
Our people need
a sense of continuity,
in order to feel safe
in these difficult times.
All of us must
stand together
for the good of Asgard.
Yes, of course.
Good. Then you
will wait for my word.
If I may
beg the indulgence
of Your Majesty to
perhaps reconsider...
We're done!
(SCOFFS)
I need a horse!
We don't have horses.
Just dogs, cats, birds...
Then give me one of those
large enough to ride.
(HONKING)
Hey, you still need a lift?
I've never done
anything like this before.
Have you ever done
anything like this before?
Many times.
But you're brave to do it.
Well, they just stole
my entire life's work.
I don't really have
much left to lose.
Yeah, but you're clever.
Far more clever
than anyone else
in this realm.
"Realm"? "Realm"?
You think me strange.
Yeah, I do.
Good strange
or bad strange?
I'm not quite sure yet.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I'm sorry.
But who are you?
Really?
You'll see soon enough.
You promised me answers.
What you seek,
it's a bridge.
Like an
Einstein-Rosen Bridge?
More like a Rainbow Bridge.
God, I hope
you're not crazy.
LOKI: (SOFTLY)
I never get used to
seeing him like this.
FRIGGA: He's put it
off for so long now,
that I fear...
How long will it last?
I don't know.
This time it's different.
We were unprepared.
So why did he lie?
He kept the truth from you
so that you would never
feel different.
You are our son, Loki,
and we, your family.
We mustn't lose hope
that your father
will return to us.
And your brother.
What hope
is there for Thor?
There's always a purpose
to everything
your father does.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
JANE: That's no
satellite crash!
They would have hauled
the wreckage away,
they wouldn't have
built a city around it.
You're going to need this.
What? Wait, why?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Now stay here.
Once I have Mjolnir,
I will return the items
they've stolen from you.
Deal?
No. Look what's down there.
You think you're
just gonna walk in,
grab our stuff
and walk out?
No. I'm going to fly out.
TECHNICIAN:
Sir, feed from the keyhole
can barely penetrate
the cloud cover.
Tech's barely
working as it is,
with all the interference
that thing's giving off.
And we've got
a commercial aircraft
coming right over us.
Southwest Airlines,
flight 5434.
Reroute it like
all the others.
Hold a sec.
We've got something
outside the fence,
west side.
AGENT: Delancey, Jackson.
West side perimeter.
Go check it out.
There it is.
Delancey, Jackson. Report.
Agent down.
We've got a perimeter breach.
(KLAXONS BLARING)
(GASPS)
You've reached
Dr. Erik Selvig.
Please leave me a message.
Hi, Erik, it's me.
Don't worry, I'm fine,
but just in case
you don't hear from me
in the next hour,
just come by the crater site
and try and find me, okay?
I did exactly what
you told me not to.
I'm sorry.
So sorry. Bye.
AGENT 1:
Bravo quadrant, move!
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(HIGH-PITCHED HUM)
AGENT 2:
Entering south tunnel!
AGENT 3: Negative, negative.
I have no comms.
AGENT 4:
Target sighted, east tunnel!
I need eyes up high,
with a gun.
Moving north!
What have we got?
There's a massive
electromagnetic surge
coming off that thing.
Systems are barely coping.
Barton? Talk to me.
You want me to
slow him down, sir?
Or are you
sending in more guys
for him to beat up?
I'll let you know.
You're big.
Fought bigger.
Better call it, Coulson,
'cause I'm starting
to root for this guy.
Last chance, sir.
COULSON: Wait.
I want to see this.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
All right, show's over.
Ground units, move in.
ERIK: He committed a crime.
He's in jail!
JANE: I can't just
leave him there!
ERIK: Why?
You didn't see what I saw!
DARCY: (GASPS) Look!
Look, it's Myeu-muh.
Where'd you find this?
ERIK: The children's section.
I just wanted to show you
how silly his story was.
But you're the one
who's always pushing me
to chase down
every possibility,
every alternative!
I'm talking
about science, not magic!
Well, magic's just science
that we don't understand yet.
Arthur C. Clarke.
Who wrote science fiction.
A precursor
to science fact!
In some cases, yeah.
Well, if there is
an Einstein-Rosen Bridge,
then there's something
on the other side.
And advanced beings
could have crossed it!
Jane.
A primitive culture
like the Vikings
might have worshipped
them as deities.
Yes! Yes, exactly.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
COULSON: You made my men,
some of the most highly
trained professionals
in the world,
look like a bunch
of minimum-wage mall cops.
That's hurtful.
In my experience,
it takes someone
who's received
similar training
to do what you did to them.
Why don't
you tell me where you
received your training?
Pakistan? Chechnya?
Afghanistan?
No, you strike me
more as the soldier
of fortune type.
Where was it? South Africa?
Certain groups
pay very well for a good
mercenary like you.
Who are you?
One way or another,
we find out what
we need to know.
We're good at that.
(PAGER BEEPING)
Don't go anywhere.
Loki! What are
you doing here?
I had to see you.
What's happened?
Tell me. Is it Jotunheim?
Let me explain to Father.
Father is dead.
What?
Your banishment,
the threat of a new war,
it was too much
for him to bear.
You mustn't blame yourself.
I know that you loved him.
I tried to tell him so,
but he wouldn't listen.
It was so cruel
to put the hammer
within your reach,
knowing that you
could never lift it.
The burden of the throne
has fallen to me now.
Can I come home?
The truce with Jotunheim
is conditional upon
your exile.
Yes, but couldn't
we find a way...
And Mother has
forbidden your return.
This is goodbye, Brother.
I'm so sorry.
No.
I am sorry.
Thank you for coming here.
Farewell.
Goodbye.
Goodbye?
I just got back.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(MJOLNIR HUMMING)
Sir?
He's got a visitor.
His name is Donald Blake?
Dr. Donald Blake.
You have dangerous
coworkers, Dr. Selvig.
He was distraught
when he found out
that you've taken
all our research.
That was years
of his life, gone!
You can understand
how a man could
go off like that.
A big, faceless
organization like yours
coming in with their
jackbooted thugs and...
That's how he put it.
That still doesn't explain
how he managed
to tear through
our security.
Steroids! He's a bit
of a fitness nut.
(ALARM BEEPS)
TECHNICIAN: Sir?
It says here
that he's an M.D.
Well, he is! Or he was.
He switched careers
and became a physicist.
A brilliant physicist.
He's a wonderful man.
He's a man in pain.
ERIK: Oh, Donny,
Donny, Donny!
There you are.
You're gonna be all right.
I'm taking you home now.
COULSON: Dr. Selvig!
Just keep him away
from the bars.
I will!
Where are we going?
To get a drink.
Follow them.
You know,
I had it all backwards.
I had it all wrong.
It's not a bad thing
finding out that you don't
have all the answers.
You start asking
the right questions.
For the first time
in my life,
I have no idea what
I'm supposed to do.
Anyone who's ever going to
find his way in this world
has to start by admitting
he doesn't know
where the hell he is.
Thank you for
what you've done.
No, don't thank me.
I only did it for Jane.
Her father and I taught
at university together.
He was a good man.
He never listened.
Neither did I.
My father was trying
to teach me something,
but I was
too stupid to see it.
I don't know
if you're delusional
or if you're pulling
some kind of con,
I don't care.
I just care about her.
I've seen the way
she looks at you.
I swear to you,
I mean her no harm.
Good.
In that case,
I'll buy you another round,
and you leave town tonight.
Two boilermakers.
LAUFEY: Kill him.
After all I've done for you?
So you're the one
who showed us
the way into Asgard.
That was just
a bit of fun, really.
To ruin
my brother's big day.
And to protect the realm
from his idiotic rule
for a while longer.
I will hear you.
I will conceal you
and a handful
of your soldiers,
lead you into
Odin's chambers,
and you can slay him
where he lies.
Why not kill him yourself?
(SNORTS)
I suspect that the Asgardians
would not take kindly
to a king who had murdered
his predecessor.
Once Odin is dead,
I will return
the Casket to you
and you can return
Jotunheim to all its...
Glory.
I...
Accept.
What troubles you,
Gatekeeper?
I turned my gaze
upon you in Jotunheim,
but could neither
see you nor hear you.
You were
shrouded from me,
like the Frost Giants
that entered this realm.
Perhaps your senses
have weakened
after your
many years of service.
Or perhaps
someone has found a way
to hide that which he
does not wish me to see.
You have
great power, Heimdall.
Did Odin ever fear you?
No.
And why is that?
Because he is my king
and I am sworn to obey him.
He was your king
and you're sworn
to obey me now.
Yes?
Yes.
Then you will open
the Bifrost to no one
until I have
repaired the damage
that my brother has done.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(GASPS) Oh, my God.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
Not injured at all.
(GROANS)
I'm sorry, my friend.
What happened?
We drank, we fought,
he made his ancestors proud.
Put him on the bed.
(GROANS)
(LAUGHING)
I still don't think
you're the God of Thunder.
But you ought to be.
Are these your chambers?
It's more of a temporary
living situation.
I'm sorry.
I don't usually
have guests.
Actually, I never
That's not
the right place for it.
I'm sorry.
Can we go outside?
Yes, of course.
I come up here sometimes
when I can't sleep
or I'm trying to
reconcile particle data,
or when Darcy's
driving me crazy.
I come up here a lot,
actually, now that
I think about it.
I'm really glad you're safe.
You've been
very kind to me,
and I've been
far less grateful
than you deserve.
Well, I hit you with my car
a couple times,
so I think that kind
of evens things out.
Perhaps I had it coming.
Oh, my God!
I don't believe it!
It was all I could get back.
I'm sorry it's not
as much as I promised.
No, no, this is great!
This is...
I don't have to start
from scratch now.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
S.H.I.E.L.D.
Whatever they are,
they're gonna do
everything in their power
to make sure this research
never sees the light of day.
No, Jane.
Listen to me.
You must not give up.
You must finish
what you've started.
Why?
Because you're right.
Here, look.
Your ancestors
called it magic,
and you call it science.
Well, I come from a place
where they're one
and the same thing.
What is that?
My father explained it
to me like this,
that your world
is one of the Nine Realms
of the Cosmos,
linked to each other
by the branches
of Yggdrasil,
the Worlds Tree.
Now you see it every day
without realizing.
The images
glimpsed through...
What did you call it?
This Hooble Telescope.
Hubble.
Hubble Telescope.
(LAUGHS)
Tell me more.
So, the Nine Realms.
Now, there is Midgard,
which is Earth.
This is Alfheim.
Vanaheim. Jotunheim.
And Asgard.
And that's where
I come from.
Thank you, Jane.
FANDRAL:
Our dearest friend banished,
Loki on the throne,
Asgard on the brink of war,
yet you've managed to consume
four wild boar, six pheasant,
a side of beef,
and two casks of ale.
Shame on you.
Don't you care?
Do not mistake
my appetite for apathy!
Stop it, both of you!
Stop.
We all know
what we have to do.
We must go.
We must find Thor.
It's treason.
To hell with treason,
it's suicide.
Thor would do
the same for us.
Now shush.
Heimdall might be watching.
(DOORS OPENING)
Heimdall demands
your presence.
VOLSTAGG: We're doomed.
You would defy the commands
of Loki, our king,
break every oath you
have taken as warriors,
and commit treason
to bring Thor back?
Yes.
Good.
So you'll help us?
I am bound by honor
to our king.
I cannot open
the bridge to you.
Complicated fellow,
isn't he?
Now what do we do?
Look!
What the hell was that?
I don't know, sir.
We got massive
energy readings
out of nowhere
and then they
just disappeared.
Fifteen miles due northwest.
Let's go take a look.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
AGENT: Base to Team 2,
we've got activity
outside the town.
Stay on your target.
(SPEAR THUDDING)
Ensure my brother
does not return.
Destroy everything.
Mom?
Is there
a Renaissance Fair in town?
Call it in.
Yeah.
Base, we've got
Xena, Jackie Chan
and Robin Hood.
It's a beautiful
theory, Jane.
But you won't
be able to convince
the scientific community
of any of it.
Not without hard evidence.
Found you!
THOR: My friends!
This is good!
This is good.
I don't believe it.
Oh, excuse me.
Lady Sif and
the Warriors Three.
My friends,
I've never been
happier to see anyone.
But you should not have come.
We're here to take you home.
You know I can't go home.
My father
is dead because of me.
And I must remain in exile.
Thor,
your father still lives.
Tell me, Loki,
how did you get
the Jotuns into Asgard?
You think
the Bifrost is the only way
in and out of this realm?
There are secret paths
between the worlds
to which even you,
with all your gifts,
are blind.
But I have need
of them no longer,
now that I am king.
And I say,
for your act of treason,
you are relieved
of your duties
as Gatekeeper,
and no longer
citizen of Asgard.
Then I need
no longer obey you.
Get somebody
from Linguistics
down here.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Was somebody else coming?
Is that one of Stark's?
I don't know. The guy
never tells me anything.
Hello.
You are using unregistered
weapons technology.
Identify yourself.
Here we go.
Incoming!
Jane, you have to leave.
What are you gonna do?
I'm staying here.
Thor's going
to fight with us!
My friends,
I'm just a man.
I'll only be in the way,
or worse,
get one of you killed.
But I can help
get these people to safety.
Well, if you're staying,
then so am I.
We'll need some time.
You'll have it!
Okay, move it, people!
Everybody out!
Use the back door.
Go, hurry!
You can eat later.
Keep it distracted.
For Asgard!
SIF: Fall back!
Go. Now. Run!
(SCREAMING)
Sif. Sif, you've done
all you can.
No. I will die
a warrior's death.
Stories will be told
of this day.
Live, and tell
those stories yourself.
Now go.
You must return to Asgard.
You have to stop Loki.
What about you?
Do not worry, my friends.
I have a plan.
Come on.
We need to fall back.
Wait!
What's he doing?
Brother, whatever I have
done to wrong you,
whatever I have done
to lead you to do this,
I am truly sorry.
But these people
are innocent.
Taking their lives
will gain you nothing.
So take mine
and end this.
No.
(GASPS)
It's over.
No. It's not over.
I mean, you're safe.
We're safe.
It's over.
(THOR INHALING DEEPLY)
No.
AGENT 1: We're spiking.
AGENT 2: Levels increase!
Whosoever holds this hammer,
if he be worthy,
shall possess
the power of Thor.
(MJOLNIR WHOOSHING)
Jane!
No. No. No!
Come!
Oh. My. God.
So, is this how
you normally look?
More or less.
It's a good look.
We must go to
the Bifrost site.
I would have words
with my brother.
COULSON: Excuse me!
Donald?
I don't think you've been
completely honest with me.
Know this, Son of Coul.
You and I,
we fight for the same cause,
the protection of this world.
From this day forward,
you can count me as your ally
if you return the items
you have taken from Jane.
Stolen.
Borrowed.
Of course, you can have
your equipment back.
You're gonna need it
to continue your research.
Would you like to see
the bridge we spoke of?
Sure.
(EXCLAIMS)
COULSON: Wait,
I need to debrief you!
Welcome to Asgard.
(MUFFLED STRAINING)
Heimdall, open the Bifrost.
Heimdall?
Heimdall!
He doesn't answer.
Then we are stranded.
Heimdall!
If you can hear me,
we need you now!
(MUFFLED ROARING)
Heimdall! We need you now!
Heimdall!
I must go back to Asgard,
but I give you my word,
I will return for you.
Deal?
Deal.
Get him to the healing room!
Leave my brother to me.
LAUFEY: It's said
you can still hear and see
what transpires around you.
I hope it's true,
so that you may know
your death came at the hand
of Laufey.
And your death came
by the son of Odin.
(GASPING)
Loki!
You saved him!
I swear to you, Mother,
that they will pay for what
they've done today.
THOR: Loki.
Thor!
I knew you'd return to us.
Why don't you tell her
how you sent the Destroyer
to kill our friends,
to kill me?
What?
Why, it must
have been enforcing
Father's last command.
You're
a talented liar, Brother.
Always have been.
It's good to have you back.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to destroy Jotunheim.
LOKI: You can't stop it.
The Bifrost will build until
it rips Jotunheim apart.
(FROST GIANTS SCREAMING)
Jane?
Why have you done this?
To prove to Father
that I am the worthy son.
When he wakes,
I will have saved his life.
I will have destroyed
that race of monsters.
And I will be true heir
to the throne!
You can't kill
an entire race!
Why not?
And what
is this newfound love
for the Frost Giants?
You could
have killed them all
with your bare hands.
I've changed.
So have I.
Now fight me.
I never wanted the throne!
I only ever wanted
to be your equal.
I will not
fight you, Brother!
I'm not your brother.
I never was.
Loki, this is madness.
Is it madness?
Is it?
Come on. What happened
to you on Earth that
turned you so soft?
Don't tell me
it was that woman.
Oh!
It was!
Well, maybe,
when we're finished here,
I'll pay her a visit myself!
(YELLING)
(LAUGHING)
Thor!
Brother, please.
(LAUGHING)
Enough!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Look at you,
the Mighty Thor,
with all your strength,
and what good does
it do you now, huh?
Do you hear me, Brother?
There's nothing you can do!
What are you doing?
If you destroy the bridge,
you'll never see her again!
Forgive me, Jane.
(BOTH YELLING)
I could have
done it, Father!
I could have done it!
For you!
For all of us!
No, Loki.
Loki, no.
No!
No.
JANE: It's gone.
(ALL LAUGHING)
And then,
with a mighty bellow,
I flew into
the giant metal creature
and laid him low!
FANDRAL:
Is that another way of saying
you fell on your huge ass?
VOLSTAGG:
As a matter of fact,
falling was a tactic
lulling the Destroyer...
My Queen, I'm so sorry
for your loss.
FRIGGA: How is he?
SIF: He mourns
for his brother.
And...
He misses her.
The mortal.
You'll be a wise king.
There will never be
a wiser king than you.
Or a better father.
I have much to learn.
I know that now.
Someday, perhaps,
I shall make you proud.
You've already
made me proud.
So Earth is lost to us.
No.
There is always hope.
Can you see her?
(HEIMDALL LAUGHS)
Yes.
ERIK: I have
the particle detectors!
Darcy, do you have
the S.H.I.E.L.D.
satellite codes?
DARCY: Yeah.
Have you seen my taser?
THOR: How is she?
ERIK: In the car.
Come on, Jane!
HEIMDALL:
She searches for you.
NICK FURY: Dr. Selvig.
So you're the man
behind all this?
It's quite a labyrinth.
I was thinking
they're taking me
down here to kill me.
I've been hearing about
the New Mexico situation.
Your work has impressed
a lot of people
who are much smarter
than I am.
I have a lot to work with.
The Foster Theory.
A gateway to
another dimension.
It's unprecedented.
Isn't it?
Legend tells us one thing,
history, another.
But every now and then,
we find something
that belongs to both.
What is it?
Power, Doctor.
If we can figure out
how to tap it,
maybe unlimited power.
Well, I guess
that's worth a look.