ROGERS: On your left.
On your left.
MAN: Uh-huh.
On my left. Got it.
Don't say it.
Don't you say it.
On your left.
Come on!
(PANTING) Oh!
(GROANING)
ROGERS: Need a medic?
(LAUGHS)
I need
a new set of lungs.
Dude, you just ran,
like, 13 miles in 30 minutes.
I guess I got
a late start.
(CHUCKLES) Really? You should
be ashamed of yourself.
You should take another lap.
Did you just take it?
I assume you just took it.
What unit you with?
58th Pararescue.
But now I'm working
down at the VA.
Sam Wilson.
Steve Rogers.
I kind of put
that together. (PANTING)
Must have freaked you out,
coming home
after the whole
defrosting thing.
(SIGHS) It takes
some getting used to.
It's good to meet you, Sam.
It's your bed, right?
What's that?
Your bed, it's too soft.
When I was over there,
I'd sleep on the ground,
use rock for pillows,
like a caveman.
Now I'm home, lying in
my bed, and it's like...
Lying on a marshmallow.
Feel like I'm gonna sink
right to the floor.
How long?
Two tours.
You must miss
the good old days, huh?
Well, things
aren't so bad.
Food's a lot better.
We used to boil
everything.
No polio is good.
Internet, so helpful.
I've been reading
that a lot, trying
to catch up.
Marvin Gaye, 1972,
Trouble Man soundtrack.
Everything you missed
jammed into one album.
I'll put it on the list.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
All right, Sam, duty calls.
Thanks for the run.
If that's what you
want to call running.
Oh, that's how it is?
Oh, that's how it is.
Okay. (LAUGHS)
Any time you want
to stop by the VA,
make me look awesome
in front of the girl
at the front desk,
just let me know.
I'll keep it in mind.
Yeah.
Hey, fellas.
Either one of you
know where the Smithsonian is?
I'm here to pick up a fossil.
ROGERS: That's hilarious.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
How you doing?
Hey.
Can't run everywhere.
No, you can't.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
INDIAN OCEAN
Target is a mobile
satellite launch platform,
the Lemurian Star.
They were sending up
their last payload
when pirates took them,
93 minutes ago.
Any demands?
Billion and a half.
ROGERS: Why so steep?
Because it's S.H.I.E.L.D.'s.
So it's not off-course.
It's trespassing.
I'm sure they
have a good reason.
You know, I'm getting
a little tired of
being Fury's janitor.
Relax. It's not
that complicated.
How many pirates?
25. Top mercs
led by this guy.
Georges Batroc.
Ex-DGSE, Action Division.
He's at the top of
Interpol's Red Notice.
Before the French
demobilized him,
he had 36 kill missions.
This guy's got a rep
for maximum casualties.
Hostages?
Oh, mostly techs.
One officer.
Jasper Sitwell.
They're in the galley.
What's Sitwell
doing on a launch ship?
All right, I'm gonna
sweep the deck
and find Batroc.
Nat, you kill the engines
and wait for instructions.
Rumlow, you sweep aft,
find the hostages,
get them to the life-pods,
get them out.
Let's move.
S.T.R.I.K.E.,
you heard the Cap.
Gear up.
Secure channel seven.
Seven secure.
Did you do anything fun
Saturday night?
Well, all the guys
from my barbershop
quartet are dead,
so, no, not really.
MALE PILOT ON RADIO:
Coming up on
the drop zone, Cap.
You know,
if you ask Kristen out,
from Statistics,
she'd probably say yes.
That's why I don't ask.
Too shy, or too scared?
Too busy!
Was he wearing a parachute?
No.
No, he wasn't.
Ahh!
(SPLASHES)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Hey!
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(COCKS GUN)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
DON'T MOVE.
Thanks.
Yeah. You seemed pretty
helpless without me.
What about the nurse
that lives across
the hall from you?
She seems kind of nice.
Secure the engine room,
then find me a date.
I'm multi-tasking.
(FRENCH PIRATE
SPEAKING FRENCH)
I TOLD BATROC...
IF WE WANT TO MAKE S.H.I.E.L.D. PAY
US...
...START SENDING THEM BODIES NOW!
I HAVE A BULLET FOR SOMEONE...
You want
a bullet in your head?
MOVE THAT FOOT - YOU WANT A BULLET
IN THE HEAD...?
Huh?
(BATROC SPEAKING FRENCH)
I DON'T LIKE WAITING.
CALL DURAND.
I WANT THIS SHIP READY TO MOVE WHEN
THE RANSOM COMES.
(RADIO PIRATE SPEAKING FRENCH)
START THE ENGINES.
Okay.
Hey, sailor.
(SCREAMS)
(CHOKING)
(PIRATE SPEAKING FRENCH)
SHUT UP.
YOU WANT TO BE A HERO? IS THAT IT?
ALL RIGHT, I'VE WAITED LONG
ENOUGH...
Hey!
FIND BATROC...
IF I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING IN TWO
MINUTES...
...I START KILLING THEM!
I'LL FIND HIM.
TWO MINUTES.
RADIO SILENCE
FROM S.H.I.E.L.D., BATROC...
Targets acquired.
S.T.R.I.K.E. in position.
Natasha, what's your status?
Status, Natasha.
Hang on!
(GROANING)
Engine room secure.
(PIRATE SPEAKING FRENCH)
TIME IS UP.
WHO DIES FIRST...?
YOU!
GET THAT ONE.
On my mark.
Three...
Two... One.
(GUNFIRE)
(PIRATES GASP)
I told you,
S.H.I.E.L.D.
doesn't negotiate.
(RADIO PIRATE SPEAKING FRENCH)
THE LINE JUST WENT DEAD.
I'VE LOST CONTACT WITH THEM...
Ahh!
Hostages en route
to extraction.
Romanoff missed
the rendezvous point, Cap.
Hostiles are still in play.
(PANTING) Natasha,
Batroc's on the move.
Circle back to Rumlow
and protect the hostages.
Natasha.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MORE THAN JUST A
SHIELD...
LET'S SEE.
(PANTING)
ROMANOFF:
Well, this is awkward.
What are you doing?
Backing up the hard drive.
It's a good habit
to get into.
Rumlow needed your help.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You're saving
S.H.I.E.L.D. intel.
Whatever I can
get my hands on.
Our mission is to
rescue hostages.
No, that's your mission,
and you've done
it beautifully.
You just jeopardized
this whole operation.
I think that's
overstating things.
(BOTH GROANING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Okay.
That one's on me.
You're damn right.
(SIGHS)
THE TRISKELION
S.H.I.E.L.D. HEADQUARTERS
ROGERS: You just
can't stop yourself
from lying, can you?
FURY: I didn't lie.
Agent Romanoff
had a different
mission than yours.
Which you didn't
feel obliged to share.
I'm not obliged
to do anything.
Those hostages
could have died, Nick.
I sent the greatest
soldier in history
to make sure
that didn't happen.
Soldiers trust each other.
That's what makes it an army.
Not a bunch of guys
running around shooting guns.
Last time
I trusted someone,
I lost an eye.
Look, I didn't want you
doing anything you
weren't comfortable with.
Agent Romanoff
is comfortable
with everything.
I can't lead a mission
when the people I'm leading
have missions of their own.
It's called
compartmentalization.
Nobody spills the
secrets, because
nobody knows them all.
Except you.
You're wrong about me.
I do share.
I'm nice like that.
Insight bay.
S.H.I.E.L.D. COMPUTER:
Captain Rogers does not have
clearance
for Project Insight.
Director override.
Fury, Nicholas J.
Confirmed.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You know,
they used to play music.
Yeah.
My grandfather operated
one of these things
for 40 years.
Granddad worked
in a nice building.
Got good tips.
He'd walk home every
night, a roll of ones
stuffed in his lunch bag.
He'd say, "Hi."
People would say,
"Hi" back.
Time went on,
the neighborhood
got rougher.
He'd say, "Hi."
They'd say,
"Keep on steppin'."
Granddad got to
gripping that lunch bag
a little tighter.
Did he ever get mugged?
(LAUGHS)
Every week some
punk would say,
"What's in the bag?"
What would he do?
He'd show them.
Bunch of crumpled ones,
and a loaded .22 Magnum.
Yeah, Granddad loved people.
But he didn't
trust them very much.
Yeah, I know.
They're a little
bit bigger than a .22.
FURY: This is Project Insight.
Three next-generation
helicarriers
synced to a network
of targeting satellites.
Launched from
the Lemurian Star.
Once we get them in the air,
they never need to come down.
Continuous sub-orbital
flight, courtesy of our
new repulsor engines.
Stark?
He had
a few suggestions
once he got
an up-close look
at our old turbines.
These new long-range
precision guns
can eliminate 1,000
hostiles a minute.
The satellites can
read a terrorist's DNA
before he steps
outside his spider hole.
We're gonna
neutralize a lot of threats
before they even happen.
Thought the punishment
usually came after the crime.
We can't afford
to wait that long.
Who's "we"?
After New York, I convinced
the World Security Council
we needed a quantum surge
in threat analysis.
For once,
we're way ahead
of the curve.
By holding a gun
to everyone on Earth
and calling it protection.
You know,
I read those SSR files.
"Greatest Generation"?
You guys did
some nasty stuff.
Yeah, we compromised.
Sometimes in ways that
made us not sleep so well.
But we did it
so that people
could be free.
This isn't freedom.
This is fear.
S.H.I.E.L.D. takes
the world as it is, not
as we'd like it to be.
And it's getting
damn near past time
for you to get with
that program, Cap.
Don't hold your breath.
WOMAN ON PA:
Welcome to the Smithsonian.
Visitor information booths are
available on the second level.
NARRATOR:
A symbol to the nation.
A hero to the world.
The story of Captain America
is one of honor,
bravery and sacrifice.
Denied enlistment
due to poor health,
Steven Rogers was chosen
for a program
unique in the annals
of American warfare.
One that would transform him
into the world's
first Super-Soldier.
WAR FOOTAGE NARRATOR:
In this rare footage,
everyone's favorite war hero,
Captain America...
NARRATOR: Battle tested,
Captain America
and his Howling Commandos
quickly earned their stripes.
Their mission:
taking down HYDRA,
the Nazi rogue
science division.
Best friends since childhood,
Bucky Barnes and Steven Rogers
were inseparable
on both schoolyard
and battlefield.
Barnes is
the only Howling Commando
to give his life
in service of his country.
PEGGY ON VIDEO:
That was a difficult winter.
A blizzard had trapped
half our battalion
behind the German line.
Steve, Captain Rogers,
he fought his way
through a HYDRA blockade
that had pinned our allies
down for months.
He saved over 1,000 men.
Including the man who would...
Who would become my husband,
as it turned out.
Even after he died,
Steve was still
changing my life.
You should be
proud of yourself, Peggy.
Mmm.
I have lived a life.
My only regret
is that you didn't
get to live yours.
What is it?
For as long as I can
remember, I just wanted
to do what was right.
I guess I'm not quite sure
what that is anymore.
And I thought I could
throw myself back in
and follow orders.
Serve.
It's just not the same.
(LAUGHS) You're
always so dramatic.
Look, you saved
the world.
We rather mucked it up.
You didn't.
Knowing that you helped
found S.H.I.E.L.D.
is half the reason I stay.
Hey.
The world has changed,
and none of us can go back.
All we can do is our best.
And sometimes the best that
we can do is to start over.
(COUGHING)
Peggy.
Steve.
Yeah?
(GASPS)
You're alive.
You came back.
Yeah, Peggy.
It's been so long.
So long.
Well, I couldn't
leave my best girl.
Not when she owes me a dance.
Secure office.
Open Lemurian Star's
satellite launch file.
S.H.I.E.L.D. COMPUTER:
Access denied.
Run decryption.
Decryption failed.
Director override.
Fury, Nicholas J.
Override denied.
All files sealed.
On whose authority?
Fury, Nicholas J.
World Security Council.
Confirmed.
ROCKWELL: If Nick Fury thinks
he can get his costumed thugs
and S.T.R.I.K.E. commandos
to mop up his mess,
he's sadly mistaken.
This failure
is unacceptable.
Considering this
attack took place
one mile from my country's
sovereign waters,
it's a bit more than that.
I move for immediate hearing.
We don't need hearings,
we need action.
It's this Council's duty
to oversee S.H.I.E.L.D.
A breach like this
raises serious questions.
Like how the hell
did a French pirate
manage to hijack
a covert S.H.I.E.L.D.
vessel in broad daylight?
For the record,
Councilman,
he's Algerian.
I can draw a map
if it'd help.
I appreciate your wit,
Secretary Pierce.
But this Council takes
things like international
piracy fairly seriously.
Really? I don't.
I don't care about one boat,
I care about the fleet.
If this Council is
going to fall to rancor
every time someone pushes us
on the playing field,
maybe we need
someone to oversee us.
YEN: Mr. Secretary,
nobody is suggesting...
Excuse me.
More trouble,
Mr. Secretary?
PIERCE: Depends
on your definition.
(DOOR OPENING)
I work 40 floors away
and it takes a hijacking
for you to visit?
A nuclear war
would do it, too.
You busy in there?
Nothing some
earmarks can't fix.
I'm here to ask a favor.
I want you to
call for a vote.
Project Insight
has to be delayed.
Nick, that's not a favor,
that's a sub-committee
hearing. A long one.
It could be nothing.
It probably is nothing.
I just need time to
make sure it's nothing.
But if it's something?
Then we'll both be damn
glad those helicarriers
aren't in the air.
Fine.
But you got to get Iron Man
to stop by my
niece's birthday party.
Thank you, sir.
And not just a flyby.
He's got to mingle.
GARCIA: The thing is,
I think
it's getting worse.
A cop pulled me
over last week.
He thought I was drunk.
I swerved to
miss a plastic bag.
I thought it was an IED.
WILSON: Some stuff
you leave there.
Other stuff you bring back.
It's our job to
figure out how to carry it.
Is it gonna be
in a big suitcase,
or in a little man-purse?
It's up to you.
I'll see you next week.
Definitely.
Look who it is,
the running man.
Caught the
last few minutes.
It's pretty intense.
Yeah, brother,
we all got the
same problems.
Guilt,
regret.
You lose someone?
My wingman, Riley.
Flying a night mission.
Standard PJ rescue op.
Nothing we hadn't done
1,000 times before.
Until an RPG knocked Riley's
dumb ass out of the sky.
Nothing I could do.
It's like I was up
there just to watch.
I'm sorry.
After that,
I had a really hard
time finding a reason
for being over there,
you know?
But you're happy now,
back in the world?
The number of people
giving me orders
is down to about zero.
So, hell yeah.
Are you thinking
about getting out?
No.
I don't know.
To be honest, I don't know
what I would do
with myself if I did.
Ultimate fighting?
(LAUGHS)
Just a great idea
off the top of my head.
Seriously, you could do
whatever you want to do.
What makes you happy?
I don't know.
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Activating communications
encryption protocol.
Open secure line 0405.
Confirmed.
This is Hill.
I need you here in D.C.
Deep shadow conditions.
Give me four hours.
You have three. Over.
Want to see my lease?
(SIREN WAILS)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Fracture detected.
(GASPING)
Recommend
anesthetic injection.
D.C. Metro Police dispatch
shows no units in this area.
Get me out of here.
Propulsion systems offline.
Then reboot, damn it!
Warning. Window
integrity compromised.
You think?
(DRILLING)
How long to propulsion?
Calculating.
Window integrity 31%.
Deploying countermeasures.
Hold that order!
Window integrity 19%.
Offensive measures advised.
Wait!
Window integrity 1%.
Now!
Propulsion systems now online.
Full acceleration! Now!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Initiate vertical takeoff!
Flight systems damaged.
Then activate
guidance cameras!
(GROANING)
Give me the wheel!
Get me Agent Hill.
Communications
array damaged.
Well, what's not damaged?
Air conditioning is
fully operational.
Traffic ahead.
Give me an alternate route.
Traffic alert on
Roosevelt Bridge.
All vehicles stopped.
17th Avenue clear
in three blocks,
directly ahead.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
Warning.
Approaching intersection.
Get me off the grid!
Calculating route
to secure location.
So sweet.
That is so nice.
Hi.
I got to go, though.
Okay. Bye.
My aunt, she's kind
of an insomniac.
Yeah.
Hey, if you want...
If you want,
you're welcome
to use my machine.
Might be cheaper
than the one in the basement.
Oh, yeah? What's it cost?
A cup of coffee?
Thank you, but
I already have
a load in downstairs,
and you really don't want
my scrubs in your machine.
I just finished a rotation
in the infectious
disease ward, so...
Well, I'll keep my distance.
Hopefully, not too far.
(1940s MUSIC PLAYING
IN THE DISTANCE)
Oh, and I think you
left your stereo on.
Oh.
Right. Thank you.
Yeah.
(1940s MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(1940s MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING)
I don't remember
giving you a key.
(GRUNTS)
You really think
I'd need one?
My wife kicked me out.
I didn't know
you were married.
A lot of things
you don't know about me.
I know, Nick.
That's the problem.
I'm sorry to
have to do this,
but I had no place
else to crash.
Who else knows
about your wife?
Just...
My friends.
Is that what we are?
That's up to you.
Ahh!
(GROANING)
(COUGHING)
Don't trust anyone.
(DOOR OPENS)
KATE: Captain Rogers?
Captain,
I'm Agent 13 of S.H.I.E.L.D.
Special Service.
Kate?
I'm assigned to protect you.
ROGERS: On whose order?
(GASPS) His.
Foxtrot is down,
he's unresponsive.
I need EMTs.
DISPATCHER:
Do we have a 20
on the shooter?
Tell him I'm in pursuit.
ROMANOFF: Is he gonna make it?
ROGERS: I don't know.
ROMANOFF:
Tell me about the shooter.
He's fast. Strong.
Had a metal arm.
Ballistics?
Three slugs, no rifling.
Completely untraceable.
Soviet-made.
Yeah.
MALE NURSE: He's in V-tach.
FEMALE NURSE:
Crash cart coming in.
DOCTOR: Nurse,
help me with the drape.
MALE NURSE: BP's dropping.
DOCTOR: Defibrillator!
I want you to
charge him at 100.
Don't do this
to me, Nick.
Stand back.
Three, two,
one. Clear.
DOCTOR: Pulse?
MALE NURSE: No pulse.
Okay, 200, please.
Stand back!
Three, two, one. Clear!
Get me epinephrine!
Pulse?
MALE NURSE: Negative.
Don't do this to me, Nick.
Don't do this to me.
DOCTOR: What's the time?
FEMALE NURSE: 1:03, Doctor.
Time of death,
1:03 a.m.
I need to take him.
ROGERS: Natasha.
Natasha!
Why was Fury in
your apartment?
(SIGHS) I don't know.
Cap, they want you
back at S.H.I.E.L.D.
Yeah, give me a second.
They want you now.
Okay.
You're a terrible liar.
SITWELL ON EARPIECE:
S.T.R.I.K.E. team,
escort Captain Rogers
back to S.H.I.E.L.D.
immediately for questioning.
RUMLOW: I told him.
Let's go.
Yeah.
S.T.R.I.K.E.,
move it out.
Captain Rogers.
Neighbor.
PIERCE: Oh. Captain.
I'm Alexander Pierce.
Sir, it's an honor.
The honor's mine, Captain.
My father served in
the 101st. Come on in.
PIERCE: That photo was
taken five years after
Nick and I met,
when I was
at State Department
in Bogota.
E.L.N. rebels
took the embassy,
and security got me out,
but the rebels took hostages.
Nick was Deputy Chief
of the S.H.I.E.L.D.
station there,
and he comes to
me with a plan.
He wants to
storm the building
through the sewers.
I said,
"No, we'll negotiate."
Turned out, the E.L.N.
didn't negotiate,
so they put out a kill order.
They stormed the basement,
and what do they find?
They find it empty.
Nick had ignored
my direct order,
and carried out
an unauthorized
military operation
on foreign soil,
and saved the lives of
a dozen political officers,
including my daughter.
So you gave him a promotion.
I've never had any
cause to regret it.
Captain, why was Nick
in your apartment last night?
I don't know.
Did you know it was bugged?
I did, because
Nick told me.
Did he tell you
he was the one
who bugged it?
I want you to see something.
INTERROGATOR:
Who hired you, Batroc?
Is that live?
Yeah, they picked him up
last night
in a not-so-safe
house in Algiers.
ROGERS: Are you saying
he's a suspect?
Assassination
isn't Batroc's line.
PIERCE: No, no. It's more
complicated than that.
Batroc was hired anonymously
to attack the Lemurian Star.
And he was contacted by email
and paid by wire transfer,
and then the money
was run through
17 fictitious accounts.
The last one going to
a holding company
that was registered
to a Jacob Veech.
Am I supposed to
know who that is?
Not likely.
Veech died six years ago.
His last address was
1435 Elmhurst Drive.
When I first met Nick,
his mother lived at 1437.
Are you saying
Fury hired the pirates? Why?
The prevailing theory
was that the hijacking was
a cover for the acquisition
and sale of
classified intelligence.
The sale went sour
and that led to Nick's death.
If you really knew
Nick Fury, you'd
know that's not true.
Why do you think
we're talking?
See, I took a seat
on the Council not
because I wanted to,
but because Nick
asked me to, because
we were both realists.
We knew that,
despite all the diplomacy
and the handshaking
and the rhetoric,
that to build
a really better world
sometimes means having
to tear the old one down.
And that makes enemies.
Those people
that call you dirty
because you got the guts
to stick your hands
in the mud and try to
build something better.
And the idea
that those people
could be happy today
makes me really,
really angry.
Captain, you were the last
one to see Nick alive.
I don't think
that's an accident.
And I don't think
you do, either.
So, I'm gonna ask again.
Why was he there?
He told me not
to trust anyone.
PIERCE: I wonder
if that included him.
I'm sorry.
Those were his last words.
Excuse me.
Captain,
somebody murdered
my friend and
I'm gonna find out why.
Anyone gets in my way,
they're gonna regret it.
Anyone.
Understood.
Operations Control.
S.H.I.E.L.D. COMPUTER:
Confirmed.
Keep all S.T.R.I.K.E.
personnel on site.
Understood.
Yes, sir.
RUMLOW: Forensics.
COMPUTER: Confirmed.
RUMLOW: Cap.
Rumlow.
Evidence Response
found some fibers
on the roof
they want us to see.
You want me to get
the tac team ready?
No, let's wait and
see what it is first.
Right.
What's the status so far?
MAN: Administrations level.
COMPUTER: Confirmed.
Excuse me.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I'm sorry about
what happened with Fury.
It's messed up,
what happened to him.
Thank you.
MAN: Records.
COMPUTER: Confirmed.
ROGERS: Before
we get started,
does anyone
want to get out?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Mobilize S.T.R.I.K.E.
units, 25th floor.
Whoa, big guy.
I just want you
to know, Cap, this
isn't personal!
(PANTING)
It kind of feels personal.
Drop the shield
and put your hands
in the air!
(GRUNTING)
S.T.R.I.K.E. AGENT:
Give it up, Rogers!
Get that door open!
You have nowhere to go!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
Are you kidding me?
He's headed for the garage.
Lock down the bridge.
PILOT: Stand down,
Captain Rogers. Stand down.
Repeat, stand down.
SITWELL: Eyes here.
Whatever your op is,
bury it.
This is Level One.
Contact DOT.
All traffic lights in
the district go red.
Shut all runways at BWI,
IAD and Reagan.
All security cameras
in the city
go through this
monitor right here.
Scan all open sources,
phones, computers,
PDAs. Whatever.
If someone
tweets about this guy,
I want to know about it.
With all due respect,
if S.H.I.E.L.D.
is conducting
a manhunt for Captain America
we deserve to know why.
PIERCE: Because he lied to us.
Captain Rogers has
information regarding
the death of Director Fury.
He refused to share it.
As difficult as
this is to accept,
Captain America
is a fugitive
from S.H.I.E.L.D.
Where is it?
Safe.
Do better.
Where did you get it?
Why would I tell you?
Fury gave it to you. Why?
What's on it?
I don't know.
Stop lying.
I only act like
I know everything, Rogers.
I bet you knew Fury hired
the pirates, didn't you?
Well, it makes sense.
The ship was
dirty, Fury needed
a way in, so do you.
I'm not gonna ask you again.
I know who killed Fury.
Most of
the intelligence community
doesn't believe he exists.
The ones that do
call him the Winter Soldier.
He's credited with over
two dozen assassinations
in the last 50 years.
So he's a ghost story.
Five years ago,
I was escorting
a nuclear engineer
out of Iran.
Somebody shot out
my tires near Odessa.
We lost control,
went straight over a cliff.
I pulled us out.
But the Winter Soldier
was there.
I was covering my engineer
so he shot him
straight through me.
Soviet slug.
No rifling. Bye-bye, bikinis.
Yeah, I bet you look
terrible in them now.
Going after him
is a dead end.
I know, I've tried.
Like you said,
he's a ghost story.
Well, let's find out
what the ghost wants.
PIERCE: Nick Fury was
murdered in cold blood.
To any reasonable person,
that would make him a martyr,
not a traitor.
ROCKWELL: You know what
makes him a traitor?
Hiring a mercenary
to hijack his own ship.
SINGH: Nick Fury
used your friendship
to coerce this Council
into delaying
Project Insight.
A project he knew
would expose his own
illegal operations.
At best, he lied to you.
At worst...
Are you calling
for my resignation?
I've got a pen and
paper right here.
That discussion can be
tabled for a later time.
But you do want to
have a discussion?
We've already had it,
Mr. Secretary.
This Council moves to
immediately reactivate
Project Insight.
If you want to say
something snappy,
now would be a good time.
First rule of going
on the run is
don't run, walk.
If I run in these shoes,
they're gonna fall off.
The drive has
a Level Six
homing program,
so as soon
as we boot up
S.H.I.E.L.D. will know
exactly where we are.
How much time will we have?
About nine minutes from
now.
ROMANOFF:
Fury was right
about that ship.
Somebody's trying
to hide something.
This drive is protected
by some sort of AI.
It keeps rewriting itself
to counter my commands.
Can you override it?
The person who
developed this is
slightly smarter than me.
Slightly.
I'm gonna try
running a tracer.
This is a program
that S.H.I.E.L.D. developed
to track hostile malware,
so if we can't
read the file,
maybe we can find out
where it came from.
Can I help you guys
with anything?
Oh, no. My fiance
was just helping me
with some
honeymoon destinations.
Right. We're getting married.
Congratulations.
Where are you guys
thinking about going?
New Jersey.
Oh.
I have the exact
same glasses.
Wow, you two are
practically twins.
Yeah, I wish.
Specimen.
If you guys need anything,
I've been Aaron.
Thank you.
You said nine minutes.
Come on.
Relax.
Got it.
You know it?
I used to. Let's go.
Standard tac team.
Two behind, two across,
and two coming
straight at us.
If they make us, I'll
engage, you hit the south
escalator to the metro.
Shut up and put
your arm around me.
Laugh at something I said.
What?
Do it.
(ROGERS LAUGHING)
Negative at the source.
Give me a floor rundown.
(OVER RADIO)
Negative on three.
Negative on two.
Snake the upper levels.
Work down to me.
Kiss me.
What?
Public displays of
affection make people
very uncomfortable.
Yes, they do.
You still uncomfortable?
It's not exactly
the word I would use.
Where did Captain America
learn how to steal a car?
Nazi Germany.
Mmm.
And we're borrowing.
Take your feet off the dash.
All right, I have
a question for you,
which you do not
have to answer.
I feel like, if you
don't answer it though,
you're kind of
answering it, you know.
What?
Was that your
first kiss since 1945?
That bad, huh?
I didn't say that.
Well, it kind of sounds like
that's what you're saying.
No, I didn't.
I just wondered
how much practice you've had.
You don't need practice.
Everybody needs practice.
It was not my
first kiss since 1945.
I'm 95, I'm not dead.
Nobody special, though?
(CHUCKLES)
Believe it or not,
it's kind of hard
to find someone with
shared life experience.
Well, that's all right.
You just make something up.
What, like you?
I don't know.
The truth is
a matter of circumstance.
It's not all things to
all people, all the time.
Neither am I.
That's a tough way to live.
It's a good way
not to die, though.
You know, it's kind of
hard to trust someone,
when you don't know
who that someone really is.
Yeah.
Who do you want me to be?
How about a friend?
Well, there's a chance
you might be
in the wrong
business, Rogers.
ROGERS: This is it.
The file came from
these coordinates.
So did I.
This camp is
where I was trained.
Change much?
A little.
DRILL SERGEANT:
Pick up the pace, ladies!
Let's go! Let's go!
Double time!
Come on, Rogers, move it!
Come on, fall in!
Rogers!
I said fall in!
ROMANOFF: This is
a dead end.
Zero heat signatures,
zero waves,
not even radio.
Whoever wrote the file
must have used a router
to throw people off.
What is it?
ROGERS: Army regulations
forbid storing munitions
within 500 yards
of the barracks.
This building is
in the wrong place.
ROMANOFF:
This is S.H.I.E.L.D.
Maybe where it started.
And there's Stark's father.
ROGERS: Howard.
Who's the girl?
If you're already working
in a secret office,
why do you need to
hide the elevator?
(MACHINE BLEEPING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
This can't be
the data point. This
technology is ancient.
(ELECTRONIC VOICE SPEAKING)
Y-E-S spells yes.
(POWERING UP)
Shall we play a game?
It's from a movie
that was really...
I know, I saw it.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
Rogers, Steven,
born 1918.
Romanoff, Natalia Alianovna,
born 1984.
It's some kind of recording.
I am not a recording,
Fraeulein.
I may not be the man I was
when the Captain took me
prisoner in 1945.
But I am.
You know this thing?
ROGERS: Arnim Zola
was a German
scientist who worked
for the Red Skull.
He's been dead for years.
ZOLA: First correction,
I am Swiss.
Second, look around you.
I have never been more alive.
In 1972, I received
a terminal diagnosis.
Science could
not save my body.
My mind, however,
that was worth saving,
on 200,000 feet
of databanks.
You are standing
in my brain.
ROGERS: How did you get here?
Invited.
It was Operation Paperclip
after World War II.
S.H.I.E.L.D. recruited
German scientists
with strategic value.
ZOLA: They thought
I could help their cause.
I also helped my own.
ROGERS: HYDRA died
with the Red Skull.
Cut off one head,
two more shall take its place.
Prove it.
Accessing archive.
HYDRA was founded on
the belief that humanity
could not be trusted
with its own freedom.
What we did not realize
was that if you try
to take that freedom,
they resist.
The war taught us much.
Humanity needed to surrender
its freedom willingly.
After the war,
S.H.I.E.L.D. was founded,
and I was recruited.
The new HYDRA grew.
A beautiful parasite
inside S.H.I.E.L.D.
For 70 years,
HYDRA has been secretly
feeding crisis, reaping war,
and when history
did not cooperate,
history was changed.
That's impossible.
S.H.I.E.L.D.
would have stopped you.
Accidents will happen.
HYDRA created
a world so chaotic
that humanity is finally ready
to sacrifice its freedom
to gain its security.
Once a purification process
is complete,
HYDRA's new world
order will arise.
We won, Captain.
Your death amounts to
the same as your life.
A zero sum.
(GRUNTS)
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
As I was saying...
What's on this drive?
Project Insight
requires insight.
So, I wrote an algorithm.
What kind of algorithm?
What does it do?
The answer to your question
is fascinating.
Unfortunately, you shall
be too dead to hear it.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Steve, we got a bogey.
Short range ballistic.
30 seconds tops.
Who fired it?
S.H.I.E.L.D.
I am afraid
I have been stalling, Captain.
Admit it.
It's better this way.
We are, both of us,
out of time.
(DEBRIS SETTLING)
(ROGERS GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(ROGERS PANTING)
(COUGHING)
Call in the asset.
RENATA: I'm going
to go, Mr. Pierce.
You need anything
before I leave?
No... Uh, it's fine, Renata,
you can go home.
Okay. Night-night.
Good night.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Want some milk?
The timetable has moved.
Our window is limited.
Two targets, Level Six.
They already cost me Zola.
I want confirmed
death in 10 hours.
Sorry,
Mr. Pierce, I...
I forgot my
phone.
Oh, Renata, I wish
you would have knocked.
(GUN FIRING)
(RENATA SHRIEKS)
(PANTING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, man.
I'm sorry about this.
We need a place to lay low.
Everyone we know is
trying to kill us.
Not everyone.
You okay?
Yeah.
What's going on?
When I first
joined S.H.I.E.L.D.
I thought I was
going straight.
But I guess I just traded in
the KGB for HYDRA.
(SIGHS)
I thought I knew
whose lies I was telling,
but I guess I can't tell
the difference anymore.
There's a chance you might
be in the wrong business.
I owe you.
It's okay.
If it was
the other way around,
and it was down to me
to save your life,
now you be honest with me,
would you trust me to do it?
I would now.
And I'm always honest.
Well, you seem pretty chipper
for someone
who just found out
they died for nothing.
Well, guess I just like to
know who I'm fighting.
WILSON: I made breakfast.
If you guys eat
that sort of thing.
So, the question is,
who at S.H.I.E.L.D.
could launch
a domestic missile strike?
Pierce.
Who happens to
be sitting on top
of the most secure
building in the world.
But he's not working alone.
Zola's algorithm
was on the Lemurian Star.
So was Jasper Sitwell.
So, the real question is,
how do the two
most wanted people
in Washington kidnap
a S.H.I.E.L.D. officer
in broad daylight?
The answer is, you don't.
What's this?
Call it a resume.
Is this Bakhmala?
The Khalid Khandil mission,
that was you?
You didn't say
he was a Pararescue.
Is this Riley?
Yeah.
ROMANOFF: I heard
they couldn't bring
in the choppers
because of the RPGs.
What did you use?
A stealth chute?
No.
These.
I thought you said
you were a pilot.
I never said pilot.
I can't ask you
to do this, Sam.
You got out
for a good reason.
Dude, Captain America
needs my help.
There's no better
reason to get back in.
Where can we get our hands
on one of these things?
The last one is
at Fort Meade.
Behind three guarded gates
and a 12-inch steel wall.
Shouldn't be a problem.
Listen, I got to
fly home tonight
because I got
some constituency
problem
and I got to
press the flesh.
Any constituent in
particular, Mr. Senator?
Oh, no, not really.
Twenty-three, kind of hot.
Real hot, you know?
Wants to be
a reporter, I think.
I don't know.
Who listens
at that point?
Doesn't sound like
much of a problem to me.
Really? Because
she's killing my back.
But this isn't
the place to
talk about it.
This is a nice pin.
Thank you.
Come here.
(WHISPERS) Hail HYDRA.
See, it's right there...
Yeah, I just saw that.
Should I get it checked?
I think you should.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
I need a minute.
Bring the car around.
Yes, sir?
WILSON: Agent Sitwell,
how was lunch?
I hear the crab cakes here
are delicious.
Who is this?
The good-looking guy
in the sunglasses,
your 10 o'clock.
Your other 10 o'clock.
There you go.
What do you want?
You're gonna go around
the corner to your right.
There's a gray car
two spaces down.
You and I are
gonna take a ride.
And why would I do that?
Because that tie
looks really expensive,
and I'd hate to mess it up.
(GRUNTING)
Tell me about
Zola's algorithm.
Never heard of it.
What were you doing
on the Lemurian Star?
I was throwing up.
I get seasick.
(GASPS)
Is this little display
meant to insinuate
that you're gonna
throw me off the roof?
Because it's really
not your style, Rogers.
You're right.
It's not.
It's hers.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, wait. What
about that girl from
Accounting, Laura...
Lillian.
Lip piercing, right?
Yeah, she's cute.
Yeah. I'm not
ready for that.
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Zola's algorithm
is a program
for choosing
Insight's targets.
What targets?
You!
A TV anchor in Cairo,
the Under Secretary
of Defense,
a high school
valedictorian
in Iowa City,
Bruce Banner,
Stephen Strange,
anyone who's a threat
to HYDRA.
Now, or in the future.
In the future?
How could it know?
(SITWELL LAUGHING)
How could it not?
The 21st century
is a digital book.
Zola taught HYDRA
how to read it.
Your bank records,
medical histories,
voting patterns,
emails, phone calls,
your damn SAT scores!
Zola's algorithm
evaluates people's past
to predict their future.
And what then?
Oh, my God.
Pierce is gonna kill me.
What then?
Then the Insight
helicarriers scratch
people off the list.
A few million at a time.
SITWELL: HYDRA
doesn't like leaks.
Then why don't you try
sticking a cork in it?
Insight's launching
in 16 hours.
We're cutting it
a little bit close here.
I know.
We'll use him to
bypass the DNA scans
and access
the helicarriers directly.
What? Are you crazy?
That is a terrible,
terrible idea.
(THUD)
(SCREAMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(SCREAMING) Shit!
ROGERS: Hang on!
(GRUNTS)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(HORN BLARES)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WINTER SOLDIER
SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I HAVE HER. FIND HIM.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Go! I got this!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
ROMANOFF: Taking fire above
and below expressway.
Civilians threatened.
Repeat, civilians threatened.
I make an LZ,
2300 block
of Virginia Avenue.
Rendezvous, two minutes.
Get out of the way!
Stay out of the way!
(GUNSHOT)
Ahh!
Bucky?
Who the hell is Bucky?
(SIRENS WAILING)
Drop the shield, Cap!
Get on your knees!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Get down, get down!
Get on your knees!
Down!
Don't move.
Put the gun down.
Not here. Not here!
ROGERS: It was him.
He looked right at me
like he didn't even know me.
How is that even possible?
It was, like, 70 years ago.
Zola.
Bucky's whole unit
was captured in '43.
Zola experimented on him.
Whatever he did
helped Bucky
survive the fall.
They must have
found him and...
None of that's
your fault, Steve.
Even when I had nothing,
I had Bucky.
We need to
get a doctor here.
If we don't put
pressure on that wound,
she's gonna bleed out
here in the truck.
(GROANING)
Ah. That thing was
squeezing my brain.
Who is this guy?
Three holes.
Start digging.
HILL: GSW.
She's lost at least a pint.
WILSON: Maybe two.
Let me take her.
She'll want to
see him first.
About damn time.
Lacerated spinal column,
cracked sternum,
shattered collarbone,
perforated liver,
and one hell of a headache.
Don't forget
your collapsed lung.
Let's not forget that.
Otherwise, I'm good.
They cut you open.
Your heart stopped.
Tetrodotoxin B.
Slows the pulse to
one beat a minute.
Banner developed it
for stress.
Didn't work so great for him,
but we found a use for it.
Why all the secrecy?
Why not just tell us?
Any attempt on
the Director's life
had to look successful.
Can't kill you if
you're already dead.
Besides,
I wasn't sure who to trust.
Sergeant Barnes.
Bucky, no!
(BUCKY SCREAMING)
ZOLA: The procedure
has already started.
You are to be
the new fist of HYDRA.
Put him on ice.
Sir.
(STAMMERS)
He's unstable.
Erratic.
Mission report.
Mission report now.
The man on the bridge.
(INAUDIBLE)
Who was he?
You met him earlier this week
on another assignment.
I knew him.
Your work has been
a gift to mankind.
You shaped the century.
And I need you to
do it one more time.
Society's at a tipping point
between order and chaos.
And tomorrow morning,
we're gonna give it a push.
But, if you don't
do your part,
I can't do mine.
And HYDRA can't
give the world the
freedom it deserves.
But I knew him.
(SIGHS)
PIERCE: Prep him.
He's been out of
cryo freeze too long.
Then wipe him
and start over.
(SCREAMING)
This man declined
the Nobel Peace Prize.
He said peace
wasn't an achievement,
it was a responsibility.
See, it's stuff like this
that gives me trust issues.
We have to
stop the launch.
I don't think the Council's
accepting my calls anymore.
What's that?
Once the helicarriers
reach 3,000 feet,
they'll triangulate
with Insight satellites,
becoming fully weaponized.
FURY: We need to
breach those carriers
and replace their targeting
blades with our own.
HILL: One or two
won't cut it.
We need to link all three
carriers for this to work,
because if even one of those
ships remains operational,
a whole lot of
people are gonna die.
We have to
assume everyone aboard
those carriers is HYDRA.
We have to get past them,
insert these server blades.
And maybe, just maybe
we can salvage what's left...
ROGERS: We're not
salvaging anything.
We're not just
taking down the
carriers, Nick.
We're taking down
S.H.I.E.L.D.
S.H.I.E.L.D. had
nothing to do with this.
You gave me this mission.
This is how it ends.
S.H.I.E.L.D.'s
been compromised.
You said so yourself.
HYDRA grew right
under your nose
and nobody noticed.
Why do you think
we're meeting in
this cave? I noticed.
How many paid the price
before you did?
Look, I didn't
know about Barnes.
ROGERS: Even if you had,
would you have told me?
Or would you have
compartmentalized that,
too?
S.H.I.E.L.D., HYDRA,
it all goes.
HILL: He's right.
WILSON: Don't look at me.
I do what he does,
just slower.
Well...
(SIGHS)
It looks like you're giving
the orders now, Captain.
BUCKY: We looked
for you, after.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
My folks wanted
to give you a ride
to the cemetery.
I know, I'm sorry.
I just kind of
wanted to be alone.
How was it?
It was okay.
She's next to Dad.
I was gonna ask...
I know what
you're gonna say, Buck.
I just...
BUCKY: We can put the
couch cushions on the floor
like when we were kids.
It'll be fun.
All you got to do
is shine my shoes,
maybe take out the trash.
Come on.
Thank you, Buck,
but I can get by on my own.
The thing is,
you don't have to.
I'm with you to
the end of the line, pal.
(SIGHS)
He's gonna be there,
you know.
I know.
Look, whoever
he used to be and
the guy he is now,
I don't think
he's the kind you save.
He's the kind you stop.
I don't know
if I can do that.
Well, he might not
give you a choice.
He doesn't know you.
He will.
Gear up. It's time.
You gonna wear that?
No. If you're gonna
fight a war, you got
to wear a uniform.
Oh, man.
I am so fired.
MAN ON PA:
We are in final
launch sequence.
We are go on guidance.
WOMAN ON PA:
All personnel to
launch stations.
PIERCE: And how
was your flight?
HAWLEY: Lovely.
The ride from
the airport, less so.
Sadly, S.H.I.E.L.D. can't
control everything.
Including
Captain America.
This facility is
biometrically controlled.
And these will give you
unrestricted access.
TECH 1: I've been parking
there for two months.
TECH 2: But it's his spot.
TECH 1: So where's he been?
TECH 2: I think Afghanistan.
Negative DT Six.
The pattern is full.
Well, he could've
said something.
(HIGH-PITCHED FEEDBACK)
ALL: Ahh!
Must be the dish.
I'll check it out.
MAN ON PA: Triskelion
command request we clear
the area for launch.
Excuse us.
PIERCE: I know the road
hasn't exactly been smooth,
and some of you
would have gladly
kicked me out of
the car along the way.
Finally, we're here.
And the world
should be grateful.
ROGERS ON PA:
Attention all
S.H.I.E.L.D. agents,
this is Steve Rogers.
You've heard a lot about me
over the last few days.
Some of you were even
ordered to hunt me down.
But I think it's time
you know the truth.
S.H.I.E.L.D. is not
what we thought it was.
It's been taken over by HYDRA.
Alexander Pierce
is their leader.
The S.T.R.I.K.E.
and Insight crew
are HYDRA as well.
I don't know how many more,
but I know
they're in the building.
They could be standing
right next to you.
They almost have
what they want.
Absolute control.
They shot Nick Fury.
And it won't end there.
If you launch
those helicarriers today,
HYDRA will be able
to kill anyone that
stands in their way.
Unless we stop them.
I know I'm asking a lot.
But the price of
freedom is high.
It always has been.
And it's a price
I'm willing to pay.
And if I'm the only one,
then so be it.
But I'm willing
to bet I'm not.
Did you write that down
first, or was it off
the top of your head?
You smug son of a bitch.
Arrest him.
I guess
I've got the floor.
Preempt the launch
sequence. Send
those ships up now.
Is there a problem?
Um...
I'm sorry, sir.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'm not gonna
launch those ships.
Captain's orders.
Move away from your station.
Like he said...
Hold it right there.
Put the gun down!
Captain's orders.
You picked
the wrong side, Agent.
Depends on where
you're standing.
(GUN CLATTERS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(PEOPLE GASP)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Close the bay door!
Close the bay door now!
They're initiating launch.
Hey, Cap, how do
we know the good guys
from the bad guys?
If they're shooting
at you, they're bad.
(GROANING)
Hey, Cap,
I found those bad guys
you were talking about.
You okay?
I'm not dead yet.
PIERCE: Let me
ask you a question.
What if Pakistan marched
into Mumbai tomorrow
and you knew that
they were going to
drag your daughters
into a soccer stadium
for execution,
and you could just stop it,
with a flick of the switch.
Wouldn't you?
Wouldn't you all?
Not if it was your switch.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(CHUCKLES)
(ALL GRUNTING)
I'm sorry.
Did I step on your moment?
Satellites in range
at 3,000 feet.
Falcon, status?
Engaging.
All right, Cap. I'm in.
Oh, shit.
(ALL GRUNTING)
HILL: Eight minutes, Cap.
Working on it.
What are you doing?
She's disabling
security protocols
and dumping all the secrets
onto the Internet.
Including HYDRA's.
And S.H.I.E.L.D.'s.
If you do this,
none of your past is
gonna remain hidden.
Are you sure you're ready
for the world to see you
as you really are?
Are you?
Alpha lock.
Falcon, where are you now?
I had to take a detour.
(GRUNTS)
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
I'm in.
Bravo lock.
Two down, one to go.
LEAD PILOT:
All S.H.I.E.L.D.
pilots, scramble.
We're the only air support
Captain Rogers has got.
(GROANS)
Disabling the encryption
is an executive order.
It takes two
Alpha Level members.
Don't worry.
Company's coming.
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
Did you get my flowers?
PIERCE: I'm glad
you're here, Nick.
FURY: Really?
Because I thought
you had me killed.
You know
how the game works.
So why make me
head of S.H.I.E.L.D.?
Because you
were the best,
and the most ruthless
person I ever met.
I did what I did
to protect people.
Our enemies are
your enemies, Nick.
Disorder. War.
It's just a matter of time
before a dirty bomb
goes off in Moscow,
or an EMP fries Chicago.
Diplomacy?
A holding action, Nick.
A band-aid.
And you know where
I learned that. Bogota.
You didn't ask.
You just did
what had to be done.
I can bring order
to the lives of
seven billion people
by sacrificing 20 million.
It's the next step, Nick.
If you have
the courage to take it.
No. I have
the courage not to.
S.H.I.E.L.D. COMPUTER:
Retinal scanner active.
(CHUCKLES)
You don't think we've
wiped your clearance
from the system?
I know you erased my password.
Probably deleted
my retinal scan.
But if you want to stay ahead
of me, Mr. Secretary,
you need to keep
both eyes open.
COMPUTER:
Alpha level confirmed.
Encryption code accepted.
Safeguards removed.
Charlie carrier is
45 degrees off the port bow.
(HYDRA SOLDIERS GROANING)
Six minutes.
Hey, Sam, gonna need a ride.
Roger. Let me know
when you're ready.
I just did!
(GROANS)
You know, you're a lot
heavier than you look.
I had a big breakfast.
Steve!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
WILSON: Cap! Cap, come in.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm here.
I'm still on the helicarrier.
Where are you?
I'm grounded.
The suit's down. Sorry, Cap.
Don't worry. I got it.
(ALARM BLARING)
WOMAN: (ON PA)
Emergency evacuation alert.
All personnel, proceed to
designated safety zones.
S.H.I.E.L.D. AGENT:
All S.H.I.E.L.D. agents
regroup at Rally Point Delta.
(YELLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
DISPATCH: (ON RADIO)
Sir, the Council's
been breached.
Repeat, Dispatch.
Black Widow's up there.
Headed up.
Falcon?
Yeah.
Rumlow's headed
for the Council.
I'm on it.
People are
gonna die, Buck.
I can't let that happen.
Please don't make me do this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Done.
And it's trending.
(GROANING)
Unless you want a two-inch
hole in your sternum,
I'd put that gun down.
That was armed the moment
you pinned it on.
(GROANS)
Ahhh!
Drop it!
(SCREAMS)
I'm on 41, headed toward
the southwest stairwell.
(GROANING)
This is gonna hurt.
There are no
prisoners with HYDRA.
Just order.
And order only
comes through pain.
You ready for yours?
Man, shut the hell up.
Lieutenant,
how much longer?
CHARLIE XO: (ON RADIO)
65 seconds to satellite link.
Targeting grid engaged.
Lowering weapons array now.
One minute.
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANS)
HILL: (ON RADIO)
30 seconds, Cap.
Stand by. (GROANS)
Charlie... (GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
CHARLIE WEAPONS TECH:
(ON RADIO) We've
reached 3,000 feet.
Sat link coming online now.
Deploy algorithm.
CHARLIE WEAPONS TECH:
Algorithm deployed.
PIERCE: (ON RADIO)
We are go to target.
CHARLIE WEAPONS TECH:
Target saturation reached.
All targets assigned.
Fire when ready.
Firing in...
Three,
two...
(GRUNTS)
One.
(PANTS) Charlie lock.
Where are the targets?
Okay, Cap, get out of there.
Fire now.
But, Steve...
Do it!
Do it now!
(WINTER SOLDIER SCREAMING)
What a waste.
ROMANOFF:
So, you still on the fence
about Rogers' chances?
Time to go, Councilwoman.
This way. Come on.
You're going to
fly me out of here.
You know, there was
a time I would've taken
a bullet for you.
You already did.
You will again,
when it's useful.
(GROANING)
Romanoff.
Natasha.
Natasha! Come on!
Ow.
Those really do sting.
(WEAKLY) Hail HYDRA.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
You're out of your depth, kid.
Son of a bitch!
Please tell me you got
that chopper in the air!
ROMANOFF: (ON RADIO)
Sam, where are you?
41st floor! Northwest corner!
We're on it!
Stay where you are!
Not an option!
41st floor! 41st!
It's not like they
put the floor numbers
on the outside
of the building.
Hill! Where's Steve?
You got a location
on Rogers?
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS)
You know me.
No, I don't!
(PANTING)
Bucky.
You've known me
your whole life.
Your name is
James Buchanan Barnes.
Shut up!
I'm not gonna fight you.
You're my friend.
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
You're my mission.
(GRUNTING)
You're my mission!
Then finish it.
Because I'm with you
to the end of the line.
(R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
On your left.
(R&B MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
FEMALE BAILIFF:
Do you solemnly
swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
ROMANOFF: I do.
COMMITTEE MEMBER:
Why haven't we yet heard
from Captain Rogers?
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
I don't know what there is
left for him to say.
I think the wreck in
the middle of the Potomac
made his point
fairly eloquently.
COMMITTEE MEMBER:
Well, he could explain how
this country is
expected to maintain
its national security
now that he and you
have laid waste to
our intelligence apparatus.
HYDRA was selling you lies,
not intelligence.
Many of which you
seemed to have had
a personal hand in telling.
Agent, you should know
that there are
some on this committee
who feel,
given your service record,
both for this country
and against it,
that you belong
in a penitentiary.
Not mouthing off
on Capitol Hill.
You're not going to
put me in a prison.
You're not going
to put any of us
in a prison. You know why?
Do enlighten us.
Because you need us.
Yes, the world is
a vulnerable place,
and yes,
we help make it that way.
But we're also the ones
best qualified to defend it.
So, if you want to
arrest me, arrest me.
You'll know where to find me.
So, you've experienced
this sort of thing before.
You get used to it.
We've been data
mining HYDRA's files.
Looks like a lot of rats
didn't go down with the ship.
I'm headed
to Europe tonight.
Wanted to ask
if you'd come.
There's something
I got to do first.
How about you, Wilson?
Could use a man
with your abilities.
I'm more of
a soldier than a spy.
All right, then.
Anybody asks for me,
tell them they can
find me, right here.
You should be honored.
That's about as
close as he gets
to saying thank you.
Not going with him?
No.
Not staying here.
Nah.
I blew all my covers.
I got to go figure
out a new one.
That might take a while.
I'm counting on it.
That thing you asked for,
I called in a few
favors from Kiev.
Will you do me a favor?
Call that nurse.
She's not a nurse.
And you're not
a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent.
What was her name again?
Sharon.
She's nice.
Be careful, Steve.
You might not want to
pull on that thread.
You're going after him.
You don't have
to come with me.
I know.
When do we start?
It's over. Fury has
released everything
to the public.
Everything he knows about.
Herr Strucker, if they get
word of our work here,
if they find out
we serve HYDRA...
HYDRA, S.H.I.E.L.D.
Two sides of a coin
that's no longer currency.
What we have
is worth more than
any of them ever knew.
We've only scratched
the surface and already,
there are other
facilities doing
HYDRA's good work
around the world.
We'll feed them
to Captain America
and his colorful friends,
and keep them
off our scent.
What about the volunteers?
The dead will
be buried so deep
their own ghosts won't
be able to find them.
And the survivors?
The twins.
Sooner or later,
they will meet the twins.
It's not a world
of spies anymore.
Not even
a world of heroes.
This is the age
of miracles, Doctor.
There's nothing
more horrifying
than a miracle.