-It's a tractor!
-Look, a tractor!
Don't stay here. Go over there.
I told you to go over there.
1986, OCTOBER 23RD
Go home.
Prick.
-Prick.
-I found it.
I found it.
-Look!
-What's all that?
-I found it!
-Hey!
-Put that back!
Put it down.
-Put it down and leave.
-It's mine.
-Hey!
That's important. Don't touch that!
Those pricks.
You annoying pricks!
See?
You dated and got dumped
by the dead Park Bo-hee.
Yes or no?
Seems about right.
Seems about right?
Take that hat off, you son of a bitch.
What girl would like you for that?
After. Watching.
Bo. Dy. Heat.
The. Film.
Body heat?
Is that an action film?
Ac… Act…
You, jackass.
As the case concerns murder of women,
please understand my wording.
For example.
Sexy.
Or pretty.
Impressions like these?
So first impression?
Well, I guess
sophisticated
despite being from the country…
Open your eyes.
You closed your eyes.
Look at me.
Not the sky. Look at me!
Are his eyes naturally like that?
One, two.
…about a middle-aged woman
and the two children.
Their stories…
LIM CHEOL-MIN (26)
ROBBERY, RAPE
Didn't you say you were going
to the military academy?
FAST DELIVERY
Did you take the test for it?
You better study hard
to go to the military academy.
Receipt.
You didn't tell us.
Stop pulling my leg.
I told you to bring the receipt.
No, you didn't.
-You said that the last time so I--
-Hey, hey!
Detective Park.
Jackass, stop lying.
You answered the call.
I need the receipt for the meal,
not the bicycle.
Hey, the receipt!
Why haven't you set up the lines?
Use a tool, not your hands!
-They can't do shit.
-This way, Detective Park.
What's this?
Footprint, sir.
How'd you find it?
By me. I found it this morning.
Go help out that kid.
Man.
Called the forensics?
Yes, they'll be here momentarily.
You know what?
We don't have the informant at the scene.
What?
No forensics yet either.
The scene's a mess!
That gaffer.
-Dal-su!
-Let's go!
-You pricks! Go away!
-Dal-su!
Hey, get rid of the kids!
Come over here.
Who got the call?
You couldn't find the informant?
The call--
We can't preserve it this way.
Forensics aren't here either.
What a shithole.
-Park Seung-gyu?
-What does this even mean?
-Photos!
-What happened here?
Take the photos when instructed!
Why'd you let the reporters in?
They were already here when I arrived.
What? Man.
I don't see Reporter Park though.
A day off?
I'm not sure either.
Hate that dickface.
What a way to end my career.
I need a preserved scene
to begin investigating.
-Hey, tractor!
-Preserve it well!
-Do it well!
Get outta here, tractor!
No, not there! Tractor!
Hey!
Don't you see me waving here!
What you got stuck up
your fucking ear hole!
You dickhead! Don't you see this?
Assholes are finally here.
Tell the people there to go away!
I called you to come ages ago!
Huh?
I can't get shit started
until you preserve the scene!
Got honey on the field?
He fucking ate it too.
Seriously, what's going on here?
Why do you keep staring at the pictures?
Doesn't it kill your appetite?
It's sick.
If I stare at it long enough
I can tell who the perp is.
Instinctively.
What are you, a psychic?
Why not consider a change of career?
Sheesh.
I have a knack for seeing through people.
That's how I make my living
and the reason they call me
the all-seeing eye around here.
If that's the case,
you see those two sitting over there?
One of the two is a rapist
and the other
is the brother of the victim.
So the brother brought in
the perp who did his sister.
Now let's see
if you can guess which one the rapist is.
It's not in.
Really?
Do it properly, will you?
I'll personally give you
a special shot today.
What an honor.
It's only a cold shot.
Do you know how much this costs?
Gwak Seol-young.
Yeah?
I hear you're doing better now
than when you were at the clinic.
When people get sick here,
they come to you, not the doctor.
Wait, I have something important to say.
I heard it while giving a shot
to the granny at the mill.
You know "Baek's Meat Shop"
in Jeongsol-myeon?
Baek's?
You know what kind of a Baek he is?
What?
He's a "gonna-jump-on-ya" Baek.
Jump on women?
Exactly.
Well, they've got a crazy son
called Baek Gwang-ho.
Apparently,
he used to chase after Lee Hyang-suk.
Lee Hyang-suk.
The dead Lee Hyang-suk?
Yes.
The woman who died
with a girdle over her head last winter.
Right.
Even more importantly
the night Lee Hyang-suk got killed
the granny saw him stalking her.
She really saw it?
I'm telling you.
There're rumors
she's been loopy since last year.
She's perfectly fine.
The son. Let's see.
Baek Gwang-ho?
What does he look like again?
This side of his face is a bit…
Gimme some details.
Anyway, he's not all that well.
Hey, Baek Gwang-ho.
Just between us guys
When you see a pretty girl,
you get the feels and want some.
Believe me, I used to do that
with my friends when I was your age.
I feel ya.
You weren't trying to kill her
from the get-go.
-You probably wanted to touch her boobs--
-I couldn't.
That's why you killed her.
To touch her when she's dead.
No.
You know.
I grew up like you, with hardships.
Yet I'm a nice person.
A man's got a lot of affection
and can be impatient
which sometimes lead to these things
but it's not a fault.
But hitting someone with a fist--
You've got a hell of a face.
Just looking at his face makes me mad.
What now?
-Oh no.
-It's scraped.
This kid.
Purdy, huh?
This is so you don't get scrapes, asshole.
Hey.
Stop that with your boots.
You're hurting the kid.
Baek Gwang-ho. Get up.
Asshole.
You're really not guilty?
Look at me in the eyes.
Huh?
Can't tell where he's looking.
Look at me in the eyes!
If you don't turn yourself in,
your limbs will rot to death.
Excuse me, is there…
Is there--
Miss!
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I was just trying to ask for direction.
-Here, let me help you up.
-Hey!
Hey!
-I'm--
-Here, get up.
-What are you--
-It's freaking daytime.
-Miss.
-Where do you think this is?
The Rape Kingdom?
Son of a bitch.
-Get over here.
-Hey!
Who the hell are you, you jackass?
What are you?
Get out here!
-Fuck!
-Miss, the victim needs to accompany!
-Hey!
-Miss!
-Stop!
-Bastard.
Hey! Fuck!
-Shit. She left.
-Hey!
Are you a cop?
You should've told me sooner.
My bad.
You're terrible at fighting
for being a cop.
You're terrible at recognizing people
What's this smell?
Oh, sneakers.
Stinks, doesn't it?
May not look it,
but that's actually evidence no. 28.
Get this developed quickly.
Sergeant.
What?
He's from Seoul--
Oh, nice to see you!
I got the call.
What happened to your face?
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
So the desk.
-Sergeant, the desk?
-Oh, right.
I got you a seat by the window.
Oh there.
I like the corner over there.
Okay, sure! Whatever you want.
-Detective Jo, say hello.
-Yeah?
Senior officer Seo Tae-yun
from the Seoul office.
-Oh, I see.
-Yea.
Jo Yong-gu. Nice to meet you.
He volunteered for this case.
What an extraordinary opportunity.
Go ahead and get settled.
Please.
Reality Show
Inspector Sergeant
I like that song. That theme song.
I need to go home
to watch Inspector Sergeant.
Which episode was tonight again?
Hey, eat.
Right, I need to call Dad.
I said, eat!
I need to call--
It's Dad!
Is it out? Come on.
Hey, Baek Gwang-ho.
This is the footprint taken
from the scene of death last year.
Take a good look.
And this is your sneakers from your place.
You wear them, right?
Yes or no?
Okay, look.
Look at the footprint in the picture
and the bottom of your shoes. Well?
Exact match, right?
This pattern.
Round. Sunken. Exactly the same, huh?
Yes or no?
That's just dirt that got wiped out
so no matter, right?
You killed all the women, right?
Fine.
You didn't kill all of them.
Right?
But you didn't not kill
Lee Hyang-suk alone.
Well?
I didn't kill anyone.
Hey!
We have all the evidence. Stop lying!
-Where's our shovel?
-A shovel?
You're a joke.
-Hey, asshole.
-Yes?
Lemme see that.
What kind of a guy
doesn't even know how to shovel?
You get it set up
and step on it, like this.
-Baek Gwang-ho.
-Yes?
-And then you scoop it up, like this.
-This moron.
-Like this.
-Whoa.
You think we're here to play?
You know what this is?
We're gonna bury you here.
Why?
You ask why?
'Cause you won't listen.
I do listen.
Then tell us.
We've got fresh air,
despite your unfortunate face.
Come over here.
Girls don't like your face, do they?
Shit, they frown and run away, don't they?
That's right.
I'm gonna kill them all.
Everyone who frowned at my face.
Kill them all.
They're all in my head.
Was Hyang-suk one of them?
Hyang-suk?
Lee Hyang-suk.
You used to chase her around.
She's pretty.
Sure, she's pretty.
But then she frowned at your face,
didn't she?
She told you to get the fuck away.
You liked her but that fucking bitch.
So you killed her.
Right?
Next to the railroad.
In the big field.
Yes, that's right.
Neck, Hyang-suk's neck.
Strangled really hard.
Using what?
-The bra.
-Bra?
Hyang-suk's white bra.
Strangled the neck really hard.
And then?
Stockings.
Stockings taken off her.
-So second is stockings.
-Yes.
Kid's got some memory. He's smart.
And then?
What was that?
What's that called?
Like a string.
Handbag strap?
Yes, handbag strap!
Using that on her neck
to strangle really hard.
And then?
Then her body shivered
and it looked
like she was completely dead.
Then what?
Pulled it over Hyang-suk's head.
Pulled what over?
Her panties.
Her panties were pulled over her head,
like a hat.
You mean a girdle?
For women?
Yes, girdle!
-Put that on like a hat.
-Yeah.
And then?
Oh, put back on her clothes.
Why was that?
I don't know. Put it back on her.
Why'd you do that? Why?
I wouldn't know.
Asshole! You've been doing great!
You jackass, what did you do next?
-Running!
-Okay, to where?
-It was raining lots!
-Run where?
-Kept running!
-You asshole!
Where'd you run to?
Lots of lightning! Boom!
Tell us where you ran to!
-Yong-gu! Dig again.
-Boom!
-Dig? But we gotta…
-Lightning! Hot!
VICTIM'S HOME
PARK BO-HEE
RIPPED BLOUSE TO TIE HANDS BEHIND
CLOSE SHOT
This is the civil defense alert alarm.
This is a drill.
The air-raid alert has been issued.
As of current,
the air-raid alert is issued nation-wide.
All public and private buildings and homes
should ensure
no light can be seen from outside
and follow the civil defense guidelines
provided by the defense control center.
Please move flammable items
to a safe location…
and return home promptly.
Turn off the lights!
-Turn off the lights!
-Hey, go home!
Rice store, turn off the lights!
Turn off the lights!
YOU HIT, YOU DIE
-What?
-Go put on some breasts.
Hey, you!
Over here.
Put it on. Did you gather everyone?
-Yes.
-Get in the car.
LEE HYANG-SUK
Turn around.
Your pants. Go take those off.
What should the headline say?
How about "the three arrest-eteers"
or "the smile of the invincible trio"?
-Detective Park, to the back.
-Hurry!
First, form a row along the rail.
That looks good.
Ms. Gwon, it's a dinner party tonight!
Okay, here we go!
Okay, now with your fists!
-Show me your fist! Great!
-Fist?
-High in the air!
-Detective Seo, get in!
-No thanks.
-Come on!
Sergeant Gu, try this!
-Okay, take one like this.
-Great!
Hey, stand right there.
Here.
Your fingers are all stuck together.
Must be hard to use chopsticks.
Since you were a kid, right?
-Take him.
-Yes, sir.
-Gwang-ho, it's here, right?
-Huh?
I don't know.
What you talking about?
-It's here!
-Hey, quiet.
Spot inspection is all about acting.
We've got a lot of eyes on us.
You got it?
How's my position?
Bend down more.
What do we do first?
What was it? Stockings.
Ideally, we should have a numbered list.
First, second, and so on.
So why didn't you make one?
I'm fucking busy.
Sergeant.
What?
It's too late
to have a proper spot inspection.
-Cancel it to save more embarrassment.
-Hey, look.
Didn't I tell you to stay away?
Why come all the way just to nag?
Come up with any excuse.
"The suspect is sick" or--
Detective Seo!
Why're you trying to ruin a done-deal?
I kept telling you that he's not the perp!
Be quiet!
Look, Sergeant.
The perp tied her neck thrice
and made a tight knot.
Have you seen his hands?
He can't tie anything with those hands!
-Get out.
-Even little kids know that much!
Get out!
Grab the bra and tie it.
Concentrate!
-Gwang-ho!
-It's Dad. Dad!
It's Dad!
Dad!
You didn't do it! You didn't kill her!
I know! I didn't do it!
Were you at the scene? Tell me!
He didn't kill them!
My son's innocent!
It's all over.
Don't say a word.
Hey.
Did you see the face
of prosecutor Choi Hong-il earlier?
Still, a fucking warrant dismissal?
We have real evidence.
You mean the picture of the footprint?
Are we really letting him loose?
What else can we do?
Confession alone won't do.
That depends on the content.
You heard the recording too.
He said details only the perp would know.
You know? Things only he would know.
Like the order in which he choked her.
You heard it too. In the mountain.
You weren't putting words in his mouth?
What?
Stop, you both. Let's eat first.
Seriously!
What's this?
I asked for the sauce on the side.
Fuck!
POLICE CHIEF RESIGNS
SEARCH FORCE REPLACED
COUNTRYSIDE SERIAL MURDER MYSTERY
NO SIGN OF SUSPECT, POLICE AT A LOSS
TAERYEONG-EUP SERIAL KILLINGS OF WOMEN
CRIME INVESTIGATION REPORT
Between the first scene of crime
and the second
the linear distance is about 1000m.
It's a short distance, less than 1km.
REPORT ON VICTIM ON DAY OF CRIME
The victim
on 12th and 16th
on these two days
at twelve o'clock…
Oh, December 16th.
On December 16th
at twelve o'lock
at Yangji Cafe located in Bangcheon…
WARRANT ISSUED
WITH INSUFFICIENT EVIDENCE
CELEBRATORY SHOT ENDS IN SMOKE
…meets Han Seong-geun
who has an office job and is 32 years old.
They were on a blind date, I think?
So and
at the scene, we found one footprint
two bloodstains
one semen
total of--
Did we have semen for this?
Yes.
Were there any similarities
between the two women who died?
Similarities?
Well they were both single.
They were quite pretty.
What else?
It was raining on both days.
Rain?
They were killed on a rainy night.
Really?
And red clothing.
The dead women were wearing red.
Both of them?
Three of them.
Three?
What's he talking about?
There's one more woman.
We just haven't found her body.
This is a missing person report.
Unique name, isn't it?
Dokgo Hyeon-sun, 27.
Filed missing two months ago, July 18th.
Oh, her.
Dokgo Hyeon-sun? I know her well.
She's famous here.
She's this pretty gal from Cheongsol-myeon
and she's as pretty as Miss Korea.
They've must've filed her missing
for leaving home--
-Shut up.
-Yong-gu, weren't you--
This is more than a missing case.
A close look at the papers say so.
Papers never lie.
She was wearing a red blouse
at the time of missing.
It's obvious from the papers alone.
What's that?
The highlighted part shows the weather
on the day she went missing.
It was raining that evening too.
Red clothes on a rainy day.
I'm sure of it.
She was killed by the same perp.
You don't know anything about this town.
She's always talked of going to Seoul--
-Hey!
-She's probably already--
I can guess where the body would be.
See the map on the last page.
I've traced and marked her route that day
and estimated the location of crime here.
Get me two squadrons of combat police.
We'll have the body in two days.
You confident?
You know, college kids.
Yeah, what's up?
When they go on MT,
I hear the guys all get laid
and everyone sleeps in the same room
and have orgies.
Is that true?
I don't know. Hurry up.
But you have an associate degree!
Membership training, orientation.
Have you never been to one?
Why don't you ask Seo there
with a four-year degree
if they have orgies?
-Here.
-Fucking four-year degree.
I did high school for four years.
Like this.
No, not that.
Forget it.
I do miss Hyeon-sun.
Right?
-She is too pretty to rot in this town.
-Hey!
She's probably in Seoul--
-Don't run. Get out!
-What's going on?
-Hm.
-There're a lot of snakes there.
Don't touch it, jackass!
A body decays at a different rate
depending on location.
See?
Despite it being old,
this part's completely intact.
The thigh.
Sign of rape?
Some semen.
But the sample's too old
for us to get a reading.
Hyeon-sun…
Once again, he only used
items belonging to the victim.
True.
She was choked using her stockings, right?
Yes.
Putting the victim's panties
over the head is the same.
The way the hands are tied up
is the same, too.
The MO and the after-measures all line up.
Thorough.
Flawless.
So what you're saying
is that there are no eyewitnesses.
Some more thin skirt for you?
We're good on the meat.
Where's Gwang-ho?
I don't see him.
Is something wrong--
I bought something for your son
but you can give it to him later.
What is this?
I saw the shoes he was wearing earlier
and saw how old and smelly they were.
I've been wanting to get him a new pair
and picked up a pair of Nikes.
You didn't have to!
He's always sleeping in weird places.
-Hey, can we get--
-On my way!
Hey, Baek Gwang-ho.
This kid.
You're size seven, right?
Try on these Nikes.
Lemme see that.
-See, earlier--
-Let's see.
-These are Nices, not Nike.
-Nice, Nike, same thing.
So long as they're sturdy to wear.
Try them on!
If you're getting him a pair,
might as well get him the real ones.
They look good!
Have a shot.
Beating is all part of affection.
If you see me on the street,
don't run and say hi.
Yong-gu here cried after you left--
That kid.
Hey, where're you off to now?
That kid…
Sergeant.
He is as far as we could get
from our perp.
All the time we wasted on a kid like--
Detective Seo.
Why don't you eat some meat?
I don't eat burnt meat.
♪Told me you'll come to me♪
♪When the flowers bloom in springtime♪
♪Like the singing swallows♪
♪On the hills♪
♪Chirping songs of joy♪
Detective Seo?
♪All alone on the hills♪
Hey, Seoul bumpkin.
What?
What are you doing here?
All the way from Seoul?
Well?
To catch the perp.
Is Seoul that big?
Is it?
BIgger than the US?
Give me a banana.
You see, in the US
there's a thing called the FBI.
Do you know how they investigate?
They fucking use their brains.
They analyze.
You know why?
Because their land is fucking massive!
So if they don't use their brains,
they can't cover all that land.
That's why the fucking FBI
has to be smart about things.
But you see, in the Republic of Korea
a few steps here and there,
and you've seen it all.
You're bound to see it all.
You know why?
The land is fucking tiny.
That's why they say
that the detectives
of the Republic of Korea
investigate with their two feet.
There's an old saying like that.
Jackass.
A smart-ass like you
should go to the US--
Damn it, stop fucking with me, fucker.
Fuck.
You son of bitch!
Let go. No?
You--
Give this to him.
Get this away now!
Getting that out
does help clear the head.
I can finally think now.
Things look clearer now.
The perp.
He's gonna strike again
on a wet, rainy night.
Therefore
we move one step in advance.
A preemptive strike.
Okay?
You bastards.
If you fight again in front of me,
I'm going to kill you both.
You understand?
["Woman in the Rain" plays]
♪I can't forget the woman in the rain♪
Everyone, when the--
WELCOME HIS EXCELLENCY
PRESIDENT JEON DU-HWAN
♪Where's is she now♪
♪Wearing a yellow raincoat♪
♪I can't forget her black eyes♪
♪With a loving smile♪
It's certainly raining.
You ready?
♪Looking at the raindrops♪
♪I walked, without a word♪
♪I can't forget the women in the rain♪
♪I can't forget her♪
Whoa, Gwi-oak.
Shut up.
What if she actually gets attacked?
I'm sure Seo's right behind her somewhere.
Fucking sting operation.
You mean we gotta do this
every time it rains?
Thanks to this,
she gets to wear a red dress.
With the make-up on,
she's a completely different person.
-So what?
-Was she always that pretty?
You like that?
-Hey, we're on an operation--
-Let's see if you got big.
-Wait--
-Wow!
Can you see from here?
People don't come out these days.
Someone's coming.
Hey, girls!
This way!
-Hey, watch out.
-You guys are soaked!
Stay here until it stops raining.
The umbrella is no use at all.
We picked this up over there.
Someone must've thrown it out.
Do you live here too, sister?
Hey, she's a detective.
You're kidding, right?
She's a detective in homicide.
-For real?
-Yes.
You guys can get a ride home
on our car later.
Whoa, we get to ride in a police car?
Hey, now.
Start getting home earlier.
Why are you out so late?
We are okay because we're always together.
You'd be fine even if you were alone.
Nam-ju, tell that story to the detectives.
What story?
Remember? When we were cleaning earlier?
Oh yeah!
Do you know where the killer lives?
I'm serious.
We go to Ansong Girl's Middle School
and there's a really old toilet
There's a crazy guy
that lives under the toilet
and apparently that's the guy!
He hides all day long
and comes out at night to kill the women!
That must mean
if the killer shows up at night
it would smell like poo
all along his path.
That's not it.
Yu-jin said some crazy woman
fell in and died.
I'll bring the umbrella to the plant then.
Uh-huh, sure.
Yes.
Okay then. I'll be right there.
♪My love, stay by my side♪
♪Please don't leave me♪
♪I still love you♪
♪When I'm walking alone♪
♪And dark night falls♪
Hello?
Everyone stay in your position.
Don't move anything around you
and don't move another--
Hey, you!
You right there!
Nobody moves until forensics get here!
Look.
This is what you call a real footprint.
You see the concrete plant there?
So he grabbed her in front of the plant
and dragged her in silence
for almost 400m.
It's like seeing
a bride and a groom enter.
We really have nothing
besides the footprint?
I thought we might find his fingerprint
on the victim's umbrella, but to no avail.
The footprint's likely no good
having been faded in the rain.
So much
for the whole preserve-the-scene fiasco.
That's where I think we have the clue.
What do you mean?
That we have no evidence
of the perp on the scene.
You see, in every rape case
you're bound to find some dick hair
somewhere on the scene.
And?
Therefore, our perp likely
has no hair down there to begin with.
Like hairlessness?
Right, hairlessness.
Completely bald.
So he has nothing to leave at the scene
from the get-go.
For example, if a monk shaved down there
it'd be a perfect scenario.
There's a temple called Yongdeoksa nearby.
Should I start there?
-Gwi-oak.
-Yes?
The radio's on.
How would you like your coffee?
Lots of sugar for me.
-Detective Seo.
-Yup.
Got anything for us?
As you saw today
the perp is very thorough.
-And?
-Therefore
we would need to think outside the box--
Then what? What are you suggesting?
Man.
I have something to show you all.
What's she showing us today?
What's this?
I got this from the FM radio stations.
It looks like a list of songs played.
Yes. It's a hit music station
that I listen to often.
There's a person
who always requests "A Gloomy Letter".
See the dates the song was played.
The song wasn't very popular
so they don't play it often.
What's the song? What letter?
"A Gloomy Letter"
sung by Yu Jae-ha.
-He used to be in Jo Yong-pil's band.
-Oh yes, the drummer.
What about it?
The days the song was played
match the dates of the crimes here.
Look, October 20th.
Park Bo-hee.
December 19th.
Lee Hyang-suk died.
You mean this was playing
when Park Myeong-ja died yesterday?
Yes, I listened to it myself yesterday.
As the DJ played the song,
he read the request postcard.
"Sent from a lonely man in Taeryeong-eup."
"Please play it on a rainy night."
Miss Gwon, nice! Good idea!
Read your share of mystery novels, did ya?
Thank you for sharing the story.
This is too spot-on to be a coincidence.
Look at the papers. Papers never lie.
Here we go again.
Maybe our perp is a psycho
-who goes crazy when the song comes on.
-Now you too?
Quit the nonsense.
No, it does make sense. It's simple.
It's like singing the national anthem
before starting the morning assembly.
Did you secure the postcard?
I did ask for it
but they're really busy over there.
Secure the postcard and check for
fingerprint, post stamp, and handwriting.
Got it!
Detective Gwon, call the station now.
Now!
Hairlessness. What about this?
What about it?
No hair down there, as we were discussing.
The bald ones.
How're you gonna look into that?
Undress every man on the street?
I called to make sure
you hold onto that postcard!
What postcard?
The one you played last night!
We've got a ton of postcards!
Mister.
Put it on.
Detective.
They took out
the trash from yesterday already.
It's no use looking in there.
Aren't you washing?
I've washed enough.
My skin's all bloated.
Did you find a hairless guy?
Find one, my ass.
I ended up spending a fortune on sauna.
I can't even expense that shit.
But your face looks clear for once.
I like it.
You like it?
Pants on and off, all day long.
I'd be surprised
if I had any hair left by now.
I asked the scrubber to let me know
when he sees a hairless guy
and handed him my card.
That fucker smirked at me.
Don't stress all by yourself
and have the other guys work on it.
Seo Tae-yun.
What's that Seoul guy doing these days?
He's studying recent hits.
What?
There's this damn thing.
He's talking nonsense these days too?
I'm at a dead-end.
if you're really at a dead end,
go see a fortune teller.
A fortune teller?
Yeah, go see a good one.
Ask where the perp is.
Well?
It's the front gate of the police station.
You gotta move it about 10m
to the southwest, not facing the east.
I just saw a face.
It must be him.
AGRICULTURAL COOP
Is it one of these?
How dare you shove
these disgusting faces at me.
-I mean, take a look.
-Get it away.
You're messing with my fortune.
JOLLY PONG, RICE SNACK
Take this and do as I say.
Don't try to sell me the talisman.
Wait, hold on.
You mix in the dirt from the crime scene.
Mix it.
She said this was the most important part.
Now, pour.
That's good.
Good.
Once this dries
the stains will turn into the shape
of the perp's face.
No way. How--
You're bringing us bad luck!
Do you know how much this is?
You're messing with our fortune.
What's that?
You should know.
A perp always returns
to the scene of the crime.
Hold on.
That's…
What's that bastard doing here?
["A Gloomy Letter" plays]
♪When I got home♪
♪And opened it up slowly♪
♪On the pretty paper♪
Are you kidding?
What happened to
science-based investigation?
How's that gonna help?
♪Line after line, carved in my mind♪
♪Sent my innocent heart…♪
He looks cool though.
♪…Afloat♪
Run!
Stop right there!
Hey!
You asshole!
Not all at once! In a line!
-Stop, you asshole!
-Fuck!
Let go!
Didn't you see a weird person here?
-No.
-What?
It's that cop.
-From the guard post.
You know him?
He's hell of a runner.
Fuck.
No? Try that way.
You sure you looked there carefully?
Do you even know this place?
You stepped on a branch earlier.
Branch, shit, who cares? It was him.
What's that?
-There he is!
-Hey!
Stop!
FASTER DELIVERY
HAPPIER LAND DEVELOPMENT
-What's this now?
-Fuck.
Hey!
Black. He was wearing black.
-Black.
-They're all wearing black.
Stop the operation!
Stop everything right now!
-Detective Jo.
-Yes.
Don't go in there.
Gather those guys.
Hey, stop moving!
-Gather around.
-Where'd he go?
-Heads up straight.
-Get over here.
-The rest of you, too.
-Tell him to hurry.
Look at me straight in the eyes.
Hey, come over here.
What's going on?
It hurts.
-Lemme see.
-What did I do?
-You! How dare you run!
-It hurts!
Get up!
Get out!
Come on!
I was just jerking off.
Is that a crime?
No, it isn't.
But why'd you run if it isn't?
Someone jumped out from the woods.
It freaked me out.
Why not jerk off at home?
I have kids at home.
And the air's fresh in the woods.
No, you went there
to think about the woman you killed.
Excuse me.
Your husband roams around outside
at night, doesn't he?
What's this?
Lemme see.
Fighting for justice, Batman!
What'd you use to make this?
But you see, these days
the things that happen here
are much more provocative
than those magazines.
I read the articles
and let my imagination run wild.
I think, 'what's wrong with me?'
but then again, I think, 'when else?'
According to the neighbors
he takes good care of his sick wife
regularly attends church
is diligent
and just a great person overall.
All perverts are like that.
Looks normal on the outside.
Can't fool my eyes though.
He's it.
Honey, I put in extra pairs of socks
so do change frequently, after dinner--
Okay, okay. Now go and feed the kids!
They're protesting. You could get hurt!
RELEASE BROTHER JO BYEONG-SUN
No faith means hell!
Release Jo Byeong-sun!
What now?
I hear Jo Byeong-sun confessed overnight.
Who said that?
Come on, Sergeant!
MAKE JUST SOCIETY
When's the official report scheduled?
No, I don't know anything.
Be patient, won't you?
You've been investigating four days
without a warrant.
People are talking about
illegal imprisonment.
This time, make it vivid like a movie.
Go.
You were so good before.
Yong-gu?
So you were hiding behind the toilet
when you saw Park Myeong-ja's flashlight
Yes, that sounds good.
Yes or no? Make it clear.
I think I dreamt that.
So I approached her
and then hit her neck with my bare hands.
Bam! That must be it.
-Bare hands--
-And then?
Then Myeong-ja probably went "ow"
and then collapsed.
Then I look at her
and get ready to jump her…
Wait, that's not it.
Oh, right!
I drag her to the pine field first.
From the rice field to the pine field
is a whopping 200m, according to the news.
That's a pretty long way.
It's raining cats and dogs
-and I drag her across.
-And then?
-Then?
-Then
I threw her on the pine field!
Strangled her.
Using what?
Bag strap.
You sure?
Stockings.
Oh, right.
Bra. A Venus bra.
I used that
to strangle her neck like this.
Like this.
That's when she picked up a stone
and hit me in the face.
Right here, next to the eye.
It hurts even though it was in the dreams.
Byeong-sun,
are you gonna keep saying "dream"?
That's enough.
Turn your face this way.
That's where you got hit with the stone.
-No, that's from yesterday when he--
-Shut up. Picture time.
You've done so well until now
so let's wrap up now.
So when I got hit in the face
I was probably disoriented.
I was lying down for a long time
and when I came to my senses…
Yes?
…I was in the bathroom.
Toilet. Shit hole.
So then I looked around
and there are maggots everywhere.
He won't wrap up.
So I washed it off
and climbed up using the hay
and boy, was that hard even in the dream.
When I got up, I saw that I wasn't home
but at a school toilet.
So I came out to the playground
and there were so many girls
-and no matter what I said, the smell--
-Hey.
Where'd you hear that story?
Everyone knows this story.
I saw it in my dream.
From beneath the point of the accident
stay on left and right
of the direction of the wind--
Do you understand?
Yes.
-Let go. Let go!
-As soon as this stage is over…
-Class 2 move to the training field…
-Okay, In-gyeong.
-Please report to the office…
-That's not cool! Stop!
You know that toilet story,
where'd you hear it?
Is that why you're here?
What's the matter?
I got a scrape on my way down.
Must've been a stone inside.
Where's the nurse?
Here, I'll put it on for you.
I got it.
Embarrassed, you kiddo?
Go sit.
Here, give me the band-aid.
Show me the scrape.
Remember what I asked earlier?
Give it a good thought.
That story of the killer
hiding under the toilet
and coming out at night.
Things like who came up with the story.
That makes no sense.
That's like asking
who came up with old jokes?
Who knows who made them up?
Maybe you should see the toilet yourself.
Do I look like I have the time?
But still.
You believed the kiddy stories
and came snooping around the toilet?
Don't you have better things to do?
-You scared the crap outta me.
-I was investigating-
What now?
Some investigation you've got going.
Oh, I wonder
if that's what they're talking about.
I've seen it a couple of times too.
-There's a woman.
-A woman?
There's a weeping woman.
When was that again?
I was in the bathroom then too.
I heard a woman crying somewhere.
I looked around when I got out.
A woman was crying,
up that field in the middle of her work.
A woman crying?
Yeah.
She kept crying.
It was a weird sight.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Do you live here?
Who are you?
I want to ask you something.
I heard that--
Wait.
Here, look.
Police.
Really?
-Yeah--
-You can't be there.
-Just a second--
-Someone might see you.
No one's around.
Leave.
Please.
We absolutely guarantee confidentiality.
I'm also female
so you can be comfortable with me.
Please be as specific as you can.
That night…
…was a drizzly night.
When was this?
It was…
…last September.
All the women killed so far…
I read all about them in the paper.
The way they were killed
were exactly the same
as what I experienced.
The same.
You remember his face, right?
I kept my face down
so I wouldn't see his face.
Even with the panties over my head
I kept my eyes shut.
If I'd seen his face,
he would've killed me.
I don't know about anything else
but I do remember this.
He had really soft hands.
The hand that was covering my mouth
was pretty like that of a woman
and soft.
All set?
Let's get some sleep now.
RECORD OF TESTIMONY
It'll be over when we stamp right here.
Just as you testified.
You like that, right?
Yes, of course.
So it's over now.
Please let me down.
Let me down.
Let him down. He's not the perp.
What?
Hey, Jo Byeong-sun.
Are you the perp?
Sure, yes.
Get outta here. You're not it.
-I think I'm the perp--
-Let him down!
What's going on?
Don't leave out a word
from her statement--
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Having fun, are you?
-You like ruining everything last minute?
-Hey.
-I was so fucking close.
-You jackass!
You weren't close to anything.
-You bastard--
-Where do you think this is?
I never liked you, fucker.
-You hung Jo Byeong-sun, right?
-He kept lying.
You gotta get your act straight!
Sergeant--
These bastards--
This.
["A Gloomy Letter" plays]
♪There's no need to speak♪
What's this?
♪Let's trust♪
Is that live radio?
This is on right now?
Yes, it's live broadcast.
♪Each other♪
First, issue a state of emergency.
And send us
two squadrons of combat police.
I know what I'm doing!
Tonight!
It's gonna happen tonight!
Hello? I need Producer-Director Lim.
It's urgent--
What? He quit?
Lemme talk to the Assistant Director.
"A Gloomy Letter" by Yu Jae-ha
you played just now.
I need name and address of the sender.
You must have the postcard!
What, a joke?I
This is the police station!
Hello?
-I'll go there myself.
-Okay.
Sergeant, do we have the back-up force?
They don't have any forces remaining.
All the combat police are out
putting down a riot in Suwon.
Name, An Mi-seon. 28.
Estimated time of death is last night,
between 7:30 and 8:00 p.m.
So he did all this
while you two were busy fighting?
Hold on a second.
I think there's something in her vagina.
This is a piece of a peach.
Total of nine.
So…
do you see things like this often
in Seoul?
Never.
You were right.
About what?
I was wasting my time on the wrong guys.
Hey.
You got a call from the radio station.
I think they found the postcard guy.
I have the postcard and the address.
Can you write it down?
Taeryeong-eup, Jinan-1-ri
No. 32, Park Hyun-kyu.
Who are you?
The police.
Where's Park Hyun-kyu? He lives here.
He should be at the plant.
Hey, Hyun-kyu. Park Hyun-kyu.
Park Hyun-kyu!
Lemme see your hand.
You've got soft hands.
How long have you worked there?
Since last September?
A little before the first case last year.
So ever since you left the army
and came to the plant in this town
we are getting a series of these cases.
Isn't that right?
Park Hyun-kyu.
You sent in this request, right?
Yes.
You've sent it many times before.
You asked it to be played on a rainy day.
Yes.
"A Gloomy Letter".
You know a woman was killed
every time this song came on.
No.
Look at the play record. You see it?
Okay, fine.
They played your song yesterday.
"A Gloomy Letter" by Yu Jae-ha.
Yes.
You listened
to the evening hit music station.
-Yes.
-Your song was played at 7:08 p.m.
The program ended at 8:00 p.m.
-Hear the end?
-Yes.
-Did you listen to it in your room?
What was the last song they played?
-I don't know.
-You should. It was yesterday!
-I don't remember.
-'Cause you weren't home!
I too was home!
An Mi-seon's estimated time of death
is between 7:30 and 8:00 p.m.
You ran out while listening to the radio.
You've gotta be joking.
-Jo Yong-gu!
-Does this look like a joke, fucker?
-Put him down.
-Stop it.
Get behind me.
You here.
Even the kids know
you're torturing innocent men here.
Shut the fuck up, you--
Get over here!
I'm not gonna fall for it.
Not a chance.
Okay, Park Hyun-kyu.
So you listened to that program
to the end, at home.
Then there's no way
you can't remember the last song.
Because as the DJ introduced the last song
he said something noteworthy.
He even talked about you
who sends in a lot of postcards.
If you were listening,
there's no way you don't remember.
So tell me, since you heard it all.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Shall I tell it instead then?
This is a recording from last night.
["A Gloomy Letter" plays]
You were listening to this
on a rainy evening yesterday.
It was pouring outside
and you heard the song come on the radio.
You start to get the itch.
Because there's a thing you do
every time you hear this song.
From the landlady's room,
you can hear the soap opera on TV.
You leave the light on in the room
and slip out quietly.
Then you walk around in the dark.
You think, 'Who's it gonna be today?'
Right?
Then you hide in the reed field
and wait for a woman to pass by.
You are soaked in the rain.
But to you, this is all fun.
It's fun and exciting.
So yesterday, you put this
inside the woman's body.
Do you remember how many pieces?
One, two.
-Three, four.
-Stop.
Five, six!
-Seven, eight!
-Shut the fuck up!
-You asshole!
-Jo Yong-gu!
You son of a bitch!
Didn't I tell you not to hit them?
I told you not to him them!
I warned you from the beginning.
I warned you about the reporters!
You moron.
You're no longer allowed
in the interrogation room from now.
This is driving me crazy.
No eyewitness.
No evidence.
I can't do shit without anything.
I don't need a fucking eyewitness.
I just need him to talk.
We can beat the crap out of him.
You've changed.
Go ahead and try.
You'll just look stupid.
Like that time with Gwang-ho.
Baek Gwang-ho.
I meant to ask you this for a while.
When we took Baek Gwang-ho to the woods.
He said specifics about Lee Hyang-suk
in the middle of shoveling.
What about it?
You sure that wasn't rehearsed?
I told you, no.
Then how does he know
the order in which she was strangled--
My question, exactly.
Where's the tape
with the recording from the woods?
Miss Gwon. Gwi-oak.
Then her body shivered and it looked like
she was completely dead.
Here, listen to the way he talks.
Pulled it over Hyang-suk's head.
Pulled what over?
Her panties.
Her panties were pulled over her head,
like a hat.
He's not talking about what he did…
-And then?
-Yeah?
…which means…
Put back on her clothes.
…he's talking about what he saw.
Why was that?
Right?
I wouldn't know.
Baek Gwang-ho is the eyewitness.
This way, sir.
-Thanks for your work here. What the--
-What's up with them?
PORK BELLY
Where's Gwang-ho?
Why? Did something happen to--
-Actually, we are--
-Nothing, we came to drink.
Give us some meat here.
What are you doing here?
Don't drink too much!
He's not in the room.
-I'll take a look around town.
-Check the arcade.
How long have you been here?
Have you seen Baek Gwang-ho?
He was one of the corrupted judges…
Them again.
--…for quasi-indecent act by force.
-I wonder how he'll be prosecuted.
Here's reporter Hwang Chan-gyu.
That bastard.
-At today's trial…
-You call those cops?
the court decided,
before the inquisition, that--
You gotta chop the dicks off
those damn detectives.
What good is that?
-The first hearing of the accused…
-They're born ignorant.
-…began today in the Incheon court.
-Be quiet. I can't hear it!
During the trial, the Prosecutor's Office
added act-by-force to the charges.
I'm Han Gang-wook.
During the trial,
District Judge Lee of Incheon
instructed a special--
-Hey!
-Nicely done!
Fuck you!
-What's wrong with you?
-If you don't like it, then don't--
-Fuck you!
-Bastard!
You bastard!
Let go!
You did it with the professor, didn't you?
Fuck you, bitch!
Let go!
Fucker! You!
Call the cops!
Let go, asshole!
Baek Gwang-ho!
Bastard!
What are we gonna do?
Let go!
You idiot!
Isn't that wood?
-Gwang-ho.
-Fuck!
-Gwang-ho!
-You can't leave!
-No, that's not it!
-Hey, Baek Gwang-ho!
Baek Gwang-ho! Stop right there!
Gwang-ho!
-I'm sorry!
-What's the matter with you?
-Hey!
-We're not here to get you. Come down.
Hey, you!
Are you gonna kill me?
Let's say the thing just now
never happened.
It could happen in any fight, right?
Everything's fine, so get down here.
You're gonna kill me, right? I know it.
We're not killing anyone. Come down--
Okay, you can stay there and talk.
Let me ask you something.
Do you remember Hyang-suk?
Hyang-suk who died.
Hyang-suk is pretty.
That's right.
The one you used to follow around.
That night, when it was pouring outside
you saw her die, right?
I already told you everything.
In the woods.
I told you when we went shoveling.
Right. You saw her get killed, here.
Yes, right here.
Here, over the railroad.
Did you see the face of the guy
who killed Hyang-suk?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Lightning. Boom!
I was sleeping in places like this
and saw it all.
So you saw his face?
Saw it three times.
Do you remember his face accurately?
He's good looking.
He's better looking than me.
Is this the face you saw?
Look closely.
Do you know how hot fire is?
Take a proper look at the photo!
-Fire is really hot!
-Come on!
Get to your senses!
Here.
Look carefully.
It's hot! Hot!
Look at the photo!
-When I was young…
-Baek Gwang-ho.
…that person threw me into the furnace.
-Gwang-ho!
-You asshole!
What's going on?
Fuck!
-Please let him go.
-Mr. Baek!
This bastard!
Why are you doing this, Detective Park?
-Fuck!
-I'm a cop!
-Let go!
-Fuck!
-Hey!
Baek Gwang-ho, hold on!
-Let go!
-You idiot!
-Where do you think you're going?
Hey, Gwang-ho!
Went all over looking for you.
Hey.
The train's coming. Get down here!
Come on!
Hey! Move over right now.
-Hey, you!
-It's dangerous there.
-Go!
-Let's go! You're gonna die!
-Don't come. Go!
-You'll get hurt!
-Hey!
-Go!
You sure it's okay to be here?
They're probably looking for you.
Yes.
When writing articles, reporters can be…
SUSPECT BAEK'S MENTAL ILLNESS
WORSENED AFTER INTERROGATION
As I told you the other day…
SUSPECT PARK RELEASED AFTER THREE DAYS
Hello?
Bastards.
Fucking bastards.
Sergeant!
What!
It's the National Forensic Service.
They found a semen sample.
What did you say?
Look carefully.
We found this drop of semen
on the victim's clothing.
My guess is that it splattered
while the perpetrator was masturbating.
-As of now--
-Hold on.
We got that.
If we can confirm
that the DNA print from the semen
and the DNA print from Park Hyun-kyu
actually match
then it's game over.
Yes, this is as sure an evidence
as we can get.
The trouble is that in Korea,
we don't have the tools to analyze this.
We need to send the semen to the US.
That's the only way for now.
The US…
As soon as the analysis is finished,
you'll get immediate results.
So we just wait
for the result to get back from the US?
Correct.
You got eyes on Park Hyun-kyu, right?
Yes, around the clock, in shifts.
Just you wait
for that result from the US!
I'm gonna knock him out
with a single blow!
-Hey.
-Yeah?
What's with your leg?
-Huh?
-What about my leg?
Did you see a doctor?
-I don't need to see a doctor for this.
-Lemme see.
I rubbed on Antiphlamine already.
-What is this?
-Remember, last time…
It keeps swelling.
Let's get going.
Let's go.
PARK JONG-JU, MD
Chop off his leg?
You want me to explain it again?
It was just a nail.
Why chop off a perfectly good leg?
He could die.
Tetanus is serious stuff.
You get stabbed by a rusty nail,
you come straight to a doctor.
You stupid morons.
It's too late to change anything.
It's not the worst of things.
We're cutting below the knee.
Let's go.
Family, right?
He's got no family.
I'm a brother of sort but--
But you are his guardian, right?
This is the agreement for the operation.
Read through and sign.
NECROSIS OF FOOT BY TETANUS
I agree not to raise any objections
regarding the treatment.
PATIENT FAMILY NAME
Son of a bitch.
Is this the post office?
This is Seo from the Investigation Unit.
Did the papers arrive yet from the US?
Did you check thoroughly?
I keep calling because it's important.
Anyway, it really is important
so let me know as soon as it arrives.
Okay.
Hello?
Right now?
Why would you call me out here?
What, am I not allowed to call you out?
Your face is a mess.
Have you been sleeping?
What detective sleeps regularly?
-Why the attitude?
-Lucky bastards, just fishing away.
Why'd you call me out? I'm busy.
This is no way to live.
I'm not the one to talk
but can't you do something else?
Can't you quit detective?
HANGOVER SOUP
Why?
Let's go.
GWANGJIN TRANSPORTATION
Calling Homicide.
Homicide!
Where are you going so late?
Cash is good, isn't it?
PHARMACY
Bo-gyeong's grandma collapsed again.
I gotta go.
Why, you deserve an award.
The Health Department should give you one!
Sergeant.
He hasn't returned home in two hours.
It's six stops from there to his place
so he definitely got off in the middle.
He's been arrested once. He wouldn't dare.
He would be more than happy
to mess with us!
He was crazy to begin with.
You look crazy right now.
As soon as we have the DNA analysis
that is the end of this.
That's right.
How could I miss him?
Stop it! You're making me anxious!
That son of a bitch.
REAL ESTATE
LAND
This is the civil defense drill alert.
A defense drill alert has been issued.
As of current,
a nation-wide drill alert has been issued.
…please prepare for safety…
OPTICIAN, SAEMAEUL BANK
…comply with the orders…
This is a drill.
What's your stance
on the investigation this time?
Stab wounds
caused by a cutter in the chest.
Goodness, what is this?
There's a lot of objects
stuck in the genital area.
What is this?
It looks like a Monami ball-point pen
and a spoon.
What the hell is this?
-Check the inside thoroughly.
-Okay.
What's that over there?
It looks like an old band-aid.
-What?
-What are you doing?
Why are you touching the body?
What are you doing?
Get up, you bastard!
Fuck.
You fucking bastard!
Get up, you bastard!
-Come on!
-Let go!
You call yourself a human?
Monster. Animal.
Son of a bitch!
Bastard!
Shit!
Say it. I can kill you right here
and no one would give a damn.
Say it.
Say you killed her.
Come on and say it alll!
Fine.
I did it.
I killed them all.
Is that what you wanna hear?
Is it?
Satisfied? Well?
Hey!
Detective Seo! It's here!
We have the paper from the US!
Hurry and read it.
You bastard.
Son of a bitch.
Fucker.
Your days of mocking us is over.
-Hey!
-Fuck.
Bastard mocked us.
What's the matter?
Since the DNA fingerprint
of the suspect Park Hyun Kyu
does not correspond exactly
to that semen sample in the victim's body
it cannot be said conclusively
that the suspect is the murderer.
Something's not right.
This is all a lie.
I don't need this.
Detective Seo, what does it say?
You're really not it?
Look at me straight in the eyes.
I said, straight in the eyes.
Damn it. I can't tell.
Do you even eat?
Go.
Go, you son of a bitch.
It's time to stop.
Chi-hyeok.
Played computer games all night?
Well?
Yes or no?
Look at me straight.
Bloodshot eyes.
Are you good at these games?
Yeah.
As you should be.
Not like you are good at studying.
If you don't wanna study,
you should go out and work out.
What's a guy doing
sitting at a computer all day long?
I didn't play.
Sure, you didn't.
You can't fool me.
He says he didn't. Have some faith.
Mr. Oh called himself the other day.
Always telling me, "that's no way to act."
How am I to act?
You can't just take his word for it.
It's all part of a strategy.
Don't worry.
I'm on my way with the goods.
GREEN POWER JUICE EXTRACTOR
Yeah.
Sure.
Let's grab a meal with Mr. Oh.
It's been a while.
Sure thing.
-Cheol-yong.
-Yeah.
Pull over for a second.
Is there something inside?
Huh?
Is there something in there?
Nah.
Then why're you looking?
Just 'cause.
That's so weird.
What is?
There was another man
looking in there the other day.
I asked him then too.
Why he's looking in.
And?
What was it again?
Oh, right.
He said he was reminiscing
what he did here a while ago.
It's been a really long time.
That's what he said.
Did you see his face?
What does he look like?
It's just
a common face.
How so?
It's just
ordinary.
Subtitle translation by: Charmy Park