Stop there!
Hey, you!
It's getting narrow!
Single file!
Miss, did a strange man
just run past here?
No.
- It's that policeman.
- What?
- At the guard post.
- You know him?
Damn, he's a
fast little bastard.
He's not there?
Did you check the
alleys properly?
You think you
know this village?
You stepped on a
stick back there.
A stick or a shit pile, who cares?
He stepped on it.
What?
Over there... Hey, you!
Stop!
Jesus, not again.
Hey, over there.
Black clothes, black clothes...
Everyone's in black except you.
Everybody stop!
Don't move an inch!
- Inspector Jo!
- Yes?
Gather them together.
Hey, stop.
Gather together.
Lift up your heads.
Everyone stand in line.
Look in my eyes.
Give me that.
What is it?
You bastard!
- Give me your hands!
- What are you doing?
You ran away from us?
But...
Is jerking off a crime?
It's not a crime.
Why'd you run away?
Someone jumped out
of the woods and ran at me,
so I panicked.
Sure, but why'd you go
all the way out there to do it?
There are kids at home,
and the air's nice in the woods.
Or did you go back to
fantasize about the dead girls?
Your husband likes
to go out at night, huh?
What's this?
Gimme that.
What did you make these with?
These days, you know,
real events in our town are
stronger than the magazines.
When I read the newspaper,
I start fantasizing.
I ask myself why I do this,
but when will this
chance come again?
According to neighbors,
he looks diligently
after his sick wife,
never misses a week at church,
that he's honest.
All perverts are like that.
Nice on the outside.
But my eyes can't be fooled.
One look, and I know.
Honey,
I put socks in here.
Change them after dinner.
Don't forget, or they'll smell.
I'll take care of it.
Go feed the kids.
Watch out for protesters.
Release Jo Byung-soon!
What now?
I heard Byung-soon
confessed last night.
Who says so?
Oh, Chief!
When will you make
an announcement?
We know nothing.
Just wait a bit more.
You've held him 4 days
without a warrant.
People are saying he's
detained illegally.
This time be realistic,
like in a movie.
Go!
You did a good job just now.
Yong-ku?
So, you were hiding
behind the outhouse,
and you saw
Park Myung-ja
coming towards you
with a flashlight, right?
Yes, yes, yes. It seems so.
Not it seems,
you bastard, be precise!
I think I dreamed it that way.
Anyway, I snuck up behind her,
and I must have chopped
the back of her neck?
With my hand like this.
Next?
Myung-ja cried out, and I
guess she collapsed?
So I laid her on the ground,
and was about to take her,
Hey, it didn't
happen there, it was...
The pine grove!
I took her there.
It was from the rice paddies
to the pine grove.
According to the news, more
than 200 meters, right?
That's so far!
So the rain was pouring, and I
dragged her through the mud.
And then?
So I threw her down
in the pine grove.
Then I strangled her.
- With what?
- The bag strap.
Really?
Her stocking!
Right.
Brassiere. A Venus brassiere.
I wrapped it around
her throat like this,
So the woman,
she took a rock and
clocked me in the head.
Where'd she hit you?
Right here, next to my eye.
It still hurts, even if
it was just a dream.
Byung-soon, are you gonna
keep saying it was a dream?
That's enough.
Turn your head.
So this bruise is from the rock?
- No, this guy here...
- Shut up! Look here.
You've done well,
now let's finish this.
So...
Since she hit me
like this with the rock,
I must have lost consciousness?
And after lying there a while,
I woke up, and looking around...
And?
I was in the bottom
of an outhouse! A shithouse!
And maggots were
creeping all over the place!
Not the outhouse again.
So after brushing them off,
I grabbed some straw,
and pulled myself up.
Even in a dream, it's hard.
But then I saw,
this wasn't someone's home,
it was a school toilet.
Walking to the playground,
I saw huge swarms of girls,
so many, and the smell...
Wait! Over here.
Where did you hear about
that school outhouse?
Everyone knows that story.
I saw it in a dream.
From below the gas attack,
run in a direction...
...perpendicular to the wind.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
Put it down. Hey!
Pretend you're dead!
Last time, who told you that
story about the outhouse?
You came because of that?
What's wrong?
I hurt myself in the chute.
There was a pebble in there.
Where's the nurse?
I'll put it on for you.
I'II do it.
Shy? You're just a kid.
Sit down.
Give it to me.
Lift up your shirt.
Think about what I asked you.
The murderer in the outhouse,
coming out at night...
Who might have
told that story first...
How would I know?
It's like asking who
made up the elephant jokes.
Why don't you go to
the outhouse yourself?
Do I look like
I have time for that?
Even still...
Some kids talk, so you
snoop around the outhouse?
You got that much time?
Giving me a heart attack.
Investigating...
Is investigating such a dirty job?
Ah! Is that why they
made up the rumor?
I saw her myself
once or twice.
That woman.
Who?
A crying woman.
When was it?
I was in the outhouse then too,
when I heard a woman crying.
When I came out,
there was a woman
working on that hill,
who kept crying.
A woman was crying?
Yes.
She kept crying on that hill.
It just seemed strange.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Are you the person
who lives here?
Who are you?
I'd like to ask something.
I heard that...
Wait!
Look here.
- I'm a policeman.
- Really?
You can't stay there.
Someone might see.
There's no one here.
Go, please.
I beg you.
Be assured this will
remain a secret.
As we're both women,
tell me everything
comfortably and in detail.
That night,
a light rain was falling.
When was it?
It was...
last September.
I had read all the articles...
...about the women killed.
The methods he used
were exactly the same.
It was the same with me.
You saw his face?
I tried not to on purpose,
keeping my chin down.
My panties covered my head,
but I closed my eyes tight.
If I saw him,
he'd have killed me.
I don't know about the rest,
but one thing I remember.
His hands were very soft.
The hand over my mouth,
was delicate,
just like a woman's.
We're done. Let's get
ourselves some sleep.
Once we get
your seal, it's done.
It's all as you said.
Sound good?
Yes, of course.
Oh, it's finally over, right?
Please let me down. Please.
Let him go.
He's not the murderer.
What?
Byung-soon, are
you the murderer?
Yes, sir, yes...
Shut up.
No you're not.
I think I am...
Let him go!
Write down everything she said...
Hey!
You toying with me?
Are you having fun?
I caught the murderer, OK?
What do you mean,
you caught him?
Did you hang him
from the ceiling?
Well, he kept lying, and...
Get hold of yourself.
Those journalists...
- Chief!
- Those goddamned bastards!
Stop!
Listen.
What is that?
- Is it live?
- It's being broadcast now?
Yes, it's live.
First, declare a
state of emergency.
And send me two
garrisons of men.
Because our
intelligence says so!
Tonight. There'll
be a murder tonight.
Hello, I need to
speak to producer Im...
What? He quit?
Get me the A.D. Now.
The song that was just
played, "Sad Letter".
Read the name and
address of the requester.
You must have the postcard.
What? Prank call?
It's the police, bastard!
Hello?
I'll go myself.
Are the garrisons coming?
They don't even have
one man available.
They went to suppress
a demonstration in Suwon city.
Name: Ahn Mi-seon, age 28.
Estimated time of death, last
night between 7:30 and 8:00.
When the two of you were
fighting like madmen. Right?
Wait a minute.
There's something
in the vagina.
Looks like a peach.
Nine pieces.
Do you see this kind of
thing in Seoul often?
Never.
You were right.
What?
These guys were a waste
of time from the start.
Hey!
A call from the radio station.
I think she found the postcard.
I've got the postcard.
It has an address.
Can you write it down?
Jinan 1-ri, Terung District
#32. Park Hyun-gyu.
Who are you?
We're policemen.
Where has Park Hyun-gyu gone?
He works at the
factory at this time.
Hey, Hyun-gyu.
Park Hyun-gyu!
Show me your hands.
They're quite smooth.
How long have you
worked in the factory office?
From September last year.
A little before the first murder.
So after doing your military
service, you came to this town,
and the murders all
began taking place.
Right?
Park Hyun-gyu.
You sent this postcard
to the station.
Yes.
You sent several others too.
You asked it to be
played on rainy days.
Yes.
"Sad Letter" You know that
each time this song played,
a woman was murdered?
No.
Look at the broadcast records.
Okay.
The song played yesterday?
"Sad Letter".
Yes.
You listened to the program?
Your song played at 7:08, and
the program finished at 8pm.
- You listened to the end?
- Yes.
- Continuously?
- What was the final song?
- I don't know.
- It was yesterday!
- I don't remember.
Because you went out!
I was home!
She was killed
between 7:30 and 8pm.
You weren't listening,
you went out!
Don't make me laugh.
You motherfucker.
Are you joking?
- Let go of him now!
- Hey!
Get back here!
Even kids in this town know
you torture innocent people.
Shut up, you!
Get back here!
Anyway, I won't be one of them.
Never.
Okay. Park Hyun-gyu.
You say you listened
at home to the end?
But you couldn't have
forgotten the last song.
Because the DJ introduced it
with some very striking words.
She mentioned you, and
the many postcards you sent.
If you heard it,
you couldn't have forgotten.
Tell me! If you really
listened to the end.
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Should I explain it for you?
This is the recording of
yesterday's program.
Last night, you sat
listening to this song.
Outside the rain was
pelting down, you listened,
and soon you started
itching with excitement.
There's something you always
do when you hear this song.
You heard a TV program playing
in the room of your landlady,
you left the lights on in your
own room and crept outside.
And in the pitch dark,
you wandered here and there.
Who will it be today?
Right?
You hid in a reed field,
waiting for a woman to pass.
The rain drenching you.
But you find all this pleasurable.
Stimulating, right?
So yesterday you stuffed
this in that woman's body!
You remember how
many pieces it was?
One piece,
two...
- Three pieces...
- Shut up!
Four, five...
six, seven, eight...
Shut the fuck up!
Yong-gu!
I told you not to hit him.
Didn't I?
I warned you.
You know why
journalists snoop around here.
You stupid bastard.
Don't even think about coming
into the interrogation room again.
I'm going crazy.
No eyewitnesses,
not one piece of evidence.
We need something, shit.
Shit, we don't need
any damn witnesses.
Just a confession will do.
Just need to beat that
bastard to an inch of his life.
You've changed.
Try it and, you'll be disgraced.
Like with Kwang-ho.
Retarded Kwang-ho...
I always wanted to ask you.
When you dragged
him up the mountain,
he talked about Hyang-sook's
death in so much detail.
So?
Did you really not rehearse
that dialogue with him?
I told you I didn't!
But how did he know the
way she was strangled...
That's my point!
The tape... Where's the tape
from the mountain?
Miss Kwon? Gui-ok.
Then, Hyang-sook's body shook a bit.
She looked completely dead.
Listen to how he speaks here.
Covered up Hyang-sook's head.
With what?
Her panties.
Her head was covered
with her panties.
He's talking like
it was someone else.
And then?
He's describing what he saw.
Kwang-ho is the witness.
Where did Kwang-ho go?
Kwang-ho...
No, no. We came for a drink.
Some meat, please.
What are you doing here?
Control yourself, huh?
He's not in his room.
I'll check outside.
Try the game arcade.
How long have you been here?
Have you seen Kwang-ho?
It is now 23 months since
the incident first surfaced.
Before interrogating
Detective Moon...
They should cut off
all detective's dicks!
Nah, it's not worth it.
They are stupid bastards.
Be quiet.
The trial of detective Moon,
suspected of police torture
and sexual assault,
opened today.
You fucked your professor,
didn't you, bitch!
Your parents pay good money...
Hey, Yong-gu!
Kwang-ho!
Don't run away!
Hey, Kwang-ho!
Kwang-ho!
I'm sorry...
What's wrong with you?
We're not here to catch you.
Come down.
You're gonna kill me?
We'll forget that any of
that happened.
If a fight breaks out,
that can happen.
It's okay,
just come down, huh?
If I do, you'll kill me?
I know it.
We won't kill you,
just come down.
Okay, just stay there for now.
We've something to ask you.
You...
You remember Hyang-sook?
The girl that died.
Hyang-sook is pretty.
That's right. You used
to follow after her.
But that night,
when it rained,
you saw her killed, huh?
That? I told you already.
In the forest.
I told you already...
You saw when Hyang-sook was
murdered, didn't you? Here?
Yeah, here.
The paddy next to
the train tracks.
That night,
did you see the killer's face?
- Yeah.
- Really?
Lightning, ka-rang!
I saw everything
from inside here.
So you saw his face?
Three times.
Do you remember him in detail?
He was handsome.
More than me.
Was this the face you saw?
Look at the picture.
You know how hot
that fire was?
Look at the photo!
It was so hot!
Snap out of it!
Here, look closely.
Hot hot hot hot!
Look at the photo!
Hey. Kwang-ho.
When I was young,
he threw me in the fire.
That man.
- Kwang-ho!
- You bastards!
What the hell!
Please forgive him.
What are you students doing?
We're police!
Bullshit!
Then we're the F.B.I.!
Hey, Kwang-ho!
We're looking for you.
Hey!
A train's coming!
Come here!
Out of the way, quick!
It's dangerous there.
Out of the way! You idiot!
Stay away. Go...
It's okay for you to be here?
They'll be looking for you.
Yes, yes.
Journalists tend
to be like that.
Sir, as I said last time...
Hello?
Assholes!
High-ranking bastards...
- Chief!
- What?
It's Investigative Crimes.
They found semen.
They found what?
Take a look.
The semen was found
on the victim's clothing.
Maybe he masturbated
on the corpse,
and semen fell on her clothes.
Wait.
So...
...if the DNA in this semen
is confirmed to match
that of Park Hyun-gyu,
then the game's over, isn't it?
Yes, that would be quite
strong evidence.
The problem is, we don't have
the technology in Korea
to carry out such tests.
It must be sent to America.
There's no other way.
Once the test's complete,
the results will be released.
So we just have to wait for
the documents from America?
That's right.
You sent people to
watch over Park Hyun-gyu?
Yes! They're watching
him 24 hours a day.
Once the result
comes in from America,
wait until we get our
hands on that bastard.
What's wrong with your leg?
Why?
Did you go to the hospital?
For this little scratch?
Come here.
It's okay.
I put on some medicine.
- What is that?
- Oh, that night...
It keeps swelling.
Come on, let's go.
Just get in.
So, you have to amputate?
Should I explain it again?
It was pierced, but why
cut off a healthy leg?
If you don't, he'll die.
Tetanous is a brutal thing.
For rusty nails, you need
to see a doctor fast.
Bunch of dim-witted boneheads.
Be grateful it's under the knee.
Crazy bastards.
Let's go.
Are you family?
He doesn't have any,
but I'm like his brother...
Anyway, you came together, right?
The authorization for surgery.
Read it, then sign.
You fucker...
Hello, post office?
It's Suh Tae-yoon,
Investigative Crimes.
Have the documents
from America arrived?
Have you checked 100%?
I keep calling because
it's important!
Since it's so important, please
call as soon as it comes.
Hello?
Uh, now?
Why'd you call me out?
Why?
Can't I do that sometimes?
Your face looks worn,
Are you sleeping well?
What kind of
detective sleeps well?
What's wrong with you?
Fishing? Damn free-riders.
Why'd you call out a busy man?
You look like a corpse.
It may be no use asking,
but can you do anything else?
Can you quit your job?
Violent Crimes Dept!
Violent Crimes!
How many visits in one night?
Is money that important?
Bo-kyung's grandmother
collapsed again. I have to go.
You deserve a medal.
Get one from
the Health Ministry.
Chief!
Park Hyun-gyu hasn't
come home for 2 hours.
It's only six stops from
there to his house.
So he must have gotten off.
Would a man under
investigation act so wild?
He's capable of it.
- He's instinctively crazy.
- You seem like the crazy one!
Once the DNA tests arrive,
he's through. Stop it.
I let him go...
Don't get so upset!
Citizens,
this is a civil defense drill.
A blackout is called for
in all buildings and houses...
Will you make any special
investigation into this incident?
A razor wound in the breast...
What the hell?
Something is stuck
inside of the vagina.
Huh?
Looks like a ball point pen,
and a spoon.
Jesus...
Look inside, closely.
Wait, what's that?
An old band-aid.
What are you doing?
Why are you touching a corpse?
What?
Get up, you bastard!
You fucker!
Get up, you fucker.
Are you human?
Nobody will care if I kill you.
Tell me!
Tell me you killed them!
You killed all those women!
Yeah.
I killed them.
I killed them all.
That's what you want
to hear, right?
Right?
You feel better?
Inspector Suh!
The papers from America!
Read them!
You asshole.
You fucker!
You mocked us, didn't you!
You bastard!
You mocked us!
What's wrong?
There's a mistake.
This document is a lie.
I don't need it.
What does it say, huh?
It really wasn't you?
Look in my eyes.
Look in my eyes!
Fuck, I don't know.
Do you get up each morning too?
Go!
Just go, fucker!
Bastard.
That's enough.
Chi-hyuk.
You played computer
games all night, right?
Did you or didn't you?
Look in my eyes, son.
Eyes all bloodshot.
Do you play well?
Yeah!
You don't study, might as
well be good at games.
If you won't study,
go get some exercise.
Sitting in front
of the computer...
I really didn't!
What do you mean you didn't?
Think you can fool my eyes?
He said he didn't.
Believe him.
No, two days ago Manager Oh
called my company.
He kept saying you can't do
this to people, it's not fair.
You can't believe him.
Did I do anything wrong?
I'm on the road now
with our product.
Sure, let's have dinner
with Manager Oh.
It's been a while.
Chul-yong!
Pull over a minute!
Is something in there?
Is anything in there?
No...
Then why are you looking?
I'm just looking.
That's so weird.
What is?
A while back,
a man was here
looking into that hole.
I asked him the same question.
Why he was looking there.
What did he say?
What was it?
Right...
He remembered doing
something here long ago,
so he came back
to take a look.
Did you see his face?
What did he look like?
Well...
Kind of plain.
In what way?
Just...
ordinary.
Starring SONG Kang-Ho as Inspector Park
KIM Sang-Kyung as Inspector Suh
Directed by BONG Joon-Ho
Screenplay by BONG Joon-Ho and SHIM Sung-Bo
Based on a story by KIM Kwang-II
Cinematography by KIM Hyung-Gu
Music by IWASHIRO Taroh
Subtitles by Mohammed Anes and Yeon Hyeon-sook
Sponsored by KOFIC - Korean Film Commission -
Processed by L.V.T. Paris