(woman's voice): I have
this reoccurring dream.
I'm a little girl
sitting with my mom
and she's singing to me.
I feel the warmth of
the sun on my skin...
and the comfort of
her arms around me.
And I wanna stay there.
Forever.
When I wake up, I
miss the dream.
I want so badly for
this dream to be real,
but that would be impossible,
because my mom died
when I was really little.
And I can't go out in the sun.
Like, at all.
I have a rare genetic condition
called Xeroderma Pigmentosum,
or XP,
which basically means a severe
sensitivity to sunlight.
If the sun hits my skin,
I get skin cancer, my
brain starts to fail
and I could die.
Pretty fun, right?
So, I spend all my time indoors
behind special windows,
hanging out with my dad
who is the best dad ever.
Thank goodness,
because growing up,
kids were, uh...
what you'd expect.
- No way.
- Yep, a vampire.
That's why they have
special windows.
Don't worry.
She can't get us during the day.
But at night, stay
far, far away.
- But not everyone
was afraid of me.
- Hey, Morgan.
- What's wrong with her?
- She has something called XP.
Basically, the
light from the sun,
it hurts her.
So she can't ever go in the sun.
- I can't be in the sun
for too long either.
Can she play at night?
- Yeah, but--
- See you tonight!
Oh! And I like pizza!
- From that point on,
it was me, Morgan and my dad.
Until one day...
I saw Charlie
and that was it.
I was completely,
totally, utterly hooked.
Stupid tree.
I saw him every day.
And yet...
he had no idea
I even existed.
(soft music)
Over time, watching Charlie
go by just became a part
of my routine.
Along with constant
doctor appointments...
sleeping during the day
and staying up all night,
which, from what I've heard,
is the schedule of
most teenagers...
and playing music
every chance I get.
All things considered,
I've got a pretty great life.
But I still hold
onto my dreams.
Stupid tree.
No matter how impossible
they may seem.
(pop song)
♪ They're not gonna break us ♪
♪ Hey we'll burn so bright ♪
♪ Making all the
people come to life ♪
♪ Hey the darkest sky ♪
♪ Can't stop me
and you tonight ♪
♪ I said, Hey, we'll
burn so bright ♪
♪ Dancing underneath
the city lights ♪
♪ Hey from way up high ♪
♪ Shining down like
stars tonight ♪
- Jeremy Pierce.
(cheering)
Kendall Porter.
- Congratulations.
- Peter Rathbard.
Charles Reed.
- Yeah, Charlie!
(cheering)
- Congratulations, Charlie.
- Katie Price!
- What are you wearing?
- Oh, cap and gown. Huh?
The faculty and staff
always wear one.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
(laughing)
- Most importantly,
this is for you.
- Hmm!
- Mm-hmm!
I assume as
valedictorian, you have a
speech prepared? Yes?
- Um...
Yes. Ahem!
That's me putting on my glasses.
- I like that. Nice touch.
- Thank you.
Um... First I would like
to thank my headmaster.
- Well, I mean, really.
- My Spanish teacher.
- De nada.
- My English teacher.
- It was my pleasure.
- But I really wanna state for
the record that my gym teacher
had absolutely no idea
what he was doing.
- What? Oh, you suck!
I lift weights.
Hey, this is for you.
- This is one of the lamest
things I've ever seen.
- Yes! Ha ha! I had to go to
three stores to find
something this lame.
- I mean, it's horrific.
- Yeah! It's the worst!
All right.
Are you ready for your present?
- There's a present involved?
- Oh, there's a present, yes!
Of course there's a present.
It's graduation.
- This keeps getting
better and better.
This is Mom's.
- Look, I know it's
kind of old...
so if you want a newer one,
I totally understand.
- No! I love it. Thank you!
Thank you so much.
- You look just
like your mother.
Lucky you. She was hot.
- Ew...
- Try and get some sleep.
All right?
(honking, shouting)
(girl): I can't
believe we graduated!
- Oh!
That's a good one.
- Ah... Something weird
is going on right here.
(laughing)
- Hey, Dad... um...
I was wondering if I could go
play my new beautiful present
at the train station tonight?
- It's 10:00.
Why can't Morgan just come over?
You could play here for me.
- Morgan's busy with her family
and Dad, I love playing for you.
I really do, but I also need to
get used to playing in front of
other people too.
Please, please, please. Fred
will be there. He'll watch out
for me.
And I graduated today!
Isn't that the American
tradition, to extend my curfew?
- Okay, I'll extend your curfew
one hour. Which means
midnight, okay?
Hey. And text me right when you
get there or I'm not just gonna
call Fred.
I'm actually gonna come down
there. And it will be
so embarrassing,
it will become urban legend on
why kids should stick to their
curfew!
- I love you.
(loud music)
(cheering)
- Hey, don't do that thing.
- What thing?
- That. I mean, you look all sad
and it makes me sad.
Please just chug this beer
and come hang out!
- Dude, you dodged
a bullet, man.
You were gonna be up at the ass
crack of dawn every morning,
taking tests, nowhere
near the beach.
And now, we get to do this
our whole lives.
- I forgot, doing this our whole
lives, it's way better than a
full ride to Berkeley.
- Zoe Carmichael. 3:00.
- Charlie.
You're in trouble.
- What did I do this time?
- You didn't get me a drink.
- I did not know
you were thirsty.
- Now you do.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Is that the bad one?
Well, now that you're
not swimming...
maybe you'll have a
little extra time for me.
- I also have some extra time
for you. And I'm not swimming.
- You were never
swimming, idiot.
- Zoe! Get over here!
- Hold on!
You're coming to my
graduation party, right?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Good.
- Yeah!
- Wha... what are you doing?
- Dodging another bullet.
- Come on, dude.
It's our graduation night.
- I'm not feeling it, boys.
I'll see you later.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Hey! Yo, Fred.
- I was wondering if I was gonna
see you tonight.
- And disappoint all my fans?
(laughing)
(train whistling
in the distance)
(soft music)
♪ While you're fast asleep ♪
♪ Counting your sheep ♪
♪ I will be there ♪
♪ I'll be up all night ♪
♪ Playing through this
twilight dream ♪
♪ 'Cause all my life
I have been patiently waiting ♪
♪ For lights to dim to
fulfill my destiny ♪
♪ I'll keep reaching ♪
♪ As far as I can
till break of day ♪
♪ I'll keep reaching ♪
♪ The light of my life
will find its way ♪
♪ I know if I reach too far ♪
♪ I may not ever recover ♪
♪ But I know the stars ♪
♪ Ain't all I'm
meant to discover ♪
♪ So I'll keep reaching ♪
♪ I know if I reach too far ♪
♪ I may not ever recover ♪
♪ But I know the stars ♪
♪ Ain't all I'm
meant to discover ♪
♪ So I'll keep rea... ♪
- Hey.
- Oh...
- Whoa!
I didn't mean to freak you out.
Here.
- Me? I'm not freaked out. Don't
worry about it, I'm not a freak.
- Why are you packing up?
Where are you going?
- Home.
I gotta go home.
- Home? Wait, you live here?
You didn't go to Purdue High.
- No. It's a very
different school.
And, you know, I graduated
today and my dad's a super
big worrier.
So, I really gotta--
Oh, God.
- Um...
- I have to go.
- Wait! Wait! Whoa...
I'm sorry, why are you...
What's the rush? Wha...
- I have to get home to my cat.
- Your cat.
- Yeah, it died.
- So, you're not in
a rush then, right?
- No, no, I am.
I have to plan... the funeral
for my dead cat that... died.
Yeah, it's super dead.
- Wait! Wait! Wait!
I didn't even get your name!
(woman): You haven't noticed any
changes in her? Motor functions
still seem strong?
- Yeah. Yeah, no loss of
intellectual function.
No difficulty
swallowing or talking.
Ha! Believe me on that.
And no corneal ulcerations.
Really, there's nothing to
suggest any neurodegeneration.
- Any exposure to sunlight?
- No. Of course not.
- I'm gonna refill her
prescription for you this time.
But she really should be coming
to these appointments with you.
- Yeah, well, you know
teenagers. They get embarrassed
by their dads.
- She has XP, Jack.
- I know exactly what she has.
- It's not gonna fall into
remission.
And every year, the risk
becomes more serious for her.
So, if she's exposed to even
the slightest bit of sunlight--
- She won't be.
- She's reached that age we
talked about.
- She won't be.
Any word on the University
of Washington study?
- I submitted Katie's name
for their Phase Two trials,
if it even gets that far.
I wouldn't get your hopes
up. Research funding
being what it is...
we're talking about a disease
that affects only one in a
million people.
- We're in luck,
'cause she is one in a million.
- A cat funeral?
(sighing)
- Please stop
saying it out loud.
- No, I mean, I've heard that
dead pets can actually be
an aphrodisiac.
- Morgan! What
should I have said?
- Any other combination of words
in the English language.
- Like, hey, I'm Katie Price.
I've watched you outside my
window for the past 10 years
and I've been in love with
you, stalking you every
minute of the day?
- Don't start with that.
- Or, how about:
Hey, you may remember
me from kindergarten
when everyone called me
a vampire.
- No one remembers that!
- Oh, what did I do?
- It's bad, but we'll fix it.
- I feel so stupid and lame.
Well, at least you
have M&Ms. So...
- Thanks.
- Oh, you've just gotta make up
for it next time.
- There's not gonna be
a next time.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
- This is good.
This is what Taylor Swift does.
She has awkward
interactions with boys
and then she just writes
amazing songs about it.
What?
- Oh, no, no.
Oh, come on.
- What's happening?
- Did you see my notebook when
you came in?
- Your notebook notebook? No.
- I think I left it
at the train station.
- Oh, God!
- Can you please
go get it for me?
Morgan, it's so important.
Please!
- You know I would but there's
like a few other popping cat
funerals I was gonna hit today.
No, no! Corner! Oh!
Hey.
My friend's been
looking for that.
- You know her? Oh, wait...
Morgan, right?
We had English class together.
I'm Charlie.
- Charlie Reed, yeah. I know.
And it was a History class.
- But how do you know her?
Did she just move here
or something?
- Notebook first.
- Or you could just tell me
where she lives and I could drop
it off.
- I have a better idea.
(text alert)
- Hey, Dad, I need to go to
the train station to pick
up my notebook.
Fred has it.
- Okay, text me when you
get there and be careful.
Fred?
Holy pregnant cow!
Oh, my God. God!
Thank you.
(phone ringing)
(sighing)
Purdue Creamery.
- Morgan?
- Hey.
How's your second date?
- How could you do this to me?
My God! I'm in sweatpants.
My hair, it's a mess.
It's tied.
Argh! Oh, my God, I
look like an idiot.
- Oh, please. Katie, you're
super freaking hot. Okay?
I can't even see you right
now and I can tell you
look gorgeous.
- Hi, excuse me. Can I just get
a large--
- Can you not see I'm
on the phone?
He really likes you,
okay? I can tell.
Just try to be yourself.
Don't ramble too much.
And call me afterwards?
- Bye!
Oh, my!
Oh...
- Wow, you exist.
I thought I was dreaming
last night or something.
- Were you in the
REM stage of sleep?
- What...
- That's when most
dreams happen, actually.
Yeah! Your brain activity is
super high and functioning
and your eyes are just going
nuts behind your eyelids.
It looks super weird. It's like
a typewriter or something.
Anyway, uh, thank you for--
- Wait, I still don't
know your name.
- Oh...
It's Katie.
- Katie, I'm Charlie.
(laughing)
- Wow, that's a weird name.
Thank God you told me it
'cause I wouldn't have known
it otherwise.
Thank you.
- Wait.
- You didn't...
you didn't read
through it, did you?
- Just a little. I...
- What?
- Are you serious?
You read through my journal?
- Look, I--
- This could have been a diary.
I mean, it is, kind of.
- I'm... I'm really sorry.
You left really quick
the other night
and I really had no idea
who it belonged to,
so I just looked through it
quickly. But I like that you
still handwrite things.
It's cool. It's old school.
- Thanks.
For finding it.
- Yeah.
Wait!
What, another cat died?
You have to...
(laughing)
- I... I had to...
I'm walking home.
- Can I walk with you?
- Um, yeah.
- So you were home-schooled,
huh? Man, that must
have been wild.
- Actually, it was the
exact opposite of wild.
My dad's pretty protective.
- He's not, like, watching
us right now, is he?
- Oh, yeah. He has his phone
tapped into every camera.
(laughing)
So, um...
what did you think of
the songs you read?
Without my permission I may add.
- Uh, honestly, I don't know.
I mean, you can't really
read a song, right?
- True.
- I guess I'd have to
hear you sing 'em?
- So anyway, I'm right up here.
So, you don't have to walk me.
- You live up there? I don't
understand how we've never met.
I've probably skated by your
house like every day on the way
to practice.
(awkward laugh)
- It's a funny coincidence.
(laughing)
Thanks.
- Hey, you wouldn't wanna do
something sometime, would you?
- Together?
- Yes, us together.
Hanging out.
- Um...
I'm really busy
during the day...
but...
I could be free at night.
- I could be free at night.
- Well, you should put
your number in here then.
(chuckling)
- I'm old school, too.
- Smooth.
- That is so romantic.
It disgusts me.
What did he say about your XP?
- It didn't come up.
- What do you mean,
it didn't come up?
- I... I didn't bring it up.
I'm not gonna just
randomly be like,
Hey, dude! By the way,
the sunlight's gonna--
(blowing raspberry)
Like, look when you tell
someone you're sick,
then you start to become more
like... a disease and less like
a person.
I'm gonna tell him, I promise.
But I don't know
when I'm gonna see him again.
- I do.
You know that annoying guy
who works with me at the
ice cream shop?
- The nerdy one you hate?
- Yes, Garver.
His parents are out of town
tonight and he's throwing a
party
and he told me to bring friends.
So, I'm gonna bring you.
- No, no, no, no!
- And you're gonna
bring Charlie.
- No! He's gotta,
like, you know...
I have to wait till he
texts me first, right?
- Yeah, totally. And then, you
know, his squire will send a
note via carrier pigeon
asking if you'd like to merge
your kingdoms. What is this,
18th-century England?
You're a hot young badass woman.
You're gonna text him whenever
you damn well please.
Be confident, okay?
Give him the facts.
- Okay.
(text alert)
- Play a little hard to get.
- All right.
- Make sure that he knows
he's not the only reason
you're going.
- Okay.
Oh!
Oh, no.
- This is gonna be a tame, safe,
parent-friendly party.
- Aha! It's a totally lame
party. You know what we should
do.
We should stay here.
We'll get Hunan Chinese.
You guys love Hunan, right?
Put some Netflix on.
It'll be perfect.
- Dad. You know I'm a good kid.
You know I'm not gonna do
anything crazy.
But I swear, if I spend
one more night here,
just listening to everyone
else outside my window
living their lives,
I might go crazy.
Tomorrow night we can order
way too much chow mein
and have a great movie marathon.
- All right.
- Yes, thank you!
- You're the best dad in
the world.
- Thanks, Mr. P!
- Okay, um...
Charlie's gonna meet us
at Garver's at eight.
- We have to get ready!
- Dude, what are you talking
about? We have, like,
three hours!
- We're already behind!
Done.
Mr. P!
May I present Katherine
Price of Washington.
- Wow!
Peanut...
you look amazing.
(upbeat music)
- Bye, Mr. P!
Let's go!
God, I can't believe
Garver's throwing a kegger.
- You came.
Is there any chance that you,
or your hot friend... hey...
...know how to get
beer out of a keg?
- Oh, no.
You didn't get a tap?
- I didn't realize they were
separate things.
Why would they sell me a barrel
of beer I can't even access?
- Garver, what the hell?
This is a tame, safe,
parent-friendly party!
- Do tame parties
have sundae bars?
- I think it's so cool.
- No, don't listen to her. Okay,
she's never been to
a party before.
She doesn't understand
how dire the situation is.
We gotta go.
- What, you're leaving?
No, no, I just made a huge thing
of chili.
- Garver, chili is not
a party food.
(car approaching)
- You see, the party's
just kicking off.
What's Charlie Reed doing here?
- Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- You look really amazing.
- Um...
Oh, it's all Morgan.
- I don't think so.
- For you, good sir.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Beef chili, huh?
Um!
That's top shelf, buddy.
That's fresh.
- And I really thought
we'd have a bigger turnout.
- I told you not to go up
against a cheerleader.
- What cheerleader?
- The mean blonde one with
a convertible.
- Zoe Carmichael?
- Yes.
- Ugh!
- She's having a party tonight
as well. Must have dinged
our turnout.
- Do you guys just wanna
go there?
- Well, I like the idea.
(doorbell ringing)
- Hey.
- I was wondering
where you were.
Who are these people?
- Oh, these are my friends.
And they brought you a keg.
- Great.
Come on in.
(loud music)
(all): Charlie!
(cheering)
- You good?
- Hey, I'm gonna go
take a lap upstairs.
Away from you two?
Thank you.
- Your friend Morgan,
she seems cool.
- Yeah.
She's really cool.
- How long have you guys known
each other?
- I don't know. Like, forever.
- He's back.
(cheering)
Whoa!
Who is this?
- Owen, Wes, this
is Katie Price.
- Hi.
- Katie.
You're a...
- You got Charlie to come to
a party... and make
a smile-like feature.
Our boy hasn't looked this good
in a long time.
- There you are.
I'm still thirsty.
Wanna get me that drink now?
I'm actually about to go take
Katie on the house party tour.
So...
You ready?
(upbeat song)
We'll be right back.
- Nice meeting you guys.
- Nice to meet you, Katie.
- I can quench your thirst.
- Shut up.
(loud music)
- Would you like to dance
with me?
- Garver...
What on Earth makes you think
I'd ever want to dance with you?
(alarm, honking)
You know, if you tell anyone
about this, I'll kill you.
- Totally.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- Gotta stay hydrated.
- Thank you.
This is really interesting.
I don't think I've ever seen...
this happen.
- Yeah.
Classic high school
awkward party.
(laughing)
- I've only
seen it at the movies.
- I gotta show you this.
Come on.
- Oh, God.
- Come on.
Okay, similar to what's
going on over here.
We just kind of hold here.
And swing the hips awkwardly.
- Am I doing it?
- Yeah, you're kind of.
And then I would slowly back up.
- Everybody! This is the
best night of my life! Yeah!
(cheering)
- You wanna go someplace else?
- Okay.
I don't get it. How could they
just take your scholarship away?
- Well, I had to have surgery
and they didn't think I could
ever swim again.
And no more scholarship
meant no more Berkeley.
- I'm really sorry.
- Yeah...
- So, how did you do it?
How did you hurt yourself?
- It was just a freak accident.
You know, I fell down
some stairs and...
And that's not true.
That's kind of what
I tell everybody.
I got really drunk one
night at Owen's house.
And my friends dared me to jump
off the roof into the pool...
and I clipped the edge
with my shoulder.
I'm such an idiot.
I don't wanna be
that guy, you know?
- Then don't be.
You know my mom used to take
me here when I was little?
- Really?
- She sat me right there.
And she tried to teach me
how to play the guitar.
Actually, this watch was hers.
I spent so much time looking
at this thing on her hand and...
Um...
She died when I was little.
She was in a car accident.
- I'm so sorry.
You know, we can go someplace--
- No! No, no!
No, I'm good.
- You sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
I promise.
- You wanna see something cool?
Ta-da.
- This is yours?
- No.
But it's something I'm taking
care of for the summer.
It's a Jespersen 53.
- Wow.
- One of these days we could
take her for a sail around
the harbor.
We can watch the sun set.
- That sounds perfect.
- Just...
(car rattling)
Sorry.
- So, what are you gonna do this
year now that you're not going
to Berkeley?
- Well, first I'm
gonna get a new truck.
(laughing)
And...
then I'm gonna drive
across country.
You know, I've been in the pool
my entire life and I haven't got
to see much else, so...
What are you gonna do--
- I'm not doing anything.
I'm just gonna take some
online courses, I think.
But I'll just be...
here.
- I... I meant what are
you doing tomorrow?
- Oh!
Oh! Oh, God.
I...
I'm busy during the day,
but I can be free
tomorrow night.
- It's perfect.
I'll see you tomorrow night?
- Okay.
I have something to tell you.
I don't actually have a cat.
- No shit.
- Who are you texting?
- No one.
- Morgan, who are you texting?
I can't hear you when
you're whispering.
- Garver! I made
out with Garver.
- No! He's really, really cute.
And he totally likes you.
By the way, can I tell my dad
that I'm going over
to yours tonight,
so I can go hang out
with Charlie later?
- You're asking me to help you
lie to your father so you can
hang out with a guy?
I've never been so proud of you!
- Uh, Dad, I'm gonna go over to
Morgan's tonight. Is that okay?
- Yeah, yeah, no problem.
Hey, how was that party?
- Party was nice.
- Did you meet any fun people?
- No.
Not really.
Everybody was kind of just,
like, ugh... you know?
Nobody was really there.
It was just...
So I'm gonna...
(clicks tongue)
skedaddle.
Love you.
- Love you more.
- I'm lying.
- Well, you were rambling,
so I kind of figured.
- I'm going to go meet a boy
named Charlie Reed who's really
nice and sweet,
and I really, really
like him. A lot.
Are you mad?
- Well, I'm not happy
that you lied to me.
You know you can always
tell me anything.
- I know. I'm sorry.
- Do you trust this guy?
- Yes.
- Will I hate him?
- No, no, you won't. I promise.
- Does he know--
- I haven't told him yet.
- No, Katie, I am not
comfortable with him not
knowing.
- I know, I'm going to. I just
need a little bit longer of...
- What?
- Being someone more
than just a disease.
- Katie.
- It's just a few more days,
please? Like a normal girl.
- Hey. Is it okay if me and
Katie hang out tonight together?
The entire night?
- I already admitted everything.
- What, you couldn't make
it two hours?
- It's pathetic.
I could've made it two hours.
- What does Katie Price
wanna do?
- There's so many things I
wanna do.
(pop song)
- I have
always wanted to do this.
Ready?
(laughing)
- Whoo!
What about that one over there?
- That one's called Altair.
And it's 16 light years away,
which means the light we're
seeing now
was actually created
when we were two.
Are you okay?
- The Berkeley coach called
my house the other night.
- Really?
- Yeah, I mean, I guess one of
the other swimmers transferred
out and...
another spot opened up.
- Wow!
That's so crazy.
You could get your spot back?
- I mean, technically, yeah.
There's this huge meet
coming up next month
and the Berkeley coach
is coming down to watch.
You know, but I'd have to get in
shape by then, which is probably
impossible.
And then I'd have to swim like
my best time ever to show that
I'm fully rehabbed.
- You can totally do it.
- But there's also some reasons
to stick around here next year.
Katie, I wanna take you
on a real date tomorrow.
- Okay.
And...
you also need to meet my dad.
- Why don't you move a
little closer there, Cody?
- My name's Charlie.
- Charlie.
- Yeah.
- I didn't know that.
So, do you go by Charlie and
not Chuck or Chuckie or C-Town?
- No, sir, just Charlie.
- Charlie, okay.
You ever been arrested?
- No, sir.
- When's your curfew?
- It's 1 a.m.
- What time do you actually
get home?
- Like, two.
- That's not one o'clock, is it,
Charlie?
- No, sir, it's not.
- You said your curfew was one.
- Yeah.
- Relax, I'm not a cop.
How many times a
week do you shave?
- Shave... uh...
Like... four.
Four times a week, sir.
- Who's your team?
- Seahawks.
- Why?
- Well, because they're great.
And one time I was at
this burger place and...
Richard Sherman actually ate
some of my fries.
- That's awesome.
Okay.
Charlie...
here's the deal.
Katie appears to be very strong.
And she is.
- Hey!
- She's dealing with- Hi!
What you guys talking about?
- Nothing.
- We were...
- We're just getting
to know each other.
- Thank you so much for letting
me take her out, Mr. Price.
- Okay.
- Oh, don't forget your...
guitar case.
Wait, I'll hold it for you.
- Hold on a second.
I wanna get a picture of this.
Okay.
All right.
Just a little.
There you go.
Little room for the Holy Ghost.
And...
- And open.
- I believe these are for you.
- Where are we going?
- I know nothing.
- Fred.
- Don't even try it.
- Thank you, Fred.
Okay, rule number one.
When you're on a train,
you must always travel with
Chinese food out of a backpack.
- Well, I wouldn't know, I've
never been on a train before.
- Neither have I.
- Really?
- Really.
Cheers.
I still cannot believe that we
grew up in the same town since
we were younger
and I've never seen you out
riding your bike or out with
a lemonade stand.
And I would've bought your
lemonade.
- No, you wouldn't have.
I don't like lemonade.
- Who doesn't like lemonade?
- Me.
- You know I know the
real story, right?
You and your dad are in the
Witness Protection Program.
And you have both testified
against a mobster.
- Very close. But...
the truth is...
I've been sent here
to monitor you.
Right. And I've been given
specific instructions to never
be seen in the daylight
and I've been watching you this
whole entire time from the
safety of my own room.
- Classic Witness Protection
Program cover story.
All right, close your eyes
and put your hands out.
- Okay.
And open.
(laughing)
- Try and catch 'em
in your mouth.
- Hey!
- Thank you.
- Oh, and look.
We're here.
(upbeat song)
- Wait, where are you taking me?
- We're here.
- Charlie, what is this place?
- It's your surprise.
- Charlie, my man.
- I thought Seattle
was my surprise.
- Come on.
(crowd shouting)
- Where are we going?
- It's your first live show.
- Yeah.
(upbeat song)
- Whoo!
- Thank you!
- That was seriously so cool.
- I know.
- That was, I mean, literally
one of the best things ever.
- Right?
- Oh, God.
Live music is beautiful.
- You are beautiful.
- You're the best.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Okay.
Your turn.
- For what?
Oh!
No, no, no, no!
I am not.
- Oh, yes, yes.
You owe me a song.
- I can't do it...
...here.
- Yes, you can.
Remember, live
shows are the best.
- Are you hungry? 'Cause I'm
hungry and you're always hungry.
- Look, we can either have come
all the way to this new city...
underneath the stars
and you don't play me a song...
or we can continue to have the
greatest night of our lives.
- Okay...
- I'll be right here watching.
Go, come on, we're waiting!
(soft music)
♪ I put my hair up I
slap my lipstick on ♪
♪ I can't decide what to wear ♪
♪ I try my clothes on
about a hundred times ♪
♪ I wanna get it right ♪
♪ But as long as I got
this perfect feeling ♪
♪ I know that everything
will be right ♪
♪ As long as I've got
this sweetest feeling ♪
♪ My troubles will be
out of my sight ♪
(humming)
♪ My troubles will
be miles away ♪
♪ I slip my shoes on
Take a spin or two ♪
♪ Tell me how does
this look to you ♪
♪ In the mirror I blow
a kiss and scoot ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm running
late for you ♪
♪ But as long as I've got
this perfect feeling ♪
♪ I know that everything
will be right ♪
♪ As long as I've got
this sweetest feeling ♪
♪ My troubles will be
out of my sight ♪
(humming)
♪ My troubles will
be miles away ♪
- She's good.
♪ When you take me all
around this town ♪
♪ All the wonder we've seen ♪
♪ As long as I've got
this perfect feeling ♪
♪ I know that everything
will be right ♪
♪ As long as I've got
this sweetest feeling ♪
♪ My troubles will be
out of my sight ♪
(humming)
♪ My troubles will
be miles away ♪
(cheering)
- Okay, I probably would have
said you were good
no matter what,
but you were really,
really good.
You know, you have to do
something with your music.
- No, I couldn't.
- You have to,
Katie. It was amazing.
- Are you ready?
- For what?
- To go swimming.
- No, Katie, you know
I don't swim anymore.
- Yes, you do. You just
haven't swam in a while.
And I've never swam in
this water before, so...
you're gonna take me.
- Ha ha...
- Come on!
- No, I'm serious.
I'm not swimming.
- But you made me sing and I
didn't want to.
- That was totally different.
- No, it's not!
- Okay, do you have any idea
how cold that water is?
- Charlie.
We could've either come
all the way to the beach
under the beautiful stars
and not go swimming.
Or we could jump into that water
and continue to make this
the best night of our lives.
- I don't have a swimsuit.
- Neither do I.
- Katie.
- You coming?
Hurry up!
Oh, my God, it's so cold.
- Put your arms forward,
and then push.
- The breast stroke? It seems
like a trick.
(laughing)
- Kinda.
- See, this isn't so bad.
You don't hate the water.
- I don't hate anything
when I'm with you.
- Have you thought any more
about your Berkeley spot?
- No.
You know, I just keep thinking
about after the surgery...
when I couldn't swim.
You know, I just realized
I didn't even know who I was.
And neither did anybody else.
All these kids that I've been
going to school with for
15 years,
they just saw me as
that guy in the pool.
I don't have to live
that life anymore.
- You know...
you're not the guy in the pool.
But...
you're not the guy that
doesn't try either.
Do everything you can right now
and then decide.
Because now is all that matters.
- You're right.
- Good.
- Speaking of tomorrow morning,
ready for the greatest sunrise
on the planet?
- What?
Charlie, what time is it?
- It's 4:50.
- It's not waterproof.
Oh, my God.
- What?
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Katie, wait!
- Oh, shit! I need to go!
- Katie, wait! Katie!
(panting)
Katie!
Shit!
Hey, get in, let me drive you!
- Go, Charlie, go!
- Katie! What the
hell is going on?
- You have to go as fast
as you can!
- Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
Katie, what--
- Please just go, Charlie!
- You're scaring me.
- You have to speed! Faster!
- Okay, okay!
Katie!
(Katie panting)
Katie, will you please
just talk to me?
Katie, please just talk to me!
- Hey! Is she inside?
- Yes.
- Is she in there? Move!
- How could you let this happen
to her?
- Let what happen? What?
- Did she not tell you?
- Tell me what?
I have no idea what's going on!
- She's sick! She's sick...
- What do you mean she's sick?
- She has XP.
She can't go in the sun at all.
It can kill her. I'm sorry.
Katie?
This is a nice hospital.
I bet they have
really good food.
- Katie Price?
We're ready.
- It was like a second, if that.
Okay? Everything's
gonna be fine.
We're good, Mr. P.
(footsteps approaching)
- Hey.
Is she okay?
- Okay, Katie, you can sit up.
Nurse Jane will take
you back outside.
- Um, actually, I wanna stay.
- Okay.
The sunlight exposure
was minimal.
The physical effects you're
seeing right now will heal.
But, as you know, XP generally
lies dormant until there's a
triggering event.
We won't know if
that's what this was
until we get the results back
from your blood work and
CT scans.
- And if this was a
triggering event?
- We'll cross that
bridge if we come to it.
If you experience any symptoms,
unexpected shaking, muscular
pain, loss of motor function,
you need to let us
know immediately.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go get dressed now.
I'm pretty busy during the day,
but I could be free at night.
(Katie's voice overlapping)
I can be free at night.
- What about UW?
What about the study? Have
they started the second phase?
- I followed up with
them last week.
No news yet.
- Okay.
Thanks.
- All right, Charlie.
Let's get back to work.
(text alert)
- Look, I know I told you to
play hard to get, but you should
at least see what he has to say.
He's asking if he can come over
and talk to you.
- Don't.
Please just delete them.
- Katie.
- Look, if I read them,
then I'm gonna reply,
then he's gonna reply
and then we're gonna meet up.
Which we can't.
- Why can't you?
You don't have to be a
martyr just to
protect Charlie's feelings.
He's a big boy.
I'm sure he can handle it.
- I can't handle it.
Okay?
He's gonna get hurt, and I'm not
gonna be the one who hurts him.
So, please, can you
just delete them?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- We should do
another set of tests.
The results could
come back different.
- Her brain has
begun to contract.
Once the neural pathways--
- What about the study?
- They shut it down, Jack.
I found out this morning.
There's no funding.
- No, I...
I did everything I
was supposed to do.
I mean, from the time
she was very young...
no matter how much she...
cried...
or screamed or moaned...
I wouldn't let her go outside.
I wouldn't let her
go to the park.
I wouldn't even let
her go to the beach.
And she begged me.
She begged me...
for things that she
had every right to.
And I denied her all of it.
And for what?
Huh?
For this?
No.
- XP is a disease that tends
to take the joy from
a child's life.
In all these years I've treated
Katie, she's never complained,
she's never sulked.
She always sees the
good in things.
And the way she talks about you?
I've never seen a teenager
so openly adore her father.
You're a good father, Jack.
- How long?
- It's hard to say for sure.
(indistinct TV)
- Hey, kiddo.
- Hey, Dad.
- I'm starving.
Wanna get some Chinese?
- Hum... Yah...
- Is that a yeah?
What are you doing?
- I'm starting you an
online dating profile.
- What?
- Yeah.
Look, okay.
So, I have this photo of you,
which I think your hair looks
better in. But then in this one
you have your camera.
- Oh, no, no, no!
This is not happening!
- No, no.
This is happening.
Here, just take a seat.
Wanna help me write it?
- Oh, I don't know.
- Okay, here's what
I have so far.
World's greatest father
and handsomest photographer.
- Ah! Veto.
- Looking for a fellow
adventurer interested in art,
photography
and nostalgia about
the Supersonics.
- Supersonics is good.
That's important.
- I knew you would like that.
A partner in crime to
travel the world with.
- I don't travel, honey.
- Uh, you will though.
- All right, we're not
doing this.
- Please, please, please,
I want to.
You lost Mom and now
you're gonna lose me, too.
- No.
No, there's always a chance.
- We've always known it's a
matter of when and not if.
So I really need
you to be selfish
and...
go out there and, you know,
take those beautiful photos
and start traveling the world
again. I want everyone to see
your photos, Dad.
- Just stop.
Okay, I can't...
I can't.
- I just want you...
to promise me that you're
gonna take care of yourself.
I really want you to have as
happy a life as the one you've
given me.
And try and find someone
that you can share these
incredible adventures with.
Because having someone...
that's the best part.
So please, just pick a rando
lady and take her out.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Promise me.
- I promise.
- Good.
Now we can order Chinese food.
- Come on!
- That was so a ball.
- That's not even baseball.
I don't know what that is.
(doorbell ringing)
- Oh, food.
Finally.
What took them so long?
Oh, my God.
Charlie's outside.
- I know. I called him.
- What?
Why?
- Because...
you said the best part was
having someone to share your
adventures with.
So, go talk to him.
Tell him the truth.
He deserves that.
And so do you.
- You exist.
This time I was
positive I dreamt you.
- Charlie, I'm so sorry.
- Katie, this isn't something
you can just not tell me.
- I'm so...
so sorry...
I didn't tell you.
That's...
unforgivable and very selfish...
on my part.
We were never gonna work.
But I wanted us to.
You, me, we...
we don't win in the end.
So...
so I'm saying goodbye, Charlie.
Goodbye.
- You know, that was the worst
break-up speech I've ever heard.
- What?
- Yeah. Like a
D- would be generous.
Zeros from all the judges,
Katie. It was a total flop.
- I've never done this before!
What do you expect?
(laughing)
Seriously, Charlie.
We can't.
- We can.
What I can't do...
I can't stop being with you.
Katie, I've done my research
on XP. I know what it is.
I know what you
are going through.
But we're not the
couple who doesn't try.
You knew that before I did.
You've changed my life, Katie.
Okay, you can either just leave
me here on this porch or...
or we can have the best
summer of our lives.
What's it gonna be?
(whistle blowing)
- Go, Charlie, push it!
- Go, Charlie!
- That's it, Charlie, come on!
- Go, Charlie! Come on, Charlie!
- Yeah!
- The Berkeley coach was
impressed and they promised to
keep in touch.
- In touch is good!
They'll be in touch.
I'm so proud of you, honey.
- So good.
Hey, I'll be right back.
- Sure.
- Hey, Charlie.
- Hi.
- The rumors are true.
Congrats.
- Thank you.
- You were great in there.
- Thank you for
letting Katie come.
- I couldn't have stopped her.
- Mr. Price...
would you mind
if I took Katie out tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think that'd be fine.
- Thank you.
Come on, come on.
- I'm so confused.
What are we...
What is this?
- It's for you.
- Is this Katie?
- Yeah.
- Let's do this.
- No, oh, my God, no.
- Now, Katie, Katie, yes.
- No, I can't.
- Yes, yes!
Yes!
- This is so crazy.
How did you even pay for this?
- Don't worry about it.
- Charlie, your truck money?
I can't let you--
- Katie, it's already done.
Okay, you helped me figure out
my dreams
and now it's payback time.
- I can't play anymore.
- Then just sing.
- Whenever you're ready, Katie.
Let's lay one down.
- Thank you.
How did you get this?
This is the song I've
been working on.
- Stole your notebook again.
(soft music)
♪ I wish I could
stand on a star ♪
♪ I wish I could be
where you are ♪
♪ They say don't
you ever give up ♪
♪ It's so hard to be
something when you're not ♪
♪ But I have walked alone ♪
♪ With the stars in
the moonlit night ♪
♪ I have walked alone ♪
♪ No one by my side ♪
♪ Now I walk with you ♪
♪ With my head held high ♪
♪ In the darkest sky ♪
♪ I feel so alive ♪
- Let me count our chips.
(laughing)
- That one.
- That one?
That's Charlinium,
'cause it is huge and powerful.
And that one is my favorite.
That one is Burritorium,
because it's shaped
like a burrito.
- That one is Procyon.
It's 11 light years away.
- So we were seven
when that light was made.
- That was...
right around the time
you got your first skateboard.
- What?
- Charlie, that night we met
at the train station...
I already knew you.
- What do you mean?
- In elementary school...
you walked by my window every
day on your way to swim
practice.
And in fourth grade...
you started skateboarding.
And in sixth grade, you wore
a Ken Griffey Jr. jersey
every day for, like,
a month straight.
And in ninth grade...
you buzzed off all your hair.
Ugh...
And...
every day...
I waited for you to
walk by my window...
and it was the best
part of my day.
- If I had just looked up...
I could've been with
you this whole time.
- You were.
I...
I love you, Charlie.
- I love you, too.
I can't believe you still
like me after that buzz cut.
- It was so ugly.
Oh, my God.
- There's some more chicken, but
I'm eating the rest of the
noodles if no one wants them.
- Okay. I'm gonna go to the
marina. I'll be back in an hour.
- Someday I wanna see this
Beyoncé-worthy yacht
you're cleaning.
- You're gonna miss your chance.
Owner's back tomorrow.
It's my last checkup.
See you in an hour?
- Okay.
- I'll walk you out.
- All right.
I'll see you.
One of these days we can...
take her for a sail
around the harbor.
We can watch the sun set.
- Wait.
I... I wanna go with him.
- Go where, honey?
- Out.
Sailing on the boat.
I wanna go with him
on the boat. Now.
- Honey.
It'd be better if you just--
- Please, Dad.
Let me do this.
It's okay, Dad.
I really want to.
- Okay.
♪ I have seen a
thousand things ♪
♪ A thousand minds and
what they bring ♪
♪ To this world and
to this home ♪
♪ But where I stand,
well I... ♪
♪ Don't know ♪
♪ I'm an open book ♪
♪ I'll tell you
everything I know ♪
♪ To the darkest corners ♪
♪ Of my mind ♪
♪ My kingdom is wide ♪
♪ So wide-eyed I can't
track the time ♪
♪ Between the spaces
of my mind ♪
♪ 'Cause I have seen
a thousand things ♪
♪ A thousand minds and
what they bring ♪
- I've waited my whole
life to feel this.
♪ But where I stand,
well I don't know ♪
♪ And people come
and people go ♪
♪ People I will never know ♪
♪ But if I did and if I could ♪
♪ I'd wonder when and
where they stood ♪
♪ 'Cause I have seen
a thousand things ♪
♪ A thousand minds and
what they bring ♪
♪ To this world and
to this home ♪
♪ But where I stand ♪
♪ Well I don't know ♪
(soft music)
- There he is.
- Hey, Mr. Price.
- Glad you made it by before
you took off.
- Of course.
I'm actually leaving today.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
The first practice is in
a couple of days, so...
- That's exciting!
- Yeah, I'm
looking forward to it.
- Your coach sent me your
schedule, so I'm hoping to make
it down for a meet.
- But why would my coach
send you the schedule?
- We stayed in touch, I guess,
after Katie reached out.
- Katie reached out?
- Yeah.
She called him.
Told him that he needed
to take another look at you.
- No, Katie never told me.
- You know what?
Hold that thought, all right?
I got something for you.
She wanted you to have that.
- I, um...
I never said sorry.
I never apologized to you.
I should have never kept
Katie out that late and I--
- Stop!
Stop!
It's nobody's fault.
Okay?
We knew from the time
that she was little...
that every day was
gonna be a gift.
I should be thanking you!
All I ever wanted to
do was make her happy.
And you made her so happy.
- Thank you.
- Good luck at school, son.
- Coming up next,
we have a song that
is blowing up on YouTube
with over two million views
in just two weeks.
Get ready to hear it all over
the airwaves. Just remember you
heard it here first.
This is Charlie's
Song by Katie Price.
♪ I wish I could be
where you are ♪
♪ They say don't
you ever give up ♪
♪ It's so hard ♪
♪ To be something
when you're not ♪
♪ But I have walked alone ♪
♪ With the stars in
the moonlit night ♪
♪ I have walked alone ♪
♪ No one by my side ♪
♪ Now I walk with you ♪
♪ With my head held high ♪
♪ In the darkest sky ♪
♪ I feel so alive ♪
(text alert)
♪ The beauty of the night ♪
♪ But I have walked alone ♪
♪ With the stars in
the moonlit night ♪
♪ I have walked alone ♪
- Yes!
Yes!
(laughing)
Hey, that's my girl! Hey, that's
my girl! Did you hear this?
Put down, put it
down! Listen. Listen.
♪ With my head held high ♪
♪ In the darkest sky ♪
♪ I feel so alive ♪
Dear Charlie.
I've always been more
comfortable writing song lyrics
than actual sentences.
There's no way I can articulate
what you've meant to me.
Since that moment we
first saw each other...
or the joy you've brought me
since I first saw you outside
my window.
Even though our time
together was short...
the stars have been burning
for every moment of it.
And the light
from those moments
will be shining down for
the next thousand years.
♪ But I have walked alone ♪
I hope that somehow I'll
be able to look down and
see you, Charlie,
and all of the incredible
moments just waiting for
you out there.
And if you need me...
all you have to do is look up.
And remember...
I love you.
♪ In the darkest sky ♪
♪ I feel so alive ♪
(upbeat song)
♪ They're not gonna break us ♪
♪ Hey we'll burn so bright ♪
♪ Making all the
people come to life ♪
♪ Hey the darkest sky ♪
♪ Can't stop me
and you tonight ♪
♪ I said, Hey, we'll
burn so bright ♪
♪ Dancing underneath
the city lights ♪
♪ Hey from way up high ♪
♪ Shining down like
stars tonight ♪
♪ When it's too far
for me to reach it ♪
♪ I close my eyes
and believe it ♪
♪ Ain't no other way to do
Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ When you fall you're
gonna hit hard ♪
♪ When you love with
your whole heart ♪
♪ Remember the hard
times make you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ That's when we'll
show the world ♪
♪ They're not gonna
break us ♪
♪ Hey we'll burn so bright ♪
♪ Making all the
people come to life ♪
♪ Hey the darkest sky ♪
♪ Can't stop me
and you tonight ♪
♪ I said, Hey, we'll
burn so bright ♪
♪ Dancing underneath
the city lights ♪
♪ Hey from way up high ♪
♪ Shining down like
stars tonight ♪
♪ When you fall you're
gonna hit hard ♪
♪ When you love with
your whole heart ♪
♪ The hard times make you
Ooh ooh ooh ♪
(upbeat music)