I have this reoccurring dream.
I'm a little girl sitting with my mom,
and she's singing to me.
I feel the warmth of the sun
on my skin
and the comfort of her arms
around me.
And I wanna stay there.
Forever.
When I wake up,
I miss the dream.
I want so badly
for this dream to be real,
but that would be impossible
because my mom died
when I was really little.
And I can't go out in the sun.
Like, at all.
I have a rare genetic condition
called Xeroderma Pigmentosum,
or XP, which basically means a
severe sensitivity to sunlight.
If the sun hits my skin,
I get skin cancer,
my brain starts to fail, and I could die.
Pretty fun, right?
So, I spend all my time indoors
behind special windows,
hanging out with my dad,
who is the best dad ever.
Thank goodness,
because growing up,
kids were, uh,
what you'd expect.
- No way.
- Yep, a vampire.
That's why they have special windows.
Don't worry.
She can't get us during the day.
But at night,
stay far, far away.
But not everyone was afraid of me.
- Hey, Morgan.
- What's wrong with her?
She has something called XP.
Basically, the light
from the sun, it hurts her.
So she can't ever go in the sun.
I can't be in the sun
for too long either.
Can she play at night?
- Yeah, but...
- See you tonight!
Oh! And I like pizza!
From that point on it was me,
Morgan, and my dad.
Until one day
I saw Charlie, and that was it.
I was completely,
totally, utterly hooked.
Stupid tree.
I saw him every day.
And yet,
he had no idea I even existed.
Over time, watching Charlie go
by just became a part of my routine.
Along with
constant doctor appointments,
sleeping during the day,
and staying up all night, which,
from what I've heard,
is the schedule of most teenagers,
and playing music
every chance I get.
All things considered,
I've got a pretty great life.
But I still hold on
to my dreams.
Stupid tree.
No matter how impossible
they may seem.
Jeremy Pierce.
- Kendall Porter.
- Congratulations.
Peter Rathbard.
Charles Reed.
Congratulations, Charlie.
Katie Price!
What are you wearing?
Oh. Cap and gown. Huh?
The faculty and staff always wear one.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Most importantly,
this is for you.
- Mmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
I assume as valedictorian,
you have a speech prepared? Yes?
Um...
Yes.
That's me putting on my glasses.
- I like that. Nice touch.
- Thank you.
Um, first, I would like
to thank my headmaster.
Well, I mean, really.
- My Spanish teacher.
- De nada.
- My English teacher.
- It was my pleasure.
But I really wanna state for
the record that my gym teacher
- had absolutely no idea what he was doing.
- What?
Oh, you suck!
I lift weights.
Hey, this is for you.
This is one of the lamest
things I've ever seen.
Yes! Ha-ha! I had to go to three
stores to find something this lame.
- I mean, it's horrific.
- Yeah! It's the worst!
All right.
Are you ready for your present?
- There's a present involved?
- Oh, there's a present, yes!
Of course there's a present.
It's graduation.
This keeps getting
better and better.
This is Mom's.
Look, I know it's kind of old,
so if you want a newer one
I totally understand.
No! I love it. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You look just like your mother.
Lucky you. She was hot.
Ew.
Try and get some sleep.
All right?
Ooh.
That's a good one.
Uh, something weird
is going on right here.
Hey, Dad, um,
I was wondering if I could go
play my new beautiful present
at the train station tonight?
It's 10:00.
Why can't Morgan just come over?
You could play here for me.
Morgan's busy with her family,
and, Dad, I love playing for you.
I really do,
but I also need to get used to
playing in front of
other people, too.
Please, please, please.
Fred will be there.
He'll watch out for me.
And I graduated today!
Isn't that the American tradition,
to extend my curfew?
Okay, I'll extend your curfew one hour.
Which means midnight,
okay? Hey.
And text me right when you get there,
or I'm not just gonna call Fred,
I'm actually gonna come down there.
And it will be so embarrassing,
it will become urban legend on why
kids should stick to their curfew!
I love you.
Oh.
- Hey, don't do that thing.
- What thing?
That. I mean, you look all sad
and it makes me sad.
Please just chug this beer
and come hang out!
Dude, you dodged a bullet, man.
You were gonna be up at the ass
crack of dawn every morning,
taking tests,
nowhere near the beach.
And now, we get to do this
our whole lives.
Mmm. I forgot, doing this
our whole lives,
it's way better than
a full ride to Berkeley.
Zoe Carmichael.
Three o'clock.
Charlie. You're in trouble.
What did I do this time?
You didn't get me a drink.
I did not know you were thirsty.
Now you do.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Is that the bad one?
Well, now that
you're not swimming,
maybe you'll have
a little extra time for me.
I also have some extra time for you.
And I'm not swimming.
You were never swimming, idiot.
- Zoe! Get over here, bitch!
- Hold on!
You're coming to
my graduation party, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Good.
Yeah!
Uh, what are you doing?
Dodging another bullet.
Come on, dude.
It's our graduation night.
I'm not feeling it, boys.
I'll see you later.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Hey-yo, Fred.
I was wondering if I was
gonna see you tonight.
What, and disappoint
all my fans?
♪ Ain't all I'm meant to discover
Hey.
Uh...
Whoa!
- Um...
- I didn't mean to freak you out.
Here.
Uh, me? I'm not freaked out.
- Don't worry about it, I'm not a freak.
- Here, I'll help you.
Why are you packing up?
Where are you going?
Um, home. I gotta go home.
Home?
Wait, you live here?
- Wait, you didn't go to Purdue High.
- No.
It's a very different school.
Um, and I graduated today,
and my dad's a super big worrier.
So, I really gotta...
Oh, God.
Um...
I have to go.
Wait! Wait!
Whoa. What...
I'm sorry, why are you...
What's the rush? What...
Um, I have to get home
to my cat.
- Your cat?
- Yeah, it died.
- So, you're not in a rush then, right?
- No, no, I am.
I have to plan the funeral
for my, um, dead cat that died.
Yeah, it's super dead.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I didn't even get your name!
You haven't noticed any changes in her?
- Motor functions still seem strong?
- Yeah.
Yeah, no loss
of intellectual function,
uh, no difficulty
swallowing or talking.
Believe me on that.
And, uh, no corneal ulcerations.
Really, there's nothing to
suggest any neurodegeneration.
Any exposure to sunlight?
No.
Of course not.
I'm gonna refill her
prescription for you this time.
But she really should be coming
to these appointments with you.
Yeah, well, you know teenagers.
They get embarrassed
by their dads.
- She has XP, Jack.
- I know exactly what she has.
It's not gonna fall
into remission.
And every year,
the risk becomes more serious for her.
So, if she's exposed to even the
slightest bit of sunlight...
She won't be.
She's reached that age
we talked about.
She won't be.
Any word on the, uh,
University of Washington study?
I submitted Katie's name
for their Phase Two trials,
if it even gets that far.
I wouldn't get your hopes up.
Research funding
being what it is,
we're talking about a disease that
affects only one in a million people.
We're in luck,
'cause she is one in a million.
A cat funeral?
Please stop saying it out loud.
No, I... I mean, I've heard that
dead pets can actually be an aphrodisiac.
Morgan! What should I have said?
Any other combination of words
in the English language.
Like, "Hey, I'm Katie Price.
"I've watched you outside my
window for the past 10 years,
"and I've been in love with you,
stalking you
- "every minute of the day"?
- Okay, don't start with that.
Or, how about, "Hey,
you may remember me from kindergarten,
"when everyone
called me a vampire."
No one remembers that.
- Oh, what did I do?
- It's bad, but we'll fix it.
I feel so stupid and lame.
Mmm. Well, at least you have M&M's. So.
Thanks.
Look, you're just gonna
make up for it next time.
There's not gonna be
a next time.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
This is good.
This is what Taylor Swift does.
She has awkward
interactions with boys,
and then she just writes
amazing songs about it.
What?
Oh, no, no.
- Oh, come on.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's happening?
Did you see my notebook
when you came in?
Your notebook-notebook? No.
I think I left it
at the train station.
Oh, God.
Can you please go get it for me?
Morgan, it's so important.
Please?
You know I would but there's
a few other popping cat funerals
I was gonna hit tonight.
No, no, not by the corner!
Hey.
My friend's
been looking for that.
Do you know her? Oh, wait...
Morgan, right?
We had, uh, English class together.
- I'm Charlie.
- Charlie Reed, yeah. I know.
And it was History class.
But how do you know her?
Did she just move here or something?
Notebook first.
Or you could just tell me where she lives,
and I could drop it off.
I have a better idea.
Hey, Dad, I need to go to the train
station to pick up my notebook.
Fred has it.
Okay, text me when you get there
and be careful.
Fred?
Holy pregnant cow.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
- Purdue Creamery.
- Morgan?
Hey. How's your second date?
How could you do this to me?
Oh, my God, I'm in sweatpants.
My hair, it's a mess.
It's tied.
Oh, my God, I look like an idiot.
Oh, please.
Katie, you're super-freaking-hot.
I can't even see you right now,
and I can tell you look gorgeous.
Hi, excuse me.
Can I just get a large, uh...
Can you not see
I'm on the phone?
He really likes you, okay?
I can tell.
Just try to be yourself.
Don't ramble too much.
And call me afterwards?
Bye.
Oh, my... Uh...
Uh...
Wow, you exist.
I thought I was dreaming
last night or something.
Were you in
the REM stage of sleep?
- Wha...
- That's when most dreams happen, actually.
Yeah. Your, uh... Your brain activity
is super high and functioning,
and your eyes are just going
nuts behind your eyelids.
It looks super weird.
It's like a typewriter or something.
Anyway, thank you for...
Wait, I, uh...
I still don't know your name.
Oh.
It's Katie.
Katie, I'm Charlie.
Wow, that's a weird name.
Thank God you told me it
'cause I wouldn't have known it otherwise.
- Wha...
- Thank you.
Wait. What...
You didn't...
You didn't read through it,
did you?
- I... Just a little.
- What?
- Are you serious?
- You read through my journal?
- Look, I...
This could have been a diary.
I mean, it is, kind of.
I'm really sorry.
You left really quick
the other night,
and I really had no idea
who it belonged to,
so I just looked
through it quickly.
But I like that
you still handwrite things.
It's cool. It's old-school.
Thanks. For finding it.
Yeah.
Wait.
What, another cat died?
You have to...
Um...
I...
I had to... I, um...
I'm walking home.
Can I walk with you?
Um, yeah.
So you were home-schooled, huh?
Man, that must have been wild.
Actually, it was
the exact opposite of wild.
My dad's pretty protective.
He's not, like, watching us
right now, is he?
Oh, yeah. He has his phone
tapped into every camera.
So, um, what did you think
of the songs you read?
Without my permission,
I may add.
Um...
Honestly, I don't know.
I mean, you can't really
read a song, right?
True.
I guess I'd have
to hear you sing them?
Um, so, anyway, I'm right up here.
So, you don't have to walk me.
You live up there?
I don't understand
how we've never met.
I've probably skated by your house
every day on the way to practice.
It's a funny coincidence.
Um...
Thanks.
Hey, you wouldn't wanna do
something sometime, would you?
Um...
- Together?
- Yes, us together.
Hanging out.
Um...
I'm really busy during the day,
but I could be free at night.
I could be free at night.
Well, you should
put your number in here then.
I'm old-school, too.
Smooth.
That is so romantic.
It disgusts me.
What did he say about your XP?
It didn't come up.
What do you mean,
it didn't come up?
I didn't bring it up.
I'm not gonna just
randomly be like, "Hey, dude.
"By the way, the sunlight's gonna..."
Like, look,
when you tell someone you're sick,
then you start to become more like
a disease and less like a person.
I'm gonna tell him, I promise.
But I don't know
when I'm gonna see him again.
I do.
You know that annoying guy
who works with me
- at the ice cream shop?
- The nerdy one you hate?
Yes, Garver.
His parents are out of town tonight,
and he's throwing a party,
and he told me to bring friends.
So, I'm gonna bring you.
- No, no, no.
- And you're gonna bring Charlie.
He's gotta, like...
You know?
Doesn't... I have to wait till
he texts me first, right?
Yeah, totally. And then
his squire will send a note
via carrier pigeon
asking if you'd like
to merge your kingdoms.
What is this, 18th century England?
You're a hot young badass woman.
You're gonna text him
whenever you damn well please.
Be confident, okay?
Give him the facts.
Okay.
- Play a little hard to get.
- All right.
Make sure that he knows he's not
the only reason you're going.
Okay. Oh!
All right.
Oh, no.
This is gonna be a tame,
safe, parent-friendly party.
Ah-hah!
It's a totally lame party.
You know what we should do?
We should stay here.
- We'll get Hunan Chinese.
You guys love Hunan, right?
Put some Netflix on.
It'll be perfect.
Dad. You know I'm a good kid.
You know I'm not gonna do
anything crazy.
But I swear, if I spend
one more night here,
just listening to everyone else
outside my window living their lives,
I might go crazy.
Tomorrow night we can order
way too much chow mein
and have a great movie marathon.
- All right.
- Yes, thank you!
You're the best dad
in the world.
Thanks, Mr. P!
Okay, um, Charlie's gonna
meet us at Garver's at 8:00.
We have to get ready!
Dude, what are you talking about?
We have, like, three hours!
We're already behind.
Done.
Mr. P!
May I present,
Katherine Price of Washington.
Wow.
Peanut, you look amazing.
Bye, Mr. P.
Let's go.
God, I can't believe
Garver's throwing a kegger.
You came.
Is there any chance that you,
or your hot friend...
Hey.
...know how to get beer
out of a keg?
Oh, no.
You didn't get a tap?
I didn't realize
they were separate things.
Why would they sell me a barrel
of beer I can't even access?
Garver, what the hell?
This is a tame, safe,
parent-friendly party!
Uh, do tame parties
have sundae bars?
I think it's so cool.
No, don't listen to her.
Okay, she's never been
to a party before.
She doesn't understand
how dire the situation is.
- We gotta go.
- What, you're leaving?
No, no, I just made
a huge thing of chili.
Garver, chili is not a party food.
You see, the party's just
kicking off.
What's Charlie Reed doing here?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
You look really amazing.
Um...
Oh, it's, uh...
It's all Morgan.
Mmm. I don't think so.
For you, good sir.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Beef chili, huh?
Mmm.
That's top shelf, buddy. That's fresh.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I really thought we'd have a bigger turnout.
I told you not to go up
against a cheerleader.
What cheerleader?
Uh, some mean blonde woman
with a convertible.
- Zoe Carmichael?
- Yes.
Ugh.
She's having a party tonight as well.
Must have dinged our turnout.
Do you guys just wanna go there?
Well, uh, I like the idea.
Hey.
I was wondering where you were.
- Who are these people?
- Oh, these are my friends.
And, uh, they brought you a keg.
Great. Come on in.
Charlie!
You good?
Hey, uh, I'm gonna
go take a lap upstairs.
Away from you two.
Thank you.
Your friend Morgan,
uh, she seems cool.
Yeah. She's really cool.
How long have you guys known each other?
I don't know.
Like, forever.
He's back.
Whoa. Who is this?
Uh, Owen, Wes,
this is Katie Price.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Katie. You're a...
You're a...
You got Charlie
to come to a party
and make a smile-like feature.
Our boy hasn't looked
this good in a long time.
There you are.
I'm still thirsty.
Wanna get me that drink now?
I'm actually about to go take
Katie on the house party tour.
So. You ready?
We'll be right back.
- Nice meeting you guys.
- Nice to meet you, Katie.
- I can quench your thirst.
- Shut up.
Would you like to dance with me?
Garver, what on Earth makes you think
I'd ever want to dance with you?
You know if you tell anyone
about this, I'll kill you.
Totally.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey.
- Gotta stay hydrated.
- Thank you.
- This is really interesting.
- Mmm-hmm.
I don't think I've ever seen this happen.
Yeah.
Classic high school awkward party.
I've only seen it in the movies.
- I gotta show you this. Come on.
- Oh, God.
Come on.
Okay, similar to
what's going on over here.
We just kind of hold here
and swing the hips awkwardly.
- Am I doing it?
- Yeah, you're kind of.
And then I would slowly back up.
Everybody!
This is the best night
of my life! Yeah!
Oh, my G...
- You wanna go someplace else?
- Okay.
I don't get it.
How could they just take
your scholarship away?
Well, I had to have surgery, and they
didn't think I could ever swim again.
And no more scholarship
meant no more Berkeley.
- I'm really sorry.
- Yeah.
So, how did you do it?
How did you hurt yourself?
It was just a freak accident.
I fell down some stairs and...
And that's not true.
That's kind of
what I tell everybody.
I got really drunk one night
at Owen's house,
and my friends dared me to jump
off the roof into the pool,
and I clipped the edge
with my shoulder.
I'm such an idiot.
I don't wanna be
that guy, you know?
Then don't be.
You know, my mom used to take
me here when I was little.
Really?
She sat me right there,
and, um, she tried to teach me
how to play the guitar.
Actually, this watch was hers.
I spent so much time looking at
this thing on her hand and...
Um...
She died when I was little.
She was in a car accident.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
- We can go someplace...
- No!
No, no. No, no.
No, I'm good.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Yeah. I promise.
You wanna see something cool?
Ta-da.
- This is yours?
- No.
But it's something I'm taking
care of for the summer.
It's a Jespersen 53.
Wow.
One of these days we could take
her for a sail around the harbor
and watch the sun set.
That sounds perfect.
Um... Just...
You gotta...
Oh.
Sorry.
So, what are you
gonna do this year,
now that you're not
going to Berkeley?
Well, first I'm gonna get
a new truck.
And then I'm gonna drive
across country.
I've been in the pool
my entire life, and, uh,
I haven't got to see
much else, so.
Um...
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm not doing anything.
I'm just gonna take some
online courses, I think.
But I'll just be here.
I, uh... I meant,
what are you doing tomorrow?
Oh. Oh!
Oh, God.
Um...
I...
I'm busy during the day,
but I can be free
tomorrow night.
That's perfect.
I'll see you tomorrow night?
Okay.
I have something to tell you.
I don't actually have a cat.
No shit.
- Who are you texting?
- No one.
- Morgan, who are you texting?
- Mmm.
- Garver.
- Hmm?
I can't hear you when you're whispering.
Garver! I made out
with Garver.
No!
He's really, really cute.
And he totally likes you.
By the way, can I tell my dad that
I'm going over to yours tonight,
so I can go hang out
with Charlie later?
You're asking me to help
you lie to your father,
so you can hang out with a guy?
I've never been so proud of you!
Uh, Dad, I'm gonna go over
to Morgan's tonight.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah, yeah, no problem.
Hey, how was that party?
Party was nice.
Did you meet any fun people?
No. Not really.
Everybody was kind of just,
like... Ugh, you know?
Nobody was really there.
It was just... Hmm.
So I'm gonna skedaddle.
- Love you.
- Love you more.
I'm lying.
Well, you were rambling,
so I kind of figured.
I'm going to go meet
a boy named Charlie Reed
who's really nice and sweet
and I really, really like him.
A lot.
Are you mad?
Well, I'm not happy
that you lied to me.
- You know you can always tell me anything.
- I know. I know.
Sorry.
- Do you trust this guy?
- Yes.
- Will I hate him?
- No, no, you won't.
I promise.
- Does he know...
- I haven't told him yet.
- No, Katie...
- But I will.
I am not comfortable
with him not knowing.
I know, I'm going to.
I just need a little bit longer of...
What?
Being someone
more than just a disease.
Katie.
It's just a few more days,
please? Like a normal girl.
Hey.
Is it okay if me and Katie
hang out tonight together?
- The entire night?
- I already admitted everything.
What, you couldn't
make it two hours?
It's pathetic.
I could've made it two hours.
What does Katie Price wanna do?
There's so many things
I wanna do.
I have always wanted to do this.
Ready?
What about that one over there?
Um, that one's called Altair.
And it's 16 light years away,
which means the light we're seeing now
was actually created
when we were two.
Are you okay?
The Berkeley coach called
my house the other night.
Really?
Yeah, I mean, I guess
one of the other swimmers
transferred out and
another spot opened up.
Wow. That's so crazy.
You could get your spot back?
I mean, technically, yeah.
There's this huge meet
coming up next month,
and the Berkeley coach
is coming down to watch.
But I'd have to
get in shape by then,
which is probably impossible.
And then I'd have to swim
my best time ever to show
that I'm fully rehabbed.
You can totally do it.
But there's also some reasons
to stick around here next year.
Katie, I wanna take you
on a real date tomorrow.
Okay.
And you also need
to meet my dad.
Why don't you move
a little closer there, Cody?
My... My name's Charlie.
- Charlie.
- Yeah.
Hah! I didn't know that.
So, what do you go by? Do you go by Charlie,
not Chuck or Chuckie or C-Town?
- No, sir, just Charlie.
- Charlie, okay.
- You ever been arrested?
- No, sir.
- When's your curfew?
- It's 1:00 a.m.
- What time do you actually get home?
- Like, 2:00.
- That's not 1:00, is it, Charlie?
- No, sir, it's not.
- You said your curfew was 1:00.
- Yeah.
Relax, I'm not a cop.
How many times a week
do you shave?
Shave? Um... Uh... Like four.
Uh, four times. Four times a week, sir.
- Who's your team?
- Seahawks.
- Why?
- Well, because they're great.
And one time I was at
this burger place and
Richard Sherman actually
ate some of my fries.
That's awesome.
Okay.
Charlie, here's the deal.
Katie appears to be very strong.
And she is.
- Hey, hi.
- She's dealing with...
- What you guys talking about?
- Nothing.
- We were...
- We're just getting to know each other.
Thank you so much for letting
me take her out, Mr. Price.
Okay.
Uh... Oh, don't forget
your guitar case.
Wait, I'll hold it for ya.
Uh, hold on a second.
I wanna get a picture of this.
Okay. All right.
Just a little...
There you go.
Little room for the Holy Ghost.
And...
And open.
I believe these are for you.
Oi!
- Where are we going?
- I know nothing.
- Fred.
- Don't even try it.
Thank you, Fred.
Okay, rule number one.
When you're on a train,
you must always travel with
Chinese food out of a backpack.
Well, I wouldn't know, I've
never been on a train before.
Neither have I.
- Really?
- Really.
Cheers.
I still cannot believe that
we grew up in the same town
since we were younger,
and I've never seen you
out riding your bike
or out with a lemonade stand.
And I would've bought
your lemonade.
No, you wouldn't have.
I don't like lemonade.
- Who doesn't like lemonade?
- Me.
You know I know
the real story, right?
You and your dad are in the
Witness Protection Program,
and you have both testified against a mobster.
Very close. But, uh,
the truth is,
I've been sent here
to monitor you.
Right. And I've been given
specific instructions
to never be seen
in the daylight,
and I've been watching you
this whole entire time
from the safety of my own room.
Classic Witness Protection
Program cover story.
All right, close your eyes
and put your hands out.
Okay.
And open.
- Try and catch 'em in your mouth.
- Hey.
Thank you.
Oh. And look. We're here.
Wait, where are you taking me?
We're here.
Charlie, what is this place?
It's your surprise.
Charlie, my man.
I thought Seattle
was my surprise.
Come on.
Where are we going?
- It's your first live show.
- Yeah.
Whoo!
- Thank you!
- That was seriously so cool.
- I know.
That was, I mean,
literally one of the best things ever.
Right?
Oh, God.
Live music is beautiful.
You're beautiful.
You're the best.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Okay.
Your turn.
For what?
Oh! No, no.
No, no, no. I am not.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
You owe me a song.
- I... I can't do it here.
- Yes, you can.
Remember, live shows
are the best.
Are you hungry? 'Cause I'm hungry,
and you're always hungry.
Look, we can either have
come all the way to this new city,
underneath the stars,
and you don't play me a song,
or we can continue to have the
greatest night of our lives.
I'll be right here watching.
Go, come on, we're waiting!
She's good.
Okay, I probably would have
said you were good no matter what,
but you were really,
really good.
You know, you have to do
something with your music.
- No, I couldn't.
- You have to, Katie.
It was amazing.
- Are you ready?
- For what?
To go swimming.
No, Katie, you know
I don't swim anymore.
Yes, you do.
You just haven't swam in a while.
And I've never swam
in this water before,
so you're gonna take me.
Come on!
No, I'm serious.
I'm not swimming.
But you made me sing,
and I didn't want to.
- That was totally different.
- No, it's not!
Okay, do you have any idea
how cold that water is?
Charlie.
We could've either come
all the way to the beach,
- under the beautiful stars, and not go swimming.
- Oh, my...
Or we could jump into that water
and continue to make this
the best night of our lives.
I don't have a swimsuit.
Neither do I.
Katie.
You coming?
Hurry up!
Oh, my God, it's so cold.
Pull your arms forward,
and then push.
The breast stroke?
It seems like a trick.
Kind of.
See, this isn't so bad.
You don't hate the water.
I don't hate anything
when I'm with you.
Have you thought any
more about your Berkeley spot?
No.
You know, I just keep thinking
about after the surgery,
when I couldn't swim.
I just realized
I didn't even know who I was.
And neither did anybody else.
All these kids that I've been
going to school with for 15 years,
they just saw me
as that guy in the pool.
I don't have to live
that life anymore.
You know...
You're not the guy in the pool.
But you're not the guy
that doesn't try either.
Do everything you can
right now, and then decide.
Because now is all that matters.
- You're right.
- Good.
Speaking of tomorrow morning,
ready for the greatest sunrise
on the planet?
What?
Charlie, what time is it?
It's 4:50.
It's not waterproof.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- Katie, wait!
- Katie, what are you doing?
- I need to go!
Katie, wait!
Katie!
Shit.
Katie, get in, let me drive you.
Go, Charlie, go!
Katie! What the hell
is going on?
- You have to go as fast as you can!
- Okay, I'm going, I'm going.
- Katie, what...
- Please just go, Charlie.
- You're scaring me.
- You have to speed!
- Faster!
- Okay, okay!
Oh, my God.
Katie!
Katie. Katie.
Katie.
Katie, will you please
just talk to me?
Katie, please just talk to me!
- Hey! Is she inside?
- Yes.
Is she in there? Move!
How could you let
this happen to her?
Let what happen?
What happen?
Did she not tell you?
Tell me what?
I have no idea what's going on!
She's sick! She's sick.
- What do you mean she's sick?
- She has XP.
She can't go in the sun at all.
It can kill her.
I'm sorry.
Katie?
This is a nice hospital.
I bet they have
really good food.
Katie Price?
We're ready.
It was like a second, if that.
Okay? Everything's gonna be fine.
We're good, Mr. P.
Hey. Is she okay?
Okay, Katie, you can sit up.
Nurse Jane will take you
back outside.
Um, actually, I wanna stay.
Okay.
The sunlight exposure
was minimal.
The physical effects you're
seeing right now will heal.
But, as you know,
XP generally lies dormant
until there's
a triggering event.
We won't know
if that's what this was
until we get the results back from
your blood work and CT scans.
And if this was
a triggering event?
We'll cross that bridge
if we come to it.
If you experience any symptoms,
unexpected shaking, muscular pain,
loss of motor function,
you need to let us know immediately.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get dressed now.
I'm really busy during the day,
but I could be free at night.
I can be free at night.
What about UW?
What about the study?
Have they started
the second phase?
I followed up with them last week.
No news yet.
Okay. Thanks.
All right, Charlie.
Let's get back to work.
Look, I know I told you
to play hard to get,
but you should at least
see what he has to say.
He's asking if he can come
over and talk to you.
Don't.
Please just delete them.
Katie.
Look, if I read them,
then I'm gonna reply,
then he's gonna reply,
and then we're gonna meet up.
Which we can't.
Why can't you? I...
You don't have to be a martyr just
to protect Charlie's feelings.
He's a big boy.
I'm sure he can handle it.
I can't handle it. Okay?
He's gonna get hurt,
and I'm not gonna be the one who hurts him.
So, please, can you just delete them?
Yeah. Okay.
We should do
another set of tests.
The results could
come back different.
Her brain has begun to contract.
Once the neural pathways...
- What about the study?
- They shut it down, Jack.
I found out this morning.
There's no funding.
No, I... I did everything
I was supposed to do.
I mean, from the time
she was very young,
no matter how much she cried
or screamed or moaned,
I wouldn't let her go outside.
I wouldn't let her go to the park.
I wouldn't even let her
go to the beach.
And she begged me.
She begged me
for things that she had
every right to.
And I denied her all of it.
And for what? Huh?
For this? No.
XP is a disease that tends to
take the joy from a child's life.
In all these years
I've treated Katie,
she's never complained,
she's never sulked.
She always sees
the good in things.
And the way she talks about you?
I've never seen a teenager
so openly adore her father.
You're a good father, Jack.
How long?
It's hard to say for sure.
- Hey, kiddo.
- Hi, Dad.
I'm starving.
Wanna get some Chinese?
- Uh, yeah.
- Is that a yeah?
What are you doing?
I'm starting you
an online dating profile.
- What?
- Yeah.
Look, okay.
So, I have this photo of you,
which I think
your hair looks better in.
But then in this one
you have your camera.
Oh! No, no, no.
This is not happening.
No, no. This is happening.
Here, just take a seat.
Wanna help me write it?
Oh, I don't know.
Okay, here's what I have so far.
"World's greatest father
and handsomest photographer."
Ugh. Veto.
"Looking for a fellow adventurer
"interested in art, photography,
and nostalgia about the Supersonics."
Supersonics is good.
That's important.
I knew you would like that.
"Um, a partner in crime
to travel the world with."
I don't travel, honey.
Uh, you will, though.
All right, we're not doing this.
Please, please, I want to.
You lost Mom, and now
you're gonna lose me, too.
No, there's always a chance.
We've always known it's a
matter of when and not if.
So I really need you
to be selfish and
go out there and take
those beautiful photos
and start traveling
the world again.
I want everyone
to see your photos, Dad.
Just stop.
Okay, I can't. I can't.
I just want you
to promise me that you're
gonna take care of yourself.
I really want you to have as happy
a life as the one you've given me.
And try and find someone
that you can share these
incredible adventures with.
Because having someone,
that's the best part.
So, please, just pick a rando lady
and take her out.
Okay. Okay.
- Promise me.
- I promise.
Good.
Now we can order Chinese food.
- Come on!
- That was so a ball.
That's... That's not even baseball.
I don't know what that is.
Oh. Food. Finally.
What took them so long?
Oh, my God.
Charlie's outside.
I know. I called him.
What? Why?
Because you said the best part
was having someone
to share your adventures with.
So, go talk to him.
Tell him the truth.
He deserves that.
And so do you.
You exist.
This time I was positive
I dreamt you.
Charlie, I'm so sorry.
Katie, this isn't something
you can just not tell me.
I'm so, so sorry
I didn't tell you.
That's
unforgivable and very
selfish on my part.
We were never gonna work.
But I wanted us to.
You, me,
we don't win in the end.
So, I'm saying goodbye, Charlie.
Goodbye.
You know, that was the worst
breakup speech I've ever heard.
- What?
- Yeah.
Like a D-would be generous.
- Zeroes from all the judges, Katie.
It was a total flop.
I've never done this before!
What do you expect?
Seriously, Charlie.
We can't.
We can.
What I can't do,
I can't stop being with you.
Katie, I've done
my research on XP.
I know what it is.
I know what you are going through.
But we're not the couple who doesn't try.
You knew that before I did.
You've changed my life, Katie.
Okay, you can either just leave
me here on this porch or...
Or we can have the best
summer of our lives.
What's it gonna be?
Go, Charlie, push it!
Go, Charlie!
That's it, Charlie, come on!
Whoo! Whoo!
Go, Charlie!
Come on, Charlie!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
The Berkeley coach was impressed,
and he promised to keep in touch.
In touch is good!
He'll be in touch.
I'm so proud of you, honey.
So good.
- Hey, I'll be right back.
- Sure.
- Hey, Charlie.
- Hi.
- The rumors are true.
- Congrats.
Thank you.
You were great in there.
Thank you
for letting Katie come.
I couldn't have stopped her.
Mr. Price, would you mind
if I took Katie out tomorrow?
Yeah. Yeah, I think
that'd be fine.
Thank you.
- Come on, come on.
- I'm so confused. What are we...
- What is this?
- It's for you.
- Is this Katie?
- Yeah.
Let's do this.
- No, oh, my God, no.
- Katie, Katie, yes.
- No, I can't, I can't.
- Yes, yes, yes. Yes.
Yes.
This is so crazy.
How did you even pay for this?
- Don't worry about it.
- Charlie, your truck money?
- I can't let you...
- Katie, it's already done.
Okay, you helped me figure out my dreams,
and now it's payback time.
I can't play anymore.
Then just sing.
Whenever you're ready, Katie.
Let's lay one down.
Thank you.
How did you get this?
This is the song
I've been working on.
Stole your notebook again.
Whoa.
Let me count our chips.
- That one.
- That one?
That's Charlinium
'cause it is huge and powerful.
And that one is my favorite.
That one is Burritorium
because it's shaped
like a burrito.
That one is Procyon.
It's 11 light years away.
So we were seven
when that light was made.
That was, um, right around the time
you got your first skateboard.
What?
Charlie, that night we met
at the train station,
I already knew you.
What do you mean?
In elementary school,
you walked by my window every day
on your way to swim practice.
And in fourth grade,
you started skateboarding.
And in sixth grade,
you wore a Ken Griffey, Jr. jersey
every day for a month straight.
And in ninth grade,
you buzzed off all your hair.
Ugh.
And
every day
I waited for you
to walk by my window,
and it was the best part
of my day.
If I had just looked up,
I could've been with you
this whole time.
You were.
I... I love you, Charlie.
I love you, too.
I can't believe you still
liked me after that buzz cut.
It was so ugly. Oh, my God.
Okay, there's some more chicken,
but I'm eating the rest of the
noodles if no one wants them.
Okay.
I'm gonna go to the marina.
I'll be back in an hour.
Someday I wanna see this
Beyoncé-worthy yacht you're cleaning.
Mmm, you're gonna miss your chance.
Owner's back tomorrow.
It's my last checkup.
- See you in an hour?
- Okay.
- I'll walk you out.
- All right.
I'll see you.
One of these days we could take
her for a sail around the harbor
and watch the sun set.
Wait.
I... I wanna go with him.
Go where, honey?
Out.
Sailing on the boat.
I wanna go with him
on the boat. Now.
Honey.
- It'd be better if you just stay here.
- Please, Dad.
Let me do this.
It's okay, Dad.
I really want to.
Okay.
I've waited my whole life
to feel this.
There he is.
Hey, Mr. Price.
Glad you made it by
before you took off.
Of course.
I'm actually leaving today.
- Wow.
- Yeah. The first practice is in a couple of days, so.
- That's exciting!
- Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Your coach sent me your schedule,
so I'm hoping to make it down for a meet.
But why would, uh, my coach
send you the schedule?
We stayed in touch, I guess,
after Katie reached out.
- Katie reached out?
- Yeah.
She called him.
Told him that he needed
to take another look at you.
Uh, no, Katie never told me.
You know what?
Hold that thought, all right?
I got something for you.
She wanted you to have that.
I, um...
I never said sorry.
I never apologized to you.
I should have never kept Katie
out that late and I...
Stop. Stop!
It's nobody's fault. Okay?
We knew from the
time that she was little
that every day was gonna be a gift.
I should be thanking you.
All I ever wanted to do
was make her happy.
And you made her so happy.
Thank you.
- Good luck at school, son.
- Thank you.
Coming up next, we have a song
that is blowing up on YouTube
with over two million views
in just two weeks.
Get ready to hear it
all over the airwaves.
Just remember you heard it here first.
This is Charlie's Song
by Katie Price.
Yes!
Hey! Hey, that's my girl!
Hey, that's my girl!
Do you hear this?
Put down the...
Put it down! Listen. Listen.
Dear Charlie,
I've always been more
comfortable writing song lyrics
than actual sentences.
There's no way I can articulate
what you've meant to me
since that moment
we first saw each other,
or the joy you've brought me since
I first saw you outside my window.
Even though our time together
was short,
the stars have been burning
for every moment of it.
And the light from those moments
will be shining down
for the next thousand years.
I hope that somehow
I'll be able to look down
and see you, Charlie.
And all of the incredible moments
just waiting for you out there.
And if you need me,
all you have to do is look up.
And remember,
I love you.