Illumination! [laughing]
[whooping]
[yells, grunts]
[exclaiming excitedly]
[grunts] Minion!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ When you wish upon a star ♪
♪ Your dreams will take you very far ♪
Ha-ha!
♪ But when you wish upon a dream ♪
♪ Life ain't always what it seems
Oh, yeah… ♪
Freeze! AVL!
[tires squealing]
-Hey! Hey!
-[yells]
-Stop right there!
-Grab her!
-Yeah, baby!
-Attention, all units.
[chuckles]
-[whoops, laughs]
-Look out!
-[laughs] You like that?
-Hey!
♪ Shining star for you to see ♪
♪ What your life can truly be ♪
-♪ What your life can truly be ♪
-[chuckles]
Ooh, baby!
The Anti-Villain League can't catch this.
Guess who stole the map.
[laughs]
Hallelujah! [laughs]
Yeah! I got this.
[whoops, laughs]
Ha-ha, good work.
The map to the legendary Zodiac Stone.
We will become
the most powerful villains in the world.
[cheering]
Okay, let's get a move on.
We leave for Asia tonight.
[laughs]
Okay, let's see here.
[chuckles]
[stone rumbling]
-[earpiece beeps]
-I'm in.
[yelling]
[grunts]
[groans]
Hello, beautiful. [laughs]
[chuckles]
-[door shuts]
-[gasps]
What?
[chittering]
Oh. [grunting]
[screams]
[grunting]
[panting]
Ha-ha! Yes!
The Zodiac Stone.
[magical ringing]
Oh.
[laughs triumphantly]
Soon, the power of these
unstoppable beasts will be ours.
[gasps] Oh, for crying out loud.
[creatures chittering]
[grunting]
Whoa! [laughs]
Whoa! [yells]
[yells]
Hurry up. I got a bunch of
deadly tchotchkes on my tail.
Roger that on the copy.
Step on it, sister.
Whoa!
Hurry up! Come on!
[yells]
Off! Off!
[laughs triumphantly]
I got it. I got the stone.
Party's over, old man.
The Vicious6 has
a new head honcho. [chuckles]
You just got played for a sucker!
[grunts] Hold on. I started this group.
We're a team.
Where's your loyalty?
Oh, please. We're villains.
There's no such thing.
-It's time for the next generation.
-[laughter]
[screaming]
["Bang, Bang" by G.E.M. playing]
[G.E.M singing in Mandarin]
[minions grunt, laugh]
[minions yelling]
[minions screaming]
[song continues]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Bang, bang ♪
[song ends]
[teacher, in English] Quiet down, class.
-[children clamoring]
-[teacher] Quiet down, class.
People, people.
So, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
-[girl] Ooh, ooh.
-Samantha.
I want to be a doctor.
Wonderful.
-Ooh, ooh!
-Bradley.
I want to be a teacher.
No, you do not.
-[boy] Ooh! Me, me!
-Yes.
I want to be a fireman
who is also the president
and also drives race cars. Yeah.
Exciting.
And what about you, Gru?
Gru?
Me?
I want to be
a supervillain.
[children laughing]
-Supervillain?
-Supervillain.
Loser!
-[bell rings]
-[excited shouting]
♪ I'm having a bad, bad day ♪
♪ It's about time that I get my way ♪
-Kelly!
-Daddy!
-Brett!
-Mom!
Gru!
Kiss-a la mama!
Oh, my favorite tiny relatives.
[minions yelling excitedly]
Oh, no. Guys, come on.
[kissing]
Hey. I got an image to uphold here.
-[minions laughing]
-[Gru yelps]
-[speaking Minionese]
-Okay.
Hey, are you guys pumped for the movie?
-[speaks Minionese excitedly]
-Let's go!
[laughs]
[yelling in Minionese]
[woman in movie screaming]
["Jaws theme" playing in movie]
[music crescendoes]
[music stops]
[fart bomb explodes]
[woman] Oh, no!
[people groaning, screaming]
[speaks Minionese]
-[woman in movie] Shark! A shark!
-[man screams]
[all laughing]
-I am a pinball wizard.
-[laughing]
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
[crackles]
-[Gru laughing]
-[minion exclaiming]
-Bello.
[speaking Minionese]
-[cheering]
-Yeah!
[woman] Everything you got.
A little more. Come on.
[sighs]
[woman] Put some of those sprinkles
on there.
I like those sprinkles.
[laughs]
Cheese ray! Cheese ray! Cheese ray!
Don't cheese me, bro.
[laughs maliciously]
[grunting] Pank you!
-Mmm. So creamy, so delicious.
-[people grunting, panting]
Worth every calorie.
♪ I'm having a bad, bad day ♪
♪ If you take it personal, that's okay ♪
♪ Watch, this is so fun to see… ♪
Bills, magazines,
S&amp;H Green Stamps.
Huh?
[exclaims]
[exclaims excitedly]
Holy guacamole!
Where can we listen? Where can we listen?
[speaking Minionese]
Hello, Mr. Gru.
We've received your application
to the world's best supervillain team,
the Vicious6.
A recent opening
has become available, and…
And?
…your interview is tomorrow at noon.
[exclaims] Dyn-o-mite!
[cheering in Minionese]
[Belle Bottom]
Please go to 417 Main Street.
The password is "You're no good."
"You're no good." Mmm-hmm.
Now, get up on the down stroke,
'cause this invitation
is gonna explode, baby.
Explode? Aw.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
[mild explosion]
[all coughing]
[mimics train horn tooting, laughing]
[exclaims] Very big news, Mom!
[guttural grunting upstairs]
Mom?
[grunting continues]
[Gru's Mom and man grunting]
Mom?
[guttural grunting continues]
-[groovy music playing softly]
-[both grunting]
What?
Mom, who is this sweaty guy?
He's stinking up the house.
I thought you were cooking cabbage.
He's my new guru.
[scoffs, retches]
[laughs, retches]
Tell your weird buddies they'd better
start pulling their weight around here,
or I'm kicking them out.
They are killing my mellow vibes.
[mimics complaining]
[Gru's Mom] Hey. I heard that.
Come on.
Let's go tell the troops the good news.
Gentlemen, to the basement,
aka, our new evil lair.
[exclaims]
This is fantastic!
Oh, construction looks great, guys.
[speaking Minionese]
[minions humming
Simon &amp; Garfunkel's "Cecilia"]
[humming continues]
My first evil lair.
Goose bumps!
[explosion]
[speaking Minionese]
Well, you've got to break a few eggs
to make an omelet. Am I right?
-Oh, great job, Ryan.
-What?
I said, great job!
-Never mind.
Adrien, Mack, looking good.
[speaking Minionese]
[sighs in relief]
[crying]
Joe, how's the family?
Hey. Good, good.
Okay, everybody, get over here.
Now, listen up. Buckle your overalls.
Hold on to your goggles.
-The Vicious6 wants to meet me.
-[minions gasp]
Tomorrow.
-[laughs]
-[all cheering]
[minions] Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
All right, all right. I'm not mini.
Please stop calling me that.
And, also, they haven't accepted me yet.
-[minions groan]
-[speaking Minionese]
Hello, Otto. What is it?
[speaking Minionese]
[sighs] Blah, blah, blah.
-[Otto continues speaking Minionese]
-Uh-huh. Well, that…
-Yes, I…
-[continues speaking Minionese]
I… Okay.
You know what would be fun?
Let's play the quiet game.
[speaking Minionese excitedly]
[holds breath]
Anyway, thanks for
the hard work today, everyone.
I got to go get some rest.
Tomorrow is the biggest day of my life.
[minions cheering]
Watch out, world. Here comes Gru!
-Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
-I'm not…
-[sighs]
-Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
[exclaims]
[Gru sighs]
These guys are the best.
I can't believe it.
[Bob whimpering]
Uh, Mini-Boss?
[speaking Minionese]
Yeah, I get it,
but I need a good night's sleep,
so get out.
Oh. [speaking Minionese]
Okay, fine, fine.
Because you had a nightmare.
But just tonight.
[speaks Minionese excitedly]
I'm not buying
the nightmare story, though.
[sighs]
[Kevin] Excuse-a.
[speaking Minionese]
-Oh, really? You too?
-Mmm-hmm.
Get in.
-Pank you.
-Good night.
Good night.
Yes, yes, yes. Good night.
-[shouts] Good night!
-[Gru gasps]
[sighs] I just want to get some sleep.
[chorus]
♪ VNC! ♪
Breaking news.
The Vicious6 is ready
to rewrite the rules of villainy.
Villains of the world,
in three days,
when the clock strikes midnight
and the Chinese New Year begins,
this bad boy's power
is gonna be unleashed.
With the power of the Zodiac,
we're gonna take out
the Anti-Villain League.
And the Vicious6 will be
the most powerful villains on the planet.
Can you dig it?
Do I dig it? Do I dig it?
I don't dig it. There's nothing to dig.
They thought they could
leave me for dead, huh?
Kick me to the curb
like a piece of old meat?
Oh, they got no idea what's coming.
Ha-ha!
-Um…
-Oh, I'm gonna make them suffer
-for what they've done to me.
-Mr. Knuckles?
-Oh, boy.
-Hey, Mr. Knuckles.
What?
We, uh, just wanted to make sure
we'd be getting paid this week.
What a mouth on you.
I'm paying you with knowledge.
You are? Oh!
Lesson one: always be prepared.
Lesson two:
the Belgian five-armed nose pick.
And lesson three: the Lithuanian haircut.
[screams]
[men grunting]
[chuckles] That's worth
all the money in the world.
-[men groan]
-Hey, guys, forget about it.
You're gonna get paid.
But first, we got to get my stone back.
♪ I see a bad Gru a-rising ♪
[scatting guitar riff]
♪ I see a villain on his way ♪
Yee-haw!
♪ I'm gonna interview with my heroes ♪
[grunting rhythmically]
♪ They're going to love me
'Cause I'm the best ♪
[imitates drum fill]
♪ Don't mess up tonight ♪
[grunts]
♪ You're going to join the Vicious6
Yeah ♪
♪ There is a bad Gru on the rise ♪
Guys!
[speaking Minionese]
Oh, you want to come.
-[speaking Minionese]
-[Stuart] Yeah.
Right, right. Okay.
[sighs]
When you guys tracked me down
and responded to my "help wanted" ad,
I was like,
"Who are these tiny tater tots?
"And where did they get so much denim?"
[scoffs]
[rain pattering]
[minions whimpering outside]
[Gru] And you just wouldn't quit.
[shivering, teeth chattering]
[sneezing]
[sighs] All right,
I surrender. Come on in.
-[speaking Minionese]
-[minions cheer]
[speaking Minionese]
We've had some great times since then,
but the thing is,
the Vicious6, they're the big leagues,
and you guys are great,
and so, the job you did on the lair,
A-plus.
It's just… What I was thinking is that
there are a lot of other villains
in the world. You know?
[speaking Minionese]
[groans] Never mind.
Look, I think
I just need to fly solo on this.
See you later, alligators.
[speaking Minionese]
-[Otto] Kevin? Kevin!
-[sighs, speaks Minionese]
[speaking Minionese]
[sighs in exasperation]
[continues in Minionese]
-[Kevin] Otto. Otto.
-[continues in Minionese]
Hide and seek.
Hide and seek? Hide and seek.
[speaks Minionese excitedly]
-[counting in Minionese]
-[Kevin speaks Minionese]
Go, go, go!
-[tires screech]
-[bicycle bell rings]
Hey, I'm walking here!
Whoa!
Ooh.
Here we go.
-[tires screech]
-[drivers exclaim]
["Vehicle" by Gary Clark Jr.
playing on speakers]
♪ That I love ya, I need ya ♪
♪ I want ya, got to have you, child… ♪
Excuse me. Sir?
[growling]
I was just wondering if you're no good.
Oh, you're good. My mistake.
[exclaims]
Oh, oh, sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
I was just, uh, trying out
this new invention of mine.
I call it Sticky Fingers.
Or Smart Goo.
I haven't quite landed on the name yet.
Come here.
I overheard you were looking
for something… special.
[Gru] Uh, yes. I was hoping…
[enunciating] You're no good.
[laughs]
I think you'll enjoy listening
in booth three.
-Right this way.
-[exclaims]
-[Otto laughs]
-[minions gasp]
-[speaking Minionese, laughing]
-[shushing]
[Boccherini's "String Quintet in E Major"
playing on speakers]
["Cat Scratch Fever" by Ted Nugent
This is it. Mum's the word.
Keep it down. Good luck.
Let 'em have it, son.
Thanks, Mr…
Nefario.
That's Dr. Nefario.
-Here, take this.
-Um…
If you ever get famous,
remember who gave you your first gadget.
Okay.
♪ Wouldn't blame him if he said to me ♪
♪ You're no good, you're no good… ♪
[knock at door]
Try backwards.
Ah.
[song playing in reverse]
[male voice] Welcome to the Vicious6.
-Whoa.
-[bell dings]
-[song continues playing]
-That is pretty--
Whoa!
-[elevator bell dings]
-[Gru screams, grunts]
[muzak playing softly]
Hello. [chuckles nervously]
[grunts, clears throat]
Everybody here for the interview?
Me too.
So, what do you guys got going on later?
Are you up to no good?
You gonna get into some mischief?
[growls softly]
Okay.
-[crackles]
-[Belle Bottom] Send the first one in.
They're ready to see you, Mr. Gru.
Oh, good.
Great. Oh…
[chuckles nervously]
[gasps]
[grunts nervously]
[doors sliding shut]
[gasps]
[Gru clears throat]
[loudly] Distinguished villains,
my name is Gru.
I feel like I'm talking too loud
even though our proximity
doesn't require this kind of volume.
[Gru's voice echoing]
[clears throat]
If you told me when I was ten
that I would have the chance
to fill the shoes
of my favorite villain ever,
Wild Knuckles,
I would say,
"You got rocks in your head."
But now that I'm 11 and three-quarters,
it makes a lot more sense.
All right, who let the kid in?
I thought he was a tiny man.
What's wrong with you?
You seriously think
a puny little child can be a villain?
Um, yes. I… I am pretty despicable.
You don't want to cross me.
Evil is for adults
who steal powerful ancient stones
and wreak havoc.
[gasps]
And not for tubby little punks
who should be at school, learning,
taking a recess,
sucking his thumb.
-[villains laughing]
-"Sucking his…"
Come back when you've done something
to impress me.
[loudly] Who's next?
I am Wing Man,
the next member of the Vicious6.
Behold, the power of flight!
[exclaims, yelling]
All right, joke's over.
Showtime.
[grunting] This is a big one.
[villains grunting]
Yeah, yeah. To the left. That's right.
[clicking]
[yelps]
[muffled grunting]
[panting]
[Wing Man screaming]
Bring him in, bring him in, boys.
Everybody pile on!
[gasps] He took the stone!
I'll get him!
[grunts]
[Gru exclaims]
-[Belle Bottom] Lock down the building.
-[Stronghold grunts angrily]
[grunting excitedly]
-[alarm ringing]
-Oh!
Oh!
-[customers mumbling]
-What?
[hesitates]
Nothing to see here.
Oh, look at you.
Frampton Comes Alive! Nice choice.
[gasps]
I…
Just keep walking.
[vehicles honking]
Who the heck is that? A kid?
[grunts]
-[Kevin clears throat]
-Oh, guys.
Bello.
Mini-Boss!
What are you doing here?
[speaking Minionese]
Okay, just get on.
-Which way did he go?
-There's that little thief!
Go! Go, go, go!
Split up!
[minions whimpering]
Knock, knock. Delivery.
[groans]
[speaking Minionese]
[all screaming]
-That demon child!
-[yells]
Otto, take the stone back to the lair.
I'll distract them.
Go! Go, go, go!
[Nun-Chuck and Jean-Clawed yelling]
[hesitates, exclaims]
[Gru] Ugh, not now.
-Come on, come on!
-[screaming]
[growls]
-Oh!
-[yells]
[strains, grunts]
[minions screaming]
[distorted, slow-motion screaming]
[screams]
Yeah, baby.
[laughs]
I'll handle this.
-[gasping]
-[laughs]
[whimpering]
Hope you enjoy
the rest of your short life.
Please work. Come on, come on, come on!
[yelling]
We're coming for you, tiny man.
[all cheering]
-[minions cheering]
-Josh, pump it up.
Up, up, up!
♪ All the young dudes ♪
♪ Hey, dudes! ♪
♪ Carry the news… ♪
They all said
the kid couldn't be a real villain.
Well…
This kid just stole something
from the worst villains in the world.
[cheering]
When I bring it back to them,
they are going to say…
[gasps dramatically]
"We have made a terrible mistake.
"Please join us. Please, Gru."
And I will say, "Yes!
"I will be the newest member
of the Vicious6."
Now all I need is Otto.
Where is Otto?
Otto le come-ay.
No, not "Otto le come-ay."
He needs to "come-ay" now.
[yelling, laughing]
[minions grunting]
-Otto!
-Mini-Boss!
There you are.
Oh, you got it?
[speaking Minionese]
Is this…
Are you pulling on my legs right now?
Otto, where is the stone?
[speaking Minionese]
[Otto continues narrating story]
[gasps, screams]
[straining]
Over there.
[continues narrating, yells]
Oh, no!
[continues narrating]
[quacks]
[both yelling]
[continues narrating]
-[frantic quacking]
-[grunting]
[all cheering]
[Otto continues narrating]
[exclaims in awe]
Mi amor. Mi amor.
I love you.
[speaking Minionese]
[Otto continues narrating]
[kissing]
[speaking Minionese]
[grunts in frustration]
Did you just trade my future
for a Pet Rock?!
Uh…
Sí?
[sighs] Okay.
Otto, where was this birthday party?
[speaking Minionese]
This is unacceptable. Unacceptable!
I told you guys that
you weren't ready for the big leagues,
and you have proven me correct.
[speaking Minionese]
All you do is mess everything up.
Up? Pump it up!
-♪ Do a little dance, make a little love ♪
-[groans in frustration]
[speaking Minionese]
[music stops]
[grunts angrily] My mom was right.
You do not belong here.
You're fired!
[minions gasp]
I'm going to find that stone.
When I get home, you all better be gone.
Mini-Boss… [speaking Minionese]
-And, Otto, close your yapper!
-Oh.
-[whispers] Josh.
-Sí, sí.
♪ I'll say good-bye to love ♪
♪ No one ever cared
If I should live or die ♪
Gru. [speaking Minionese]
Por favor. Por favor.
Kevin, no. I will be better off on my own.
♪ And all I know of love is
How to live without it ♪
-♪ I just can't seem to find it ♪
-[thunder rumbling]
♪ So I've made my mind up ♪
♪ I must live my life alone ♪
♪ And though it's not the easy way
I guess I've always known ♪
♪ I'd say good-bye to love ♪
♪ There are no tomorrows
For this heart of mine ♪
-♪ Surely time will lose… ♪
-[shouts, speaks Minionese]
[screaming]
♪ And I'll find that there is
Someone to believe in and to live for ♪
Mini-Boss!
[panting]
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I thought you'd be impressed.
Could I just speak
to Belle Bottom? She'll…
[Gru screams]
[grunts, gasps]
Wild Knuckles! [exclaims]
You're alive?
Wow, my favorite villain
is also my kidnapper?
This could be a great opportunity
if you don't kill me.
Shut up and give me the stone.
Oh, yes, the stone.
Here's the thing about that.
Kind of a funny story.
Give it to him!
[Gru] And it's all going to go south
very quickly.
What the heck is this?
[grunting]
[Gru screaming]
Where is it, boy?
I don't have it! I don't have it!
I know you're hiding it somewhere.
I'm not. I'm not. I swear.
Cross my heart and hope to die,
stick a needle in my eye.
Don't actually do that, though.
Somebody bring me a phone.
Call home.
It's ransom time.
No, no, no!
My mom will probably pay you to keep me!
[chuckles] Good one.
Call!
[dialing]
[cooing]
[minions speaking indistinctly]
-[shushing]
-[telephone ringing faintly]
La telefono.
[speaking Minionese]
[laughs]
[screams]
[telephone ringing]
Bello. La casa de Mini-Boss.
-Who is this?
-Kevin. Kevin, le minion.
-"Kevin le" what?
-Le minion.
You kidding me?
You got henchmen? [chuckles]
-Well, that's the end of that.
-Mini-Boss?
Listen, you,
bring the stone to me in San Francisco.
-6830 Green Street. Got it?
-[speaking Minionese]
Now, you got two days,
or you are never going to see
your little boss again.
[gasps]
Bello? Bello. [gasps]
[speaking Minionese]
Otto… [speaking Minionese]
Uh… [sucks teeth]
[describing in Minionese]
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Huh?
No… [speaks Minionese, sighs]
[speaking Minionese angrily]
[speaking Minionese]
Otto. [speaking Minionese angrily]
Okay. Sí, sí. [speaking Minionese]
[gasps, speaks Minionese]
[over stereo]
♪ Hey, ho, let's go ♪
♪ Hey, ho ♪
[speaking Minionese]
Okay. Go, go, go.
♪ They're going through a tight wind ♪
♪ The kids are losing their minds ♪
-[motorcycle engine idling]
-Oh?
Oh.
Oh, the stone!
[speaking Minionese]
Gave that to my uncle.
It's more his style.
Oh!
[gasps]
La… La… La stone-a!
Kevin! Kevin!
[shouts]
La stone-a!
[speaking Minionese]
[groans] I told you.
I don't know where he went,
you stupid Twinkies.
[grunts angrily]
[exclaims, yells]
[chuckles nervously, speaks Minionese]
Pank you. Bye-bye.
Huh?
Oh, not cool, man.
[speaking Minionese]
[bus honking]
San Pan-pisco.
[speaking Minionese]
Vamos!
[hesitating]
[speaking Minionese]
Let's rock and roll.
Time to get our stone back.
We're coming for you, Mr. Gru.
Hallelujah!
[villains yelling, laughing]
[whoops, laughs]
Smash! Smash!
[organ playing dramatic riff]
[speaking Minionese]
[whooping]
[woman on PA]
Flight 1109 will now depart at gate 27B.
Bello. [speaking Minionese]
San Francisco? Okay.
How will you be paying?
Uh…
[Bob] No problemo.
Oh, great.
You know, if you have any hair balls,
we can upgrade you to first class.
-[woman] Get out.
-[Kevin sighs]
[speaking Minionese]
[man] So there I was.
We lost thrust in both engines,
and I had to turn back at LaGuardia.
[all laughing]
Ooh-la-la.
-Hey, Sally.
-Hey.
[indistinct conversation]
♪ I wanna fly like an eagle ♪
♪ To the sea ♪
♪ Fly like an eagle
Let my spirit carry me ♪
Okay. Vamos.
[speaking Minionese]
Ooh.
[clears throat, speaks Minionese]
[continues over speakers]
[babbles, blows raspberries] Good flight.
[grunting] Bello. Peanut?
Oh, yes, please.
Peanut.
-Peanut.
-Uh…
Peanut? Peanut!
Peanut?
Hey, baby, peanut?
[baby crying]
Aw.
[speaking Minionese]
Hey!
[both speaking Minionese]
[humming Johann Strauss II's
"The Blue Danube"]
-[speaks Minionese frantically]
-[continues humming]
[man and woman gasp]
-[screams]
-[hums, gasps]
[all screaming]
[screaming]
["The Blue Danube" playing]
-[retches]
-[speaks Minionese]
[gags]
[sighs]
[continues crying]
Oh, bello!
Bello.
[groans]
-[air whooshing]
-[gasps, screams]
[muffled screaming]
[beeping]
[speaks Minionese]
[speaking Minionese]
[people gasp]
You see me, you see me not.
[laughs, exclaims playfully]
[screaming]
[yells]
[music crescendoes]
[music ends]
[people cheering]
[whooping, laughing triumphantly]
No. No "ha-ha."
You got real moxie, kid,
stealing from the Vicious6.
I got moxie, really?
[gasps] Did I just receive a compliment
from Wild Knuckles?
Oh, all my dreams
are coming true right now!
Well, it's about to become your nightmare.
Welcome to my newest torture device,
the Disco Inferno.
[machine whirring]
["More, More, More"
by Andrea True Connection playing]
Your Minions better get here
by sundown tomorrow,
because if 48 hours of disco
don't kill you,
the blade will.
[yelps]
No, no, no, no, no!
[Wild Knuckles laughs]
[yelling]
[Otto grunting]
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
[gurgling] Stone-a!
-Stone-a! Stone-a!
-Hey!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
[yelling]
[all cheering]
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a…
[speaking Minionese]
Look-a the map-a.
[continues speaking Minionese]
Gru…
[minions groaning,
complaining in Minionese]
-[screaming]
-Bob!
[yelling]
[screaming]
[laughing]
Bello! [laughs]
[both panting]
[speaking Minionese]
-[bell ringing]
-[mimicking bell]
[driver] Next stop, Green Street.
Bye-bye.
[arguing in Minionese]
Hey, hey. Look-a.
Come-ay! Come-ay!
[speaking Minionese]
[straining, sighing]
-["More, More, More" continues playing]
-[Kevin gasps] Mini-Boss.
[all grunting]
[yells]
-[Stuart speaks Minionese]
-Stuart.
-Mini-Boss.
-No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
[Bob gasps]
[speaking Minionese]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[yelling]
[speaking Minionese]
[mimics bird call]
[Bob gibbering excitedly]
[speaking Minionese]
[henchmen grunting]
Okay. Go, go, go.
[henchman] Hmm.
Hey. Go, go, go.
Hey, wait a minute.
[whimpering] Bello.
-Oh, no! Bob!
-[Stuart yelling]
[Bob speaks Minionese]
[Stuart and Kevin shouting]
[henchman yells]
Trespassers!
-Get 'em!
-Hey, you. Come back here!
-Go, go!
-[grunts]
Kevin! Oh, okay. [laughs]
[henchmen panting]
[speaking Minionese]
Get your little butts back here!
[shouting in Minionese]
[chimes tinkling]
Okay, now, you might feel a little pinch.
-[minions yelling]
-[henchman laughs]
Got you now.
Time to break some bones.
[yells]
-[chimes tinkling]
-[muffled grunting, yelling]
-[henchman yells]
-[screams]
Any plans for the weekend?
[sighs]
Take five deep breaths.
I'll be right back.
Hey! You like picking on little guys, huh?
Go take a nap, old lady.
[laughing]
Old lady?
[grunts]
-[yells]
-[groans]
I am a master
of the ancient Shaolin art of kung fu.
[gasps]
[henchmen yelling]
[all grunting]
Huh? [groans]
[yelling]
-Ha!
-[grunting]
[henchman groans]
[shouting]
[speaks Minionese]
Get lost! [chuckling]
-[minions laughing]
-[blows raspberry]
If you come back to our place,
you're dead.
Come-ay. [speaking Minionese]
Pank you. Pank you…
[shushing]
You can thank me by going away.
I'm working.
[speaking Minionese]
You want to learn kung fu? [laughs]
Ah, Kevin. [speaks Minionese]
Bello, chica.
[speaking Minionese]
…kung fu por smoochie, smoochie? Mmm-mmm?
[yells in Minionese]
My teaching days are over.
This is my life now.
[whimpers, speaks Minionese]
…kung fu para…
para save-a le Mini-Boss. Por favor.
[all whimpering]
Ay-ya. Fine.
I will teach you.
[minions cheering]
[Gru's Mom] Hey!
-Those are not for you.
-Excuse-a, excuse-a.
The name of the game is sell, sell, sell!
[speaking Minionese]
[Tupperware makes fart sounds]
-[laughing]
-[fart sounds continue]
[harmonizing with fart sounds]
[rumbling]
-[saw buzzing]
-[gasping]
What?
-[Stronghold grunts]
-[women screaming]
-[villains yelling]
-[people screaming]
Where's Gru?
Huh. How should I know?
What's with the costumes?
Halloween was four months ago.
You look stupid.
-Buzz off. Shoo!
-[grunts]
I'm getting my meat tenderizer.
Let me help you with that, dearie.
-[Gru's Mom] Uh-uh-uh. Don't touch me.
-Now, where's the boy?
[stuttering, speaking Minionese]
Oh, I didn't mean to scare you.
Don't worry. We're not mad at him.
We just want to
hire him.
[speaking Minionese]
Where is he?
Wild Knuckles, San Pan-pisco.
Wild Knuckles is alive?
And working with the kid. Hmm.
We're going to San Francisco.
-[all laughing]
-Let's hit it.
[angelic choir harmonizing]
[Gru's Mom grunting]
You had better be paying for my roof.
[minions] Ay-yi-yi.
-[minions gasping, exclaiming]
-Pretty groovy, huh?
-[door slams shut]
-[Master Chow grunts]
We begin with a basic kick.
[yells] Now you.
[minions yell]
[yells]
Okay.
No kicking.
This is a melon hammer. It's a weapon.
This is Fred. He is a dummy.
Never underestimate a dummy.
-[scoffs] Dummy.
-Bello, Fred.
Now attack!
[yelling]
[cheering, whooping] Stuart! Stuart!
[muffled grunting]
[mutters angrily in Minionese]
Fred.
Doubt tells me I cannot break this wood.
-Uh-huh.
-But doubt exists only in the mind.
You know what I say to my mind?
[exclaims]
Now you.
[hesitates]
-[Stuart] Mmm-hmm.
-[groans]
[exclaims]
[yells]
[groans]
[sighs] Kevin, Kevin, Kevin.
-[yelling]
-[screaming]
[speaking Minionese]
-[pained grunt]
-[gasps, whimpers]
Okay. Clearly, we are not ready
for philosophy.
Let's just train.
-["Funkytown" playing on stereo]
-[grunting rhythmically]
[exclaims rhythmically]
♪ A-won't you take me to Funkytown ♪
[song stops]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay, okay, okay.
[exclaims unenthusiastically]
-[song resumes]
-Yeah!
-♪ Won't you take me to Funkytown ♪
-[all exclaim]
-[minions screaming]
-[song stops]
-[stick clatters]
-[Kevin screams, exclaims]
Rest up.
Tomorrow's going to be even worse.
[Wild Knuckles] What, you're quitting?
I told you, when I get that stone,
we're gonna be unstoppable.
I have had enough!
There's nothing sadder
than an aging villain.
So long, old man.
-Guys, come on. We're a team.
-[door slams]
["More, More, More"
continues playing faintly]
♪ More, more, more ♪
♪ How do you like… ♪
[song stops]
♪ How do you like it?
How do you like… ♪
[groans]
Is this heaven?
I just had to fire my henchmen.
You know why?
'Cause they weren't getting the job done.
Okay, I'm just gonna untie you now
because I, uh…
I need you to do some stuff for me
around the house.
And it might be, you know,
kind of nice to have
a little company around here.
Oh… Oh, yeah.
Two villains just doing some chores.
Who knows what kind of trouble
we could get into?
[chuckles maliciously, grunts]
What's that? That's your evil chuckle?
Obviously.
Well, it stinks. You sound like
a clown who swallowed a kazoo.
Really? Well, you look like a wizard
going through an end-of-life crisis.
-[grunts]
-Easy there, Don Rickles.
[Gru] Who's Don Rickles?
[Otto groaning] Stone-a.
Stone-a.
Stone-a!
Stone-a…
Dude. [laughs]
I thought we lost you there for a minute.
-[speaking Minionese]
-Hey, chill, chill, chill…
Hey, you want to try this on, little dude?
[speaks Minionese]
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
La stone-a! [kissing]
Hey, hey, hey, soul brother,
where you jettin' off to?
[speaking Minionese] San Pan-pisco.
Frisco disco!
It's your lucky day, kid.
I'm headed up the coast.
I could drop you off on the way.
Yee-haw! [cheers]
[speaking Minionese]
…la stone-a!
Oh, look-a!
[speaking Minionese] Hey.
[laughs]
Hey, yo, hermano!
[horn blares]
[mimics horn blaring]
-[laughs]
-[speaking Minionese]
Start with the pool.
This place has got to be spick-and-span.
[Gru] What are you doing?
You look like the overcooked turkey
my mom makes on Thanksgiving.
[screams] Oh, God.
Oh, yeah. I forgot to mention,
the pool is filled with my pet crocodiles.
[grunts] Yeah, well, well,
doesn't scare me.
[gasps, grunts]
Be careful. I can't have you lose an arm,
because I need you to change
some light bulbs after this.
Here, let me show you how it's done.
Betsy, knock it off.
Hey!
[grunts] Oh, no.
Marvin, no, no. Stop that.
[Wild Knuckles yelling]
Whoa! Help! Oh, no.
The net!
I got you! I got you!
I don't got you.
[grunting]
Take my hand.
[both straining]
I got you!
[both grunt]
[both panting]
You could've run, but you… but you didn't.
I told you,
you are my favorite villain in the world.
I could not let you
get eaten by crocodiles.
Even though that would've been
kind of cool to watch.
So… So you want to be
a great villain, huh?
[gasps] That's all I ever wanted.
You want, uh… I don't know, you want me…
You want me to teach you a thing or two?
Mmm-hmm!
[Master Chow, echoing]
Many fighters have asked me,
how did I become a great master?
Hey, look-a!
[grunting]
Even the smallest of us
are capable of great things.
You just dig down deep,
find your inner beast, and…
[roaring]
Gesundheit?
Now you try.
[roars]
[coughs]
[blows raspberry]
[roars weakly]
[sighs]
Find your inner beast!
[minions whimper]
Stop this kick.
[grunts]
[screams]
We have a lot more work to do.
-[Jackson Wang's "Born to Be Alive" plays]
-[all exclaiming]
[yells]
[minions grunting, yelling]
[speaking Minionese]
[speaking Minionese frantically]
[humming]
[speaking Minionese]
[laughs]
-[screams]
-[barking happily]
[sneezes]
[gasps, apologizes in Minionese]
[speaking Minionese]
-[shouts in Minionese]
-[yelling playfully]
[speaking Minionese]
[exclaims]
-[Bob exclaims]
-[Stuart farts]
-[minions screaming]
-[objects clattering]
Kevin, Stuart and Bob, you are ready.
[cheering]
[Kevin speaking Minionese]
No, no, no, no, no!
Ready for your junior kung fu
achievement badges.
[sighs] They're dead.
[minions cheering in distance]
First rule of heists,
always stay in character.
Got it, Grandpa.
Say, do you mind if we use the john?
Poindexter here
can't hold it in till we get home.
Uh-huh.
[gasps] The Bank of Evil.
[indistinct conversations]
It's showtime, kid.
Follow my lead, and don't forget your cue.
Hello. I… I just need to cash this.
Wowie zowie! What a big bank.
How many security guards are in here?
Who's this little guy?
Well, that's my grandson,
who still has not learned
that children should be seen
and not heard.
[laughs] Kids.
I actually have a son of my own.
Ugh. He looks weird.
[chuckles] Don't listen to him.
Your son is very, uh, cute.
[Perkins grunts softly]
[yells] Oh, no!
[groaning]
Oh, help! I'm seeing a white light.
Helen, I'm coming for ya!
Helen, I'm coming for ya.
Oh. Help!
-[groans]
-Help my pop-pop!
Somebody help him!
Huh?
-My grandpa!
-[man] We need a doctor!
This is the big one.
[groans, yells]
[Wild Knuckles] You hear that?
It's the sweet sound of angels.
-Help!
-[grunts]
Do something!
My life is flashing before my eyes.
[grunting]
No, no, no. The other way.
The other way. [groans]
[exclaims, screams]
All right, everyone stand back.
-[defibrillator powering up]
-Uh-oh.
-Clear!
-No, wait a minute. Wait.
[groans]
Don't give up on me now, buddy.
No, no, no, I'm feeling better.
Clear!
[grunting]
[medic] Maximum charge.
-Clear!
-Thank you.
You saved my grandpa.
Did we… Did we do the heist?
[chuckles] Grandpas say
the darndest things.
You dropped these.
[Wild Knuckles groans]
Look what I got!
Hey. Not bad. Not bad at all.
We make a good team.
We do?
Oh, yeah. Hey, we got to keep at it.
Wait till you see
what I'm gonna teach you next.
I cannot wait.
[Wild Knuckles] Oh, this is gonna be fun.
-[Stuart grunting instructions]
-[Bob] Mmm-hmm.
[exclaiming fiercely]
[speaking Minionese]
[yelling]
Hoo! Mini-Boss!
Okay, Stuart… Bob… [speaking Minionese]
Time to strike!
Mini-Boss! [speaking Minionese]
[screaming]
[laughing maniacally]
[yells] They're not here.
Fan out and find them.
[speaking Minionese]
[sirens wailing]
Something big's going down in Frisco.
Oh! Look-a.
[fireworks exploding]
[Biker] Whoo, there it is.
[speaking Minionese]
[panicked whimpering]
It's been one heck of a ride, little man.
Oh, dude.
You know, I'm gonna miss you.
[speaking Minionese]
Hey, soul brother, good luck!
[speaks Minionese]
-[funky music playing]
-[gasps, exclaims]
[speaking Minionese]
[exclaims in awe]
[stammers, screams]
My friend, you're now gonna learn
from the old school.
[both gasp]
Oh, no.
[gasps]
[glass crunching underfoot]
I can't believe they did this to me!
I… I taught them everything they know!
We were a team!
[sighs] I give up.
Hey, you are a great bad guy,
and they are stupid idiots.
Only dream I ever had
was doing bad stuff with my buddies.
Now look at me. Old, alone.
Well, you are old, but you're not alone.
[groans]
All right.
Listen up, buster.
We are starting a new team,
and it's going to be called
"The Terrible Twos."
We can find a better name later,
but right now
we're going to find that stone
and show everybody that you still got it.
Come on. You're just a little kid.
It's over. Go home.
-But you said we--
-Go home!
[crowd cheering]
[girl] Come on, come on. Let's go!
[Otto whooping, speaking Minionese]
[exclaiming]
Otto?
Otto!
-Yee-haw! [laughing]
-Otto!
Otto! It's Mini-Boss!
[gasps] Mini-Boss!
[laughs triumphantly]
-Mini-Boss!
-Otto!
[Otto] Look-a! Look-a!
-[speaking Minionese] Stone-a.
-[gasps]
You found the stone.
Otto, I'm so proud of you.
[chuckles shyly]
All right, we don't have much time.
We got to get this to Wild Knuckles.
-Okay. Okay.
-[gasps]
Get him!
-[angelic music plays]
-[Otto yelps]
[exclaiming]
-[Gru and Otto scream]
-[Otto] Go, go, go!
[yelling]
Long time, no see, punk.
I'll take that.
-[laughs]
-[sirens wailing]
Yes!
Don't move!
-[growls]
-Right there! Freeze!
Anti-Villain League.
You are under arrest.
[sighs, speaks Minionese]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Everybody.
Did you forget what time it is?
[bell tolls]
Happy New Year!
[laughs maniacally]
[people clamoring]
Fire!
[roars]
[laughs evilly]
[gasps]
[laughs, growls]
[growls]
[exclaims in Minionese]
Stand your ground.
Look out! Whoa!
[roars]
[screams]
[all screaming]
[laughs]
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-[screaming]
Where do you think you're going, hmm?
You stole from us,
and now you're gonna pay!
[yelling]
[screams]
-[panting, speaking Minionese]
-[Belle Bottom cackles]
Enjoy being torn apart.
Hey! [speaking Minionese] …Mini-Boss!
Guys!
Oh. Why don't we make this
a fair fight? [laughs]
[gasps, yells]
[laughing]
[laughs]
-[clucks]
-[Bob giggles]
Oh, you thought I was serious. [laughs]
Run!
[minions shouting]
No! [screams]
-Hello, traitors.
-[gasps]
Remember me?
You.
You can leave me for dead,
you can destroy everything I own,
but I will not let you hurt that kid!
Oh, so you're gonna save the kid?
[laughs] Yeah, you and what army?
-[minions yelling]
-This army!
Okay. This army.
[Kevin snarls]
[villains growling]
[growls]
-[hissing]
-[growling]
[exclaims fiercely]
[bleats fiercely]
[clucking]
[screams]
[minions yelling]
[villains growling]
[screams]
[clucking]
-[hisses]
-[clucks]
[screams]
[whimpering]
[strains, whimpers]
[growls]
[whimpering]
[Master Chow] Dig down deep.
Find your inner beast.
[roaring]
[grunts]
[groans]
[clucks fiercely]
[yells]
[grunting]
[hisses]
[cheeping]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[cheeping]
-[groans]
-[Gru screaming]
[shouts in Minionese]
[grunting in pain]
[Wild Knuckles grunts]
[minions yelling, grunting]
[whimpering]
[growls]
Otto!
Hurry! Faster!
-No!
-[roars]
[snarls]
[screams]
Got you.
[Otto sputters, screams]
[speaking Minionese] Go, go, go!
[gasps]
[Wild Knuckles laughs]
No. [gasps]
[groans]
[screams, grunts]
Get away from him!
Destroy the kid.
[minions yelling]
Oh!
[laughs maliciously]
[villains groaning]
No!
[squeaking]
Hey, hey. How does it feel
to be beaten by a tubby little punk?
[laughs]
[villains squeaking]
You guys were amazing!
The kung fu… Where did that come from?
-Obviously, you guys are rehired.
-[Bob bleating]
[chuckles] Stuart!
[speaking Minionese, laughing]
[laughter]
[squeaking angrily]
-[gasps]
-[man] It's all yours, sir.
[woman] Where do you want it?
Can you feel this, sir? Right here.
Oh, no. Wild Knuckles.
[coughs]
Hey.
You're gonna be okay, right?
Don't worry about me, kid.
I'll be fine.
[Silas] Finally.
You're going away for a long, long time.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't bet on it.
No.
See you soon, kiddo.
[siren wailing]
-[exclaims in Minionese]
-[Bob whimpers]
-[Otto sucks teeth]
-[Stuart sighs]
[minions harmonizing somber melody]
[singing "You Can't Always Get
What You Want" in Minionese]
-[clears throat]
-[singing continues]
Wild Knuckles was my favorite villain.
We didn't have much time together,
but the time we did have,
I'm so grateful for.
I've been thinking about
how you won't see me grow up
or be there for all the terrible things
that I'm going to do.
[voice breaking] And believe me,
there are gonna be some awful things.
[guitar music playing]
[clears throat]
But I'm going to make you proud.
I'm going to be the best villain ever
because of you.
Because you taught me what matters.
You can't do anything alone.
Find your tribe,
and never, ever let them go.
Otto?
Sí. [sucks teeth]
[singing "You Can't Always Get
What You Want" in Minionese]
[all yelling frantically]
[minions grunting]
[chuckles nervously]
[continues singing]
-[minions singing along]
-[clapping rhythmically]
You better stay out of trouble, kid.
I will lead a good and honest life.
[chuckles maliciously]
[gasps] You're alive?
Oh! [chuckles softly]
You just blew my mind.
How did you do that?
[laughs]
I cannot wait to fake my own death
to avoid the authorities.
Shoot for the moon, kid.
Shoot for the moon.
[chuckles] See you later, suckers!
[all cheering]
♪ You can't always get what you want ♪
-[Otto shouting in Minionese]
-♪ You can't always get what you want ♪
♪ You can't always get what you want ♪
♪ But if you try sometimes ♪
♪ You just might find
You just might find ♪
♪ You get what you need ♪
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh… ♪
[song fades]
-[doorbell jingles]
-Sorry, we're closed.
Oh!
I just wanted to thank you for this.
Worked like a charm.
All right, let me cut to the chase here.
I need a genius mad scientist.
You want to come work for me?
No, I am done with villainy.
Off to happier horizons.
Good-bye, little chap.
Por favor.
[whimpering]
[minions whimpering]
[cheeps sweetly]
Oh, all right, all right. Fine.
Stop with the face. I'm in.
Want to see something cool?
Oh, are you kidding me?
[women gasp]
[Gru laughing wildly]
[minions] Big Boss! Big Boss!
Big Boss! Big Boss!
[Gru] "Big Boss." I like that.
["Turn Up The Sunshine"
by Diana Ross feat. Tame Impala playing]
♪ We can make it further ♪
♪ We running and don't look back ♪
♪ It's a light at the end of the tunnel
If you stay on track ♪
♪ But I know any minute
When your fingers turn it up like snap ♪
♪ So hard to lose like that ♪
♪ Hey, let's do it ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ Think about it ♪
♪ All the boys and girls ♪
♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ Said it's been a long night
Long night ♪
♪ Waiting for the light
Waiting for the light ♪
♪ Let's do it ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ We gotta turn it up ♪
♪ Make it hard to lose like that ♪
♪ If this weather makes you frown ♪
♪ And some people get you down ♪
♪ Remember ♪
♪ Love, like sound ♪
♪ It's better when it's loud ♪
♪ And if there's no song inside ♪
♪ We can bring the light together ♪
♪ Day or night ♪
♪ We're shining from inside ♪
♪ Turn up the…
Turn it up ♪
♪ Turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ Turn up the…
Turn it up ♪
♪ Turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ Think about it ♪
♪ All the boys and girls ♪
♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ Said it's been a ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♪ We gotta turn it up ♪
♪ Make it hard to lose like that ♪
["Funkytown" by St. Vincent playing]
♪ Gotta make a move
To a town that's right for me ♪
♪ Time to keep me movin'
Keep me movin' with some energy ♪
♪ Well, I talk about it, talk about it
Talk about it, talk about it ♪
♪ Talk about it, talk about it
Talk about movin' ♪
♪ Gotta move on ♪
♪ Won't you take me to Funkytown ♪
[music continues]
["You're No Good" by Weyes Blood playing]
♪ Feeling better now that we're through ♪
♪ Feeling better 'cause I'm over you ♪
♪ I learned my lesson and it left a scar ♪
♪ Now I see how you really are ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
♪ I broke a heart that's gentle and true ♪
♪ Well, I broke a heart
Over someone like you ♪
♪ I'll beg his forgiveness
On bended knee ♪
♪ I wouldn't blame him if he said to me ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
[music continues]
♪ I'm turning you down, baby
And I'm going my way ♪
♪ Forget about you, baby
'Cause I'm leaving to stay ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪
♪ Oh, oh, no ♪
♪ You're no good
You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪ Baby, you're no good ♪