Illumination!
(LAUGHING, WHOOPING)
(GRUNTS) Minion!
Yeah
Ooh
When you wish upon a star
Your dreams will take
you very far
But when you wish upon a
dream
Life ain't always
what it seems
Oh, yeah
Freeze! AVL!
No matter who you are...
Hey! Hey!
(YELLS)
Stop right there!
Grab her!
Yeah, baby!
Attention, all units.
Look out!
(LAUGHS) You like that?
Hey!
Shining star for you to see
What your life can truly be
What your life
can truly be
Ooh, baby!
The Anti-Villain League
can't catch this.
Guess who stole the map.
Hallelujah! (LAUGHS)
Yeah! I got this.
Ha-ha, good work.
The map to the legendary
Zodiac Stone.
We will become
the most powerful
villains in the world.
(ALL CHEERING)
Okay, let's get a move on.
We leave for Asia tonight.
Okay, let's see here.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm in.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Hello, beautiful.
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(GASPS)
What?
(CHITTERS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
Ha-ha, yes!
The Zodiac Stone.
Oh.
(LAUGHS TRIUMPHANTLY)
Soon, the power of these
unstoppable beasts
will be ours.
(GASPS)
Oh, for crying out loud.
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
Whoa! (YELLS)
(YELLING)
Hurry up!
I got a bunch of
deadly tchotchkes on my tail.
Roger that on the copy.
Step on it, sister.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hurry up! Come on!
(YELLS)
Off! Off!
(CREATURES SCREAMING)
(LAUGHS TRIUMPHANTLY)
I got it. I got the stone.
Party's over, old man.
The Vicious6 has a new head
honcho. (CHUCKLES)
You just got played
for a sucker!
(GRUNTS) Hold on.
I started this group.
We're a team.
Where's your loyalty?
Oh, please. We're villains.
There's no such thing.
It's time for the next
generation. (LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING)
(SINGING IN MANDARIN)
Bang, bang
(SINGING RESUMES IN MANDARIN)
(MINIONS YELLING)
Hey
Bang, bang
TEACHER: Quiet down, class.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
People, people.
So, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
GIRL: Ooh, ooh.
Samantha.
I want to be a doctor.
Wonderful.
Ooh, ooh!
Bradley.
I want to be a teacher.
No, you do not.
Me, me!
Yes.
I want to be a fireman
who is also the president
and also drives
race cars. Yeah.
Exciting.
And what about you, Gru?
Gru?
Me?
I want to be...
a supervillain.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Supervillain?
Supervillain.
Loser!
(BELL RINGS)
I'm having a bad, bad day
It's about time that
I get my way
Kelly!
Daddy!
Brett!
Mom!
Gru!
Kiss-a la mama!
Oh, my favorite
tiny relatives.
(MINIONS YELLING EXCITEDLY)
Oh, no. Guys, come on.
(KISSING)
Hey. I got an image
to uphold here.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay.
Hey, are you guys pumped
for the movie?
Let's go!
Hey, hey, hey!
(JAWS THEME PLAYING
IN BACKGROUND)
(FART BOMB EXPLODES)
WOMAN: Oh, no!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
WOMAN IN MOVIE: Shark!
A shark!
(ALL LAUGHING)
I am a pinball wizard.
(LAUGHS)
Swish. Swish. Swish.
Swish. Swish.
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
(MINION EXCLAIMS)
Bello.
(MINION BABBLING)
(CHEERING)
Yeah!
WOMAN: Everything you got.
A little more. Come on.
(SIGHS)
WOMAN: Put some of those
sprinkles on there.
I like those sprinkles.
Cheese ray! Cheese ray!
Cheese ray!
(LAUGHS)
Don't cheese me, bro.
(LAUGHS WICKEDLY)
Pank you!
Mmm.
So creamy, so delicious.
Worth every calorie.
I'm having a bad, bad day
If you take it
personal, that's okay
Watch, this is so fun to
see...
Bills, magazines,
S&H Green Stamps.
Huh?
(EXCLAIMS)
Holy guacamole!
Where can we listen?
Hello, Mr. Gru.
We've received
your application
to the world's
best supervillain
team, the Vicious6.
A recent opening
has become available, and...
And?
...your interview
is tomorrow at noon.
(EXCLAIMS) Dyn-o-mite!
(MINIONS CHEER)
BELLE: Please go to
417 Main Street.
The password is,
"You're no good."
Mmm-hmm.
Now, get up
on the down stroke,
'cause this invitation
is gonna explode, baby.
Explode? Aw.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
(EXPLODES)
(ALL COUGHING)
(TOOTING)
Very big news, Mom!
Mom?
(WOMAN GROANING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
Mom?
(BOTH GROANING)
What?
Mom, who is this sweaty guy?
He's stinking up the house.
I thought you were
cooking cabbage.
He's my new guru.
Blah!
(BABBLING)
Tell your weird buddies
they'd better start pulling
their weight around here,
or I'm kicking them out.
They are killing
my mellow vibes.
(MIMICS COMPLAINING)
GRU'S MOM: Hey!
I heard that!
Come on. Let's go tell the
troops the good news.
Gentlemen, to the basement,
aka our new evil lair.
(EXCLAIMS)
This is fantastic!
Oh, construction
looks great, guys.
(MINIONS CHANTING)
My first evil lair.
Goose bumps!
(EXPLOSION)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Well, you've got
to break a few eggs
to make an omelet.
Am I right?
Oh, great job, Ryan.
What?
I said great job!
Never mind.
Adrien, Mack, looking good.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(CRYING)
Joe, how's the family?
Hey. Good, good.
Okay, everybody,
get over here.
Now, listen up.
Buckle your overalls.
Hold on to your goggles.
The Vicious6 wants to meet me.
Tomorrow.
(LAUGHS)
(ALL CHEERING)
MINIONS: Mini-Boss!
Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
All right, all right.
I'm not mini.
Please stop calling me that.
And also, they haven't
accepted me yet.
(ALL GROAN)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hello, Otto. What is it?
(SIGHS) Blah, blah, blah.
Uh-huh. Well, that...
Yes, I...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
I... Okay.
You know what would be fun?
Let's play the quiet game.
The quiet game! Si, si!
Anyway, thanks for the
hard work today, everyone.
I got to go get some rest.
Tomorrow is the biggest day
of my life.
(ALL CHEERING)
Watch out, world.
Here comes Gru!
Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
I'm not...
(SIGHS)
Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRU SIGHS)
These guys are the best.
I can't believe it.
Uh... Mini-Boss?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Yeah, I get it,
but I need a good night's
sleep, so get out.
Oh. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay, fine, fine.
Because you had a nightmare.
But just tonight.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE EXCITEDLY)
I'm not buying
the nightmare story, though.
KEVIN: Excuse-a.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh, really? You, too?
KEVIN: Mmm-hmm
Get in.
Good night.
Yes, yes, yes. Good night.
Good night!
(GRU EXCLAIMS)
(SIGHS)
I just want to
get some sleep.
(CHORUS SINGING) VNC
Breaking news.
The Vicious6
is ready to rewrite
the rules of villainy.
Villains of the world,
in three days, when the
clock strikes midnight
and the Chinese
New Year begins,
this bad boy's power
is gonna be unleashed.
With the power of the Zodiac,
we're gonna take out
the Anti-Villain League.
And the Vicious6 will be
the most powerful villains
on the planet.
Can you dig it?
Do I dig it? Do I dig it?
I don't dig it.
There's nothing to dig.
They thought they could
leave me for dead, huh?
Kick me to the curb
like a piece of old meat?
Oh, they got no idea
what's coming.
Ha-ha!
Oh, I'm gonna make them suffer
for what they've done to me.
Mr. Knuckles?
Oh, boy.
Hey, Mr. Knuckles.
What?
We just wanted
to make sure we'd be
getting paid this week.
What a mouth on you.
I'm paying you with knowledge.
You are? (EXCLAIMS)
Lesson one,
always be prepared.
Lesson two, the Belgian
eyeball nose pick.
And lesson three,
the Lithuanian haircut.
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS) That's worth
all the money in the world.
Hey, guys, forget about it.
You're gonna get paid.
But first, we got to
get my stone back.
I see a bad Gru a-rising
I see a villain on his way
Yee-haw!
I'm gonna interview
with my heroes
They're going to love me
'cause I'm the best
Don't mess up tonight
You're going to join
the Vicious6, yeah
There is a bad Gru
on the rise
Guys!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh, you want to come.
STUART: Yeah.
Right, right.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
When you guys tracked me down
and responded to my
"help wanted" ad...
...I was like,
"Who are these
tiny tater tots?
"And where did they get
so much denim?"
(MINIONS SHIVERING)
GRU: And you
just wouldn't quit.
(MINIONS SHIVERING)
(SNEEZES)
(SIGHS) All right,
I surrender. Come on in.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MINIONS CHEER)
We've had some
great times since then,
but the thing is,
the Vicious6,
they're the big leagues,
and you guys are great,
and so, the job you did
on the lair...
A-plus.
It's just...
What I was thinking is that
there are a lot of
other villains in the world.
You know?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GROANS) Never mind.
Look, I think I just need
to fly solo on this.
See you later, alligators.
Kevin? Kevin!
Oh... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE AT KEVIN)
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
Otto. Otto.
Hide and seek.
Hide and seek? Hide and seek.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE EXCITEDLY)
Go, go, go!
Hey, I'm walking here!
Whoa!
Ooh.
Here we go.
(DRIVER EXCLAIMS)
That I love ya, I need ya
I want ya
got to have you, child...
Excuse me. Sir?
(GROWLS)
I was just wondering
if you're no good.
(GROWLS)
Oh, you're good. My mistake.
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I was just trying out
this new invention of mine.
I call it Sticky Fingers.
Or Smart Goo.
I haven't quite landed
on the name yet.
Come here.
I overheard you were looking
for something... special.
Uh, yes. I was hoping...
You're no good.
(LAUGHS)
I think you'll enjoy
listening in booth three.
Right this way.
(EXCLAIMS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(OVERLAPPING MUSIC PLAYING)
Cat scratch fever...
This is it. Mum's the word.
Keep it down. Good luck.
Let 'em have it, son.
Thanks, Mister... Nefario.
That's Dr. Nefario.
Here, take this.
If you ever get famous,
remember who gave you
your first gadget.
Okay.
Wouldn't blame him
if he said to me
You're no good
You're no good...
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Try backwards.
Ah.
DISTORTED VOICE:
Welcome to the Vicious6.
That is pretty... Whoa!
(ELEVATOR BELL RINGS)
(GRU GRUNTS)
Hello.
Everybody here
for the interview?
Me, too.
So, what do you guys
got going on later?
Are you up to no good?
You gonna get into
some mischief?
Okay.
BELLE: Send the first one in.
They're ready to
see you, Mr. Gru.
Oh, good.
Great.
Distinguished villains,
my name is Gru.
I feel like I'm talking
too loud even though
our proximity
doesn't require
this kind of volume.
(GRU'S VOICE ECHOING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
If you told me when I was ten
that I would have the chance
to fill the shoes
of my favorite villain ever,
Wild Knuckles, I would say,
"You got rocks in your head."
But now that I'm 11
and three quarters,
it makes a lot more sense.
All right, who let the kid in?
I thought he was a tiny man.
What's wrong with you?
You seriously think
a puny little child
can be a villain?
Um, yes.
I am pretty despicable.
You don't want to cross me.
Evil is for adults
who steal powerful ancient
stones and wreak havoc.
(GASPS)
And not for tubby little punks
who should be
at school, learning,
taking a recess,
sucking his thumb.
(ALL LAUGHING)
"Sucking his..."
Come back when you've done
something to impress me.
Who's next?
I am Wing Man,
the next member
of the Vicious6.
Behold, the power of flight!
(EXCLAIMS)
All right, joke's over.
Showtime.
This is a big one. (GRUNTS)
Yeah, yeah. To the left.
That's right.
Bring him in,
bring him in, boys.
Everybody pile on!
(GASPS) He took the stone!
I'll get him!
(GRU EXCLAIMS)
Lock down the building.
(GASPS)
(CUSTOMERS MUMBLING)
What?
(STAMMERS)
Nothing to see here.
Look at you.
Frampton Comes Alive!
Nice choice. (GASPS)
I...
Just keep walking.
Who the heck is that? A kid?
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, guys.
Bello.
Mini-Boss!
What are you doing here?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay, just get on.
Which way did he go?
There's that little thief!
Go! Go, go, go!
Split up!
Knock, knock. Delivery.
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
That demon child!
(YELLS)
Otto, take the stone
back to the lair.
I'll distract them.
Go! Go, go, go!
GRU: Ugh, not now.
Come on, come on!
(MINION SCREAMING)
(YELLING IN SLOW MOTION)
(SCREAMS)
Yeah, baby.
I'll handle this.
(LAUGHS)
Hope you enjoy
the rest of your short life.
Please work.
Come on, come on, come on!
(YELLING)
We're coming for you,
tiny man.
Yeah!
(ALL CHEERING)
(MINIONS CHEERING)
Josh, pump it up.
Up, up, up!
All the young dudes
Hey, dudes!
Carry the news...
They all said the kid couldn't
be a real villain.
Well...
This kid just stole something
from the worst villains
in the world.
When I bring it back to them,
they are going to say,
(GASPS) "We have made
a terrible mistake.
"Please join us. Please, Gru."
And I will say, "Yes!
"I will be the newest member
of the Vicious6."
Now all I need is Otto.
Where is Otto?
Otto le come-ay.
No, not "Otto le come-ay."
He needs to "come-ay" now.
(MUFFLED YELLING)
Otto!
Mini-Boss!
There you are.
Oh, you got it?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Is this... Are you pulling
on my legs right now?
Otto, where is the stone?
(OTTO SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Over there.
(YELLS)
Oh, no!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
(OTTO SPEAKS
MINIONESE LOVINGLY)
I love you.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Did you just trade my future
for a Pet Rock?
Si?
Oh... Okay. Otto, where was
this birthday party?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
This is unacceptable.
Unacceptable!
I told you guys
that you weren't ready
for the big leagues,
and you have
proven me correct.
(OTTO SPEAKS MINIONESE)
All you do
is mess everything up.
Up? Pump it up!
Do a little dance
Make a little love
(GROANS IN FRUSTRATION)
My mom was right.
You do not belong here.
You're fired!
I'm going to find that stone.
When I get home,
you all better be gone.
Mini-Boss...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
And, Otto, close your yapper!
Josh.
Si, si.
(SONG PLAYING)
I'll say goodbye to love
No one ever cared
if I should live or die
Gru. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Por favor. Por favor.
Time and time again
Kevin, no.
I will be better off
on my own.
And all I know of love is
how to live without it
I just can't seem to find it
So I've made my mind up
I must live my life alone
And though it's not the
easy way I guess I've
always known
I'd say goodbye to love
There are no tomorrows
For this heart of mine
Surely time will lose
these bitter memories
(SCREAMING)
And I'll find that there is
Someone to believe in
and to live for
Mini-Boss!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I thought
you'd be impressed.
Could I just speak
to Belle Bottom? She'll...
Wild Knuckles! (EXCLAIMS)
You're alive?
Wow, my favorite villain
is also my kidnapper?
This could be
a great opportunity
if you don't kill me.
Shut up and give me the stone.
Oh, yes, the stone.
Here's the thing about that.
Kind of a funny story.
Give it to him!
And it's all going to go south
very quickly.
What the heck is this?
(GRU SCREAMS)
Where is it, boy?
I don't have it!
I know you're
hiding it somewhere.
I'm not. I'm not. I swear.
Cross my heart
and hope to die,
stick a needle in my eye.
Don't actually
do that, though.
Somebody bring me a phone.
Call home.
It's ransom time.
No, no, no. My mom will
probably pay you to keep me!
(LAUGHS)
Good one. Call!
(SHUSHING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING FAINTLY)
La telefono.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Bello. La casa de Mini-Boss.
Who is this?
Kevin.
Kevin, le Minion.
"Kevin le" what?
Le Minion.
You kidding me?
You got henchmen? (CHUCKLES)
Well, that's the end of that.
Mini-Boss?
Listen, you,
bring the stone to
me in San Francisco.
6830 Green Street. Got it?
Si...
Now, you got two days,
or you are never going to see
your little boss again.
(GASPS)
Bello? Bello.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Otto...
(OTTO SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
No. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
Otto...
Okay. Si, si.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GASPS)
Hey, ho, let's go
Hey, ho
Otto... (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay. Go, go, go.
They're going through
a tight wind
The kids are losing their
minds
The blitzkrieg bop
Oh.
Oh, the stone!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Gave that to my uncle.
It's more his style.
Oh!
(GASPS)
La... La... La stone-a!
Kevin! Kevin!
La stone-a!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GROANS) I told you.
I don't know where he went,
you stupid Twinkies.
(EXCLAIMS)
Okay.
Pank you. Bye-bye.
Huh?
Oh, not cool, man.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(CAR HORN HONKS)
San Pan-pisco.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Let's rock and roll.
Time to get our stone back.
We're coming for you, Mr. Gru.
Hallelujah!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(WHOOPS, LAUGHS)
Smash! Smash!
(ORGANS PLAYING)
Whoo-hoo!
WOMAN ON INTERCOM:
Flight 1109 will now
depart at gate 27B.
Bello.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
San Francisco? Okay.
How will you be paying?
Uh...
No problemo.
Oh, great.
You know, if you have
any hair balls, we can
upgrade you to first class.
WOMAN: Get out.
MAN: So there I was.
We lost thrust
in both engines,
and I had to turn back
at LaGuardia.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Ooh-la-la.
Hey, Sally.
Hey.
I wanna fly like an eagle
To the sea
Fly like an eagle...
Okay. Vamos.
(CLEARS THROAT,
SPEAKS MINIONESE ON INTERCOM)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE CONTINUES)
Bello. Peanut?
Oh, yes, please.
Peanut.
Peanut? Peanut.
Peanut?
Hey, baby, peanut?
(BABY CRYING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hey!
(BOTH SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MINION HUMMING
CLASSICAL MUSIC)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(MINION SCREAMING)
(GAGS)
(BABY CRYING)
Oh, bello!
Bello.
(AIR WHOOSHING)
(BEEPING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
You see me, you see me not.
(ALL CHEERING)
Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHS TRIUMPHANTLY)
No. No "ha-ha."
You got real moxie, kid,
stealing from the Vicious6.
I got moxie, really?
(GASPS)
Did I just receive
a compliment
from Wild Knuckles?
Oh, all my dreams
are coming true right now!
Well, it's about to
become your nightmare.
Welcome to my newest
torture device,
the Disco Inferno.
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
Your Minions better get here
by sundown tomorrow,
because if 48 hours of disco
don't kill you...
...the blade will.
(YELPS)
No, no, no, no, no!
(WILD KNUCKLES LAUGHS)
(YELLS)
(MINION GRUNTING)
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
(OTTO GURGLES)
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Hey!
(YELLS)
(ALL CHEERING)
Stone-a! Stone-a!
Stone-a! Stone-a...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Look-a the map-a.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Gru...
(MINIONS GROANING)
(BOB SCREAMING)
Bob!
(YELLS)
(CHEERING)
Bello! (LAUGHS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(MIMICKING BELL)
Next stop, Green Street.
Bye-bye.
Hey, hey. Look-a.
Come-ay! Come-ay!
More, more, more
KEVIN: Mini-Boss.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
Stuart.
Mini-Boss.
No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Go, go, go.
Hey. Go, go, go.
Hey, wait a minute.
Bello.
Oh, no! Bob!
(STUART GROWLING)
(MINIONS SHOUTING)
(YELLS)
Trespassers!
Get 'em!
Hey, you. Come back here!
Go, go!
Kevin! Oh, okay. (LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Get your little
butts back here!
Okay, now, you might feel
a little pinch.
Got you now.
Time to break some bones.
(YELLS)
(MUFFLED EXCLAIMING)
Any plans for the weekend?
(SIGHS)
Take five deep breaths.
I'll be right back.
(MINIONS GRUNTING)
Hey!
You like picking on
little guys, huh?
Go take a nap, old lady.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Old lady?
Hi-ya!
(GROANS)
I am a master of the ancient
Shaolin art of kung fu.
(GASPS)
(HENCHMEN GRUNTING)
Huh? (GRUNTS)
Ha!
(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Get lost!
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
If you come back to our place,
you're dead.
Come-ay. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Pank you.
Pank you...
Shh, shh, shh. You can
thank me by going away.
I'm working.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...kung fu...
You want to learn kung fu?
Ah, Kevin.
Bello, chica.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...kung fu por
smoochie, smoochie?
Hmm, hmm?
(EXCLAIMS)
My teaching days are over.
This is my life now.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...kung fu para...
para save-a le Mini-Boss.
Por favor.
(MINIONS WHIMPERING)
Ay-ya. Fine.
I will teach you.
(MINIONS CHEERING)
Hey!
Those are not for you.
Excuse-a, excuse-a.
The name of the game is sell,
sell, sell!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(TUPPERWARE MAKES FART SOUNDS)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(FART SOUNDS CONTINUE)
(MINIONS SINGING IN TUNE
WITH FART SOUNDS)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
What?
(VILLAINS YELLING)
Where's Gru?
Ah, how should I know?
What's with the costumes?
Halloween was four months ago.
You look stupid.
Buzz off. Shoo!
I'm getting
my meat tenderizer.
Let me help you
with that, dearie.
GRU'S MOM: Don't touch me.
Now, where's the boy?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh, I didn't mean
to scare you.
Don't worry.
We're not mad at him.
We just want to...
hire him.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Where is he?
Wild Knuckles, San Pan-pisco.
Wild Knuckles is alive?
And working with the kid.
Hmm.
We're going to San Francisco.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Let's hit it.
You had better be paying
for my roof.
MINIONS: Ay-yi-yi.
Pretty groovy, huh?
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
We begin with a basic kick.
(YELLS) Now you.
(MINIONS YELL)
Okay.
No kicking.
This is a melon hammer.
It's a weapon.
This is Fred. He is a dummy.
Never underestimate a dummy.
Ha. Dummy.
Bello, Fred.
Now attack!
(YELLING)
(MINION CHEERING)
Stuart! Stuart! Woo-hoo!
(MUTTERS)
Fred.
Doubt tells me I cannot break
this wood.
But doubt exists only
in the mind.
You know what
I say to my mind?
(EXCLAIMS)
Now you.
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS) Kevin, Kevin, Kevin.
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay. Clearly, we are not
ready for philosophy.
Let's just train.
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
(FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING
FROM BOOMBOX)
A-won't you take me to
Funkytown
(MUSIC FROM BOOMBOX ENDS)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ya... Ya... Ya...
(MUSIC FROM BOOMBOX RESUMES)
Yeah!
Town
Won't you take me to
Yeah!
(MINIONS GRUNTING)
(MINIONS SCREAMING)
(MUSIC FROM BOOMBOX ENDS)
Rest up.
Tomorrow's going to be
even worse.
WILD KNUCKLES: What,
you're quitting?
I told you, when I get that
stone, we're gonna be
unstoppable.
I have had enough!
There's nothing sadder
than an aging villain.
So long, old man!
Guys, come on. We're a team.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(MUFFLED DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
More, more, more
How do you like...
(DISCO MUSIC ENDS)
(SINGS) How do you like it?
How do you like...
Is this heaven?
I just had to fire
my henchmen.
You know why? 'Cause they
weren't getting the job done.
Okay, I'm just gonna untie you
now because I...
I need you to do some stuff
for me around the house.
And it might be, you know,
kind of nice to have
a little company around here.
Oh, yeah. Two villains just
doing some chores.
Who knows what kind of trouble
we could get into?
(CHUCKLES, GRUNTS)
What's that?
That's your evil chuckle?
Obviously.
Well, it stinks.
You sound like a clown
who swallowed a kazoo.
Really? Well, you look like
a wizard going through
an end-of-life crisis.
(GRUNTS)
Easy there, Don Rickles.
GRU: Who's Don Rickles?
OTTO: Stone-a.
Stone-a.
Stone-a!
Stone-a...
Dude. (LAUGHS)
I thought we lost you
there for a minute.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hey, chill, chill, chill...
Hey, you want to try this on,
little dude?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
La stone-a!
Hey, hey, hey, soul brother,
where you jettin' off to?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
San Pan-pisco.
Frisco disco!
It's your lucky day, kid.
I'm headed up the coast.
I could drop you off
on the way.
Yee-haw! (CHEERS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...la stone-a!
Oh, look-a!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Hey.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, yo, hermano!
(HORN BLARES)
(MIMICS HORN BLARING)
(LAUGHS)
Start with the pool.
This place has got to be
spick-and-span.
What are you doing?
You look like the overcooked
turkey my mom makes
on Thanksgiving.
(SCREAMS) Oh, God.
Oh, yeah. I forgot to mention,
the pool is filled
with my pet crocodiles.
Yeah, well, well,
doesn't scare me.
Be careful. I can't have you
lose an arm,
because I need you to change
some light bulbs after this.
Here, let me show you
how it's done.
Betsy, knock it off.
Hey!
(GRUNTS) Oh, no.
Marvin, no, no. Stop that.
(WILD KNUCKLES YELLING)
(EXCLAIMS) Help! Oh, no.
The net!
I got you! I got you!
I don't got you.
Take my hand.
I got you!
(BOTH GRUNT)
Whoa. Whoa.
(GRU PANTING)
You could've run, but you,
but you didn't.
I told you,
you are my favorite
villain in the world.
I could not let you
get eaten by crocodiles.
Even though that would've been
kind of cool to watch.
So... So you want to be
a great villain, huh?
(GASPS) That's all
I ever wanted.
You want... I don't know, you
want me...
You want me to teach you
a thing or two?
Mmm-hmm!
MASTER CHOW: Many fighters
have asked me,
how did I become
a great master?
Hey, look-a!
Even the smallest of us
are capable of great things.
You just dig down deep,
find your inner beast, and...
(ROARS)
Gesundheit?
Now you try.
(ROARS)
(COUGHS)
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(ROARS WEAKLY)
(SIGHS)
Find your inner beast!
Stop this kick.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
We have a lot more work to do.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS, YELLS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
Kevin, Stuart and Bob,
you are ready.
(MINIONS CHEERING)
No, no, no, no, no!
Ready for your junior kung fu
achievement badges.
(SIGHS)
They're dead.
First rule of heists,
always stay in character.
Got it, Grandpa.
Say, do you mind if we
use the john?
Poindexter here can't
hold it in till we get home.
GRU: The Bank of Evil.
It's showtime, kid.
Follow my lead, and don't
forget your cue.
Hello. I... I just need
to cash this.
Wowie zowie! What a big bank.
How many security guards
are in here?
Who's this little guy?
Well, that's my grandson,
who still has not learned
that children should be seen
and not heard.
(LAUGHS) Kids.
I actually have a son
of my own.
Ugh. He looks weird.
Oh, ho-ho!
Don't listen to him.
Your son is very, uh... Cute.
(YELLS) Oh, no!
Oh, help! I'm seeing
a white light.
Helen, I'm coming for ya!
Helen, I'm coming for ya.
Oh. Help!
(GROANS)
Help my pop-pop!
Somebody help him!
Huh?
My grandpa!
MAN: We need a doctor!
This is the big one.
(GROANS, YELLS)
WILD KNUCKLES: You hear that?
It's the sweet sound
of angels.
Help!
Do something!
My life is flashing
before my eyes.
No, no, no. The other way.
The other way.
(EXCLAIMS)
All right,
everyone stand back.
Uh-oh.
Clear!
No, wait a minute. Wait.
(EXCLAIMS PAINFULLY)
Don't give up
on me now, buddy.
No, no, no,
I'm feeling better.
Clear!
(EXCLAIMS PAINFULLY)
Maximum charge.
Clear!
Thank you.
You saved my grandpa.
Did we... Did we do the heist?
Grandpas say
the darndest things.
You dropped these.
(WILD KNUCKLES GROANS)
Look what I got!
Hey. Not bad.
Not bad at all.
We make a good team.
We do?
Oh, yeah. Hey,
we got to keep at it.
Wait till you see
what I'm gonna teach you next.
I cannot wait.
WILD KNUCKLES: Oh,
this is gonna be fun.
(MIMIC MARTIAL ARTS NOISES)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(YELLS)
Hoo! Mini-Boss!
Okay, Stuart...
Bob... (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Time to strike!
Mini-Boss!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MECHANICAL LAUGHTER)
(YELLS)
(YELLS) They're not here.
Fan out and find them.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Something big's
going down in Frisco.
Oh! Look-a.
(FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
BIKER: Whoo, there it is.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
It's been one heck of a ride,
little man.
Oh, dude.
You know, I'm gonna miss you.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hey, soul brother, good luck!
(FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Ooh.
(STAMMERS, YELLS)
My friend, you're now gonna
learn from the old school.
(BOTH GASP)
Oh, no.
I can't believe they
did this to me!
I taught them everything
they know!
We were a team!
(SIGHS) I give up.
Hey, you are a great bad guy,
and they are stupid idiots.
Only dream I ever had
was doing bad stuff
with my buddies.
Now look at me. Old, alone.
Well, you are old,
but you're not alone.
(GROANS)
All right.
Listen up, buster.
We are starting a new team,
and it's going to be called
The Terrible Twos.
We can find
a better name later,
but right now
we're going to find that stone
and show everybody that you
still got it.
Come on.
You're just a little kid.
It's over. Go home.
But you said we...
Go home!
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Come on, come on. Let's go!
(OTTO EXCLAIMING,
SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Whoa, hey!
Otto?
Otto!
Yee-haw! (LAUGHS)
Otto! It's Mini-Boss!
(EXCLAIMS) Mini-Boss!
(LAUGHS TRIUMPHANTLY)
Mini-Boss!
Otto!
OTTO: Look-a! Look-a!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Stone-a.
You found the stone.
Otto, I'm so proud of you.
(STAMMERS)
All right, we don't have
much time.
We got to get this
to Wild Knuckles.
Okay.
(GASPS)
Get him!
(NUN-CHUCK EXCLAIMS)
(GRU AND OTTO SCREAM)
Go, go, go!
(YELLS)
Long time, no see, punk.
I'll take that.
(LAUGHS)
Yes!
Don't move!
Right there! Freeze!
Anti-Villain League.
You are under arrest.
Oh, phew.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Everybody.
Did you forget
what time it is?
(BELL RINGS)
Happy New Year!
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
Fire!
(ROARS)
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
(LAUGHS AND ROARS)
(GROANS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Stand your ground.
Look out!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(LAUGHS)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
Where do you think
you're going? Hmm?
You stole from us,
and now you're gonna pay!
(YELLS)
Enjoy being torn apart.
Hey! (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...Mini-Boss!
Guys!
Oh. Why don't we
make this a fair fight?
(LAUGHS)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(CROWS)
Oh, you thought I was serious.
(LAUGHS)
Run!
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
No! (YELLS)
Hello, traitors.
(GASPS)
Remember me?
You.
You can leave me for dead,
you can destroy
everything I own,
but I will not let you
hurt that kid!
So you're gonna save the kid?
(LAUGHS) Yeah,
you and what army?
(MINIONS YELLING)
This army!
Okay. This army.
(GRIMACES)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(CROWS)
(YELLS)
(ALL YELLING)
(SCREAMS)
(HISSES)
(CROWS)
(YELLS)
MASTER CHOW: Dig down deep.
Find your inner beast.
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(HISSES)
(CHEEPING)
(YELLING)
(GRU YELLING)
(YELLS IN PAIN)
(WILD KNUCKLES YELLS)
(GROANS)
Otto!
Hurry! Faster!
No!
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
Got you.
Go, go, go!
(GASPS)
Ha-ha!
(EXCLAIMS) No.
(WILD KNUCKLES GRUNTS)
Get away from him!
Destroy the kid.
(MINIONS ROARING)
Oh!
(LAUGHS TRIUMPHANTLY)
No!
Hey, hey.
How does it feel to be
beaten by a tubby little punk?
(LAUGHS)
You guys were amazing!
The kung fu...
Where did that come from?
Obviously,
you guys are rehired.
Stuart! (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(CHITTERING)
MAN: It's all yours, sir.
WOMAN: Where do you want it?
WOMAN: Can you feel this, sir?
Right here.
Oh, no. Wild Knuckles.
(COUGHS)
Hey.
You're gonna be okay, right?
Don't worry about me, kid.
I'll be fine.
Finally.
You're going away for a long,
long time.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't bet on it.
No.
See you soon, kiddo.
(MINIONS SINGING SOFTLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Wild Knuckles
was my favorite villain.
We didn't have
much time together,
but the time we did have,
I'm so grateful for.
I've been thinking about
how you won't see me grow up
or be there for all
the terrible things
that I'm going to do.
And believe me, there are
gonna be some awful things.
(CRYING)
Ahem.
But I'm going
to make you proud.
I'm going to be the best
villain ever because of you.
Because you taught me
what matters.
You can't do anything alone.
Find your tribe,
and never, ever let them go.
Otto?
Si.
(SINGING)
(MINIONS CLAMORING)
(CONTINUES SINGING)
(MINIONS SINGING)
You better
stay out of trouble, kid.
I will lead
a good and honest life.
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS) You're alive?
Oh!
You just blew my mind.
How did you do that?
(LAUGHS)
I cannot wait
to fake my own death
to avoid the authorities.
Shoot for the moon, kid.
Shoot for the moon.
(CHUCKLES)
See you later, suckers!
(ALL CHEERING)
You can't always get
what you want
But if you try sometime
You just might find
you just might find
You get what you need
Ah, yeah
Sorry, we're closed.
Oh!
I just wanted
to thank you for this.
Worked like a charm.
All right, let me
cut to the chase here.
I need a genius mad scientist.
You want to come work for me?
No, I am done with villainy.
Off to happier horizons.
Goodbye, little chap.
Por favor.
(MINIONS WHIMPERING)
(CHEEPS)
Oh, all right, all right.
Fine. Stop with the face.
I'm in.
Want to see something cool?
Oh, are you kidding me?
(GRU LAUGHING)
MINIONS: Big Boss! Big Boss!
Big Boss! Big Boss!
GRU: "Big Boss."
I like that.
(SONG PLAYING)
We can make it further
We running
and don't look back
It's a light at the end
of the tunnel
If you stay on track
But I know any minute
When your fingers turn
it up like snap
So hard to lose like that
Hey, let's do it
All around the world
We gotta turn up the
sunshine
Think about it
All the boys and girls
You gotta turn up
the sunshine
Said it's been a
long night, long night
Waiting for the light
Let's do it
All around the world
We gotta turn up the
sunshine
We gotta turn it up
Make it hard to lose
like that
If this weather
makes you frown
And some people get you down
Remember
Love, like sound
It's better when it's loud
And if there's no
song inside
We can bring the light
together
Day or night
We're shining from inside
Turn up the, turn it up
Turn up the sunshine
All around the world
We gotta turn up the
sunshine
Think about it
All the boys and girls
You gotta turn up
the sunshine
Said it's been a
All around the world
We gotta turn up the
sunshine
We gotta turn it up
Make it hard to lose
like that
Gotta make a move to a town
that's right for me
Time to keep me movin'
Keep me groovin'
with some energy
Well, I talk about it
Talk about it
Talk about it, talk about it
Talk about movin'
Gotta move on
Won't you take me to
Funkytown
Feeling better
Now that we're through
'cause I'm over you
I learned my lesson
And it left a scar
Now I see how you really are
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
I broke a heart
that's gentle and true
Well, I broke a heart
over someone like you
I'll beg his forgiveness
on bended knee
I wouldn't blame him
if he said to me
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
I'm turning you down, baby
And I'm going my way
Forget about you, baby
'Cause I'm leaving to stay
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
I'm gonna say it again
You're no good
Baby, you're no good
Oh, oh, no
You're no good
Baby, you're no good