Translated By:
|| Killer_Sub ||
Minions!
Have you ever wondered where they came from?
They've been on this planet far longer than we have.
They're all different.
But they all share the same goal.
Boss!
To find the biggest, baddest villain to serve!
Finding a Master was easy.
Keeping a Master...?
That's where things got tricky.
Nope, it wasn't easy for these guys.
But nonetheless they kept on looking!
Ladies and Gentlemen, Scarlet Overkill!
Have any of you ever dreamt of working for
the greatest super-villain of all time?!
I love you, Scarlet!
These are the new recruits.
No, no - don't say anything.
I won't understand.
Do you know who this is?
This is Queen Elizabeth!
And I really, really, REALLY want her crown!
You came for the Queen's crown, did you?
Well you're going to have to get through ME!
Gentlemen do not steal ladies' crowns!
You backstabbing little traitors!
Don't you Scarlet me!
I don't want you to take this the wrong way
but I HATE you.
This is TORTURE.
Guys, cut it out!
This is REALLY unprofessional!