AI Translated and Resynced by Sosoy
Almost there, just an easy little hawk.
Kind of.
Hey, you wanted to come this time.
Just a little higher.
Hey, hey, ow.
You hear anything?
I don't like it.
There's gotta be other
people out here, other villages.
And one day someone's gonna end certain.
Never change.
Hey, hey, sweet beautiful chicken.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go home.
I can't wait till I retire.
You're bruised.
You're in my face.
I don't love anything.
How could I beat this chicken?
New look.
Yep, even better.
Oh, look.
The name is Boo.
Hi, kid.
You can do it.
Hold on.
Lay it on me.
I mean, it takes a
bit to rotate the sails.
Got it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's called a hair whip.
A hair whip.
Let it from those guys.
So, how did go this time?
You found something.
It was in a clearing,
which I found a little help from.
Hey, but this isn't from our village.
I don't even know what
it's made of, but it's proof.
There are other people out there.
I don't know why we haven't
found them yet, but Dad, that island,
I think that's where they're going to be.
I just have to figure
out how to find those stars.
Little fish!
I thought you were gone forever.
It was three days,
but I missed you every...
Mr. Baby.
Bring you?
You said you'd bring me a present.
Hmm.
Well, let me see.
Whoa.
What's it do?
What's it not?
Where are we going?
This is the place of our ancestors,
where I learned our people are voyagers.
Where Grandma showed me who we are.
She said to Grandma
by the ear and tell him,
I am a one and I'm a two-newie.
You'll board my boat and
restore the heart of the fishy.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
How much did it take?
A few weeks.
Weeks?
That's longer than forever.
I know, but it was important.
And if I hadn't fallen, I
never would have become a wayfinder.
Like our ancient chiefs, like
the last great navigator, Taotai Busa.
Before Maui stole
Timothy's heart and we stopped voyaging,
Taotai Busa wanted to connect our island
to all the people of the entire ocean.
Because together, what we can
do, how far we all can go, it's endless.
And now that I'm a wayfinder,
it's my job to continue what he started.
And this, this is my first cool how.
You should make Maui
go so you can stay with me.
Well, Maui's out
demigodding, but if he ever shows up,
you'll grab him by
the ear and tell him that.
I'm not here to cause trouble, just
a super chiseled demigodd passing through.
Now open the portal to
the island and I'll be on my way.
And why would I risk
breaking the rules for you
when you've already
caused my boss so much trouble?
Who?
Maui started it.
And you'll finish it?
Team up with your precious human again.
Team? You mean the girl with
the canoe and that goofy little chicken?
We weren't a team. I
just used her to get my hook.
Ow!
Nalo is a god, Maui.
If you try to reconnect the
people of the ocean, he will destroy you.
And then he'll destroy her too.
This is between him and me.
Moana has nothing to do with it.
Ooh, you've made her a way by now, Maui.
So now, she has everything to do with it.
It's done!
I'd like a sound like that.
Woo hoot!
Here you are.
Well, eat up.
We don't want the port getting old.
Why don't you watch me now?
Wanna.
Tonight isn't just a feast.
Long ago,
there was a title given
to the last great wayfinder.
With dreams as big as yours.
The sacred title.
More than a chief.
A tall tide.
Leader.
Connector of the entire sea.
My dear.
Would you honor us
tonight by accepting this title?
How people's first
tall tide in a thousand years.
And show us all
just how far we'll go.
Tonight, we drink
from our ancestors' form.
As tall tide us all once did.
To bestow this title.
On you.
To connect to our past.
Our present.
And the future that lies beyond.
May the ancestors continue to guide us.
I am
honored to serve our people.
May the ancestors continue to guide us.
One truth may too be ...
...under the stars.
S
You are my people.
So type one.
This is your future
if you cannot find others.
In isolation, this
is how your story ends.
I don't understand.
Returning to
Hichi's heart was the beginning.
You must brave the storm.
Reconnect our people.
Find Mochufetsu.
I don't know how to reach it.
A fire in the sky will guide you.
Wait, I don't even know how far it is.
Farther than I was able to go.
Find Mochufetsu.
Reconnect us all.
Mochufetsu.
The island I have to find is Mochufetsu.
Okay.
Took some searching, but...
Mochufetsu.
What is it?
An ancient island where the
channels of the ocean once came together,
connecting the people of the
entire sea until it was lost, cursed.
In a terrible storm
of a power-hungry god, novel.
He believed he'd be stronger by separating
the people of the ocean to weaken us,
to end our story.
Our ancestors believed reaching
Mochufetsu would break Nalo's curse,
restore the channels.
It's the only way to
bring our people together again.
Or historians.
We need to convene a council of people.
Fire in the sky.
He wants me to follow it.
Two new stars.
It could take a lifetime.
Don't dive us. I
didn't make it back at all.
It's a call from the ancestors to him.
But if we never see her again...
I do mean everything you want to get.
Sami... No, I mean that's...
I don't want you to leave.
Mom, it's...
It's so fast. What if...
You're a tough time now, Moana.
For some things...
We never feel ready.
My mom.
I'll always be right beside you.
But perhaps you're meant for more.
Oh, what are you so worried about?
It's not like last time.
Last time you
weren't old enough to understand.
Oh, you could lose or learn.
And here we are together
still just a little different.
I can't see where your story leads.
But we never stop choosing who we are.
This is bigger than what you do.
Bigger than us.
So I will sail into this new sky to
reconnect the people of the entire ocean.
And then I will return home.
Moana, you need a crew.
Hey, hey, Apuwa, don't count.
It's the other side of the ocean.
How could I ask them to?
Our people will rise if you let them.
Last time the chicken made it.
Well, I'm going to need a bigger canal.
Yes, brand new.
Sleep.
Double health design.
My fist can do this.
Sweet.
I'm hoping to line
up greats with the crew.
I'd like you on the crew.
Well, we should do better than this.
A farmer on the sea.
We're going to
need to eat more than fish.
You need irrigation.
Plant propagation.
Take even my best apprentice.
Good stuff.
Exactly.
We need a master.
Yes, you too.
Thanks, Kelly.
You're the best.
I walked onto that one.
Hey, Maui, it's been a while.
I don't know where you are,
but I could really use your help.
Maui!
Oh, Moni.
It's both of us, actually.
Maui and me.
It's part of a series.
Wow.
It's too bad Maui isn't here.
We really need someone
who knows all the old stories.
Someone who's like super
strong and has great hair and just...
I know someone else.
Kind of like that?
Yes!
I'm going with Donna
on a call from the ancestors.
Whoo!
Get ready for some
eyewitness accounts, people.
I'm coming with you.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I promise.
What if you don't come back?
The ocean is my friend.
Our friend.
He connects us.
So, there is nowhere I could
ever go that I won't be with you.
Go.
So you can take a piece of hold.
Okay, okay, okay.
One more time.
This is not the end of our story.
This is not where our destiny is denied.
Together, we rise as one.
Together, we take our freedom.
That guy gets it.
Yep, I made you handsome.
Now all you gotta do is catch my hook.
Come on.
Yes, yes.
Come on, you got it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, keep doing it.
That's it, higher.
We're almost there.
Just a little higher.
Don't worry.
Come on, you know
me, I'll get us out of here.
No, I don't need her to save me.
Again.
Because she'll die.
Melo hates humans
even more than he hates me.
And let me tell you something.
He hates me a lot.
So the farther Curly is
from any of this, the better.
We're on our own.
Yeah, I got it.
I would let you out, but I'm
really hoping to meet your little friend.
I have plans for you both.
Hey, hey, hey, enjoy your lunch.
Melo, what are you doing?
I'm making improvements.
Okay.
Who is perfect as it is?
The fictions of it.
There is only
failing, then learning, then death.
What is the order?
Of course.
That's why you're the wayfinder.
No, no, no.
Guys, the entire
ocean is kind of counting on us.
We've got to rise to the moment.
Stay on course and
kick everyone off the canoe.
Wait, where's the harbor?
Ow.
When will the canoe stop?
Moving.
Well, we're kind of on the ocean.
Oh, Moni.
Lotto, Moni's the other one.
Guys, we'll never make it.
What?
If you don't embrace the ocean.
He kind of breaks the liquid.
Otto, I cannot swim.
You don't use a human.
Now everyone looks sad.
And whoever designs
the canoe, forgot our macros.
Yes, sir.
I am unclear as to what you are doing.
Guys, we want to reach
Motufetu, break Nalo's curse.
We've got to come together.
Find our friends.
I don't use anyone.
Oh, we'll see in the back.
Don't be dead on your feet.
It's time to live your own story.
Even if you disagree.
Try this mandatory look of trials.
What could be better than this?
It would be better than this.
I'm sure it could be so great.
Why, you just need your son.
You can't live here forever.
But it was all the fun.
Don't you know it's
gathers better than you see?
Nothing is better than this.
I'm going to be sick.
Fascinating. It's like an acid.
Can I get a chihu?
Oh, yeah!
Now I just gotta get my baby.
The tattoo, Mommy.
Listen to me. I am a demi-god.
I want to be slept by the tattoo.
Hey! Okay. Rule number one.
Okay.
Roll me back. I'll
roll you back. Not him.
This is what happens
when you meet your heroes.
I know, right?
Rule number one.
You never saw me like this.
Even though I still look very
cool. You look like a kidney stone.
You look like someone
who would know what that is.
Now.
Well, hello, bacon.
Okay. I feel like there's
some back story that
I need to get caught up on.
Actually, you know what? Scratch that.
I don't want to get attached if you all...
You know what?
Which... which... you guys won't.
You're not gonna do that. I
don't even know why I said that.
The point is, there's
some serious god stuff going down.
So I'm gonna go handle my disc.
Alright. Be back in a bit.
Until then, stay alive. Talk to no one.
And if you see a crazy
bat lady, run. She is the worst.
Stay away or you will die. Be good.
Maui, out.
Boat snack. Boat snack.
Where's Moana?
Simia? Simia!
How are you here?
I'm not. You got sucked inside
a giant, um, and her story will end.
Cause now you will never
help the people of the ocean.
And their ancestors will be
like, "Moana, we hate you forever."
You got this.
Here. You got this. You got this.
Relax. I don't bite.
Here come I.
It's been a while
since I've seen a wayfinder.
Love the oar. Would
you like to see me use it?
Ooh, feisty. We
have that in common, Moana.
The human who's got all the gods talking.
Who are you, Matani?
Guardian of this little slice of paradise.
You live here?
No, by choice. Maui never mentioned me.
Probably too busy
playing with his tattoo.
Well, come on then.
Um, I'm not going anywhere with you.
Get out of here, break
Nala's curse, find Motufetsu.
Here to help. You
know the way to Motufetsu?
You think you can only
get somewhere if you know the way?
That's kind of what wave-biting is.
So much to learn.
A true wayfinder
doesn't know the path at all.
That's the whole point. To find
your way to what's never been found.
If you want to break Nala's curse,
you've got to stop playing and save Sis.
Get a little lost.
Why would I listen to anything you say?
Because Nala trapped me too.
I want you to beat
Nala. Because then, I'll be free.
There's always another
way to get where you need to go.
You just have to
think a little different.
Different?
Play it right?
Let him save you, then I
know the rules around the bridge.
It's time to get lost.
He's terribly nice.
You know you're questioning.
Take a look around.
I've got to let you up and
down, cause at the end you cannot drown.
In the rain for memories.
It's been too late to see.
And put your trust in me,
because you've got potential and trouble.
The distance are real
existential and lost through existence.
And there is no map beyond estimation.
No explanation,
please hold this equation.
We're gonna get back,
come loose, and lose our way.
There ain't no
time in holding that faith.
You better not try the
thrill of living dangerously.
You've got along a way to go keep crazy.
You'll never know
the rules around the bridge.
What is this?
Don't you know how good you have it?
You're all there stopping you.
You want me, I'm stuck like static.
Can you imagine?
That life is time to carry the nerve.
You've got a chance, don't take it.
I know you're scared, but life's unfair.
It's the truth of
choices making it small.
Trust the fall, and you can have it all.
You gotta come loose and lose your way.
There ain't no
time in holding that faith.
You better not try the
thrill of living dangerously.
You've got along a way to go keep crazy.
You'll never know
the rules around the bridge.
What is this?
You're all there.
There's always another way in my life.
What are you doing to me?
You're all there.
Oh, yeah.
There's always another way.
Order of the guards.
One get you all the way to Motufi 2,
a little short on the
commute for you and your crew.
And Mr. Coconut Oil.
Who's Mr. Coconut Oil?
I've always used my patience.
Do not fear. You have been rescued.
Kwa-ki-na, kwa-ki-na!
We're home, we're home!
Please!
She's opening.
They're such a plan.
They keep you in a snack game
because you want us to go together?"
Well, I certainly did not
keep you for the conversation.
Oh, wait.
Well, shall we?
Do you... can't leave?
Break Nalo's curse.
And maybe one day
we'll see each other again
Remember there's always another way
Even if you have to get lost to find it
Good luck. Hold by one
You got this
Let Nalo find out I
helped will die by lightning
Huh?
Molly looks good
Woah! I'm kissing the pig!
We're in a portal of the gods!
Hey!
Hey guys!
I got her again!
Plus Molly?
Where's Molly?
What's up girlie?
Molly!
You could have told
me we were doing new outfits
But Rocket leaves on
my cheeks for a thousand years
Oh! I can't believe we're here!
Hey buddy, I missed ya!
Oh! Sorry, that was weird
Is that weird?
This is the craziest thing in my life
Love this guy! Not creeping me out at all
Gotta join me for a second
This is cool!
Oh! And did you meet the papa mora?
I thought he'd do this in a climb
But it turned out to be super great
Because otherwise I
never would have met Montagny
Who's great by the way
And now you!
And now we're gonna
bring all of us together
Sorry, you go
You're all gonna die
What?
Nalo didn't just hide Motofetu in a storm
He hid it in a monster storm
In a cursed ocean you can't escape from
And then sunk into the bottom of the sea
Which means a human can't reach it
So unless I break the curse
You just bought a
one way ticket to Densville
Which is why I didn't want
you coming out in the first place
Because now you're
stuck and you're gonna die
Your crew's gonna die
And this time so is the chicken
But it's great to see you
And we're here
And we?
But this place looks perfectly nice
And look!
A constellation!
It's right there!
Guys, the ancestors wouldn't have called
If we couldn't do this
Unless it was a bot dial
That'll make sense in two thousand years
Tell Tybaza said reaching Motofetu
Is the only way to
give our people a future
If you know so much
How come he didn't tell you it was f♪♪♪
Suck
Because he told me to
follow the fire in the sky
That led me straight to you
Which makes sense
Because if Nalo thinks he's
stronger by keeping people apart
Then maybe the way to
break his curse is by coming together
You lift the island and I step on it
Mommy and Moana!
You're doing it again
You're so amazing
This is gonna work
Right? Ocean?
Ocean?
Moana,
The ocean
Cannot help you here
Grandma!
Actually,
I believe that's a welcome gift
From Nalo
Take that, sucka!
Humans, get your positions,
work together, and let's do this!
We really gotta talk
about your quitting process
Rabs!
Down below
Hate these guys
I'm an elder
And I'm three thousand years old
Which makes me elder, Earl
Just gotta outrun them till sunrise
Oh, I didn't open up
Uh, sure
Oh, yeah!
Woohoo!
Did he just freak out?
Behind us!
If Moana becomes turned
that time to this title, it'll work!
Oh, no!
Wait!
Woah!
Hey, what?
What?
No!
Moana!
Moana! Moana!
Well, figure this out
Yeah, sister Moana
Don't tell Fazza's!
I know!
Uh, uh, uh, it's a
bad time to say I told you so
So I'm not gonna do that,
because that would make you feel worse
But I believe in you
No one else does
There you go, walk it off, camp
What? I must be nice!
Ow! No purple, no purple, stop!
Okay, I'll talk to her
I know, Maui, it's just...
Every time I think I know what
I'm supposed to do, everything changes
I can't...
Moana almost died!
If I'm the reason her
people's story just... ends...
This is serious!
Is something distracting you?
Maybe breaking the curses like you said
We gotta work together
I pull it from the sea, but
a human has to land on its shores
Look, I get it
No one else can do this Look, I get it
No one likes sucking at their job
Why are you even here?
Because... because I've been low before
And I couldn't see a way forward
And then someone came along
Someone who I underestimated
And she lifted me up
I haven't done anything right
Since I left behind that topic
Hey, there is a way out
You wanna get through
it? You just gotta... gee who it?
You are so bad at this
I'm the best at this
I was a human, but now I'm a demigod
You never know what's next
I do all those monstrous form?
Well, you wanna get through it?
Stop trying
You're down in the dumps
You think you're way off your game
Come on, come on, remember your name
Don't waste all this energy
You got the
remedy, and I know your legacy
You got greatness inside
And you just gotta believe
You think you don't have the tricks
But they're right up your sleeve
These waters are frightening
But you bring the reckoning
So drop all the fear and the questioning
I need a... can I get a...
Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you gonna be?
You're gonna... you're gonna...
You need the history
Who are you? Who are you?
You gotta... you're gonna...
You need the level up
For sure, for sure
You're gonna be nuts and nuts
You're gonna... you're gonna...
You're gonna be...
You used to be
that bullying, storm cause,
conflicting for real
Can you imagine the
legend is at this point for reals?
You think that it's doomsday
It's a Tuesday
You know what, I'm
coming to play, come to play
And you click right
there for you and I'm trapped
And I'm gonna impress you and cut you up
You're gonna come and be a legend
It's a whole lot of becoming a friend
But now you got me invested
I'm gonna use that I call a blessing
Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you gonna be?
You're gonna... you're gonna...
I'm gonna make some ass do it
You're gonna fall
on a focus and then spin me
Pull it up, pull it up
It's my turn to
give a motivational speech
It's your job to
finally practice what you preach
Because of you, a better me
I didn't even
think that was a possibility
You copy that a mess after mess
Then he got into stress,
but now they're also reversed
You're being put to the desk
And breaking the curves,
leaving the law, that's gonna be worse
I'm making the bet
on the breakers and breakers
I've ever met
I'm gonna make some ass do it
Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you?
I'm gonna make some ass do it
You're gonna fall
on a focus and then spin me
Pull it up, pull it up
You're gonna... you're gonna...
I'm gonna make some ass do it
You're gonna fall
on a focus and then spin me
Pull it up, pull it up
Go get your ass do it
Come here
Pull it up, pull it up
You're gonna fall on your desk do it
You're gonna have to get free up
Pull it up, pull it up
Go find your desk do it
Come here
Pull it up
Go get him princess
Still not a princess
What do you think you are?
I know what I've asked you is a lot
That our canoe is in really rough shape
But I believe that together we...
We found a way to fix it
A little help from the ancestors, man
I did the decorations
We used the chicken
Respect
Nala wants to end our story
But we're not letting that happen
We're not letting that happen
We're not letting that happen We're not letting that happen We're not letting
that happen We're not letting that happen But we're not letting that happen
We just have to outsmart him
Find some new
traits he's never seen before
Well, I have been working on some ideas
Also, we do have a demigod
Sure, he's a little scruffy
But I get out better than nothing
I think you'll agree
Okay, we sail to
the heart of Nala's storm
Once I raise the
island, you all have to get to it
It would be harder
than anything we faced before
So if anyone wants to...
I spent my whole life
learning our people's stories
Because of you, I get to live for it
Alright then
Let's break a curse
Yeah, been a while since
I pulled an island from the sea
I know I have to bend it to knees
I have great posture
You know what? You farted
He's growing on me
Like a witch
That's beautiful
Okay, we do this
We make it home
Curly
Is this work?
I'm doing it one
Well, now I kind
of miss a lot of monsters
Ah, it's a big wave
We can go around it
Everyone get to your position
Be ready to switch it up
Here, it's fucked up
You might want to check the sundial
Why? What time is it?
It's bowie time
Let's lift an island and
show the swing back who's boss
Bring the thunder
I mean it's got a foot right?
Yeah
Switch it up
We're going over
Hold on, I don't want it
Help me
Hello
What about this?
I'm going to pull the finger
Hold on
There
Let's do it
Oh, come on
They keep coming across
We got to turn
Hold on
Get up Get up
Help me
Hold me
It's okay, I got a half of them
More board
Oh, I'm going to throw this thing
I'm going to throw this thing
Well, now it's a cheater
I am the coward for avoiding
You know
He doesn't care about you
Oh, he cares about me
I'm saying
It's humans, he wants to stop us
Why are you smiling?
Because we can use it
Distract all of, let him come after us
While Maui reaches the
center and lifts the island
We switch it up
Okay, Curly, you
couldn't outmaneuver the storm before
How are you going to do it now?
I think I am digging it out
I will need to chuck the glass
If you keep coming back to
help us, we'll never break Nolo's curse
We can draw the storm Maui
It's the only way
I'm going to throw this thing
I'm going to throw this thing I'm going
to throw this thing Go as fast as you can
Uh, look, I could
pull up a million islands
But if you're not
there to land on them, then
See you up there, Maui
See how they're Moana
Bacon? Eggs?
Yeah
Giant Hawk
So serious
See you on the island
The Spedy thing is coming
Stop placing the protons like this
Pickle
You can see it!
I couldn't have done it without Maui
A little dizzy!
Lightening and windows...
solemnizing
We have been gone.
You're ready!!!
I can't talk again.
I'm fine...
What happened?
Are we worse?
[whispering,
['mMYiness]
Fibers
Z