GRAMMA: In the beginning...
there was only ocean...
until the mother island emerged.
Te Fiti.
Her heart held the greatest power
ever known.
It could create life itself.
And Te Fiti shared it with the world.
But in time...
some began to seek Te Fiti's heart.
They believed
if they could possess it...
the great power of creation
would be theirs.
And one day...
the most daring of them all...
voyaged across the vast ocean
to take it.
He was a demigod of the wind and sea.
He was a warrior.
A trickster.
A shapeshifter who
could change form...
with the power of his magical fish hook.
And his name...
was Maui.
(CHUCKLES)
(RUMBLING)
But without her heart,
Te Fiti began to crumble...
giving birth to a terrible darkness.
Maui tried to escape...
but was confronted by another
who sought the heart.
Te Kā!
A demon of earth and fire.
Maui was struck from the sky...
never to be seen again.
And his magical fish hook
and the heart of Te Fiti...
were lost to the sea.
Where, even now...
1,000 years later...
Te Kā and the demons of the deep...
still hunt for the heart.
Hiding in a darkness
that will continue to spread...
chasing away our fish...
draining the life
from island after island...
until every one of us is devoured...
by the bloodthirsty jaws...
of inescapable death!
(WAILING)
But one day...
the heart will be found...
by someone who will journey
beyond our reef...
find Maui...
deliver him across the great ocean...
to restore Te Fiti's heart...
and save us all.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Thank you, Mother. That's enough.
Papa.
No one goes outside the reef.
We are safe here. There is no darkness.
There are no monsters.
Monsters!
-There's no monsters, no monsters...
-It's the darkness!
No, there is nothing beyond our reef,
but storms and rough seas.
I'm gonna throw up.
TUI: As long as we stay
on our very safe island...
...we'll be fine.
GRAMMA: The legends are true.
Someone will have to go.
TUI: Mother, Motunui is paradise.
Who would want to go anywhere else?
(BIRDS SCREECHING)
Shoo, shoo!
(EXCLAIMING)
(ETHEREAL WHISPERING)
(GIGGLING)
TUI: Moana!
There you are, Moana.
What are you doing? You scared me.
What? I wanna's go back.
I know, I know.
But you don't go out there.
It's dangerous.
Moana, come on.
Let's go back to the village.
You are the next great chief
of our people.
And you will do wondrous things,
my little minnow.
Oh, yes. But first, you must learn
where you're meant to be.
Moana
Make way, make way
Moana, it's time you knew
The village of Motunui is all you need
The dancers are practicing
They dance to an ancient song
Who needs a new song
This old one's all we need
This tradition is our mission
And Moana, there's so much to do
Don't trip on the taro root
That's all you need
We share everything we make
We joke and we weave our baskets
The fishermen come back from the sea
I wanna see
Don't walk away
Moana, stay on the ground now
Our people will need a chief
-And there you are
-There you are
There comes a day
When you're gonna look around
And realize happiness is
Where you are
Consider the coconut
-The what
-Consider its tree
We use each part of the coconut
It's all we need
We make our nets from the fibers
The water is sweet inside
We use the leaves to build fires
We cook up the meat inside
Consider the coconuts
The trunks and the leaves
The island gives us what we need
And no one leaves
That's right, we stay
We're safe and we're well-provided
And when we look to the future
There you are
You'll be okay
In time you'll learn just as I did
You must find happiness
right where you are
I like to dance with the water
The undertow and the waves
The water is mischievous
Ha! I like how it misbehaves
The village may think I'm crazy
Or say that I drift too far
But once you know what you like
Well, there you are
You are your father's daughter
Stubbornness and pride
Mind what he says but remember
You may hear a voice inside
And if the voice starts to whisper
To follow the farthest star
Moana, that voice inside
is who you are
-Uh-huh.
-Dad!
I was only looking at the boats.
I wasn't gonna get on 'em.
(SIGHS)
Come on.
There's something I need to show you.
I've wanted to bring you here from
the moment you opened your eyes.
This is a sacred place.
A place of chiefs.
There will come a time...
when you will stand on this peak
and place a stone on this mountain.
Like I did. Like my father did.
And his father, and every chief
that has ever been.
And on that day...
when you add your stone...
you will raise this whole island higher.
You are the future of our people, Moana.
And they are not out there.
They are right here.
It's time to be who they need you to be.
-We make our nets from the fibers
-We weave our nets from the fibers
-The water is sweet inside
-A real tasty treat inside
-We use the leaves to build fires
-We sing these songs in our choirs
-To cook up the meat inside
-We have mouths to feed inside
-The village believes in us
-That's right
The village believes
The island gives us what we need
And no one leaves
So here I'll stay
My home, my people beside me
And when I think of tomorrow
There we are
I'll lead the way
I'll have my people to guide me
We'll build our future together
Where we are
'Cause every path leads ya back to
Where you are
You can find happiness right
And every storm, this roof leaks,
no matter how many fronds I add.
MOANA: Fixed!
Not the fronds.
-Wind shifted the post.
-Ah!
-Mmm! That's good pork!
-(PUA GRUNTING)
Oh! I didn't mean... I wasn't...
(CLEARS THROAT) What?
They're calling me, so I gotta... Bye!
VILLAGER: Ow! Ow! Ow!
You're doing great.
Is it done yet?
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
So close.
(DRUM BEATS PLAYING)
I'm curious about that chicken
eating the rock.
He seems to lack the basic intelligence
required for pretty much everything.
Should we maybe just cook him?
Sometimes our strengths lie
beneath the surface.
Far beneath in some cases.
But I'm sure there's more to Heihei
-than meets the eye.
-(HEIHEI CAWING)
It's the harvest.
This morning,
I was husking the coconuts and...
Well...
we should clear the diseased trees
and we will start a new grove.
There.
Thanks, Moana.
She's doing great.
This suits you.
FISHERMAN: Chief?
(PANTING)
There's something you need to see.
Our traps in the east lagoon...
they're pulling up less and less fish.
Then we'll rotate the fishing grounds.
Uh, we have. There's no fish.
Oh. Then we'll fish
the far side of the island.
We tried.
The windward side.
And the leeward side, the shallows,
the channel.
We've tried the whole lagoon.
They're just gone.
TUI:
Have you tried using a different bait?
FISHERMAN: I don't think it's the bait.
There's no fish.
It seems like
it's getting worse and worse.
TUI: Of course, I understand
you have reason for concern.
I will talk to the council.
I'm sure we...
What if we fish beyond the reef?
No one goes beyond the reef.
I know. But if there are no fish
in the lagoon...
-Moana.
-And there's a whole ocean.
We have one rule.
An old rule, when there were fish.
-A rule that keeps us safe...
-But Dad, I...
...instead of endangering our people
so you can run right back to the water.
(EXHALES)
(HUFFING)
Every time I think you're past this...
No one goes beyond the reef!
Well, it's not like you said it
in front of your dad.
Standing on a boat.
I didn't say go beyond the reef,
because I want to be on the ocean.
But you still do.
(MOANA SIGHS)
-He's hard on you because...
-Because he doesn't get me.
Because he was you.
Drawn to the ocean.
Down by the shore.
He took a canoe, Moana.
He crossed the reef...
and found an unforgiving sea.
Waves like mountains.
His best friend begged
to be on that boat.
Your dad couldn't save him.
He's hoping he can save you.
Sometimes...
who we wish we were,
what we wish we could do...
it's just not meant to be.
I've been staring
at the edge of the water
Long as I can remember
Never really knowing why
I wish I could be the perfect daughter
But I come back to the water
No matter how hard I try
Every turn I take
Every trail I track
Every path I make
Every road leads back
To the place I know
Where I cannot go
Where I long to be
See the line where the
sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea
Stays behind me
One day I'll know
If I go, there's just no telling
how far I'll go
I know everybody on this island
Seems so happy on this island
Everything is by design
(SQUEALS)
I know everybody on this island
Has a role on this island
So maybe I can roll with mine
I can lead with pride
I can make us strong
I'll be satisfied
If I play along
But the voice inside
Sings a different song
What is wrong with me
See the light as it shines on the sea
It's blinding
But no one knows
How deep it goes
And it seems like it's calling out to me
So come find me
And let me know
What's beyond that line
Will I cross that line
The line where the sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea
stays behind me
One day I'll know
How far I'll go
Whoa.
We're okay, Pua.
I can do this.
(EXHALES)
There's more fish beyond the reef.
There's more beyond the reef.
(PUA SQUEALING)
Not so bad.
(GASPS)
-(PUA SQUEALING FRANTICALLY)
-Pua!
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
(PUA SQUEALING)
(WINCES)
Whatever just happened...
blame it on the pig.
Gramma.
Are you gonna tell Dad?
I'm his mom.
I don't have to tell him anything.
He was right.
About going out there.
It's time to put my stone
on the mountain.
Okay. Well, then, head on back.
Put that stone up there.
Why aren't you trying
to talk me out of it?
You said that's what you wanted.
It is.
(GRAMMA HUMMING)
GRAMMA: When I die...
I'm going to come back as one of these.
Or I chose the wrong tattoo.
Why are you acting weird?
I'm the village crazy lady.
That's my job.
If there's something you want to tell me,
just tell me!
Is there something you wanna tell me?
Is there something you want to hear?
You've been told
all our people's stories...
but one.
What is this place?
Do you really think
our ancestors stayed within the reef?
(GASPS)
Ooh!
MOANA: What's in there?
The answer to the question
you keep asking yourself.
Who are you meant to be?
Go inside...
bang the drum...
and find out.
(GASPS)
Whoa.
Oh.
Bang the drum.
(DRUM BEAT ECHOING)
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
(ETHEREAL VOICES ECHOING)
(SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
We read the wind and the sky
When the sun is high
We sail the length of the seas
On the ocean breeze
At night we name every star
We know where we are
We know who we are
Who we are
We set a course to find
A brand new island
everywhere we roam
We keep our island in our mind
And when it's time to find home
We know the way
We are explorers reading every sign
We tell the stories of our elders
In a never-ending chain
We know the way
We were voyagers.
We were voyagers!
We were voyagers! We were voyagers!
Why'd we stop?
Maui.
When he stole from the mother island,
darkness fell.
Te Kā awoke.
Monsters lurked
and boats stopped coming back.
To protect our people,
the ancient chiefs forbid voyaging...
and now we have forgotten who we are.
And the darkness
has continued to spread...
chasing away our fish...
draining the life...
from island after island.
Our island.
But, one day...
someone will journey beyond our reef,
find Maui...
deliver him across the great ocean...
to restore the heart of Te Fiti.
I was there that day.
The ocean chose you.
I thought it was a dream.
(YELPS)
Nope!
Our ancestors
believed Maui lies there...
at the bottom of his hook.
Follow it, and you will find him.
But why would it choose me?
I don't even know
how to make it past the reef.
But I know who does!
(SIGHS)
VILLAGER 1: The crops
are turning black.
VILLAGER 2: What about the fish?
VILLAGER 3:
This is happening all over the island.
-Please, please settle down.
-What are you going to do?
We will dig new fields.
We will find a way to...
We can stop the darkness!
Save our island!
There's a cavern of boats.
Huge canoes.
We can take them, find Maui,
make him restore the heart.
We were voyagers.
We can voyage again!
You told me to help our people.
This is how we help our people.
Dad?
What are you doing?
I should've burned those boats
a long time ago!
No! Don't!
We have to find Maui.
We have to restore the heart!
There is no heart!
This is just a rock!
No!
(HORN BLOWING)
Chief! It's your mother!
Mother...
TUI: What can be done?
(VILLAGERS TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(WEAKLY) Go.
Gramma.
Go.
Not now. I can't.
You must!
The ocean chose you.
Follow the fish hook.
Gramma...
And when you find Maui...
you grab him by the ear. You say...
"I am Moana of Motunui.
"You will board my boat...
"sail across the sea...
"and restore the heart of Te Fiti."
(VOICE BREAKING) I can't leave you.
There is nowhere you could go
that I won't be with you.
Go!
There's a line
where the sky meets the sea
And it calls me
But no one knows
How far it goes
All that time wondering where I need
to be is behind me
I'm on my own
To worlds unknown
Every turn I take
Every trail I track
Is a choice I make
Now I can't turn back
from the great unknown
Where I go alone
Where I long to be
See her light up the night in the sea
She calls me
And yes, I know
That I can go
There's a moon in the sky
And the wind is behind me
Soon I'll know
How far I'll go
I am Moana of Motunui.
You will board my boat...
sail across the sea
and restore the heart of Te Fiti.
-(GRUNTING) I am Moana...
-(THUDDING)
-of Motu...
-(THUDDING CONTINUES)
...nui.
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
Heihei?
(CAWING LOUDLY)
(CAWING STOPS)
(CAWS AND STOPS AGAIN)
It's okay. You're all right.
See?
There we go. Nice water.
The ocean is a friend of mine.
Heihei?
Heihei!
(GASPS)
Stay.
Okay. Next stop, Maui.
I am Moana of Motunui.
You will board my boat...
sail... across the sea...
and restore the heart of Te Fiti.
(MUMBLING) I am Moana of Motu...
Board my boat!
Oh, no.
(GROANING IN FRUSTRATION)
No, no, no!
Ocean...
can I get a little help?
No, no.
Please.
Come on!
Help me!
Please!
(SCREAMS)
(CLUCKING)
(CAWS IN ALARM)
Whew!
Um...
What?
I said help me!
And wrecking my boat?
Not helping!
Fish pee in you all day!
So...
(HEIHEI CLUCKING)
Maui?
Maui!
Maui, demigod of the wind and sea...
I am Moana of Motunui.
You will board my boat.
No. You will board my boat.
Yeah. I am Moana of Motunui.
You will board my...
Boat! A boat!
The gods have given me a...
(SCREAMING)
(MOANA CLEARS THROAT)
Maui, shapeshifter...
demigod of the wind and sea...
-I am Moana of...
-Hero of men.
What?
It's actually, Maui, shapeshifter,
demigod of the wind and sea...
hero of men.
I interrupted.
From the top. Hero of men. Go.
I am...
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
And women. Men and women.
Both. All.
Not a guy, girl thing.
You know, Maui is a hero to all.
You're doing great.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
What? No! I'm here to...
Of course.
Yes, yes, yes.
Maui always has time for his fans.
When you use a bird to write with...
it's called tweeting.
(CHUCKLES) I know, not every day
you get a chance to meet your hero.
You are not my hero.
And I'm not here
so you can sign my oar!
I'm here 'cause
you stole the heart of Te Fiti!
And you will board my boat...
and sail across the sea and put it back!
Um...
Yeah, it almost sounded
like you don't like me...
which is impossible because...
I got stuck here for 1,000 years...
trying to get the heart
as a gift for you mortals.
So you could have the power
to create life itself.
Yeah. So, what I believe
you were trying to say...
is "thank you."
-"Thank you?"
-You're welcome.
What? No, no, no!
I didn't... I wasn't...
Why would I ever say that?
Okay, okay.
I see what's happening
Yeah
You're face to face with greatness
and it's strange
You don't even know how you feel
It's adorable
Well it's nice to see that humans
never change
Open your eyes
Let's begin
Yes, it's really me
It's Maui
Breathe it in
I know it's a lot
The hair
The bod
When you're staring at a demigod
What can I say except
You're welcome
For the tides, the sun, the sky
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
You're welcome
I'm just an ordinary demiguy
Hey!
What has two thumbs
and pulled up the sky
When you were waddling yay high?
This guy
When the nights got cold
Who stole you fire from down below?
You're looking at him yo
Oh also I lassoed the sun
You're welcome
To stretch your days and bring you fun
Also I harnessed the breeze
You're welcome
To fill your sails and shake your trees
So what can I say except
You're welcome
For the islands I pulled from the sea
There's no need to pray
It's okay
You're welcome
Ha
I guess it's just my way of being me
You're welcome
Well come to think of it
Kid, honestly I could go on and on
I could explain every
natural phenomenon
The tide, the grass, the ground
Oh that was Maui just messing around
I killed an eel
I buried its guts
Sprouted a tree
Now you got coconuts
What's the lesson?
What is the take away?
Don't mess with Maui
when he's on a breakaway
And the tapestry here on my skin
Is a map of the victories I win
Look where I've been
I make everything happen
Look at that
Mean Mini-Maui just tickety tappin'
Ha ha
Hey
Well anyway let me say
You're welcome
For the wonderful world you know
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
You're welcome
Well come to think of it
I gotta go
Hey it's your day to say
You're welcome
'Cause I'm gonna need that boat
I'm sailing away away
You're welcome
'Cause Maui can do
everything but float
-You're welcome
Huh?
And thank you!
Hey!
Let me out! You lying, slimy son of a...
(HUMMING)
You're welcome
You're so welcome.
No. I'm not going to Te Fiti
with some kid.
I'm going to get my hook.
You have yours and
I'm not Maui without mine.
Okay, talk to the back.
Boat snack.
(SCREAMING)
Good riddance,
you filthy pile of pebbles.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't look at me like that.
It's a beautiful cave.
She's gonna love it.
And I'm going to love you in ma belly.
Now, let's fatten you up, drumstick.
I could watch that all day.
Okay. Enjoy the island.
Maui, out.
No! Stop!
Hey! You have to put back the heart!
(CLUCKS)
Did not see that coming.
I am Moana of Motunui.
This is my canoe...
and you will journey to...
All right, get over it. We gotta move.
And she's back.
I am Moana of Motunui...
It was Moana, right?
Yes.
And you will restore the heart!
All right. I'm out.
Oh, come on!
What is your problem?
Are you afraid of it?
No! No.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
I'm not afraid.
Stay out of it
or you're sleeping in my armpit.
You, stop it.
That is not a heart. It is a curse.
The second I took it,
I got blasted outta the sky...
and I lost my hook.
Get it away from me.
Get this away?
Hey, hey, hey! I'm a demigod, okay?
Stop that. I will smite you!
You wanna get smote?
Smotten?
Listen, that thing doesn't give you
power to create life...
it's a homing beacon of death.
If you don't put it away,
bad things are gonna come for it.
Come for this? The heart?
You mean this heart right here?
Don't, you can't
raise your voice like that!
-Come and get it!
-(MAUI SHUSHING)
You are gonna get us killed!
No, I'm gonna get us to Te Fiti,
so you can put it back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Kakamora.
Kaka-what?
Murdering little pirates.
Wonder what they're here for.
They're kinda cute.
Ocean!
Do something! Help us!
The ocean doesn't help you,
you help yourself!
Tighten the halyard. Bind the stays!
You can't sail?
I, uh...
I am self-taught.
Can't you shapeshift or something?
Do you see my hook?
No magic hook, no magic powers!
Their boat is turning into more boats!
(HORN BLOWING)
Yep, I just did that.
MOANA: No, no!
Heihei!
Maui!
They took the heart!
That's a chicken.
The heart is in the...
(FRUSTRATED GRUNTING)
We have to get him back!
Maui!
Cheeeehoooo!
There! Right there!
You're turning?
What are you doing?
Escaping!
The heart!
Forget it! You'll never get it back!
Besides, you got a better one.
Hey!
What am I gonna steer with?
They're just gonna kill ya!
Coconuts.
Got it!
Hey!
MOANA: Yeah!
We did it!
Congratulations
on not being dead, girlie.
You surprise me.
But I'm still not taking that thing back.
You wanna get to Te Fiti you gotta
go through a whole ocean of bad.
Not to mention Te Kā.
Lava monster?
Ever defeat a lava monster?
No. Have you?
I'm not going on a suicide mission
with some mortal.
You can't restore the heart without me...
and me says no.
I'm getting my hook.
End of discussion.
You'd be a hero.
That's what you're all about, right?
Little girl, I am a hero.
Maybe you were.
But now...
now you're just the guy
who stole the heart of Te Fiti.
The guy who cursed the world.
You're no one's hero.
(SCOFFS) No one?
But...
put this back...
save the world...
you'd be everyone's hero.
Maui! Maui! Maui!
You're so amazing!
We'd never make it without my hook.
Not past Te Kā.
Then we get your hook.
We get your hook, take out Te Kā,
restore the heart.
Unless you don't wanna be...
Maui, demigod of the wind and sea.
Hero to...
all.
First, we get my hook.
Then save the world.
Deal?
Deal.
Worth a shot.
Okay, we go east.
To the lair of Tamatoa.
If anyone has my hook,
it's that beady-eyed bottom-feeder.
Teach me to sail.
My job is to deliver Maui
across the great ocean.
I should...
I should be sailing.
It's called wayfinding, princess.
And it's not just sails and knots...
it's seeing where you're going
in your mind.
Knowing where you are...
by knowing where you've been.
Okay, first, I'm not a princess.
I am the daughter of the chief.
-Same difference.
-No.
If you wear a dress,
and you have an animal sidekick...
you're a princess.
You are not a wayfinder.
You will never be a wayfinder,
you will never be a...
Really? Blow dart in my butt cheek?
You are a bad person.
If you can talk, you can teach.
Wayfinding.
Lesson one. Hit it.
(GROANS)
Pull the sheet.
Not the sheet.
No.
Nope.
Nope. No.
Tried that one already.
You're measuring the stars,
not giving the sky a high-five.
If the current's warm,
you're going the right way.
It's cold.
Wait, it's getting warmer. (GASPS)
Aah! That is disgusting!
What is wrong with you?
(MAUI CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
We're here?
See, told you I could do it!
Motunui?
I'm home?
-TUI: Moana!
-Dad?
SINA: Moana!
Mom?
Help!
No!
Moana!
(GASPS)
MAUI: Enjoy your beauty rest?
You know,
a real wayfinder never sleeps...
so they actually get
where they need to go.
Muscle up, buttercup.
We're here.
You're sure this guy's gonna
have your hook?
Tamatoa? Oh, he'll have it.
He's a scavenger. Collects stuff.
Thinks it makes him look cool.
Ah!
And for Tamatoa, trust me...
my hook is the coolest collectible.
And he lives up there?
No, no, no.
That's just the entrance...
to Lalotai.
(GASPS) Lalotai?
Realm of monsters?
We're going to the realm of monsters?
We? No. Me.
You are gonna stay here
with the other chicken. (CLUCKING)
That's what I'm talking about.
Gimme some.
Come on. That was a good one.
How do you not get it?
I called her a chicken,
there's a chicken on the boat.
I know she's human,
but that's not the...
You know what? Forget it. Forget it!
I'm not explaining it to you.
'Cause then it's not funny.
(GRUNTING)
(MOANA GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
So, daughter of the chief...
I thought you stayed in the village.
You know, kissing babies and things.
Hey, I'm just trying to understand...
why your people decided to send...
How do I phrase this? You.
My people didn't send me.
The ocean did.
The ocean?
Makes sense.
You're what, eight? Can't sail.
Obvious choice.
It chose me for a reason.
If the ocean's so smart...
why didn't it just take the heart
back to Te Fiti itself?
Or bring me my hook?
The ocean's straight up kooky-dooks.
But I'm sure it's not wrong about you.
You're the Chosen One!
The ocean chose you for a reason.
If you start singing,
I'm gonna throw up.
So, not seeing an entrance.
Yes, because it only appears...
after a human sacrifice.
Kidding. (LAUGHS)
So serious.
(COUGHING)
(SHOUTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Don't worry...
it's a lot farther down than it looks.
Cheeeehoooo!
I am still falling!
(WATER SPLASHES)
You can do this.
Go!
And he sticks the landing.
Huh?
What? Dum-dum, she's not even here.
No mortal's gonna jump
into the realm of...
Huh?
Well, she's dead.
Okay, let's get my hook.
Ew! Ew, ew, ew, ew.
(PANTING)
(SCREECHING)
(CREATURE GROWLING)
Maui's fishhook!
Yeah! (GROANS)
(GASPS) Sorry!
I thought you were a monster...
But I found your hook.
And, you're right, this Tamatoa guy
really likes his treasure.
Stay.
What? No. I'm the one who found...
Listen. For a thousand years...
I've only been thinking of
keeping this hair silky...
getting my hook...
and being awesome again.
And it's not getting screwed up
by a mortal...
who has no business
inside of a monster cave, except...
Except...
maybe as bait.
Huh?
Wow!
The shiny, glittery cave.
And just like me...
it is covered in sparkly treasure.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
You're not selling it!
This is stupid!
I'm just gonna walk up and get it!
You go up there, he will kill you.
Just stick to the plan.
Oh, when he shows up,
keep him distracted.
Make him talk about himself.
He loves bragging about
how great he is.
You two must get along swell.
No, not since I ripped off his leg.
You ripped off his...
Maui?
(LAUGHING)
What have we here?
It's a sparkly, shiny... Wait a minute.
(YELPS)
Ugh! It's a human!
What are you doing down here,
in the realm of the...
Just pick an eye, babe.
I can't concentrate
on what I'm saying if you keep...
Yeah, pick one, pick one!
You're a funny-looking little thing,
aren't you?
Don't! That's my gramma's!
"That's my gramma's!"
I ate my gramma!
And it took a week,
'cause she was absolutely humongous.
Why are you here?
'Cause you're amazing!
And we mortals have heard of the tale
of the crab who became a legend!
And I just had to know...
how you became so...
crabulous?
Are you just trying to get me
to talk about myself?
Because if you are...
I will gladly do so.
Huh?
In song form!
Well, Tamatoa
hasn't always been this glam
I was a drab little crab once
Now I know I can be happy as a clam
Because I'm beautiful, baby
And did your granny say
Listen to your heart
Be who you are on the inside
I need three words
To tear her argument apart
Your granny lied
I'd rather be shiny
Like a treasure
From a sunken pirate wreck
Scrub the deck
And make it look shiny
I will sparkle like a
Wealthy woman's neck
Just a sec
Don't ya know
Fish are dumb, dumb, dumb
They chase anything that glitters
Beginners
Oh, and here they come, come, come
To the brightest thing that glitters
Mm, fish dinners
I just love free food
And you look like seafood
MAUI: Hey, crab cake!
I'm back.
It's Maui Time!
(GASPS)
What do you say, little buddy?
Giant hawk? Coming up!
Cheeeehoooo!
Well, well, well.
Little Maui's having
trouble with his look
Ya little semi-demi-mini-god
Ouch
What a terrible performance
Get the hook
Get it?
You don't swing it
Like you used to, man
Yet I have to give you
Credit for my start
And your tattoos on the outside
For just like you
I made myself a work of art
I'll never hide
I can't
I'm too shiny
Watch me dazzle
Like a diamond in the rough
Strut my stuff
My stuff is so shiny
Send your armies
But they'll never be enough
My shell's too tough
Maui, man
You can try, try, try
But you can't expect a demigod
To beat a decapod
Look it up
You will die, die, die
Now it's time for me to take apart
Your achin' heart
Far from the ones who abandoned you
Chasing the love of these humans
Who made you feel wanted
You tried to be tough
But your armor's just not hard enough
Maui
Now it's time to kick your heinie
Ever seen someone so shiny
Soak it in
'Cause it's the last you'll ever see
C'est la vie
Mon ami
I'm so shiny
Now I eat you so
prepare your final plea
Just for me
You'll never be quite as shiny
You wish you were nice and shiny
-MOANA: Hey!
-Huh?
I got something shiny for ya!
The heart of Te Fiti.
You can't run from me!
Oh, you can. You keep surprising me.
There's only so far you can get
on those two little legs.
(YELLS)
(LAUGHING)
The power of creation...
for a crustacean.
Where is it? Where is it?
We gotta go!
What about the heart?
He can have it. I've got a better one.
Yes, I have the...
Wait a minute.
I see, she's taken a barnacle
and she's covered it in...
bioluminescent algae as a diversion.
Come back here!
Cheeeehoooo!
Hey!
Did you like the song?
(THUDDING)
We're alive!
Listen...
I appreciate what you did down there.
Mm-hmm.
-Took guts.
-Mm-hmm.
-But...
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to be sincere for once,
and it feels like you're distracted.
No, no. No way!
Really? Because you're looking at me
like I have a...
(GASPS)
shark head.
What? Do you have a shark head?
Look, the point is...
for a little girl, child, thing,
whatever...
who had no business
being down there...
you did me a solid.
But you also almost died.
And I couldn't even beat that dumb crab.
So, chances of beating Te Kā?
Bupkis.
We're never making it to Te Fiti.
This mission is cursed.
It's not cursed.
Shark head.
It is not cursed.
(GROANS)
Cursed.
What can I say except
We're dead soon
Can you at least try?
Giant hawk.
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
We're dead soon
All right, break time's over.
Get up.
Why? Are you gonna
give me a speech?
Tell me I can beat Te Kā
'cause I'm "Maui?"
Take a hike, Tiny.
How do you get your tattoos?
They show up. When I earn them.
How'd you earn that one?
What's that for?
That's man's discovery of Nunya.
What's Nunya?
Nunya business.
I'll just keep asking.
What's it for?
You need to stop doing that.
-Back off.
-Just tell me what it is.
I said back off.
Is it why your hook's not working?
You don't wanna talk, don't talk.
You wanna throw me off the boat...
throw me off.
You wanna tell me
I don't know what I'm doing...
I know I don't.
I have no idea why the ocean chose me.
You're right.
But my island is dying...
so I am here.
It's just me and you.
And I want to help...
but I can't if you don't let me.
(SIGHS)
MAUI: I wasn't born a demigod.
I had human parents.
They took one look and decided...
they did not want me.
They threw me into the sea...
like I was nothing.
Somehow, I was found by the gods.
They gave me the hook.
They made me...
Maui.
And back to the humans I went.
I gave them islands, fire, coconuts.
Anything they could ever want.
You took the heart for them.
You did everything for them.
So they'd love you.
It was never enough.
Maybe the gods found you for a reason.
Maybe the ocean brought you to them...
because it saw someone
who was worthy of being saved.
But the gods aren't the ones
who make you Maui.
You are.
Okay, okay.
I love you, too, buddy.
Cheeeehoooo!
Yeah!
Next stop, Te Fiti.
What?
I figured it out.
You know, the ocean used to love
when I pulled up islands...
'cause your ancestors
would sail her seas and find 'em.
All those new lands, new villages.
It was the water that connected 'em all.
And if I were the ocean...
I think I'd be looking for
a curly-haired non-princess...
to start that again.
That is literally the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
Probably should have saved it
for Te Fiti.
I did.
Moana of Motunui...
I believe you have officially
delivered Maui across the great sea.
Moana! Moana! Moana!
You're so amazing!
It's time.
Go save the world.
Cheeeehoooo!
(GASPS)
(ROARING)
(GROANS)
Maui!
What are you doing?
Finding you a better way in!
-We won't make it!
-Yes, we will!
-Turn around!
-No!
Moana, stop!
No!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Are you okay?
Maui?
I told you to turn back.
I thought we could make it.
We?
I thought I could make it.
We can fix it.
It was made by the gods.
You can't fix it!
Next time we'll be more careful.
Te Kā was stuck on the barrier islands.
It's lava, it can't go in the water.
We can find a way around.
I'm not going back.
We still have to restore the heart.
My hook is cracked.
One more hit, and it's over.
Maui, you have to restore the heart.
Without my hook, I am nothing.
That's not true!
Without my hook, I am nothing!
(SHUDDERING)
We are only here...
because you stole the heart
in the first place.
No, we're here because
the ocean told you you're special...
and you believed it.
I am Moana of Motunui.
-You will board my boat...
-Goodbye, Moana.
...sail across the sea...
I'm not killing myself...
so you can prove
you're something you're not!
...and restore the heart of Te Fiti!
The ocean chose me!
It chose wrong.
Maui!
Why did you bring me here?
I'm not the right person.
You have to choose someone else.
Choose someone else.
Please.
(SOBBING)
No.
GRAMMA: You're a long ways
past the reef.
Gramma?
Guess I chose the right tattoo.
Gramma!
I tried, Gramma.
I couldn't do it.
It's not your fault.
I never should have put so much
on your shoulders.
If you are ready to go home...
I will be with you.
Why do you hesitate?
I don't know.
I know a girl from an island
She stands apart from the crowd
She loves the sea and her people
She makes her whole family proud
Sometimes the world
seems against you
The journey may leave a scar
But scars can heal and reveal just
Where you are
The people you love will change you
The things you have
learned will guide you
And nothing on earth can silence
The quiet voice still inside you
And when that voice starts to whisper
Moana, you've come so far
Moana, listen
Do you know who you are?
Who am I?
I am a girl who loves my island
And the girl who loves the sea
It calls me
I am the daughter of the village chief
We are descended from voyagers
Who found their way across the world
They call me
I've delivered us to where we are
I have journeyed farther
I am everything I've learned and more
Still it calls me
And the call isn't out there at all
It's inside me
It's like the tide
Always falling and rising
I will carry you here in my heart
You remind me
That come what may
I know the way
I am Moana
(GRUNTS)
I am Moana of Motunui.
Aboard my boat...
I will sail across the sea...
and restore the heart of Te Fiti.
Te Kā can't follow us into the water.
We make it past the barrier islands...
we make it to Te Fiti.
None of which you understand...
-because you are a chicken.
-(CLUCKING)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
No!
Heihei! No, no, no!
Nice work!
Te Fiti.
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(EAGLE SCREECHING)
Maui!
You came back.
(CHUCKLES)
But your hook.
One more hit and...
Te Kā's gotta catch me first.
(TE KĀ ROARING)
I got your back, Chosen One.
Go save the world.
Maui.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Cheeeehoooo!
(SCREAMING)
Hot-hot-hot, hot-hot-hot!
Hey, Te Kā!
Shark head!
Cheeeehoooo!
(GROANS)
Moana!
Get the heart to the spiral!
Te Fiti...
it's gone.
MAUI: Te Kā!
(SHOUTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Let her come to me.
(ROARING)
I have crossed the horizon to find you
I know your name
They have stolen the
heart from inside you
But this does not define you
This is not who you are
You know who you are
Who you truly are.
Te Fiti!
(HEIHEI SCREECHING)
The chicken lives.
I'm sorry about your hook.
Well, hook, no hook...
I'm Maui.
(GASPS) Te Fiti!
(LAUGHING SHEEPISHLY)
Hey, I mean, how you been?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Look, what I did was...
wrong.
I have no excuse.
I'm sorry.
(GASPS)
You know, it'd be rude to refuse
a gift from a goddess.
Cheeeehoooo!
Thank you.
Your kind gesture is
deeply appreciated.
Cheeeehoooo.
Gonna miss you, drumstick.
You could come with us, you know.
My people are going to need
a master wayfinder.
They already have one.
See you out there, Maui.
See you out there, Moana.
Cheeeehoooo!
Mom! Dad!
Moana!
I may have gone
a little ways past the reef.
It suits you.
MALE VILLAGER: She's back!
-FEMALE VILLAGER: Moana!
-(PUA SQUEALING)
MOANA: Pua!
Moana!
Welcome home!
(VILLAGERS CHEERING)
We set a course to find
A brand new island
everywhere we roam
We keep our island in our mind
And when it's time to find home
We know the way
We are explorers reading every sign
We tell the stories of our elders
In a never-ending chain
We know the way
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I've been staring
at the edge of the water
Long as I can remember
Never really knowing why
I wish I could be the perfect daughter
But I come back to the water
No matter how hard I try
Every turn I take
Every trail I track
Every path I make
Every road leads back
To the place I know
Where I cannot go
Where I long to be
See the line
where the sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea
Stays behind me
One day I'll know
If I go, there's just no telling
how far I'll go
I know everybody on this island
Seems so happy on this island
Everything is by design
I know everybody on this island
Has a role on this island
So maybe I can roll with mine
I can lead with pride
I can make us strong
I'll be satisfied
If I play along
But the voice inside
Sings a different song
What is wrong with me
See the light as it shines on the sea
It's blinding
But no one knows
How deep it goes
And it seems like it's calling out to me
So come find me
And let me know
What's beyond that line
Will I cross that line
See the line
where the sky meets the sea
It calls me
And no one knows
How far it goes
If the wind in my sail on the sea
stays behind me
One day I'll know
How far I'll go
(FOLK MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I see what's happening
Yeah
You're face to face with greatness
and it's strange
You don't even know how you feel
It's adorable
It's nice to see that humans
never change
Open your eyes
Let's begin
Yes, it's really me
Breathe it in
I know it's a lot
The hair
The bod
When you're staring at a demigod
So what can I say except
You're welcome
For the tides, the sun, the sky
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
You're welcome
I'm just an ordinary demiguy
What can I say except
You're welcome
For the tides, the sun, the sky
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
You're welcome
I'm just an ordinary demiguy
Honestly, I could go on and on
I could explain
every natural phenomenon
The tide, the grass, the ground
Oh, that was me, I was messing around
I killed a snake
I buried its guts
Sprouted a tree
Now you got coconuts
What's the lesson?
What is the take away?
Don't mess with Maui
when he's on a breakaway
And the tapestry here on my skin
Is a map of the victories I win
Look where I've been
I make everything happen
Look at that
Mean Mini-Maui just tickety tappin'
Singing and scratchin'
Flipping and snappin'
People are clappin', hearing me rap
Bring the chorus back in
Well, anyway let me say
You're welcome
For the wonderful world you know
Hey, it's okay, it's okay
You're welcome
Well, come to think of it
I gotta go
Hey, it's your day to say
You're welcome
'Cause I'm gonna need that boat
I'm sailing away, away
You're welcome
'Cause Maui's the ultimate God
Shiny
I'm so shiny
Didn't help me though, did it?
Still upside down here.
Just need a little push.
(GROANS)
Can we be real?
If my name was Sebastian
and I had a cool Jamaican accent...
you'd totally help me.
You would. You know you would.