1
00:00:11,271 --> 00:00:13,479
- Dad.
- Yes, I'll tell him now.

2
00:00:13,896 --> 00:00:16,312
Of course, now when he... I don't know.

3
00:00:16,396 --> 00:00:18,937
OK. Dad, here he comes.

4
00:00:19,021 --> 00:00:21,854
Here he comes.

5
00:00:23,271 --> 00:00:27,854
Professor, would you like some coffee?

6
00:00:28,771 --> 00:00:31,187
Well... yes, that'd be great, thank you.

7
00:00:32,062 --> 00:00:32,937
Good morning.

8
00:00:37,646 --> 00:00:39,021
Here is your coffee.

9
00:00:39,104 --> 00:00:40,312
And some cookies?

10
00:00:40,437 --> 00:00:42,854
Yes... thank you.

11
00:00:48,187 --> 00:00:49,812
What is it?

12
00:00:52,521 --> 00:00:53,521
Let's see.

13
00:00:54,312 --> 00:00:55,562
- Just one thing.
- Yes.

14
00:00:55,646 --> 00:00:58,021
A small matter.

15
00:00:59,187 --> 00:01:01,687
- Do you have any siblings?
- Moscow, please.

16
00:01:01,771 --> 00:01:04,771
No personal questions.
It's one of the first rules.

17
00:01:04,854 --> 00:01:08,354
I have a friend
who's practically a brother to me.

18
00:01:08,437 --> 00:01:11,812
He was with me in the mine,
on robberies, and in prison.

19
00:01:11,896 --> 00:01:13,187
That's the problem.

20
00:01:13,271 --> 00:01:16,396
I got let out,
but he still has five years left.

21
00:01:16,479 --> 00:01:17,812
Five years, Professor.

22
00:01:17,896 --> 00:01:21,979
Yes, well, sorry,
but I don't see what I can do for your...

23
00:01:22,437 --> 00:01:24,354
friend, brother, or whoever.

24
00:01:24,437 --> 00:01:25,979
No, his son.

25
00:01:26,062 --> 00:01:28,312
- His son?
- Yes, Juanito. My godson.

26
00:01:28,396 --> 00:01:30,312
And he's like a brother to me.

27
00:01:30,396 --> 00:01:33,729
I promised I'd look after him
when I got out of prison.

28
00:01:33,812 --> 00:01:37,854
We haven't seen him for a while,
and we've heard he's not doing well.

29
00:01:37,937 --> 00:01:40,479
He's out of work, almost destitute.

30
00:01:40,562 --> 00:01:44,312
I thought I could get him back on track
and bring him here.

31
00:01:44,396 --> 00:01:48,521
- Being in a heist is back on track?
- Well, this is a respectable heist.

32
00:01:49,229 --> 00:01:53,312
Just look at this guy.
I've never seen him so focused in my life.

33
00:01:53,396 --> 00:01:56,771
If it goes well,
there'll be plenty to go around, right?

34
00:01:56,854 --> 00:01:58,687
- I'm sorry but...
- Professor.

35
00:01:58,771 --> 00:02:01,854
The guy's awesome.
I've known him since we were kids.

36
00:02:01,937 --> 00:02:03,729
He's a pro at everything:

37
00:02:03,812 --> 00:02:05,271
cars, break-ins...

38
00:02:05,354 --> 00:02:09,562
Why do we call you Denver and you Moscow?
And him Helsinki? For safety.

39
00:02:09,646 --> 00:02:12,979
No one can know each other's names.
We can't...

40
00:02:13,062 --> 00:02:14,312
- Yeah.
- Let's see.

41
00:02:14,396 --> 00:02:17,479
I made an exception for your son.
Now your godson?

42
00:02:17,562 --> 00:02:21,271
This isn't a family business.
We can't take on every cousin...

43
00:02:21,354 --> 00:02:23,021
What are you saying, loser?

44
00:02:23,104 --> 00:02:24,604
- Sorry?
- He's the Professor.

45
00:02:24,687 --> 00:02:27,854
We're talking about a kid
who's almost destitute, Dad.

46
00:02:27,937 --> 00:02:30,104
We're saying we'd trust him
with our lives,

47
00:02:30,187 --> 00:02:32,604
and he comes out with
that shit about city names!

48
00:02:32,687 --> 00:02:35,896
Do you know what you can do
with the name "Denver"?

49
00:02:35,979 --> 00:02:38,937
You can stick it up your ass.
My name is Dani, Dad.

50
00:02:39,021 --> 00:02:41,354
I'm Dani, always have been. Also:

51
00:02:41,437 --> 00:02:44,396
your infallible plan for the Royal Mint

52
00:02:44,479 --> 00:02:47,229
is really fucking shit.

53
00:02:47,312 --> 00:02:50,437
Print the bills at a print shop.
It'll be cheaper.

54
00:02:51,312 --> 00:02:52,896
Thank you for the coffee.

55
00:02:57,479 --> 00:03:01,271
That better be the last time
you speak to him like that.

56
00:03:01,354 --> 00:03:04,979
I'm ashamed of you.
Can't you see he's an intellectual?

57
00:03:06,187 --> 00:03:07,937
Well, to each their own.

58
00:03:08,521 --> 00:03:11,604
You have to trust that man
and respect him.

59
00:03:11,687 --> 00:03:13,312
- Don't I respect him?
- No.

60
00:03:13,854 --> 00:03:16,979
No, maybe the kid's right.

61
00:03:17,354 --> 00:03:20,729
If we print them at home,
we'd save ourselves a lot of trouble.

62
00:03:20,812 --> 00:03:23,062
And the cost of weapons...

63
00:03:23,479 --> 00:03:24,646
of ammunition...

64
00:03:26,229 --> 00:03:30,437
Denver, you bring the printer,
we'll download the bills on the internet.

65
00:03:31,937 --> 00:03:35,146
A stroke of genius. No, even better...

66
00:03:35,604 --> 00:03:38,396
I draw the bills, and you color them.

67
00:03:39,437 --> 00:03:41,312
Perhaps we can make two a day.

68
00:03:41,979 --> 00:03:44,729
Look how good I am at drawing.

69
00:03:46,604 --> 00:03:48,937
It's called "Passion for Juanito."

70
00:03:50,062 --> 00:03:51,854
Are you gonna keep this up?

71
00:03:51,937 --> 00:03:56,187
Maybe I'll start throwing punches,
and you'll be printing new teeth.

72
00:03:56,271 --> 00:03:57,562
Fuck off.

73
00:03:57,646 --> 00:04:00,187
Denver, don't get mad. It's a joke.

74
00:04:09,812 --> 00:04:12,896
I woke up in lockdown within our lockdown.

75
00:04:13,146 --> 00:04:16,271
In chains, dazed,
and with a madman in front of me.

76
00:04:16,812 --> 00:04:20,187
I'd lost my freedom,
and I was running out of time.

77
00:04:21,021 --> 00:04:24,062
Within only 15 minutes
of me opening my eyes,

78
00:04:24,396 --> 00:04:26,979
Gandía would've already shot
at most of us.

79
00:04:32,521 --> 00:04:34,396
What are you doing?

80
00:04:34,479 --> 00:04:36,479
I won't hit you
because you're tied up.

81
00:04:36,562 --> 00:04:38,021
Let me go.

82
00:04:38,437 --> 00:04:40,562
Then we'll see who's punching who.

83
00:04:48,812 --> 00:04:50,187
Why didn't you kill me?

84
00:04:50,896 --> 00:04:53,729
- I'm no murderer.
- You're not a murderer?

85
00:04:54,521 --> 00:04:58,104
You tried to kill Nairobi and Helsinki,
and you're not a murderer?

86
00:05:00,562 --> 00:05:02,729
Why didn't you kill me?

87
00:05:04,229 --> 00:05:05,521
You're my guinea pig.

88
00:05:06,271 --> 00:05:07,187
And you?

89
00:05:10,521 --> 00:05:12,312
What the hell are you?

90
00:05:13,021 --> 00:05:14,729
I'm the tamer.

91
00:05:15,187 --> 00:05:17,187
And you're lucky.

92
00:05:18,146 --> 00:05:20,104
I'm going to tame you.

93
00:05:28,354 --> 00:05:31,062
The next time you kick me,
I'll beat you so hard,

94
00:05:31,146 --> 00:05:33,646
your crippled friend
won't recognize you.

95
00:05:33,729 --> 00:05:35,729
Keep still.

96
00:05:40,354 --> 00:05:42,354
Listen to me. I'll explain.

97
00:05:42,437 --> 00:05:44,021
It's very easy.

98
00:05:46,771 --> 00:05:47,854
Son of a bitch.

99
00:05:48,271 --> 00:05:49,104
Look.

100
00:05:51,604 --> 00:05:53,562
My first card is you:

101
00:05:54,979 --> 00:05:55,896
missing.

102
00:05:56,771 --> 00:06:02,187
They have no choice but to look for you.
And they're going about it like maniacs.

103
00:06:05,229 --> 00:06:08,896
Divided and nervous. I'm already winning.

104
00:06:10,771 --> 00:06:12,479
The next card:

105
00:06:13,521 --> 00:06:14,604
break up the team.

106
00:06:15,312 --> 00:06:17,187
Didn't you wonder how I escaped?

107
00:06:24,562 --> 00:06:25,646
This is Gandía,

108
00:06:25,729 --> 00:06:28,354
head of security at the Bank of Spain.

109
00:06:28,437 --> 00:06:29,812
I'm hidden,

110
00:06:29,896 --> 00:06:33,687
safe and sound,
and ready to undertake any action

111
00:06:33,771 --> 00:06:35,854
that may be necessary to regain

112
00:06:35,937 --> 00:06:38,937
- control and safety...
- He wants to kill us one by one!

113
00:06:39,021 --> 00:06:40,937
Stay together. He's watching!

114
00:06:41,646 --> 00:06:44,812
As you've just heard,
I'm in wonderful company.

115
00:07:52,062 --> 00:07:54,229
You need to start behaving better.

116
00:07:54,604 --> 00:07:57,771
Otherwise, you'll end up immobilized,

117
00:07:58,396 --> 00:08:02,271
tied up, gagged, and blindfolded.

118
00:08:03,354 --> 00:08:07,979
Then we won't be able to
get to know each other, OK?

119
00:08:15,229 --> 00:08:17,937
I just wanted to thank Palermo.

120
00:08:18,021 --> 00:08:21,937
His tip on escaping from my handcuffs
by dislocating my thumb

121
00:08:22,021 --> 00:08:23,729
made me a free man.

122
00:08:23,812 --> 00:08:26,687
Thanks to him,
I hope to be able to help you.

123
00:08:26,771 --> 00:08:28,187
And all hell breaks loose...

124
00:08:33,562 --> 00:08:34,604
Is that true?

125
00:08:34,687 --> 00:08:38,854
If you prefer to believe a psychopath
over one of us, that's up to you.

126
00:08:39,479 --> 00:08:42,562
Silence. You can speak at your trial,
son of a bitch.

127
00:08:57,437 --> 00:08:59,604
- I need to use the bathroom.
- Later.

128
00:08:59,687 --> 00:09:00,937
I'm telling you...

129
00:09:02,896 --> 00:09:04,812
my stomach doesn't feel good.

130
00:09:05,396 --> 00:09:07,646
I need to go to the bathroom urgently.

131
00:09:17,937 --> 00:09:18,771
What's wrong?

132
00:09:18,854 --> 00:09:20,479
The museum is big.

133
00:09:22,979 --> 00:09:26,396
And 60, 70 hostages
are difficult to manage.

134
00:09:26,479 --> 00:09:29,021
The tiniest spark
could ignite a rebellion.

135
00:09:30,229 --> 00:09:31,062
No.

136
00:09:31,646 --> 00:09:35,521
That would be suicide. In these cases,
survival instinct prevails.

137
00:09:36,812 --> 00:09:38,854
Or not. Fear.

138
00:09:39,604 --> 00:09:41,937
Fear and more fear.
They could do anything.

139
00:09:42,021 --> 00:09:46,021
Like setting upon one of us
even though we have M16s.

140
00:09:48,729 --> 00:09:51,271
- What have you got in mind?
- An infiltrator.

141
00:09:52,646 --> 00:09:56,687
They wouldn't have any contact with us
unless there's a rebellion.

142
00:09:56,771 --> 00:10:00,187
If there are no problems,
they'll leave with the hostages.

143
00:10:00,396 --> 00:10:04,187
It's a job the smoking monkey
from the Ringling Circus could do.

144
00:10:06,396 --> 00:10:08,604
And this Juanito guy could do it.

145
00:10:17,104 --> 00:10:18,271
Here it comes.

146
00:10:35,687 --> 00:10:36,562
Is that him?

147
00:10:37,229 --> 00:10:38,062
- No.
- No.

148
00:10:39,104 --> 00:10:41,146
- Well, that was his bus.
- I know.

149
00:10:41,229 --> 00:10:42,896
It's a bad start. Let's go.

150
00:10:42,979 --> 00:10:45,646
No, Professor. Maybe he just got confused.

151
00:10:45,729 --> 00:10:47,521
Or got off at the wrong stop.

152
00:10:47,604 --> 00:10:49,229
Yeah, the wrong stop.

153
00:10:49,312 --> 00:10:51,604
- And he's there...
- He got confused?

154
00:10:56,271 --> 00:10:57,271
Godfather.

155
00:11:04,521 --> 00:11:05,437
My God.

156
00:11:06,104 --> 00:11:06,979
It's me.

157
00:11:08,479 --> 00:11:09,312
Juanito?

158
00:11:11,146 --> 00:11:11,979
Julia.

159
00:11:13,146 --> 00:11:15,187
It's been too long, hasn't it?

160
00:11:17,187 --> 00:11:19,062
You look stunning, my girl.

161
00:11:20,021 --> 00:11:20,896
Well...

162
00:11:21,854 --> 00:11:24,354
you've always been handsome. Pretty.

163
00:11:25,146 --> 00:11:26,104
Those eyes...

164
00:11:26,187 --> 00:11:27,979
that mouth, that smile...

165
00:11:28,062 --> 00:11:29,937
You're beautiful, Julia.

166
00:11:37,687 --> 00:11:39,687
What's wrong, Daniel?

167
00:11:40,896 --> 00:11:42,229
Is this weird for you?

168
00:11:42,312 --> 00:11:46,687
No. Not at all.
I... I think it's fucking great.

169
00:11:47,229 --> 00:11:51,479
Everyone is free to do
whatever they want with whatever.

170
00:11:52,312 --> 00:11:53,354
So?

171
00:11:53,646 --> 00:11:57,521
Well, I look you in the eyes,
and you're still Juanito, but...

172
00:11:58,771 --> 00:12:00,062
you look so hot!

173
00:12:01,729 --> 00:12:03,979
- Come here, give me a hug.
- Wow.

174
00:12:07,687 --> 00:12:09,312
Hey, does your father know?

175
00:12:09,396 --> 00:12:12,187
I saw him a year ago,
and he didn't mention it.

176
00:12:12,771 --> 00:12:14,604
My father wholly supports me.

177
00:12:14,687 --> 00:12:17,604
He says he always wanted a daughter.
He's sweet.

178
00:12:19,687 --> 00:12:20,521
Who's this?

179
00:12:23,104 --> 00:12:24,604
The guy behind the job?

180
00:12:29,021 --> 00:12:30,187
That's right.

181
00:12:31,604 --> 00:12:33,562
And what does the job involve?

182
00:12:33,896 --> 00:12:36,646
Gandía's telling the truth.
Palermo helped him.

183
00:12:36,729 --> 00:12:39,979
- How do you know?
- I saw him pointing at his thumb.

184
00:12:40,062 --> 00:12:42,729
They were talking.
Palermo kept going over.

185
00:12:42,812 --> 00:12:43,771
Why didn't you say?

186
00:12:43,854 --> 00:12:47,229
I couldn't hear. I didn't know
he'd tell him to break his thumb.

187
00:12:47,312 --> 00:12:49,062
Get closer. You're not tied up.

188
00:12:49,146 --> 00:12:52,771
No, I'm here to watch the hostages,
not to watch you guys.

189
00:12:58,896 --> 00:13:01,812
- You hear a lot of shit in here.
- I know.

190
00:13:03,021 --> 00:13:03,979
How is Nairobi?

191
00:13:04,062 --> 00:13:06,812
She's recovering as best she can.

192
00:13:07,937 --> 00:13:10,146
With Tokyo captured, that's two down.

193
00:13:10,937 --> 00:13:13,646
We're starting to look a bit screwed,
right?

194
00:13:13,812 --> 00:13:16,271
Julia. What do you want?

195
00:13:17,687 --> 00:13:20,562
Let me go. Give me a gun.
Let me join the others.

196
00:13:20,646 --> 00:13:22,854
My butt's going numb from sitting.

197
00:13:22,937 --> 00:13:25,437
They need to think you're a hostage
in case it gets bad.

198
00:13:25,521 --> 00:13:28,229
- Worse than this?
- Just go back to your place.

199
00:13:28,312 --> 00:13:31,479
Matías is down there
with a gun he can barely hold.

200
00:13:31,562 --> 00:13:33,354
No, orders are orders.

201
00:13:33,437 --> 00:13:38,021
- You have to go back to your place.
- You give the orders. You're in charge.

202
00:13:38,104 --> 00:13:40,437
- I'm not in charge.
- Of course you are.

203
00:13:40,521 --> 00:13:42,687
Nairobi was shot,
Tokyo's been captured,

204
00:13:42,771 --> 00:13:46,896
Palermo... How can we trust him?
Think about it. You're next in line.

205
00:13:46,979 --> 00:13:49,062
- No one else.
- You're stressing me out.

206
00:13:50,687 --> 00:13:52,354
Start giving orders.

207
00:13:52,437 --> 00:13:55,187
Give me a gun,
a bulletproof vest, whatever.

208
00:13:55,604 --> 00:14:00,229
And... call me Manila,
because I'm Manila, Dani.

209
00:14:00,312 --> 00:14:03,271
You're not Manila yet.
You're still a hostage.

210
00:14:03,354 --> 00:14:06,687
And don't call me Dani. My name is Denver.
Let's go.

211
00:14:07,562 --> 00:14:09,271
And another thing:

212
00:14:09,437 --> 00:14:12,771
don't stare at me.
People are starting to notice.

213
00:14:12,854 --> 00:14:13,937
Stare?

214
00:14:14,562 --> 00:14:16,812
I was sending you signals, you idiot.

215
00:14:16,896 --> 00:14:17,896
"Intently."

216
00:14:26,771 --> 00:14:28,479
It's a fucking sauna in here.

217
00:14:30,146 --> 00:14:31,354
Turn the AC on.

218
00:14:31,437 --> 00:14:33,562
If I turn it on, they'll find us.

219
00:14:33,646 --> 00:14:35,104
That would be a shame.

220
00:14:35,187 --> 00:14:38,562
Of course. We have so much to talk about.

221
00:14:39,771 --> 00:14:42,146
Without the AC, there's not much oxygen,

222
00:14:42,271 --> 00:14:44,812
so you should ration your breathing.

223
00:14:46,854 --> 00:14:48,687
Don't you worry about me.

224
00:14:50,021 --> 00:14:53,396
They've broken into
the vault of the national reserve.

225
00:14:53,479 --> 00:14:56,354
What do you think they'll do
to your shitty bunker?

226
00:14:57,437 --> 00:14:58,854
You're dead.

227
00:14:59,354 --> 00:15:03,604
You're sweaty. Shall I open your jumpsuit?
We can't have poor hygiene...

228
00:15:03,687 --> 00:15:06,229
Touch me, and I'll rip your arm off.

229
00:15:08,396 --> 00:15:10,854
Hey, what happened with that boy?

230
00:15:11,312 --> 00:15:14,812
The one with curly hair.
He doesn't turn you on anymore?

231
00:15:18,604 --> 00:15:19,729
Like crazy.

232
00:15:19,812 --> 00:15:23,062
I don't think so.
For you, kids and IT guys...

233
00:15:27,104 --> 00:15:28,937
I set up this heist for him.

234
00:15:30,646 --> 00:15:35,604
What's the most someone's done for you?
Given you a drill on Father's Day?

235
00:15:35,687 --> 00:15:37,604
Real men are more your type.

236
00:15:38,896 --> 00:15:40,437
- Like you.
- Like me.

237
00:15:40,521 --> 00:15:41,354
Of course.

238
00:15:41,437 --> 00:15:43,271
You've even stopped kicking me.

239
00:15:43,729 --> 00:15:46,437
Because you tied my legs,
you fucking idiot.

240
00:15:46,521 --> 00:15:50,771
Well, whatever the reason...
the main thing is, you're more receptive.

241
00:15:53,562 --> 00:15:55,896
And your toenails are painted.

242
00:15:57,437 --> 00:15:58,562
I love it.

243
00:16:00,812 --> 00:16:02,937
Is it true you helped Gandía escape?

244
00:16:03,021 --> 00:16:03,896
Yes, sir.

245
00:16:04,312 --> 00:16:07,854
Are you aware he almost killed
Nairobi and Helsinki?

246
00:16:07,937 --> 00:16:09,062
Collateral damage.

247
00:16:09,146 --> 00:16:12,229
- Collateral damage? Bastard!
- Take it easy.

248
00:16:12,312 --> 00:16:14,062
Why did you do it, Palermo?

249
00:16:14,146 --> 00:16:16,312
Tokyo staged a coup, sir.

250
00:16:16,979 --> 00:16:18,771
I felt morally obligated

251
00:16:19,771 --> 00:16:22,937
to save the plan.
That's where my loyalty lies.

252
00:16:23,021 --> 00:16:27,729
I had to restore the established order,
because you never relieved me of my post.

253
00:16:27,812 --> 00:16:29,146
I did it de facto.

254
00:16:29,271 --> 00:16:32,271
Besides, that has nothing to do with
freeing Gandía.

255
00:16:32,354 --> 00:16:33,229
It does.

256
00:16:33,312 --> 00:16:36,521
I had to create chaos.
It was clear he'd target her.

257
00:16:36,604 --> 00:16:38,562
He could have killed her.

258
00:16:39,187 --> 00:16:42,104
- I repeat, she staged a coup, sir.
- It's all lies!

259
00:16:42,187 --> 00:16:45,937
He was going to escape like a rat!
He had the state secrets.

260
00:16:46,021 --> 00:16:47,854
The kid is mistaken.

261
00:16:48,187 --> 00:16:50,854
I stopped you at the door,
with the briefcase.

262
00:16:51,562 --> 00:16:53,479
You were gonna negotiate, jerk.

263
00:16:53,562 --> 00:16:57,062
That so? With the documents I stole?
The briefcase is there.

264
00:16:57,146 --> 00:16:59,812
- Why don't you have a look?
- Denver, open it.

265
00:17:05,604 --> 00:17:06,687
What's inside?

266
00:17:08,187 --> 00:17:09,187
Muffins.

267
00:17:13,229 --> 00:17:16,521
Whatever's in the briefcase,
it makes no difference.

268
00:17:17,812 --> 00:17:20,479
You betrayed the gang.

269
00:17:20,562 --> 00:17:22,229
You put everyone in danger,

270
00:17:22,312 --> 00:17:25,229
and thanks to you,
Gandía has my commanding officer.

271
00:17:26,521 --> 00:17:29,854
Listen, I'm going to give you
one chance to make amends.

272
00:17:31,104 --> 00:17:35,354
But I won't forget what you did.
And of course, you won't be in charge.

273
00:17:36,562 --> 00:17:39,687
So I go back to the lobby
with the hostages? What do I do?

274
00:17:39,771 --> 00:17:41,187
First of all, shut up.

275
00:17:42,521 --> 00:17:45,521
And no, you won't go back there.
Release him.

276
00:17:47,937 --> 00:17:50,021
With a killer here, we can't be divided.

277
00:17:50,104 --> 00:17:51,604
When all this is over,

278
00:17:52,229 --> 00:17:54,104
then we'll decide his sentence.

279
00:18:22,604 --> 00:18:24,146
Now, listen closely.

280
00:18:25,146 --> 00:18:26,771
With a lone wolf out there,

281
00:18:27,271 --> 00:18:31,062
the most vulnerable place is the lobby.
We need to evacuate it.

282
00:18:31,146 --> 00:18:34,687
Palermo, Stockholm, Helsinki,
get the hostages to the library.

283
00:18:34,771 --> 00:18:38,104
He wants to kill you, not escape.
The door doesn't matter.

284
00:18:38,187 --> 00:18:39,562
Do not wear your masks.

285
00:18:39,646 --> 00:18:42,187
He could do the same,
and he would blend in.

286
00:18:43,104 --> 00:18:45,937
Bogotá, what's the situation
in the foundry?

287
00:18:46,021 --> 00:18:48,104
The furnaces are off. They're scared.

288
00:18:48,604 --> 00:18:52,687
Take Nairobi to the library, then go down.
The foundry cannot be idle.

289
00:18:53,729 --> 00:18:54,562
Denver.

290
00:18:54,646 --> 00:18:57,812
- Yes.
- You and Rio will act. Begin the hunt.

291
00:18:58,437 --> 00:19:01,437
You will be the most exposed.
Equip yourselves well.

292
00:19:01,521 --> 00:19:04,146
Helmets, ammunition, magazines.
Everything you need.

293
00:19:04,229 --> 00:19:07,479
Sweep the first floor.
Once you finish a room, seal it.

294
00:19:07,562 --> 00:19:08,854
And the other floors?

295
00:19:08,937 --> 00:19:12,562
Helsinki and Stockholm will do them
once hostages are in the library.

296
00:19:14,604 --> 00:19:16,229
Everyone know what to do?

297
00:19:16,312 --> 00:19:18,521
- Yes, sir.
- Yes.

298
00:19:19,937 --> 00:19:20,854
One more thing.

299
00:19:23,271 --> 00:19:24,146
Good luck.

300
00:19:26,062 --> 00:19:27,187
Be very careful.

301
00:19:27,771 --> 00:19:28,604
Let's go!

302
00:19:40,437 --> 00:19:42,812
- How are you feeling, little one?
- Fine.

303
00:19:43,354 --> 00:19:44,812
I have a good nurse.

304
00:19:48,479 --> 00:19:50,021
You like the big guy, huh?

305
00:19:51,187 --> 00:19:52,229
Maybe.

306
00:19:53,771 --> 00:19:54,604
Hang in there.

307
00:19:56,271 --> 00:19:57,271
You too.

308
00:20:06,062 --> 00:20:09,021
Wow, that woman is so drunk, Helsinki.

309
00:20:09,104 --> 00:20:13,229
Do you know what she said? She said,
"What a hunk you've got yourself."

310
00:20:13,729 --> 00:20:17,187
She means you.
Everyone thinks we're husband and wife.

311
00:20:17,271 --> 00:20:19,729
Better. That way, no one notices us.

312
00:20:20,062 --> 00:20:23,271
It's not better.
Neither of us will get any action.

313
00:20:23,354 --> 00:20:25,729
Never mind action, Nairobi. Cheers.

314
00:20:28,354 --> 00:20:32,646
A day or two is OK, but at this rate,
we'll become virgins again.

315
00:20:33,937 --> 00:20:37,854
Truth is, you and I
make an excellent couple.

316
00:20:41,354 --> 00:20:42,312
You and I?

317
00:20:42,396 --> 00:20:44,187
We're family, that's for sure.

318
00:20:44,812 --> 00:20:45,812
Forever.

319
00:20:47,104 --> 00:20:48,271
Well, that's why.

320
00:20:48,646 --> 00:20:51,687
I've been through more with you
than with anyone.

321
00:20:52,396 --> 00:20:53,937
This, Helsi...

322
00:20:55,687 --> 00:20:57,396
is a love story.

323
00:20:57,979 --> 00:21:00,521
One of those beautiful love stories.

324
00:21:03,521 --> 00:21:07,312
No. Someday someone will show up,

325
00:21:08,312 --> 00:21:09,646
and that will be love.

326
00:21:10,896 --> 00:21:11,937
But this isn't.

327
00:21:12,521 --> 00:21:15,104
You have to be free and brave.

328
00:21:15,354 --> 00:21:19,937
Because believe me,
you need more courage for love...

329
00:21:21,771 --> 00:21:23,229
than for war.

330
00:21:23,312 --> 00:21:24,187
And you...

331
00:21:25,562 --> 00:21:26,729
you're brave.

332
00:21:29,979 --> 00:21:30,937
Put it on.

333
00:21:34,146 --> 00:21:35,771
We're going to the foundry.

334
00:21:37,604 --> 00:21:39,229
We're going to the library.

335
00:21:40,146 --> 00:21:41,396
Those are the orders.

336
00:21:42,521 --> 00:21:43,562
Bogotá.

337
00:21:48,604 --> 00:21:49,729
Don't fuck with me.

338
00:21:50,479 --> 00:21:51,812
They're scared, right?

339
00:21:51,896 --> 00:21:54,812
If so, they won't last 5 minutes
against Gandía.

340
00:21:55,937 --> 00:21:57,354
I need to speak to them.

341
00:21:59,271 --> 00:22:01,062
When did you eat last?

342
00:22:05,229 --> 00:22:06,146
Two days ago.

343
00:22:08,687 --> 00:22:11,187
- Maybe three.
- And the last time you slept?

344
00:22:15,187 --> 00:22:18,979
I've slept twice since I arrived,
two hours each time. Anything else?

345
00:22:24,562 --> 00:22:27,271
Before you eat,
I'm going to clean that wound.

346
00:22:48,896 --> 00:22:49,979
Stay still.

347
00:22:51,854 --> 00:22:53,562
Your hair is all stuck in it.

348
00:22:55,396 --> 00:22:56,896
I hit you hard, didn't I?

349
00:23:04,729 --> 00:23:06,687
- Library clear.
- Copy that.

350
00:23:08,146 --> 00:23:10,771
Everyone on your feet
and into four lines.

351
00:23:10,854 --> 00:23:12,687
Dear hostages...

352
00:23:14,021 --> 00:23:14,979
I am back.

353
00:23:16,146 --> 00:23:19,521
As you know, a wolf's on the loose,
and you are the lambs.

354
00:23:19,604 --> 00:23:22,437
So we're taking you into the barn.

355
00:23:22,521 --> 00:23:25,604
You will be escorted
by my colleagues and shepherds:

356
00:23:25,687 --> 00:23:27,104
Helsinki and Stockholm.

357
00:23:27,729 --> 00:23:29,521
Let's go, now, quickly!

358
00:23:29,604 --> 00:23:31,729
Everyone up! Come on!

359
00:23:34,687 --> 00:23:35,979
Stay here with me.

360
00:23:36,062 --> 00:23:38,646
You're my best shield against Gandía.

361
00:23:38,729 --> 00:23:40,062
That's it, quickly.

362
00:23:45,896 --> 00:23:47,646
Here. This works wonders.

363
00:23:49,062 --> 00:23:50,896
It's not too strong, is it?

364
00:23:50,979 --> 00:23:52,021
Amanda, right?

365
00:23:53,104 --> 00:23:54,937
- Yes.
- Are you OK?

366
00:23:57,521 --> 00:23:58,687
Yes.

367
00:23:58,771 --> 00:23:59,979
Are you sure?

368
00:24:00,979 --> 00:24:02,062
Well...

369
00:24:02,646 --> 00:24:04,104
I'm a bit dizzy.

370
00:24:04,562 --> 00:24:07,354
It must have been
those pills Mr. Román gave me.

371
00:24:17,021 --> 00:24:18,521
Hello, how are you?

372
00:24:19,187 --> 00:24:20,021
Fine.

373
00:24:20,562 --> 00:24:21,604
I'm Arturo.

374
00:24:22,604 --> 00:24:23,479
Arturo Román.

375
00:24:24,396 --> 00:24:26,271
You looked very tense before,

376
00:24:26,354 --> 00:24:29,062
asking to go to the bathroom.
I was worried.

377
00:24:29,854 --> 00:24:32,437
It's my nerves. It's tough being in here.

378
00:24:32,521 --> 00:24:36,896
With these terrorists,
it'd be tough anywhere. I know.

379
00:24:39,479 --> 00:24:41,854
It was just some anxiety.
I'm OK. Thanks.

380
00:24:41,937 --> 00:24:45,104
We only have each other.
We have to stick together.

381
00:24:45,812 --> 00:24:46,771
Trust me.

382
00:24:47,646 --> 00:24:48,479
Yeah.

383
00:24:53,104 --> 00:24:55,562
If you feel anxious again,

384
00:24:56,729 --> 00:24:58,937
I've got something that might help.

385
00:24:59,521 --> 00:25:01,479
Oh, really? What is it?

386
00:25:04,229 --> 00:25:05,812
Veteran's privileges.

387
00:25:07,646 --> 00:25:08,812
That's everyone.

388
00:25:08,896 --> 00:25:12,521
We've brought you to the library because,
as the saying goes,

389
00:25:12,604 --> 00:25:14,396
knowledge takes up no space.

390
00:25:14,854 --> 00:25:17,396
In this case,
it could also save your lives.

391
00:25:17,479 --> 00:25:20,854
In Search of Lost Time,
for example, by Marcel Proust.

392
00:25:21,146 --> 00:25:24,312
Terrific. Beautiful novel. I'm certain...

393
00:25:24,729 --> 00:25:26,062
that whoever finds it

394
00:25:26,604 --> 00:25:29,021
and hugs it to their chest

395
00:25:29,729 --> 00:25:32,271
will be able to deflect bullets
from an M16.

396
00:25:34,771 --> 00:25:37,812
It's a joke. Relax.

397
00:25:38,812 --> 00:25:41,021
We'll be in here for a long time.

398
00:25:41,271 --> 00:25:43,646
These are the rules. Number one...

399
00:25:46,396 --> 00:25:48,479
Bogotá, Nairobi, where are you?

400
00:25:50,437 --> 00:25:53,437
5:00 MINUTES EARLIER

401
00:25:54,687 --> 00:25:56,104
Don't move!

402
00:25:56,187 --> 00:25:59,271
Are you all stupid or what?
Lower your weapons.

403
00:26:11,354 --> 00:26:12,562
Are you scared?

404
00:26:12,646 --> 00:26:16,146
There's a madman on the loose
who's armed to the teeth.

405
00:26:17,479 --> 00:26:18,687
I'm scared too.

406
00:26:19,437 --> 00:26:22,271
- Bogotá, are you scared?
- As much as anyone else.

407
00:26:25,646 --> 00:26:28,896
Palermo, Helsinki, and Stockholm
are scared as well.

408
00:26:31,312 --> 00:26:33,687
But they're taking hostages
to the library.

409
00:26:35,146 --> 00:26:39,812
Denver and Rio are really damn scared.

410
00:26:42,271 --> 00:26:44,021
Because they're after Gandía.

411
00:26:44,854 --> 00:26:45,937
And Gandía...

412
00:26:46,437 --> 00:26:49,812
is the most scared,
but he won't stop until he kills us.

413
00:26:50,354 --> 00:26:51,562
That's fine with me.

414
00:26:52,604 --> 00:26:53,604
"That's fine."

415
00:27:06,687 --> 00:27:08,854
Everyone's doing their jobs.

416
00:27:10,187 --> 00:27:13,271
And here you are, scared shitless.

417
00:27:14,146 --> 00:27:15,854
Hiding in a makeshift trench.

418
00:27:15,937 --> 00:27:18,729
- We didn't come here to shoot people.
- I know.

419
00:27:21,396 --> 00:27:25,312
But there's no choice.
This is the easiest place to defend.

420
00:27:25,937 --> 00:27:27,729
That's the only way in,

421
00:27:28,771 --> 00:27:31,646
and from here,
any one of us could mow him down.

422
00:27:32,604 --> 00:27:34,937
But what do you see when you enter?

423
00:27:36,437 --> 00:27:38,979
The chicken squadron peering out.

424
00:27:40,562 --> 00:27:43,729
I don't recognize you.

425
00:27:45,562 --> 00:27:47,562
You are workers.

426
00:27:48,771 --> 00:27:50,062
You are welders.

427
00:27:50,979 --> 00:27:53,771
The toughest guys
I've ever met in my life.

428
00:27:53,854 --> 00:27:54,979
My golden boys.

429
00:27:56,187 --> 00:27:57,479
You're not chickens.

430
00:28:00,812 --> 00:28:03,146
You know what else is scary?

431
00:28:05,146 --> 00:28:07,062
Walking home alone at night.

432
00:28:09,062 --> 00:28:11,646
But us women keep doing it.

433
00:28:12,854 --> 00:28:16,479
Take fear by the hand and keep living.

434
00:28:18,854 --> 00:28:21,479
Because you have to live, gentlemen!

435
00:28:22,271 --> 00:28:24,062
You have to live to the end!

436
00:28:31,229 --> 00:28:32,604
Fuck, believe me.

437
00:28:33,354 --> 00:28:36,062
You made me come back from the dead
to nag you.

438
00:28:40,354 --> 00:28:44,312
What? Aren't you going to give me a hug?

439
00:28:50,562 --> 00:28:52,437
- How are you?
- I don't know.

440
00:28:52,521 --> 00:28:54,021
Pumped full of drugs.

441
00:28:54,104 --> 00:28:55,937
I'm not hearing any music.

442
00:28:56,021 --> 00:28:58,937
- Are we going to work unhappy?
- Music, dammit.

443
00:28:59,021 --> 00:29:00,562
Are we Latinos or Germans?

444
00:29:01,521 --> 00:29:03,437
Nice wheels. Is it a Harley?

445
00:29:03,521 --> 00:29:05,521
Don't start ribbing me now, hey?

446
00:29:05,604 --> 00:29:07,729
How many tons have we melted?

447
00:29:07,812 --> 00:29:09,229
Forty-three and a half.

448
00:29:09,812 --> 00:29:12,937
We need to step it up a gear.
I want the furnaces on.

449
00:29:13,021 --> 00:29:16,021
And two-hour shifts
to get the remaining ingots.

450
00:29:16,104 --> 00:29:17,937
Bring me a sample of the shot.

451
00:29:23,104 --> 00:29:23,979
Let's see.

452
00:29:28,604 --> 00:29:31,437
Turn up the gas pressure
by two kilopascals.

453
00:29:32,187 --> 00:29:34,187
The diameter's a bit big.

454
00:29:34,271 --> 00:29:36,937
I want to see you working like always...

455
00:29:37,021 --> 00:29:38,937
with rhythm, with joy.

456
00:29:55,812 --> 00:29:56,937
What's up with you?

457
00:30:00,979 --> 00:30:02,062
What do you mean?

458
00:30:03,104 --> 00:30:03,937
Nothing.

459
00:30:05,896 --> 00:30:08,896
I'll have to say
that ten-foot pole thing again.

460
00:30:09,562 --> 00:30:11,771
When I said that, at least...

461
00:30:12,937 --> 00:30:14,146
you flirted with me.

462
00:30:14,729 --> 00:30:15,729
But now...

463
00:30:17,146 --> 00:30:18,687
it's like I've got typhus.

464
00:30:22,687 --> 00:30:24,812
I don't wanna take advantage.
You're hurt.

465
00:30:28,979 --> 00:30:29,812
Right.

466
00:30:30,687 --> 00:30:31,729
Well, OK.

467
00:30:32,812 --> 00:30:34,604
We'll wait until I'm better,

468
00:30:35,229 --> 00:30:38,062
until we get out of here,
we find my father,

469
00:30:38,146 --> 00:30:39,687
you ask him for my hand...

470
00:30:44,479 --> 00:30:47,312
If the fire's gone out, let me know.

471
00:31:12,562 --> 00:31:14,187
What sort of kiss was that?

472
00:31:18,062 --> 00:31:19,104
Help me up.

473
00:31:43,937 --> 00:31:44,937
Better down here.

474
00:31:45,854 --> 00:31:47,021
Yes.

475
00:31:51,854 --> 00:31:53,271
- Are you OK?
- Yes. You?

476
00:31:53,354 --> 00:31:54,854
- Yes.
- Bogotá, Nairobi,

477
00:31:54,937 --> 00:31:57,021
- location?
- Elevator. We're OK.

478
00:31:57,104 --> 00:31:58,479
And Denver and Rio?

479
00:31:59,729 --> 00:32:01,646
5:00 MINUTES EARLIER

480
00:32:05,771 --> 00:32:07,979
- Library clear.
- Copy that.

481
00:32:24,562 --> 00:32:26,396
About the Maserati thing...

482
00:32:26,479 --> 00:32:29,229
- What about it?
- I'd like to say something.

483
00:32:29,312 --> 00:32:31,562
Now? What do you want?

484
00:32:31,646 --> 00:32:35,146
Tokyo may be a Maserati,
but you're hanging off the back.

485
00:32:35,437 --> 00:32:37,229
Like cans on a wedding car.

486
00:32:37,312 --> 00:32:38,521
Yes.

487
00:32:38,604 --> 00:32:40,396
Rio.

488
00:32:41,104 --> 00:32:41,937
The office.

489
00:32:42,937 --> 00:32:43,854
Go.

490
00:33:03,146 --> 00:33:04,229
Do you like her?

491
00:33:04,312 --> 00:33:07,312
- What are you talking about?
- The fucking Maserati.

492
00:33:08,479 --> 00:33:11,104
If you wanna take her for a ride,
go ahead.

493
00:33:11,187 --> 00:33:13,479
Can you hear the crap you're saying?

494
00:33:19,437 --> 00:33:23,021
First of all, she feels,
thinks, and decides.

495
00:33:25,146 --> 00:33:28,146
The thing is,
she's messed up about the break-up.

496
00:33:29,229 --> 00:33:32,604
I'll tell you one thing.
Respect a friend's girlfriend.

497
00:33:32,687 --> 00:33:34,562
- Ex-girlfriend.
- Same thing.

498
00:33:34,646 --> 00:33:38,812
Ex or not, a friend's girlfriend
is like a radioactive town.

499
00:33:38,896 --> 00:33:42,521
Even after 20,000 years,
it's still contaminated land.

500
00:33:42,604 --> 00:33:45,562
You don't go there,
even with the ex's permission.

501
00:33:45,646 --> 00:33:47,646
- That's stupid.
- No, it's ethics.

502
00:33:47,729 --> 00:33:49,562
The most sacred kind of ethics.

503
00:33:49,937 --> 00:33:52,646
What were you doing
on the sofa with Stockholm?

504
00:33:53,562 --> 00:33:54,604
We were talking.

505
00:33:56,187 --> 00:33:58,354
Barefoot? Come on, man.

506
00:33:58,729 --> 00:34:02,937
- Well, yes, barefoot. What does it matter?
- It does matter, Rio.

507
00:34:03,021 --> 00:34:06,062
I don't talk to Lisbon
barefoot on the sofa.

508
00:34:06,146 --> 00:34:10,146
It would be fucking weird.
I'd feel uncomfortable. Do you know why?

509
00:34:10,229 --> 00:34:12,229
That's the Professor's territory.

510
00:34:14,521 --> 00:34:17,854
There's your boyfriend.
Want to say anything to him?

511
00:34:17,937 --> 00:34:19,187
Rio! Rio, isn't it?

512
00:34:20,021 --> 00:34:22,354
Rio! Denver!

513
00:34:22,437 --> 00:34:24,646
Help me, please!

514
00:34:24,729 --> 00:34:31,312
I'm trapped! Friends from the gang, help!

515
00:34:37,437 --> 00:34:41,104
That's what 70 centimeters
of reinforced concrete does.

516
00:34:41,812 --> 00:34:45,437
It's like shouting in a submarine
at the bottom of the sea.

517
00:34:54,104 --> 00:34:55,312
Third card:

518
00:34:56,521 --> 00:34:57,604
to draw blood.

519
00:35:01,104 --> 00:35:02,771
I'm going out for a moment.

520
00:35:14,646 --> 00:35:17,646
I was telling her I have PTSD, asshole.

521
00:35:17,729 --> 00:35:19,896
I wasn't stealing your girlfriend.

522
00:35:19,979 --> 00:35:24,062
- Talking to her calms me down.
- Talking to Stockholm calms you down?

523
00:35:24,146 --> 00:35:24,979
Well, yes.

524
00:35:25,812 --> 00:35:31,229
She is smart, nice, and she listens.
She empathizes. You can tell her anything.

525
00:35:31,312 --> 00:35:34,854
You can tell me anything too,
but you don't want to.

526
00:35:44,396 --> 00:35:46,562
I haven't been able to sleep.

527
00:35:47,521 --> 00:35:50,604
Whenever I closed my eyes,
I had nightmares, anxiety,

528
00:35:50,687 --> 00:35:52,646
palpitations, attacks, dude.

529
00:35:53,771 --> 00:35:57,021
I've only been able to sleep
knowing she was by my side.

530
00:35:57,979 --> 00:35:59,812
Do you know what I mean?

531
00:36:01,979 --> 00:36:04,604
You sleep with her
and tell me to my face.

532
00:36:05,604 --> 00:36:10,479
I haven't slept with her, Denver.
She was just keeping me company.

533
00:36:15,396 --> 00:36:17,396
Are you my friend or not, damn it?

534
00:36:19,729 --> 00:36:22,562
- I'm your friend.
- Doesn't seem like it.

535
00:36:27,187 --> 00:36:28,646
Jesus fucking Christ!

536
00:36:29,812 --> 00:36:32,479
Your helmet! Your vest!

537
00:36:32,562 --> 00:36:34,062
Put pressure on it!

538
00:36:34,937 --> 00:36:36,229
Denver, hold on!

539
00:36:44,604 --> 00:36:47,104
- Bogotá, Nairobi, location?
- Elevator.

540
00:36:47,187 --> 00:36:49,312
We're OK. And Denver and Rio?

541
00:36:49,687 --> 00:36:50,896
Denver, Rio.

542
00:36:52,187 --> 00:36:53,937
- Denver, Rio.
- I'll go.

543
00:36:54,021 --> 00:36:56,187
No, you stay with the hostages.

544
00:36:56,271 --> 00:36:57,937
Come on, Helsinki.

545
00:37:10,146 --> 00:37:12,437
Careful, the bastard's here somewhere.

546
00:37:25,146 --> 00:37:27,812
It was in the elevator
on the first floor.

547
00:37:27,896 --> 00:37:28,979
Received.

548
00:37:30,104 --> 00:37:32,729
He may be nearby. We'll stay here.

549
00:37:35,437 --> 00:37:36,604
Come on, big man.

550
00:37:54,146 --> 00:37:55,562
Stay calm. We're here!

551
00:37:58,646 --> 00:38:00,896
- Get up.
- Denver.

552
00:38:01,687 --> 00:38:04,604
Are you OK?

553
00:38:10,896 --> 00:38:11,854
Are you OK?

554
00:38:15,521 --> 00:38:17,437
Get down!

555
00:38:28,854 --> 00:38:30,521
Motherfucker!

556
00:38:34,479 --> 00:38:35,687
We're taking fire!

557
00:38:35,771 --> 00:38:38,396
First floor, elevator.
Reinforcements, now!

558
00:38:39,562 --> 00:38:40,521
Go.

559
00:38:44,562 --> 00:38:45,854
Go.

560
00:40:40,979 --> 00:40:43,687
Third time's the charm, mutt.

