1
00:00:25,771 --> 00:00:26,771
How do I look?

2
00:00:31,854 --> 00:00:33,021
Powerful.

3
00:00:34,437 --> 00:00:35,271
Beautiful.

4
00:00:39,354 --> 00:00:40,271
Martín...

5
00:00:40,896 --> 00:00:44,479
for years,
you've been going around in circles...

6
00:00:46,062 --> 00:00:47,312
feeling this way.

7
00:00:50,104 --> 00:00:52,646
I think it's time you moved on.

8
00:00:53,521 --> 00:00:55,687
We can move on to wine, if you like.

9
00:00:56,604 --> 00:00:58,271
- Shall we have a glass?
- No.

10
00:00:58,354 --> 00:01:00,354
I'm not drinking that with you.

11
00:01:01,812 --> 00:01:04,021
I'm going to dinner. With Tatiana.

12
00:01:04,521 --> 00:01:06,646
- Right.
- You'll think about me,

13
00:01:07,937 --> 00:01:08,771
but...

14
00:01:09,979 --> 00:01:11,396
I won't think about you.

15
00:01:16,021 --> 00:01:19,104
You don't have to spell it out for me.
It's clear.

16
00:01:19,187 --> 00:01:22,437
Oh, please. Do you think I don't love you?

17
00:01:22,521 --> 00:01:25,021
I also feel that what we have between us

18
00:01:25,104 --> 00:01:27,521
is extraordinary, unique, wonderful.

19
00:01:28,937 --> 00:01:31,187
I know about love.
I've been married 5 times.

20
00:01:31,271 --> 00:01:34,062
- OK.
- What I've never told you is that...

21
00:01:35,187 --> 00:01:38,021
I've never felt anything
with any of those women

22
00:01:38,521 --> 00:01:41,062
remotely similar to what I have with you.

23
00:01:42,229 --> 00:01:43,396
Not even close.

24
00:01:45,312 --> 00:01:47,146
You and I are soul mates.

25
00:01:48,896 --> 00:01:50,812
But only 99%.

26
00:01:52,104 --> 00:01:55,854
As you know, I really like women.

27
00:01:59,271 --> 00:02:00,854
And you like me too much.

28
00:02:02,896 --> 00:02:06,271
And what's 1% against 99%?

29
00:02:08,729 --> 00:02:13,562
- Unless you're not brave enough to try it.
- That 1% is a tiny mitochondrion...

30
00:02:15,354 --> 00:02:16,937
but it defines my desire.

31
00:02:17,937 --> 00:02:19,062
Mitochondrion.

32
00:02:25,812 --> 00:02:27,229
Where's your desire?

33
00:02:33,354 --> 00:02:34,187
Here?

34
00:02:38,354 --> 00:02:39,312
Where is it?

35
00:02:41,604 --> 00:02:43,562
Don't worry. Relax.

36
00:02:44,979 --> 00:02:45,979
Don't be afraid.

37
00:02:55,562 --> 00:02:57,771
You're a coward, huh?

38
00:02:59,187 --> 00:03:00,146
Where is it?

39
00:03:27,271 --> 00:03:28,187
Look...

40
00:03:31,437 --> 00:03:35,229
I'd give anything to feel that, but...

41
00:03:41,396 --> 00:03:42,687
it's impossible.

42
00:03:43,812 --> 00:03:45,229
It's impossible.

43
00:03:54,146 --> 00:03:55,521
I love you, Martín.

44
00:03:56,479 --> 00:03:59,437
But my brother is right.
We must part ways.

45
00:04:01,479 --> 00:04:03,271
And we have to scrap the plan.

46
00:04:04,146 --> 00:04:07,062
Your son-of-a-bitch brother
told you I loved you

47
00:04:07,146 --> 00:04:08,521
to break up this house.

48
00:04:08,604 --> 00:04:12,521
You're going to go and make photocopies
in the Royal Mint, right?

49
00:04:13,021 --> 00:04:14,812
I suggested melting gold together.

50
00:04:14,896 --> 00:04:17,479
You're hooked on something
that will never exist!

51
00:04:24,854 --> 00:04:26,854
I have to leave you. It's...

52
00:04:27,771 --> 00:04:28,646
for love.

53
00:04:31,937 --> 00:04:33,229
For brotherhood.

54
00:04:34,896 --> 00:04:36,896
For the commitment I have to you.

55
00:04:39,729 --> 00:04:40,937
Leave...

56
00:04:41,812 --> 00:04:43,146
and heal the wound.

57
00:04:44,146 --> 00:04:46,687
Sometimes distance
is the only way to find peace.

58
00:04:50,062 --> 00:04:51,479
Farewell, my friend.

59
00:04:52,312 --> 00:04:56,854
I'm sure that one way or another,
time will bring us back together.

60
00:05:21,562 --> 00:05:24,354
As Alicia Sierra
walked towards the slaughterhouse...

61
00:05:26,229 --> 00:05:28,812
she wore an enigmatic smile
that no one noticed.

62
00:05:31,271 --> 00:05:35,146
It was not the smile
of someone about to throw in the towel.

63
00:05:39,521 --> 00:05:40,812
Please, over here.

64
00:05:40,896 --> 00:05:44,854
Is it true you sent for the daughter
of Ágata Jiménez, Nairobi,

65
00:05:44,937 --> 00:05:47,896
so she'd go to the window
and you could shoot her?

66
00:05:47,979 --> 00:05:50,937
- Did she die from that shot?
- That is untrue.

67
00:05:53,812 --> 00:05:55,604
It was a boy, not a girl.

68
00:05:56,187 --> 00:05:57,312
Nine years old.

69
00:05:57,396 --> 00:05:59,354
And yes, I sent for him.

70
00:05:59,437 --> 00:06:02,812
With the knowledge of my superiors,
of course.

71
00:06:02,896 --> 00:06:05,562
- What are you doing?
- We shot her in the chest.

72
00:06:06,271 --> 00:06:09,021
I didn't allow a doctor to go in
to operate.

73
00:06:09,104 --> 00:06:11,062
Antoñanzas, turn the volume up!

74
00:06:11,437 --> 00:06:13,854
Her friends saved her. All for nothing.

75
00:06:14,521 --> 00:06:18,104
She was killed
by the Bank of Spain's head of security,

76
00:06:18,187 --> 00:06:21,062
Gandía,
with the backing of Colonel Tamayo.

77
00:06:21,146 --> 00:06:23,687
- Fucking bitch.
- It needs to be said.

78
00:06:24,562 --> 00:06:25,896
More questions.

79
00:06:25,979 --> 00:06:28,312
Is it true that this Osman...

80
00:06:28,396 --> 00:06:30,312
I don't know if you know him...

81
00:06:30,396 --> 00:06:31,854
buried Cortés alive?

82
00:06:31,937 --> 00:06:34,312
Yes, we buried him alive.

83
00:06:34,396 --> 00:06:35,604
In Timimoun...

84
00:06:35,687 --> 00:06:37,812
Tamayo's world was falling apart.

85
00:06:37,896 --> 00:06:40,396
Of course I know Osman.
He's a professional.

86
00:06:41,687 --> 00:06:43,979
Capable of burying a man alive...

87
00:06:44,062 --> 00:06:46,896
and leaving him shaking like a leaf
without him dying.

88
00:06:47,437 --> 00:06:51,646
His public image was crumbling,
and the worst was yet to come.

89
00:06:52,021 --> 00:06:55,312
Inside the bank,
his big gamble was unconscious.

90
00:06:55,396 --> 00:06:56,229
Palermo.

91
00:06:56,771 --> 00:06:58,771
- How is he?
- We're operating.

92
00:06:59,271 --> 00:07:01,812
On a stretcher and badly wounded.

93
00:07:04,021 --> 00:07:05,896
Save his life.

94
00:07:07,562 --> 00:07:09,479
Didn't you drug him?

95
00:07:09,812 --> 00:07:12,437
Drugs? We drugged him.

96
00:07:12,521 --> 00:07:13,729
Inhaled, to be precise.

97
00:07:13,812 --> 00:07:17,479
We hung him up, threw cold water on him,
and he shat himself.

98
00:07:17,562 --> 00:07:21,187
Everything the boy said
is absolutely and totally true.

99
00:07:21,271 --> 00:07:24,521
And there are plenty of things
that he forgot to say.

100
00:07:24,604 --> 00:07:26,562
Was the government aware of this?

101
00:07:27,604 --> 00:07:28,437
Aware?

102
00:07:30,312 --> 00:07:32,354
The government gave the orders.

103
00:07:34,021 --> 00:07:37,437
I didn't wake up one day and say,
"I'll interrogate the boy hard."

104
00:07:37,521 --> 00:07:39,396
No! I had everyone's backing.

105
00:07:39,479 --> 00:07:43,646
The CNI, police commanders,
and the Ministry of the Interior.

106
00:07:43,729 --> 00:07:46,604
Absolutely everyone knew about it.

107
00:07:47,146 --> 00:07:49,437
And now you know. Thank you very much.

108
00:07:51,646 --> 00:07:54,437
Alicia Sierra,
negotiator at the Bank of Spain,

109
00:07:54,521 --> 00:07:57,062
reveals all, and nobody is spared.

110
00:07:57,146 --> 00:08:00,396
She admits to torture
but holds the government responsible.

111
00:08:00,896 --> 00:08:05,271
The government gave the orders,
and she says, "Everyone knew."

112
00:08:05,354 --> 00:08:08,062
We have to bury that bitch.

113
00:09:32,396 --> 00:09:34,646
While all of Spain was glued to the TV,

114
00:09:35,729 --> 00:09:38,687
in a former Chinese restaurant
in Madrid,

115
00:09:38,771 --> 00:09:40,687
Benjamín and his men...

116
00:09:41,646 --> 00:09:43,479
were raising hell.

117
00:09:45,937 --> 00:09:46,771
Marseille.

118
00:09:46,854 --> 00:09:48,854
Arriving at extraction point.

119
00:09:48,937 --> 00:09:50,271
Received.

120
00:09:56,979 --> 00:09:58,687
One, two, three.

121
00:10:10,521 --> 00:10:11,854
How many meters?

122
00:10:19,396 --> 00:10:20,521
Four meters.

123
00:10:25,021 --> 00:10:26,687
I need you to work faster.

124
00:10:30,021 --> 00:10:35,187
Lisbon will be guarded by 26 officers,
split between seven vehicles.

125
00:10:37,479 --> 00:10:38,437
Three behind...

126
00:10:39,354 --> 00:10:40,771
and three in front.

127
00:10:42,521 --> 00:10:44,687
In the middle, the van she'll be in.

128
00:10:45,104 --> 00:10:48,729
They'll go to the National Court first
and then to the prison.

129
00:10:48,812 --> 00:10:51,771
What's the most vulnerable point?

130
00:10:51,854 --> 00:10:54,646
On the road. From point A to B.

131
00:10:54,729 --> 00:10:57,354
- No.
- In the courtroom?

132
00:10:57,937 --> 00:10:58,771
No.

133
00:10:58,854 --> 00:11:01,604
- Are we going to tunnel into the prison?
- No.

134
00:11:01,687 --> 00:11:05,437
But there is a place that is vulnerable.

135
00:11:05,521 --> 00:11:07,104
We've all seen it.

136
00:11:07,771 --> 00:11:08,937
On TV.

137
00:11:10,146 --> 00:11:14,896
When the National Court's entrance is
full of journalists, what do the cops do?

138
00:11:15,187 --> 00:11:17,771
They take the prisoner...

139
00:11:19,312 --> 00:11:20,812
through the parking garage.

140
00:11:25,687 --> 00:11:27,687
Only the van goes in.

141
00:11:29,479 --> 00:11:33,687
In 30 seconds, that armored convoy
goes from having 26 officers...

142
00:11:34,312 --> 00:11:37,187
to six. And from seven vehicles...

143
00:11:40,937 --> 00:11:41,854
to one.

144
00:11:46,521 --> 00:11:47,437
POLICE

145
00:11:47,521 --> 00:11:51,229
And a parking garage is not a bunker
or a high-security prison.

146
00:11:51,312 --> 00:11:53,187
- It's...
- A parking garage.

147
00:11:53,271 --> 00:11:54,479
Exactly.

148
00:12:04,896 --> 00:12:07,187
From the National Court parking garage

149
00:12:07,271 --> 00:12:09,979
to the basement of our restaurant,

150
00:12:10,312 --> 00:12:11,812
there are exactly...

151
00:12:12,562 --> 00:12:16,062
11 meters and 68 centimeters of sandstone.

152
00:12:16,646 --> 00:12:19,187
Sandstone. You are Asturian miners.

153
00:12:19,271 --> 00:12:20,854
- The best.
- What's that to you?

154
00:12:20,937 --> 00:12:22,479
Nothing. Pick, shovel, grinder.

155
00:12:28,437 --> 00:12:30,896
Minimum noise, maximum efficiency.

156
00:12:30,979 --> 00:12:33,354
Ten hours, Benjamín, to have it ready.

157
00:12:33,437 --> 00:12:36,521
- And the extraction?
- Silent industrial machinery.

158
00:12:39,646 --> 00:12:42,312
We'll take the rubble to the kitchen.

159
00:12:44,021 --> 00:12:46,812
It'll be a clean and quick operation.

160
00:12:56,437 --> 00:12:57,521
Benjamín?

161
00:12:58,896 --> 00:12:59,896
Five meters.

162
00:13:03,146 --> 00:13:03,979
Palermo.

163
00:13:05,646 --> 00:13:07,271
I'm listening, Professor.

164
00:13:07,771 --> 00:13:09,062
How is he?

165
00:13:13,146 --> 00:13:14,562
He's conscious.

166
00:13:14,979 --> 00:13:16,812
General physical condition?

167
00:13:18,812 --> 00:13:23,312
He can't move one arm. He's lost blood.
He can hardly breathe.

168
00:13:23,396 --> 00:13:24,604
He's a total wreck.

169
00:13:24,812 --> 00:13:26,104
But will he recover?

170
00:13:26,187 --> 00:13:28,896
If I were his mother,
I'd be lighting candles.

171
00:13:29,521 --> 00:13:31,729
I'm telling you that he'll recover.

172
00:13:31,812 --> 00:13:33,854
I'll make sure of it personally.

173
00:13:33,937 --> 00:13:36,854
Even if I have to be with him
for six months.

174
00:13:37,562 --> 00:13:39,146
But I'll make you better.

175
00:13:41,062 --> 00:13:45,354
I'll feed you soup.
I'll make you strong again.

176
00:13:45,437 --> 00:13:49,354
And when you're as strong as an ox,
do you know what will happen?

177
00:13:50,812 --> 00:13:52,146
I'll kill you.

178
00:13:52,896 --> 00:13:54,479
I'll beat you to death.

179
00:13:56,104 --> 00:13:59,562
Why the fuck are we saving
this motherfucker's life?

180
00:13:59,646 --> 00:14:02,437
- Can he speak?
- So far, he's not saying much.

181
00:14:03,271 --> 00:14:06,146
My name is Stockholm. Do you remember me?

182
00:14:06,979 --> 00:14:09,937
Let go of me, fucking bitch, scumbag.

183
00:14:10,021 --> 00:14:10,854
Let go.

184
00:14:15,729 --> 00:14:17,646
Professor, he can talk.

185
00:14:18,146 --> 00:14:19,437
He killed Nairobi.

186
00:14:19,521 --> 00:14:21,521
What the fuck are we doing?

187
00:14:21,604 --> 00:14:24,521
- We have to kill him!
- That'll depend on him, Rio.

188
00:14:25,854 --> 00:14:28,021
If he wants to live, he'll live.

189
00:14:28,812 --> 00:14:30,062
If he wants to die...

190
00:14:31,187 --> 00:14:32,021
he'll die.

191
00:14:33,437 --> 00:14:34,812
It depends on him?

192
00:14:36,562 --> 00:14:37,979
You can't say that.

193
00:14:38,062 --> 00:14:40,854
You have no clue
how we're feeling in here.

194
00:14:40,937 --> 00:14:43,854
You don't know what it's like
to look him in the eyes.

195
00:14:43,937 --> 00:14:46,896
- Tokyo...
- Don't talk to me like you're my dad.

196
00:14:47,437 --> 00:14:49,229
Do you know how I feel?

197
00:14:50,896 --> 00:14:53,229
Do you know how Helsinki feels?

198
00:14:54,271 --> 00:14:57,729
Helsinki... is stitching him up.

199
00:14:58,646 --> 00:15:02,979
He's treating him.
Do you know who he treated before? No.

200
00:15:03,062 --> 00:15:05,312
You don't know. Of course you don't.

201
00:15:05,396 --> 00:15:08,854
You don't know anything.
You're hiding like a rat.

202
00:15:08,937 --> 00:15:11,854
That's how you keep giving orders
after Nairobi's death,

203
00:15:11,937 --> 00:15:16,729
without shedding a tear.
You feel nothing!

204
00:15:16,812 --> 00:15:18,437
Enough!

205
00:15:18,521 --> 00:15:19,979
You feel nothing!

206
00:15:20,062 --> 00:15:21,021
Stop.

207
00:15:21,104 --> 00:15:22,229
- Nothing!
- Stop!

208
00:15:26,812 --> 00:15:28,854
Do you want to feed him soup too?

209
00:15:30,479 --> 00:15:32,021
Tokyo, I would take him

210
00:15:32,437 --> 00:15:35,229
and I'd stick a burning iron through him.

211
00:15:35,771 --> 00:15:37,771
I'd take him down to the foundry,

212
00:15:38,187 --> 00:15:41,187
and I'd put his head in the furnace
to finish him off.

213
00:15:42,979 --> 00:15:47,146
You think I'm not hurting over Nairobi?
That the Professor isn't too?

214
00:15:47,229 --> 00:15:48,562
Doesn't seem like it.

215
00:15:50,104 --> 00:15:51,437
He's a prisoner.

216
00:15:51,521 --> 00:15:53,812
And we don't kill prisoners.

217
00:15:53,896 --> 00:15:57,187
As much as it pains us,
we don't kill prisoners.

218
00:15:57,312 --> 00:15:59,021
Nor do we kill in cold blood.

219
00:15:59,104 --> 00:16:00,896
But he did!

220
00:16:00,979 --> 00:16:05,604
He killed Nairobi! She was sick.
She was unarmed. She'd surrendered!

221
00:16:06,771 --> 00:16:08,937
We had a truce, for fuck's sake!

222
00:16:10,187 --> 00:16:13,521
Now it's about saving our lives, Rio,
like we saved yours.

223
00:16:13,604 --> 00:16:17,396
That involves collateral damage,
like swallowing the pain.

224
00:16:17,812 --> 00:16:20,437
We've run out of time.
They broke the truce.

225
00:16:20,521 --> 00:16:22,771
We have to turn this situation around.

226
00:16:23,979 --> 00:16:24,854
Helsinki.

227
00:16:25,354 --> 00:16:26,312
Helsinki!

228
00:16:27,562 --> 00:16:28,437
Helsinki, no!

229
00:16:30,104 --> 00:16:33,104
- No!
- Why did you kill her,

230
00:16:33,187 --> 00:16:35,146
you son of a bitch?

231
00:16:41,021 --> 00:16:43,062
Why'd you kill her?

232
00:16:52,271 --> 00:16:53,271
Palermo.

233
00:16:53,354 --> 00:16:54,771
Helsinki, look at me.

234
00:16:54,854 --> 00:16:56,229
Look me in the eyes.

235
00:16:56,687 --> 00:16:57,646
Helsinki!

236
00:17:05,187 --> 00:17:06,896
Come on, brother.

237
00:17:14,146 --> 00:17:15,229
Rio, Denver.

238
00:17:15,604 --> 00:17:16,521
Get to work.

239
00:17:17,021 --> 00:17:17,854
Now.

240
00:17:20,604 --> 00:17:21,562
Palermo?

241
00:17:22,354 --> 00:17:23,687
He's alive, sir.

242
00:17:28,521 --> 00:17:29,729
Son of a bitch.

243
00:17:47,979 --> 00:17:49,187
Are you having one?

244
00:17:50,521 --> 00:17:52,854
You're having an anxiety thing.

245
00:17:52,937 --> 00:17:55,021
It was very tense up there.

246
00:17:56,687 --> 00:17:58,062
It'll pass in a minute.

247
00:18:35,146 --> 00:18:39,146
I already know I'm fucked, Commissioner.
You don't need to remind me.

248
00:18:42,062 --> 00:18:45,229
- What I want to know is what happened.
- Call them.

249
00:18:45,312 --> 00:18:49,146
I've been a negotiator for 15 years.
I know when a deal's been accepted.

250
00:18:49,229 --> 00:18:52,021
Call them.
You'll be with them in 24 hours.

251
00:18:52,104 --> 00:18:53,479
We won't come after you.

252
00:18:53,562 --> 00:18:57,021
She was against the ropes.
She was going to sell the Professor out.

253
00:18:57,104 --> 00:18:59,521
I'd worn her down.
I'd almost defeated her.

254
00:18:59,604 --> 00:19:00,812
Then something happened.

255
00:19:03,271 --> 00:19:05,937
But what can happen
when someone is incommunicado?

256
00:19:11,229 --> 00:19:12,937
Maybe she wasn't incommunicado.

257
00:19:13,021 --> 00:19:15,354
Antoñanzas, stay and watch Murillo.

258
00:19:15,604 --> 00:19:16,937
Don't let anyone in.

259
00:19:32,354 --> 00:19:33,771
Antoñanzas?

260
00:19:35,521 --> 00:19:37,062
What do you think...

261
00:19:38,104 --> 00:19:38,937
Commissioner?

262
00:19:39,687 --> 00:19:41,562
Should we go after Antoñanzas?

263
00:19:42,979 --> 00:19:45,021
Smart creature.

264
00:19:51,187 --> 00:19:53,896
It's really like a vacation.

265
00:19:55,479 --> 00:19:57,979
I'll come back for you, Commissioner.

266
00:20:01,729 --> 00:20:06,354
Court proceedings have been initiated
against Alicia Sierra

267
00:20:06,437 --> 00:20:08,437
and a warrant issued for her arrest.

268
00:20:08,521 --> 00:20:11,229
The police negotiator
could be the first arrest

269
00:20:11,312 --> 00:20:13,979
in the Bank of Spain heist,
absurd as it sounds.

270
00:20:14,062 --> 00:20:16,771
She's accused of false imprisonment
and torture

271
00:20:16,854 --> 00:20:20,687
following the press conference
from the Ministry of the Interior.

272
00:20:20,771 --> 00:20:24,979
The minister, the director of the CNI,
and police commanders

273
00:20:25,062 --> 00:20:29,187
are preparing libel and slander lawsuits
against the inspector.

274
00:20:29,271 --> 00:20:32,312
Confirmed.
Interior requests her immediate arrest.

275
00:20:35,937 --> 00:20:37,187
Go after her!

276
00:20:50,396 --> 00:20:51,479
I'm sorry.

277
00:20:56,812 --> 00:20:59,604
I'm directly responsible
for all this shit.

278
00:21:01,729 --> 00:21:05,021
I didn't calculate the pain
it'd cause you. I'm sorry.

279
00:21:05,687 --> 00:21:07,937
What do you know about pain, Palermo?

280
00:21:13,854 --> 00:21:15,437
Pain is a loan shark.

281
00:21:19,646 --> 00:21:22,812
It leaves you with a debt
that you can never pay back.

282
00:21:24,604 --> 00:21:25,729
I can take pain.

283
00:21:26,521 --> 00:21:27,562
A lot of pain.

284
00:21:29,187 --> 00:21:34,271
Oh, yeah?
What about the pain you're feeling now?

285
00:21:36,062 --> 00:21:37,646
It's different, right?

286
00:21:38,187 --> 00:21:39,979
I saw it in your eyes.

287
00:21:42,437 --> 00:21:45,229
It was like seeing myself in the mirror.

288
00:21:46,937 --> 00:21:48,771
You have no idea...

289
00:21:50,562 --> 00:21:51,896
where you'll fall.

290
00:21:53,646 --> 00:21:55,396
Get out of there now.

291
00:21:59,896 --> 00:22:04,021
Otherwise, you run the risk of...
becoming a piece of shit like me.

292
00:22:04,396 --> 00:22:09,437
This horrible monster I've turned into.
A guy who destroys everything he touches.

293
00:22:11,229 --> 00:22:13,771
Someone who's wanted to die
for many years.

294
00:22:17,646 --> 00:22:20,729
And you can't get out of there.
You never get out.

295
00:22:22,062 --> 00:22:22,979
Look, brother.

296
00:22:24,812 --> 00:22:27,062
All that "boom, boom, ciao" crap...

297
00:22:27,146 --> 00:22:29,354
I treated you like shit.

298
00:22:29,729 --> 00:22:32,396
I didn't dare. I couldn't.
I didn't know how.

299
00:22:33,354 --> 00:22:36,354
But let me say, I'm by your side.
I won't let you fall.

300
00:22:36,437 --> 00:22:37,604
I know.

301
00:22:38,562 --> 00:22:40,479
I've known from the start.

302
00:22:41,604 --> 00:22:43,229
I know who you are.

303
00:22:46,312 --> 00:22:48,479
My name is Martín Berrote.

304
00:22:50,562 --> 00:22:55,437
I was born in Buenos Aires,
but I live in Palermo, Sicily.

305
00:22:55,521 --> 00:22:59,687
I'm going to get you out of here alive.
Even if I have to die doing it.

306
00:23:00,937 --> 00:23:02,771
My name is Mirko Dragic.

307
00:23:03,646 --> 00:23:05,021
I'm from Belgrade.

308
00:23:05,396 --> 00:23:08,146
I lost Oslo in the Mint.

309
00:23:08,604 --> 00:23:09,937
I lost Nairobi.

310
00:23:11,146 --> 00:23:13,437
And I'm not losing anyone else.

311
00:23:14,354 --> 00:23:17,271
You included, Martín Berrote.

312
00:23:29,812 --> 00:23:31,604
NATIONAL COURT
09:34 HOURS

313
00:23:31,687 --> 00:23:34,521
Lisbon will start testifying
at the National Court.

314
00:23:34,604 --> 00:23:38,771
She'll give reliable, specific details,
earning the judge's trust.

315
00:23:38,854 --> 00:23:41,937
And she'll do it meticulously
because all of this...

316
00:23:43,021 --> 00:23:44,979
is part of the Paris Plan.

317
00:23:45,687 --> 00:23:47,271
What is the Paris Plan?

318
00:23:50,729 --> 00:23:53,396
A rescue plan
in case either of us is caught.

319
00:23:58,396 --> 00:23:59,646
But why Paris?

320
00:24:03,687 --> 00:24:06,937
Because Paris is the city of freedom.

321
00:24:11,896 --> 00:24:13,312
And of love.

322
00:24:15,146 --> 00:24:18,521
Who hasn't strolled around Paris in love?
Right, boys?

323
00:24:20,229 --> 00:24:22,479
What will Lisbon tell the judge?

324
00:24:22,562 --> 00:24:25,354
The truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.

325
00:24:25,437 --> 00:24:27,937
And in fact, she'll start with love.

326
00:24:28,646 --> 00:24:32,896
How did you reunite with Sergio Marquina?
Did you arrange it?

327
00:24:33,896 --> 00:24:36,062
I met him a year after we escaped,

328
00:24:36,146 --> 00:24:37,937
in Palawan in the Philippines.

329
00:24:38,354 --> 00:24:42,562
He left me a puzzle with coordinates.
He might not look it, but he's romantic.

330
00:24:42,646 --> 00:24:44,687
She'll tell them everything.

331
00:24:44,854 --> 00:24:48,437
Everything: where we lived,
how often we relocated.

332
00:24:48,521 --> 00:24:51,937
After an hour and a half,
she'll tell them the plan.

333
00:24:52,021 --> 00:24:53,104
What do you mean?

334
00:24:53,187 --> 00:24:54,896
- She can't do that.
- She can.

335
00:24:54,979 --> 00:24:58,312
Truth is the basis of trust,
and that's a fact.

336
00:24:58,396 --> 00:25:01,646
The plan's to steal 90 tons of gold
from the national reserve.

337
00:25:01,729 --> 00:25:03,979
We're melting it.

338
00:25:04,521 --> 00:25:07,271
- They're melting it in there?
- Of course.

339
00:25:07,354 --> 00:25:09,812
By now, they'll have done around 50 tons.

340
00:25:09,896 --> 00:25:13,062
We're using industrial furnaces
made by Hormund.

341
00:25:13,146 --> 00:25:14,146
Hormund.

342
00:25:14,229 --> 00:25:15,854
German. They're the best.

343
00:25:16,896 --> 00:25:20,146
- Benjamín, how are we doing?
- Seven and a half meters!

344
00:25:20,229 --> 00:25:21,354
Faster.

345
00:25:21,437 --> 00:25:22,646
Faster!

346
00:25:23,979 --> 00:25:25,979
We'll give them all the details.

347
00:25:26,062 --> 00:25:29,729
They reach 2,300ºC,
and gold melts at 1,064ºC.

348
00:25:30,312 --> 00:25:34,104
We'll overwhelm them
with technical details, so their brains...

349
00:25:34,187 --> 00:25:36,312
have to keep processing information.

350
00:25:36,396 --> 00:25:41,187
We knew that the vault floods
at a rate of 7,500 liters a minute.

351
00:25:41,271 --> 00:25:43,146
Very detailed information.

352
00:25:43,229 --> 00:25:44,687
And we'll do that to...

353
00:25:45,354 --> 00:25:47,312
- tire them out.
- That's right.

354
00:25:47,396 --> 00:25:49,604
The challenge
was the interconnection tube.

355
00:25:49,687 --> 00:25:51,521
Can I have some paper and a pen?

356
00:25:51,604 --> 00:25:53,562
I'm going to tire you out.

357
00:25:57,604 --> 00:25:59,854
- Meters?
- Nine meters!

358
00:25:59,937 --> 00:26:00,771
Faster.

359
00:26:00,854 --> 00:26:02,562
The vault door...

360
00:26:02,646 --> 00:26:03,896
14 tons of steel...

361
00:26:03,979 --> 00:26:06,854
We had to cut a circle in it
in just minutes...

362
00:26:06,937 --> 00:26:08,187
The bathyscaphe floods...

363
00:26:08,271 --> 00:26:11,271
The diver enters...
We weld the tube...

364
00:26:11,354 --> 00:26:15,104
...to equalize the pressure...
...it comes out the other side.

365
00:26:15,187 --> 00:26:16,562
A bit like this.

366
00:26:21,604 --> 00:26:23,604
Have some dinner brought in.

367
00:26:27,437 --> 00:26:30,521
They say that pregnant women
have a sharper sense of smell.

368
00:26:31,396 --> 00:26:34,354
It was perhaps the only thing
the Professor hadn't foreseen.

369
00:26:35,146 --> 00:26:37,771
It was the first time
someone had picked up his scent

370
00:26:37,854 --> 00:26:39,229
without him sensing it.

371
00:26:42,979 --> 00:26:46,354
Antoñanzas's wife
had not yet seen the news.

372
00:26:47,562 --> 00:26:49,896
- Marisa?
- Sierra took less than 3 minutes

373
00:26:49,979 --> 00:26:51,979
to get the information she needed.

374
00:26:52,062 --> 00:26:55,104
- I'm a colleague of Benito's.
- I know who you are.

375
00:26:56,104 --> 00:27:00,354
Let me see, where do I begin?
Benito has been acting...

376
00:27:00,979 --> 00:27:04,771
- weird lately, nervous...
- Antoñanzas had seemed anxious at home.

377
00:27:04,854 --> 00:27:07,521
So much so,
he'd been swimming late at night

378
00:27:07,604 --> 00:27:09,646
with two friends in the pool.

379
00:27:10,437 --> 00:27:13,146
And it seemed like he was drunk.

380
00:27:16,687 --> 00:27:19,896
Colonel, Sierra isn't at home.
She must have fled.

381
00:27:19,979 --> 00:27:21,979
Fucking bitch.

382
00:27:23,104 --> 00:27:26,646
All units, an arrest warrant's been issued
for Alicia Sierra.

383
00:27:28,187 --> 00:27:31,521
I can't give you the footage
even if you are an officer.

384
00:27:31,687 --> 00:27:36,146
I need permission from a judge
or the residents' association president.

385
00:27:36,229 --> 00:27:39,021
Oh wait, someone's calling me.

386
00:27:40,104 --> 00:27:43,021
It's the residents' association president.

387
00:27:43,646 --> 00:27:45,312
How are you, President?

388
00:27:49,146 --> 00:27:50,521
OK, thank you.

389
00:27:52,646 --> 00:27:53,479
He says yes.

390
00:27:54,729 --> 00:27:58,021
Give me the tapes of the entrance,

391
00:27:58,104 --> 00:28:01,604
the pool, the parking lot, the street...
All of them.

392
00:28:17,396 --> 00:28:18,771
Listen, Amanda.

393
00:28:20,104 --> 00:28:21,812
What you did before...

394
00:28:22,062 --> 00:28:24,896
Making unfounded accusations against me...

395
00:28:24,979 --> 00:28:27,812
- I don't want to hear it. Leave me alone.
- Look...

396
00:28:27,896 --> 00:28:32,187
Didn't you hear her? Leave her alone.
Don't make me kick you out of here.

397
00:28:32,271 --> 00:28:33,437
What are you doing?

398
00:28:33,521 --> 00:28:35,854
Everyone quiet, now!

399
00:28:40,354 --> 00:28:43,396
You're despicable. You make me cringe.

400
00:28:43,479 --> 00:28:45,979
You're calling me despicable? You?

401
00:28:46,062 --> 00:28:47,146
A banker.

402
00:28:47,229 --> 00:28:50,312
A puppet of the system and of capitalism.

403
00:28:50,396 --> 00:28:53,271
You're giving me lessons in ethics?

404
00:28:53,354 --> 00:28:56,687
A man who didn't have the balls
to defend his workers

405
00:28:56,771 --> 00:28:58,729
- and face the terrorists.
- Enough!

406
00:29:00,604 --> 00:29:01,437
On the ground!

407
00:29:01,521 --> 00:29:03,812
Hands behind your head!

408
00:29:03,896 --> 00:29:05,521
Come on. All right!

409
00:29:05,604 --> 00:29:06,854
You, over there!

410
00:29:06,937 --> 00:29:09,104
- Arturo!
- Everyone on their feet.

411
00:29:09,187 --> 00:29:10,937
I'll get you out, I promise.

412
00:29:11,021 --> 00:29:14,812
All of you! That's the difference
between you and me, Governor.

413
00:29:14,896 --> 00:29:18,437
I came to save all these people,
to be a hero.

414
00:29:18,521 --> 00:29:22,312
While you piss your pants
at the slightest thing.

415
00:29:22,396 --> 00:29:24,479
- Governor.
- Arturo.

416
00:29:25,354 --> 00:29:26,396
She's got a gun.

417
00:29:26,479 --> 00:29:31,562
You're going to put that G36 on the floor
in the next three seconds.

418
00:29:31,646 --> 00:29:33,396
If you don't, you're dead.

419
00:29:35,771 --> 00:29:38,562
Who are you?
If you don't mind me asking.

420
00:29:38,646 --> 00:29:41,646
Manila. Undercover agent for the gang.

421
00:29:41,729 --> 00:29:42,646
Well, look...

422
00:29:43,562 --> 00:29:45,854
Manila, I don't buy a word of it.

423
00:29:45,937 --> 00:29:49,021
And that gun is one of the fake ones
they give us.

424
00:29:49,104 --> 00:29:50,187
You don't fool me.

425
00:29:51,312 --> 00:29:53,979
You have two seconds.
Put the gun down,

426
00:29:54,062 --> 00:29:56,604
and pray it's not true you raped Amanda.

427
00:29:56,687 --> 00:29:59,729
You're pissing me off.
I'm losing my patience.

428
00:29:59,812 --> 00:30:01,021
- One.
- So...

429
00:30:06,521 --> 00:30:08,604
I didn't rape her.

430
00:30:09,229 --> 00:30:11,562
I just gave her some anxiety meds.

431
00:30:11,646 --> 00:30:12,979
I'm bleeding out.

432
00:30:13,562 --> 00:30:14,646
I'm dying.

433
00:30:14,729 --> 00:30:17,062
You're not. There's an exit wound.

434
00:30:17,146 --> 00:30:20,062
There are no arteries
or anything important there.

435
00:30:20,562 --> 00:30:24,687
Arturo, you're under arrest,
accused of rape.

436
00:30:25,062 --> 00:30:25,937
And...

437
00:30:27,937 --> 00:30:33,771
may I remind you
that you offered me pills too, scumbag.

438
00:30:36,187 --> 00:30:39,062
That night in the bank, no one slept.

439
00:30:39,521 --> 00:30:41,146
But the worst news

440
00:30:41,812 --> 00:30:45,312
was that, outside,
our biggest enemy was wasting no time.

441
00:30:47,646 --> 00:30:51,979
Sierra saw Antoñanzas fall.
She saw him hit the springboard.

442
00:30:54,479 --> 00:30:57,396
Seconds later,
the Professor and Marseille appeared.

443
00:30:59,354 --> 00:31:01,854
It was 3:11 in the morning.

444
00:31:09,646 --> 00:31:13,271
Minutes later, she had the license plate.

445
00:31:18,604 --> 00:31:20,687
What's up, cutie?

446
00:31:21,312 --> 00:31:24,312
- Fuck, Alicia, don't give me shit.
- Take it easy.

447
00:31:24,396 --> 00:31:27,479
I have a license plate
from April 7 at 3:00 a.m.

448
00:31:27,562 --> 00:31:30,812
It left a street off the M-30.
I need to know where it went.

449
00:31:30,896 --> 00:31:33,437
You're a wanted woman.
I'm taking a risk.

450
00:31:33,521 --> 00:31:36,229
How many times
have I taken risks for you, Raúl?

451
00:31:37,104 --> 00:31:40,604
Should I remind you of the last time?
Don't fuck with me.

452
00:31:47,896 --> 00:31:48,729
Meters?

453
00:31:48,812 --> 00:31:50,187
Nine and a half!

454
00:31:50,521 --> 00:31:52,312
Lisbon's mission...

455
00:31:53,021 --> 00:31:56,104
is to buy us the time we need.

456
00:31:56,187 --> 00:31:57,146
You see...

457
00:31:58,187 --> 00:32:00,729
people can concentrate
for about 50 minutes.

458
00:32:00,812 --> 00:32:03,729
However important that information is,

459
00:32:03,812 --> 00:32:06,396
there's a point
when you can't take any more.

460
00:32:07,229 --> 00:32:10,271
They'll have no choice
but to continue the next day.

461
00:32:10,354 --> 00:32:13,062
Do you know anything
about underwater welding?

462
00:32:13,146 --> 00:32:16,021
Or about how to use
a thermic lance underwater?

463
00:32:16,104 --> 00:32:18,396
In water, you cut metal with fire.

464
00:32:18,479 --> 00:32:20,021
Fire? Underwater?

465
00:32:20,104 --> 00:32:22,437
- How are we doing?
- Ten meters!

466
00:32:22,937 --> 00:32:24,354
Faster.

467
00:32:24,437 --> 00:32:25,729
Faster!

468
00:32:25,812 --> 00:32:28,729
Fire underwater
to get to the state secrets,

469
00:32:28,812 --> 00:32:30,104
key to the negotiation.

470
00:32:30,187 --> 00:32:32,979
But it didn't work.
We had to use the dolphin.

471
00:32:33,062 --> 00:32:34,562
A dolphin?

472
00:32:34,646 --> 00:32:36,104
Ten and a half.

473
00:32:37,604 --> 00:32:41,646
Flipper is the name we gave
the governor of the Bank of Spain.

474
00:32:41,729 --> 00:32:44,937
It was the fastest way
to get the secrets and negotiate.

475
00:32:45,021 --> 00:32:46,937
That's an act of coercion.

476
00:32:47,021 --> 00:32:49,104
- I know.
- And disclosure of secrets.

477
00:32:49,687 --> 00:32:51,854
We sent the secrets to an external server.

478
00:32:51,937 --> 00:32:55,646
Lend me the pencil,
and I can outline how the IT system works.

479
00:32:56,979 --> 00:32:58,896
It's almost one in the morning.

480
00:32:58,979 --> 00:33:01,687
Maybe we should take a break.

481
00:33:01,771 --> 00:33:05,437
If the prosecution
and the defense agree...

482
00:33:09,021 --> 00:33:10,354
She'll go back to prison.

483
00:33:12,062 --> 00:33:13,771
And we'll keep chipping away...

484
00:33:14,729 --> 00:33:17,021
and chipping away.

485
00:33:17,896 --> 00:33:22,562
And between 4:00 and 4:30 in the morning,
we'll have drilled through

486
00:33:22,646 --> 00:33:25,812
the 11 meters and 68 centimeters
of our tunnel.

487
00:33:25,896 --> 00:33:30,021
And at last...
we'll access the parking garage.

488
00:33:32,146 --> 00:33:34,687
- Questions?
- How do we get into the garage

489
00:33:34,771 --> 00:33:36,604
without being seen?

490
00:33:36,854 --> 00:33:38,646
Good!

491
00:33:38,729 --> 00:33:40,354
Very good question.

492
00:33:40,437 --> 00:33:42,812
In two stages. First: Pakistan.

493
00:33:42,896 --> 00:33:43,937
- Pakistan.
- Yes.

494
00:33:44,021 --> 00:33:45,854
And you'll give the order.

495
00:33:55,646 --> 00:33:57,562
The mole is out for a walk.

496
00:33:58,896 --> 00:33:59,896
Shakir.

497
00:34:00,437 --> 00:34:02,521
- Shakir, now.
- Perfect, Professor.

498
00:34:02,604 --> 00:34:07,187
From Pakistan, they'll change the signal
of the internal CCTV.

499
00:34:07,271 --> 00:34:11,312
And from then on,
the guards will see a recording.

500
00:34:14,312 --> 00:34:16,937
Stage two: Marseille.

501
00:34:17,812 --> 00:34:20,562
Marseille will be
at that critical point on a night out,

502
00:34:20,646 --> 00:34:23,812
when all the bars in Madrid
have closed, but...

503
00:34:24,604 --> 00:34:28,479
you want to keep dancing
with your new hookup,

504
00:34:28,562 --> 00:34:29,854
Sheila.

505
00:34:31,146 --> 00:34:31,979
Marseille.

506
00:34:32,771 --> 00:34:33,771
Speaking.

507
00:34:34,562 --> 00:34:36,271
- Benjamín?
- Speaking.

508
00:34:36,354 --> 00:34:40,271
And that will drown out the noise
of the angle grinders.

509
00:34:40,854 --> 00:34:41,854
Stopwatches.

510
00:34:46,312 --> 00:34:48,146
Three, two...

511
00:34:48,229 --> 00:34:49,271
one...

512
00:34:50,271 --> 00:34:51,104
now.

513
00:34:53,396 --> 00:34:54,771
Now.

514
00:35:18,646 --> 00:35:21,271
Good evening. Is there a problem?

515
00:35:21,354 --> 00:35:23,229
What the hell are you doing?

516
00:35:23,312 --> 00:35:25,812
Having a party. All the bars are closed.

517
00:35:25,896 --> 00:35:29,687
So we're having a little party
here in the car.

518
00:35:30,437 --> 00:35:32,729
Marseille, hang on.

519
00:35:32,812 --> 00:35:34,104
Hang on, Marseille.

520
00:35:35,729 --> 00:35:36,812
One minute!

521
00:35:38,646 --> 00:35:42,021
What sort of party is it
with alcohol-free beer?

522
00:35:42,604 --> 00:35:44,854
Well, I want to make love tonight.

523
00:35:44,937 --> 00:35:46,812
And with alcohol...

524
00:35:47,396 --> 00:35:48,812
And without alcohol...

525
00:35:50,562 --> 00:35:51,771
Turn off the music.

526
00:35:54,271 --> 00:35:55,229
Benjamín!

527
00:35:55,312 --> 00:35:56,396
Thirty seconds!

528
00:35:57,021 --> 00:35:58,854
Don't turn it off, Marseille.

529
00:35:58,937 --> 00:36:00,771
- What?
- Turn off the music.

530
00:36:03,562 --> 00:36:04,979
Twenty seconds!

531
00:36:05,396 --> 00:36:08,896
- Turn off the damn music.
- Hold on, Marseille.

532
00:36:11,354 --> 00:36:13,104
- Get out of the car.
- Hold on.

533
00:36:13,187 --> 00:36:14,437
Ten seconds!

534
00:36:15,521 --> 00:36:17,354
- Get out.
- Five seconds!

535
00:36:22,979 --> 00:36:24,771
The burrow is open.

536
00:36:25,229 --> 00:36:26,271
We're in.

537
00:36:26,354 --> 00:36:28,937
OK.

538
00:36:30,896 --> 00:36:31,937
Get out of here.

539
00:36:55,937 --> 00:36:57,229
We're in.

540
00:36:57,937 --> 00:36:58,771
Benjamín.

541
00:37:00,062 --> 00:37:00,896
Stage three.

542
00:37:01,396 --> 00:37:02,437
Roger that.

543
00:37:12,354 --> 00:37:13,187
Hello.

544
00:37:13,646 --> 00:37:14,896
M-607.

545
00:37:14,979 --> 00:37:19,021
The last CCTV sighting was
at kilometer 29, the Colmenar Viejo exit.

546
00:37:32,521 --> 00:37:38,437
Eight in the morning on the second day...
the last stage begins.

547
00:37:39,271 --> 00:37:41,979
That's when Lisbon will leave
Soto del Real prison,

548
00:37:42,062 --> 00:37:45,312
guarded by the same convoy
as the day before.

549
00:37:50,271 --> 00:37:51,896
She's just left the prison.

550
00:37:52,604 --> 00:37:53,521
Get ready.

551
00:37:54,646 --> 00:37:57,229
Tokyo, get Gandía ready.

552
00:37:57,312 --> 00:38:00,437
At 8:35, she'll arrive
at the National Court.

553
00:38:00,521 --> 00:38:03,229
The entrance
will still be full of journalists.

554
00:38:03,312 --> 00:38:05,604
They'll repeat the same procedure.

555
00:38:06,729 --> 00:38:09,271
They'll go into the parking garage.

556
00:38:10,396 --> 00:38:12,229
But there's one difference...

557
00:38:13,021 --> 00:38:15,229
you will already be there.

558
00:38:15,854 --> 00:38:17,937
But nobody will be able to see you.

559
00:38:18,521 --> 00:38:20,437
Because overnight...

560
00:38:21,229 --> 00:38:23,229
you'll have built a false wall.

561
00:38:23,312 --> 00:38:24,896
Jeez, Louise!

562
00:38:24,979 --> 00:38:27,937
You'll have three hours to build that wall

563
00:38:28,021 --> 00:38:32,354
before the first National Court employees
arrive at 7:00 a.m.

564
00:38:34,646 --> 00:38:35,771
That wall

565
00:38:35,854 --> 00:38:39,687
will be just small enough
that no one will notice it,

566
00:38:40,604 --> 00:38:43,271
but big enough for you to hide behind.

567
00:38:55,271 --> 00:38:56,146
Perfect.

568
00:39:04,396 --> 00:39:07,104
And then comes
the David Copperfield moment.

569
00:39:07,854 --> 00:39:11,229
How to extract someone

570
00:39:11,312 --> 00:39:15,979
from a van guarded by six other vehicles
and surrounded by civil guards

571
00:39:16,521 --> 00:39:20,604
without anyone realizing.

572
00:39:21,771 --> 00:39:24,187
How to do it so that life goes on...

573
00:39:25,521 --> 00:39:27,521
as if nothing had happened.

574
00:39:30,562 --> 00:39:34,021
For that, we need to move
the next piece on the board.

575
00:39:36,479 --> 00:39:39,229
And it's an essential piece.

576
00:39:47,604 --> 00:39:51,437
The time has come...
for you to decide your fate:

577
00:39:52,437 --> 00:39:54,562
life or death.

578
00:39:55,354 --> 00:39:57,604
We've reconnected your equipment.

579
00:39:57,729 --> 00:40:00,896
You'll call the tent,
you'll speak to Tamayo,

580
00:40:00,979 --> 00:40:03,479
and you'll say you killed Nairobi.

581
00:40:05,104 --> 00:40:06,646
Fucking son of a bitch.

582
00:40:09,521 --> 00:40:11,229
And killed me too.

583
00:40:13,104 --> 00:40:15,729
That we haven't found the panic room yet,

584
00:40:15,896 --> 00:40:17,604
but that we're about to.

585
00:40:17,771 --> 00:40:20,854
That you're going out
and that you've got a radio.

586
00:40:21,479 --> 00:40:22,354
What's up?

587
00:40:24,312 --> 00:40:27,396
Am I turning you on
like when I rammed the shrapnel into you?

588
00:40:30,104 --> 00:40:31,021
Get to it.

589
00:40:44,729 --> 00:40:45,771
Command center.

590
00:40:48,854 --> 00:40:50,312
It's César Gandía.

591
00:40:51,312 --> 00:40:54,521
Head of security
for the governor of the Bank of Spain.

592
00:40:56,396 --> 00:41:00,146
It's a ruse. They caught me!
They're trying to set you up!

593
00:41:00,646 --> 00:41:01,479
Gandía...

594
00:41:02,896 --> 00:41:04,021
it's the Professor.

595
00:41:04,937 --> 00:41:06,937
We fully expected you to do this,

596
00:41:07,021 --> 00:41:10,479
but that was your one chance
to get it wrong.

597
00:41:10,687 --> 00:41:12,687
The next call will be to Tamayo.

598
00:41:12,771 --> 00:41:15,562
- Do it again...
- Think of your son, Juanito.

599
00:41:16,896 --> 00:41:18,562
...and Tokyo will kill you.

600
00:41:19,062 --> 00:41:20,354
You hear me, Tokyo?

601
00:41:20,896 --> 00:41:23,521
- Loud and clear.
- Listen to me, Tokyo.

602
00:41:24,354 --> 00:41:28,771
You'll hang up... and you'll kill him.

603
00:41:30,146 --> 00:41:32,271
I want you to understand one thing.

604
00:41:32,354 --> 00:41:35,771
You can't win now.
You've already lost. Do you understand?

605
00:41:35,854 --> 00:41:39,229
The heroic thing to do
is to see your wife and son again.

606
00:41:40,354 --> 00:41:41,979
If not, they'll lose you.

607
00:41:43,396 --> 00:41:44,604
They'll lose you.

608
00:41:45,604 --> 00:41:47,104
Do you hear me, Tokyo?

609
00:41:48,521 --> 00:41:49,687
Get to it.

610
00:42:04,771 --> 00:42:05,604
Suárez.

611
00:42:07,146 --> 00:42:08,312
Martínez!

612
00:42:09,979 --> 00:42:10,812
Colonel!

613
00:42:10,896 --> 00:42:11,937
It's Gandía.

614
00:42:13,187 --> 00:42:14,479
Gandía, I'm here.

615
00:42:14,562 --> 00:42:17,062
Colonel, I'm in the panic room.

616
00:42:17,937 --> 00:42:19,854
They're about to find it.

617
00:42:19,937 --> 00:42:22,104
I've eliminated Nairobi and Tokyo.

618
00:42:22,854 --> 00:42:24,771
I'm launching another attack.

619
00:42:24,854 --> 00:42:27,354
I'll take a radio. This is the frequency.

620
00:42:29,104 --> 00:42:32,646
- I want all units on alert.
- Alpha and Beta units, get ready.

621
00:42:32,729 --> 00:42:35,937
- Everyone ready and on alert.
- Go.

622
00:42:38,646 --> 00:42:40,312
Four, six, two,

623
00:42:40,396 --> 00:42:43,104
point, six, six, two.

624
00:42:47,396 --> 00:42:48,646
Come with us.

625
00:42:50,937 --> 00:42:53,896
If we don't get Lisbon
when she arrives, what do we do?

626
00:42:53,979 --> 00:42:55,604
Wait in the wall for 10 hours?

627
00:42:55,687 --> 00:42:59,854
This time, it'll take her
less than 20 minutes to come back.

628
00:43:01,312 --> 00:43:04,812
They'll insist, of course,
but she'll be within her rights.

629
00:43:07,937 --> 00:43:09,937
I've decided not to testify.

630
00:43:10,021 --> 00:43:13,562
Mrs. Murillo, yesterday
you seriously incriminated yourself.

631
00:43:13,771 --> 00:43:15,937
I advise you not to backtrack.

632
00:43:16,354 --> 00:43:18,812
You could get penal benefits.

633
00:43:18,896 --> 00:43:22,479
The judge will be forced
to send her to prison.

634
00:43:22,562 --> 00:43:26,937
The same guards who took her in
will take her back to the parking garage.

635
00:43:27,562 --> 00:43:31,229
But no one will be watching,
because the security control room

636
00:43:31,312 --> 00:43:34,021
will be seeing the recording
from the night before.

637
00:43:37,687 --> 00:43:39,812
The first time Lisbon arrived.

638
00:43:39,896 --> 00:43:41,187
And then,

639
00:43:41,271 --> 00:43:43,062
they'll cross paths with...

640
00:43:44,062 --> 00:43:46,937
a judge... a prosecutor...

641
00:43:49,771 --> 00:43:50,979
a police officer...

642
00:43:51,312 --> 00:43:53,312
and two lawyers.

643
00:43:55,937 --> 00:43:58,396
Well, maybe you should be the prisoner.

644
00:44:01,271 --> 00:44:02,271
Benjamín.

645
00:44:03,104 --> 00:44:05,146
- Everyone ready?
- Ready.

646
00:44:09,229 --> 00:44:10,437
Now.

647
00:44:20,854 --> 00:44:22,687
- Benjamín.
- I see her.

648
00:44:28,771 --> 00:44:30,229
Twenty-five meters.

649
00:44:35,854 --> 00:44:37,104
Ten meters.

650
00:44:41,604 --> 00:44:43,229
The signal will be...

651
00:44:45,854 --> 00:44:46,854
"Good morning."

652
00:44:46,937 --> 00:44:47,937
Three meters.

653
00:44:49,979 --> 00:44:51,021
Good morning.

654
00:45:06,729 --> 00:45:09,354
- Good morning, Ms. Lisbon.
- Hello.

655
00:45:10,479 --> 00:45:11,437
Let's go.

656
00:45:11,687 --> 00:45:14,604
We won't make it easy for them:
within 45 seconds,

657
00:45:14,687 --> 00:45:17,646
they'll have explosives
strapped to their chests.

658
00:45:17,729 --> 00:45:22,604
Within 55, two cameras and two microphones
will be watching them so that...

659
00:45:25,354 --> 00:45:27,437
if they change the route...

660
00:45:27,521 --> 00:45:28,437
Boom.

661
00:45:29,062 --> 00:45:31,729
If they attempt to raise the alarm...

662
00:45:32,312 --> 00:45:33,271
Boom.

663
00:45:33,354 --> 00:45:36,521
If you don't drive the prisoner
back to the prison...

664
00:45:36,604 --> 00:45:37,521
Boom.

665
00:45:39,396 --> 00:45:42,187
Are we taking the prisoner or not?

666
00:45:42,271 --> 00:45:45,021
We'll give them another Lisbon.

667
00:45:59,146 --> 00:45:59,979
Officers...

668
00:46:01,812 --> 00:46:04,604
everything OK? You're taking a long time.

669
00:46:07,062 --> 00:46:08,937
Yes, everything's fine.

670
00:46:09,021 --> 00:46:11,771
- We're coming up now.
- OK, understood.

671
00:46:13,896 --> 00:46:17,646
And that's when
the great magic trick begins.

672
00:46:17,729 --> 00:46:20,187
The climax
of the David Copperfield show.

673
00:46:20,271 --> 00:46:22,687
- Who is this Copperfield?
- The magician.

674
00:46:22,771 --> 00:46:26,229
- Wasn't that Harry Potter?
- It'll seem like nothing's changed.

675
00:46:32,687 --> 00:46:34,062
But it won't be.

676
00:46:38,521 --> 00:46:42,479
Because we'll have someone crawling
through the tunnel at top speed.

677
00:47:01,229 --> 00:47:02,062
Come on.

678
00:47:08,062 --> 00:47:09,021
Come on.

679
00:48:17,312 --> 00:48:18,187
Let's go.

680
00:48:24,562 --> 00:48:25,396
Tokyo...

681
00:48:26,312 --> 00:48:27,812
Lisbon is on the way.

682
00:48:27,896 --> 00:48:30,271
Begin the countdown... now.

683
00:48:32,104 --> 00:48:33,062
Run!

684
00:48:34,937 --> 00:48:36,937
Colonel, they're shooting!

685
00:48:37,979 --> 00:48:38,937
Gandía!

686
00:48:39,021 --> 00:48:41,187
- Gandía, answer me.
- Gandía here.

687
00:48:41,312 --> 00:48:42,604
Gandía here!

688
00:48:42,687 --> 00:48:45,896
- They're closing in on me.
- They're closing in on me.

689
00:48:45,979 --> 00:48:48,104
- I'm caught in the cross fire.
- Good.

690
00:48:49,729 --> 00:48:50,562
Up you go.

691
00:48:53,062 --> 00:48:56,146
- Where are you? Can we give cover fire?
- Negative.

692
00:48:56,229 --> 00:48:57,562
Negative, Colonel.

693
00:48:57,646 --> 00:49:00,479
- I'm going to the roof.
- I'm going to the roof.

694
00:49:00,562 --> 00:49:03,354
- I request evacuation.
- I request evacuation!

695
00:49:03,437 --> 00:49:05,771
Suárez, send a helicopter, now.

696
00:49:05,854 --> 00:49:07,896
- Come on!
- Delta 1, prepare for takeoff.

697
00:49:07,979 --> 00:49:10,021
Rescue operation at the Bank of Spain,
now!

698
00:49:11,896 --> 00:49:13,229
Hold on, Gandía.

699
00:49:13,312 --> 00:49:15,187
I have an M16 and 3 magazines.

700
00:49:15,271 --> 00:49:17,646
I don't know how long I can hold out.

701
00:49:18,812 --> 00:49:19,979
Fire. Now.

702
00:49:29,271 --> 00:49:32,979
- They started a fire.
- They're starting a fire. I can't see!

703
00:49:33,062 --> 00:49:34,854
Colonel.

704
00:49:34,937 --> 00:49:36,104
Smoke on the roof.

705
00:49:36,187 --> 00:49:38,354
Hold on. The helicopter's coming.

706
00:49:53,687 --> 00:49:54,646
Lisbon.

707
00:49:54,729 --> 00:49:56,521
- Marseille.
- Marseille.

708
00:49:57,146 --> 00:49:58,646
We have Lisbon.

709
00:49:59,312 --> 00:50:00,354
Switch to blanks.

710
00:50:12,354 --> 00:50:13,979
Let's go!

711
00:50:27,104 --> 00:50:29,771
Where will you get a military helicopter?

712
00:50:30,771 --> 00:50:34,812
The same place we got the vehicles
for the heist: the black market.

713
00:50:34,896 --> 00:50:37,896
Not only that,
we'll intercept their communications

714
00:50:37,979 --> 00:50:43,187
so that when they contact the helicopter,
it'll be us who answer.

715
00:50:44,437 --> 00:50:46,187
Where's the helicopter?

716
00:50:46,271 --> 00:50:47,521
Delta, position.

717
00:50:48,104 --> 00:50:48,937
Time?

718
00:50:49,021 --> 00:50:50,771
Two minutes, fifty seconds.

719
00:50:50,854 --> 00:50:54,521
- Two minutes, 50 seconds.
- Go to the roof. We'll cover you.

720
00:50:54,604 --> 00:50:57,437
I can't.
There's plastic explosive on the door.

721
00:50:57,521 --> 00:51:00,771
- For fuck's sake! Bomb disposal!
- Bomb disposal!

722
00:51:02,479 --> 00:51:05,354
- Describe the device.
- Blue wire to the primer.

723
00:51:05,437 --> 00:51:08,687
There's a movement sensor
and a blue wire to the primer.

724
00:51:14,187 --> 00:51:16,312
Cut it. It's a simple device.

725
00:51:16,396 --> 00:51:17,354
- You sure?
- Yes.

726
00:51:17,437 --> 00:51:18,646
- No!
- Cut it.

727
00:51:18,729 --> 00:51:20,062
No. Colonel!

728
00:51:22,979 --> 00:51:26,062
- Wire cut.
- Wire cut!

729
00:51:26,146 --> 00:51:27,396
Denver, now.

730
00:51:28,396 --> 00:51:30,396
I'm in black. Don't shoot.

731
00:51:30,479 --> 00:51:31,687
- Door.
- Exiting now.

732
00:51:31,771 --> 00:51:34,521
I'm wearing black and a ski mask.
Hold fire.

733
00:51:36,646 --> 00:51:38,271
Our man's in black. Cover him.

734
00:51:38,354 --> 00:51:40,979
- Be ready for possible cross fire.
- Copy.

735
00:51:45,271 --> 00:51:46,896
Switch to blanks.

736
00:51:46,979 --> 00:51:47,979
Go!

737
00:51:48,479 --> 00:51:50,187
Let's go!

738
00:51:53,854 --> 00:51:55,729
They're on the roof. They're firing!

739
00:51:59,687 --> 00:52:01,604
Cover fire!

740
00:52:01,687 --> 00:52:03,479
There's smoke. I don't have a shot.

741
00:52:05,812 --> 00:52:07,437
- Tokyo, now.
- Palermo?

742
00:52:09,479 --> 00:52:10,771
Open.

743
00:52:28,521 --> 00:52:30,354
- Searching for target.
- No visual.

744
00:52:30,854 --> 00:52:32,187
I've got them. I see them!

745
00:52:33,271 --> 00:52:34,687
Target in sight.

746
00:52:37,312 --> 00:52:38,521
Permission to shoot.

747
00:52:39,312 --> 00:52:40,771
Permission to shoot.

748
00:52:41,437 --> 00:52:43,896
- They're shooting at us!
- Motherfuckers.

749
00:52:43,979 --> 00:52:45,271
We're exposed.

750
00:52:45,354 --> 00:52:47,354
- They're exposed!
- Take cover!

751
00:52:47,437 --> 00:52:49,187
We're retreating to cover.

752
00:52:49,271 --> 00:52:53,104
Delta, begin approach maneuver.
Rescue protocol.

753
00:52:53,437 --> 00:52:55,437
I want a quick, clean extraction.

754
00:53:04,562 --> 00:53:05,437
Marseille.

755
00:53:05,521 --> 00:53:07,937
- Arriving.
- Helicopter in position.

756
00:53:08,021 --> 00:53:10,896
- Get it down there!
- Go ahead.

757
00:53:21,562 --> 00:53:24,062
- Permission to descend, sir!
- Proceed.

758
00:53:32,687 --> 00:53:34,479
Back in the helicopter, now!

759
00:53:44,271 --> 00:53:45,229
Lisbon!

760
00:53:45,312 --> 00:53:47,937
- Denver!
- Welcome to the Bank of Spain!

761
00:53:56,771 --> 00:54:00,396
Package delivered, Professor.
I'll be out in two minutes.

762
00:54:02,896 --> 00:54:04,771
Where's the helicopter going?

763
00:54:05,854 --> 00:54:09,062
Delta 1, what's going on?
Return to your position!

764
00:54:09,146 --> 00:54:10,729
- Delta 1, come in!
- Fuck!

765
00:54:19,562 --> 00:54:22,896
There's a problem with the helicopter.
We're gonna tackle them.

766
00:54:26,937 --> 00:54:29,104
Where'd that agent come from?
What balls.

767
00:54:39,729 --> 00:54:41,562
They're retreating.

768
00:54:49,396 --> 00:54:50,437
Are you OK?

769
00:54:54,854 --> 00:54:55,687
Yes?

770
00:54:56,354 --> 00:54:57,562
What?

771
00:54:58,771 --> 00:55:02,104
A call from Soto del Real.
The convoy that transferred Murillo.

772
00:55:02,187 --> 00:55:05,812
I have a woman here who was kidnapped
as she left the hairdressers.

773
00:55:05,896 --> 00:55:09,437
What do I care?
This is the command center for the heist!

774
00:55:09,521 --> 00:55:10,771
Here, asshole.

775
00:55:11,479 --> 00:55:13,104
Gandía, hold on!

776
00:55:13,187 --> 00:55:15,812
Stay on the stairs
till the helicopter returns.

777
00:55:15,896 --> 00:55:17,854
Where's the fucking helicopter?

778
00:55:20,896 --> 00:55:21,729
Colonel...

779
00:55:22,521 --> 00:55:23,562
- What?
- Colonel.

780
00:55:26,271 --> 00:55:29,271
The situation seems to be... a trick.

781
00:55:45,812 --> 00:55:48,187
- Yes!
- Come on!

782
00:55:51,729 --> 00:55:53,104
Yes!

783
00:55:56,312 --> 00:55:57,687
Fuck yeah!

784
00:55:57,771 --> 00:55:59,146
- Yes!
- Professor.

785
00:55:59,229 --> 00:56:00,687
Lisbon is with us.

786
00:56:00,771 --> 00:56:03,937
I repeat, Lisbon is with us!

787
00:56:19,646 --> 00:56:20,854
Fuck yeah!

788
00:56:22,312 --> 00:56:23,479
Listen to me.

789
00:56:27,187 --> 00:56:28,271
This war...

790
00:56:30,521 --> 00:56:31,729
We're going to win.

791
00:56:34,396 --> 00:56:35,354
For Nairobi.

792
00:56:36,604 --> 00:56:37,479
For Nairobi.

793
00:56:39,646 --> 00:56:40,521
For Nairobi.

794
00:56:42,771 --> 00:56:44,896
For Nairobi.

795
00:56:45,854 --> 00:56:47,229
For Nairobi.

796
00:56:48,229 --> 00:56:49,271
For Nairobi.

797
00:56:51,604 --> 00:56:53,479
For Nairobi!

798
00:56:54,104 --> 00:57:08,521
For Nairobi!

799
00:57:13,146 --> 00:57:15,354
For Nairobi!

800
00:57:19,521 --> 00:57:20,437
Don't move.

801
00:57:51,854 --> 00:57:53,604
Checkmate, son of a bitch.

