How do I look?
Powerful.
Beautiful.
Martín...
you've been going around...
for years and years...
carrying that thing inside you.
I think it's about time you took it out.
I can take out some wine if you like. Hmm?
- Shall we have some?
- No.
No, I'm not gonna drink
that wine with you.
I'm going out for dinner with Tatiana.
- Yeah.
- You'll think about me...
but...
I'm won't think about you.
You don't have to say another word.
I get it.
Come on!
You think I don't love you? I feel it too.
There's something between us, something...
extraordinary, unique, marvelous.
I know about love.
I've been married five times.
- Well...
- What I've never told you is that...
none of these women
ever made me feel something remotely...
similar to what I feel with you.
Not even close.
You and I are soul mates.
But just 99 percent. Hmm?
You know,
I really like women. I like them a lot.
And you like me too much.
And what's that one percent against 99?
Unless you're not brave enough to try it.
That one percent is a tiny mitochondrion,
but it defines my desire.
Mitochondrion.
Where is the desire?
Hey?
Here?
Where?
Don't worry.
Relax.
Don't be afraid.
Are you a coward, huh?
Where is it?
Huh?
Martín...
Listen... Hmm.
I'd give anything
so I could feel this, but...
it's impossible.
It's impossible.
I love you, Martín.
But my brother's right.
We have to part ways.
Mm?
And we have to give up the plan.
It was that son of a bitch,
your brother,
who didn't understand my love for you
and tore us apart.
You're gonna make photocopies
in that fucking mint.
I offered to melt gold with you.
You're hanging onto something
that doesn't exist and never will!
I have to leave you. It's...
because of love.
And also for our friendship.
For the bond I have with you.
Now go away...
so you can heal your wound.
Sometimes distance
is the only way to find peace.
Adiós, my friend.
I'm confident that,
one way or another,
time will bring us back together.
Alicia Sierra walked towards
the slaughterhouse,
and nobody noticed
the mysterious smile on her face.
That smile...
wasn't the look
of someone about to give up.
Is it true that you used the daughter
of Ágata Jiménez, alias Nairobi,
to make her approach the window
and then shoot her?
- Did she die from the shot?
- That is absolutely false.
It wasn't her daughter. It was her son.
Nine years old.
And yes, I used him.
My superiors knew about it
and authorized it, of course.
- What are you doing, Alicia?
- We shot her in the chest.
Then they asked for a doctor,
and I didn't send one in.
Antoñanzas, turn up the volume!
Her friends saved her,
but that didn't matter.
She was executed by the chief of security
for the Bank of Spain,
Gandía, with the full support
of Colonel Tamayo.
- Alicia, you fucking bitch!
- That's it.
Next question.
Is it also true that this guy Osman,
I don't know if you know him,
that he buried Cortés alive?
Yes, we buried him alive.
In Timimoun...
Tamayo's world
was falling to pieces.
And of course I know Osman.
He's a professional.
He's able to bury people alive...
and make them shiver like dogs
without killing them.
They were being eviscerated
in the eyes of the public,
and he was unaware of something worse.
In the bank,
his biggest hope was lying unconscious...
Palermo.
- How is he doing?
- We're operating.
...on a stretcher,
shards in his back.
You have to save his life.
Drugs? We gave him drugs.
Inhaled, to be precise.
Then we hung him up,
threw buckets of cold water at him,
and he shit himself.
Everything the kid said
is absolutely, completely true.
And, since I'm being honest,
there's a bunch of other stuff
I think he forgot about.
And was the Government aware of this?
Aware?
The Government gave the orders.
It's not like
I just got up one morning and said,
"I'm gonna torture this kid."
I had everyone's approval.
The National Intelligence Agency,
chief of police
and Ministry of the Interior. All of them!
Absolutely all of them knew about it.
And now all of you know too.
Thank you so much.
Alicia Sierra,
negotiator for the Bank of Spain case,
has been fired, and she's taken
other people down with her.
Sierra confesses to the torture but also
confirms Government participation.
Her superiors gave the order,
meaning everyone knew about it.
We have to bury that fucking bitch.
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Stoned soul ♪
♪ Making you rock ♪
♪ Making you roll... ♪
While everyone in Spain
was glued to the TV,
in a former Chinese restaurant
in the center of Madrid,
Benjamín and his team...
were getting ready to make a mess.
- Marseille?
- Arriving at the extraction point.
Received.
♪ You've got a feeling ♪
♪ You've got a feeling... ♪
One, two, three.
Whoa!
♪ You've got a feeling ♪
♪ Stoned soul ♪
♪ You've got a feeling
A feeling... ♪
How many meters?
♪ Stoned soul! ♪
Four meters.
We need to pick up the pace.
Lisbon will be guarded by 26 officers,
distributed between seven vehicles.
Three behind,
and three in front.
And in the center, the van she'll be in.
They'll go to the Supreme Court first.
From there, they'll take her to prison.
Tell me
where is the most vulnerable point?
On the road between point A and point B.
- No.
- In the Supreme Court with the judge?
No.
Don't tell me we gonna make
a hole in prison?
No, but there is one place
that is vulnerable.
In fact, we've all seen it before.
On TV.
When the doors of the Supreme Court
are crowded with journalists,
what are the cops going to do?
They will take the prisoner...
through the parking garage.
Only the van goes in there.
In 30 seconds, the armed convoy
goes from having 26 officers
to six, and from seven vehicles...
to one.
POLICE
And a parking garage is not a bunker
or a prison with lots of security.
- A garage is...
- For parking.
Exactly.
From the Supreme Court's
garage
to our Chinese restaurant's basement,
there's exactly...
eleven meters
and 68 centimeters of sandstone.
Sandstone. You guys are Asturian miners.
The best ones.
- What's that for you?
- Nothing. Pick, shovel and grinder.
♪ We're the kings of adrenaline... ♪
Minimum noise,
maximum efficiency.
Ten hours
to get everything ready, Benjamín.
And the extraction?
Industrial machinery, but silent.
♪ We're the kings of adrenaline... ♪
We'll take all the rubble to the kitchen.
It'll be quick and clean.
♪ We're the kings of adrenaline... ♪
Benjamín?
Five meters.
♪ The kings of adrenaline ♪
Palermo.
I hear you, Professor.
Palermo, how is he?
He's conscious.
What's his physical condition?
One of his arms is completely immobilized.
He's lost a lot of blood.
He's breathing like a fucked up stuck pig.
Is he going to recover?
If I was his mother,
I'd be lighting candles for him, sir.
He'll recover. Don't you worry
I'm gonna take care of it personally,
even if I have to get him to a hospital
and sit next to him for six months.
I'll make sure you recover.
I'll spoon-feed you soup.
I'll take good care of you.
And when you're strong like a bull,
know what's gonna happen?
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill you with my bare hands.
What's going on? Why the fuck
are we saving this motherfucker's life?
- Can he talk?
- He's refuses to talk.
My name's Stockholm. Do you remember me?
Let go of me, you fucking bitch.
Fuck you. Let go!
Professor, he can talk.
He killed Nairobi.
What the fuck are we doing right now?
We have to kill him!
That's up to him, Rio.
If he wants to live,
he'll live.
But if he wants to die,
he's going to die.
Why is it up to him?
You've no right to say that
because you have no idea
what it feels like in here.
You don't know what it feels like
to look him in the eyes.
Tokyo...
Don't talk to me like you're my father.
Do you have any idea how I feel?
Do you have any idea how Helsinki feels?
Helsinki...
was sewing him up.
He's treating him.
Do you know who Helsinki treated before?
No!
No, you don't know.
Of course, you don't know.
You don't know anything because you sit
in a hole, hidden like a rat.
That's why they killed Nairobi,
and you're giving orders
without shedding a tear
because you don't feel anything!
- Tokyo...
- Because you don't feel anything!
You don't feel anything!
- You don't feel anything!
- Stop! Stop!
- No! Nothing!
- Stop!
Do you want to spoon-feed him soup too?
Look, Tokyo, if I could,
I'd impale him with a fucking hot iron.
I'd take him down to the foundry.
I'd shove his head
inside the fucking furnace.
You think what happened to Nairobi
doesn't hurt?
That it doesn't hurt the Professor?
It doesn't seem like it.
Gandía's a prisoner,
and we don't kill prisoners.
No matter how fucking hard it is,
we don't kill prisoners.
And we're not cold-blooded killers, Tokyo.
But he is!
He fucking killed Nairobi! She was sick,
unarmed. She'd surrendered!
We had a truce, for fuck's sake!
Now we have to save our own lives,
like we did with you.
And that involves collateral damage,
including dealing with the pain.
We are running out of time.
They've broken the truce,
and we have to turn this situation around.
Helsinki!
Helsinki, no!
- No!
- Why the fuck
would you kill her, you motherfucker?
Why would you kill her,
motherfucker?
- Palermo!
- Helsinki, look me in the eyes.
Fatty, look me in the eyes. Come on!
Helsinki!
My brother.
Rio, Denver, back to work.
Go.
Palermo?
He's alive, sir.
You son of a bitch.
You're having one, right?
You're having a panic attack.
There was too much tension in there.
It'll pass.
Here.
I know I'm fucked, Commissioner.
You don't need to remind me.
Hmm.
I just want to know what happened.
- Call them.
- I've been a negotiator for 15 years,
and I know
when someone has accepted a deal.
You call them.
In 24 hours, you'll all be together.
We'll never come after you.
She was up against the ropes.
She was gonna betray the Professor.
I'd broken her. She was about to give up.
Then something happened.
But what could happen
when someone's incommunicado?
Or maybe she wasn't so incommunicado.
Antoñanzas, you stay and watch Murillo.
Don't let anyone in.
Antoñanzas.
What do you think?
Commissioner?
Should we go after Antoñanzas?
Clever kitty.
Well, to be honest,
it's more like a vacation.
Commissioner,
I'll come back for you.
The official magistrate of Madrid
has initiated proceedings
against Alicia Sierra
and put out an order for her arrest.
The police negotiator, who was seeking
the arrest of the Dalís,
is to be arrested first.
She's being prosecuted for the crime
of illegal detention, for torture,
and for the attempted murder
of Ágata Jiménez, alias Nairobi.
That's not all. The minister, the director
of the CNI and their police chiefs
are preparing libel, slander
and defamation of character claims
against the inspector.
We've confirmed it, Colonel.
The ministry has ordered her arrest.
Go get her!
I'm sorry.
I'm personally responsible
for all this shit.
I didn't realize the amount of pain
I'd cause, and I'm very sorry.
What do you know about pain, Palermo?
Pain is like a loan.
And no matter what you do,
you can never pay back the debt.
I can handle pain.
Lots of pain.
Oh, yeah?
Even the pain you're feeling right now?
This one's different, right?
I saw it in your eyes.
I saw it, and it reminds me of myself.
You have no idea...
where the pain will take you, my friend.
Get out of it while you can.
Otherwise, you could end up
becoming a piece of shit like me.
A miserable monster.
A guy who ruins everything he touches.
Someone who flirted with death for years.
Once you're there, you can't get out.
You can never get out.
Look, brother...
because of all that bullshit
boom, boom, ciao,
I treated you like trash.
I wasn't brave. I couldn't be.
I didn't have the strength.
But I'm telling you, I'm here with you.
You're not alone.
I know.
I've known that from the beginning.
I know who you are.
My name is Martín Berrote.
I was born in Buenos Aires,
but I live in Palermo, Sicily.
And I am going
to get you out of here alive,
even if I have to give my own life.
My name is Mirko Dragic.
I'm from Belgrade.
I lost Oslo at the Royal Mint of Spain,
and I lost Nairobi.
And I'm not gonna lose anyone else.
Not even you, Martín Berrote.
NATIONAL COURT
09:34 HOURS
Lisbon is going to testify
in the Supreme Court.
She'll earn the judge's trust,
giving them information,
cooperating and being reliable.
She'll give every little detail
about the heist because all of this...
is part of plan Paris.
What is plan Paris?
A rescue plan
in case one of us gets caught.
And why Paris?
Well, it's...
It's the city of freedom.
Mm.
And of love.
Who hasn't walked around Paris in love?
Right, boys?
What will Lisbon tell the judge?
The truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
And in fact, she'll start with love.
How did you reconnect after
the first heist with Sergio Marquina?
How was it arranged?
I met the Professor
one year after they escaped
in Palawan, Philippines.
He left a puzzle with coordinates.
He doesn't look like it,
but he's a romantic.
She'll tell them everything.
Everything! Where we live, how often we've
had to move, how we move.
After about an hour, an hour and a half,
she'll start to tell them the plan.
The plan?
- She can't tell them.
- She can.
Truth is the basis of any relationship,
and that's how she'll earn it.
The plan is to steal 90 tons of gold
from the national reserve,
and what we're doing now is melting it.
You're melting the gold in the bank?
As of now, they've melted about 50 tons.
We're using industrial furnaces
made by a company called Harmand.
Harmand.
German. They're the best.
Benjamín, how are we doing?
Seven and a half meters!
We need to go faster.
Go faster! Go faster!
We'll give them every single detail.
They reach 2,300 degrees.
- Gold melts at 1,064.
- We'll overwhelm them
with so many technicalities
that their poor brains
won't be able to process
that much information.
We knew that the vault would flood
with a water flow
of 7,500 liters per minute.
That information is very detailed.
And we're doing it so...
- they get tired?
- Exactly.
The biggest challenge
was the interconnection chamber.
Could I have a pen and paper?
Let's get you tired first.
- Meters?
- Nine meters!
Go faster.
The door to the vault,
fourteen tons of steel,
we had to drill through it in just a few
minutes. A perfect circle with a radius...
The bathyscaphe floods...
That's how the divers...
We weld the interconnection chamber...
There's a balance in pressure...
To compensate...
Twenty three hundred degrees Celsius...
And it comes out the other side.
Can we get some dinner in here, please?
They say pregnant women
have a sharper sense of smell.
The Professor hadn't anticipated
Sierra would have that superpower.
It was the first time
someone was tracking his scent
without him realizing it.
Antoñanzas's wife
hadn't seen the news yet.
- Marisa?
- Sierra got all the information
she needed in under three minutes.
I work with Benito.
I don't know if you know me.
I know you.
Okay, how do I say this?
I've just been feeling
like Benito hasn't...
been himself these days...
Antoñanzas was acting nervous at home,
and then he was found in the pool
with two friends
in the middle of the night.
And to top it off,
he was wasted.
Colonel, it looks like Alicia Sierra
isn't home. We can't find her.
Fucking bitch!
Attention, all units. Orders are out for
the search and capture of Alicia Sierra.
It doesn't matter who you are.
I can't give you the videos.
I need authorization from a judge,
or at least the president
of the community.
Wait, wait a second. Someone's calling me.
Look at that.
The president of the community.
How are you doing, Mr. President?
That's great. Thank you so much.
He says yes.
He says give me the tapes,
the ones from the entrance,
the pool, parking lot, street.
Do it.
Listen, Amanda.
Shit. What you said earlier...
All those fake,
unfounded accusations about me, you know?
I don't wanna hear you.
I don't want you near me.
- Come on...
- Didn't you hear her?
Leave her alone, Mr. Arturo.
Don't force me to take you out
because I will.
What are you doing?
Everyone, shut up now!
Listen, you scumbag.
- You disgust me.
- You're calling me a scumbag?
You?
A banker.
A puppet of the system and capitalism.
You're gonna try and talk to me
about ethics?
You didn't even have enough balls
to stand up for your employees. Scumbag!
I said shut up now!
On the ground!
Hands where I can see them,
behind your head!
Come on! What are you gonna do?
You get over there!
Come on. Everyone up.
I'm gonna get you all out of here,
I promise.
Everyone!
See, that's the difference
between you and me, Governor.
I came here to save all these people.
To be a hero!
In the meantime, you can just stay
over there and piss your pants in fear,
- Mr. Governor.
- Arturo!
You're gonna put that G36 on the floor
in approximately three seconds
because If you don't, you're a dead man.
Who do you think are you,
if you don't mind me asking.
Manila. Undercover agent for the gang.
Well, listen, Manila.
I don't believe that bullshit.
Besides, that gun's fake,
like the ones they gave us before.
You're not fooling me.
You have two seconds left.
Put the gun on the floor
and pray it's not true you raped Amanda.
You're really getting on my nerves, honey.
I'm almost running out of patience.
One!
I didn't rape her!
I only gave her some pills
for the anxiety.
I'm bleeding to death!
I'm gonna die!
You're not gonna die.
It's just a surface wound.
It didn't hit any arteries,
or anything important.
Arturo, consider yourself under arrest,
accused of rape.
And...
I just remembered.
You offered me some pills too, didn't you?
You piece of shit.
In the bank,
no one slept that night.
In the meantime, outside,
our biggest enemy was wide awake.
First, Sierra saw Antoñanzas fly
then crash into the diving board.
A few seconds later,
the Professor and Marseille appeared.
It was 3:11 in the morning.
Minutes later,
she had their license plate.
Hey. What's up, sweetheart?
Uh, for fuck's sake, Alicia.
What the fuck?
Relax.
I have a license plate
from a car that drove on the M-30
at three in the morning on April 7th.
I need to know where it went.
Alicia, the police are after you.
I can't do it. It's too risky.
How many times
have I taken risks for you, Raúl?
Do you remember last time?
Cut the bullshit.
Meters?
Nine and a half!
Lisbon's mission...
is to give us the time that we will need.
Look...
An average person can concentrate
for about 50 minutes.
But no matter how important
the information is,
there always comes a point
when the brain gets too exhausted.
And all that's left to do
is come back the next day.
Do you know the only way
to cut metal underwater?
Have you ever heard about
underwater welding?
Because down there,
we cut metal with fire.
Fire? Underwater?
- Benjamín, how are we doing?
- Ten meters!
We need to go faster!
Go faster! Go faster!
Again, fire underwater
to get to the State secrets,
which are key for negotiation,
but it didn't work out.
- So we had to use the dolphin.
- Wait. A dolphin?
Ten and a half.
Flipper is the code name we assigned
to the governor of the Bank of Spain.
It was the fastest way of getting
hold of the secrets for negotiation.
That's an offense of coercion.
- I know.
- And it's also a disclosure of secrets.
We sent all the secrets
to an external server.
If I could get the pencil again,
I'll draw a diagram
of how the computer structure works.
It's almost one in the morning.
Maybe a recess would be a good idea,
if the prosecution
and the defense are in favor of it.
She'll go back to jail,
and we'll keep on digging...
and digging and digging.
And between 4:00 and 4:30 in the morning,
we're going to reach the end
of the 11 meters and 68 centimeters
of our tunnel,
which means that we're finally...
getting to the parking garage.
- Questions?
- How do we enter parking
without being seen?
Good! Good!
A good question. A very good question.
In two stages. First: Pakistan.
- Pakistan.
- That's right. And you'll give the order.
The mole's out for a walk.
Shakir.
- Shakir, now.
- Perfect, Professor.
The guys from Pakistan
will switch the video signal
of the internal security's computers,
and from then on, the guards
will only be watching a recording.
Stage two:
Marseille.
Marseille will be at the very peak
of his partying
when all the bars in Madrid have closed,
but...
he'll certainly want to keep dancing
with his new girl,
Sheila.
Marseille.
On the line.
- Benjamín?
- I'm listening.
That will provide us
with the acoustic cover we need
so they don't hear the grinders.
Stopwatches.
Three... two... one.
Now.
Good evening.
Is there a problem?
What the fuck are you doing?
A party!
They've closed all the bars,
so we're having a little party
here in my car, sir.
Marseille, keep stalling.
Keep stalling, Marseille.
One minute!
So what kind of party are you two having
with alcohol-free beer?
It's just I wanna make love tonight,
and with alcohol, ooh...
And no alcohol, hmm!
Turn off the music.
Benjamín!
Thirty seconds!
Don't turn it off, Marseille.
- What?
- Turn off the music.
Twenty seconds!
- Turn off the music!
- Keep stalling. Keep stalling.
- Get out.
- Hold on.
Ten!
- Get out of the car.
- Five!
The rabbit hole is open.
We're inside.
Okay! Okay! Okay, okay, okay!
Get out of here.
We are inside.
Benjamín...
stage three.
Roger.
Tell me.
M-607.
The trail dies on the security camera
at kilometer 29,
the exit to Colmenar Viejo.
Eight in the morning
on the second day...
we begin the final stage.
At 8 a.m., Lisbon will depart
from Soto del Real prison,
and she'll be transferred
by the same convoy as the day before.
Lisbon just left the prison.
Get ready.
Tokyo,
prepare Gandía.
At 8:35,
he'll arrive at the Supreme Court,
and the entrance
will still be filled with journalists,
so they'll have to repeat
the same procedure.
They'll get in through the parking garage.
But this time, there's a difference.
You guys will already be there,
but no one will be able to see you
because what you'll be doing overnight...
is constructing an entire fake wall.
Oh, my God! That's crazy.
After you open the hole,
you'll have three hours to build the wall
before the first employees
at the Supreme Court
arrive at seven in the morning.
Okay. So the wall
has to be small enough
so that no one realizes it's there,
but big enough
so five of you can hide behind it.
Perfect.
And now comes
the David Copperfield moment.
How do we extract
a person coming out of a van
escorted by six vehicles
and surrounded by police officers
without...
anyone...
realizing?
Life has to follow its course
after we do it...
as if nothing had ever happened.
We're going to have to move the next piece
on the board for that,
and this piece is fundamental.
Your moment has arrived.
Now you get to choose your own fate.
Life... or death?
We reconnected your little toys,
so you're gonna call the tent,
you'll talk to Tamayo,
and you'll tell him you murdered Nairobi.
You fucking son of a bitch.
And that you've killed me too.
Also we still haven't found
the panic room, but we're just about to.
That you're going out,
and you've got a radio.
What's wrong?
Do I still make you horny, like when
I stuck the grenade shard in you?
Let's go.
This is the command center.
This is César Gandía,
chief of security
for the governor of the Bank of Spain.
They've caught me. They're trying
to use me so they can trick you.
It's a trap!
Gandía...
it's the Professor.
We knew perfectly well you would do this,
but remember, this was
your only opportunity to get it wrong.
The next call is directly to Tamayo,
- and if you make the same mistake...
- Think about your son Juanito.
...Tokyo will execute you.
You heard that, Tokyo?
- Loud and clear.
- Listen to me, Tokyo.
You'll hang up...
and you'll kill him.
So I want you to understand
one thing, Gandía.
You can't win anymore.
You've already lost. Do you understand?
The only heroic thing you can do
is see your wife and son again.
Otherwise, they'll lose you.
They'll lose you.
Understood, Tokyo?
Let's go.
Suarez.
Martínez!
Colonel!
We have Gandía.
Gandía, talk to me.
Colonel, I'm in the panic room.
They're about to discover it.
I've eliminated Nairobi and Tokyo.
I'm going on another attack.
I'll take a radio.
I'll give you the frequency.
Suarez, I want all units ready to go.
Units alpha and beta, get in position.
I want everyone on alert.
462.662.
Time to go.
If we can't kidnap Lisbon when
she gets there, what should we do?
Wait in the wall
until she's done testifying?
This time Lisbon won't take more
than 20 minutes
to get back to the parking garage.
They'll object. Of course they'll object,
but she'll be within her rights.
I've decided against testifying.
Mrs. Murillo,
you incriminated yourself yesterday.
I advise you to still cooperate.
There could be benefits for you doing so.
So the judge will be forced to give
an early sentence and send her to prison,
and the same men who brought her in
will return to the parking garage
with her.
But this time, no one will be watching
because the security guards
will be looking at the recording
from the previous night.
They'll watch Lisbon's first arrival,
and then...
they'll cross paths with...
a judge...
a prosecutor...
a police officer...
and two lawyers.
Okay, maybe it's better
if you're a prisoner.
Benjamín.
- Everyone ready?
- We're prepared.
Now.
- Benjamín.
- I see her.
Twenty-five meters.
Ten meters.
The signal will be...
"Good morning."
Three meters.
Good morning.
Good morning, Ms. Lisbon.
Hi.
Let's go.
We're going to complicate their lives
a bit because in 45 seconds
we'll make them wear belts
with explosives around their chests.
In 55, we'll have two cameras
and two microphones monitor them
so that...
if they decide to change the route...
Boom!
If they give
even the slightest sign of alarm...
Boom!
If you don't bring the prisoner
to the prison...
Boom!
Wait, we're the ones
taking the prisoner, no?
We're going to give them another Lisbon.
Convoy unit.
Everything okay down there?
You're taking too long.
Yeah, yeah. Everything's fine.
- We're on our way.
- Okay, okay. Got it.
And that...
is when our greatest illusion begins.
Our David Copperfield moment.
- Who's this guy Copperfield?
- The magician.
Magician? Like Harry Potter?
It'll look like everything's the same.
But it won't be.
Because at that moment,
Lisbon will be crawling at full speed
through the tunnel we dug.
Come on.
Here we go.
Tokyo...
Lisbon's on her way.
Start the countdown... now.
Start running!
Colonel, they opened fire!
Gandía!
- Gandía, respond!
- "I'm here."
I'm here!
- "They're closing in on me."
- They're closing in on me, sir.
- I'm caught in the fucking cross fire!
- Very good.
Going up.
What's your position?
Can we give covering fire?
"Negative."
Negative, Colonel.
- "Heading to the roof."
- Heading to the roof, sir.
- "Requesting immediate evac."
- Requesting immediate evac!
Suarez, for Christ's sake,
send a fucking helicopter now.
- Let's go!
- Delta 1, get ready for takeoff.
Rescue operation
at the Bank of Spain now.
Hang in there, Gandía.
I have an M16 and three cartridges.
I don't know how much longer I can last!
Fire. Now.
- "They've started a fire."
- They've started a fire.
I can't see anything!
Colonel. Colonel!
Smoke's coming through the roof.
Hang on there, Gandía.
The helicopter's on its way.
- Lisbon.
- Marseille.
Marseille.
Professor, we have Lisbon.
Blue ammo clips.
Let's go!
How are we gonna get
the military helicopter?
The same place
we got the vehicles we used
to get into the bank: the black market.
And not just that, we're going
to intercept their communications
so that when they wanna talk
to their own chopper,
we're the ones that are going to answer.
Where is that helicopter?
Delta unit, position.
Time?
Two minutes, fifty seconds.
Two minutes, fifty seconds, sir.
Get up to the roof. We'll cover you.
Impossible!
There's plastic explosive on the door.
- Fuck! Where's the bomb expert?
- We need a bomb expert!
Gandía, describe the device.
"Blue wire to the starter."
There's a motion sensor,
a blue wire, to the starter.
Cut it. That's a basic bomb device.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- No!
- Cut it.
No, Colonel. Colonel!
"I've cut the wire."
I've cut the wire.
Denver, now.
- Go, go, go!
- "I'm wearing black. Hold your fire."
I'm exiting now.
I have a mask and I'm dressed in black.
Hold your fire!
Our man's dressed in black.
Give him cover.
- Be ready for cross fire.
- Roger.
Blue ammo clips.
Now!
Go, go, go, go!
They're on the roof.
They've opened fire!
We need cover fire!
I can't see them.
There's too much smoke.
- Tokyo, now.
- Palermo...
Open it.
- Searching for target.
- Got a visual.
I can see them!
I repeat, I've got a visual.
Permission to fire, sir.
- Don't shoot!
- Those motherfuckers.
We're exposed.
- They're completely exposed!
- Taking cover!
We're taking cover, sir.
Delta unit, begin approaching our target.
Rescue protocol.
I want the extraction
to be quick and clean.
Marseille.
Arriving. Helicopter in position, sir.
Get them out of there, for fuck's sake!
Okay, Delta 1. Get in there.
- Permission to descend, sir!
- Go ahead.
Fall back to the helicopter now!
Lisbon!
Denver!
Welcome to the Bank of Spain!
Son a bitch!
Package delivered, Professor.
I'm out in two minutes.
Where is the helicopter going?
Delta 1, what happened?
Delta 1, return to your position!
- Delta 1, come in!
- Goddamn it!
There's a problem with the helicopter.
We're going in!
Where did that agent come from?
She's insane!
Colonel, they're pulling back!
Are you okay?
Yes?
What?
They're calling from Soto del Real.
It's the convoy that transferred Murillo.
Colonel Tamayo? There's a woman
claiming she was kidnapped
on her way out of the salon.
What do I care, idiot?
This is the command center for the heist!
Take it, you moron.
Gandía, hang in there!
Hold down the stairs
until the helicopter gets back.
Suarez, where's the fucking helicopter?
Colonel...
- What?
- Colonel.
It looks like we've been... mislead.
Yes!
Come on!
Yeah!
Professor,
Lisbon's here.
I repeat, Lisbon... We've got Lisbon!
Listen to me.
This war...
we're going to win it.
For Nairobi.
For Nairobi.
For Nairobi!
For Nairobi! For Nairobi!
Don't move.
Checkmate, you son of a bitch.
♪ Goodbye my beautiful
Goodbye my beautiful. Bye, bye ♪
♪ One morning I awakened ♪
♪ And I found the invader
Goodbye my beautiful ♪
♪ Oh, partisan
♪ Carry me away
Goodbye my beautiful ♪
♪ Goodbye my beautiful
Goodbye my beautiful. Bye, bye ♪
♪ Oh, partisan
Goodbye my beautiful ♪
♪ Carry me away
♪ Because I feel death approaching ♪
♪ And if I die ♪
♪ As a partisan ♪
♪ Goodbye my beautiful
Goodbye my beautiful. Bye, bye ♪
♪ And if I die ♪
♪ On the mountain ♪
♪ Then you must bury me ♪
♪ Bury me up in the mountain ♪