- Papa?
- Yeah, I'm gonna talk to him.
- You promise?
- Of course.
- We'll do it soon.
- Okay.
Papa! Papa, he's coming.
- He's coming.
- Calm down.
- There he is.
- I'll ask him.
Professor...
Professor, would you like a little...
a little coffee, huh?
Well, yes, that'd be great. Thank you.
Good morning.
Here's your coffee.
Want some cookies, Professor?
Okay, um...
Thank you.
You have something to ask me?
Mm... Um...
Uh...
- One little thing.
- Yeah, uh...
A really quick question.
Do you have a brother?
Please. No personal questions.
It's one of the first rules, so please...
So, I have a buddy.
He's... He's like a brother.
We were in the mine together,
stole together, in jail together.
And that's the problem, because I'm out,
and he still has five years left.
- Five years, Professor.
- Yes, well, it's just that...
I'm sorry, but I don't know
what I can do for your...
for your friend or your brother, whoever.
No, it's his son.
- For his son?
- Yes, Juanito. He's my godson.
He's also like a brother to me.
I promised him
when I got out of jail to look after him.
And we haven't seen him in a long time,
and we've just heard he's not doing well.
He's out of work, almost homeless.
And I thought it'll give him
a fresh start... if we bring him here.
You think it's better
getting him involved with a heist?
This heist is incredible.
Just look at this kid.
I've never seen him
more focused in my life.
And if it works out, when there's food
for a hundred, there's food for one more.
- Moscow, I'm really sorry. It's...
- This guy is incredible.
No. It doesn't matter if he's amazing.
He's good at everything.
Why do you think
we call you Denver and you Moscow
and Helsinki? It's a matter safety.
No one's supposed to know the names
of the others in the heist. You can't...
Moscow, listen to me.
I already made an exception by bringing in
your son. And now your godson?
It's not a family business where we can
suddenly give your second cousin a job...
Wait. What the fuck
are you talking about, nerd?
- What?
- Hey, hey. Watch your language!
Hold on.
What we're talking about here is a guy
- who's almost homeless, Papa.
- Relax.
We're putting our lives on the line
for this jerk, and he repays us
with some shit about city names?
Professor, do you know what I'm gonna do
with the name Denver?
I'm gonna stick it up your ass
because my name is Dani.
I've been Dani my whole life.
I'll tell you another thing.
Your plan, your perfect plan
for the Royal Mint of Spain,
it's bullshit.
Real fucking bullshit.
There's a printer downstairs.
We can print the bills here
and it'll be a lot easier.
Thank you so much for the coffee.
This is the last time you speak
to that man like that. Understand me?
This is embarrassing for me.
He's an intellectual.
Well, we have to do something.
You have to trust this man.
You have to respect him.
- You don't think I respect him?
- No!
No, no, no. The thing is,
maybe the kid's onto something.
If we print the bills at home,
we'd avoid a lot of problems,
and we don't have to spend
any money on guns
or ammunition. Right?
Denver, you bring us the printer,
and we'll download bills
from the internet.
Nice work, maestro.
No, no, no.
Better yet...
I could draw the bills...
and you can color them.
We could manage two a day.
Hm? After all,
I pride myself on my artistry.
I call it
Passion for Juanito.
Are you gonna keep busting my balls?
Because maybe I could
bust your fucking face in,
and then we could print some new teeth
for you. You're so funny!
Everyone, go fuck yourselves.
Denver, don't get mad. It's a joke.
I woke up as a prisoner
of one of our prisoners.
Chained,
disoriented, with a madman in front of me.
I'd lost my freedom,
and the clock was ticking.
Only 15 minutes after I opened my eyes,
Gandía would've already attacked
most of the gang.
What are you doing? Hm?
- If you weren't tied up, I'd break you.
- Let me go.
Then we'll see who breaks who.
Why didn't you kill me?
I am not a murderer.
You're not a murderer?
You tried to kill Nairobi and Helsinki,
and you're not a murderer?
So why didn't you kill me?
You're my chained beast.
And you?
What the fuck are you?
I'm the tamer.
And you're in luck.
I'm turning you domesticated.
The next time you kick me,
I'll beat the shit out of you so hard
that nobody in your gang
will ever recognize you.
Stay still.
You will stay still.
Listen to me. I'm gonna explain.
It's very easy.
Motherfucker.
Ssh. Look.
My first card is you.
Missing.
They have no choice but to look for you.
And the search will drive them mad.
Divided and nervous.
I'm already winning.
The next card...
Shatter your team.
Didn't you wonder how I escaped?
This is Gandía,
chief of security for the Bank of Spain.
At the moment, I'm hidden.
I'm safe, and I'm capable
of taking whatever action
is necessary to recover
- full control and security...
- He wants to kill all of us!
Stay together. He's watching you!
As you've just heard,
I'm with marvelous company.
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
You'd better start behaving
because if you don't,
you'll be completely immobilized.
Tied up with a gag in your mouth,
a blindfold over your eyes.
And then we won't be able
to continue getting to know each other.
Get it?
Good.
I'd like to take this moment
to give my thanks to Palermo.
His advice
on how to escape from my handcuffs
by dislocating my thumb
is what made me a free man.
Thanks to him,
I hope to be able to help all of you.
Well, this will be fun.
Is that true?
If you prefer believing a psychopath
before a colleague, okay.
That's your decision.
Save your breath, you motherfucker.
- Mr. Denver, I need to use the bathroom.
- It's not a good time.
What I'm telling you is...
Is that I have a really bad stomach ache.
I need to go to the bathroom urgently.
What's wrong?
The museum is big.
And 60, 70 hostages
are difficult to control.
Those numbers could spark a rebellion.
No.
That would be suicide,
and under those circumstances,
what prevails
is the instinct to stay safe.
No.
Fear.
Fear and more fear
will allow them to make poor decisions,
like desperately attacking one of us
even if we're carrying M16s.
- What are you thinking?
- Infiltrate someone.
They wouldn't have any direct contact with
us except in case a rebellion breaks out.
And if there aren't any problems,
they'll leave like the other hostages.
It‘s a job that even a smoking monkey
from Ringling Brothers could do.
Maybe even that Juanito guy could do it.
That's it.
Is that him?
- No.
- Well, that was his bus.
- Yeah.
- This isn't good. We're leaving.
- No, Professor. Maybe he got confused.
Sure.
Or maybe he got out at a different stop.
Or maybe he fell asleep,
and he's still on the bus.
Godfather.
Jesus.
It's me.
Juanito?
Julia.
It's been a long time, no?
You look very beautiful, Julia.
Well...
you were always handsome. Pretty.
Those eyes,
that mouth, that smile.
You're very beautiful, Julia.
Everything okay, Daniel?
You look freaked out.
No, I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
I-I-I think it's really fucking great.
I mean, you know, everyone is free to do
whatever they want
and when they want it.
Well, then.
Well, it's just that I look in your eyes,
and you're still Juanito, but...
you're beautiful!
Come here. Give me a hug.
Okay.
Hey, does your father know?
'Cause I saw him a year ago,
and he said nothing.
My father's so supportive.
He always said he wanted a daughter,
so this worked out.
And who's this?
The boy with the plan, no?
The boy with the plan, yes.
And what are we doing for this heist?
Gandía's telling the truth. Palermo
helped him escape from his handcuffs.
- How do you know?
- I saw him gesturing to his thumb.
They were talking. Palermo kept going
over to him the entire day.
- You didn't say anything?
- Because I couldn't hear them,
and I didn't know he'd tell him
to break his finger.
Then move closer! That's why you're here.
No, no, no, no. I'm here to keep an eye
on the hostages, not on the gang.
Uh...
You hear so much shit in here.
- Yeah, I know.
- Hm.
How's Nairobi?
Well, she's still recovering
as best as she can.
And Tokyo was abducted. Two down.
Hmm. Things are starting
to get a little fucked up, no?
Julia.
What do you want?
I want you to let me go, give me a weapon,
and let me join the others
'cause my ass is constantly asleep
from sitting on it...
They have think you're a hostage
in case things get more fucked up.
- More? It's gonna get worse?
- Quit fucking around and sit back down.
Jesus! Even Matías has a gun.
It's bigger than him.
He doesn't know how to hold it.
No, no. Just listen to me.
Orders are orders.
What you have to do
is go back to your place.
And the orders are given by you
because you're in charge here.
- Me? What do you mean I'm in charge?
- Of course you're in charge!
Nairobi's been shot.
Tokyo's been taken. Palermo...
Well, nobody could ever trust Palermo.
Do the math, Dani. You're next.
You're in charge.
You're really starting to piss me off.
So start giving orders.
It's easy. Give me a gun,
a vest and all the gear you have.
And...
start calling me Manila
because I'm Manila, Dani.
No, you're not Manila
because you're still a hostage.
And don't call me Dani. My name is Denver.
We're gonna go.
And I'll tell you something else.
Don't stare at me that way
because people are starting to notice.
Stare at you?
I was sending you signals,
you fucking moron.
Stare at you!
Oh, fuck.
It feels like a fucking sauna.
Turn on the air-conditioning.
If I turn it on,
they'll know where we are.
- That would be a shame.
- It would.
We have so much to talk about.
Without the AC, there's not much oxygen,
so I suggest you ration your breathing.
Don't worry about me.
The people out there broke into
the vaults of the national reserve.
You think they won't find a way
into this bunker?
You're a dead man.
You're sweating.
May I open your jumpsuit?
We can't afford poor hygiene here.
Touch me and I'll rip your arm off,
motherfucker.
Oh, yeah?
What happened to that kid up there?
The one with the curly hair.
He's not making you horny?
Like an animal.
I really doubt that.
You're not into IT guys or kids.
I set up this heist for him.
What's the most
someone's ever done for you?
Give you a drill on Father's Day?
You're more into real men.
- Kinda like you?
- Mm-hmm. Like me.
That's right.
You've even stopped kicking me.
Because you've tied up my legs,
you fucking imbecile.
Well, whatever the reason,
the important thing is
you're much more receptive.
And you even painted your toes for me.
I love it.
Is it true you helped Gandía escape?
Yes, sir.
And are you aware that he almost killed
Nairobi and Helsinki?
- Collateral damage.
- Collateral damage?
- You are such a piece of shit.
- Relax.
Why did you do it, Palermo?
Tokyo staged a coup d'etát, sir.
I felt morally obligated...
to save the plan.
The plan is where my loyalty lies.
I had to restore the order
that was established because you never
relieved me in my position.
As a matter of fact, I did.
And that has absolutely nothing
to do with releasing Gandía.
Of course, it does.
I had to generate chaos.
It was obvious he would go after her.
He could kill her, you fuck up.
- I repeat, she stole my command from me.
- He's full of shit.
He was gonna abandon ship
like a rat,
- and he was taking the state secrets.
- The child is incorrect.
I stopped you at the door
with the briefcase.
You were gonna make a deal,
you fucker.
I was?
With the documents that I stole in my
briefcase? It's right there. Have a look.
Denver, open the briefcase.
What's inside?
Muffins.
I don't care what's in the briefcase.
It doesn't make any difference.
You have betrayed the gang.
You've put everyone in danger,
and it's your fault that Gandía has taken
my officer in command as his prisoner.
Listen. I'm going to give you...
one opportunity to redeem yourself.
But I won't forget what you've done.
And, you'll never have your command back.
Then I'll go back to the hostages.
What should I do?
First, you shut your mouth.
And no, don't go back to the hall.
Release him.
We have a murderer on the loose.
This is not the time to be divided.
When all this is over,
then we'll decide on a judgment.
Now, listen to me carefully.
Gandía is a lone wolf.
The most vulnerable place is the lobby,
so that's the first place
we have to evacuate.
Palermo, Stockholm, Helsinki,
gather the hostages together
in the library. Gandía doesn't want
to escape. He wants to kill you.
The door doesn't matter.
Don't wear your masks,
he could do the same
and we wouldn't
be able to distinguish him.
Bogotá, what's the situation
in the basement?
They've stopped the furnaces.
They're scared.
Bring Nairobi to safety in the library
and go to the basement.
We have to keep melting the gold.
Denver.
- Talk to me.
- You and Rio take action.
Let the hunt begin.
You'll be more exposed,
so equip the appropriate tools.
Helmets, ammunition, magazines.
Everything you might need.
Search every room on the first floor,
and when you've searched a room, seal it.
And the other floors?
Split them with Helsinki and Stockholm.
They'll join after the hostages
are in the library.
Everyone know what to do?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
One more thing.
Good luck.
- And be very careful.
- Let's go!
- How are you feeling, sweetheart?
- I'm okay.
I've got a real good nurse.
You like the big guy, huh?
We'll see.
Stay strong.
You too.
Whoo!
Holy shit!
That lady is so wasted, Helsinki!
You know what she said to me? She said,
"You've got yourself some piece of ass!"
She was talking about you.
- Everyone thinks we're married.
- It's better.
- We can go unnoticed.
- No, it's not better!
It's not better. This way neither of us
will get laid.
We don't need to get laid, Nairobi.
- Salud!
- Cheers.
It's fine for a day or two,
but if it goes on too long,
we might both grow our hymens back.
Truth is, me and you,
we make a great couple.
We're spectacular.
You and me...
family, and we'll be...
family forever.
You're damn right.
The things I've experienced with you
I've never experienced with anyone.
This, Helsi...
This is a love story.
Not just any love story,
but a perfect one.
No.
One day, you'll meet someone,
and that will be love.
But not this.
You have to be open and brave
because, believe me,
it takes much more courage
to be in love...
than it does for war.
And you...
you're courageous.
Put it on.
We're going to the basement.
We're going to the library.
Those are the orders.
Bogotá!
Don't fuck with me.
They're probably shitting themselves.
They won't last five minutes
against Gandía if they're that scared.
I need to talk to them.
How long since you ate?
Two days.
- Three.
- And since you slept?
I've probably slept two two-hour shifts
since I got here.
Do you wanna know anything else?
Before you eat,
I'm gonna disinfect that wound of yours.
Ssh. Quiet.
Your hair is stuck in it.
I hit you hard, huh?
- Library is clear.
- Copy that.
Everyone stand up
and make four lines, now!
My dear hostages...
I'm back.
As you know, there's a wolf on the loose,
and you're the lambs,
so we're going to kindly escort you
to your stable.
Our escorts for today
will be my colleagues and shepherds,
Helsinki and Stockholm.
Let's go, quickly! Let's go!
Everyone, follow me. Now!
You stay here with me, sir.
You're the best shield
I have against Gandía.
Keep moving. Quicker.
Here. This works miracles.
But isn't that too much?
Amanda, right?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Are you sure?
Well...
I'm a little dizzy.
It's probably just those pills I got
from Mr. Roman.
Hey, there. How's it goin'?
Fine.
I-I'm Arturo.
- Arturo Roman.
- Mmm-hm.
You looked real tense earlier.
When you insisted
on going to the bathroom, I was worried.
I'm just nervous.
It's not easy being in here.
With these terrorists,
it's not going to be a day in the park.
Take it from experience.
I was a little bit anxious.
I'm good. Thank you.
We're all stuck, so we have
to stay together and help each other.
Trust me.
Yeah.
If you start feeling
a little anxious again,
I've got something to make you feel great.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
What's that?
Some advice from a veteran. Ssh.
That's all the hostages.
We've brought you
to the library because,
as the old, well-known saying goes,
knowledge is power.
And in this case,
it might also save your lives.
In Search of Lost Time,
for example, by Marcel Proust.
Monumental. Beautiful novel.
I'm convinced
that whoever finds it
and presses it firmly against their chest
will be able to deflect the bullets
from an M16.
It's a joke.
I'm joking. Calm down.
We're going to be here for a few hours.
These are the rules of coexisting.
Number one...
Bogotá, Nairobi, where are you?
5:00 MINUTES EARLIER
Don't move!
Are you fucking idiots?
Put your guns down.
Are you afraid?
Come on, man.
There's a lunatic armed to the teeth.
I'm afraid too, you know.
- Bogotá, are you afraid?
- Maybe the most.
Palermo, Helsinki and Stockholm
are scared too.
They're taking the hostages
to the library.
Denver and Rio are practically
shitting themselves upstairs.
Because they're looking for Gandía.
And Gandía...
Gandía is the most afraid, so he's
won't stop until he kills us all.
Kill us, my ass.
"My ass."
Everyone else is doing their jobs,
and we're over here...
scared shitless...
hiding behind a little trench.
- We didn't come here for a fucking war.
- I know, honey.
We don't have any other choice.
This is the easiest place to defend.
You can only get in from over there,
and if he does, we'll know, and any of us
can shoot the shit out of him.
But what would he see
if he came through that door now?
A squad of chickens
clucking and shitting in fear.
I don't recognize you
I don't recognize you.
All of you are workers.
You're welders.
The toughest guys
I've ever met in my fucking life.
My golden boys.
You're not fucking chickens.
You know what else
is a really scary thing?
Going home alone every night.
But you all continue doing it.
You grab fear by the hand,
and you keep on living.
Because we have to live!
Gentlemen!
We have to live until the finale!
Fuck! Look at this.
You brought me back from the dead
to bust all your balls?
What?
Aren't you going to give me a hug
or something?
- How are you?
- I don't even know.
I'm so full of drugs right now.
What happened to the music, Bogotá?
- Is work gonna be depressing from now on?
- The music? Of course.
Are we Latinos or Germans?
Nice motorcycle, boss. Is it a Harley?
Real funny. Tease me again
and you'll regret it, okay?
Bogotá, how many tons do we have?
Forty-three and a half.
We can do better!
I want the furnace on high
and two-hour shifts so we can
pick up the gold bars left.
You, get me a sample of the grains.
Let's see.
Ooh!
We have to turn up the gas pressure
by two kilopascals.
We've gone over the ideal diameter.
And I wanna see you working
just like before.
With rhythm. With passion.
Chickie boom, chickie boom, chickie boom!
What's with you?
What about me?
Nothing.
I'll have to tell you again
that I wouldn't touch you
with a ten-foot pole.
Because when I said that, at least you...
paid some attention to me.
But now...
it's like I have typhus.
I don't wanna take advantage of you
while you're hurt.
Ah!
Yeah.
Okay, then.
We'll wait until I'm better,
until we get out of here,
and then we'll look for my father.
You'll ask him for my hand.
If you changed your mind... let me know.
[light romantic music playing[
You call that a fucking kiss?
Help me up.
Ow, ow, ow!
Hands down there.
Yeah.
Shit!
- Are you okay?
- Yes. You?
- Yeah.
- Bogotá, Nairobi,
- where are you?
- Freight elevator. We're fine.
Where's Denver and Rio?
5:00 MINUTES EARLIER
- The library is clear.
- Copy that.
- That thing you said about the Maserati...
- What about it?
I wanna tell you something.
Right now?
What is it?
Tokyo might be a Maserati,
but I was always
just hanging off the back
like the cans on a wedding car.
Yeah, yeah.
Rio. Rio.
The office.
Go.
Are you into her?
- What the fuck are you saying?
- The Maserati. Fuck.
If you're into her and you wanna take her
for a ride, be my guest.
Are you listening
to the shit coming out of your mouth?
First, she has to feel it.
She thinks and she decides.
The thing is,
she's pretty fucked from the breakup.
I'm gonna tell you something.
You're my friend,
- and I respect your girlfriend.
- Ex-girlfriend.
Who cares?
Ex or not, a friend's girlfriend is like
a radioactive city. Do you understand?
Even after 20,000 years, it's still
contaminated land and you don't enter it,
not even with the blessing of her ex
or your dick in a hazmat suit.
- That's fucking bullshit.
- No, it's ethics.
It's ethics that should be sacred.
What were you doing
on the couch with Stockholm?
We just were talking.
Barefoot?
Come on, man.
What difference is it
that we were barefoot?
It makes a difference, Rio.
I wouldn't take my shoes off
and talk to Lisbon on a sofa.
It'd be weird as shit.
And I'd be uncomfortable.
Do you know why?
That's the territory of the Professor.
Look. It's your boyfriend.
Wanna say hi?
Rio! Rio, right?
Rio! Denver!
Help me! I'm begging you!
I'm tied up in here!
Little friends from the gang,
please help me now!
The walls around you are made
of 70 centimeters of reinforced concrete.
It's like screaming on a submarine
in the middle of the sea.
The third card...
I spill blood.
I'm heading out for a bit.
I was telling her about my
post-traumatic stress, moron.
- Shh.
- I wasn't stealing your girlfriend.
Talking to her just calms me down.
- You calm down when you talk to Stockholm?
- Yeah.
She's intelligent, sympathetic.
She listens.
She's kind.
You could talk to her about anything.
You could talk to me too,
but you don't
because you're thinking with your dick!
I haven't been able to sleep for shit.
When I close my eyes,
I have nightmares, anxiety attacks,
tachycardia, sweating, man.
I was only able to sleep
if I knew she was next to me.
Do you understand what I mean?
You're telling me you slept with her
to my face.
I didn't sleep with her, Denver.
She was keeping me company, okay?
Are you my fucking friend or not?
- Yes, I'm your friend.
- It doesn't sound like it, Rio.
Motherfucker!
No, no, no, no!
Your helmet!
Now your vest!
We've gotta push down on the grenade!
Come on, Denver! With me!
- Bogotá, Nairobi, where are you?
- The freight elevator.
We're fine. Where's Denver and Rio?
Denver, Rio.
- Denver, Rio!
- I'll do it. I'll go.
No. You stay here with the hostages.
Come on, Helsinki. Let's go.
Careful. That son of a bitch
is around here.
Bogotá, the explosion was in the elevator
on the first floor.
Copy that.
He could be close.
We're gonna stay here.
Come on, fatty.
It's okay. We're here.
We've got you!
- Come on. Get up!
- Denver...
Are you okay?
Let me take a look.
Okay?
Are you okay?
Get down!
Fire back, Helsinki!
Fucking Gandía there!
Motherfucker!
We're cornered.
First floor elevator. We need backup now!
Go.
Go. Go.
Looks like third time's the charm, mutt.