[classical piano playing]
[server] Good evening.
-Good evening, thank you.
-Good evening.
[Berlin] Ah, wonderful.
They have lobster thermidor.
We'll eat like royalty tonight, my love.
Andrés, we need to talk.
I really don't like
the sound of that sentence at all.
It always comes
at the beginning of a breakup.
I know.
I've tried to find
the best time to tell you,
but I don't think I ever will.
Don't tell me it's because of my illness.
Hey, my love.
My love,
see that's the best reason
for us to stay together.
Can't you see it?
We're not weighed down by
"For the rest of your life."
The burden of every relationship.
Our love is only about delight.
Because it's vibrant, light, fleeting.
And above all, hopeful. You know why?
Because loving a person
who's terminally ill
always opens the path to the next love.
[chuckles] Of course, it's…
It's like one of those marvelous trips
you take around Europe.
First, you go to Rome, then Vienna…
You don't like Vienna?
It's not a problem. Later comes Istanbul.
What if I tell you that's not it?
What if I tell you
that our relationship changed?
That we used to have big dreams.
We wanted to visit Greenland,
the northern lights. But…
after the vineyards in California
came Madrid.
And we haven't left.
You used to talk about
stealing the Spanish gold reserve.
But now we're just city hopping.
Doing what?
Stealing a couple diamonds here,
some Viking gold chalices there…
You always play your best cards
when you're trying to charm someone.
But it's not easy
keeping that flame alive.
So, you're asking for a divorce.
Yeah.
Have you decided on your order yet?
No, we haven't yet.
You don't need to fill her glass.
It seems I'll be having this wine alone.
There's just one thing
that I want you to tell me.
It's nothing, just one question. May I?
Who is he?
Don't make this any harder.
No, no. Come on, I can't believe it.
[laughing] Is that the last thing
you're going to say to me?
Tatiana, all my life I've been
searching for the genuine
in every single moment,
in every decision I've made.
And now you're leaving me
with two of the most
overused sentences in movie history?
"We need to talk"
and "Don't make this any harder"?
[footsteps going away]
[thunder rumbling]
Follow that car.
Stop. Stop here.
["My Life Is Going On"
by Cecilia Krull playing]
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time
My life is going on ♪
[tense, energetic music playing]
We're running out of water.
This is the stormwater tank.
There's less water flowing.
[beeping]
That's it! The last pellets
just came out the pipes!
-It's all out!
-[all cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
[water sloshing]
[Martínez] Colonel.
Besides the engine, it's like I'm hearing
a really strong suction noise.
What do you mean "suction"?
What the fuck are you talking about?
It's like a vacuum cleaner
sucking water out of a pipe, but massive.
They're extracting water. A lot of it.
No…
Play it again.
Clean the signal as much as possible.
[mouse clicking]
[water sloshing]
It does sound like water being suctioned.
I'd say they've emptied
the secure gold vault.
So they got the gold out?
I don't know. It's possible.
You and the other engineer
told me it wasn't possible.
It wasn't possible
using the pump in the Bank of Spain.
It wouldn't have enough force
to get that gold out.
Unless maybe they reduced it
to the size of a particle.
Still, I don't think
they could get 90 tons out.
You don't know
what those bastards are capable of.
They're getting the fucking gold
out right now!
You have to tell me where! Figure it out!
[Lisbon] Professor?
Hey, you didn't tell us
it'd be so hard to get the gold out.
Hmm?
I didn't tell you it'd be easy either.
Otherwise, I'd stop looking like
the criminal mastermind
you fell madly in love with.
You're such an idiot. [chuckles]
[Professor] Over and out.
Well, looks like we're about done, right?
Yeah.
When we get outta here…
I'm gonna buy a motorcycle,
and I'll get a custom-made seat
in the shape of my ass.
And I'll travel the world.
Mm-hmm. Very nice.
What do you prefer? Beach or pool?
Beach?
Bikini or one-piece?
[playful music playing]
-What is this, a quiz for a magazine?
-[chuckles]
I'm just-- just talking.
But if you want, um, when we get out,
I'll treat you to a gin and tonic.
And we can finish the quiz. [chuckles]
[rhythmic drum music playing]
[crew singing "Bella Ciao"]
[song ends suddenly]
[Tokyo] All the hugging wasn't
just a celebration of our triumph,
or a heartfelt tribute
to the ones we lost along the way.
It was the primal roar
of a handful of insignificant people
who had managed to get
90 tons of gold out through a pipe.
That accomplishment was
a message of hope to the world.
"There's nothing that's impossible."
But the heist wasn't over yet.
And all that hope would be essential
during the next few hours.
Because what we were about to face
was simply the most
severe reality check to date.
I heard we managed to get the gold out.
I kissed Manila.
Honestly, that's not what matters most.
What matters most
is that I'm actually really confused.
I think I have way more in common
with her than with you.
You-- You know
what I used to do in Indonesia?
I'd tell you that I was gonna go buy wood,
but I'd go partying for two days.
I'd lie about it because I had this
feeling that everything I wanted was bad.
I don't know.
And reconnecting with Manila,
it actually made me realize,
somehow, that what I am isn't bad.
You're not going to say anything?
To be honest,
I'd rather talk another time, Denver.
I've got an awful headache and…
I'd prefer to get some rest.
Alone.
Sure.
[man] They're probably pumping it through
the stream channel that floods the vault.
All that water is then gathered
in two natural streams,
and after that, it's drained
into another stream in the south.
Those goddamn motherfuckers.
They weren't gonna get it out
through the drain or sewer.
They're pumping the gold farther away,
through that stream.
They must have brought in
a much more powerful pump.
I mean, it's at least 25 km of pipelines
carrying 90 tons of gold.
They'd probably need an oil pipeline pump.
Find Suárez. We need to
comb through that whole stream.
And get me the pipeline plans.
I want to know every single spot
those channels go through,
where they lead, everything.
Get a team. We're launching an offensive.
[sighs] What now?
Well, now we take turns
keeping an eye on the outside,
we freshen up. How's that sound?
Then we wait for the Professor's magic.
Where do you think the gold is going?
These channels lead to several factories,
uh, treatment plants,
and hydraulic facilities,
to, uh, stormwater tanks--
We need to track it down!
Every single gram of it.
I want soldiers combing every
cubic centimeter of water in those pipes.
There were 5,000 soldiers
outside the Bank of Spain
and more on Operation Cage
to find the Professor.
-How many policemen can we expect?
-About 480 units.
And your men, Suárez. Get your asses
over to that fucking stream! Come on!
Communication constantly.
[sirens wailing]
SUBWAY
BANK OF SPAIN
[officer] Vamos, vamos, vamos!
There's not a lot of movement outside.
Just a few vehicles leaving the perimeter.
Stay alert, but it should
get quiet for a little while.
The police are still looking for me
in downtown Madrid.
Take this time to rest.
[tense action music playing]
Arteche, do you copy?
Arteche, what's going on?
I need a few minutes.
Okay, roger that.
[music stops]
-[thuds]
-[gasps]
-[crashing]
-[shuddering]
[banging continues]
[thuds]
[female voice] Stockholm…
Stockholm…
Stockholm. It's Tokyo.
I'm here.
[screaming]
What's going on? Mónica!
[screaming] Mónica! Mónica!
[gun clatters]
What happened? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Hey.
I'm going crazy.
I saw Arturo. Arturo talks to me.
And Tokyo… Tokyo's in the…
She's out there in the dumbwaiter.
Hey, it's nothing. It's nothing, okay?
I think I'm having a psychotic break.
I see things and shoot at them.
I'm dangerous. I need to get out.
-I need medical help.
-No. You can't get out of here.
Denver, I surrender. I want to get out.
I was so close to killing you.
-I'm dangerous.
-Hey, listen to me.
I'll tell you what, okay?
Here's what we'll do.
Listen, we're gonna lock you inside
one of those vaults.
-No.
-You won't be able to hurt anyone.
-I'm dangerous. I have to get out.
-I'll take care of you.
I'll take care of you.
If you don't get better, I'll get you out.
Okay?
Okay.
-[kisses]
-[sobbing]
[grunting]
Suárez, all the locations
have to be checked.
Your unit will go
to the sewage treatment plant.
The other units will continue south.
[tires screeching]
BANK OF SPAIN
STREAM TREATMENT PLANT
SOUTH WATER CHANNEL
WATER LEVEL CONTROL SYSTEM
LA DEHESA HYDRAULIC DAM
SANTA JUSTA STORMWATER TANK
I shouldn't have said anything. Sorry.
I don't know why I told you about Manila.
No, Denver.
What you said was painful but…
somehow I'm glad you said it.
I think it's the most honest thing
you've said to me
in a very long time.
And anyway, I knew about Manila,
so it's all right.
I knew that already.
What do you mean you already knew?
She told me herself.
And I also knew about Indonesia too.
I mean, I sort of guessed.
Why did you let me lie to you?
I suppose it was easier to accept
that you needed an escape than…
to ask you whether our life together was…
that boring to you,
in case you said "yes," Denver.
Because, well, I loved our life together.
A lot.
I loved it too.
Then why did you lie?
I don't know.
I don't…
I guess I was afraid
that my dad was right.
He always used to say
I wasn't good enough for you.
That I didn't measure up, you know?
He was right.
Who'd want to be with a guy
who needs to go 60 miles away from home
just to go partying in a club,
drink like crazy,
getting hammered and picking a fight
with the first person I see?
I was afraid to show you that side of me.
That animal.
I was afraid you'd leave me.
-Are they here?
-Yeah.
The ectoplasms?
It's-- It's not funny, Denver.
-No, no, no, I-- I wasn't joking.
-No.
-You know what pisses me off?
-What?
That fucking Arturo.
He's a pain in the ass.
So much, he even manages
to get into your psychotic breaks.
-[scoffs]
-I know they're real.
Because it's, well, post-traumatic stress,
tension during the heist…
A psychotic break. I know.
But this whole having visions thing…
Just imagine nice things.
-What do you want me to imagine?
-Something that makes you smile.
Anything that doesn't make you
want to empty your gun, okay?
-'Cause you almost killed me.
-[chuckles]
You know what I would like to imagine?
What?
You.
In one of those clubs,
dancing like a maniac.
[laughing] I'm not sure
you'd like that, I'm telling you.
Yeah?
And you?
-What?
-Dancing.
-Here?
-Yeah.
-No.
-Yeah, dance for me.
-No, I can't.
-Why not?
Look at me, I'm all filthy
in these red overalls. No. No.
I can work with that.
You're gonna love it.
[both laughing]
[sirens wailing]
[over radio] Colonel, it's Suárez.
Approaching the sewage treatment plant.
[tires screech]
[Suárez] Come on, guys, let's go.
Eyes open, come on!
[tense music playing]
[guns cocking]
[Suárez] Colonel,
we're entering the underground floor.
[officers] Police!
Don't move! Hands up!
[music building]
[music ends suddenly]
Colonel, everything's clear here.
Move on to the next one.
[Ángel] Hydraulic dam.
I repeat, hydraulic dam.
[sirens wailing]
["Why So Serious" by Alice Merton playing]
So?
♪ When did we forget ♪
♪ All the crazy things
That made us feel so part of it? ♪
♪ Our youth, so confident… ♪
My God.
♪ Not caring if it ends ♪
[Denver laughing]
♪ Try to learn to let go
Of all those things that tie you down ♪
♪ Get rid of it
The voice inside that tells me that ♪
♪ I'm scared, yeah, scared as shit ♪
♪ But I wanna let go of it now ♪
♪ So someone tell me ♪
♪ Why so serious? ♪
♪ Why are we so serious? ♪
♪ Oh, why so serious? ♪
♪ When did we get like this? ♪
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ We weren't grown up like this ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
[Denver giggling]
[song fades out]
[grunting]
[wincing]
[gasping]
[breathing laboriously]
[tense, energetic music playing]
I'm heading to the main entrance
to defuse the last explosives.
Copy that, Arteche. Keep me informed.
[sirens wailing]
[officer 1] Unit 2 approaching
the hydraulic dam.
-Come on, guys. Let's go.
-[radio chirping]
[guns cocking]
[officer 1] We've entered the dam, sir.
Keep an eye on the corners.
-[officer 2] Roger that.
-Roger that.
[officer 1] Now.
[shouting] Police! Don't move!
On the ground! On the ground!
Hands where I can see them.
Hands up!
[officer 1] We got the suspects cornered.
-[worker] What's going on?
-On your six!
Don't move! On the ground!
It's not them, Colonel.
Fuck!
[Tamayo] On to the next one.
SANTA JUSTA STORMWATER TANK
[dramatic music playing]
[inaudible]
-Here we go! To the 90 tons. Yeah, baby.
-[Bogotá] To the 90 tons.
[helicopters whirring]
[sirens wailing in the distance]
Guys…
I want a city name.
What? Right now?
Come on, man…
Imagine if things go south here,
and they arrest us.
What will they say on TV?
"They've arrested Palermo, Rio,
Manila, Bogotá…
and Matías Caño."
Like I'm a fucking intern?
[all laughing]
Okay, so tell us
what you have in mind, huh?
Pamplona.
Yeah, you nailed it.
A city in Spain. How unexpected.
-[all laughing]
-What the fuck is wrong with "Pamplona"?
Get a real name. Something mythical.
Something that sounds good, like…
Rio.
Mm-hmm.
Sweetie, "Manila."
Manila is exotic, sexy, burlesque…
-"Sydney."
-"Palermo."
-[Bogotá] It's taken--
-"Marrakesh."
-[Palermo] "Charbonier."
For fuck's sake.
Have you ever been to Pamplona?
Huh? The wildest festival in the world
is held there, the Sanfermines.
Even people from Japan
come to run with the bulls.
And Hemingway wrote a novel.
They even study it in the States.
You know what it's called in Spain?
Huh? The novel?
Fiesta.
It's called Fiesta!
You want party time?
Then go to the fucking Sanfermines!
-[all laughing]
-Yeah, fuck it. That's it, "Pamplona."
[all] To Pamplona!
-To Pamplona, cheers.
-[Palermo] Yeah!
-[Manila] Pamplona it is.
-[Palermo] That's right.
[Manila] It's all good.
[indistinct chatter]
[thunder rumbling]
[woman singing]
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off of you ♪
♪ You'd be like Heaven to touch ♪
♪ I wanna hold you so much ♪
♪ At long last, love has arrived ♪
♪ And I thank God I'm alive ♪
-♪ You're just too good to be true… ♪
-[chuckles]
Don't worry, okay?
Tatiana just went upstairs to her room.
[server] Good evening.
A Negroni, please.
Do you know what elegance is?
Look at that.
When you see a guy like that,
dapper, impeccable,
you think,
"I'd go fuck his wife right now"
without ever seeing her.
Because you're absolutely convinced
that his wife must look incredible.
That's why you decided
to sleep with my wife.
Theoretically, you should be
the one seducing wives.
I'm not sure it should be your father
who seduces them on your behalf.
I just couldn't help it.
I wish that, um, well,
that I could have told you
about the whole situation myself, but I…
I-- I couldn't help it, Dad.
And I'm-- I'm sorry.
-I just couldn't help it--
-[slams on table]
Shh-shh-shh, shh-shh.
For how long?
Uh, two weeks. Um…
Three.
Three weeks.
Then what we had
wasn't so powerful and so strong
as to… to resist the advances
of a casual lover.
Casual?
Seriously, Dad?
Casual, huh?
Maybe Tatiana's in love with me.
Have you thought of that?
You didn't consider that option, did you?
Because I'm absolutely
in love with her, Dad.
Really.
And no matter what anybody else thinks,
this is a true love story.
It was inevitable.
[scoffing]
Wow, look at you.
This is the first time I actually feel
like you might measure up.
And I also would've pursued
my father's wife
if I'd fallen in love with her.
I wouldn't think about it
even for a minute.
I would have broken
the sacred limits of our family,
and respect,
just to satisfy my love.
And in this light, I'm…
very proud of you.
[chuckling]
Look who's coming.
I have to admit,
you're better off with him.
He's young, attractive,
intelligent,
ambitious, unscrupulous like his father,
and apparently healthy.
Of course, the downside
is that in just a year, maybe two years,
you'll miss out on the widow's pension
and a truly enormous inheritance.
We had a great time. [kisses]
I wish you the best.
You may go in peace.
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ And if it's quite all right ♪
♪ I need you, baby ♪
♪ To warm the lonely night ♪
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down, I pray ♪
♪ Oh, pretty, pretty baby ♪
♪ Now that I've found you, stay ♪
♪ And let me love you ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪
♪ I love you, baby ♪
♪ I need you, baby ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down, I pray ♪
♪ I've found you, stay… ♪
[Tokyo] That was
the only time Berlin went to jail.
Arrested for vandalism.
And all because of a broken heart.
He let them catch him.
On top of that,
they matched his fingerprints
with a pair found at another robbery.
So he was charged a few extra months.
But he didn't care about jail.
Not when his heart
had just been shattered.
[sirens wailing]
[Ángel] Santa Justa stormwater tank.
I repeat, the next place is
the Santa Justa stormwater tank.
This is Bronze Unit to Tamayo.
We're approaching the exit.
[tires screeching]
[action music playing]
Colonel, this is Suárez.
We're approaching the stormwater tank.
Let's go, guys. Come on.
It has to be here! We got 'em!
[alarm wailing]
[yelling] It's the police!
They're coming!
Come on! Take your weapons!
[men clamoring]
They're coming!
Hurry up!
[slow, ominous music playing]
[voices fading]
[sirens wailing]
[Benjamín, muffled] Come on, let's go.
Come on. Grab the weapons,
for fuck's sake.
[muffled] Professor, take shelter.
Take the weapon. Take the weapon.
Take it!
Professor! What's wrong with you? Wake up!
They're coming! Take the weapon!
-Take it, Professor!
-No. No, no. Drop the weapon.
Drop your weapons!
It's just four cars.
We can deal with them.
No. Right now it's four cars.
[sirens wailing]
Then it'll be ten, then 50, then the army.
Don't you get it?
They found out we're here.
We can't do anything, Benjamín.
They know we're here.
There's nothing to do.
Benjamín, nothing! Do you hear me?
Everyone, drop your weapons.
-Didn't you hear me? Drop your weapons!
-[gun firing]
Come on! Let's defend ourselves!
-No! Please, Marseille, don't do it.
-Get out of the way.
Out of the way.
I didn't surrender
when they arrested Lisbon.
I didn't do it when
that whole Spanish army entered the bank,
or when that motherfucking
Gandía killed Nairobi!
-You're going to do it now.
-No.
[Professor] It's an order!
Sergio, they killed Tokyo!
[grunts]
Marseille, listen to me.
-Listen to me. Listen to me.
-[grunting]
-I'm not allowing this to be a slaughter.
-No.
I won't let innocent people die
for something that's already lost.
No!
It's already lost.
[sirens approaching]
[groans]
["Arrieros Somos"
by Chavela Vargas playing]
[officer shouting indistinctly]
[officers shouting]
[crying]
Mmm.
I just got out of jail.
You picked me up, brought me here,
and for the last 157 km,
you've been completely silent.
There's really nothing you want to know?
Maybe I've been raped in the showers.
Or maybe I tattooed our mother's name
on my biceps. [chuckling]
You let them catch you.
You've pulled 27 heists
across half of Europe,
but that day you decided
to smash a cocktail bar
in downtown Madrid
and you let them catch you?
The Negroni was terrible.
I couldn't tolerate such an abomination.
I lost my son and it broke my heart.
I can understand
being betrayed by my wife.
Or a partner, or even my son.
But I lost him,
right when I decided
to admit his existence for the first time.
That's like getting hit in the face
by your own failure.
By the certainty
that something in your life is wrong.
And there it is.
In your failure…
is how a man is defined.
Some people hide like cowards.
Others face it.
Some rebel against it,
but without dignity.
And other people
can't help but to destroy everything
in order to have another life.
I swear to you…
I don't have much time,
but I'll squeeze every second,
every second till its last drop.
That's why now I want to help you…
[chuckling] …to pull off
the heist of a lifetime.
[laughing]
Before I die, you and I are going to rob
the Royal Mint of Spain.
[cackling]
[wineglass plunks]
[laughing]
God! God!
God!
[yelling wildly] Oh! God!
[laughing] Little brother!
God!
[melancholic music playing]
[siren wailing]
How long will we get?
[grunts] A thousand years.
[police radio chirping]
[police radios continue chirping]
-How long have we been here?
-Fifteen, 20 minutes.
They should have taken us
into police custody by now.
Exactly.
They must be waiting for forensics.
I can hear the sirens.
I can hear the radios,
but I'm not hearing any of the cars.
Why can't we hear any of the cars?
[sirens wailing]
[Professor] Why wouldn't the police
be waiting on the other side?
-That's an excellent question, Sergio.
-Good question.
And we've got the answer to that as well.
Of course we'll get the gold out
through the only place we can, but…
not in the direction
the police will expect.
It's a tank for residual water.
Suárez, just go for it!
Go for it! They're in there!
-Police!
-[Tamayo] We got 'em!
Colonel, this entire place is empty.
[Ángel] Fuck! It doesn't make sense.
[Berlin] The most logical decision
would be to take advantage
of the gentle river slope
and get the gold out that direction, but,
mm, that would just be way too easy.
It's the last place where
the channels flow into. I don't get it!
How is this possible?
Then, we'll take advantage
of the 5,000 kilowatts of our pump
to push the gold upstream
almost 18 km.
We'll get the gold up the river,
like a fucking salmon,
running all the way
to this stormwater tank.
And that, my dear friend,
no one will expect.
We've combed 25 km of pipes
with metal detectors and found nothing.
[Palermo] Not the police, nor the CNI,
nor the Spanish National Research Council.
No one.
[Ángel] Ninety tons of gold
can't just disappear.
They didn't get it out that way, damn it!
They didn't.
Then where the fuck is that gold?
They couldn't have gotten it out
any other way!
Someone tell me
where the fuck is that fucking gold!
BANK OF SPAIN
LOS MIGUELES STORMWATER TANK
[sirens wailing]
-[Victoria crying]
-You're fucking kidding me.
[speaking indistinctly]
-Victoria. Victoria…
-[grunting]
[Alicia] My baby.
[screaming] Fuck!
[Alicia gasps]
[Victoria wailing in distress]
[crying]
[sirens approaching]
-Victoria.
-[sobbing]
Someone's stolen the gold.
[laughing]
[screaming joyfully]
Fuck yeah! We did it!
[laughing]
[electronic music playing]