1
00:00:16,437 --> 00:00:18,271
Gandía was an animal.

2
00:00:19,229 --> 00:00:22,979
He could've taken shelter in his den
after hurting two of his prey,

3
00:00:26,312 --> 00:00:28,812
but that would've gone
against his nature.

4
00:00:33,812 --> 00:00:35,229
He was a predator.

5
00:00:35,562 --> 00:00:39,229
And he wasn't going to stop
until he'd finished off the whole flock.

6
00:00:49,396 --> 00:00:50,271
Nairobi.

7
00:00:50,812 --> 00:00:51,687
Fuck!

8
00:00:51,937 --> 00:00:54,062
Rio, Denver, come with me, now.

9
00:00:57,479 --> 00:00:59,562
This links to the bathroom below.

10
00:00:59,646 --> 00:01:02,021
Denver, are you up to crawling in there?

11
00:01:02,104 --> 00:01:03,312
- Sure.
- I'll go too.

12
00:01:03,396 --> 00:01:05,229
Go kill that son of a bitch.

13
00:01:06,021 --> 00:01:07,104
Let's go.

14
00:01:40,562 --> 00:01:42,021
Don't move or I'll kill her!

15
00:02:23,646 --> 00:02:26,479
- Stay still all of you!
- Where did he shoot you?

16
00:02:27,562 --> 00:02:28,604
In my hand.

17
00:02:28,687 --> 00:02:30,687
The next one goes in her head!

18
00:03:40,062 --> 00:03:43,271
- Merry Christmas!
- Why "Merry Christmas"?

19
00:03:43,354 --> 00:03:45,729
This feels a bit like Christmas, right?

20
00:03:45,812 --> 00:03:48,437
Here we are, setting the table...

21
00:03:48,854 --> 00:03:50,479
the family is coming...

22
00:03:50,562 --> 00:03:53,687
Family? It's the support team:
Manila, the foundry workers...

23
00:03:53,771 --> 00:03:56,437
- But it's good to get to know one another.
- Yeah.

24
00:03:56,521 --> 00:03:58,646
They're like distant cousins.

25
00:04:01,271 --> 00:04:03,229
Know why I came back for this heist?

26
00:04:06,146 --> 00:04:08,937
Before you scattered us
all across the globe,

27
00:04:09,479 --> 00:04:13,146
this gang
was the closest thing to a family

28
00:04:13,229 --> 00:04:14,729
I've ever had.

29
00:04:15,854 --> 00:04:19,396
I've never had a Christmas
like the ones you see in commercials

30
00:04:19,479 --> 00:04:22,312
with the grandma
and the turrón and all that.

31
00:04:22,396 --> 00:04:24,687
- With Axel's dad, didn't you celebrate...
- No.

32
00:04:36,854 --> 00:04:38,062
You know? I...

33
00:04:38,854 --> 00:04:40,521
I had already given up on...

34
00:04:43,521 --> 00:04:46,021
having a family. Completely.

35
00:04:48,104 --> 00:04:51,312
But now I think
there's another way of doing things.

36
00:04:51,896 --> 00:04:53,896
I really want to be a mother.

37
00:04:54,521 --> 00:04:57,854
Do it differently than before,
and have a bunch of kids

38
00:04:57,937 --> 00:04:59,896
and a dog and whatever else.

39
00:04:59,979 --> 00:05:02,521
What you're saying is beautiful, Nairobi.

40
00:05:07,437 --> 00:05:08,312
Would you...?

41
00:05:11,729 --> 00:05:13,812
Would you be the father of my child?

42
00:05:16,104 --> 00:05:17,021
- Look.
- Sorry?

43
00:05:17,729 --> 00:05:20,937
Genetics are very important.

44
00:05:22,396 --> 00:05:23,604
I see you in class,

45
00:05:24,312 --> 00:05:25,187
and I think...

46
00:05:26,979 --> 00:05:28,521
"What a brilliant man.

47
00:05:29,062 --> 00:05:30,354
He's so honorable.

48
00:05:30,854 --> 00:05:33,062
So sensitive. So handsome.

49
00:05:34,062 --> 00:05:35,562
And he has principles."

50
00:05:37,229 --> 00:05:39,146
I believe in what you want to do.

51
00:05:40,604 --> 00:05:43,312
That's very flattering.

52
00:05:44,687 --> 00:05:48,354
And as for honorable...
well, that's one way of seeing it.

53
00:05:48,437 --> 00:05:52,312
But... you're asking the impossible.

54
00:05:52,396 --> 00:05:55,062
Why? Robbing the Bank of Spain
is impossible.

55
00:05:55,646 --> 00:05:58,479
I'm not asking you to act like a dad,
unless you want to.

56
00:05:58,562 --> 00:06:00,896
I'm asking you for a donation

57
00:06:01,312 --> 00:06:03,396
so I can do things differently.

58
00:06:05,271 --> 00:06:07,521
- No strings attached.
- Nairobi.

59
00:06:07,604 --> 00:06:11,187
Look, I set up the Royal Mint heist

60
00:06:11,271 --> 00:06:12,771
in my father's memory.

61
00:06:13,604 --> 00:06:18,687
I've set up this one in my brother's.
I'm not the type to let go of attachments.

62
00:06:20,021 --> 00:06:22,021
I'd never be able to stop thinking

63
00:06:22,104 --> 00:06:25,229
that I have a child out there,
somewhere in the world.

64
00:06:26,396 --> 00:06:27,687
- OK.
- I'm sorry.

65
00:06:29,187 --> 00:06:32,812
You set this family up,
and you taught us

66
00:06:32,896 --> 00:06:35,646
to do anything for each other.

67
00:06:35,729 --> 00:06:39,562
- But what you're asking...
- What I'm asking you is the same.

68
00:06:39,646 --> 00:06:42,937
Family members help each other,
no questions asked.

69
00:06:43,729 --> 00:06:46,437
Because it makes you happy
and your life depends on it.

70
00:06:47,729 --> 00:06:49,437
You have your plan, I know.

71
00:06:50,271 --> 00:06:51,646
Well, I have one, too.

72
00:06:52,687 --> 00:06:55,271
You've taught me that we help each other.

73
00:06:55,354 --> 00:06:56,812
That's who we are.

74
00:07:02,437 --> 00:07:03,604
Ágata.

75
00:07:15,396 --> 00:07:19,812
- I've asked more difficult things of you.
- Well, a bit more, yeah.

76
00:07:20,479 --> 00:07:24,979
And... I've entered the lion's den,
no questions asked.

77
00:07:25,062 --> 00:07:28,687
I know. I've asked you to do
some very risky things.

78
00:07:29,562 --> 00:07:30,437
Very risky.

79
00:07:31,729 --> 00:07:33,771
Riskier than what you're asking.

80
00:07:35,521 --> 00:07:37,104
Is that a yes?

81
00:07:38,937 --> 00:07:40,937
That's a yes.

82
00:07:43,604 --> 00:07:45,604
Oh, my God!

83
00:07:46,854 --> 00:07:47,771
Come here.

84
00:07:49,979 --> 00:07:52,146
Thank you.

85
00:07:53,604 --> 00:07:56,812
I swear, you'll never regret it.

86
00:07:56,979 --> 00:08:00,021
We'll find the best IVF clinic
in the world.

87
00:08:00,354 --> 00:08:02,812
Or we can do it the natural way.

88
00:08:02,896 --> 00:08:05,687
- The natural way is out of the question.
- Fine.

89
00:08:05,771 --> 00:08:08,271
- We'll leave it to the professionals.
- OK.

90
00:08:08,896 --> 00:08:10,562
And once the heist is over.

91
00:08:11,229 --> 00:08:12,271
OK.

92
00:08:14,729 --> 00:08:16,396
This is going to be amazing.

93
00:08:26,937 --> 00:08:29,187
You're doing really well, mutt.

94
00:08:31,729 --> 00:08:33,354
You look like Jesus Christ.

95
00:08:39,521 --> 00:08:43,396
- How's your hand? Does it hurt?
- I'm loaded with morphine.

96
00:08:43,479 --> 00:08:46,979
- Did you find Tokyo?
- He still has her in the panic room.

97
00:08:54,687 --> 00:08:56,396
We're making a lot of noise.

98
00:09:03,521 --> 00:09:05,187
Let's take our boots off.

99
00:09:21,937 --> 00:09:23,021
What was that?

100
00:09:41,104 --> 00:09:42,062
No.

101
00:09:45,604 --> 00:09:46,562
Shit.

102
00:09:48,229 --> 00:09:49,396
Move!

103
00:09:57,479 --> 00:09:58,646
Rio, Denver, you OK?

104
00:09:59,771 --> 00:10:00,896
We have cover.

105
00:10:02,437 --> 00:10:04,354
You can't escape.

106
00:10:04,437 --> 00:10:07,271
Who says I want to escape,
you one-eyed queer?

107
00:10:07,729 --> 00:10:09,854
All the fun is in here.

108
00:10:09,937 --> 00:10:12,187
How many magazines do you have left?

109
00:10:12,271 --> 00:10:14,896
Why don't you come in here and count them?

110
00:10:25,104 --> 00:10:28,187
Bring the drills.
Start drilling holes in the wall.

111
00:10:30,479 --> 00:10:33,104
For each hole,
I'll make another one in you.

112
00:10:36,479 --> 00:10:37,812
He won't touch me.

113
00:10:38,812 --> 00:10:40,271
If he kills me, you kill him.

114
00:10:40,354 --> 00:10:43,687
- And he knows it.
- She's right. We have a chance.

115
00:10:43,771 --> 00:10:46,604
He'll keep shooting her. It's too risky.

116
00:10:47,479 --> 00:10:48,729
Gandía!

117
00:10:49,937 --> 00:10:51,437
Do you know what?

118
00:10:52,896 --> 00:10:55,687
You're going to be killed by two queers.

119
00:10:56,396 --> 00:11:00,479
What's worse? Being killed by the Serbian
or the one-eyed Argentinian?

120
00:11:01,812 --> 00:11:04,271
Helsinki,
promise you'll kill this bastard.

121
00:11:04,354 --> 00:11:06,687
I promise, Nairobi. I swear I will.

122
00:11:06,771 --> 00:11:10,104
What will your friends
at the shooting club say, Gandía?

123
00:11:10,187 --> 00:11:13,146
You're gonna get killed by a little bear.

124
00:11:13,229 --> 00:11:14,896
Nairobi, save your strength.

125
00:11:14,979 --> 00:11:18,687
You're making my hostage nervous.
And I want her calm.

126
00:11:18,771 --> 00:11:20,229
So we're going to sing.

127
00:11:20,312 --> 00:11:23,104
I want to hear everyone
so I know where you are.

128
00:11:23,187 --> 00:11:26,604
For each person I can't hear singing,
I'll shoot.

129
00:11:26,687 --> 00:11:28,771
Right, Nairobi? Come on, you start.

130
00:11:29,062 --> 00:11:31,562
Do you know "Lord, You Have Come"?

131
00:11:33,312 --> 00:11:35,812
Stop fucking kicking me, for fuck's sake!

132
00:11:35,896 --> 00:11:36,979
Sing!

133
00:11:37,312 --> 00:11:38,271
Sing.

134
00:11:38,979 --> 00:11:39,937
You

135
00:11:40,812 --> 00:11:44,479
Have come to the shore

136
00:11:44,562 --> 00:11:45,604
Come on!

137
00:11:47,771 --> 00:11:50,521
Neither searching for

138
00:11:50,604 --> 00:11:52,312
The wise

139
00:11:52,396 --> 00:11:54,937
Nor the rich

140
00:11:55,021 --> 00:11:58,812
I told you to sing!
And anyone who doesn't know it, hum!

141
00:11:58,896 --> 00:12:03,021
Desiring only

142
00:12:03,104 --> 00:12:07,104
That I should follow you

143
00:12:08,604 --> 00:12:10,562
Oh, Lord

144
00:12:10,646 --> 00:12:15,187
With your eyes set upon me

145
00:12:16,687 --> 00:12:18,146
I can't hear the choir!

146
00:12:18,229 --> 00:12:21,271
I left my boat

147
00:12:21,396 --> 00:12:25,854
On the shore

148
00:12:26,396 --> 00:12:29,479
At your side

149
00:12:29,854 --> 00:12:38,854
I will seek another sea

150
00:12:41,062 --> 00:12:43,396
That song had a funeral vibe to it.

151
00:12:44,312 --> 00:12:46,604
Our own funeral.

152
00:12:47,687 --> 00:12:49,771
And that slap of reality

153
00:12:49,854 --> 00:12:51,729
began to wake up the Professor.

154
00:12:53,021 --> 00:12:54,687
We're up against the ropes.

155
00:12:55,396 --> 00:12:56,812
Nairobi, TKO.

156
00:12:57,854 --> 00:12:59,312
Tokyo, TKO.

157
00:13:01,479 --> 00:13:03,396
Lisbon, TKO.

158
00:13:06,937 --> 00:13:07,979
Professor.

159
00:13:08,604 --> 00:13:12,229
I can't think.
I have too many emotional attachments.

160
00:13:12,312 --> 00:13:14,979
I used to have
a gang with city names. Now...

161
00:13:16,021 --> 00:13:20,312
now I could have a child,
not with one, but with two of the gang.

162
00:13:21,146 --> 00:13:24,396
Mixing professional
and personal doesn't work.

163
00:13:24,479 --> 00:13:26,521
Tokyo is in the panic room.

164
00:13:27,354 --> 00:13:29,062
And that's precisely where...

165
00:13:29,729 --> 00:13:31,104
Gandía...

166
00:13:31,646 --> 00:13:33,646
wants to get to.

167
00:13:37,104 --> 00:13:39,937
We have to find the room
and ensure there's no way out.

168
00:13:42,021 --> 00:13:44,021
Where would you put a panic room?

169
00:13:44,104 --> 00:13:46,812
A place you need to protect.
Where the gold is.

170
00:13:46,896 --> 00:13:47,812
No.

171
00:13:48,354 --> 00:13:53,146
Panic rooms protect lives, not gold.
Whose life is most important there?

172
00:13:53,229 --> 00:13:55,354
- The governor's.
- Exactly.

173
00:13:55,687 --> 00:13:58,271
It must be close to the governor's office.

174
00:13:58,354 --> 00:14:00,729
But why isn't it in the blueprints?

175
00:14:00,812 --> 00:14:03,104
- Perhaps they renovated.
- No.

176
00:14:15,271 --> 00:14:16,812
Palermo, don't answer.

177
00:14:17,479 --> 00:14:20,271
The panic room's
behind the governor's bathroom.

178
00:14:20,354 --> 00:14:22,354
It's not in the blueprints.

179
00:14:22,437 --> 00:14:26,104
They must have falsified
the room measurements, but trust me.

180
00:14:26,521 --> 00:14:27,396
I'm sure.

181
00:14:33,354 --> 00:14:35,354
They're singing hymns.

182
00:14:36,646 --> 00:14:38,396
That's a bad omen, right?

183
00:14:38,479 --> 00:14:41,604
These people are eccentric like that.

184
00:14:41,687 --> 00:14:44,104
However, those shots before...

185
00:14:45,146 --> 00:14:49,146
could mean the gang is in dire straits,
don't you reckon, Governor?

186
00:14:49,229 --> 00:14:50,521
How would you know?

187
00:14:52,521 --> 00:14:56,021
I don't know.
The shouting, the grenades...

188
00:14:56,146 --> 00:14:58,312
Also, that guy watching us...

189
00:14:58,396 --> 00:15:02,396
I have no fucking clue who he is,
but he doesn't belong to the gang.

190
00:15:02,479 --> 00:15:06,896
We should take advantage of this situation
and tip the scales in our favor.

191
00:15:06,979 --> 00:15:10,604
Even a small push
could mean victory for us.

192
00:15:11,437 --> 00:15:12,896
And if I may, Governor,

193
00:15:12,979 --> 00:15:16,687
I think that small push
is our responsibility: yours and mine.

194
00:15:17,771 --> 00:15:22,271
We must be the ones
to save all these people.

195
00:15:22,854 --> 00:15:24,396
What we must do

196
00:15:24,479 --> 00:15:26,896
is remain calm and wait.

197
00:15:26,979 --> 00:15:30,354
Quiet! If you so much as sigh again,
I'll start shooting.

198
00:15:31,646 --> 00:15:34,521
I'm sorry to disagree with you, Governor,

199
00:15:34,604 --> 00:15:36,521
but it's your responsibility.

200
00:15:36,604 --> 00:15:39,354
You are the governor of the Bank of Spain.

201
00:15:39,604 --> 00:15:42,312
It's your responsibility as a man,
damn it.

202
00:15:42,771 --> 00:15:45,437
Make some decisions, face the problems.

203
00:15:45,562 --> 00:15:51,229
As I always say... sometimes it's better
to get up and die on your feet

204
00:15:51,312 --> 00:15:54,521
than to live forever on your knees.

205
00:15:57,562 --> 00:16:00,021
- Know what I think?
- Tell me.

206
00:16:00,521 --> 00:16:02,521
You're a clown.

207
00:16:03,146 --> 00:16:05,854
You put us all at risk
with your little walks

208
00:16:05,937 --> 00:16:08,646
and your snake-oil salesman spiel.

209
00:16:09,771 --> 00:16:10,854
Leave us in peace.

210
00:16:11,646 --> 00:16:15,521
If you want to die on your feet,
get up and do it.

211
00:16:23,396 --> 00:16:26,437
Grenades, shooting...

212
00:16:26,854 --> 00:16:28,271
All that in six minutes.

213
00:16:29,104 --> 00:16:31,854
And here you are, so calm.
What am I missing?

214
00:16:31,937 --> 00:16:34,271
- I know the same as you, Alicia.
- Liar.

215
00:16:34,646 --> 00:16:37,187
- What's going on in there?
- I don't know.

216
00:16:37,271 --> 00:16:38,896
Why don't we intervene?

217
00:16:38,979 --> 00:16:42,479
If shots are heard,
protocol says we should intervene.

218
00:16:46,687 --> 00:16:47,729
It's Gandía,

219
00:16:47,812 --> 00:16:49,687
- the head of security.
- Shit.

220
00:16:49,771 --> 00:16:52,896
He's on the loose,
armed and acting of his own accord.

221
00:16:52,979 --> 00:16:55,479
Wait a minute. Did you talk to him?

222
00:16:57,812 --> 00:17:01,146
Did you give him the green light
to wage war and kill everyone?

223
00:17:01,229 --> 00:17:03,479
I officially ordered him not to do it.

224
00:17:03,562 --> 00:17:06,479
He said balls to that,
he'd do it in self-defense.

225
00:17:06,562 --> 00:17:09,521
If he wants to defend himself,
I can't stop him.

226
00:17:09,854 --> 00:17:11,229
You're trash, Tamayo.

227
00:17:11,312 --> 00:17:15,854
Out there, you're a saint,
worried about your public image,

228
00:17:15,937 --> 00:17:17,604
holding an absurd truce,

229
00:17:17,687 --> 00:17:20,604
while you send a lunatic
to do the dirty work.

230
00:17:20,687 --> 00:17:23,854
If it goes well, you'll take the credit.
If not, you'll say,

231
00:17:23,937 --> 00:17:26,312
"I told him, but he was a nutcase."

232
00:17:26,396 --> 00:17:28,854
Us nutcases always do your dirty work.

233
00:17:28,937 --> 00:17:32,312
Do you have a problem
with Gandía waging a guerrilla war?

234
00:17:32,396 --> 00:17:35,437
Or with him sabotaging,
injuring, or killing them?

235
00:17:35,521 --> 00:17:36,604
You don't, right?

236
00:17:37,187 --> 00:17:38,937
Then keep your mouth shut.

237
00:17:44,271 --> 00:17:45,729
Are you thinking?

238
00:17:45,812 --> 00:17:47,229
Yes, I'm thinking.

239
00:17:49,062 --> 00:17:53,104
- What about?
- When was the first time we lost control?

240
00:17:54,187 --> 00:17:56,812
When Gandía didn't go out
with the red boxes.

241
00:17:58,146 --> 00:18:00,229
- The second time?
- I have a problem.

242
00:18:02,021 --> 00:18:05,271
When Lisbon couldn't climb the tree.

243
00:18:05,354 --> 00:18:08,812
Those two mistakes
have put us up against the ropes.

244
00:18:10,937 --> 00:18:14,104
And we need to go back...

245
00:18:17,146 --> 00:18:18,771
and undo them.

246
00:18:18,854 --> 00:18:22,021
I need to exercise to clear my head.
Palermo.

247
00:18:23,562 --> 00:18:25,146
Hold on, you hear me?

248
00:18:26,729 --> 00:18:27,562
Hold on.

249
00:18:38,354 --> 00:18:39,771
Fucking hell!

250
00:18:47,021 --> 00:18:48,437
Mr. Arturo.

251
00:18:51,104 --> 00:18:54,146
I've got something
that may help with that push.

252
00:18:54,521 --> 00:18:55,354
What?

253
00:18:55,937 --> 00:18:58,104
- A phone.
- Hide it.

254
00:18:58,187 --> 00:19:00,937
It's Nairobi's.
The one the police sent in.

255
00:19:07,437 --> 00:19:08,896
I found it while cleaning.

256
00:19:12,021 --> 00:19:14,104
You'll know what to do with it.

257
00:19:14,187 --> 00:19:16,104
What the fuck's going on there?

258
00:19:16,187 --> 00:19:18,687
If I hear so much as a sigh,
I'll shoot.

259
00:19:25,687 --> 00:19:27,937
Sir, I need to use the bathroom. Now.

260
00:19:28,479 --> 00:19:29,604
Now's not the time.

261
00:19:29,687 --> 00:19:33,021
No one is leaving this place,
so sit down and relax.

262
00:19:50,187 --> 00:19:51,062
After you.

263
00:19:52,062 --> 00:19:53,687
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.

264
00:19:56,354 --> 00:20:01,521
- What's going on, Daniel? I was eating...
- No, not Daniel. Here, I'm Denver.

265
00:20:02,187 --> 00:20:03,062
OK? Denver.

266
00:20:03,146 --> 00:20:05,979
I'm sorry,
I'm not used to your new identity.

267
00:20:07,771 --> 00:20:08,896
Well, about that...

268
00:20:10,604 --> 00:20:12,521
There are a few things...

269
00:20:13,229 --> 00:20:16,354
that I'd like to understand,
and it's not easy for me.

270
00:20:18,187 --> 00:20:20,229
Ask away. I'm the same person.

271
00:20:20,312 --> 00:20:23,771
You're not exactly the same person.
You have boobs now.

272
00:20:24,896 --> 00:20:26,396
- Well...
- You have boobs.

273
00:20:26,479 --> 00:20:30,146
- Yes, I do.
- You're a woman, I understand that part.

274
00:20:32,229 --> 00:20:35,312
Are you gay as well? Or how does it work?

275
00:20:37,396 --> 00:20:42,271
So what you're worried about right now
is whether I like men or not, is that it?

276
00:20:42,354 --> 00:20:43,187
Yes.

277
00:20:44,396 --> 00:20:48,271
I like men, to be honest.
I like them very much.

278
00:20:48,854 --> 00:20:51,646
Mind you, not just any type of man.

279
00:20:52,146 --> 00:20:56,104
I like them strong, you know?
The kind that go to the gym.

280
00:20:56,187 --> 00:20:59,771
Tough guys, but well-read too,
so I can learn from them.

281
00:21:00,812 --> 00:21:04,396
The type that watch football.
But in a macho way, you know?

282
00:21:04,479 --> 00:21:08,229
Beer in hand, legs spread wide,
and their hand on their groin.

283
00:21:08,312 --> 00:21:10,021
OK, I get it. It's clear.

284
00:21:10,812 --> 00:21:11,646
But...

285
00:21:12,062 --> 00:21:14,021
have you always liked men?

286
00:21:14,437 --> 00:21:16,812
Or was this
a result of becoming a woman?

287
00:21:16,896 --> 00:21:17,854
First of all,

288
00:21:17,937 --> 00:21:19,687
I've always been a woman.

289
00:21:20,521 --> 00:21:21,354
No.

290
00:21:21,437 --> 00:21:22,896
No, you haven't.

291
00:21:22,979 --> 00:21:25,562
I did robberies with you.
You weren't a woman.

292
00:21:25,646 --> 00:21:28,396
How does a woman rob?
By scratching and pulling hair?

293
00:21:28,479 --> 00:21:29,687
I'm not a caveman.

294
00:21:29,771 --> 00:21:34,604
But, I mean, at the end of the day,
you can spot a woman.

295
00:21:34,687 --> 00:21:37,854
When I did a robbery,
I went with Juanito, not a woman.

296
00:21:38,521 --> 00:21:43,021
Maybe this thing about being a woman...
happened later.

297
00:21:45,437 --> 00:21:46,437
Listen.

298
00:21:48,062 --> 00:21:51,396
Juanito would finish a robbery with you...

299
00:21:52,229 --> 00:21:54,437
and go back home, to his room.

300
00:21:55,937 --> 00:21:57,937
He'd put some music on,

301
00:21:58,437 --> 00:22:00,437
he'd roll a joint,

302
00:22:00,729 --> 00:22:04,437
and he'd put some red lipstick on,
a wonderful lipstick I had.

303
00:22:04,521 --> 00:22:05,687
It was Ferrari red.

304
00:22:06,187 --> 00:22:07,437
He'd take his joint

305
00:22:07,521 --> 00:22:09,354
and lie on the bed.

306
00:22:11,771 --> 00:22:14,437
And right there, in those moments,

307
00:22:15,062 --> 00:22:18,187
all alone, relaxed,
and looking gorgeous...

308
00:22:20,521 --> 00:22:23,562
that was when I was really myself.

309
00:22:24,687 --> 00:22:28,104
- You've always been a woman?
- Always.

310
00:22:29,771 --> 00:22:31,187
And I never noticed?

311
00:22:31,271 --> 00:22:34,562
Do you know who made me
really horny back then?

312
00:22:37,562 --> 00:22:39,479
- Of course I do.
- Really?

313
00:22:39,562 --> 00:22:42,604
David Beckham.
You talked about him all damn day.

314
00:22:42,687 --> 00:22:45,396
Beckham made me horny too,
always has, but no.

315
00:22:46,479 --> 00:22:49,187
You. You turned me on so much.

316
00:22:53,354 --> 00:22:54,896
No, I didn't.

317
00:22:54,979 --> 00:22:58,354
- I was in love with you.
- Don't joke about love.

318
00:22:58,437 --> 00:23:01,729
Why do you think
I followed you around, doing jobs?

319
00:23:01,812 --> 00:23:03,146
To be near you.

320
00:23:03,229 --> 00:23:05,229
- Are you serious?
- Yes.

321
00:23:05,312 --> 00:23:07,312
I used to grope you on the bike.

322
00:23:07,396 --> 00:23:10,729
You didn't notice,
but I'd grab onto your leg and back...

323
00:23:10,812 --> 00:23:13,312
And your scent drove me wild.

324
00:23:13,396 --> 00:23:16,312
Don't you realize this is serious?

325
00:23:16,396 --> 00:23:18,437
You were taking advantage of me.

326
00:23:20,354 --> 00:23:23,562
I'm pulling your leg,
you dickhead. I mean...

327
00:23:23,646 --> 00:23:24,646
Fucking hell.

328
00:23:26,062 --> 00:23:27,312
Give me a hug, come on.

329
00:23:40,896 --> 00:23:43,437
Excuse me, sir,
but I can't wait any longer.

330
00:23:43,521 --> 00:23:46,396
Nobody move!
I don't want to hear a sound!

331
00:23:53,771 --> 00:23:55,729
Miguel, listen.

332
00:23:55,812 --> 00:23:59,021
We need to establish communication
with the outside.

333
00:23:59,104 --> 00:24:00,104
OK?

334
00:24:00,771 --> 00:24:01,687
Here, hide it.

335
00:24:02,604 --> 00:24:05,021
They've got me in their sights. You're OK.

336
00:24:12,771 --> 00:24:15,312
- What are you doing here?
- What the fuck?

337
00:24:15,979 --> 00:24:17,979
What's happening? Where's Denver?

338
00:24:18,062 --> 00:24:19,562
- He's fine.
- Who's there?

339
00:24:21,021 --> 00:24:23,187
- It's a hostage.
- Take her away.

340
00:24:23,271 --> 00:24:25,271
- Come on.
- Like hell, I'm staying.

341
00:24:25,354 --> 00:24:26,187
Give me a gun.

342
00:24:26,271 --> 00:24:28,521
You're not here for this, Manila. Go.

343
00:24:28,604 --> 00:24:30,729
You're in trouble. Give me a gun.

344
00:24:34,437 --> 00:24:36,312
Get out of here right now.

345
00:24:36,687 --> 00:24:37,771
Come on, damn it.

346
00:24:38,937 --> 00:24:39,979
Stay calm.

347
00:24:48,354 --> 00:24:52,229
From now on, you and I will be
the backbone of the resistance.

348
00:24:53,354 --> 00:24:55,229
My mouth went dry just hearing that.

349
00:25:07,021 --> 00:25:08,187
Denver.

350
00:25:10,437 --> 00:25:11,854
It's four seconds at most.

351
00:25:13,354 --> 00:25:15,562
One advances,
the other provides cover fire.

352
00:25:15,646 --> 00:25:16,812
And we save Nairobi.

353
00:25:16,896 --> 00:25:19,604
Tell us what you want, Gandía.
Let's negotiate.

354
00:25:19,937 --> 00:25:22,646
Negotiate?
Look, let me explain the situation.

355
00:25:23,146 --> 00:25:24,146
Option one:

356
00:25:24,229 --> 00:25:27,687
I come out with the gun to Nairobi's head.

357
00:25:28,229 --> 00:25:30,937
You stay up against the right wall.

358
00:25:31,437 --> 00:25:33,437
I let her go, and nobody dies.

359
00:25:34,062 --> 00:25:37,396
It's a good deal for both of us.
Zero-zero. A tie.

360
00:25:37,896 --> 00:25:39,146
Option two:

361
00:25:39,729 --> 00:25:42,396
instead of me coming out, you come in.

362
00:25:42,812 --> 00:25:44,729
I blow Nairobi's head off.

363
00:25:45,396 --> 00:25:46,521
You shoot me.

364
00:25:46,771 --> 00:25:49,396
But I'd still have a free hand
to shoot back,

365
00:25:49,479 --> 00:25:52,479
and I swear,
I'll take out more than one of you.

366
00:25:52,562 --> 00:25:56,062
You forgot option three:
come out on your knees, unarmed.

367
00:25:56,146 --> 00:25:58,312
You surrender and give us Nairobi.

368
00:25:58,396 --> 00:25:59,979
That's a tie too. How's that?

369
00:26:00,062 --> 00:26:02,604
I won't kneel,
not even before God Almighty.

370
00:26:02,687 --> 00:26:05,687
I'll give you one minute.
Then, I start shooting.

371
00:26:05,771 --> 00:26:07,437
I may well win six-zero.

372
00:26:08,604 --> 00:26:09,937
What an asshole.

373
00:26:10,687 --> 00:26:13,146
Gandía, darling, you couldn't do that.

374
00:26:13,854 --> 00:26:15,062
You're an idiot.

375
00:26:15,146 --> 00:26:19,437
The other day, I turned up with my friend,

376
00:26:19,521 --> 00:26:21,271
and we got you good.

377
00:26:21,354 --> 00:26:22,604
Shut up.

378
00:26:22,687 --> 00:26:27,021
Tokyo really got you with the water trick.

379
00:26:27,104 --> 00:26:28,479
Nairobi, shut up.

380
00:26:29,687 --> 00:26:32,729
- The door handle hit you in the face...
- Shut up.

381
00:26:32,812 --> 00:26:34,479
...and knocked you out.

382
00:26:34,562 --> 00:26:36,479
Why is she doing that?

383
00:26:36,562 --> 00:26:40,812
Where are your macho balls now?

384
00:26:41,646 --> 00:26:44,021
- So clumsy.
- She wants to save Tokyo.

385
00:26:44,104 --> 00:26:45,646
You're useless.

386
00:26:46,062 --> 00:26:48,396
She knows if he kills her, we'll kill him.

387
00:26:48,479 --> 00:26:52,146
You've spent your whole life
waiting for this moment, right?

388
00:26:52,229 --> 00:26:54,604
With your well-trained little soldiers.

389
00:26:54,687 --> 00:26:57,562
And two chicks show up
and get you real good.

390
00:26:57,646 --> 00:27:00,271
- Should I shoot you now?
- Surprise me.

391
00:27:01,271 --> 00:27:03,312
Should I put a bullet in your ass?

392
00:27:16,146 --> 00:27:18,521
We have to get her out now.

393
00:27:18,604 --> 00:27:20,646
If we let him out,

394
00:27:20,729 --> 00:27:23,812
he'll do whatever he wants.
I don't trust him.

395
00:27:23,896 --> 00:27:26,604
- We have to hold on.
- Why do you want to?

396
00:27:26,687 --> 00:27:29,729
She's there because of you.
You freed that butcher.

397
00:27:29,812 --> 00:27:31,396
We have to get her out.

398
00:27:31,896 --> 00:27:33,187
Do you all agree?

399
00:27:37,896 --> 00:27:38,937
OK, Gandía.

400
00:27:39,729 --> 00:27:41,187
We're letting you out.

401
00:27:41,562 --> 00:27:43,062
OK, good.

402
00:27:43,437 --> 00:27:44,729
This is how it'll go:

403
00:27:44,812 --> 00:27:47,229
you'll see Nairobi the whole time.

404
00:27:47,312 --> 00:27:51,312
We'll walk forward with my gun to her head

405
00:27:51,396 --> 00:27:55,354
once she confirms you're all
up against the wall on the right.

406
00:27:55,937 --> 00:27:59,354
Starting with
those two fucking kids up there!

407
00:28:01,687 --> 00:28:04,104
Did you hear that? You have to come down.

408
00:28:04,271 --> 00:28:05,312
OK.

409
00:28:18,646 --> 00:28:22,354
Earlier you asked me
if sleeping with me made my husband sick,

410
00:28:22,437 --> 00:28:23,562
and I didn't reply.

411
00:28:24,312 --> 00:28:26,854
No. I didn't make him sick.

412
00:28:29,521 --> 00:28:31,354
Because I wasn't a bitch then.

413
00:28:38,146 --> 00:28:39,396
But now I am.

414
00:28:40,854 --> 00:28:43,062
And yes, we had sex.

415
00:28:43,146 --> 00:28:44,312
Everywhere.

416
00:28:45,646 --> 00:28:47,646
And highly creative sex.

417
00:28:47,937 --> 00:28:52,521
I guess you and the Professor are
more the type to do it once every 30 days.

418
00:28:52,604 --> 00:28:55,562
Missionary position,
even though you're billionaires.

419
00:28:56,312 --> 00:28:59,979
All that poison inside you
is eating away at you, Alicia.

420
00:29:00,729 --> 00:29:02,229
I can see it in your face.

421
00:29:07,271 --> 00:29:08,646
What's wrong with it?

422
00:29:10,187 --> 00:29:13,479
You're a caricature of yourself,
going on about sex. What's wrong?

423
00:29:13,562 --> 00:29:16,354
Is it the hormones?
Try downloading an app.

424
00:29:16,437 --> 00:29:19,854
There are tons of perverts
who want to fuck pregnant women.

425
00:29:19,937 --> 00:29:21,896
I like to get to know them first.

426
00:29:21,979 --> 00:29:25,021
I don't go off with the first hipster
who comes along,

427
00:29:25,104 --> 00:29:27,062
gives me his number, and says,

428
00:29:27,312 --> 00:29:30,771
"Hey, gorgeous,
why don't you come to my storehouse

429
00:29:30,854 --> 00:29:33,021
to try my cider? It's very tasty."

430
00:29:33,104 --> 00:29:34,104
Know what it is?

431
00:29:35,521 --> 00:29:36,354
No, tell me.

432
00:29:36,437 --> 00:29:38,812
If your mask slips, you crumble.

433
00:29:39,979 --> 00:29:43,354
You're in danger of collapse.
And I get it.

434
00:29:45,896 --> 00:29:47,521
I'm not the one in a mask.

435
00:29:48,896 --> 00:29:52,104
Let's see, earlier, we had a deal.

436
00:29:52,187 --> 00:29:54,312
You were holding the phone,

437
00:29:55,146 --> 00:29:56,312
and you backed out.

438
00:29:57,604 --> 00:29:58,646
What happened?

439
00:29:59,687 --> 00:30:03,104
I made you waste your time
while you were questioning me.

440
00:30:03,937 --> 00:30:06,771
I pretended
you were slowly wearing me down,

441
00:30:06,854 --> 00:30:08,354
that I was giving in.

442
00:30:08,437 --> 00:30:12,021
In the meantime, the Professor
escaped your cordon.

443
00:30:12,104 --> 00:30:14,854
It's called "diversion tactics."

444
00:30:14,937 --> 00:30:16,646
And it worked.

445
00:30:18,271 --> 00:30:19,896
Do you know what I think?

446
00:30:21,021 --> 00:30:24,354
Your little shepherd
somehow made it in time.

447
00:30:27,937 --> 00:30:29,104
I'll find out.

448
00:30:30,354 --> 00:30:31,312
Come on.

449
00:30:46,479 --> 00:30:48,521
- Think.
- I knew we weren't in Spain.

450
00:30:50,146 --> 00:30:54,229
- I could hear the call to prayer.
- Think, you can do it.

451
00:30:54,312 --> 00:30:56,229
Fly with me.

452
00:31:06,687 --> 00:31:07,521
Shakir.

453
00:31:08,479 --> 00:31:09,812
Can you hear me?

454
00:31:10,771 --> 00:31:12,771
Yes, Shakir speaking, Professor.

455
00:31:12,854 --> 00:31:15,479
I need you to track Rio's flight to Spain.

456
00:31:15,562 --> 00:31:18,687
It's a Spanish Air Force
Beechcraft Air King 250.

457
00:31:18,771 --> 00:31:21,354
The flight landed at 16:30 on April 4.

458
00:31:21,437 --> 00:31:24,104
Check all the air navigation satellites.

459
00:31:24,187 --> 00:31:26,729
I need the exact point of origin.

460
00:31:32,646 --> 00:31:33,896
Does it have battery?

461
00:31:35,562 --> 00:31:37,729
- It does.
- And signal?

462
00:31:41,521 --> 00:31:42,854
Yes, sir.

463
00:31:42,937 --> 00:31:44,771
OK, go to the call log.

464
00:31:45,604 --> 00:31:48,896
Miguel, you need to keep a cool head, OK?

465
00:31:48,979 --> 00:31:51,229
They don't suspect you at all.

466
00:31:51,312 --> 00:31:54,104
- Yes, but my fingers are sweating.
- Stay calm.

467
00:31:58,812 --> 00:32:01,937
- There's a call from a hidden number.
- Go to contacts.

468
00:32:03,979 --> 00:32:05,021
There's a number.

469
00:32:06,479 --> 00:32:07,479
Call it.

470
00:32:09,021 --> 00:32:10,396
I hope nobody answers.

471
00:32:13,812 --> 00:32:15,354
It's Nairobi's phone.

472
00:32:18,021 --> 00:32:19,854
- What are you doing?
- I won't talk.

473
00:32:19,937 --> 00:32:21,812
- Fuck.
- They hung up.

474
00:32:23,062 --> 00:32:26,229
I'm leaving my fingerprints.
I'm not calling the cops.

475
00:32:26,312 --> 00:32:27,146
Listen.

476
00:32:27,229 --> 00:32:29,771
You just need to leave the call connected

477
00:32:29,854 --> 00:32:33,187
and hold a normal conversation,
between hostages.

478
00:32:33,271 --> 00:32:34,812
They'll know what to do.

479
00:32:36,104 --> 00:32:36,937
Understood?

480
00:32:43,396 --> 00:32:44,896
They're calling again.

481
00:32:45,479 --> 00:32:47,229
- Speak.
- So...

482
00:32:48,937 --> 00:32:50,187
we're here,

483
00:32:50,271 --> 00:32:51,646
in the library.

484
00:32:52,229 --> 00:32:53,562
All the hostages.

485
00:32:53,896 --> 00:32:57,771
Being watched by just one of the gang,
a guy called Matías.

486
00:32:57,854 --> 00:33:00,729
- Turn the volume up.
- I think it's Arturo Román.

487
00:33:00,812 --> 00:33:02,937
There's no one in the lobby, right?

488
00:33:03,229 --> 00:33:04,229
No one.

489
00:33:07,562 --> 00:33:08,729
I've lost my voice.

490
00:33:09,729 --> 00:33:11,896
And since Gandía is free,

491
00:33:11,979 --> 00:33:14,854
it'd be the perfect time
for the police to go in.

492
00:33:15,104 --> 00:33:18,604
Because, I repeat,
there's no one in the lobby.

493
00:33:18,687 --> 00:33:21,979
They've been decimated.
There have been shots, grenades,

494
00:33:22,062 --> 00:33:24,437
shouting, and hymns, right, Miguel?

495
00:33:24,521 --> 00:33:25,354
That's right.

496
00:33:28,646 --> 00:33:29,479
Sorry.

497
00:33:33,229 --> 00:33:36,854
- We have to go in.
- The Presidency says no more armored vans.

498
00:33:36,937 --> 00:33:40,479
They're looking the other way.
We'll catch them off guard.

499
00:33:40,562 --> 00:33:41,729
I can't.

500
00:33:42,271 --> 00:33:44,229
What the fuck are you doing?

501
00:33:44,812 --> 00:33:47,604
It's this kid.
He's very nervous. He's lost it.

502
00:33:47,687 --> 00:33:49,229
Poor guy, he was praying.

503
00:33:49,312 --> 00:33:51,687
- He seemed... I don't know.
- Come on.

504
00:33:53,354 --> 00:33:56,062
Over here, in silence and close to me.

505
00:33:56,729 --> 00:33:58,646
You, hands where I can see them.

506
00:33:58,729 --> 00:34:03,229
Lower them an inch, and I'll shoot you.
Move an inch, and I'll shoot you.

507
00:34:04,187 --> 00:34:06,479
Say a fucking word...

508
00:34:06,562 --> 00:34:08,687
- And you'll shoot me.
- That's right.

509
00:34:08,771 --> 00:34:11,437
- I might just shoot you anyway.
- Come on.

510
00:34:12,062 --> 00:34:12,937
Behave.

511
00:34:16,437 --> 00:34:20,312
Suárez! Prepare an intervention unit.
We'll go in through the lobby.

512
00:34:20,396 --> 00:34:22,979
Call Gandía in the panic room
to coordinate.

513
00:34:23,062 --> 00:34:25,896
Thank God.
You're finally showing you have balls.

514
00:34:38,937 --> 00:34:39,937
Professor.

515
00:34:40,896 --> 00:34:43,479
The Beechcraft Air King 250

516
00:34:43,562 --> 00:34:47,854
that brought Rio to Spain
took off from Algeria at 15:03 hours,

517
00:34:47,937 --> 00:34:50,062
from a town called Timimoun.

518
00:34:50,854 --> 00:34:53,687
It's in the Atlas Mountains.

519
00:34:58,937 --> 00:34:59,896
Good.

520
00:34:59,979 --> 00:35:03,562
Minutes earlier, they'd have driven him
to the aircraft.

521
00:35:03,646 --> 00:35:04,646
Find that car.

522
00:35:05,271 --> 00:35:07,271
I see it's a desert. No trees.

523
00:35:07,354 --> 00:35:09,646
So you can go back through the images

524
00:35:09,729 --> 00:35:11,854
- to see where the car came from.
- OK.

525
00:35:11,937 --> 00:35:14,021
We'll use the weather satellites.

526
00:35:14,104 --> 00:35:15,021
Very good.

527
00:35:22,854 --> 00:35:25,729
Go to Algeria.
I want you in Timimoun in four hours.

528
00:35:25,812 --> 00:35:27,646
I can't fly with weapons.

529
00:35:27,729 --> 00:35:30,354
I know. You'll get backup once you arrive.

530
00:35:30,771 --> 00:35:32,562
The plan was to not leave you.

531
00:35:32,646 --> 00:35:34,979
The plan has just changed, Marseille.

532
00:35:35,062 --> 00:35:37,771
I need to bring together
the Serbs and Benjamín's team

533
00:35:37,854 --> 00:35:39,271
and go on the offensive.

534
00:35:39,354 --> 00:35:42,062
We'll strike them everywhere,
so hard and fast,

535
00:35:42,146 --> 00:35:44,229
they won't know which way is up.

536
00:36:06,062 --> 00:36:07,062
How are you?

537
00:36:08,604 --> 00:36:09,771
My stitches...

538
00:36:11,146 --> 00:36:12,146
have come undone.

539
00:36:14,271 --> 00:36:15,187
Where is he?

540
00:36:15,646 --> 00:36:16,479
I don't know.

541
00:36:17,687 --> 00:36:18,729
Where is he?

542
00:36:22,312 --> 00:36:23,146
Denver...

543
00:36:27,771 --> 00:36:28,687
I don't know.

544
00:36:32,562 --> 00:36:35,396
We're here, fucking scumbag.

545
00:36:36,479 --> 00:36:37,812
Where's the other one?

546
00:36:38,896 --> 00:36:39,812
I'm here.

547
00:36:40,521 --> 00:36:43,187
Very well.
I'll start cutting Nairobi loose.

548
00:36:48,187 --> 00:36:49,104
Mutt.

549
00:36:50,396 --> 00:36:52,687
Want to say anything before the dance?

550
00:36:53,771 --> 00:36:55,437
No? Well...

551
00:37:02,271 --> 00:37:03,729
- Party time?
- Party time.

552
00:37:14,604 --> 00:37:15,771
Nairobi.

553
00:37:15,854 --> 00:37:16,937
Sleepyhead.

554
00:37:18,437 --> 00:37:20,146
You're brave, asleep up here

555
00:37:20,229 --> 00:37:22,979
with everyone at the table
waiting for you.

556
00:37:23,062 --> 00:37:24,354
Come on, wake up.

557
00:37:25,354 --> 00:37:26,312
Hey.

558
00:37:27,521 --> 00:37:28,479
What?

559
00:37:29,271 --> 00:37:30,646
He said yes.

560
00:37:33,896 --> 00:37:35,021
The Professor.

561
00:37:36,771 --> 00:37:37,937
He said yes.

562
00:37:41,687 --> 00:37:43,896
- You're going to be an aunt!
- An aunt!

563
00:37:44,687 --> 00:37:47,271
- I'm so happy for you.
- I can't believe it.

564
00:37:47,562 --> 00:37:48,437
Hey.

565
00:37:48,521 --> 00:37:50,979
- What?
- You'll have a little genius.

566
00:37:51,062 --> 00:37:53,062
Yes. We're going to name them...

567
00:37:55,021 --> 00:37:55,854
What?

568
00:37:58,271 --> 00:37:59,229
Ibiza.

569
00:38:01,479 --> 00:38:03,479
My God, I love it. Ibiza.

570
00:38:03,562 --> 00:38:04,771
I love it.

571
00:38:04,854 --> 00:38:06,021
Call them Ibiza...

572
00:38:07,312 --> 00:38:09,979
and you know
you'll have so much fun together.

573
00:38:10,062 --> 00:38:12,771
Fuck, they'll be so popular at school.

574
00:38:12,854 --> 00:38:15,146
But it's not a city, it's an island.

575
00:38:15,229 --> 00:38:18,437
Do you know what other rule
we're going to break?

576
00:38:18,521 --> 00:38:19,937
Not seeing each other.

577
00:38:20,021 --> 00:38:21,562
You'll be their aunt.

578
00:38:22,604 --> 00:38:23,979
Look, you know what?

579
00:38:24,062 --> 00:38:25,729
You'll be their godmother.

580
00:38:26,729 --> 00:38:27,562
Yes, darling.

581
00:38:29,896 --> 00:38:32,271
- I'm so looking forward to it.
- So am I.

582
00:38:33,604 --> 00:38:34,562
So am I.

583
00:38:38,937 --> 00:38:40,271
I can't believe it.

584
00:38:41,437 --> 00:38:43,187
What?

585
00:38:43,646 --> 00:38:45,271
- Ibiza, right?
- Of course.

586
00:38:45,354 --> 00:38:48,271
No more spending Christmas
alone with Helsinki.

587
00:38:48,354 --> 00:38:50,562
He doesn't know any Christmas carols.

588
00:38:50,646 --> 00:38:53,854
From now on,
Christmas will be spent with family.

589
00:38:53,937 --> 00:38:56,229
- What's going on?
- What are you doing?

590
00:38:56,312 --> 00:38:59,896
Party for a single mother.

591
00:39:01,021 --> 00:39:02,104
Are you pregnant?

592
00:39:02,187 --> 00:39:06,646
- Yes! No, after the heist.
- I didn't know you had a boyfriend.

593
00:39:06,729 --> 00:39:08,146
Me neither.

594
00:39:08,229 --> 00:39:10,354
- What?
- It's a friend with benefits.

595
00:39:10,437 --> 00:39:12,229
Want to know the baby's name?

596
00:39:13,062 --> 00:39:14,479
- Ibiza!
- Ibiza!

597
00:39:27,604 --> 00:39:29,271
Mutt.

598
00:39:39,854 --> 00:39:42,937
I want you all against the wall.
Lower your weapons.

599
00:39:43,937 --> 00:39:46,021
I'd ask you to put them on the ground,

600
00:39:46,104 --> 00:39:50,271
but I know myself. If I see you unarmed,
I might get carried away.

601
00:39:50,354 --> 00:39:53,021
So let's show some mutual respect.

602
00:39:54,646 --> 00:39:55,479
Lower them.

603
00:39:55,562 --> 00:39:56,812
Come on.

604
00:39:58,104 --> 00:40:00,104
I'm aiming at her head.

605
00:40:00,812 --> 00:40:03,229
I have a bulletproof vest.
She's tied up.

606
00:40:03,604 --> 00:40:05,229
You won't get me.

607
00:40:05,312 --> 00:40:06,604
Come on, let's go.

608
00:40:13,354 --> 00:40:15,271
Lower the fucking gun, idiot!

609
00:40:15,354 --> 00:40:16,604
Didn't you hear me?

610
00:40:21,104 --> 00:40:22,146
That's it.

611
00:40:22,854 --> 00:40:24,854
Slowly.

612
00:40:30,229 --> 00:40:31,729
Shall we dance?

613
00:40:31,812 --> 00:40:33,271
Come on, let's dance.

614
00:40:39,104 --> 00:40:40,604
You're falling, darling.

615
00:40:41,104 --> 00:40:42,437
Sorry.

616
00:40:44,146 --> 00:40:46,687
Look at your big man. Hello, big man.

617
00:40:47,437 --> 00:40:48,437
That's enough.

618
00:40:49,437 --> 00:40:50,604
Let her go now.

619
00:40:50,687 --> 00:40:52,896
Take it easy.

620
00:40:53,604 --> 00:40:55,104
Easy.

621
00:40:55,187 --> 00:40:57,896
I'm about to let her go. Take it easy.

622
00:40:57,979 --> 00:40:59,479
I'm about to let her go.

623
00:40:59,562 --> 00:41:01,062
Here we go.

624
00:41:07,937 --> 00:41:09,062
That's it.

625
00:41:20,812 --> 00:41:21,854
Mutt.

626
00:41:30,729 --> 00:41:32,729
I said I was going to kill you.

627
00:41:34,854 --> 00:41:36,187
No!

