Professor!
Tell me where the gold is.
I don't know.
Asshole.
I thought as much.
Look.
This is your doing.
Look him in the eye!
Tell the kid that,
on top of his endless list of crimes,
he'll get five dead soldiers added to it.
Life sentence. Tell him!
How old are you, boy?
I'm 23.
Those are the only years of freedom
you'll ever see.
Thanks to you.
Like Stockholm. Look at her.
Look at her, you piece of shit!
When she gets out,
her son will be a 45-year-old man.
Do you enjoy causing all this suffering,
you son of a bitch? Do you?
Same as Denver.
Got anything to say to him?
Tell him he's lost his son,
just like he lost his dad.
And in both instances
the same person was responsible, you!
Did you really love her?
Well, look at her.
I want you to think of this face
every day you spend in jail,
and that if you'd stayed away from her,
she'd still have a life,
a mother, a daughter.
She's got nothing now!
I don't care
what you plan to do with the fucking gold.
Because I won't even try to find it.
One of them will tell me.
Do you know why?
Because I'll offer a new life
to whoever tells me.
A life sentence or set for life.
One of you will make today
the happiest day of your life.
And mine!
I'm glad you're so happy,
because dark times are coming.
You don't get it, Tamayo.
What you believe to be the end of the game
is really just the beginning.
On your knees.
The Professor was playing
the biggest poker game in history.
But the craziest part
wasn't that he was bluffing.
It was that he didn't have any cards,
and the person who had to find the deck
didn't know where to start.
PALAWAN, PHILIPPINES
TWO MONTHS AFTER THE FIRST HEIST
After the heist at the Royal Mint,
the Professor was haunted by the guilt
of his brother's death.
He felt he had pushed him away
from the Bank of Spain heist
to pull off his own job.
And now he was dead.
After many sleepless nights,
he found solace in an obsession,
figuring out the impossible
Bank of Spain heist.
Maybe Berlin and Palermo
knew how to get the gold out.
But what was really impossible
to figure out
was something else.
We know how to get the gold out.
But how do you get out?
And more importantly, free.
I've been studying this for a long time.
The starting point is rather simple.
Step one.
Tell the truth
about how we got the gold out,
with your videos.
And we'll do it from Pakistan.
Shakir.
In eight minutes…
the show starts.
STATEMENT FROM THE GANG
Lovers and enthusiasts of the heist genre
and generally inquisitive minds, welcome.
We'll show you how to get the gold out
of a country's national reserve.
In this instance, Spain's.
Join us on this fascinating journey
to the depths
of the largest heist of all times.
They're broadcasting simultaneously
from hundreds of servers.
It's gone viral.
TV stations are streaming it live.
The robbers say they got the gold out
of the Bank of Spain.
They're explaining how they did it.
Spain may have lost its national reserve.
This changes everything.
…the vault would flood in minutes.
How do we fix that?
By welding this pipe
so a diver can get in.
They've made it entertaining
so everyone in Spain gets it.
…one of the greatest heroes of this heist.
How are you?
How many ingots did you take out?
So many. 7,258.
27.5 pounds each. 600,000 euros.
That's about 4,355 million euros.
-Lots of dough.
-Anything else you'd like to add?
-I want to say "hi" to my kids.
-Go ahead.
My dear children, Emilio in Venezuela,
Julián in Mexico City,
Erik in Iceland.
Hanna in Finland…
It's on CNN.
…Ivana in Odessa.
Dad sends you all kisses.
A moving story.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you want
to know how we got 90 tons of gold
out of the Bank of Spain,
stay tuned
and wait for our next installments.
NEW INSTALLMENTS COMING SOON
This could be serious.
I know what you're doing.
You want to cause a financial crisis,
put the country on the ropes,
and blackmail me with it.
Bad news. I've got the support
of the European Central Bank
to inject cash or buy debt.
I can also halt stock-exchange trading.
What do we think?
I don't give a flying fuck
about your financial storm.
And step two?
2. THE CASINO
Financial markets operate
like a large betting shop.
You can gamble on anything.
On the NYSE rising, on wheat dropping,
or on a country collapsing.
You can bet and make a lot of money.
It's perfectly legal.
And what are we going to offer
those funding bodies and corporations
in search of a victim to profit from?
Assurance.
When we tell them
the gold is outside the bank,
betting against Spain
will be their winning horse.
At the same time,
that panic will drive investors
to sell Spanish debt and shares
in huge quantities,
which will make
the stock market tumble.
And more importantly,
the risk premium
will skyrocket to over 800 points.
What does that mean?
Spain won't be able to get funds
from the markets,
will become insolvent
and therefore bankrupt.
Exactly.
And this domino effect
will put huge pressure on the government.
And we'll be the only ones
who can stop it,
all with a single move.
Giving back the gold.
What?
Wait a minute, I don't think I got it.
Are you telling me that my life
depends on a goddamn betting shop?
On the market crashing?
What if it doesn't?
It always does, Denver.
It happened in Greece.
It's the very nature of the system.
It's designed to react like that.
-And it's predictable.
-Predictable?
A tunnel is predictable.
You go in one side and out the other.
That's predictable,
but this is out of our control.
-Denver, please.
-Don't "Denver, please" me.
He can't play with our lives like that.
Listen up.
That won't work.
You came in here
to make sure nobody came out
so you could finish your extortion.
Well, now that we all know
that the economic conspiracy
is a bunch of fucking humbug,
know what I'm gonna do?
I'm going to interrogate you one by one.
And those who won't talk
will go through that door,
straight to a life sentence.
In front of the TV cameras and barefaced,
so there's no going back.
Each one of us you take out,
I swear, equals ten tons of gold
you'll never get back.
Son of a bitch.
I said you couldn't play that card.
-Shut up. The game isn't over.
-"Shut up?"
-Denver.
-What?
Shut up.
You want me to shut up?
We're all here, on our knees,
with a goddamn rifle pointed at our necks
because we listened to a nutcase!
Quiet, Denver!
-I won't shut up!
-Shut up now!
Separate those two
from the rest of the gang.
Denver.
You go first.
Denver, remember what I told you!
Someone stole the gold.
If anyone finds out, it's over.
I swear on our son's life
I'll get you out of here.
Denver, don't do anything.
Denver, listen to me.
Denver, remember what I told you!
While the gang was on the ropes…
This pump extracts aggregates
from the seabed.
They were able to send it upstream
with this pump.
…Ángel thought
he had discovered the truth.
We were searching in the wrong direction.
But that truth was just part
of the Tom Thumb Plan.
I need eight men at the door,
right now. Let's go.
Where the fuck would you hide
90 tons of gold, Benjamín?
In a forest?
Or a wasteland.
Or an abandoned area nobody ever goes to.
We need to think like an MIT engineer.
Minimize risk.
And minimizing risk means
that we have to make sure
no idiots will come by looking
for bottle caps with a metal detector.
There's only one way to do that,
by restricting access to it.
Private property.
Exactly.
Private property
relatively close to the stormwater tank.
They knew the plan very well,
but with Berlin being dead,
they couldn't have imagined
the heist would actually happen.
Fuck!
They took action
as soon as the heist began.
We have to find a plot
bought in the last five days.
All roads lead to the same place.
The land register.
We need to be armed when we go in.
This can be your new identity.
And there's more.
Three million euros for a fresh start
without any financial hardship.
You can buy a house with a hot tub,
throw some parties,
in the country of your choice.
And a lifetime allowance of 25,000 euros
a month at the expense of the government.
A premium retiree.
What do you think?
And what about my family?
We can make an exception. Two for one.
Tell me where the gold is
and Stockholm, you,
and the kid you've got out there
can get a fresh start.
Okay, but I don't know where the gold is.
I really don't know.
You know something.
I need an informer
to give me all the plan details.
You get your freedom
and I find the gold later.
I know it's tough,
but you don't even need
to say it out loud.
Just write down, right here,
what Raquel Murillo
doesn't want you to tell me.
Just a simple answer
for a life of freedom.
A fucking life of freedom.
"One, two, buckle my shoe.
Three, four, shut the door."
"Five, six, balls and dicks."
Put that in the GPS
and it'll take you straight to the gold.
-Get out now!
-Great.
Three million in cash, please.
I hate going to the ATM.
-Take him away.
-I want a house in the Dominican Republic.
Let's go! Get in there!
Stop moving.
Stop moving!
I love you.
Come on.
This is your future.
I'll give you a moment to picture it
and I'll come back for the next one.
MADRID, FIVE YEARS EARLIER
Sergio, why are you planning a heist?
It suits my dad, right?
But you, with all that knowledge…
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Why does it suit me?
You're the definition of a hedonist.
You need your time
to enjoy art, love, travel…
I don't think
you'd have time left to work.
-So, enjoying life doesn't suit me?
-Wait a minute.
Robbery isn't only a job, which it is.
It's a family tradition for us.
It's important that you remember that.
There are families of doctors, right?
Families of lawyers.
Families who honor a profession.
Your grandfather started this family line.
How did it go in Denmark?
An exquisite swap.
Where were you when grandpa died?
In the kitchen.
The radio said
a robber had been shot down.
Grandma froze,
with the fridge door wide open.
Suddenly,
she came and hugged me…
and then and there, I knew it was my dad.
Then the fridge started to beep.
Did you also find out like that?
No.
Yes, you were there.
You had just come back from the hospital.
It was one of the few times
you weren't hospitalized.
-I was there, but I already knew.
-What?
That morning, a noise woke me up.
I jumped out of bed, in my pajamas.
I went to the courtyard window
and I saw Dad.
He was loading the trunk.
I thought, "Fishing gear."
He promised me that,
when I got out of the hospital,
he'd take me fishing with him.
So I quickly got dressed
and ran down after him.
I ran down the stairs.
Dad!
I missed him by three seconds.
By three seconds!
So I grabbed your bike.
And I pedaled as fast as I could.
Dad!
I saw the car in the distance.
I was getting closer.
He stopped at a light
and when I was about to catch up with him,
it turned green.
Dad!
He got away again.
When I saw him in the distance,
he switched cars.
And after five or six minutes…
I saw the car, but no one was in it.
And then…
I heard two gunshots.
I was scared to death.
And then I saw Dad coming out of the bank.
Don't move or I'll shoot! Get down!
And he saw me.
They started yelling at him, "Kneel down!"
-Kneel down!
-"Kneel down."
On your knees, now!
Get down on the ground!
But he didn't, Andrés.
Because he was looking at me.
And then…
BANK OF SPAIN
That's how I found out.
And what did you do?
Nothing. I rode home.
I was there when you got home.
Yes.
Why didn't you say anything?
Because for me, it was like a movie.
Your grandpa told robbery
and heist stories as if they were movies.
So,
while riding back home, I thought…
"This is a movie."
"If I don't say anything,
it'll always be one."
And it worked,
until it came on the radio.
When you ask me why I plan heists,
the answer is simple.
To talk to him.
He told me about his dream
to rob the Royal Mint that same night.
We laughed so hard.
"Can you imagine a machine
that can make money?"
I'm the one telling him movie stories now.
"Dad, what do you think about this part
of the plan? See any weak points?"
I talk to him often.
I talk more with him
than with any living creature.
-Shoot.
-Colonel.
We found the Professor's hideout.
No trace of the gold.
They burnt everything.
Fuck, give me some good news.
It seems they melted the gold
back into ingots
so they could carry it in trucks.
Colonel, those trucks can be traced.
Talk with Interpol.
Issue an international warrant
and activate all European satellites.
We're going to fucking find them.
Okay.
PASAJES PORT, 3:07 A.M.
Those trucks were part
of the breadcrumbs
Marseille was leaving behind.
It was a criminal trail
leading to a non-existent loot
that would help drive the police crazy.
So?
The European Central Bank
won't back us.
They're very skeptical…
after how we've managed the crisis.
And what does that mean?
Minister?
They'll let us collapse.
The stock market has plummeted
14% in three hours.
That will be a joke compared
to what will happen at nine
when the markets open.
You've got the brains of the operation.
He's on his knees,
surrendered and handcuffed.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
You, get out of here.
Son of a bitch!
No!
-You're wrong about me.
-Tamayo!
If you cross that line,
there's no turning back.
Look who's talking.
Watch this.
I'm smashing your face in
to make one thing clear.
You won't have an autopsy.
I'll destroy you
in front of your girlfriend,
and I won't stop
until either you tell me where the gold is
or you die.
Because either I win or no one does.
Stop!
What if you're wrong
about what winning means?
Picture yourself a few months from now,
at home,
listening to the unemployment figures,
the debt maturities.
The entire country
has plunged into deep bankruptcy
in an unprecedented crisis,
in absolute chaos.
Which Tamayo would have won more?
The one who put us in jail?
The one who killed us but lost the gold?
Or the one who got it back and stopped
the biggest financial collapse in history?
Listen to me.
Tamayo.
I know you'll struggle to grasp this.
Really, I do.
But right now, we only have one choice.
Just one.
Either we both win…
or we both lose.
I don't know where the gold is. I don't.
I don't. Lisbon doesn't. My people don't.
What did you expect?
Why would I come in here
if I had that information?
Tamayo, you bury people in the desert.
You would've gotten the information
out of us sooner or later.
I couldn't give that information
to anyone in the bank, not even myself.
That's the firewall.
The gold is out.
On the move.
So this is your last pathetic magic trick.
Ninety tons of gold out and about…
gracefully dancing around.
But you're right about one thing.
I don't know how I can win anymore.
Maybe both of us have to lose.
You and I are insignificant
compared to the upcoming economic tsunami.
Absolutely insignificant.
You know there's only one way out.
You know it.
LAND REGISTRY, 6:50 A.M.
Good morning.
The auction begins.
BACK IN 2 HOURS
Who's been working here
for more than 15 years?
More than 20?
Twenty-two?
Sold.
Come with me.
Today you get to experience
something you've seen on TV,
collaborating with an armed group.
But there's no risk
because you've been coerced.
Thrilling, huh?
Yes, ma'am.
Like in a treasure hunt,
everyone was looking for the gold.
Sierra knew the gold was the only way
to keep everyone out of jail.
It's here.
Ángel was running,
speeding along the same glimmering trail.
He had swallowed the bait whole.
Hello?
We've tracked down the trucks.
They're heading north, along Route 1.
They're at Pasajes port.
The Professor won't say a word, Ángel.
Get your ass there now.
I'm taking a helicopter.
Go!
Sergio.
Does it hurt?
What?
Your eyebrow's bleeding.
No. I'm fine.
I'm doing great.
I took a few punches, but…
You should see the other guy.
If he had stayed two more minutes…
-He'd be dead.
I don't doubt it.
I'm glad you don't.
The last time we talked
I think you called me a coward.
And you told me to shut up.
True.
We argue a lot during heists, don't we?
Maybe we should quit.
It's not as easy as canceling
a library card. You need money.
You can't be on the most-wanted list
in 130 countries…
You need a new identity.
And right now, my face
is in no condition
to take a passport photo.
More importantly, you don't want to stop.
Tell me something.
After you got out of the Royal Mint,
how long did it take you
to start thinking about this heist?
Forty-eight hours.
Perhaps 24.
I owed it to my brother.
Right, you and your tributes
to dead relatives.
Some people throw ashes in the sea,
others bring flowers to the cemetery.
You steal the national reserve.
You know what?
You don't do it for your father
or your brother.
You do it for yourself.
No, it's my way of talking to them.
How? With a Ouija board?
No.
That's just inside your head
because you need to hide
everything behind a mask.
Because you love masks.
You live life
pretending to have an inferiority complex,
with your glasses, your origami…
But the truth is…
The truth is…
you walk right into the bank,
confident that you're going to arm-wrestle
an entire country.
You're your own magic trick, Sergio.
In your Clark Kent costume.
But it's about time you take it off
and accept who you really are.
Will you marry me?
Did I say it right this time? Fuck.
I just let it slip out again,
like at the motor home.
-I can't believe it…
-No.
It was good.
And?
Yes.
Yes, I will.
Let's get them.
Despite the setbacks,
they really do love each other.
A total of 612 purchases
have gone through in the last five days.
Mr. Anselmo Bueno Gutiérrez
sold an urban plot--
No, wait. Let's keep it short.
Only read the ones purchased in cash,
without a mortgage.
That narrows down my search a lot.
But would you please
stop pointing the gun at me?
-Benjamín.
-Oops, sorry.
Here, Ms. María Flores González
purchased a plot in Robledo de Chavela.
The seller is Rosario Pineda Hernández.
The plot covers an area of 3,189…
While Alicia Sierra realized she
was running out of time to find the gold…
TOM THUMB PLAN
…the police were starting
to see the light.
Our man in the shadows will leave
lots of breadcrumbs in his path.
Marseille, go to the stormwater tank.
Start the Tom Thumb Plan.
At 11:07 the night before,
they prepared
an Oscar-winning crime scene.
The cargo on the red trucks
had been transported.
At 8:10 in the morning,
Ángel had made an amazing discovery.
I've got images of some guys
loading pallets from trucks
onto a fishing boat.
-A fishing boat?
-Breadcrumbs.
To find them, they'll have use
their satellites, NATO allies, Interpol.
They'll scan all the traffic cameras
in Spain, and all that will…
erase their doubts.
Zoom in.
Zoom in here, on the main screen.
Those bastards.
They're loading the gold onto a boat.
Because the harder the route is
and the more it takes to traverse it,
the more you believe
that what you'll find is the real deal.
That's why Tamayo didn't hesitate.
The cornerstone of the investigation
was the Virgen del Carmen IV,
an anchovy fishing boat
in the Cantabrian Sea.
Where did that boat go?
I don't know. They turned off the GPS.
And once they have no clue
what our route is,
they'll discover another strange event.
Kidnapping at sea.
The boat has surfaced in Cantabria.
It's 107 miles away, with the captain
and crew tied up in the cabins.
I'm on my way.
What did you say? Tied up?
Many things need to be happening at once,
so they don't have time to stop and think.
Tell me what happened.
Well, we sailed
for about three or four hours.
Then we heard some noises on the deck,
as if someone was fishing.
What noises?
The winch,
like they were emptying the hold.
Emptying it, where?
At sea. They were throwing
the bundles into the sea.
Don't fuck with me. That makes no sense.
They would move it to another boat,
not throw it in the sea.
I don't know. There must be a reason.
And that question…
is important.
It'll be answered by forensics.
Everything was burnt.
The few things we could rescue
were pieces of nautical cartography.
They show the Bay of Biscay,
but the radius is too big.
-How big?
-About 30 to 40 nautical miles.
-There's something else.
-What's that?
A depth-buoy diagram.
It says that it's 230 feet
under the surface.
The buoys could be marking something
anchored to the seabed.
And then,
with all the information spread out
on the table, what seemed crazy
will suddenly make sense.
Where is the only place
you can leave tons of gold unattended
for centuries
without being discovered?
Where are all the lost treasures
of Spanish galleons?
At the bottom of the sea?
At the bottom of the sea.
Here's the buoy.
We need to mobilize the Navy.
I want frigates, battleships,
aircraft carriers, everything!
Let's comb the Cantabrian Sea!
CANTABRIAN SEA
We're changing directions. New course,
the Bay of Biscay. Start tracking.
Tamayo was trying really hard
to hide the fact that the gold
had already left the bank.
He thought the best way to do so
was by pretending we were still fighting.
Fire at will!
We can hear shots
coming from the Bank of Spain.
The shooting continues,
but we're getting no information
about what's going on.
Shots?
Yes. Fuck yes!
-Do you hear that?
-Shut up!
-Do you know what that means?
-Get down!
It's a fucking smoke screen.
A smoke screen
or they just executed the Professor.
We have to hold out hope.
The Professor's here
because we're getting out.
You put the Professor on a pedestal.
Let's stay positive.
Here it comes, the positivity of fools.
Shit, take a look around.
How many clips do you have?
But if you want to stay positive,
we can use a kung-fu hold
and before you know it,
we're on the subway.
Positive thinking
has been the downfall of civilization.
I may even beat you up,
optimistic as I am.
And do you know why?
I was inside a tomb in Algeria.
All I could do was imagine
that I'd get out, and here I am.
You are here
because I got involved in all this.
And him.
And him over there.
Understood?
Well, I agree with Rio.
I've been in a war all my fucking life.
And I want peace.
So, I'll think about…
a positive future.
No one has ever loved me.
I've never had a serious relationship.
I think that it's time.
Are we in jail, properly arrested,
waiting to be judged?
Are you dead inside a plastic bag?
No, right?
Why do you think that is?
What do you know that I don't?
I'm just looking at the signs, friend.
We've been held captive for 24 hours
and we're still alive.
Denver is outside.
He's been arrested.
That's a sign.
It's irreversible.
He knows something.
It's just a bit
of positive thinking, friends.
The last thing Tamayo needed
was a video showing the world
everything he was trying to hide.
We're keeping our promise.
How did we get the gold out?
It was thanks to this baby.
This pump propelled the gold
11 miles away from here,
where our team outside received the grit,
melted it again
and turned it into ingots.
That's the blatant proof
that we don't have the gold.
In today's treasury auction,
we're bound to lose billions of euros,
week after week,
until we won't be able to get any funding.
At that exact moment,
the country will go bankrupt.
Shut it down.
I don't care if it's been open
for three minutes. Stop it!
The Professor was right.
Everything's going to shit.
And then, when everyone thought
the Spanish economy
couldn't be discredited any further…
-Hey!
-…the final image was broadcast.
We could have been lying.
But to see the Navy combing
the sea in search of gold
was the official acknowledgment
of the success of our heist.
Who the fuck tipped off the press?
Multiply everything I just said by ten.
That'll be the end of the Tom Thumb Plan.
And that's when…
That's when we'll be
in a position to negotiate.
No dirt has been moved in some time.
The garden is well kept.
How many left?
One. It's 4.3 miles away.
Let's go.
It's a country house from 1926,
built in stone.
This one is prefab, right?
The lawn.
What do we do now?
Should we all shoot on the count of three?
Perfect.
Nobody is listening.
-I guess you've got a plan.
-You're going to give a press conference.
And you'll say the police investigation
has found the gold.
If I do that, you leave me high and dry.
If I leave you high and dry,
you'll stop trusting me.
-That's not good for anyone.
-It's not a matter of trust.
It's a matter of life and death.
Suárez, Cañizo, go ahead.
Stand up!
Now.
What the fuck is happening, Palermo?
No fucking clue, Manila.
The smallest trick and I'll give the order
to have them executed.
-Did you hear me, Suárez?
-Yes.
Now you know the game we're playing,
do you really want me to go out
and talk to the press?
I told you, either we both win…
or we both lose.
I know the plan
to steal the Bank of Spain's gold.
And what I don't know, I figure out.
You want to use the gold
as a bargaining chip, right?
But I won't let that happen.
Because the true miracle
was getting it out.
And that already happened.
You must be the Professor's nephew.
Rafael.
Your uncle asked me to give you this.
Good morning.
I apologize for the short notice,
but I have an important announcement.
The police investigation has paid off.
We've intercepted two trucks
carrying the Bank of Spain's gold.
-What?
-Where?
-Please.
-And you'll say more.
That I came into the bank
to negotiate the gang's surrender
and stop anything worse from happening.
He went down to the bank's basement,
157 feet deep,
where the robbers are still entrenched,
fending off the attacks
of the State Security Forces.
You'll wrap it up with a message
of trust and transparency.
As soon as you appear on TV,
those trucks will start moving.
You can escort them
along the Northern Highway.
How can you give the order
while arrested and handcuffed?
It won't be me.
You, on TV,
reading that statement, are the order.
It's part of the plan.
You'll have won
and everyone will see that.
Dramatic effect.
The gold returns to the Bank of Spain
and the stock market settles.
The government and economists agree
the debt crisis is now under control
and it may recover as fast as it fell.
Civil servants from the Bank of Spain
and the State Security Forces
are now unloading the ingots
to put them all back in the vault.
What are those trucks?
It's part of the plan.
Part of the plan I don't know?
Not every secret is told in bed.
What does that mean?
-Relax.
-I can't relax.
Things I don't know about are happening.
It was necessary.
You can fool everyone but me, Sergio.
I don't get it.
You would never go back in there
to surrender the gold.
Ever.
-Of course not. I'll go in to rescue Rio.
-Sure, right. What a nice guy.
Why don't you tell me
that part of the plan?
None of those going into the bank
can know the last part of the plan.
I understand that.
But then I'm out.
Martín.
What's a country's gold?
Its wealth?
No.
It's an illusion.
It's totally useless.
Spain doesn't pay for anything
with that gold. Not one transaction.
It's a psychological backup.
Gold for brass.
Will you do to the Bank of Spain
what Berlin did with the Viking treasure?
-How did it go in Denmark?
-An exquisite swap.
Out!
The ingots in those trucks
are made of gold-coated brass.
I warned you.
Suárez, Cañizo, aim!
Aim!
Tamayo, wait.
Those ingots have stopped
the debt catastrophe.
Weren't you Robin Hood?
And you're stealing a country's gold?
I'm a thief.
The son of a thief.
The brother of a thief.
Someday, I hope to be a thief's father.
We can't deny our nature, Tamayo.
I'm giving you an honorable way out.
Think about it, Colonel.
It's almost funny.
Don't tell me it doesn't fit in
with Spanish tradition.
What other country could have
a national reserve of brass
and still be one
of the most important world economies?
The Spanish guile.
Lazarillo de Tormes
wasn't written by the English,
was it?
Tamayo,
you'll be a hero.
A hero.
This tiny, metallic difference
will be just another state secret.
It'll pass down from president to
president for the next 50, 60 or 70 years,
and deep down…
it won't matter. Nothing will happen.
-Load your weapons.
-Load!
No, Tamayo. Don't!
Did you think you were going to walk out
and leave me a national reserve of brass?
Tell me where the gold is.
-Ten.
-Ten!
The brass reserve
is your best option right now.
-Nine.
-You can't do it, Colonel. You can't.
-Eight.
-Eight!
If they shoot,
I'll prove what you have is junk!
-Seven.
-I've got videos, documents.
-Everything will instantly go public.
-Six.
Know what that means?
Debt will skyrocket.
The stock market will plummet. No funding.
-Five.
-Five!
It'll be bankruptcy.
You won't have a plan B!
-Four.
-Four!
That brass is the best of all worlds!
-Three.
-Three!
Sergio!
Accept it.
The rest of the markets did.
The rest of the world did.
You have to accept it.
-Two.
-Two!
You'll never find it, you hear me?
It's not up to me.
The plan follows its course.
The gold is to protect the gang,
the ones inside and the ones outside.
-It'll never be returned.
-One!
If you shoot,
you'll only have the dead and bankruptcy.
I've said it once and I'll say it again,
either we both win or we both lose!
Colonel,
it's time you accept it.
It's checkmate.
Good morning.
The heist is over.
The Army's Special Forces
have managed to take the bank's basement
with the use of explosives,
therefore releasing the last hostages.
HOSTAGES RELEASED FROM THE BANK OF SPAIN
During the operation,
and after strong resistance,
the following robbers were shot down.
Aníbal Cortés, AKA Rio.
Santiago López, AKA Bogotá.
Julia Martínez, AKA Manila.
POLICE TAKE DOWN ROBBERS
Matías Caño, AKA Pamplona.
Mirko Dragic, AKA Helsinki.
Mónica Gaztambide, AKA Stockholm.
Martín Berrotti, AKA Palermo.
Raquel Murillo, AKA Lisbon.
And Sergio Marquina, AKA the Professor.
The police investigation that led
to the recovery of the national reserve
was decisively propelled forward
with the cooperation
of Daniel Ramos, AKA Denver,
who will be under witness protection
until all legal actions have concluded.
No one chases a dead person, Colonel.
The real gold is our hostage.
If you don't want the biggest state secret
to come to light,
this chase ends here and now.
For good.
THE DREAM ISN'T OVER
What you're really wondering
is what happened to the real gold.
He would've wanted this.
Are you sure he'll give you your share?
Yes.
It's a family matter.
24 HOURS LATER
We're alive.
-You have to believe, brother.
-Always.
Thank you.
I almost blew it.
Good thing the Professor
always has a backup plan.
You bastards.
I didn't say a word, all right?
It didn't all turn out
the way we wanted it to.
We're not all here.
But…
We got something out of it all.
Come on.
I think you have something for me.
Lucía?
And Victoria's.
Where's the gold?
It's already in Portugal.
In a small house.
The little treasure house.
When this story began,
nobody could've imagined
that we'd end up being escorted
and hidden by an elite military team.
That the mission would be making sure
we had a new life without anyone knowing.
A new life, a free life,
loaded with gold.
So no member of the gang
had to rob a bank ever again.
OUR LEGACY CONTINUES THANKS TO ALL OF YOU,
THE REAL RESISTANCE.
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick