- Rise and shine, baby.
- Good morning, my queen.
- Wanna fuck?
- Sure, of course I do. First, come look.
Look.
They're Brazilians. Hasn't it been a while
since we've seen Brazilians?
I think the last people we saw
were from Puerto Rico or Guyana.
No idea.
They seem nice, no?
CIA, FBI,
Interpol… they've all got agents
that seem nice too.
Come on. They're tourists.
Take one look and you can tell.
My love.
We need to get a social life.
I'm being serious.
Couples have a social life.
They go out, see friends, go to dinner.
They don't hang out all day with the Kuna,
laying on the beach.
- No.
- "No" what?
No way.
Please, come on.
Absolutely not.
Tokyo, look, it's not safe.
Hey!
Hello, mis amigos!
Rio! Rio! Rio!
DAY THREE
Aníbal Cortés is here,
walking towards the Bank of Spain.
The police are handing over one
of the most wanted fugitives in the world.
It's only been 44 hours
since the heist began
and the police are already giving in.
They're handing over Cortés,
the man who was allegedly tortured.
The Professor's gang is reunited.
Rio is at the entrance
of the bank.
Now it's your turn.
Doors.
Helsinki,
all clear.
Advance!
HOSTAGE SWAP AT THE BANK OF SPAIN
You look so handsome!
Look at you, tie and everything!
It was the only nice thing
the police did for me.
I can imagine.
You look beautiful
in that red jumpsuit.
How are you?
- Better now.
- Really?
What the fuck are you doing
in the Bank of Spain?
We came to rescue you.
It's over now, son.
You're back home, my friends!
All of Spain is standing with you!
Look at this bravery! So much bravery!
Don't worry. You're with me now.
You're all with me.
Let's see what Suárez has to say.
Where is he? Suárez!
- Get me back there!
- Calm down.
I need more men! Explosives!
We were this close! I'm gonna kill them!
- Can we calm down, please?
- Tamayo!
Isn't this your little friend?
That's Arturo Román. The former director
of the Royal Mint of Spain.
Shut the doors!
That motherfucker!
Don't shoot, don't shoot! I'm unarmed.
I'm Arturo Román.
Arturito?
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
Whoo!
Come on, everyone! Round of applause!
Hey, you're Arturo Román, yeah?
Obviously.
I… I read your book.
Fucking psychos!
You could be out there,
living the good life.
Instead, you're here,
in the fucking lion's den.
Have you seen that shit outside?
Shut up and come hug your Helsi!
You may be completely fucking nuts, Helsi,
but you're a big softy.
Hey!
- What should I call you, Mónica?
- No, Stockholm.
Looking great. Brother!
How high did you have to be
to end up here?
The life of a millionaire
is boring anyway.
Thank you, man.
The fact that you're here, after all
you've lost, is fucking incredible.
NAIROBI: Oh, my baby!
- My little baby! I could eat your face.
- What's up gorgeous?
I feel like I gave birth to you myself.
You're all fucking amazing.
Yeah, we're fucking amazing.
But the real rock star here
is your girlfriend, the ugly one.
- If it wasn't for her…
- Okay.
You'll have to excuse me,
but now… it's my turn.
I'll be right back.
How are your men?
Positive for halothane.
But there are no traces
of anything else. We're all fine.
Glad to hear. They won this battle,
but not the war.
So chins up, for fuck's sake!
And one more thing.
This operation never happened.
- Understand?
- Are you serious?
That kind of command isn't even worthy
of a unit in Burkina Faso.
How about a bit of respect?
This won't go any further than it has.
No victims, we rescued 40 hostages,
so let's try to be positive
and just keep moving forward.
Yeah, I'm being positive.
Look at this. I'm super positive.
The problem is we never learn our lesson.
This guy's the Einstein of heists,
so we decide to send agents in
through the toilets.
Everything we've done
was strictly necessary.
What did the Navy Seals do
when they hunted down Bin Laden?
The Russians in the Dubrovnik?
What they had to.
Exactly, we're following the manual.
How long did it take us
to make this decision?
Twenty minutes?
Because this guy has been thinking
of the answers for years.
Every move we've made so far,
he's had a response ready.
These types of operations
always have the risks. Always.
Unless you care to enlighten us
with a proposal that doesn't have any.
Not one,
no less the three.
Antoñanzas, donuts.
Mónica.
- You look beautiful.
- I'm Stockholm.
Sit there.
Lift up your shirt.
Put your arms up.
Why are you here?
You could have been hurt.
I don't care.
Life hasn't meant shit to me
since I lost everything.
Laura left me and took the kids away.
I live in an apartment
with the kitchen inside the closet.
I have cans of tuna for dinner.
And all my stuff is still in boxes
in the hallway, but…
Well, I'm still trying.
Bit by bit, Arturo.
Listen, I was terrible of both of you
I'll admit that.
Believe me, Laura's on my mind, but…
But I always think about you.
I can't stop thinking about you.
About you and our son.
The kid's a boy, right?
Yes, he's a boy. Put this on.
I know I fucked up, Mónica.
But I don't wanna lose my son.
You lost him the moment
you said you weren't his father.
Put on the jumpsuit, please.
What did you expect?
Think about how fucked up it is
to tell a married guy with three kids,
"Look at this pregnancy test.
This kid is yours." I was terrified.
Yeah, I was fucking scared to death but…
Who wouldn't be scared by that?
But it was only three minutes.
Three minutes of complete insanity
right after those terrorists came in
and started shooting up the whole place.
Please, don't judge me
for those three minutes.
And I know I have no right
to just show up out of nowhere…
ask you to let me be
the father of our son.
I know.
But I'd like to see him, that's all.
Just to hug him, you know?
See what he's like.
I don't care where he is.
I'd go all the way to Brazil,
Romania, Burma, Thailand… wherever!
He's my son and I just wanna meet him.
Please.
Even if you deserve that,
I don't know if I'll be able to.
I'll try, all right?
Thank you.
Some things never change, huh?
Look.
What?
Look at me, look at this.
- God, Arturo.
- Look. Come here.
I know you still think about me.
About how we fucked on my desk.
I know you still want it.
I know you want it.
Touch me again and you're a dead man.
You're disgusting, Arturo!
You disgust me.
I disgust you? I disgust you?
Shoot me!
Shoot me right here.
If you don't, this will be
the only face our kid ever sees.
They'll put you away with Denver
and you'll never see the light of day.
Arturito Junior will never know
who his mother was.
He'll call me Papa! Me!
His real father!
That's why I came here, you understand?
My son is called Cincinnati.
And you'll never meet him
in your fucking life!
Helsinki, finish this.
Arturito.
Relax.
You remember… men look after men.
Let's go. Take off your clothes.
♪ I want you ♪
♪ Oh, and I want you ♪
♪ But that's all the reason for me
For me, for I want you ♪
♪ Oh, I want you ♪
Those were the happiest moments
of the heist.
And it may have been
the happiest moments in my life.
But happiness is like lightning.
Blink and you'll miss it.
After that came the fall.
When you reach heaven,
the fall is devastating.
We were all rushing
towards the edge of the abyss,
even the Professor.
Point number one, we're making
the very same mistake
we've made with the last heist
by choosing to go after the Professor.
He's a professional card sharp.
We need to change our strategy and focus
on the only thing we know that's inside.
The gold.
If we find out
how they plan to get it out,
they'll only be able
to negotiate one thing.
Their surrender. That's why
we'll interrogate all hostages.
No one is going home.
I wanna know if they're working.
How they're working. How many?
When? And finally…
Who is this? These two?
Because these new guys, right here,
are the key to the plan.
And most importantly, the compensation.
Shit, these guys
are handing out cash and what?
The state isn't offering anything?
I want to offer the biggest reward
in Western history.
Tamayo, how much do you think
a snitch would cost us?
- I don't know. Three million euros?
- Any higher bidders?
- Three and a half million.
- The auction's open!
Martínez.
- Four million?
- Four million.
- Five million!
- Shit, that's great! Antoñanzas?
Six million.
Suárez, you have a counteroffer?
Six million going once, going twice…
Eight!
Eight. Get paid and get laid.
If we round up,
we're talking ten million euros.
And for that kind of reward
any Spaniard would sell their own mother.
- Ángel, give me some good news.
- We've got something.
- Somebody saw them.
- Great!
A Civil Guard here raised the alarm.
We've narrowed down our search area
and the radio signal suggests movement.
They're close by.
- Where are you?
- In Aracena, Huelva.
In some kind of warehouse.
There's an RV. They were here, Colonel.
Looks like they left it in a hurry.
- Do you think this could be a trap?
- I don't think so.
I'm going in.
There's no one here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shit.
Shit, Colonel. This is some kind of
command center of something.
There are screens
and radio equipment everywhere.
I need the forensic in here now.
They had an accident yesterday
and some farmers helped them.
They've confirmed their identity, Colonel.
Great work, Ángel.
You got the army, the police
and whatever you need at your disposal.
Let's start the hunt.
I got you, fucker. I got you.
Colonel, give me a helicopter.
I'll be in charge of the hunt.
Let's go.
Inspector, they're talking
to the Professor.
Rio, I need you to answer
as precisely as possible.
Where did they keep you?
In a cell.
Very small.
Like a coffin. I couldn't sit.
I would stand the entire time.
- How many days?
- I don't know.
I lost track at the fourth or fifth day.
There wasn't any natural light.
Rio, can you continue?
Yeah.
What did they feed you?
Some sort of lumpy mush.
Maybe made from flour. And coffee.
Lots of coffee.
Thirty, forty, fifty coffees a day.
I was amped.
They deprived you of sleep.
Do you think that the coffee
had any other substance in it?
It's possible.
It tasted like shit.
Either way, I was drugged.
When they interrogated me,
they made me inhale this gas.
I don't know what the fuck it was.
When that happened,
at least I could leave the cell.
Sometimes I could even sit down.
Apart from when
they were interrogating you,
did they ever let you out for…
for anything?
Not even to shit.
They left me
covered in shit and piss for hours.
Days.
I don't know.
Did they ever
let you wash yourself?
The most they've ever did
was spray me with a hose.
And what was like, Rio?
First, they would hang me naked,
in chains.
Then, they'd aim the pressure hose at me.
"If you want this all to end,
just tell us where the Professor is."
Alicia kept saying that.
I swear to God, Professor…
if I'd known where the fuck you were
I would have said it.
Anyone would have.
You were afraid for your life, right?
I knew we weren't in Spain.
When the wind changed direction,
I could hear the call to prayer
from a mosque.
And I was completely convinced…
that they were gonna shoot me
and bury me in the desert.
Every day…
I'd wake up wondering if it was my last.
It's all over now, Rio.
Listen, I need you to tell me
exactly what happened
when they took you out of there.
They put me on a plane.
When we landed, they put me in a car
and they took me to a military hospital.
So… so how was last night?
The best sleep I've ever had.
They gave me some powerful shit
and I didn't open my eyes
until this morning,
when I was woken up by Alicia.
So, what now?
Where's my red jumpsuit?
If they hand over Rio, they'll probably
have implanted a microphone.
So if it's suspicious, the code phrase
will then be "small vacation."
Rest a bit more.
Someone prepare him a hot bath.
You've earned a small vacation.
A GPS beacon in a dental implant.
A mic hidden in the intramuscular
tissue of his skull, anywhere.
And whatever the cavity,
we'll teach you how to remove it.
Any volunteers?
I… I won't do it.
Is the shy guy afraid
of the little scalpel?
No. I have my principles.
It's just that I'm against
the suffering of animals.
But you're a soldier. You kill people.
What's the problem? I don't get it.
People are one thing,
animals are something else.
And I love animals.
An assassin and animal lover.
Can I believe whatever I want or
are you gonna tell me what to believe in?
You mean with loving animals?
That's it.
Oh, yes.
This is what I have to say.
If you truly love that pig,
you'll open it and take out the chip.
And with all the love in the world,
you'll eat it.
I won't cut the pig.
I can do the same with a dummy.
No. There's no dummy
because we need it to be real.
This is the best we can get
for simulating human tissue.
I was in the war.
With a dog, right here, next to me.
The whole time, with me.
People ran away,
but the dog stayed with me.
From then on, I promised.
I won't cut the pig.
Cut open the fucking pig!
You're a hit man.
Hey, hey, hey!
Back off!
You push me again and the tissue I'll cut
will be yours entirely.
From top to bottom.
Marseille. The scalpel.
- Both of you leave the room.
- Me?
It was his fault. He wouldn't cut the pig.
Get out.
- I can go but if I do--
- Right now.
Fine.
Okay then.
Okay, continuing from there.
I don't care who, but you have 15 minutes
to locate the chip and start surgery.
Tokyo, until we operate on Rio,
it's important that you behave normally.
And robbing the Bank of Spain,
is that normal?
They can't suspect we know.
You need to speak with Rio
the way you always do. Act naturally.
Talk about what you missed
about each other.
Do what you logically do.
Are you suggesting that we have sex?
Because Rio needs to be hugged.
Not fucked.
The police know you're together
and haven't seen each other in two months.
They need to think they have access
to your intimate moments, that way,
they won't suspect anything.
Tokyo.
They'll do what they have to do.
Seriously? Seriously,
all of this is necessary?
They had this poor kid two months
without sleep, stuck in a hole,
shitting and pissing himself,
thinking he was on fucking death row
and you use him like that?
This is the moment for us
to capture a piece that's fundamental.
Fundamental for winning this war.
To get control
of the microphone and trackers
they could have put in his body.
If they have to have sex,
even if they're not in the mood,
they have to do it.
You haven't realized
Tokyo hasn't answered you.
You're complaining more than she did.
That's the problem,
that I'm here.
And you'd prefer to do this alone.
Like a lone wolf.
Let's be clear about something.
What's happening?
Sergio, look at me. What's happening?
- What? Tell me.
- I feel like I'm betraying the gang.
What?
It's like I'm disrespecting
the heist.
My brother could do all this
and be in a relationship. Not me.
It's impossible. I can't, Raquel.
I'm a chess player.
Bobby Fischer would never have faced
Spassky with his girlfriend by his side.
I'm not here because I'm your girlfriend.
I'm here because I know the police
much better than you
and much better than anyone on this team.
You know the protocols,
how they negotiate, but so do I.
I got you last time, Raquel.
You got me last time. Did you?
I must be an idiot.
Because I thought
that we'd fallen in love.
Look, I have my mom and my daughter
in the Philippines
and every police is looking for them.
I never asked you to come with me.
What if this is just revenge, right?
Since the Philippines.
Since you got up
in the middle of the night,
dreaming of your brother.
And everything with Rio
is nothing but an excuse to avenge Berlin.
Is that it?
Do you know what happened?
You've totally fucked up my life.
Shit.
Come on, let's go.
♪ Di doo di doo dah ♪
♪ Oh di doo di doo dah ♪
♪ Melancholic and disillusioned ♪
♪ Di doo di doo dah ♪
♪ Oh di doo di doo dah ♪
♪ I've got a bit of tomboy in me ♪
DON'T SAY ANYTHING
♪ Oh di doo di doo di doo dah ♪
THEY IMPLANTED A MIC IN YOU
♪ I've never played with a doll ♪
FOLLOW MY LEAD
♪ Oh di doo di doo di doo dah ♪
What color do you think my underwear is?
Burgundy.
Black.
If you're wearing any.
What?
Bingo.
Antoñanzas, any news?
No, sir.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE SURGERY
♪ Oh di doo di doo di doo dah ♪
Rio and I always told the truth
when we fucked.
But you don't always want
to hear the truth.
Tokyo…
I can't be with you.
I've been thinking about it.
I realized I've always been following you
like a little dog.
In that cell, I discovered I was strong.
I used to be afraid.
I was terrified of living without you.
On the island, after only three days…
…I went crazy,
and that's a shitty way to live.
- I'd just be like that again.
- Rio.
Tokyo, this is your world.
- No.
- Yes, I'm really sorry.
I swear, but I don't wanna live
on your roller coaster.
That was the beginning
of my downfall.
Suddenly, I felt like a ship
that falls into the abyss
at the edge of the world.
And there, while falling,
you can only look up
and watch as what you love most
gets smaller and smaller.
If I had known that was
the last time we were gonna fuck,
I would've never let it end.
You're the person
I've loved most in my life.
And I know that I'm just 22.
But I'll feel the same way when I'm 70.
Rio, don't leave me, please.
Please, don't leave me.
Do you hear me? Don't leave me.
Don't leave.
You'll find someone much better than me.
- You're gorgeous and loaded.
- No.
In a few years, we'll run into each other
and I'll have two or three kids
and some shopping bags.
And you'll be
in a fancy convertible with some
hot Brazilian guy
or something like that, yeah.
We'll have a glass of wine
and laugh about this.
I wanna go back to the island with you.
Please.
DON'T BE AFRAID
Colonel, a drone
has located the Professor.
- You have a visual?
- Yes.
Put it on the screen.
Colonel Tamayo speaking.
Do you copy? Zoom in.
EMERGENCY
That's right, get in closer.
Get in closer. More.
- Ready?
- Ready.
No, no.
Shit. Pull up,
for fuck's sake! Get higher.
I wanna see where this bastard comes out.
Locate the end of that path.
I need to speak to you
about the escape protocol.
Take off those grandpa pajamas.
I think the protocol can wait.
That's perfectly fine.
No, no, no. Tell me.
Think of it as… ah…
a type of training exercise,
work-related, under pressure.
Very well. Um…
Point one.
Dispersal.
In the event that we're located,
our chances of escape double
if we separate.
And, well… we'll have to do so
very rapidly.
Raquel.
Be careful.
Stay alive or I'll kill you.
Very good on plan A.
And plan B?
Plan B?
I'm not hearing
the second part, Professor.
Um, part B. In the emergency backpacks,
we're gonna have to store money…
Uh-huh.
…a camouflage net,
a thermal blanket,
a gun.
The gun.
And water to last a minimum of 72…
Seventy-two hours.
Well, what's the name of the second part?
Since you give everything a name.
Epicenter.
- Everyone's thinks…
- Uh-huh.
…the fugitive
is always going to try to run away.
But we won't run away.
We're going to stay.
No matter what happens to us,
we'll be within a 500-meter radius
of where they're looking for us.
- The epicenter.
- The epicenter. Very good.
We'll be just a few meters away from them
and they won't find us
as long as we remain hidden
during the first four minutes.
How are we going to hide?
Seven, eight meters above ground.
In the treetops.
We'll use the same technique
that military snipers use to hide.
A perfect camouflage.
Class is over.
Raquel, you should be in position.
We have a problem.
What's wrong?
Fuck.
I won't have time. They're here.
No. Stick to the plan.
Raquel!
There it is!
Get in closer.
Fuck!
I want all forensics units there now!
We've caught them with their pants down.
And that ambulance
must be full of evidence. Let's go!
Raquel, I'm about two kilometers
northwest of the epicenter.
There are soldiers everywhere.
Did you get up there?
- No, I had to improvise.
- What?
There's a farm 400 meters
south of your location.
That's the first place
they'll look.
It's the only option.
Raquel?
The Ministry of the Interior
has just announced
the highest reward in history.
Ten million euros for any information
that aids the authorities in catching
the Professor or thwarting the heist.
Popular support is one
of the authorities' main concerns.
All of the hostages have confirmed
that this guy here
took a group of them to go help him.
He said they were going to work
at more than 65 degrees Celsius.
They're smelting the gold.
Why smelt the gold?
Stop fucking with me.
What are you saying?
They have a blast furnace?
An industrial furnace
occupies less space than a dishwasher.
- They went in with military trucks.
- Those motherfuckers!
Okay so, why would they
be smelting the National Reserve?
To take it out.
It's much easier to transport.
They can mold it however they want.
They could push it through the plumbing
or fly it out in their blimps,
convert it into pellets…
I don't know.
Go ahead with your plan.
We go after the gold.
They won't get a single gram!
Great.
Gentlemen, they have to be in the area.
Give the dogs the traces
we found in the RV.
And turn this place upside down!
Leave no stone unturned!
Any nearby buildings must
be thoroughly searched! Is that clear?
Let's go!
All right.
Come on, everybody. Let's go!
♪ Poor little girl ♪
♪ Oh, my little doll ♪
♪ She is all so pretty ♪
♪ All in bronze ♪
♪ I approach myself ♪
♪ But this little doll ♪
♪ Not moving ♪
♪ What does she have? ♪
♪ She is so fragile ♪
♪ What is she doing
In the middle of the rough sea? ♪
♪ She is so fragile ♪
♪ Unconscious ♪
♪ On a piece of wood ♪
♪ I wonder if it's me ♪
♪ Maybe that's what keeps me ♪
♪ To take it in my hands ♪
♪ Me? It's me? ♪
♪ I hope not ♪
♪ Me? It's me? I hope not ♪
♪ But I fear it ♪