1
00:00:27,229 --> 00:00:29,896
We think love is declared
with flowers and chocolates,

2
00:00:31,437 --> 00:00:34,271
but you can also
declare your love with a hammer.

3
00:00:35,104 --> 00:00:36,604
Or with an angle grinder.

4
00:00:49,937 --> 00:00:53,271
Kidnapping a police officer
can be a declaration of love.

5
00:00:53,812 --> 00:00:56,229
Saving him from the bottom of his pool

6
00:00:56,646 --> 00:00:57,521
is another.

7
00:01:12,437 --> 00:01:14,187
What's going on down there?

8
00:01:14,646 --> 00:01:15,812
What are you doing?

9
00:01:16,729 --> 00:01:19,312
- Pretend we're drunk.
- No, I won't pretend.

10
00:01:19,396 --> 00:01:21,646
Play drunk or I'll snap your neck.

11
00:01:22,187 --> 00:01:24,979
- Have you no shame?
- I'm calling the police!

12
00:01:28,104 --> 00:01:31,146
I am the police, ma'am.

13
00:01:31,229 --> 00:01:35,229
- That's Benito!
- Do you want to call them? Ring, ring.

14
00:01:35,312 --> 00:01:36,854
What are you doing?

15
00:01:38,187 --> 00:01:39,187
Pretend, come on.

16
00:01:49,646 --> 00:01:51,354
The house is full of them.

17
00:01:52,896 --> 00:01:54,479
And so is your car.

18
00:01:55,021 --> 00:01:56,437
And your wife's car.

19
00:01:57,771 --> 00:02:00,187
It looks like C-4, but it's only plastic.

20
00:02:00,937 --> 00:02:04,312
That's your alibi.
You wouldn't be a criminal, you'd be...

21
00:02:04,396 --> 00:02:07,062
a scared father, and they'll understand.

22
00:02:07,729 --> 00:02:11,521
Once I get out, I'll report you
and come back with 3,000 officers.

23
00:02:11,604 --> 00:02:13,354
We can also use real C-4.

24
00:02:14,146 --> 00:02:15,979
Anywhere you can imagine.

25
00:02:24,229 --> 00:02:25,812
Don't get the wrong idea.

26
00:02:25,896 --> 00:02:28,562
We don't want you
to do this for money, but...

27
00:02:28,646 --> 00:02:32,187
we understand the inconvenience
this could cause.

28
00:02:32,271 --> 00:02:33,437
One million euros.

29
00:02:33,521 --> 00:02:36,354
With this money and the alibi,
you're free to choose

30
00:02:36,437 --> 00:02:37,937
who you want to be with.

31
00:02:38,021 --> 00:02:40,521
With a woman
who illegally arrests people,

32
00:02:40,979 --> 00:02:42,062
tortures them,

33
00:02:42,312 --> 00:02:45,062
and abuses the power given to her
by the Constitution.

34
00:02:52,062 --> 00:02:53,271
Or with us.

35
00:02:57,146 --> 00:03:00,229
- Now you'll answer some questions.
- I'll decide that.

36
00:03:01,729 --> 00:03:04,896
Is Inspector Murillo alive?

37
00:03:07,187 --> 00:03:08,229
She might be.

38
00:03:11,312 --> 00:03:12,437
Is she in the tent?

39
00:03:13,854 --> 00:03:14,729
She might be.

40
00:03:15,812 --> 00:03:20,062
I just need you to let her know
that the Professor knows she's alive.

41
00:03:20,146 --> 00:03:21,562
She won't believe me.

42
00:03:22,396 --> 00:03:25,312
If I'd been with you,
why wouldn't I have arrested you?

43
00:03:27,229 --> 00:03:31,687
If she sees you wearing this watch,
she'll believe you.

44
00:03:32,229 --> 00:03:35,812
Because when love is concerned,
there's always a ticking clock.

45
00:03:37,229 --> 00:03:38,979
There's always a countdown.

46
00:03:41,021 --> 00:03:42,729
Loving someone is not enough,

47
00:03:44,104 --> 00:03:45,812
you have to make it in time.

48
00:04:08,437 --> 00:04:09,396
What's that?

49
00:04:11,229 --> 00:04:15,687
- For when she wakes up.
- That's a beautiful gift and gesture.

50
00:04:18,354 --> 00:04:21,104
She said she wouldn't touch me
with a ten-foot pole.

51
00:04:28,396 --> 00:04:30,437
Let me give you a piece of advice:

52
00:04:33,771 --> 00:04:35,854
don't fall in love during a heist.

53
00:04:42,229 --> 00:04:43,479
It's bad luck.

54
00:05:48,479 --> 00:05:50,062
Paulita!

55
00:05:51,271 --> 00:05:52,646
Miss Mariví!

56
00:05:54,646 --> 00:05:59,021
MINDANAO
DAY 1 OF THE HEIST

57
00:05:59,104 --> 00:06:00,271
The phone!

58
00:06:01,812 --> 00:06:03,812
SOUTHERN SPAIN
DAY 1 OF THE HEIST

59
00:06:03,896 --> 00:06:04,729
Mom?

60
00:06:05,562 --> 00:06:07,062
Paula, honey.

61
00:06:07,146 --> 00:06:09,437
How are you? What did you do today?

62
00:06:09,604 --> 00:06:11,271
The same as yesterday, Mom.

63
00:06:11,354 --> 00:06:13,896
I'm sure you did something great today.

64
00:06:13,979 --> 00:06:16,854
- Tell me something.
- I can't think of anything.

65
00:06:17,312 --> 00:06:18,521
Do you miss me?

66
00:06:18,646 --> 00:06:19,521
Yes.

67
00:06:20,062 --> 00:06:22,312
What's wrong?
You're watching TV, aren't you?

68
00:06:22,396 --> 00:06:24,479
No, I was playing with Grandma.

69
00:06:24,896 --> 00:06:26,104
Put her on, please.

70
00:06:26,479 --> 00:06:28,062
OK. Grandma!

71
00:06:28,521 --> 00:06:29,521
Darling?

72
00:06:30,354 --> 00:06:33,312
Is Paula all right? She sounds odd.

73
00:06:33,396 --> 00:06:34,521
I don't know.

74
00:06:35,854 --> 00:06:36,771
She seems fine.

75
00:06:37,521 --> 00:06:40,354
But you can talk to her
when you come for dinner.

76
00:06:42,562 --> 00:06:45,396
- Sure, Mom.
- And don't forget to buy some bread.

77
00:07:30,146 --> 00:07:31,687
It's six in the morning.

78
00:07:32,729 --> 00:07:37,354
The ambulance is in the crime lab.
In about an hour, Alberto will be there.

79
00:07:37,437 --> 00:07:38,687
Like a bloodhound.

80
00:07:41,104 --> 00:07:44,271
Sniffing out the trail of his new prey:
your daughter.

81
00:07:44,604 --> 00:07:48,562
Do you think I leave her address
stuck on the fridge with a magnet?

82
00:07:48,646 --> 00:07:50,937
I think you feel guilty
for being a bad mother.

83
00:07:51,021 --> 00:07:52,604
You don't simply go off...

84
00:07:53,271 --> 00:07:55,771
away on a heist for weeks and not call.

85
00:07:56,229 --> 00:07:59,062
Am I wrong?
What about your bad-daughter complex?

86
00:07:59,146 --> 00:08:00,437
Because your mom...

87
00:08:01,479 --> 00:08:04,729
You can't even leave her
to eat a yogurt on her own.

88
00:08:05,479 --> 00:08:09,229
How did you do it?
How did you call from the motor home?

89
00:08:09,312 --> 00:08:12,354
This may surprise you,
but we thought this through.

90
00:08:12,896 --> 00:08:15,854
Alberto can go in
like a pig in search of truffles.

91
00:08:15,937 --> 00:08:17,437
He won't find a thing.

92
00:08:35,354 --> 00:08:40,312
- What happened to your head?
- I'm obsessed with the heist, Colonel.

93
00:08:41,187 --> 00:08:43,979
I wake up very early. I'm not sleeping.

94
00:08:45,021 --> 00:08:48,729
I was tying my shoelaces
and thinking about the heist,

95
00:08:48,812 --> 00:08:52,937
and as I stood up, I banged my head
on the window so hard I nearly broke it.

96
00:08:55,521 --> 00:08:57,354
You're like me, Antoñanzas.

97
00:08:57,729 --> 00:08:59,979
Even with the truce, I couldn't sleep.

98
00:09:00,062 --> 00:09:01,979
I was wide awake at 3:00 a.m.,

99
00:09:02,062 --> 00:09:04,937
wondering how the Professor
would ruin our day.

100
00:09:05,021 --> 00:09:07,437
I'm going in to see if Sierra needs...

101
00:09:07,521 --> 00:09:09,646
Murillo is in total isolation.

102
00:09:10,062 --> 00:09:14,271
I'm only going to go in
to give the inspector her coffee.

103
00:09:17,604 --> 00:09:20,146
Murillo can only have contact with Sierra.

104
00:09:20,229 --> 00:09:23,646
She didn't let her sleep all night.
She's wearing her down.

105
00:09:25,479 --> 00:09:27,146
Let's go for a coffee.

106
00:09:29,062 --> 00:09:32,271
A crime's worst enemy isn't the police.

107
00:09:33,437 --> 00:09:34,396
It's rushing.

108
00:09:35,771 --> 00:09:38,312
The motor home was clean as a whistle.

109
00:09:38,521 --> 00:09:39,729
You left it...

110
00:09:40,604 --> 00:09:41,521
like new.

111
00:09:42,229 --> 00:09:43,687
But the ambulance...

112
00:09:45,146 --> 00:09:47,229
You hauled ass out of there.

113
00:09:47,312 --> 00:09:51,187
There's always something left. Always.
A hair on the pillow...

114
00:09:51,521 --> 00:09:52,687
A sock...

115
00:09:52,979 --> 00:09:56,854
And then forensics arrives
with UV light and luminol, and... bang!

116
00:09:58,146 --> 00:09:59,187
Gotcha.

117
00:10:01,771 --> 00:10:02,854
I repeat my offer:

118
00:10:03,771 --> 00:10:07,979
I'll go there now and remove that hair
that'll lead us to your family.

119
00:10:08,604 --> 00:10:10,104
Or we wait for your ex...

120
00:10:10,937 --> 00:10:12,021
to fuck you over.

121
00:10:17,021 --> 00:10:18,271
You've got nothing.

122
00:10:20,187 --> 00:10:23,729
You're threatening me with
"Maybe we'll find something."

123
00:10:29,104 --> 00:10:33,021
You know what? Your pregnancy
has made you so high on estrogen

124
00:10:33,104 --> 00:10:36,354
that you feel like
the most optimistic woman in Spain.

125
00:10:37,312 --> 00:10:40,062
But that isn't meant for work.
It's for the delivery,

126
00:10:40,146 --> 00:10:41,604
which is fucking hard.

127
00:10:45,646 --> 00:10:47,104
What will you do when it's born?

128
00:10:49,229 --> 00:10:50,771
Is it a boy or a girl?

129
00:10:52,312 --> 00:10:53,396
You don't know?

130
00:10:56,271 --> 00:10:57,271
Poor thing.

131
00:11:08,812 --> 00:11:10,229
What the fuck happened?

132
00:11:11,062 --> 00:11:12,562
They were barefoot, man.

133
00:11:12,646 --> 00:11:14,187
Barefoot? Who?

134
00:11:14,271 --> 00:11:15,562
Rio and Stockholm.

135
00:11:16,271 --> 00:11:18,062
- So?
- What do you mean, "So?"

136
00:11:18,479 --> 00:11:20,562
Who goes barefoot during a heist?

137
00:11:21,312 --> 00:11:25,271
Taking your shoes off on a couch
in the middle of a heist is weird.

138
00:11:26,354 --> 00:11:27,479
Are you stupid?

139
00:11:37,437 --> 00:11:41,854
If they were thinking of fucking,
they'd fuck... not take their shoes off.

140
00:11:42,396 --> 00:11:43,271
Well...

141
00:11:44,437 --> 00:11:46,854
What were you doing in here last night?

142
00:11:51,812 --> 00:11:52,646
Well, this.

143
00:11:57,562 --> 00:11:59,562
- This is what you were doing?
- Yes.

144
00:12:05,854 --> 00:12:10,521
You beat a guy up,
completely change how she sees you,

145
00:12:11,437 --> 00:12:14,771
and you think giving her
a heart is going to fix it?

146
00:12:15,146 --> 00:12:16,479
What can I do then?

147
00:12:18,687 --> 00:12:19,771
Change.

148
00:12:22,646 --> 00:12:26,146
In her eyes... you're a bad guy now.

149
00:12:26,604 --> 00:12:29,979
A violent guy.
What made her fall in love with you?

150
00:12:31,729 --> 00:12:32,854
I shot her.

151
00:12:33,437 --> 00:12:36,187
I mean, I shot her in the leg
to save her life.

152
00:12:36,687 --> 00:12:37,854
To save her life.

153
00:12:39,312 --> 00:12:40,271
I don't know.

154
00:12:44,729 --> 00:12:46,437
I did a cool dance for her.

155
00:12:47,437 --> 00:12:50,604
- You did a dance for her?
- Yes. I danced for her.

156
00:12:51,312 --> 00:12:55,021
I told her stories.
We laughed a lot together.

157
00:12:57,562 --> 00:13:02,354
And...
how long is it since you told her stories?

158
00:13:02,437 --> 00:13:04,646
Since you made her laugh?

159
00:13:04,937 --> 00:13:07,646
How long since you danced for her?

160
00:13:21,646 --> 00:13:24,021
Hey, Rio, can you get me a black coffee?

161
00:13:25,937 --> 00:13:29,729
I came up with this plan.
You're safe thanks to me.

162
00:13:29,812 --> 00:13:31,312
How about some gratitude?

163
00:13:32,229 --> 00:13:34,312
You're tied up. Why don't you rest?

164
00:13:34,396 --> 00:13:37,062
Can I at least have some water, please?

165
00:13:38,062 --> 00:13:39,687
Just a bit of water.

166
00:13:49,937 --> 00:13:51,062
I'm sorry, but...

167
00:13:52,104 --> 00:13:52,937
Thanks.

168
00:13:54,312 --> 00:13:55,729
You look awful.

169
00:13:56,104 --> 00:13:57,062
Can't you sleep?

170
00:14:01,354 --> 00:14:04,771
How many times do you wake up at night?
Three, four, more?

171
00:14:11,479 --> 00:14:12,437
Hey, Rio...

172
00:14:13,312 --> 00:14:14,687
if you need anything...

173
00:14:15,271 --> 00:14:17,271
to talk or whatever, I'm here.

174
00:14:20,396 --> 00:14:21,354
Thank you.

175
00:14:30,687 --> 00:14:32,271
He's the weakest link.

176
00:14:32,687 --> 00:14:36,229
Palpitations,
excessive sweating, insomnia.

177
00:14:36,979 --> 00:14:39,271
Break free during his watch.

178
00:14:39,354 --> 00:14:41,896
He won't be capable
of pulling the trigger.

179
00:14:43,937 --> 00:14:47,104
What makes you think I won't kill you
as soon as I'm free?

180
00:14:47,187 --> 00:14:48,146
Well...

181
00:14:48,812 --> 00:14:50,312
I smashed your head in.

182
00:14:50,604 --> 00:14:52,271
You fucked my eyes up.

183
00:14:52,771 --> 00:14:55,687
That's a tie. A gentlemen's agreement.

184
00:14:55,771 --> 00:14:58,646
Are you asking me to trust you?

185
00:14:59,146 --> 00:15:02,396
What I'm saying is,
a truce has been declared out there.

186
00:15:02,562 --> 00:15:03,812
No armored vans are coming.

187
00:15:06,146 --> 00:15:08,146
It's a fucking cold war.

188
00:15:08,229 --> 00:15:10,521
- And we are captives.
- So?

189
00:15:11,562 --> 00:15:15,187
You should become
the agent of chaos we need.

190
00:15:17,187 --> 00:15:19,187
Like the creature in Alien.

191
00:15:22,437 --> 00:15:25,521
Like John McClane in Die Hard.

192
00:15:37,312 --> 00:15:38,729
STORM RESERVOIR
KEEP OUT

193
00:15:58,896 --> 00:15:59,854
Let's go.

194
00:16:31,354 --> 00:16:34,896
When he got to the storm reservoir,
the Professor was thinking of Raquel,

195
00:16:36,521 --> 00:16:39,687
just like Alberto
as he stepped into the ambulance.

196
00:16:43,312 --> 00:16:46,396
It's strange how you can
think about one person,

197
00:16:46,896 --> 00:16:50,562
at the same time, in such different ways.

198
00:16:52,104 --> 00:16:57,354
They say love makes the world go round.
But hatred certainly isn't far behind.

199
00:17:01,354 --> 00:17:02,687
You were right.

200
00:17:03,104 --> 00:17:04,312
Lisbon is alive.

201
00:17:07,146 --> 00:17:07,979
Where is she?

202
00:17:08,062 --> 00:17:10,979
In the tent.
I imagine she's being interrogated.

203
00:17:11,062 --> 00:17:13,646
- How long can they keep her?
- I don't know.

204
00:17:13,729 --> 00:17:16,771
I don't think they'll stick
to the usual 72 hours.

205
00:17:17,729 --> 00:17:19,687
They'll transfer her at some point.

206
00:17:19,979 --> 00:17:22,062
- Can you rescue her?
- Not during a transfer.

207
00:17:22,146 --> 00:17:26,104
It'd be stupid. We did it with you.
They'll expect it. It'd be suicide.

208
00:17:26,187 --> 00:17:27,687
What are you going to do?

209
00:17:28,687 --> 00:17:31,521
They have Lisbon there
with the whole plan in her head.

210
00:17:32,104 --> 00:17:34,604
Including the place
you're calling me from.

211
00:17:42,521 --> 00:17:43,521
Professor?

212
00:17:45,812 --> 00:17:46,854
I don't know.

213
00:17:49,187 --> 00:17:52,229
I'm so tired, Tokyo. I can't think.

214
00:17:55,312 --> 00:17:57,604
But I'll find a solution. Don't worry.

215
00:17:59,604 --> 00:18:02,229
I'm making ravioli. You need energy.

216
00:18:07,812 --> 00:18:09,729
- Is Palermo still tied up?
- Yes.

217
00:18:09,896 --> 00:18:12,104
I want you to go and tell him this...

218
00:18:12,187 --> 00:18:16,604
No, I'm not telling him anything.
He'd bite me like an animal.

219
00:18:17,062 --> 00:18:19,604
Well, you'll have to.
Tell him exactly this:

220
00:18:20,396 --> 00:18:25,312
"You have a message from the Professor.
Lisbon is alive.

221
00:18:25,396 --> 00:18:27,271
She's being held in the tent.

222
00:18:27,354 --> 00:18:30,021
I need you to think of a way to save her."

223
00:18:31,437 --> 00:18:33,604
- He won't do it.
- Listen to me.

224
00:18:33,687 --> 00:18:38,104
All I'm trying to do is to get Palermo
to fall back in love with the plan.

225
00:18:38,187 --> 00:18:40,187
I need him back on our side.

226
00:18:40,479 --> 00:18:45,229
Go tell him.
I'll think of something. Understood?

227
00:18:50,396 --> 00:18:51,396
Understood.

228
00:19:10,854 --> 00:19:14,021
I'm going to the bathroom.
Want to come with me, Sergio?

229
00:19:16,729 --> 00:19:22,354
Have you ever had the privilege
of an experienced man giving you fellatio?

230
00:19:32,062 --> 00:19:34,062
He's absolutely unpredictable.

231
00:19:34,437 --> 00:19:37,646
He simply offered you fellatio, gallantly.

232
00:19:37,729 --> 00:19:39,604
- He...
- You know what I mean.

233
00:19:39,687 --> 00:19:42,062
He's uncontrollable.
He's sick with egomania.

234
00:19:42,146 --> 00:19:43,479
He'll respect the hierarchy.

235
00:19:43,562 --> 00:19:46,729
He would in a heist
lasting two or three hours, or a night.

236
00:19:47,062 --> 00:19:49,021
We're talking about several days.

237
00:19:49,104 --> 00:19:51,771
Under infinitely higher pressure.

238
00:19:52,146 --> 00:19:54,146
- I can control Martín...
- You can't!

239
00:19:54,771 --> 00:19:58,354
- I've been doing it for years.
- You can't. He's an egomaniac.

240
00:19:58,521 --> 00:20:00,354
He's obsessed with power.

241
00:20:00,896 --> 00:20:02,896
That only means one thing:

242
00:20:03,854 --> 00:20:07,521
if he's not in charge,
he'll do anything to change that.

243
00:20:08,854 --> 00:20:12,771
And he won't hesitate to execute,
betray, or create chaos.

244
00:20:12,854 --> 00:20:17,771
He's an obsessive egomaniac,
he believes in himself, and he's a genius.

245
00:20:17,896 --> 00:20:18,771
Like you.

246
00:20:18,854 --> 00:20:22,646
If you prefer, use second-raters.
They'll follow you like sheep.

247
00:20:22,729 --> 00:20:25,729
You don't get it.
The fact he's a genius complicates things.

248
00:20:25,812 --> 00:20:27,979
He's dangerous
because we won't see him coming.

249
00:20:28,396 --> 00:20:29,521
You're my brother.

250
00:20:29,604 --> 00:20:33,187
I would put you in charge
of any heist in a heartbeat.

251
00:20:36,312 --> 00:20:37,187
But him...

252
00:20:38,187 --> 00:20:41,354
You're wrong to trust me and not him.
I'm less trustworthy.

253
00:20:44,396 --> 00:20:45,437
Two beers.

254
00:20:52,187 --> 00:20:53,854
Don't get more peanuts.

255
00:20:54,562 --> 00:20:56,896
You're already
as overweight as an orangutan.

256
00:20:58,229 --> 00:21:01,354
If you laugh at my bow tie,
you're laughing at me.

257
00:21:01,687 --> 00:21:02,812
If you laugh at me,

258
00:21:02,896 --> 00:21:06,312
you'll remember this March 17th
for the rest of your life,

259
00:21:06,396 --> 00:21:08,729
but we don't quite know why yet.

260
00:21:10,687 --> 00:21:12,354
Don't you find it thrilling?

261
00:21:24,979 --> 00:21:26,187
Is something wrong?

262
00:21:26,979 --> 00:21:27,979
Not at all.

263
00:21:32,937 --> 00:21:35,437
There are prints on most of the surfaces.

264
00:21:37,021 --> 00:21:40,812
The walls are covered
with plans, maps, diagrams...

265
00:21:43,604 --> 00:21:44,646
I see an oven.

266
00:21:45,146 --> 00:21:48,187
They probably used it
to get rid of evidence.

267
00:21:50,354 --> 00:21:51,771
I'm going to examine it.

268
00:22:01,812 --> 00:22:05,812
There are some plastic fragments,
perhaps from an electronic device.

269
00:22:06,812 --> 00:22:09,187
I'm separating the burnt pieces.

270
00:22:13,021 --> 00:22:14,521
I think I have something.

271
00:22:17,729 --> 00:22:19,521
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.

272
00:22:25,521 --> 00:22:27,062
So I'm a Maserati, am I?

273
00:22:27,646 --> 00:22:31,479
For fuck's sake,
did he put it in the papers too?

274
00:22:31,562 --> 00:22:32,687
It's OK.

275
00:22:36,312 --> 00:22:39,271
- If you want, I'll give you a ride.
- What the hell?

276
00:22:39,687 --> 00:22:41,187
It's just a ride.

277
00:22:41,271 --> 00:22:42,104
"Just a ride"?

278
00:22:42,937 --> 00:22:45,812
Then we push a button, erase the tape,

279
00:22:45,896 --> 00:22:49,979
destroy the black box,
and it's like nothing happened.

280
00:23:03,187 --> 00:23:04,312
Mónica dumped me.

281
00:23:04,896 --> 00:23:06,104
I'm a free man.

282
00:23:06,896 --> 00:23:09,187
I don't need to erase any black box.

283
00:23:09,271 --> 00:23:11,646
I'll take the Maserati,
put the pedal to the metal,

284
00:23:11,729 --> 00:23:14,312
and start doing donuts
until I burn rubber.

285
00:23:14,562 --> 00:23:16,229
Cool as a cucumber.

286
00:23:17,146 --> 00:23:20,396
- You're so macho, aren't you?
- Very macho, so watch out.

287
00:23:20,479 --> 00:23:23,896
In case you have to go to the garage
to change the suspension.

288
00:23:24,437 --> 00:23:26,604
Wait until you see
the state of the chassis.

289
00:23:28,562 --> 00:23:29,562
Scary.

290
00:23:45,729 --> 00:23:48,479
This bastard even leaves misleading clues
in the bidet.

291
00:23:50,021 --> 00:23:51,937
I'm sure they planted it there.

292
00:23:52,021 --> 00:23:56,271
It was at the bottom of the oven, melted.
It's impossible it was planted.

293
00:23:56,354 --> 00:23:57,271
So?

294
00:23:57,354 --> 00:24:00,729
A SIM card is engraved
with a number of up to 19 digits,

295
00:24:00,812 --> 00:24:02,146
unique to each card.

296
00:24:02,771 --> 00:24:06,521
This one disappeared when it was burnt,
but, during the process,

297
00:24:06,604 --> 00:24:08,437
it bent over the metallic chip,

298
00:24:08,521 --> 00:24:10,604
branding seven numbers on it.

299
00:24:10,687 --> 00:24:13,062
We cross-checked it
with data from carriers,

300
00:24:13,146 --> 00:24:17,687
and we came up with 354 cards
matching those end numbers.

301
00:24:18,312 --> 00:24:22,604
One of them was bought three months ago
and has only made one call.

302
00:24:23,104 --> 00:24:24,479
During the heist.

303
00:24:24,562 --> 00:24:25,437
Bingo!

304
00:24:25,521 --> 00:24:26,937
Where did they call?

305
00:24:27,021 --> 00:24:30,104
Wait! A little suspense, no?

306
00:24:34,896 --> 00:24:36,771
Mindanao, the Philippines.

307
00:24:36,854 --> 00:24:38,104
Holy shit, I knew it!

308
00:24:40,854 --> 00:24:42,312
We'll talk to Interpol.

309
00:24:53,937 --> 00:24:56,687
- Hello?
- Mindanao, the Philippines. They know.

310
00:25:00,937 --> 00:25:03,896
- How?
- A half-burnt SIM card. In the ambulance.

311
00:25:13,062 --> 00:25:14,521
Nothing changes for you.

312
00:25:14,604 --> 00:25:17,979
You've got to go into the office now,
show her the watch,

313
00:25:18,479 --> 00:25:22,562
- and tell her: "I'm with you."
- That I am? Should I say it like that?

314
00:25:22,979 --> 00:25:23,854
Excuse me?

315
00:25:23,937 --> 00:25:25,937
"I'm with you" could be confusing.

316
00:25:26,021 --> 00:25:28,479
She might just think I'm weird.
A communist cop.

317
00:25:28,562 --> 00:25:31,979
If I say "The Professor's with you,"
it's clearer.

318
00:25:32,062 --> 00:25:34,687
Just show her the watch. That's all.

319
00:25:34,771 --> 00:25:35,687
Understood.

320
00:25:43,312 --> 00:25:44,729
Get the hostages out.

321
00:25:44,979 --> 00:25:49,187
- Get up and go to the stairs.
- How's the pressure of being in charge?

322
00:25:49,271 --> 00:25:50,854
Fantastic.

323
00:25:53,854 --> 00:25:55,854
I'm all ears. I'm listening.

324
00:25:56,937 --> 00:26:00,396
You have a message from the Professor:
"Lisbon is alive.

325
00:26:00,479 --> 00:26:03,562
She's in the tent.
Think of a way to save her."

326
00:26:04,187 --> 00:26:05,104
It's an order.

327
00:26:05,979 --> 00:26:08,812
First you stage a coup,
now you give me an order.

328
00:26:08,896 --> 00:26:10,562
That's odd. I'd say it's...

329
00:26:11,062 --> 00:26:13,604
a dangerous thing to do, but it's also...

330
00:26:13,687 --> 00:26:15,729
understandable, of course.

331
00:26:15,812 --> 00:26:18,562
There they are, the empowered women.

332
00:26:20,687 --> 00:26:22,187
This is all bullshit.

333
00:26:22,646 --> 00:26:24,604
- And it's about to end.
- Are you done?

334
00:26:27,104 --> 00:26:28,521
What's wrong with you?

335
00:26:28,604 --> 00:26:33,062
- With me?
- Are you angry at your mom?

336
00:26:33,937 --> 00:26:36,396
Didn't she breastfeed you long enough?

337
00:26:38,146 --> 00:26:41,854
Is that why you keep on looking
for something to complain about?

338
00:26:47,854 --> 00:26:52,896
The order comes from the Professor.
He's got a dick, just like you.

339
00:27:09,146 --> 00:27:10,396
They are in Mindanao.

340
00:27:12,562 --> 00:27:14,771
In 24 hours, we'll have found them.

341
00:27:14,854 --> 00:27:16,437
You know the protocol:

342
00:27:16,521 --> 00:27:17,771
Paula arrives here,

343
00:27:18,354 --> 00:27:21,021
you're declared guilty of child abduction,

344
00:27:21,104 --> 00:27:22,437
you lose custody,

345
00:27:23,229 --> 00:27:24,979
and she goes to live with her dad.

346
00:27:30,271 --> 00:27:33,979
Have you come to tell me I'm screwed?
I already know that.

347
00:27:40,437 --> 00:27:41,354
It depends.

348
00:27:42,146 --> 00:27:44,437
I'll let you call them. Here and now.

349
00:27:45,521 --> 00:27:46,646
And you save them.

350
00:27:46,729 --> 00:27:49,729
When we get to the house in Mindanao,
they won't be there.

351
00:27:49,812 --> 00:27:51,104
We screwed up.

352
00:27:52,229 --> 00:27:55,396
I'm not thrilled at the idea
of Paula going to Alberto either.

353
00:28:01,062 --> 00:28:02,646
I wonder what she's doing now.

354
00:28:06,687 --> 00:28:08,396
Close your eyes. Picture her.

355
00:28:09,604 --> 00:28:10,604
Tucked in bed.

356
00:28:10,687 --> 00:28:14,104
Her hair spread across the blanket.
You can almost smell her.

357
00:28:15,521 --> 00:28:18,229
Close your eyes. Picture her.

358
00:28:20,521 --> 00:28:21,437
Close them.

359
00:28:21,937 --> 00:28:23,521
What are you doing?

360
00:28:25,812 --> 00:28:29,646
It's only a five-year wait.
Then you'll see each other again.

361
00:28:30,062 --> 00:28:31,854
She comes running. "Mommy!"

362
00:28:32,229 --> 00:28:34,521
She hugs you like this, wraps you up.

363
00:28:34,604 --> 00:28:37,271
She clings to you like a little monkey.

364
00:28:38,437 --> 00:28:40,396
And you press her against you...

365
00:28:41,937 --> 00:28:43,604
and hold her face.

366
00:28:44,437 --> 00:28:45,646
To look at her.

367
00:28:48,521 --> 00:28:49,896
But she won't let go.

368
00:28:50,396 --> 00:28:51,896
She repeats endlessly,

369
00:28:52,271 --> 00:28:55,146
like a mantra to save her
from the bad things:

370
00:28:55,229 --> 00:28:59,979
"Mommy, don't leave me."

371
00:29:00,479 --> 00:29:01,937
"Mommy, don't leave me."

372
00:29:02,521 --> 00:29:04,521
"Mommy, don't leave me."

373
00:29:05,021 --> 00:29:05,854
Raquel,

374
00:29:05,937 --> 00:29:08,562
I know you love him. And he loves you.

375
00:29:08,812 --> 00:29:13,312
For that exact reason...
what do you think he'd tell you to do?

376
00:29:18,604 --> 00:29:19,854
I offered you...

377
00:29:20,979 --> 00:29:24,104
five years in prison.
I'll change it to five minutes.

378
00:29:28,854 --> 00:29:30,229
I'm offering you freedom.

379
00:29:31,687 --> 00:29:34,312
Sergio goes to jail. You go free.

380
00:29:35,104 --> 00:29:40,812
Your arrest was never official.
Call them, bring them to safety.

381
00:29:41,312 --> 00:29:43,354
You'll be with them in 24 hours.

382
00:29:44,562 --> 00:29:48,354
We'll never come after you.
Everything will be over, honey.

383
00:30:38,812 --> 00:30:39,937
Better?

384
00:30:52,104 --> 00:30:53,021
Well?

385
00:30:53,812 --> 00:30:55,354
Did you get any rest?

386
00:30:57,062 --> 00:30:59,229
I've tried to, but I can't sleep.

387
00:31:01,687 --> 00:31:02,937
Do you have nightmares?

388
00:31:03,937 --> 00:31:06,396
Every time I close my eyes,
I relive it.

389
00:31:20,604 --> 00:31:25,437
Hey, what happened to the alpha male?
I thought you were a free man.

390
00:31:26,812 --> 00:31:28,687
What are they talking about?

391
00:31:29,771 --> 00:31:31,771
Hello, cutie.

392
00:31:32,854 --> 00:31:34,604
Come to my island, if you like.

393
00:31:35,771 --> 00:31:40,354
Provided you don't party much.
I'm not really into that noisy music.

394
00:31:43,979 --> 00:31:46,979
If you invite me over,
I'll show you my best bikini.

395
00:31:51,646 --> 00:31:53,354
Why didn't you tell us?

396
00:31:54,771 --> 00:31:55,687
I couldn't.

397
00:31:57,187 --> 00:31:59,187
You need to talk about it, Rio.

398
00:32:02,104 --> 00:32:04,021
They took me out of my cell one night,

399
00:32:05,312 --> 00:32:07,896
forced me to dig my own grave
in the desert.

400
00:32:11,729 --> 00:32:14,187
I'm such a sweet girl.

401
00:32:14,646 --> 00:32:17,021
That's why I'm smiling all damn day.

402
00:32:18,687 --> 00:32:21,312
Then they made me
place a coffin in the hole.

403
00:32:25,021 --> 00:32:26,812
And they made me get inside.

404
00:32:29,729 --> 00:32:31,562
Then they threw sand on top.

405
00:32:34,354 --> 00:32:35,437
Until I was buried.

406
00:32:38,729 --> 00:32:40,104
And they left me there.

407
00:32:43,021 --> 00:32:44,062
In the darkness.

408
00:32:46,187 --> 00:32:49,479
In silence and barely able to breathe.

409
00:32:52,521 --> 00:32:53,562
Easy.

410
00:32:54,979 --> 00:32:55,854
Easy.

411
00:32:58,521 --> 00:32:59,812
I'm here with you.

412
00:33:01,229 --> 00:33:03,146
Do you know the only thing on my mind?

413
00:33:05,437 --> 00:33:06,271
What?

414
00:33:07,396 --> 00:33:11,937
It should have been the Professor
being buried alive, not me.

415
00:33:15,521 --> 00:33:16,562
I'm sorry.

416
00:33:17,646 --> 00:33:19,062
Look.

417
00:33:34,646 --> 00:33:35,771
Come on, let's go.

418
00:33:53,479 --> 00:33:56,187
Excuse me a second.
I'm going to the bathroom.

419
00:34:03,604 --> 00:34:04,771
You don't trust me.

420
00:34:12,937 --> 00:34:14,354
I'm an egomaniac.

421
00:34:16,812 --> 00:34:19,146
I'll only be willing to follow my plan.

422
00:34:20,937 --> 00:34:22,687
I'm obsessed with being the boss.

423
00:34:22,771 --> 00:34:25,312
So much so that if things don't go
how I planned...

424
00:34:27,146 --> 00:34:29,229
I might become a risk, right?

425
00:34:34,854 --> 00:34:35,687
Yes.

426
00:34:36,812 --> 00:34:38,021
That's what I think.

427
00:34:39,854 --> 00:34:40,979
You figured me out.

428
00:34:42,521 --> 00:34:44,562
But there's something
you haven't considered.

429
00:34:45,437 --> 00:34:50,146
It's that not only do I love your brother,
but I also love the plan...

430
00:34:50,396 --> 00:34:51,896
to the same extent.

431
00:34:52,271 --> 00:34:54,812
I would sell you out, no problem.

432
00:34:55,271 --> 00:34:57,062
And the rest of the gang, too.

433
00:34:57,187 --> 00:34:59,187
But I'd never betray the plan.

434
00:35:00,562 --> 00:35:02,312
That's where my loyalty lies.

435
00:35:04,812 --> 00:35:07,479
This is more than a heist,
and you know it.

436
00:35:08,521 --> 00:35:11,271
The plan isn't perfect yet.
I accept that.

437
00:35:11,354 --> 00:35:12,979
It's an unfinished poem.

438
00:35:14,604 --> 00:35:16,021
We need you, brother.

439
00:35:28,479 --> 00:35:29,479
Please.

440
00:35:46,521 --> 00:35:48,771
You seemed very brave out there.

441
00:35:50,979 --> 00:35:52,271
Which is admirable.

442
00:35:56,021 --> 00:35:57,229
Commendable.

443
00:36:09,521 --> 00:36:10,771
Come on, let me past.

444
00:36:16,104 --> 00:36:19,771
You seemed very brave earlier,
but now you have to prove it.

445
00:36:28,437 --> 00:36:30,062
Let's see those balls.

446
00:36:33,312 --> 00:36:34,271
Hold on.

447
00:36:37,437 --> 00:36:39,771
Hold on. Tell me what you prefer?

448
00:36:41,312 --> 00:36:42,146
Death?

449
00:36:42,896 --> 00:36:47,354
Look at me. Or impotence?
Sometimes you have to make hard choices.

450
00:36:47,437 --> 00:36:50,854
For me: what do I do
with this jerk laughing at my bow tie?

451
00:36:50,937 --> 00:36:54,396
For you: is it worth living
without a penis?

452
00:37:01,896 --> 00:37:03,312
He's taking a long time.

453
00:37:03,396 --> 00:37:06,229
He's beating up the fat guy
in the bathroom.

454
00:37:07,229 --> 00:37:09,104
We would've heard something.

455
00:37:10,896 --> 00:37:13,104
Real chaos, dear Sergio...

456
00:37:14,604 --> 00:37:15,812
makes no noise.

457
00:37:19,729 --> 00:37:21,687
Palermo was loyal to the heist.

458
00:37:21,771 --> 00:37:24,562
But in his head,
that only meant one thing:

459
00:37:25,396 --> 00:37:28,854
for the heist to continue,
he had to be back in charge.

460
00:37:29,521 --> 00:37:33,062
It was his silent way of ensuring
we didn't see the chaos coming.

461
00:37:33,354 --> 00:37:36,229
You know what you have to do.
Don't be a coward.

462
00:37:37,187 --> 00:37:39,354
You have to dislocate the joint

463
00:37:40,021 --> 00:37:42,979
between the first metacarpal
and the trapezium.

464
00:37:43,062 --> 00:37:45,062
Firmly, without hesitation.

465
00:37:45,854 --> 00:37:50,229
You twist it around like that.
There's no shackle it won't work on.

466
00:37:51,104 --> 00:37:53,062
Don't make me have to separate you.

467
00:38:00,437 --> 00:38:04,729
It'll hurt. But freedom will be worth it,
don't you think?

468
00:38:08,437 --> 00:38:09,312
Come on.

469
00:38:42,521 --> 00:38:43,396
Don't move!

470
00:38:49,771 --> 00:38:51,146
- Don't move.
- Easy, kid.

471
00:38:51,979 --> 00:38:54,021
I'm just a fucking security guard.

472
00:38:54,979 --> 00:38:55,937
On the ground.

473
00:38:57,687 --> 00:38:59,937
- No way.
- I said, on the ground now.

474
00:39:00,562 --> 00:39:03,146
What are you going to do?
Shoot me, unarmed?

475
00:39:04,979 --> 00:39:07,312
I swear if I have to, I will shoot you.

476
00:39:07,604 --> 00:39:11,604
You'll shoot an unarmed father
who is only trying to escape?

477
00:39:14,396 --> 00:39:15,354
Go ahead.

478
00:39:21,354 --> 00:39:22,521
Here I am.

479
00:39:22,812 --> 00:39:25,021
Don't move!

480
00:39:27,229 --> 00:39:29,521
Get on the fucking ground, Gandía!

481
00:39:30,812 --> 00:39:31,937
You won't shoot.

482
00:39:32,021 --> 00:39:33,479
On the ground!

483
00:39:35,396 --> 00:39:37,396
Don't move, for fuck's sake!

484
00:39:38,062 --> 00:39:39,271
I said, don't move!

485
00:39:45,979 --> 00:39:47,229
See you soon.

