BARENTS SEA, FIVE YEARS BEFORE D-DAY
We've sabotaged this priceless pump
to get it out of here.
Tell him we're going to steal it from him.
Tell him that we're also
taking this gentleman here with us.
He spends so much time alone underwater,
breathing a mix of oxygen and helium,
that he's realized his wallet is full
of photos of the seven families
he hasn't had.
His kids call him "güey" and "sir"
because nobody calls a stranger "Dad."
That's why he wants
to get involved in our heist,
to see if he can have a family
that isn't just on photo paper.
By the way,
tell the foreman we charge 50% up front.
He's going to have to pay us
to rob him. Translate, sir.
This guy is awesome.
Ask him if he has a sister.
LÓPEZ DE ORGAZ STREET
3 LÓPEZ DE ORGAZ ST.