MADRID, D-DAY
Remember Plan Chernobyl?
It was a desperate plan
from our last heist.
It involved raining money down on Madrid
so we could make our escape
if everything went wrong.
It was intended to create chaos.
And that was exactly
what we needed right now.
Chaos.
- Do you wanna get that?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah?
What blimps?
I'll be there in eight minutes.
The blimps are programmed
to go to specific coordinates,
and once they get there,
their doors will open.
After that,
they'll fly in a radius of 250 meters
releasing bills at intervals of 40 seconds
for a 50-minute period.
Imagine
on that day the money raining down
will be like Manna from heaven.
In total, we'll release 140 million euros.
It ain't cheap
going into the lion's den, right?
They call you
and all of us Robin Hoods.
It makes sense that some of the money
goes back to the people.
This message…
is for all of you who see this mask
as a symbol of resistance.
We need you.
The state has declared war on us.
A filthy war.
And we've decided to stand up to them.
The police have arrested
one of us in a foreign country.
Aníbal.
You can't sleep?
Aníbal Cortés.
Come on,
let's get some coffee.
It's been more than two months
since his arrest.
And no formal charges have been made.
They haven't requested extradition.
They haven't provided a lawyer.
He's being held captive
in some unknown place.
And in all likelihood,
they are torturing him.
So we are demanding
that his illegal detention
be brought to an end right now
and that he's brought to justice
while respecting legal standards.
The state began this war.
We're not going to hide.
Whoa.
We're going to fight…
blow
by blow.
And this time…
CALLAO MOVIE THEATER
…the heist will be even bigger.
Furthermore…
what is really going on is a chess game.
We are moving pieces
that force central intelligence
to move other pieces.
And Prieto can only do one thing.
I want the army in the streets!
They're waiting for us
to go running after those balloons.
But they don't know it's the best
diversion we've seen in our fucking lives.
Raise the alert to level 5.
If they have the balls
to announce they're going to rob us,
they're gonna find
everything fortified. Fuck!
Whoever attacks first
will have more time.
But whoever's defending the attack
won't have any time to prepare.
So, on the spot, Prieto will be forced
to improvise with his best defense.
Yes, the president gave the green light.
I want Madrid filled with soldiers.
Bring out the LMV, the troop trucks
and armored cars--
Armored cars, fuck!
There's nothing wrong with my mouth.
And this is how we'll lay our trap.
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
Coming!
♪ I've been picking up the pieces
Left on the floor ♪
Martín.
♪ Would have carried you away
Like a songbird in a storm ♪
May I?
♪ I swear that I can see it
I can see it in your eyes ♪
PALERMO, ITALY
TWO MONTHS UNTIL D-DAY
♪ I can see it, see it coming
But I couldn’t stop it if I tried ♪
You want a drink?
♪ As he's watching the skies ♪
♪ I feel your heart beating
Yeah, I can feel it from the other side ♪
♪ I must carry on ♪
♪ So carry on ♪
It was a beautiful heist, huh?
And I'm glad that you're alive.
Thank you.
Of course, the rat that hides outside
always has a better chance
of surviving, right?
I was the most exposed during the heist.
No, don't give me that bullshit.
The ones who face the bullets
are the most exposed, my dear.
- How many times were you shot at?
- I'm not here to argue.
Look, if I'm being frank,
I couldn't care less
why the fuck you came here.
All I know is after more than three years,
here we are.
So I'm gonna tell you
why you didn't enter the Royal Mint.
Because you're a coward.
And because
you had him do the dirty work.
Your brother.
A heist like that
always has a contingency.
A contingency?
I'll be very clear.
You didn't go in
and a third of your crew died,
you son of a bitch.
A third of your crew died
and you did nothing, not a fucking thing.
I feel it just like you do.
How the fuck could you feel like me?
You son of a bitch!
I wouldn't have let him die!
I'd have gone in and gotten him out!
I would have done
whatever the fuck it took!
Even if I had to blow the building up!
I'd blow the fucking building,
but I wouldn't have let him die.
You let him die.
Who do you think you're talking to,
you son of a bitch?
Some dumbass from your gang?
I know you, Sergio.
I know what kind of person you are.
He was my friend.
He was everything to me.
He was my other half.
Look me in the eyes
and tell me you never thought of it.
That he'd let himself get killed.
With all your calculations,
you son of a bitch,
tell me you didn't consider
your brother's death.
Hmm?
I didn't consider my brother's death.
Not even once.
I don't know how to live without him.
I'm sorry, it's not your fault either.
You know that, right?
It wasn't your fault,
okay?
Okay.
How are you?
I'm… I'm fine.
Hanging with Johnnie Walker…
…popping pills, eating from cans.
But I'm all right.
Because I found the key.
Music.
You've locked yourself in here
this whole time, listening to music?
I put on music from
when I was a teenager and I travel there.
To the skankiest dive bars
of Buenos Aires.
♪ Who can it be knocking at my door? ♪
I dance like I used to
before there was any pain.
♪ Can't you see that it's late at night? ♪
Dance with me.
Come on, don't be a pussy.
Dance!
♪ All I wish is to be alone ♪
There you go.
Remember this one?
♪ Don't you invade my home
Best off if you hang outside ♪
♪ Don't come in ♪
Why did you come here?
♪ Who can it be now? ♪
To ask for permission.
I'm going to steal the gold.
I could say
it's a homage to my brother but,
the truth is…
I need to do it.
And I'm not gonna do it without you.
♪ Who can it , who can it ♪
Whoo!
♪ Who can it be now? ♪
Mónica.
- Denver, not now.
- No, right now.
I can't go inside 'til we fix this.
- Grab your gun and do what you have to do.
- Mónica, let me explain.
It was 3:00 a.m. I didn't know
what I was saying. Forgive me.
So that's a good reason
not to talk to me for three days?
It's about to begin.
Can you hear me?
Affirmative.
- You hear me?
- Hold on.
Now. Try again.
Inspector, what are you wearing?
Let's get started.
When you have money
to invest in R & D,
you can do marvelous things.
Three weeks before the heist,
we'd already hacked
the mobile phones of the CNI and police
through applications like WhatsApp.
We could activate their microphones,
cameras and GPS.
ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN
It took less than one hour to tap into
the telecommunications system
of the entire defense staff.
The work Rio used to do
was now handled by 65 Pakistanis.
They didn't look like
Silicon Valley hipsters,
but they were geniuses.
Thanks to them,
we had access to everything.
Seventy-six.
All channels clear.
A collapse of the signal
is expected in a few hours.
Three.
Secondary units stand by…
Three hundred twelve.
…becoming momentarily…
Second platoon, first Brunete company,
house of congress.
First platoon, second Four Winds company,
the Royal Palace.
Third platoon,
first Paracuellos company, the senate.
First platoon, seventh El Goloso company,
Moncloa Palace.
First platoon, sixth BRIPAC company,
Bank of Spain.
BANK OF SPAIN
Third platoon…
Attention.
You're the first platoon
of the sixth company, BRIPAC.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're the first platoon
of the sixth company, BRIPAC.
One, six, BRIPAC.
You've got 17 minutes.
You've got 16 minutes and 45 seconds!
I want your blood boiling
and your mind frosty, let's go!
BRIPAC!
Sixth company!
Is that the sixth? Good.
Come on.
Let's go.
Do I need to repeat myself?
Let's go, goddamn it.
I want us there in seven minutes!
To the war!
THREE DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
Stop with the leg.
You're gonna wake Cincinnati.
Cincinnati is fine.
I'm the one who's not fine.
Mónica, I'll be honest with you.
I don't want you in that bank.
- I mean, fuck, sweetie, we have a son.
- Calm down before--
How am I gonna calm down? It's been
three weeks since I've had any sleep.
We're not Bonnie and Clyde, Mónica.
Fuck, you were a secretary
at the Mint, not Rambo.
Shit!
- Denver…
- What?
I'm ready to go in there
and no matter what, I'm gonna do it.
How are you ready? From hanging out here,
studying with the Professor at crime camp?
- Give me a fucking break.
- Listen.
No, you listen to me, Mónica!
I've been preparing for this
my whole life, since I was a kid.
I'd go out to play with a ball
and some assholes would take it away
to fuck with me, so I fight them.
The next day was the same,
they do it again and again…
By nine, not even God himself
would fuck with me.
You don't learn that overnight.
And you don't abandon a kid…
here with some monks.
I'm not abandoning him.
- It's three days, not his entire life.
- What about breastfeeding?
- Breastfeeding?
- Come on.
- Mother's milk.
- Helsi!
Helsi, are you awake?
Yeah, I'm awake.
You're his mother…
- I can't sleep with Jesus looking at me.
- Jesus? What about them?
Denver's unbelievable… I'm so over this.
Just shut up!
Listen to me.
I am a mother, but I'm also your wife.
- And now I'm a thief.
- No, you're not.
And having a child
doesn't mean I stop being other things.
You're a father
and you're not staying here.
All right, we're not Bonnie and Clyde,
but I learn fast and I'm not afraid.
I prepared for the entrance exam
for the Mint for only six weeks.
You can prepare for the Mint.
You can't prepare for something like this.
That secretary doesn't exist.
Mónica Gaztambide
no longer exists, Denver.
She stayed there in the Royal Mint
shooting at the police
to save your ass, Tokyo's and Rio's.
Don't tell me to stay
and warm baby bottles
'cause I'm as much of a thief
as you mother fuckers.
You sexist asshole.
- Nairobi.
- What?
- Don't leave me alone.
- Hey, girl.
Hey, hey, are you okay?
No. No, I'm not okay.
I'm not surprised. I heard everything.
- That ape pulled the breast…
- Mónica…
You are part of the gang.
Mónica, you didn't understand what I was--
She understood everything.
You're a caveman.
What does that mean? "A caveman."
- To your cave!
- What's wrong, girls? What's going on?
Oh, hey, buddy.
Just dealing with the patriarchy.
The patriarchy?
That old paradigm
and its chauvinistic tendencies.
Let's talk about it.
You know what the real patriarchy is?
- What?
- The meat between my legs.
What the fuck is going on?
- Take it easy.
- Go do the dishes!
You're not sexist.
You're an asshole! Fuck this!
Go to your room!
"Me and my dick."
Do you know the time?
It's 3:00 a.m.
In the morning,
you're practicing with thermal lances.
They're 3,000 degrees Celsius.
I think
you should all be well-rested.
To your beds.
Mónica, come back to bed, please.
Forgive us, Professor.
We just had an argument tonight.
I'm going to sleep with Tokyo.
FORTY-TWO MINUTES SINCE D-DAY
Are you okay?
I'm nervous.
Well, relax. After all, it's just like…
like a game of chess.
Only it's the Chess World Championship
and so…
It'll be a long match.
There will be an opening
a battle and
two opposing strategies.
And then finally checkmate.
Oh!
Look, on this side.
Can you feel it?
Another.
Yeah.
They're little kicks.
When I drink coffee,
the baby throws a party in there.
Tell me what you know about the carrier.
I don't know anything about a carrier.
No?
Yes.
Put the mask on.
I don't want to.
You put it on or Osman puts it on.
That's it, come on.
Another little horsey ride.
Let's see if we can remember.
My ankles are killing me.
There they are.
I wasn't prepared
for the crowds of people protesting us.
♪ When you walk ♪
I just wanted to lean
out the window and scream at them,
"I'm Tokyo, I'm one of you."
"We are Dalí."
This mask has become a symbol
throughout the world
of resistance,
of indignation, of skepticism… whatever.
What is important
is it's inspired a lot of people.
Take a look.
This is a demonstration
against corruption in Rio de Janeiro.
Buenos Aires, Argentina,
several protests for women's rights.
Colombia.
Rome.
Paris.
The G20 Summit in Hamburg.
They filled entire stadiums.
This is in France.
Saudi Arabia.
What I'm trying to tell you is
we inspired a lot of people to fight.
And now these people are one of us.
♪ Walk on ♪
♪ We'll all… ♪
Don't forget that.
There they were.
The Professor had put on the mask,
called out the Dalís
and the Dalís had answered.
They organized over social networks,
WhatsApp groups
and began shouting in the streets.
They were telling us
what we most needed to hear.
"You will never walk alone."
ENOUGH
♪ And you'll never… ♪
But all that was just poetry.
The real action started now.
TRAITORS
BANK OF SPAIN, 47 MINUTES SINCE D-DAY
Come on! Move it, move it!
Make sure they stay where they are!
Everybody, calm down.
I said calm down!
Everyone, move back!
The real BRIPAC convoy's on the way.
Eight kilometers out.
8 kilometers takes 6 minutes.
They only have six minutes to do it.
Hail Mary, full of grace…
Quit fucking around.
Hey, you have to say
"The Lord is with thee."
We're in a sacred place.
Have some fucking respect.
Good afternoon. May I?
Of course, Sergio. Here.
Thank you.
I've been studying the two plans in depth.
I've compared them and I have to say
that the plan for the Mint is difficult,
very difficult,
but it's possible and thorough.
But the Bank of Spain…
It's just crazy
and, above all, it's impossible.
- It seems impossible…
- It is.
The fact that it seems impossible
is what makes it so beautiful.
It looks impossible, but…
Palermo, the details.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Bank of Spain.
We're going down ten meters,
twenty,
thirty,
forty…
Until we reach her.
The vault,
which is exactly 48 meters underground.
The chamber is completely airtight.
Why?
Because it floods, ladies and gentlemen.
Those ingenious Galician bastards.
You have to be a sadistic
son of a bitch to invent this.
- Show a little respect.
- It's a compliment, maestro.
It's a genius piece of engineering.
It's a marvel. One of a kind.
They channeled two streams
to run directly to the gold vault.
Forty-five kilometers
of reinforced underground piping.
Why?
If anyone dares
to knock on this tiny door…
the vault will flood
in less than 20 minutes, my friends.
You might touch the gold, but you'll
get squished like a toad and drown.
It's incredible.
Everything is so difficult that
nobody expects anyone to try to break in.
And that's why it'll work.
In fact, it's very simple.
If you apply a bit of talent
and science.
The best minds in engineering,
in physics,
in fluid mechanics…
Just picture them planning a heist.
Excellence in robbery.
But how the fuck will you get in?
Let's see.
There's Civil Guard officers, security men
and the governor's personal escort.
It's a strategic location.
The army will arrive in minutes.
It is impossible to get in
dressed as a thief, of course.
Now Sergio,
imagine that you're the hero
the whole world is waiting for
to save them from the chaos.
It's very easy
to create chaos, little brother.
I'm telling you,
they will receive us with open arms.
CIVIL GUARD
I'm Captain Garrido,
first platoon, sixth BRIPAC company.
Lieutenant Alcázar.
My orders are to assume control
over security of the building.
Remove these people.
Enlarge the perimeter to 150 meters
from the front of the bank.
And open the back door.
Convoy is on its way.
Girls, we're pulling up.
We have orders to coordinate
with you… but not to let a convoy inside.
Sir, the convoy's arrived.
I will not give that order to my men.
Stop the truck.
They're stopping us.
Sir.
They require immediate access.
Jiménez.
Give me a radio.
Defense staff headquarters.
This is Lieutenant Alcázar,
Civil Guard detachment.
I need confirmation for access
of the BRIPAC platoon
to enter the Bank of Spain.
What the fuck is happening?
This is Colonel Castro.
We just declared alert level 5.
I repeat, alert level 5.
From this moment on, the defense
of the interior of the Bank of Spain
and its perimeter is assigned to the army.
You're to put all your men
under Captain Garrido's command
until the arrival
of Colonel Cerceda, understand?
Understood. Right away, Colonel.
Push back the security perimeter!
I want all that riffraff
on the other side of the street.
Clear the area
until the full company arrives.
Prepare the smoke canisters.
Prepare the smoke canisters!
♪ All right, good ♪
Authorization confirmed.
♪ You move it to the left ♪
♪ And you go for yourself ♪
♪ You move it to the right
If it takes all night ♪
♪ Oh, come on baby ♪
Now we're in business. We are in.
♪ So you move to the left all night ♪
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
- Have you ever heard of aikido?
- I have, it's an air conditioner.
It's those chocolate-covered sticks
that taste like cardboard
that everybody eats but nobody likes.
Aikido.
Using the strength of your enemy
in your favor.
For instance, the ten of us cannot take
the Bank of Spain.
The strength of our enemy is
far greater than our own. That's why…
we will apply aikido.
What do you mean, Professor?
Whatever we can't do ourselves
will be done by the Civil Guard,
the Spanish Army
and even the bank's own security.
They will make sure
no one gets within 150 meters.
We will find out the exact number
of hostages in the building.
How many people are in this building?
The bank security guards
will give us the number.
Three hundred sixty-seven.
Aikido.
I want all 367 down here in three minutes.
We'll place charges
on the facade and windows
in broad daylight without being seen.
And how?
The smoke bombs the Civil Guard
will set off to disperse the crowd.
Aikido.
Evacuation protocol…
I want everyone down here
in three minutes. Come on!
- This is not a drill.
- Let's go.
Evacuation protocol.
We'll get the staff and customers
out by using perfectly-rehearsed protocol.
And how?
You heard it, we are evacuating.
Everyone, gather in the hall right now!
Come on, come on.
Evacuation protocol.
I want you to head out
in an orderly manner.
Civil Guard and security
will sweep the building, office by office,
and evacuate everyone
in less than three minutes.
Aikido!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry! Let's go, quickly!
Come on, come on.
That's it, keep going.
They will help load in all the materials
we need for the heist.
I'm going to ask you all
to please keep calm.
We're going to evacuate the building
in two phases. Group one and group two.
They will escort
all the extra hostages out of the building
and will have taken a problem
off our hands.
Aikido!
Group one, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's go. All the way down,
all the way down! Go!
Do not stop. Let's go!
I said do not stop!
All the way! Go!
Go, go!
Move, move!
And then,
when everyone is where they should be…
we just have to press a button.
And this button…
I'm the one who's gonna press it.
No turning back now.