1
00:00:18,562 --> 00:00:20,896
There are always happier days to remember.

2
00:00:21,771 --> 00:00:26,521
The more fucked you are,
the happier those days seem to be.

3
00:00:27,104 --> 00:00:28,646
While hoping for a miracle

4
00:00:28,729 --> 00:00:31,229
and hearing the beep
of Nairobi's vital signs,

5
00:00:31,312 --> 00:00:35,562
I remembered those days,
like the soccer match at the monastery.

6
00:00:36,146 --> 00:00:38,437
- Keep up the defense. One minute left.
- Come on.

7
00:00:38,521 --> 00:00:40,437
- Hey!
- Come on.

8
00:00:40,521 --> 00:00:41,479
Go.

9
00:00:42,187 --> 00:00:43,021
Take this.

10
00:00:43,104 --> 00:00:47,521
I never imagined the seconds before
a corner kick could be so much fun.

11
00:00:48,271 --> 00:00:49,187
Hey!

12
00:00:49,271 --> 00:00:50,854
Ref, he touched my balls!

13
00:00:50,937 --> 00:00:52,021
You saw that.

14
00:00:53,021 --> 00:00:57,021
Please! Enough. There's a minute left.
Are you going to waste it arguing?

15
00:00:57,104 --> 00:00:59,104
I was defending. He was glued to my ass!

16
00:00:59,187 --> 00:01:01,396
I saw you touching his balls, pig.

17
00:01:01,479 --> 00:01:04,854
That's enough!
Don't touch him again... anywhere, OK?

18
00:01:04,937 --> 00:01:06,854
- Or you'll be sent off.
- OK, go.

19
00:01:06,937 --> 00:01:07,771
Come on, go!

20
00:01:09,729 --> 00:01:10,854
It's a goal!

21
00:01:12,312 --> 00:01:13,271
Penalty!

22
00:01:13,354 --> 00:01:16,271
- Let's see what happens.
- There's gonna be a fight.

23
00:01:18,479 --> 00:01:19,396
There we go!

24
00:01:19,479 --> 00:01:21,937
Penalty and a red card. Get out of here!

25
00:01:25,604 --> 00:01:27,062
- Tokyo!
- Go.

26
00:01:29,771 --> 00:01:32,771
- There's no signal. Everything's down.
- What do we do?

27
00:01:32,854 --> 00:01:35,396
- We're losing her.
- No, fuck!

28
00:01:59,396 --> 00:02:00,437
Carefully.

29
00:02:01,229 --> 00:02:02,229
Slowly.

30
00:02:03,521 --> 00:02:04,854
OK, I have it.

31
00:02:06,021 --> 00:02:07,271
A little bit higher.

32
00:02:08,396 --> 00:02:09,937
You're doing really well.

33
00:02:10,604 --> 00:02:12,271
Now remove the bullet.

34
00:02:14,812 --> 00:02:15,729
Go on.

35
00:02:18,521 --> 00:02:19,437
That's it.

36
00:02:20,312 --> 00:02:21,271
Good.

37
00:02:21,354 --> 00:02:22,979
Be careful. That's it.

38
00:02:23,729 --> 00:02:24,896
There it is.

39
00:02:50,937 --> 00:02:52,146
That is nostalgia:

40
00:02:52,896 --> 00:02:57,437
finding out that past events
you hadn't even imagined were happiness

41
00:02:58,104 --> 00:02:58,937
actually were.

42
00:03:09,062 --> 00:03:10,396
Yeah!

43
00:03:15,812 --> 00:03:18,771
We hadn't even
reached the end of the first half,

44
00:03:18,854 --> 00:03:23,229
and Lisbon was 3 kilometers from the tent
and forced to switch jerseys.

45
00:03:23,687 --> 00:03:25,437
Goal by Sierra into the top corner.

46
00:03:28,396 --> 00:03:30,437
Meanwhile, like robots,

47
00:03:30,771 --> 00:03:33,312
we removed a piece of Nairobi's lung.

48
00:03:34,271 --> 00:03:36,687
We didn't know
if we were saving her life

49
00:03:36,771 --> 00:03:38,229
or finishing her off.

50
00:03:38,812 --> 00:03:40,271
A second teammate down.

51
00:03:41,229 --> 00:03:42,937
And a second goal against us.

52
00:03:45,229 --> 00:03:47,979
And the third was yet to come,
from Palermo.

53
00:03:48,437 --> 00:03:50,021
But it'd be on our side.

54
00:03:57,479 --> 00:03:59,104
He had been a good captain.

55
00:04:01,396 --> 00:04:03,396
But he was an awful team player.

56
00:04:26,521 --> 00:04:30,479
The only thing resembling the plan
was the Professor's arrival in Madrid.

57
00:04:30,646 --> 00:04:34,521
But not even that was right.
A rider was missing.

58
00:04:35,854 --> 00:04:36,771
Professor...

59
00:04:37,479 --> 00:04:38,396
we have to go.

60
00:04:51,687 --> 00:04:55,729
By motorbike and along forest trails,
dirt roads, and cattle routes,

61
00:04:55,812 --> 00:04:58,354
they crossed La Mancha,
avoiding checkpoints.

62
00:04:58,437 --> 00:04:59,896
The knight and his squire,

63
00:04:59,979 --> 00:05:04,604
defeat after defeat, advancing towards
a battle of fools in this unwinnable war.

64
00:05:05,187 --> 00:05:07,979
Meanwhile, everything
was about to explode.

65
00:06:32,021 --> 00:06:33,354
Can you believe this?

66
00:06:35,812 --> 00:06:37,187
Me, pregnant.

67
00:06:38,979 --> 00:06:40,521
Who would have thought?

68
00:06:41,479 --> 00:06:42,604
Congratulations.

69
00:06:43,896 --> 00:06:44,812
Thank you.

70
00:07:51,812 --> 00:07:52,771
Seriously...

71
00:07:54,437 --> 00:07:56,104
you're very brave, you know?

72
00:07:56,604 --> 00:07:57,896
I did what I had to.

73
00:07:57,979 --> 00:08:00,979
Unless we make a stand,
they'll trample us like in Auschwitz.

74
00:08:01,396 --> 00:08:03,062
If it stings too much, tell me.

75
00:08:03,146 --> 00:08:06,854
Go ahead, put alcohol on it.
I can handle pain. I'm used to it.

76
00:08:08,229 --> 00:08:09,062
Let's see...

77
00:08:13,437 --> 00:08:14,271
Keep going.

78
00:08:39,854 --> 00:08:44,521
Have you lost your mind?
You beat the crap out of him.

79
00:08:44,687 --> 00:08:48,312
- You can't lose it like that!
- How can I not? This is a pressure cooker.

80
00:08:48,396 --> 00:08:49,312
Exactly!

81
00:08:49,646 --> 00:08:53,562
That's why you can't come to blows
with people, like a spoiled brat!

82
00:08:58,979 --> 00:09:00,812
You have blood... Your top's...

83
00:09:01,562 --> 00:09:04,521
Don't worry about me.
I can't see with this eye.

84
00:09:12,937 --> 00:09:14,187
Listen, Amanda...

85
00:09:14,854 --> 00:09:18,146
have you had any anxiety attacks
because of the heist?

86
00:09:20,437 --> 00:09:23,229
- Well... I think so.
- I see.

87
00:09:24,896 --> 00:09:28,604
And I can't sleep
for more than 30 minutes straight.

88
00:09:28,687 --> 00:09:31,437
Because I have a knot right here, and I...

89
00:09:33,937 --> 00:09:36,104
That's normal in these cases.

90
00:09:36,437 --> 00:09:38,271
There's a lot of tension.

91
00:09:38,937 --> 00:09:42,812
A lot of tension. But don't worry,
I'll get you some sedatives.

92
00:09:43,229 --> 00:09:49,521
We don't want you getting PTSD,
because it's so hard to get over.

93
00:09:49,604 --> 00:09:51,187
In fact, sometimes...

94
00:09:51,729 --> 00:09:53,104
it lasts forever.

95
00:09:55,646 --> 00:09:58,229
Let me help you. You have some blood here.

96
00:10:00,062 --> 00:10:05,021
Don't worry, while I'm around...
you'll have everything you need.

97
00:10:08,687 --> 00:10:10,562
You'll be my personal project.

98
00:10:13,729 --> 00:10:18,104
We're holding up the Bank of Spain.
Maybe you've forgotten, but I haven't.

99
00:10:18,187 --> 00:10:21,271
- We never acted like dicks before.
- Maybe I'm traumatized.

100
00:10:21,354 --> 00:10:24,146
Maybe that's what's up.
We're all traumatized.

101
00:10:25,146 --> 00:10:27,687
What the fuck do you mean?
What's my trauma?

102
00:10:28,354 --> 00:10:29,521
- I'm not...
- Tell me.

103
00:10:29,604 --> 00:10:30,812
You broke up with Tokyo.

104
00:10:31,354 --> 00:10:34,187
How many guys do you know
who would leave Tokyo?

105
00:10:34,562 --> 00:10:36,854
None, because you don't leave Tokyo.

106
00:10:39,354 --> 00:10:41,104
What do you know about Tokyo?

107
00:10:41,187 --> 00:10:44,104
Tokyo is a fucking Maserati.
Everyone wants one.

108
00:10:44,187 --> 00:10:45,979
If you leave one in the street

109
00:10:46,062 --> 00:10:49,646
with the doors open and keys in it,
you've gotta be fucked up.

110
00:10:51,979 --> 00:10:54,646
Look, Rio. I'm gonna make this very clear:

111
00:10:56,021 --> 00:10:59,021
maybe your trauma comes
from them affecting your manhood.

112
00:10:59,979 --> 00:11:03,146
Maybe they pushed you too far...
with the torture.

113
00:11:04,437 --> 00:11:08,062
You need to let it out.
That's why you left Tokyo, isn't it?

114
00:11:08,521 --> 00:11:12,354
If one person did it or if it was a group,
the trauma it causes is different.

115
00:11:12,437 --> 00:11:13,437
Let it out!

116
00:11:15,771 --> 00:11:19,604
You can count on me...
for whatever you need.

117
00:11:21,271 --> 00:11:22,229
Anything.

118
00:11:38,021 --> 00:11:39,604
Ladies and gentlemen...

119
00:11:41,146 --> 00:11:43,854
I regret to inform you
that I must say goodbye.

120
00:11:44,146 --> 00:11:45,062
I'm leaving.

121
00:11:45,687 --> 00:11:49,937
- Keep up the good spirits.
- What the fuck are you doing?

122
00:11:51,354 --> 00:11:52,229
Matías...

123
00:11:53,562 --> 00:11:54,521
I'm leaving.

124
00:11:56,937 --> 00:11:59,729
Pleasure working with you, as always.

125
00:12:01,396 --> 00:12:02,646
I would even say...

126
00:12:04,146 --> 00:12:05,937
that I love you a lot, Matías.

127
00:12:06,687 --> 00:12:08,312
As for all of you...

128
00:12:08,771 --> 00:12:11,312
I hope my leadership
hasn't been too traumatic.

129
00:12:11,396 --> 00:12:15,604
You can tell your grandchildren
and loved ones this story. Anyway...

130
00:12:16,062 --> 00:12:17,687
Ladies and gentlemen,

131
00:12:18,104 --> 00:12:19,437
it's been a pleasure.

132
00:12:25,437 --> 00:12:26,812
What the...?

133
00:12:32,896 --> 00:12:34,062
Calm down.

134
00:12:35,562 --> 00:12:37,646
Palermo, calm down.

135
00:12:38,604 --> 00:12:41,646
Let's talk... calmly.

136
00:12:43,854 --> 00:12:45,354
But you're not leaving.

137
00:12:51,521 --> 00:12:52,687
Fucking hell!

138
00:12:53,312 --> 00:12:56,896
You staged a coup d'état, you bitch!
What did you expect?

139
00:12:56,979 --> 00:13:00,479
I'm in charge of the military side,
you're in charge of the technical.

140
00:13:00,562 --> 00:13:01,729
The technical side?

141
00:13:03,104 --> 00:13:06,396
Do I look like
some nerdy engineer with glasses?

142
00:13:08,229 --> 00:13:10,937
What sort of orders would I give?

143
00:13:11,729 --> 00:13:13,521
Now melt, now don't!

144
00:13:13,604 --> 00:13:17,062
Bathyscaphe out! Bathyscaphe in!
Immersion! Emersion!

145
00:13:18,687 --> 00:13:20,729
Who the fuck do you think I am?

146
00:13:21,271 --> 00:13:25,354
I didn't come here for this shit!
This is beneath me. I'm off.

147
00:13:28,229 --> 00:13:32,479
I'm activating the manual door,
and I'm doing you a favor.

148
00:13:34,271 --> 00:13:36,896
Because if I stay,
I'll shoot the shit out of you

149
00:13:36,979 --> 00:13:38,437
and the rest of them.

150
00:13:40,646 --> 00:13:42,396
I'm not on your side anymore.

151
00:13:51,146 --> 00:13:56,521
It's me who's doing you a favor.
Because I swear, the next thing I'll do...

152
00:13:57,521 --> 00:13:58,979
is kill you.

153
00:13:59,604 --> 00:14:00,604
I don't think so.

154
00:14:01,812 --> 00:14:02,854
I think so.

155
00:14:12,354 --> 00:14:13,729
Claymore mines...

156
00:14:14,979 --> 00:14:16,479
which, as you can see...

157
00:14:17,437 --> 00:14:19,229
are pointing towards you.

158
00:14:19,604 --> 00:14:21,146
They won't get me.

159
00:14:22,646 --> 00:14:25,479
You know I have no qualms
about killing you.

160
00:14:26,312 --> 00:14:27,396
Easy.

161
00:14:27,479 --> 00:14:29,437
You can't betray us like this.

162
00:14:30,229 --> 00:14:31,354
Do you want to bet?

163
00:14:33,687 --> 00:14:36,562
Palermo! Don't move!

164
00:14:37,646 --> 00:14:38,521
Oh, good.

165
00:14:38,604 --> 00:14:42,604
The mad princess came
to wave her prince goodbye at the station.

166
00:14:42,687 --> 00:14:44,521
Have some dignity!

167
00:14:44,979 --> 00:14:48,187
Where are you going? To prison?

168
00:14:49,937 --> 00:14:51,604
To be shot in the forehead?

169
00:14:52,271 --> 00:14:53,604
To sell us out?

170
00:14:53,687 --> 00:14:55,229
I won't sell anyone out.

171
00:14:55,312 --> 00:14:57,604
I have a safeguard: state secrets.

172
00:14:57,687 --> 00:14:59,312
I won't betray you.

173
00:14:59,396 --> 00:15:00,812
Leaving is betrayal.

174
00:15:01,312 --> 00:15:03,312
Leaving us alone here is betrayal.

175
00:15:04,146 --> 00:15:05,229
Don't...

176
00:15:05,312 --> 00:15:07,729
move, I don't want to kill you, big man.

177
00:15:08,937 --> 00:15:10,479
You don't want to kill me?

178
00:15:16,271 --> 00:15:17,771
You'll have to kill me.

179
00:15:18,396 --> 00:15:20,896
What you're doing is crazy, Helsinki.

180
00:15:22,854 --> 00:15:24,437
If you leave, Palermo...

181
00:15:25,812 --> 00:15:26,812
I swear...

182
00:15:27,854 --> 00:15:29,771
I'll go boom...

183
00:15:29,854 --> 00:15:32,187
boom... ciao.

184
00:15:34,729 --> 00:15:38,354
I'm serious, Palermo. I will.

185
00:15:45,229 --> 00:15:46,229
Seriously.

186
00:15:50,396 --> 00:15:51,687
I got you.

187
00:16:12,937 --> 00:16:14,937
What the hell did you say to Rio?

188
00:16:15,021 --> 00:16:17,562
- About what?
- You told him he's traumatized.

189
00:16:17,979 --> 00:16:20,437
Call it what you like,
but something's up.

190
00:16:20,521 --> 00:16:22,771
Something's up?
Because he left Tokyo?

191
00:16:22,854 --> 00:16:25,396
- Because she's a... Maserati.
- Look...

192
00:16:26,479 --> 00:16:28,854
The Maserati thing is the way guys talk.

193
00:16:28,937 --> 00:16:32,437
What I'm saying is
something happened during the torture.

194
00:16:33,187 --> 00:16:36,062
- They pushed him too far.
- They did what?

195
00:16:36,146 --> 00:16:38,687
Forty sweaty guys opened his back door.

196
00:16:38,979 --> 00:16:40,479
In his back door.

197
00:16:40,562 --> 00:16:44,479
Rio was tortured,
and you go and give him all that shit.

198
00:16:44,562 --> 00:16:47,271
It's true.
I asked if they crossed the line.

199
00:16:47,354 --> 00:16:51,396
Know what? He went quiet
because he can't face it. A textbook case.

200
00:16:51,479 --> 00:16:52,312
No.

201
00:16:54,104 --> 00:16:55,021
I can't.

202
00:16:56,312 --> 00:16:57,312
You can't what?

203
00:16:58,646 --> 00:17:00,937
You know? All of a sudden I feel...

204
00:17:02,104 --> 00:17:04,771
- as if the bubble has burst.
- What bubble?

205
00:17:04,937 --> 00:17:05,854
What bubble?

206
00:17:07,062 --> 00:17:10,146
No, I want to know
what bubble we're talking about.

207
00:17:10,437 --> 00:17:11,354
What bubble?

208
00:17:14,312 --> 00:17:17,187
It's as if a blindfold
has fallen from my eyes.

209
00:17:18,146 --> 00:17:20,146
I don't recognize you.

210
00:17:21,062 --> 00:17:25,271
I don't know what we're doing together.
I don't know who you are.

211
00:17:25,687 --> 00:17:27,854
Mónica... don't get me wrong.

212
00:17:27,979 --> 00:17:31,187
Tokyo may be a Maserati,
but it doesn't mean you're a 600.

213
00:17:36,479 --> 00:17:37,646
I'm sorry, Denver.

214
00:17:38,479 --> 00:17:39,854
I can't stay with you.

215
00:17:56,521 --> 00:17:57,479
Right.

216
00:17:59,396 --> 00:18:03,437
When you see her coming at you,
angry like a hydra, shut up.

217
00:18:05,104 --> 00:18:09,104
A hydra... A... Never mind.
Just keep your fucking mouth shut.

218
00:18:09,187 --> 00:18:11,187
- And not defend myself?
- No.

219
00:18:11,271 --> 00:18:14,062
Because you don't even know
why she's angry.

220
00:18:14,271 --> 00:18:15,812
You, hush.

221
00:18:15,896 --> 00:18:18,146
The less you know
what she's talking about,

222
00:18:18,229 --> 00:18:19,271
the sorrier you are.

223
00:18:19,729 --> 00:18:23,521
You say, "Yes, sorry, darling"
to everything.

224
00:18:23,604 --> 00:18:25,396
Now, that is a textbook case.

225
00:18:25,479 --> 00:18:28,979
- From a textbook for the henpecked.
- No, for survivors.

226
00:18:29,062 --> 00:18:30,896
You wait for the storm to pass.

227
00:18:30,979 --> 00:18:33,896
When you work out
which way the wind is blowing,

228
00:18:33,979 --> 00:18:36,604
and when she has calmed down,

229
00:18:37,104 --> 00:18:39,854
then, and only then...

230
00:18:41,521 --> 00:18:42,687
you make your move.

231
00:18:45,062 --> 00:18:46,562
Didn't you see me before?

232
00:18:46,979 --> 00:18:50,646
We've had problems since the monastery.
That's what's going on.

233
00:18:50,729 --> 00:18:53,437
- Well...
- This has been building up.

234
00:18:54,271 --> 00:18:57,062
And with all this pressure,
it all comes out.

235
00:18:58,729 --> 00:18:59,979
That's what's up.

236
00:19:17,812 --> 00:19:18,646
Professor.

237
00:19:20,521 --> 00:19:21,396
It's Tokyo.

238
00:19:26,021 --> 00:19:29,437
- You just staged a coup d'état.
- Palermo's gone crazy.

239
00:19:29,521 --> 00:19:32,021
He almost blew up the lobby.

240
00:19:32,104 --> 00:19:34,937
- But we've got it under control.
- You don't.

241
00:19:35,021 --> 00:19:37,521
You can't control him. He's unpredictable.

242
00:19:37,604 --> 00:19:39,687
He's tied up and under surveillance 24/7.

243
00:19:39,771 --> 00:19:42,104
Tokyo, the plan is falling to pieces!

244
00:19:43,437 --> 00:19:45,437
I'm still here, Professor.

245
00:19:45,521 --> 00:19:47,146
So what?

246
00:19:47,229 --> 00:19:49,854
Without Palermo,
we can't get the gold out.

247
00:19:49,937 --> 00:19:51,562
Do you know how to do it?

248
00:19:52,021 --> 00:19:53,229
And without Nairobi!

249
00:19:53,979 --> 00:19:55,146
And without Lisbon!

250
00:20:13,271 --> 00:20:17,062
Palermo was leaving
because it's the only smart thing to do.

251
00:20:18,396 --> 00:20:19,229
Professor...

252
00:20:20,062 --> 00:20:22,062
you've been my guardian angel.

253
00:20:23,521 --> 00:20:24,604
Now it's my turn.

254
00:20:28,937 --> 00:20:30,062
How did it happen?

255
00:20:31,937 --> 00:20:33,646
She died to protect me.

256
00:20:34,104 --> 00:20:35,687
I'm really sorry.

257
00:20:36,312 --> 00:20:37,229
I...

258
00:20:38,104 --> 00:20:41,146
was camouflaged
in a tree, and there were...

259
00:20:42,812 --> 00:20:45,271
soldiers and police officers everywhere.

260
00:20:47,021 --> 00:20:49,937
She was on a farm.
That's where they found her.

261
00:20:50,771 --> 00:20:54,646
They made her kneel down, unarmed,
and they asked her about me.

262
00:20:55,229 --> 00:20:57,312
I ran and ran.

263
00:20:57,396 --> 00:20:59,604
They asked her, "Where's the Professor?"

264
00:21:02,021 --> 00:21:03,687
I said, "Tell them, Raquel.

265
00:21:05,021 --> 00:21:08,604
Tell them where I am,
tell them I'll surrender, please."

266
00:21:10,104 --> 00:21:11,354
"I don't know."

267
00:21:12,396 --> 00:21:14,312
She repeated, "I don't know."

268
00:21:16,646 --> 00:21:18,229
And they shot her twice.

269
00:21:20,896 --> 00:21:23,271
She was unarmed,
and they shot her twice.

270
00:21:27,146 --> 00:21:28,896
I didn't make it in time.

271
00:21:40,937 --> 00:21:41,896
Did you see it?

272
00:21:43,646 --> 00:21:44,854
You only heard it?

273
00:21:46,354 --> 00:21:49,812
Professor,
did you see them moving her body?

274
00:21:49,896 --> 00:21:51,229
I had to run.

275
00:21:52,146 --> 00:21:53,062
Listen to me.

276
00:21:53,771 --> 00:21:56,396
I also heard
my mother tell me to come home,

277
00:21:56,687 --> 00:21:58,354
that I'd be safer there.

278
00:21:58,479 --> 00:22:01,021
But 20 cops
were waiting in her kitchen.

279
00:22:01,687 --> 00:22:06,562
And in the tent,
they also heard us fleeing from the bank,

280
00:22:07,729 --> 00:22:08,979
but we're still here.

281
00:22:09,479 --> 00:22:12,187
The only one who left
was a ferret with a hood.

282
00:22:15,229 --> 00:22:16,812
Is there anything in the news?

283
00:22:17,396 --> 00:22:18,271
Nothing.

284
00:22:21,729 --> 00:22:23,062
The same as with Rio.

285
00:22:26,479 --> 00:22:28,396
If they'd killed her, we'd know.

286
00:22:33,146 --> 00:22:34,562
She's being interrogated.

287
00:22:37,437 --> 00:22:40,021
- Where are you going?
- The Bank of Spain.

288
00:22:40,104 --> 00:22:42,687
It's not a good idea. It's too risky.

289
00:22:43,521 --> 00:22:45,271
I appreciate your concern,

290
00:22:45,354 --> 00:22:48,812
but it's the only place I can find out
if my partner's alive. Move.

291
00:22:48,896 --> 00:22:50,396
- No.
- I'm asking you.

292
00:22:50,479 --> 00:22:52,271
- No, Professor.
- Move.

293
00:22:52,354 --> 00:22:54,812
I won't let you get on the motorbike.

294
00:23:05,562 --> 00:23:06,479
Seventy.

295
00:23:09,896 --> 00:23:14,062
With what we have in those reports,
you'll be 70 when you're released.

296
00:23:15,354 --> 00:23:16,396
Paula will be 40.

297
00:23:17,187 --> 00:23:21,104
And your mother will be so long dead,
she'll be bones in a grave.

298
00:23:21,187 --> 00:23:23,146
Stop, you don't need to go on.

299
00:23:24,187 --> 00:23:26,896
The recommended sentence
depends on the prosecutor, not you.

300
00:23:27,312 --> 00:23:29,312
And the final decision, on the judge.

301
00:23:31,521 --> 00:23:32,896
But you know full well

302
00:23:33,521 --> 00:23:35,771
that the prosecutor and the judge

303
00:23:35,937 --> 00:23:39,896
work with what I write in these reports.

304
00:23:41,479 --> 00:23:43,479
And I can write whatever I want.

305
00:23:45,021 --> 00:23:46,729
What do you want me to write?

306
00:23:48,229 --> 00:23:50,812
You're going to make me
resort to violence.

307
00:23:50,896 --> 00:23:53,437
- I'm protecting the plan.
- It's my plan.

308
00:23:53,521 --> 00:23:56,146
This isn't the plan. It's improvisation.

309
00:23:56,229 --> 00:23:59,229
You always say, "No improvising."

310
00:23:59,312 --> 00:24:01,062
I won't give in.

311
00:24:01,854 --> 00:24:03,312
You need to understand

312
00:24:03,396 --> 00:24:06,187
that that's the only place
I can get answers.

313
00:24:06,271 --> 00:24:07,437
In the Bank of...

314
00:24:10,771 --> 00:24:12,146
Very well.

315
00:24:13,229 --> 00:24:14,646
Seriously, Professor?

316
00:24:16,396 --> 00:24:19,729
I don't know where the Professor is,
or what he'll do.

317
00:24:21,271 --> 00:24:22,354
Can't you think?

318
00:24:23,562 --> 00:24:25,479
Has love clouded your mind?

319
00:24:26,354 --> 00:24:28,771
The plan includes this kind of firewall.

320
00:24:29,771 --> 00:24:31,771
It's nothing to do with love.

321
00:24:31,854 --> 00:24:33,187
Of course it is.

322
00:24:33,271 --> 00:24:37,354
But just think,
in prison, love drains away like water.

323
00:24:37,437 --> 00:24:40,771
It disappears fast.
In two months, it's all dried up.

324
00:24:40,854 --> 00:24:43,396
Two months of suffering
or a life in prison?

325
00:24:45,896 --> 00:24:48,271
Even if you were reincarnated seven times,

326
00:24:48,937 --> 00:24:51,354
you still wouldn't understand
our love.

327
00:24:51,437 --> 00:24:52,812
To protect the plan,

328
00:24:52,896 --> 00:24:55,521
we need to see
if she's being interrogated there.

329
00:24:55,604 --> 00:24:58,062
If so, it'll be Alicia Sierra doing it,

330
00:24:58,146 --> 00:25:01,021
and she'll be at the Bank of Spain.

331
00:25:01,979 --> 00:25:03,229
But you can't go!

332
00:25:03,771 --> 00:25:07,312
Let me tell you
about the nature of your love.

333
00:25:07,646 --> 00:25:09,937
One in jail in Soto del Real,
the other in Cádiz,

334
00:25:10,021 --> 00:25:12,021
waiting for a yearly conjugal visit.

335
00:25:12,104 --> 00:25:15,729
That's if you're lucky.
Because if we don't catch your lover,

336
00:25:15,812 --> 00:25:18,437
you won't ever fucking see him again.

337
00:25:18,771 --> 00:25:23,354
Choose between that or getting out in time
to be a mother to your daughter.

338
00:25:23,437 --> 00:25:26,271
You're trying
to emotionally manipulate me.

339
00:25:26,354 --> 00:25:28,021
I'm just speaking the truth.

340
00:25:29,021 --> 00:25:30,104
As always.

341
00:25:31,646 --> 00:25:33,437
To protect the plan, we must go.

342
00:25:33,521 --> 00:25:37,396
How will you go to the tent
if your face is all over the news?

343
00:25:39,104 --> 00:25:40,437
Like everyone else.

344
00:25:41,937 --> 00:25:43,687
In a red jumpsuit and a Dalí mask.

345
00:25:44,354 --> 00:25:46,021
Oh, good.

346
00:25:47,896 --> 00:25:49,562
She won't betray us.

347
00:25:49,646 --> 00:25:50,771
Give me your hand.

348
00:25:54,729 --> 00:25:55,812
Give me your hand.

349
00:25:59,187 --> 00:26:02,312
How many times have you thought
you'd fallen in love before?

350
00:26:06,687 --> 00:26:10,312
The same will happen this time,
and you know it.

351
00:26:17,312 --> 00:26:20,229
Everyone is capable of betrayal,
Marseille.

352
00:26:20,312 --> 00:26:21,729
You only have to know...

353
00:26:24,937 --> 00:26:27,812
That was quite a punch...
I thought we were finished.

354
00:26:28,354 --> 00:26:29,187
Were we?

355
00:26:30,146 --> 00:26:31,021
I didn't know.

356
00:27:15,896 --> 00:27:18,646
- Have some more to drink.
- I've had two.

357
00:27:18,729 --> 00:27:19,979
You look so serious.

358
00:27:21,229 --> 00:27:23,229
This is a weird wedding, Andrés.

359
00:27:23,312 --> 00:27:24,562
It's a great party!

360
00:27:24,646 --> 00:27:26,896
- Brother!
- I feel bad for her. She's young,

361
00:27:26,979 --> 00:27:29,854
and she's in love, but you're sick.

362
00:27:29,937 --> 00:27:33,854
Didn't you hear the priest?
"Till death do you part."

363
00:27:35,812 --> 00:27:38,271
Maybe for you it's the grand finale,

364
00:27:38,354 --> 00:27:41,562
but for her, it's the beginning,
and it isn't a fair one.

365
00:27:42,562 --> 00:27:44,396
She knows I'm sick.

366
00:27:44,479 --> 00:27:46,479
Everyone knows I'm sick.

367
00:27:46,562 --> 00:27:48,812
You're betraying her feelings.

368
00:27:50,604 --> 00:27:54,146
I'll give her
the best two or three years of her life.

369
00:27:54,271 --> 00:27:58,187
Yes, and after that...
Actually, I will betray her in a way.

370
00:27:59,812 --> 00:28:00,854
Anyway.

371
00:28:00,937 --> 00:28:03,312
Betrayal is an inherent part of love.

372
00:28:03,687 --> 00:28:06,062
Since we're on the subject, have a look.

373
00:28:06,146 --> 00:28:07,021
Martín.

374
00:28:08,396 --> 00:28:11,396
What a legend! My best friend. He's happy.

375
00:28:11,729 --> 00:28:13,104
Would he betray me?

376
00:28:15,229 --> 00:28:16,729
Of course he would,

377
00:28:16,812 --> 00:28:19,396
in the right circumstances. Tatiana?

378
00:28:21,354 --> 00:28:22,604
Tatiana would too.

379
00:28:22,687 --> 00:28:28,312
You say you experience love,
but you only see traitors everywhere.

380
00:28:28,396 --> 00:28:29,937
No, I'm not saying that.

381
00:28:30,771 --> 00:28:35,646
I'm saying, betrayal doesn't depend on
how or how much you love someone.

382
00:28:35,729 --> 00:28:39,646
It depends on
how difficult your dilemma is.

383
00:28:40,062 --> 00:28:42,729
Would you betray your beloved?
In theory, no.

384
00:28:42,812 --> 00:28:45,396
But what if you were told
that if you did,

385
00:28:45,479 --> 00:28:48,771
you'd be given a drug
to save your beloved brother?

386
00:28:50,937 --> 00:28:52,604
That is a real dilemma.

387
00:29:19,521 --> 00:29:21,646
Sergio Marquina. Emotional coldness.

388
00:29:22,687 --> 00:29:24,604
Compulsive narcissism.

389
00:29:24,979 --> 00:29:26,729
Pathological shyness.

390
00:29:27,146 --> 00:29:28,729
Psychopathic traits...

391
00:29:31,146 --> 00:29:32,729
- In short, a gem.
- Well.

392
00:29:33,687 --> 00:29:37,104
A report written by a mock expert
without interviewing the subject.

393
00:29:37,854 --> 00:29:41,146
He's much more fun
than what it says there.

394
00:29:42,312 --> 00:29:43,146
Cool.

395
00:29:44,437 --> 00:29:46,979
Yeah, a psychopath can be so much fun.

396
00:29:48,146 --> 00:29:49,479
Then there's your profile.

397
00:29:50,937 --> 00:29:52,229
What about it?

398
00:29:52,312 --> 00:29:55,729
You're the caring type that gets attached
to this sort of jerk.

399
00:29:57,271 --> 00:29:58,396
You idealize them.

400
00:29:59,354 --> 00:30:04,396
Gradually, you get smaller by their side.
Then, they use and manipulate you.

401
00:30:05,521 --> 00:30:08,604
When did you give up on
your gut instinct, inspector?

402
00:30:09,687 --> 00:30:12,187
Before the Professor came into your life?

403
00:30:13,229 --> 00:30:18,021
Because Alberto used to beat you up.
How does this one humiliate you?

404
00:30:19,896 --> 00:30:23,771
First you use my mother's Alzheimer's
and now domestic violence.

405
00:30:23,854 --> 00:30:28,604
Tell me the story is not repeating itself.
Tell me at some point it hasn't clicked,

406
00:30:28,687 --> 00:30:32,229
and you've thought, "Careful,
this guy could be a bastard."

407
00:30:33,521 --> 00:30:34,646
Say it's not true.

408
00:30:35,771 --> 00:30:38,396
You know about protocols and negotiation,
but so do I.

409
00:30:38,812 --> 00:30:40,104
I beat you, Raquel.

410
00:30:40,521 --> 00:30:44,187
I must be a fool,
because I thought we had fallen in love.

411
00:30:44,271 --> 00:30:45,479
I didn't ask you to come.

412
00:30:45,562 --> 00:30:46,937
It was a bluff.

413
00:30:47,021 --> 00:30:49,396
She hung up,
and we didn't even play our hand!

414
00:30:49,479 --> 00:30:52,062
She went for you
because you're the weakest link.

415
00:30:54,187 --> 00:30:55,562
What's he done for you?

416
00:30:55,646 --> 00:30:58,229
Would he go to an island
with his family for you?

417
00:30:59,396 --> 00:31:01,396
Would he follow a plan of yours?

418
00:31:02,771 --> 00:31:06,812
Have you ever been the protagonist? Ever?

419
00:31:08,062 --> 00:31:10,687
Or have you always followed him
like a puppy?

420
00:31:11,229 --> 00:31:14,271
I warned you about Alberto.
He was a son of a bitch.

421
00:31:15,229 --> 00:31:16,687
And this guy's the same.

422
00:31:18,062 --> 00:31:20,187
The question is very simple, Raquel:

423
00:31:22,062 --> 00:31:24,562
do you deserve to spend 30 years in prison

424
00:31:25,146 --> 00:31:27,062
for an idiot in a mask?

425
00:31:33,437 --> 00:31:34,354
Colonel...

426
00:31:35,812 --> 00:31:39,271
I've been checking the reports,
and it may be my mistake,

427
00:31:39,354 --> 00:31:42,479
but I can't find
the records for Murillo's arrest.

428
00:31:43,021 --> 00:31:46,437
- You've been checking what?
- I don't want a technicality...

429
00:31:46,521 --> 00:31:49,729
Well, you know...
it's a question of human rights.

430
00:31:49,812 --> 00:31:52,896
What's wrong with you?
Did you join an NGO?

431
00:31:52,979 --> 00:31:55,271
Amnesty International? Cut the crap.

432
00:31:55,354 --> 00:31:57,062
But according to the law...

433
00:31:57,146 --> 00:32:00,312
Do you know
when we start applying the law in here?

434
00:32:01,271 --> 00:32:02,979
Can you guess?

435
00:32:03,521 --> 00:32:04,771
Give me an answer.

436
00:32:06,187 --> 00:32:08,187
- When you...
- ...fucking say so.

437
00:32:08,271 --> 00:32:10,812
Specifically, whenever I fucking want to.

438
00:32:10,896 --> 00:32:14,687
I don't give a shit about arrest reports
or procedural guarantees.

439
00:32:16,479 --> 00:32:18,312
Do you understand?

440
00:32:19,687 --> 00:32:21,437
Yes, I do.

441
00:32:24,479 --> 00:32:25,937
So until then...

442
00:32:27,812 --> 00:32:32,937
Until then, that bitch will be sat there
with no sleep, peeing in a bucket.

443
00:32:33,687 --> 00:32:35,187
Got a problem with that?

444
00:32:35,396 --> 00:32:37,771
No... no problem.

445
00:32:37,854 --> 00:32:40,146
Good, Antoñanzas. Good.

446
00:32:44,604 --> 00:32:46,187
TRANSPARENCY

447
00:32:51,437 --> 00:32:53,062
GIVE ME A RAISE

448
00:32:56,354 --> 00:32:58,771
LONG LIVE EVIL
LONG LIVE CAPITAL

449
00:32:58,854 --> 00:33:01,937
This system does not represent us!

450
00:33:02,021 --> 00:33:06,854
The Professor would've loved X-ray vision
to see if Lisbon was behind the canvas.

451
00:33:07,021 --> 00:33:08,604
But he wasn't Superman.

452
00:33:08,687 --> 00:33:11,604
So he had to make do
with being Sherlock Holmes.

453
00:33:12,021 --> 00:33:15,396
He arrived at the bank
in search of a thread to pull.

454
00:33:15,479 --> 00:33:16,604
And he found three.

455
00:33:17,729 --> 00:33:19,979
The van. What was it doing there?

456
00:33:21,146 --> 00:33:22,937
And why did it have mud on it?

457
00:33:23,854 --> 00:33:26,187
CNP85600N.

458
00:33:26,271 --> 00:33:28,271
Pakistan found the answer.

459
00:33:28,354 --> 00:33:30,937
The van belonged
to the police in Huelva,

460
00:33:31,021 --> 00:33:33,896
near where Lisbon
had supposedly been killed.

461
00:33:37,312 --> 00:33:38,187
Ángel.

462
00:33:40,021 --> 00:33:44,229
If anyone should have been following
the Hamelin plan trail, it was him.

463
00:33:44,604 --> 00:33:47,187
Unless he had
something more important to do.

464
00:33:47,562 --> 00:33:49,562
Like transferring Lisbon to Madrid.

465
00:33:50,062 --> 00:33:54,146
If anyone should have been mourning
a friend's death, it was also him.

466
00:33:58,354 --> 00:34:01,771
And Alicia Sierra.
The truce had been declared hours ago.

467
00:34:01,854 --> 00:34:03,396
But there she was.

468
00:34:03,479 --> 00:34:05,437
As much of a workaholic as she was,

469
00:34:05,521 --> 00:34:08,854
she should have been home
soaking her ankles.

470
00:34:09,979 --> 00:34:12,062
Unless she got off on interrogating

471
00:34:12,146 --> 00:34:15,062
one of the most-wanted criminals
in the country.

472
00:34:16,729 --> 00:34:18,146
Lisbon might be alive.

473
00:34:18,729 --> 00:34:20,354
But he needed to check

474
00:34:20,437 --> 00:34:23,312
and let her know he wouldn't abandon her.

475
00:34:41,896 --> 00:34:44,896
The ambulance you used
as a communication center arrived.

476
00:34:48,646 --> 00:34:50,396
Know who'll inspect it?

477
00:34:55,771 --> 00:34:57,604
Alberto, your ex-husband.

478
00:34:59,062 --> 00:35:00,812
Besides being the best CSI,

479
00:35:00,896 --> 00:35:04,062
he's very eager
to fuck your life up even more.

480
00:35:05,354 --> 00:35:06,687
There's another option.

481
00:35:14,729 --> 00:35:20,229
I could go in there... before anyone else
and get rid of all the evidence.

482
00:35:28,812 --> 00:35:30,354
You won't find anything.

483
00:35:35,812 --> 00:35:36,979
Shit, Raquel.

484
00:35:38,354 --> 00:35:39,479
You should know.

485
00:35:41,604 --> 00:35:43,146
We always find something.

486
00:35:44,771 --> 00:35:48,229
We'll find a clue that leads us
to your mom and daughter.

487
00:35:48,979 --> 00:35:50,021
You'll see.

488
00:36:44,562 --> 00:36:48,229
Next five, get ready
to go to the bathroom with my colleague.

489
00:36:58,979 --> 00:37:02,771
Hey, Gandía, now we're on the same team,
may I ask a question?

490
00:37:02,854 --> 00:37:06,812
I'm confused.
Are we... the good guys or the bad guys?

491
00:37:09,687 --> 00:37:11,604
I'll cut your nutsack open,

492
00:37:11,687 --> 00:37:15,312
pull out your balls,
and shove them in your mouth.

493
00:37:15,687 --> 00:37:17,021
That'd be interesting.

494
00:37:17,729 --> 00:37:19,937
But your hands are tied up, buddy.

495
00:37:30,146 --> 00:37:35,021
Did you know the reliability of handcuffs
is based on one anatomical feature?

496
00:37:36,354 --> 00:37:38,604
The metacarpal stops them coming off.

497
00:37:39,812 --> 00:37:43,146
But it's very easy to dislocate it.

498
00:37:44,437 --> 00:37:46,479
- Really?
- Well...

499
00:37:47,021 --> 00:37:49,021
they're ideas for freedom.

500
00:37:50,812 --> 00:37:52,354
Free

501
00:37:53,354 --> 00:37:55,812
Like the sun at dawn

502
00:37:55,896 --> 00:37:58,146
I'm free

503
00:37:58,479 --> 00:38:01,437
Like the sea

504
00:38:01,729 --> 00:38:03,687
Free

505
00:38:03,771 --> 00:38:07,562
Like the bird that escaped from its prison

506
00:38:08,021 --> 00:38:11,062
And can finally fly

507
00:38:11,271 --> 00:38:12,896
Free

508
00:38:12,979 --> 00:38:15,354
Like the wind that gathers

509
00:38:15,437 --> 00:38:19,396
My lament and my regret

510
00:38:19,479 --> 00:38:21,479
I walk endlessly

511
00:38:21,937 --> 00:38:25,854
In search of the truth
And I'll finally know

512
00:38:25,937 --> 00:38:29,646
What freedom is

513
00:38:33,604 --> 00:38:34,687
Go to sleep.

514
00:38:37,979 --> 00:38:39,687
Four corners to my bed,

515
00:38:40,896 --> 00:38:42,979
four angels round my head.

516
00:38:43,354 --> 00:38:45,646
Luke, Matthew, and Joseph,

517
00:38:46,146 --> 00:38:48,312
our Lord and the Virgin Mary.

518
00:39:06,021 --> 00:39:07,229
Antoñanzas.

519
00:39:10,062 --> 00:39:11,187
Why are you here?

520
00:39:12,646 --> 00:39:13,646
You're...

521
00:39:15,562 --> 00:39:16,854
You're under arrest!

522
00:39:21,562 --> 00:39:22,729
On your knees.

523
00:39:24,062 --> 00:39:25,854
I was only testing the waters.

524
00:39:27,646 --> 00:39:29,104
On your knees.

525
00:39:36,771 --> 00:39:39,271
Please, my wife and daughters are in bed.

526
00:39:40,354 --> 00:39:41,812
They'll be fine.

527
00:39:43,646 --> 00:39:47,354
You just have to follow instructions
and answer some questions.

528
00:39:48,229 --> 00:39:51,104
I won't speak to someone
who has a gun to my head.

529
00:39:53,146 --> 00:39:54,271
You will speak.

530
00:39:57,437 --> 00:39:59,729
We've got, one:

531
00:40:01,687 --> 00:40:02,687
the ambulance.

532
00:40:07,021 --> 00:40:08,271
Two:

533
00:40:10,229 --> 00:40:11,771
the dotty grandma.

534
00:40:12,479 --> 00:40:15,479
Where am I?

535
00:40:15,562 --> 00:40:16,729
I can't do it.

536
00:40:17,271 --> 00:40:20,687
Three: the motherless child.

537
00:40:21,146 --> 00:40:22,146
Mommy.

538
00:40:22,812 --> 00:40:24,979
Mommy.

539
00:40:26,146 --> 00:40:27,146
Four:

540
00:40:32,646 --> 00:40:34,979
the Professor's love,

541
00:40:36,354 --> 00:40:39,396
which will last two days
once you're in prison.

542
00:40:42,187 --> 00:40:44,854
And now, the final scene.

543
00:40:49,646 --> 00:40:53,937
You're assaulting an officer.
You don't know what you're getting into.

544
00:40:54,021 --> 00:40:55,104
We called a truce.

545
00:40:56,021 --> 00:40:58,854
A truce can be
the most important part of a war.

546
00:41:05,521 --> 00:41:06,521
I can't...

547
00:41:07,437 --> 00:41:08,562
I can't breathe.

548
00:41:12,854 --> 00:41:14,479
Pull yourself together.

549
00:41:15,687 --> 00:41:16,729
Calm down.

550
00:41:19,646 --> 00:41:20,562
I can't breathe.

551
00:41:23,396 --> 00:41:24,396
Marseille.

552
00:41:44,771 --> 00:41:45,646
Better?

553
00:42:05,187 --> 00:42:06,437
If you cooperate,

554
00:42:07,437 --> 00:42:10,646
the prosecution will request 12 years,
you'll get 10,

555
00:42:11,354 --> 00:42:12,896
and you'll be out in five.

556
00:42:13,771 --> 00:42:15,646
That's how your life could be.

557
00:42:16,812 --> 00:42:19,562
If you don't cooperate,
you'll get 30 years.

558
00:42:20,521 --> 00:42:22,271
That's how your life will be.

559
00:42:24,312 --> 00:42:26,604
Your choice, Inspector.

