The good thing
about really fucked-up situations
is that they can only happen once.
You can only get killed once.
You only lose the love of your life once.
You're only robbed of the greatest
treasure anyone has ever stolen once.
But the fact
that all these things only happen once
doesn't make them less painful.
You feel devastated.
You see the faces
of the people you've disappointed.
It's like a cannonball
hurling through your chest.
At that point,
when the anxiety won't let you breathe,
you have two options.
Accept your defeat
or fight.
And the Professor chose to fight.
Although he knew that all was lost,
that he was, most likely,
only prolonging his suffering,
he chose to fight.
Turn on the GPS.
Find the signal for the trucks.
They don't know they're being tracked.
Palermo, Lisbon, private line.
They're 2.5 miles away.
They aren't moving.
At the next crossroads, everyone go west.
Roger that.
Weapons ready, they're 2.5 miles away.
Lisbon, do you copy?
Come on, Lisbon, respond.
This is Lisbon.
I'm with Palermo. What is it?
The gold is gone.
What did you say?
They came in pretending to be police
when we had the gold loaded up.
They tied us up and took everything.
-How many were there?
-Ten.
Wait a minute, Sergio.
Did they arrive
right when the ingots were in the trucks?
-That's when they went in?
-Yes.
You know what that means, right?
We have a mole.
It's an abandoned quarry.
They're not moving.
They're unloading the gold.
They're in the old Santa Bárbara quarry.
For fuck's sake! No!
-God!
-Palermo.
You know this bank better than anyone.
Tell me there's another way out.
Without the gold, we're done for.
Then we're done for.
There they are.
Go easy.
Darko, we're getting out.
Cover the flanks.
We'll check the trucks.
The rest of you, cover us.
They could be anywhere.
Now.
Cover them.
Guy with the beard, here.
Watch the baby.
Fuck!
No!
The trucks are empty.
They unloaded 90 tons of gold
in half an hour. This…
This wasn't improvised.
They knew the plan.
It could only have been one person.
You know exactly who it was.
No. She knew about the target.
She didn't know how we'd get the gold out
or any details of the plan.
You put everything in the safe each night.
Your brother was in love.
Do you really think strategy
was more important to him than love?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
Considering our lives depend on it, yes!
People talk in bed, Sergio.
And you're no exception.
You told me about the Paris Plan in bed,
because you knew no one could hear it.
You knew you were putting a noose
around your associates' necks
to save me.
We both knew
they would come in after that.
And now Tokyo is dead.
That's what people talk about in bed.
About secrets that endanger
other people's lives.
Your brother did it,
you did it,
and I did it.
Sergio.
Let's lighten the mood.
Who were you talking about?
About my brother's ex-wife.
Great, and what does she do?
She's a pianist.
And a thief!
She knew everything!
All this time,
they've been staying here, watching us.
They saw everything.
All they had to do was time us.
They knew that, once the trucks went in,
it would be eight to ten hours
until they left, that's why…
That's why they got there just in time.
We don't have all day, guys!
Let's go, guys!
Come on! Hurry up!
Let's go!
Move!
Let's go! Come on, that's good.
All right, that's good.
-Eight minutes and we're done.
-Let's go!
Come on!
Let's go!
This message is for the whole gang.
Someone stole our gold.
They came into the stormwater tank
pretending to be police.
We're going after them.
We're looking for several dump trucks.
They loaded them with the ingots
and covered them in dirt.
The cargo is uncovered
to avoid arousing suspicion.
It's crucial that no one knows
the gold's been stolen.
Not the hostages, not the police, no one.
Because any setback
would finish us off, got that?
Got it.
Copy.
-Helsinki?
-Got it.
-Manila?
-Copy.
Denver? Stockholm?
Denver, Stockholm, do you copy?
Rio, listen to me.
I need you to hack all the traffic cameras
near the Santa Bárbara quarry, okay?
Go to the stormwater tank.
Take miners, the Captain and those trucks.
Get rid of the police vans
and start the Tom Thumb Plan.
Got it. Captain, the Polish guy and you,
get in the trucks.
And everyone else,
before a crisis unfolds,
think about what you want to study
in a maximum-security prison.
I give you my word…
…we'll get the gold back
and get you out.
That was the first time the Professor
said something nobody believed.
-You can't just remove it.
-Yes, you can.
You'll see.
Who did it?
Who is the funny guy,
or girl, who put this hake in my bed?
Fine.
You know what?
I resign as the brains of the gang.
I'd rather party. Pass the patxarán.
It's more of an amaretto than patxarán--
I don't give a shit what it is.
Drink up. Drink.
-I'll have a smoke too.
-Good for you.
Do you know why you're here?
You're here to let off steam.
Because concentrating all day
is difficult, isn't it?
It's exhausting, isn't it?
This party you've organized is a sign.
A sign of weakness.
It shows you don't have what it takes
to be stressed all day.
Nairobi's the only responsible one.
You have to be on guard all day.
You have to be on guard all day,
clenching your fists, Bogotá.
Tokyo. Helsinki.
Your ass has to be as tight as a drum.
That's the way to be.
On the lookout, like an owl.
Stiff, vigilant.
Because as soon as you lower your guard,
they'll get you.
Some son of a bitch, some bastard,
will be on guard all day long,
and he'll get you.
-We'll clean up.
-No!
You need to let off steam?
Hey, then let's let off steam.
Let's relax then.
Everybody relax. Let's see.
No class tomorrow.
You can share notes.
Come on, let's all dance!
-Come on.
-Let's do it.
The day the gang fell,
we all thought about
that night with the hake.
But we didn't lower our guard
because we needed to let off steam.
We did it out of despair
from having lost the gold,
and with it, something even worse,
the trust we had in our leader.
So it was hard to stay on guard
and realize that the real danger…
had lurked around us
from the exact moment
we thought we had broken Sagasta.
We came in here with the mission
to end this heist,
and that's what we're going to do.
There's two of you and one psycho.
Right now, you don't stand a chance.
More than ever,
because this time
they really won't see it coming.
We need someone to put an end to all this.
Pay attention.
You're going to go inside
the ventilation ducts,
but don't do anything.
Even if you find three of them sleeping
in front of you and you could kill them,
restrain yourself.
I'm at the main entrance.
-Status?
-There are four charges.
You have to move like a ghost.
We'll buy you time.
I'll negotiate for surgeons
to be allowed in to operate on Ramiro.
You'll radio the command post.
The doctors they send in
should be soldiers.
They're going to take part
in a covert operation.
What is the mission?
To open this fucking building.
They feel strong locked up in here.
But there's less than 10 of them
and the army's outside.
You're going to open up three gaps.
The loading docks,
large windows on the first floor,
and, most importantly, the main entrance.
Once you've done that,
we will have won this war.
They'll take the bank
in under ten minutes.
And you?
Together with you, and the surgeons,
we're the Trojan horse.
Main access cleared.
Good job. We'll wait for your signal.
Hey, so…
Considering how confused you were about…
your past, you, Manila, I don't know,
you seemed really into it.
How was I "into it"?
Your eagerness, your thrust…
I overdid it, right?
I overdid it. I should've been gentler,
but with the striptease you did for me,
you didn't make it easy for me.
Did you like it? Was it okay?
But seriously,
how do you feel now?
Everything is clearer now.
-Really?
-Yes.
Yes,
because before you have an orgasm,
your head is full of noise.
When you ejaculate,
only one of two things can happen,
you want to get the hell out
or stay with that person forever.
And what do you want to do?
I want to stay here,
with you,
holding you, forever.
If you want to, of course.
But with one condition.
What?
That the next time you want to go out,
don't lie to me.
Take me with you.
Party with me until the sun rises.
-Or until it sets again.
-Exactly.
Fuck, can't you knock?
What's wrong with you?
Someone stole the gold.
What?
Not a word about this.
If anyone finds out,
it's over, we're dead.
Fucking hell.
Come on, hurry up!
Let's go.
I have access to the server.
I'm in. We have the traffic cameras.
Check the ones on the M60.
They must have exited at kilometer 26.
Got it. Exit 26, Madrid-Barcelona.
We're looking for three dump trucks,
maybe four, between 10:55 and 11:10.
I don't see any trucks there.
Look for heavy goods vehicles.
Nothing.
Nothing in those 15
or the next 15 minutes.
They took a country road with no cameras.
Any idiot knows that.
-No one will be able to find them.
-We still have time.
We still have time
to protect our people outside.
Cincinnati, my daughter and my mom.
I'm not going to give up now.
You already did.
When you put your hands up.
You had weapons, men,
a secure position, and you surrendered.
It was a lost war.
They came in with patrol cars,
special operations vans.
It looked serious. Killing 20 policemen
wouldn't have saved us.
They weren't police!
It was a fucking magic trick!
You fell for your own tricks,
your own disguises.
-You fell for it!
-Shut up!
Wait a second.
Palermo already said it.
It's Berlin's son.
They're playing the same cards as us.
Lisbon was right.
Of course it's a magic trick.
It was a trick when they stole our gold.
It's still a trick now.
They knew we would check
the security cameras.
That's all we could do.
And that we would believe what we saw.
But maybe what we're seeing isn't real.
Rio, check the images again.
Look for something, a loop,
anything, a sign that the images are fake.
The asphalt. It's wet.
It rained yesterday, not today.
They altered the images instead
of taking a side road with no cameras.
-Why go to all that trouble?
-Because they need to.
Exactly.
They're going somewhere
they can only get to on this road.
The M60 is a beltway.
They'd never use it to flee Madrid.
Because they're not fleeing.
They're hiding.
No one flees
with 90 tons of a country's gold.
What do you do
when you have so much money and gold
you can't take it with you?
What did Pablo Escobar do?
-What do pirates do?
-Bury the loot!
That's why they're using dump trucks.
-That's right.
-The gold is underground.
-Correct!
-Where do you bury that kind of loot?
Wherever it is,
the hole you need to dig
to bury 90 tons of gold
requires moving so much dirt
and machinery…
that we still have a chance to find it.
Higher.
Attention!
I want everyone dressed
as anything other than a soldier.
Doctor, civil protection,
ambulance driver…
We'll intervene when they least expect it.
We'll approach the bank in camouflage,
gather troops in blind spots
and wait for Sergeant Arteche's signal.
-Got that?
-Yes, sir!
Go get them!
Let's go!
I'm entering the library.
I'm about to make contact
with Major Sagasta.
Copy, Sergeant.
All units in position.
Suárez, keep your men in a blind spot.
Copy, Colonel.
Wait for my command.
Established visual contact with the major.
Mendizábal, status?
-We're in position, Colonel.
-Copy.
Let's go!
Get ready!
We're still in a blind spot.
-Cañizo?
-Colonel, the charge is ready.
Sargent, all units are ready
and awaiting your signal.
Keep your head down.
There's nothing to see here.
Arteche.
Arteche, what's going on?
-Another heist man has come back in.
-Head down.
I'm going to wait.
How's that leg doing, Fatty?
Good. I can't feel anything yet.
-Are the hostages giving you trouble?
-No.
They're quiet.
I have to tell you something.
This sounds like a goodbye.
The Professor lost the gold.
I doubt we'll get out of here.
Palermo, you'll get me out of here.
You promised,
and you'll do it.
You may have your doubts,
but I don't.
-Someone do something.
-What's going on?
Initiating phase two.
Let us go. He needs
immediate medical attention, please.
Okay, don't move.
Hostages, get down!
Get down or I'll kill you!
Open your mouth.
Stick your tongue out!
I'm inside.
Units on alert, Arteche is going in.
It's not epilepsy.
He probably has brain damage.
-Subdural hematoma.
-We need to trepan it now.
Release us, please.
-Release the doctors, fuck!
-Major, shut up!
Come here. Slowly.
You too.
Move and I'll blow your head off, bastard!
Shoot, Fatty!
Shoot and I'll blow his head off.
You have a machine gun, kill them!
-Drop the weapon.
-I'm dying to kill him.
Give me an excuse.
Five.
Four.
-Three. Two.
-Fucking do it!
-Don't do it.
-One.
Drop it, damn.
Major, do you copy?
Library cleared.
Major Sagasta is operational
and in charge of the Trojan horse.
Colonel.
You have the green light to proceed.
Calling all units. We're going in now!
Come on! Get down!
Charge!
Don't move!
Get down on the ground!
-Get down!
-Stop!
Don't move!
Charge!
Let's go!
Hands on your head!
Get down!
Major Sagasta here,
informing you that the gang has fallen.
There are no casualties
on our side or theirs.
The hostages are safe.
Over and out.
Professor, this is Tamayo.
You'll be surprised to hear me
on your gang's radio.
I regret to inform you that
this is not a trick like one of yours.
If you want proof, hold on.
Don't worry.
We're all alive, but on our knees.
They deactivated the charges
and entered in a coordinated manner.
And if you need visual confirmation,
just turn on the TV,
because they're going
to appear live before a judge,
one at a time, the whole band.
Like the Rolling Stones.
So I recommend you find
the deepest, darkest hole you can.
We're coming for you.
That won't be necessary.
I'm turning myself in.
Even my own gang never fully understood
why I stayed outside the bank.
Some thought I did it out of cowardice.
If something went wrong…
I'd be outside and they wouldn't.
I promised myself
that if the gang went down,
I'd go down with them.
You've already won, Tamayo.
So it makes no sense for us
to keep dragging this out with a chase
while we endanger more lives.
I'm asking…
man to man,
that you accept my surrender and…
And allow me to go into the bank
and come out in handcuffs
with my associates.
I'll be there in 20 minutes,
just in time for the photo op.
Try to make that 15 minutes instead of 20.
You're surrendering?
This is Colonel Tamayo.
Keep the hostages in the library.
Don't let anyone out of there.
Nobody gets to leave! Understood?
What are you trying to do?
Be a hero? Or a martyr?
Listen to me.
If the gang leaves the bank, it's over.
All will be lost.
There will be no turning back, but now…
We still have a chance.
It's one in a million, but it's there.
A chance to do what?
I need you to find the gold.
-What?
-With Benjamín.
-I need you to find the gold.
Now. Right now.
I need you to find the gold.
My God.
-Listen.
-Did you hear that, Logroño?
It turns out that we,
the new mom and the ex-convict,
are in charge of delivering
the final blow, the checkmate,
the masterstroke.
Don't fuck with me.
If anyone can do it, it's you.
I am a woman who just had a baby
and I'm breastfeeding.
I can't think straight
and I'm tired, very tired.
I don't know if I can deal with a war
between organized crime families.
-I don't know.
-All you have to do is find some robbers.
You've been doing it your whole life.
You're the best.
-Don't suck up to me, Sergio.
-You found me.
I'm the most wanted man in all of Spain.
Alicia, Interpol spent month after month
looking for me all over the planet.
They never found me. You did.
In a few hours.
You snuck out of a press conference
full of journalists.
You ran away from Tamayo,
from the entire police force,
while you were 9 months pregnant
and you found me!
You're going to find that gold!
So take those cars and this gang…
and go find the biggest loot in history.
Alicia. Yes.
Consider yourself lucky.
This is the first time
I've given a real hug
since Germán died.
And most importantly,
it's the first time I've smiled for real.
What made you smile?
Well, you're leaving me with Columbo…
and Starsky and Hutch and friends.
They're the best.
Sure.
I need you to do me one last favor.
I can't go in our cars,
they can be traced, but that one…
Go now.
Gentlemen, let's go!
When you see my daughter, tell her…
Tell her that I love her lots.
-Good afternoon.
-Are you the Professor?
That's right.
You have a lovely car.
Come on, push.
Jesus Christ.
They've cleaned us out, Colonel.
They took the entire national reserve.
Do you know what that means?
It's a country's credit guarantee.
Its solvency! Its collateral!
-Do you understand?
-I understand, Mr. Mario.
-Cañizo.
-Colonel.
I want your men to fire
intermittent bursts every other minute,
as if they're holding the fort down here.
At your command.
Until we know what the fuck to say,
the operation continues.
Cincinnati.
Fuck, Cincinnati. I have to go, Professor.
-I have to go.
-Okay.
-It's my turn.
Look at that. Only the party professionals
are left standing.
That's you and me.
Now this is the resistance.
-Exactly.
-No.
-That?
No, this is.
I love you a lot, Tokyo.
A lot.
Me too.
You know why?
Because of my dance moves?
What?
Because you always make it to the end.
That's why you're still here
with me at 8:00 a.m.
Am I wrong? Am I?
No, it's true.
I realized that you're a hero.
The rest of us can drink and horse around
because you're on the other side,
holding the fort down.
Yes.
With you, we know nothing can go wrong.
You'll have an ace up your sleeve.
You'll do a magic trick.
That's why we go back in the lion's den.
Even if they point tons of guns at us.
Because we believe in you.
Like a mantra.
Professor!
You're our faith.
We have faith that,
even if all else fails,
we'll still have you.
No matter how bad things get…
even if they've beaten us,
even if it looks like there's no hope,
like we're almost dead…
we'll still believe.
We know we'll always have the Professor.
Professor!
Subtitle translation by: Molly Yurick