("FEELING GOOD"
BY ALEX OLMEDO PLAYS)
CRISIS!
(CROWD CLAMORS)
♪ Birds in the sky ♪
♪ You know how I feel ♪
♪ Sun in the sky ♪
♪ You know how I feel ♪
♪ Breeze driftin' on by ♪
♪ It's a new dawn ♪
♪ It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Fish in the sea ♪
♪ You know how I feel ♪
♪ River running free ♪
♪ Blossom on a tree ♪
♪ You know how I feel ♪
♪ It's a new dawn ♪
♪ It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
(SCREAMING)
♪ Dragonfly out in the sun ♪
♪ You know what I mean, oh ♪
They're attacking the bank.
The bank is under attack!
(CROWD SCREAMING)
Seal off the building!
I repeat, seal off the building!
Code red. Seal the doors of the bank.
I repeat, seal the doors of the bank.
Everyone, get your vests on now!
♪ And the old world ♪
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
And then the Bank of Spain will be sealed.
("MY LIFE IS GOING ON"
BY CECILIA KRULL PLAYS)
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
HELSINKI: Even if sealed,
it's a huge building, Professor.
Many windows, few men.
(CHUCKLES) We can't defend it all.
Good point, Helsinki.
Very good point, but you see,
this building
has tricks.
This is the part of the Bank of Spain
we're focused on.
Its entire structure
is reinforced with concrete walls
and steel sheets
that measure 180 centimeters thick.
From the outside,
it's basically a giant safe.
And from the inside, it's impenetrable.
Once code red has been activated, no one…
no one will be allowed in
or out for one hour.
That's the time we have to get our hands
on a piece that's absolutely crucial
for stage two of the plan.
What piece?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
The governor of the Bank of Spain
will be in his office
surrounded by his five personal bodyguards
who won't exactly have a sense of humor.
BERLIN: It's much like
a spooky Carnival ride.
Everyone can sense something is
gonna jump out at them but
nobody knows when and where
it's gonna happen.
Excuse me, Governor,
my name is Lieutenant Lorenzo.
You need to come with us.
We have an armored car
ready to evacuate you.
Thank you.
At this moment, I'm not leaving my office.
Sir.
It's an order from General Salas Núñez.
It's from the JEMAD.
No, I received the order,
but I'm not following it.
I'll not leave the Bank until
the last of the employees have left.
So, if you want is to escort me,
you'll just have to sit back and wait.
Want some coffee?
Amanda, if you would.
Come in, come in.
TOKYO: In that moment,
I wondered what Nairobi was thinking.
I only had one thought in my mind,
draw my gun and start shooting.
GOVERNOR: Relax.
Take a seat.
May I ask which regiment you belong to?
We belong to the paratroopers.
The BRIPAC.
Brigade six.
Mm.
We've cleared mines in Mali, Lebanon,
Afghanistan.
TOKYO: There were five bodyguards.
Nairobi and I had two guns.
So, we could incapacitate two men each.
But one would be left standing.
That's a dangerous job.
- Mm-hmm.
- GOVERNOR: By the way…
How do you deactivate a live mine?
It depends.
With mines, there are several
different types and they…
they each have different mechanisms.
There's the Green Parrots,
the Butterflies, the PMF1…
Some are set off using methods
that would defuse others.
Some explode when detecting movement.
Others explode when…
when you open them.
There are some that explode even when
you get a little too close to them.
May I use the bathroom?
Of course. You can use mine.
Excuse me.
GOVERNOR: Amanda, please.
Over there.
But the worst are the Russian ones.
TOKYO: The Professor had prepared us
for every eventuality.
But let's be honest.
It was one thing in theory
and another in practice.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
You're safe in here.
There's nothing to worry about
among writers and poets, right?
Stay calm.
Rise your hands.
Like you're in a robbery.
Come on.
Good.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Palermo.
And I have two pieces of news for you.
One good, one bad.
The bad news is that the Bank of Spain
is under attack.
And the good news…
(LAUGHS)
…is that we're the ones
attacking you, muchachos. (LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING)
DENVER: Get back, back!
Everyone, calm down!
Stay calm!
VP13.
VP13?
There's an electronic deployment system
which works via seismic sensor control.
Touch one
and you take it up your ass.
(LAUGHS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Afghanistan was full of them.
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
GOVERNOR: I see they trained you well.
Wait, don't move, sir.
Are you all right, Lieutenant?
Lieutenant!
Boo!
Mr. Governor,
now you have to come with us.
Get up.
With me.
(GUNS COCK
(WHISPERS) What are you doing?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Don't move.
- (SHOUTS)
- Drop your weapon.
Put the guns down.
Drop your weapon. Now!
Well…
It seems like the two of us
have reached a stalemate.
(CRIES)
Why don't you put your gun down?
What the fuck makes you think
this is a stalemate?
You won't shoot the governor,
but I'll put a bullet
in this bitch's head.
That's right.
(GUNSHOT)
GOVERNOR: Gandía!
Let go of the girl.
(CRIES)
Calm down, Amanda. It's all right. Okay?
Everything's fine.
- Gandía, let go of the girl.
- GANDÍA: No.
GOVERNOR: I don't want anyone harmed.
That's an order.
Let go the girl, Gandía!
(GRUNTS)
I'm going with them.
I don't want you to do anything.
That's it.
I don't know what's your plan is.
There's no way you're getting out.
Then I guess we're not leaving.
(TENSE MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC ENDS)
- (TOKYO GRUNTS)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- NAIROBI: Shit!
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Shit!
But what the fuck just happened?
What the fuck just happened? Shit!
- What are you doing?
- They're going down. We have to go up.
(ELEVATOR ROARS)
- We need to go down.
- What do you mean?
If we stay here, we're dead.
We need to go down.
We're all in, Tokyo style.
It's party time.
From now on, you're all part
of our wonderful family of hostages.
You'll enjoy some days
of total disconnection, hmm?
So take your masks
and put them on, please.
Put on your masks on, goddamn it! Move!
And so that nobody feels tempted
to play the hero,
you'll hand your cell phones
to my colleague, Denver.
(HOSTAGES CRYING)
Here's what we're gonna do.
Anyone here who has kids,
put up your hand.
All right.
We'll place a red tag on your phones
so you'll be able to call them once a day.
Why are you doing this, you moron?
Because I want to.
I'm the hostage coordinator.
Did you take a little course or something?
Are you papa of the year?
Everyone hand over your phones, now!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DENVER: Oh, my God!
Grow a pair, Helsinki.
He's such a cutie. What's his real name?
You should ask his father.
Cincinnati.
NAIROBI: No way!
It's the truth.
The love of my life
liked the name Cynthia
when she thought was a girl,
but…
- (LAUGHS)
- We couldn't really tell from the scan.
- How come?
- I could only get the first one done.
Yeah, where was that? Do you remember?
- Yeah.
- In a clinic in Sulawao.
- It was Sulawesi.
- Sulawesi.
- DENVER: Sulawao, Sulawesi…
It was like a grimy mechanic shop.
Oh my God!
We didn't return.
I had a bullet removed
in a tractor garage during the war.
- You never told me that, my love.
- I did.
- Where?
- In my ass. Wanna see?
- No…
- No!
No, show them your pet, Helsi.
- No.
- Your little pet.
Come on. Show them. Introduce them.
- Come on. Show us.
- We're family here.
- All right. Ready?
- (LAUGHS)
- Hey, no, no, no.
- No!
No…
(LAUGHS)
(ALL GASP)
- (IMITATES BEAR)
- Fatty, want me to train your teddy bear?
I'm good at training animals. Understand?
- Did you want a girl or a boy, Mónica?
- Didn't really matter what we got.
You know, it didn't make a difference.
As parents you love it.
No matter what it is, am I right or no?
(ASIAN MUSIC PLAYS)
(BABY CRYING)
(IN THAI) It's a boy.
(IN THAI) A boy?
A boy?
It's a boy.
It's a boy!
A boy! A boy! It's a boy!
It's a boy! It's a boy!
It's a boy!
(CHANTING) A boy! A boy!
- (ALL LAUGH)
- It's a boy.
I thought something happened
to the kid. Damn.
It's a boy!
The whole town hear him yelling
"It's a boy! It's a boy!"
That's right! So, it went from Cynthia…
Cinthy…
Cincy-nati. Cincinnati.
Sure, that's logical.
It was logical. It makes sense
because he's named after a city.
Just like the family.
This family.
Cincinnati.
You know?
A boy.
It's a boy. A boy.
A beautiful boy.
ALL: To Cincinnati.
ALL: Cheers.
Look, friends.
I wanna thank you
for everything you guys are doing.
On behalf of Rio and me.
- Thank you.
- To Rio.
ALL: To Rio.
- ALL: Cheers.
- ALL: Salud.
Tokyo, we're doing all this for you but…
for all of us as well.
Right now, they're convinced
they can't lose.
Chasing us like dogs,
forcing us out of our holes…
Torturing us and violating
our human rights. They don't care.
Doesn't matter if we hide like rats,
they'll come after us again.
One by one.
There's only one way out.
We have to face them.
Listen.
In this world…
everything is governed by balance.
There's…
what you stand to gain
and what you stand to lose.
At this moment…
they think they have nothing to lose.
And when you believe
you've got nothing to lose,
you're overconfident.
Good.
We'll be the ones
that are going to show them…
just how much
they have to lose.
(ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
Where's the governor?
Where is he?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
STOCKHOLM: Palermo!
We have a big problem.
Tokyo.
Easy, easy.
- NAIROBI: Tokyo.
- TOKYO: Calm down, calm down. Calm down.
(MUSIC BUILDS)
On three, shoot and drop to the ground.
One…
Two…
Drop your weapons, you rats!
Gentlemen, let me introduce myself.
My name's Palermo
and I'm in charge of this heist.
So, please, turn your guns on me.
I'm your most prized target.
On her!
Stay on her.
Good.
It seems we've got a few seconds left
before it starts,
so let's have a chat about anatomy,
what do you think?
A human being has two eyes.
Which, unlike a chameleon's,
are fixed and found
at the front of the face.
That leaves you with quite some handicap
in the event of a shoot-out.
Don't you think?
Shoot and your girls will be dead.
I'm talking to you, Gandía.
I know you spend
every Sunday at the shooting range,
that you buy gun magazines.
Your whole fucking life
you've been waiting for this moment
to become a hero.
Let me recommend something.
Think carefully about Marisa,
picture your son Juanito's angelic face
and put down the gun, you son of a bitch.
Fine.
Okay.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GRUNTS)
(PROFESSOR BREATHES HEAVILY)
TOKYO: At that moment,
the Professor realized
that this heist was very different
from the one at the Royal Mint.
This one didn't come from his head
and he didn't have enough time
to make it his own.
If he'd had a rewind button,
he would have pressed it in an instant.
But he didn't have one.
NAIROBI: Tokyo, are you okay?
Say something! Are you okay?
Go help Palermo!
TOKYO: We unloaded ammo on their vests,
like the Professor told us.
But we were too late.
("ANOTHER SUNNY DAY"
BY BELLE AND SEBASTIAN PLAYS)
♪ Another sunny day
I met you up in the garden ♪
♪ You were digging plants
I dug you, beg your pardon ♪
(SIRENS WAIL)
♪ I took a photograph of you
In the herbaceous border ♪
Hey, wake up. Hey, wake up!
Where's the governor?
♪ …Flowers and girls and trees ♪
♪ Another rainy day… ♪
Tokyo, we need to get him out of here.
Get a stretcher!
♪ Chocolate on the boil
Steamy windows when we met ♪
♪ You've got the attic window
Looking out on the cathedral ♪
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Everything has gone to shit.
Look at his eyes! Shit! Shit! Shit!
♪ Ghost figures of past, present
Future haunting the… ♪
Help me!
- He'll be okay.
- Out of my way!
Everyone up against the wall!
Move it! Move it!
Come on! Hurry!
Move it. Move!
Move!
- TOKYO: Almost.
- We're almost there.
All right, stay calm. Calm down.
- Painkillers!
(GRUNTS)
Calm down, Palermo.
I'm gonna take this off. Nice and slow.
Nice and slow.
Carefully. Very good.
(GRUNTS)
Great, that's good.
Now open your eyes real slow.
There we go.
Come on.
Very good.
I can't keep my eyes open for long.
I can't.
Can you see?
I can't fucking see shit.
What's happening?
Oh, fuck.
Okay. Okay.
Do you see the light?
Like the floodlights at Maracanã Stadium.
Does it make a difference?
You an eye specialist now, Tokyo?
Tokyo, he needs an eye doctor.
- Let's call the Professor.
- Yeah.
I can see the glass.
Stockholm, first aid kit number four.
The surgical one.
- Right now!
- DENVER: Go, go, go.
(INHALES)
What's on your mind, Tokyo?
I'm gonna get it out.
- How do you plan to do that?
- With tweezers.
I wouldn't mess with that, Tokyo.
Let's call the Professor,
release three hostages
and get him a specialist.
- Denver. Shut the fuck up and leave!
- Okay.
Listen to me, Palermo.
My hand's steadier
than a fucking Swiss' watch, okay?
Now, I'm gonna get that glass out.
Do you know why
a laser is used for eye surgery?
- Yes.
- Just a tiny detail.
The precision. It requires extreme
precision to perform surgery on the eye.
Come look at this, Denver.
Ms. Tokyo here wants to use
the very same tweezers
she uses to trim her think bush.
Jesus Christ!
This is ridiculous!
I dare you to say that again.
Say it again.
(MUMBLES)
What was that?
I'm sure you're right, the hair
in your bush is very silky and smooth.
Say, "I'll never mention
my colleagues' fucking pussies again."
I will never mention
my colleagues' pussies again.
I don't hear you.
I said I'll never mention
your pussy again, bitch.
That's fucking great, Palermo.
We're at your service.
Good. We'll deal with my eyes later.
- Denver, on my right.
- Yeah, what's up?
Give me your arm.
You're going to be my lieutenant, okay?
- I'm gonna be your guide dog now?
- Be quiet!
- Tokyo!
- Yes.
We're sitting on 14 tons of steel below.
Tell me Nairobi is with Bogotá.
She is.
Come on!
Listen to me. Is this your big plan?
You going to tie us up
and treat us like dogs?
No, my dear.
We're all family in here. If you need help
taking a piss, let me know.
I'm gonna kill you.
(LAUGHS)
Governor, if I may.
HELSINKI: Get out of here. Move!
See this? I'm gonna hold onto it for you.
May I have your attention, please?
We've placed 460 kilograms of explosives
in the windows and in all the doors,
at every entrance and in all of the exits.
So, if anyone tries to escape…
- Boom!
- (HOSTAGES GASP)
They'll escape, but in pieces.
It's not worth the trouble.
Unfortunately, we're all shacked up in
here together for a few days, all right?
But during this time
all of you
will have our protection.
And in return,
you are going to protect all of us.
Marvelous.
And now, whenever you like,
you may all take off your masks.
Now!
(HOSTAGES CRY)
NAIROBI: Hey there!
How is it going?
Now that we can all see
each other's beautiful faces,
let me introduce Mr. Bogotá.
He'll be picking four volunteers.
My name is Bogotá.
I came to do the hard part of the job.
We'll be working at 65 degrees Celsius.
That's essentially a fucking crematorium.
We're doing shifts
of 12, 14, 16 or 24 hours.
Whatever you can handle.
So, who's in?
Name!
Agustín.
- Agustín Montero.
- Why are you here?
I came
to exchange money.
Congratulations. Step forward, sir.
Our first volunteer.
Next up.
Miguel Fernández Talanilla
from Totana, Murcia.
NAIROBI: Very good.
- What do you do, Miguel?
- I work here in system operations.
I mean, IT.
- Unqualified.
- Unqualified. Okay, next!
Name and why are you here?
Alfonso.
I have… I had an appointment
with the debt department.
Step forward. Congratulations,
you are our second volunteer. And next!
BOGOTÁ: Name. Why are you here?
Amanda. I'm the governor's secretary.
Unqualified. Next up, come on!
Name!
Matías Caño.
Qualified! Come on, step forward.
No, ma'am.
Don't call me "ma'am." I'm not a ma'am.
Step forward. You're volunteering.
I'm no volunteer.
Look at me. Do you see this finger?
This is the finger
that points out the volunteers
and it keeps pointing at you
over and over and over again.
So do me a favor, step forward
because you're a volunteer.
Listen, woman, I'm no volunteer.
- What did you say your name was?
- Matías Caño.
What?
Matías Caño.
Very well, Matías Caño.
You're coming with me right fucking now.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
BOGOTÁ: Let's go.
NAIROBI: Let's go!
To the elevator.
Stay there!
(CARD READER BEEPS)
Get in!
What was that?
Are you an idiot?
What was shit about not being a volunteer?
I thought I'd make it believable.
"Believable"? You think
you're fucking Anthony Hopkins?
(CHUCKLES)
I had to act like a hostage.
Are you fucking kidding?
From the producers of "My balls," coming
to a theater near you, "Blacksmith Actor"?
I thought I did a good job.
It was really fluid.
I'll make fluid come out of you…
Six years!
Six years working with this guy
and I always have this urge
to slam his head into a goddamn wall.
(SUSHES)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC ENDS)
Listen up, guys.
We're playing hardball now.
And your balls are on the line.
Sergio!
The CNI has arrived.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Tap them.
Colonel Tamayo.
Inspector.
- When was the explosion?
- 12:04.
Then we heard a shootout.
They've placed explosives everywhere.
- How were the charges detonated?
- We're still not sure.
Plastic explosive. RDX. Expertly made.
- It's a decoy.
- No, it doesn't look like it, Colonel.
There's explosives at the front,
the roof, inside, on the windows…
I've studied them.
They won't blow up the Bank of Spain.
With all due respect,
these people are capable of anything.
I could go out there and take a piss
and nothing would happen.
- Listen to me, Colonel.
- Please!
Alfonso.
How are you feeling?
PRIETO: I'm absolutely fucked, Luis.
Can't do it.
I'm sorry. You take over.
Don't worry about it.
Go and rest.
Luis.
Call her.
I sent her to interrogate Aníbal Cortés.
Everyone,
we know each other already.
I'm Colonel Tamayo from Intelligence.
I'm taking over this operation.
First of all,
I want the queen of all bitches here now.
Call Alicia Sierra.
Get her on the phone now.
Come on, back to work.
Get me Inspector Sierra right now.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
It's her.
(COUGHS)
Inspector Sierra, there's a call for you
from Colonel Tamayo.
- Talk to me.
- Alicia, it's Tamayo.
Did you get anything out of him?
Nothing that can help us, Luis.
Send him back to his mommy,
she'll make him some soup.
He's worn out
from all the chitchat and all the drugs.
Put him on a plane
and bring him to Madrid.
You've got work to do here.
(EXHALES) Bring me on board, Luis.
Tell me you want me
to force that fucking shepherd
and his flock out of the bank.
Exactly.
Fuck me.
I'm so happy my water's gonna break.
(NAIL BREAKS)
(CHURCH BELLS RING)
BERLIN: I hate I have to tell you this
in front of all this beauty.
I have to confess
something a bit unpleasant.
I have the same illness as mother.
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
How long?
Three years.
At least that.
You know how pessimistic doctors are.
It'll end up being six
or nine.
Like the lives of a stray cat.
Andrés. Andrés.
We'll call the whole thing off
and go abroad to find treatment.
First of all, there's no cure.
Second of all,
I'll have a much better time stealing.
Do you really want to spend your
little time you have left in jail?
If a painter told you
he had three years left to live,
would you tell him to stop painting?
- Andrés, please…
- (SUSHES)
Look.
Would you have told Michelangelo
to stop sculpting David?
No. No, of course not.
You would have said,
"Forza, Michelangelo!"
(IN ITALIAN)
"Continue doing your passion."
Painter? Poet? Same thing.
"Gentlemen…
continue your quest for beauty."
This heist, Sergio…
is a tribute to beauty.
It'll be our masterpiece.
NAIROBI: Sixteen minutes
and 15 seconds.
Sixteen minutes
That's all we got.
From the moment you touch this door,
this vault will begin to flood with water.
Sixteen minutes and 15 seconds.
Until all that water reaches here.
Either we make a hole
and weld the interconnecting tube
in that time,
or else
we all end up in prison
for nothing.
(LAUGHS) For breaking a door.
But that…
That's not gonna happen.
No, no, no. Not to us.
Why is that not going to happen to us?
Because… Bogotá.
What are we?
The fucking bosses.
(LAUGH) No, no, no… That's no good.
That's not gonna melt
through a 14-ton door.
So, again. What are we?
The fucking bosses!
What are we?
What are we?!
ALL: The fucking bosses!
Now we're talking! Raise your lances!
What you see before you is not a door.
It's just fucking butter.
And all of you… (LAUGHS)
…you're gonna melt right through it.
Burnt butter! Positions!
(ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
BERLIN: Come on, Sergio.
It's not so bad. Imagine it.
Imagine it. You're good at that.
Set out on a journey with me, hmm?
It's a 14-ton steel door.
And in front of it,
the best blacksmiths in the world.
NAIROBI: Ready?
(IMITATES TICKING BOMB)
And now!
(ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
When we touch that door,
the vault will flood with water.
7,500 liters per minute.
(ALARM BLARES)
- NAIROBI: Ticktock, ticktock!
- BOGOTÁ: Come on! Let's go, let's go!
NAIROBI: Don't stop!
BERLIN: Once it's full,
you'd be crushed
if you opened the door.
But we're not going to open that door.
Exactly.
We're just going to penetrate it.
NAIROBI: Bring the ram! Move, move, move!
- (ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
- (ALARM BLARING)
NAIROBI: Now!
The tube!
BOGOTÁ: Come on! Go forward, go forward.
In the 16 minutes
that it'll take for the vault to fill up,
we'll play…
(LAUGHS) …Jacques-Yves
Cousteau.
ALL: One, two, three.
NAIROBI: Push! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Go!
The door stays closed
and the welder enters.
NAIROBI: Here.
Okay, okay. We're ready.
It's all up to you.
NAIROBI: The oxygen first.
Put on the oxygen first.
- BOGOTÁ: I've got time.
- NAIROBI: What?
- BOGOTÁ: I've got time!
- Are you kidding? The oxygen! Bogotá!
Why, God damn it, why?
There always has to be a fucking hero.
The fucking hero
showing off his big fucking balls.
And in there, the water's rising
and rising and rising by the minute,
so begins the real fantasy
of the new millennium,
to weld from both sides
a small antechamber, fully interconnected.
With the water rising every minute,
don't you think this is better
than a James Bond movie?
Not even James Bond could weld that
chamber in such a short amount of time.
Exactly!
That's why we'll hire
the best welder in the entire world.
If the water reaches the welded joint
and it's not perfectly sealed…
the water will push through the cracks
with such forces
we'd need several days
to get that man out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he'd be dead!
He'd be dead!
But what job comes without risks, huh?
Go, go, go!
No time to waste!
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Look, little brother, hey,
let's not think about that right now.
NAIROBI: Come on! One more minute!
Just give me one more minute!
One more damn minute.
Tell me.
Who could ever conceive such a plan?
Who?
(NAIROBI EXHALES)
(ALARM BLARES)
I'm going in!
An antechamber fully interconnected…
like a bathyscaphe.
And then,
sweet brother of my den, come the bubbles.
You used to love
documentaries about the ocean.
Now, here's your childhood dream
come true.
Watching the flotation level out.
NAIROBI: You're alive!
You turn around…
and see how the bubbles are rising…
they are splendid.
Perfection sliding through
the golden bricks,
until they crash against the roof.
You feel like you're in a space station.
But no.
You're in the vault of the Bank of Spain.
(LAUGHS) There… floating…
(LAUGHS)
It'll be like swimming
through a sunken galleon
with 90 tons of 24-karat gold.
What do you think?
It's the most beautiful thing
I've heard in my life.
(BERLIN LAUGHS)
I knew it.
("GUAJIRA GUANTANAMERA"
BY COMPANY SEGUNDO PLAYS)
(MOANS)
Compay! (LAUGHS)
(BERLIN SINGS ALONG WITH MUSIC)
♪ Guajira guantanamera ♪
♪ Guantanamera ♪
♪ Do not leave me in the dark ♪
♪ To die like a traitor ♪
♪ I am good and good as I am ♪
♪ I will die facing the sun ♪
Looking at the sun, little brother.
I want to die on a beach.
I want the judge to say,
when lifting my corpse, "That bastard."
(LAUGHS)
♪ Guajira guantanamera ♪
Come on! Hey.
♪Guantanamera ♪
♪ Guajira guantanamera ♪
Darling, darling, darling…
I'm back and I brought a present.
(ALL LAUGH)
I found these cute little earrings.
What do you think?
Think I can pull them off?
Look at this bling!
("GUAJIRA GUANTANAMERA" CONTINUES)
That's right! Dance!