But be very careful, because
the second any blood is shed,
we'll no longer be Robin Hoods but
just a bunch of plain motherfucking punks
Rio, Rio!
Damn it to Hell!
The fucking first rule!
You know it! It was
the first fucking rule!
Fuck!
Fuckers!
Paula, you're missing the purple.
Paula.
I don't understand why papa can't
come to my birthday party tomorrow.
I already told you, Paula.
A judge has denied him custody
and now I'll take care of you.
It wasn't a judge.
- Oh no?
- No.
Then who?
It was you. You don't want him
to come to my birthday.
Right, grandma?
Well, you see, mom and dad
are not on good terms right now.
- They'll figure it out, you'll see.
- Mom, could you?
Yes, chief.
Raquel, I know this is your day off,
but we have a situation with hostages.
The suspects tried to get away with
the money, but they weren't successful.
They wounded two cops.
And now they're holed up at the Royal Mint.
I want you at the scene
to be the negotiator.
- Better send a car.
- It's already outside.
What the fuck was that?
Explain to me what the fuck was that!
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Are you a psycho bitch?
8 HOURS INTO ROBBERY
- You shot a cop, god damn it!
- Calm down.
A fucking cop began shooting, alright.
What would you do, spit on him?
- I don't give a shit!
- What would I do?
I would follow the the
fucking plan, damn it!
We've been over it 400 million times.
FRIDAY 6:25 P.M.
Didn't we agree, no one gets hurt.
- I blacked out from the impact...
- I don't care!
Nairobi and I covered you,
but aimed at the ground,
We didn't aim at the cops, asshole!
They're taking the wounded cops away.
Are the phones connected?
Drop any radio or wireless signal.
We're switching to analogue.
Call the Professor.
What are you wearing?
- What happened?
- Two cops were wounded.
Who fired?
Tokyo.
Connect the cameras for the Professor.
Rio got grazed and Tokyo opened fire.
Apparently, they're involved.
Let me talk to her.
- What?
- Is this true?
- That you were involved with Rio?
- Are you serious?
No.
The love of my life died because of me,
so the last thing I want
is getting involved with a kid.
I only fired to protect
myself and my partner.
And Professor, no matter
how much you thought it out,
things don't always
end up how you planned.
What's happening?
It looks like they blew
up one of the vaults
in an attempt to take the
last of the printed sheets.
- Why didn't the alarms go off?
- We don't know.
A manual alarm went off, we assume
one of the employees activated it.
How many hostages?
It's impossible to say,
the museum was open.
Give me a number.
Confirmed: 35 employees, 11 security guards
and 17 students from the British School.
- Why would students be in there?
- A field trip.
- Has the media reported it?
- No, not yet.
And the suspects?
We don't know yet. We're compiling
images from nearby businesses.
How many are there?
Well, four came out, we think
there's no more than six.
- Weapons?
- We know they have at least three M16s.
- And they're extremely aggressive.
- And SWAT is here.
Yes, they were the first to arrive.
Okay, please, give me
some good news, alright.
Well, the cops that
were shot, they're alive.
Thank goodness.
Let's go.
What's on the images from the cameras?
- The ones that are on the inside?
- There's no signal.
- What do you mean?
- There's no signal
I don't know. Maybe
they smashed them.
There's no signal.
We're working on it.
What about the network?
They took down the fiber optic,
therefore we can't hack them.
Everybody, listen carefully,
Police, Public Safety Teams,
I want every phone disconnected.
Just in case they try
to contact us,
we'll free the relay that's
on the roof of the building
Whatever cellphone signal
that is in the perimeter
must go directly through us.
Okay, I want the analysts here,
in two seconds. Got it?
Do we have the floor
plans for the building?
Yes, I'm looking
it over for a way in.
Isn't love exciting.
And they say that civil
servants aren't well taken care of.
What the hell are you doing?
This is our short break
They have to set up camp,
send in a drone, look
for the building plans.
We need to allow them some time
so the police can get organized.
Hey, why did Tokyo pretend that
you two are not together?
Because we're not.
Then why did I hear her headboard
thumping like a sledgehammer every night?
You think she might be learning to dance
the samba at 5 o'clock in the morning?
I have no fucking idea if she's dancing
samba or if she's a nervous sleeper.
Tell me, you think
I'm an asshole?
And that you can just
lie right to my face?
I'm joking.
I'd do the samba with her, too.
In fact, I might try.
I think you're mistaken.
I'm dead serious about her.
Dead serious?
You mean, serious like
plant a flower garden
and do household
chores on the weekends?
That's it.
And fill it with kids.
Sit down.
Look, kid,
women will give you
sex and fun because...
they're programmed to
be impregnated by you,
and bend your will.
After that, you're nonexistent.
During labor you'll realize that.
A birth is the biggest
event for a father.
During labor...
what you'll see between her legs is a
nuclear warhead that'll destroy all.
First, the wonderful cave
that you used to put your dick in
will never be the same.
And while she's curses your name
and asks for the
epidural, she'll shit herself.
Do you know what
she's telling you with that?
That she will no longer be sexy.
That from now on that fatso
will be the center of the universe.
They're all like that.
Take it from me,
with five divorces.
Do you know what
five divorces is?
Five times I thought I was in love.
What the fuck's going on in your head, man?
Huh?
So why did he put you in command?
For my sensitivity
toward people, of course.
Now take the little lamb
to one of the offices.
And don't leave her side,
even if she has to change her tampon.
Alright.
Okay, we need to be back
in 30 minutes. 30 minutes.
Excuse me.
Well, look, I uh...
I'm going for a quick jog,
to stretch my legs a bit.
Go ahead. Enjoy the view.
Learning a language
is easier than it seems,
It's just a matter of semantics.
Come on.
Relax. I'm taking you somewhere
else so you can rest, that's all.
Raquel, all communications
from inside the building
must be done from that phone
or radio, no cell phones, alright?
Make the call right now,
I want to talk with the suspects.
Angel, what the hell
is Colonel Prieto doing here?
I don't know. I don't know.
There's some guys firing guns in the
same place where money is printed.
Don't you think that Intelligence
should be involved?
Raquel, we're making the call now.
Chief, phone call is going through.
Hello.
Good evening.
This is Raquel Murillo, the inspector
in charge of negotiations. Who are you?
The man in charge of the heist.
- He has a voice changer.
- Cleaning up the signal.
How are your colleagues doing?
At least as of now, we don't
have any casualties to report.
I'm glad.
Honestly, I'm glad.
Sorry, but your voice sounds strange.
Yes, my apologies for
this hideous metallic voice,
but you have to understand
that I must protect my identity,
unless you get us a helicopter
so we can go to Brazil.
That's what you need, a helicopter?
For now, what I want
is to is to negotiate
with someone who
doesn't waste time,
who doesn't have to
check with a supervisor, or
with Intelligence or even their
mother to get a yes or a no.
Then you should talk
directly with the president,
but since he's kind of busy
running the country right now,
I'll do my best to stand in
for him, if you don't mind.
Are there any other questions?
Yes.
What are you wearing?
What?
How are you dressed?
Don't you think our clothes
say a lot about our personalities?
Look, I really don't mind
answering your questions,
but I think I should let you know
that this conversation is being
heard by several members
of UDEV, the UIT, the CNI
and their liaison office, the head
of the GEOs and several more officers.
In that case, I believe the polite
thing to do is to introduce ourselves.
Gentlemen, it is a pleasure
Forgive me for not giving you my name,
but you can call me Professor.
That's what everybody calls me.
Hello. I'm Angel, Deputy
Inspector of the Police Department.
Pleased to meet you, Angel.
How are you?
- Fine, good morning.
- Good morning.
Hello, how are you?
Very good. I'm well, thank
you for asking. And you?
Well, this was a touching moment.
Tell me,
what do you want?
Time...
to try to set things straight.
Listen, Madam Inspector.
It was a matter of seconds
for us to be able to flee,
but we are perfectly prepared
to defend ourselves, so
try to avoid any
type of intervention.
Can I trust you?
Yes, of course.
But in order for me to trust you,
you must give me something.
Let those school kids go,
they're minors.
It will go a lot easier.
But, Inspector, you haven't yet
told me what you are wearing.
I have on a light grey
suit, with a blue shirt,
high heeled black boots and...
Well, I think that's
enough for now, don't you?
I can imagine you much better.
But, Inspector, a women's suit
comes with a pair of slacks or a skirt,
so when I ask you about your
clothing next time, please be
a bit more specific.
I'll think about your request.
Al right, what kind of nut-job
holding 60 hostages
plays games with his negotiator?
No, he's way too
calm to be a nut-job.
I want a helicopter flying
above his head, 24/7!
There will be no food, water or
any other requests. Is that clear?
Excuse me, Inspector.
I don't think they'll surrender just
because you took away their dessert.
The head of the GEOs, and I believe
what we need now is an
immediate intervention.
If they had wanted a disaster
like the one they had in Moscow,
they'd have called you directly,
but unfortunately you're only here
to bust everyone's balls, aren't you.
Please, Inspector, don't
get defensive about it
I'm here to help you.
I know you're going
through a rough patch.
If you're referring to menstruation, that's
not it, but thanks for asking anyway.
I'm referring to the complaint of
domestic violence against your ex-husband.
Wow, great Intelligence job.
There's not one asshole you
won't stick your nose in, is there?
Internal Affairs does it's job.
In fact, they believe
your complaint is not valid.
Your ex-husband has rebuilt his life
privately and professionally at the force.
But some women just can't let go
Look, I don't know if
you're just a pig or...
it's simply your method.
If anyone's interested
in my private affairs,
well then, I'd like to let you know
that the matter has been dealt with
and now it's up to a judge.
I want to thank you for
your concern, colonel.
Incoming call on the museum's relay.
- Record it.
- Yes, we're recording.
Turn up the volume. Silence, please!
Honey, I can't make it.
How come you're
not coming for dinner?
I'm working.
Explain to your mother and sister.
- I can't believe you're not coming.
Give my apologies. Please, believe me.
Don't give me grief, sweetheart.
I'll be there as quick as I can.
Almansa!
I need to go now. I love you
very much. I'll see you soon, okay.
Drop it.
It was Almansa.
Why did you take me here?
It's okay.
They sent me to protect you.
That's all.
Take your clothes off,
put on the red overalls.
All right.
If everything goes south?
What if the plan fails?
Well, puppy dog,
same as always: back to the can,
cigarette in the courtyard,
four shrimp for Christmas,
personal visits,
shower once a week.
That sounds cool.
The fucked up thing
is, if it goes well,
what do we do
with all that money?
Look, I'm getting a Maserati,
color: clear sky blue.
- I can see it.
- And a martial arts studio.
Why not.
And a nightclub, but
a three story nightclub
With huge speakers that
will make your ears bleed.
- Boom, boom, pam, pim pam pum.
- Okay, yeah. There you go.
- For him, three million is enough.
- And for you, new lungs,
because you fucked them
up working in the mine.
You're going to spend all
your money on a pair of lungs, huh?
Come on, enough already.
And can you tell us where the hell
you're getting those lungs?
There's people that sell kidneys.
There must be people that sell lungs.
As for me... a winery in Provence.
A 250 acre vineyard
to make my own wine,
oak casks...
yeah, but...
you can just go to the grocery store
and buy any bottle of wine you want.
Why go through
all that hassle?
For the art.
As for me, I want an island.
- Get more than one.
- Yeah, get three.
- Three is a crowd.
- Oh, yeah, like an archipelago.
No, I want a tiny island
with a huge house,
with a balcony overlooking the sea.
So I just get up from bed
and jump in the water.
At last someone with some brains.
Yeah, well I think some
of us need to pay off
a few outstanding debts first.
Well, I do, at least.
And with whatever's
left, a plane.
So I can fly it.
Why not have
a pilot who's hot?
No, you don't get it,
I want to have fun
with the control tower, so I could say;
everybody clear the runway
because this lady is landing.
Even if you were to buy all
those things you could imagine,
at an expensive price.
Let's say the most lavish,
Even then, you would have
lots of money left over.
If we're stealing huge,
then think huge.
Well, I'd record a music
album, the corridos.
With this face on the cover.
Like Bertín Osborne,
but 60 pounds heavier.
That Bertín, he sings
rancheras, I said corridos,
it's completely different music.
Show them what a
corrido is, papa. Come on.
No way man, no.
- Come on!
- Come on, man.
- But you love them.
- You've all been drinking too much.
- We want a song.
Because I didn't have your lips
I cried for the first time
And I cursed knowing you
to not stop loving you
I wanted to make you my wife
I looked for luck loveless
I took out my gun
And fate brought death
María, my life, my love
I won't stop loving you
I lost you due to bullets
You won't see me again.
Stand up.
Come on, come on.
Take off your masks.
Come on, let's see those faces.
Behave.
Listen, something unexpected happened.
And in spite of those helicopters,
I know for a fact they're
giving us a few hours of a truce
so you'll be able to rest.
In a few minutes we'll
distribute some sleeping bags,
water and a sandwich.
And I want to ask you a favor.
Take your clothes off.
I want to give you a red
overall just like this one
so you're more comfortable.
Excuse me, sir,
I don't mean to bother you.
But there's some of the folks here
who have things like heart conditions,
ladies who are pregnant,
diabetics, and even teenagers...
I beg you, please, let
the most vulnerable go.
I don't think they can withstand
this anguish all night long.
- Who do you think you are, fucking Gandhi?
- Relax Denver,
He's a friend of mine.
We share a fondness for movies.
Here, take the gun.
I'm not asking you, I'm
ordering you to take the gun.
Go ahead, take the gun from
me. Take the gun from me.
- Now point it at me.
- No, please.
I said for you to point the gun at me.
It's a fucking order.
Point the gun at me.
Here. Alright.
Now, shoot me.
- What?
- I said, shoot me.
- Shoot me.
- Please.
- No, please!
- Either you shoot me
or I'll shoot you. You got ten seconds.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...
They're fake, Arturito,
but you did great.
You did great. It's a
gift, you can keep it.
Now we're going to
distribute some fake guns.
In a few hours we'll be
needing your cooperation.
And, as you've seen, the only
thing you need to do is obey.
So just trust us... and obey.
Why are you all still dressed?
Come on.
What are you wearing?
Raquel, neither walkies,
cellphones, or electronic devices.
We haven't been able to trace
any radio frequencies from inside.
You're saying that they're
communicating with a cup and a string
- so we can't trace them?
- I have no ideaif it's a cup
or they're deaf-mutes, but we
haven't found any radio frequencies.
What the hell are those
armored cars doing here?
We're going to enter, right now.
Only if I give the order.
I'm in charge and
I haven't done that.
We got the orders, ma'am.
I'd like someone to tell me
what the fuck is going on here
or should I personally call
the Minister of Interior?
What the fuck is going on?
In there is a top priority person.
Do you know
what top priority is?
No. I don't belong to your Intelligence
gang, so I don't know what that means.
They will go in.
They will go in because
we have our little lamb.
Alison Parker.
The daughter of Mr. Benjamin Parker,
the United Kingdom's ambassador
and close friend of
the Queen of England.
That's why we have no
other choice but to enter,
because, if we don't do it now,
tomorrow the whole country will know.
They'll think we're not aware.
They'll think they successfully kept
all this information from the public.
Today she's just
another hostage,
but tomorrow she'll
be their main target and
all the guns will be
pointed at her head.
Is that what you want? Huh?
That's why, on
the first night,
they'll come in. And
they'll do it before 4:15.
Because at 6:30 the sun rises.
Can you imagine what
it would mean for Spain
a hostage crisis
negotiated by the UK?
And it's best they come
in without much thought
then our chances of winning
are improved greatly.
Inspector Murillo,
we're going in now
and we're bringing
that girl out alive.
Hey.
- I have to talk to you...
- Quiet.
I promise.
Shut up, or they'll kill us.
Sorry.
Apparently, you don't
like your boss, do you?
How do you know he's my boss?
Because I know everything about you.
I studied.
And, I saw the pregnancy test on your desk.
And now it's easy to imagine the father.
He didn't like the idea?
What did he say?
He doesn't want the hassle?
It's not easy to let it go.
What are you going to do?
Abort it.
Intervention units 1, 2 and 3, be ready.
- We're going in.
- Go, go, go!
Teams 1, 2 and 3, on my go.
Do it.
Team 1, barricade the main entrance.
Watch the rooftop and the higher flanks.
Yes?
Berlin,
- They're coming.
- On our way.
People, it's time!
The time to follow my orders has come!
Come with us.
And that's how the nation's security forces
did exactly what the
Professor told us they'd do,
but when he told us that afternoon,
we were out in the country,
not a single one of us was thinking
about getting a bullet in the head.
They'll try to come in
through these four places:
the main entrance,
the loading zone,
the emergency exit and rooftop.
Cover all the doors in the back.
Don't let anyone out.
But they'll wait.
They'll wait...
for the tactical team to set up
surveillance and assess the area inside.
They'll do that from the loading zone.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, they're already at the door.
You ready?
Get me eyes on the room.
Your masks on.
Raquel, there's an incoming call
from one of the hostage's cellphones,
Alison Parker.
Turn up the volume.
We have another listener on the phone.
I'm not a listener.
I'm a hostage and I've been kidnapped.
My name is Alison Parker. I'm
the daughter of the UK ambassador.
They're airing this live.
I'm making this call right
now from inside the Royal Mint.
Drop that call immediately! Now!
- I said drop the call!
- Drop the call!
They've dressed us up
just like the kidnappers.
Colonel, we have a visual on the interior.
What the hell is that?
They made us wear the
same masks, and gave us guns.
- Zoom in. Right there.
- Nobody knows who is who.
It's a mounted
Browning machine gun.
Those motherfuckers.
If the police come in,
they're gonna shoot.
They're entrenched
with the hostages.
They're all dressed
the same way.
It's impossible to know
who they're firing at.
- Don't do it.
- Stop this.
Stop it!
- Don't come in.
- Call it off.
Abandon all positions. Aborting operation.
Inspector...
Finish what you started, colonel.
I don't want to have
anything to do with this.
And that's how we won our first battle
on our first night,
without engaging in combat
and with common sense.
And 20 minutes later...
we started doing what we came to do.
Alright, now the
best part starts,
we begin the work.
With me:
Torres, Sánchez, Biesma,
Lennon,
Guatsani,
Molina, García,
Domingo, De Gora, Mateo.
Go on, up there.
Molla, Pérez.
Let's go.
Now then, I want to see
these machines working 24/7
I want it to feel like
we're in a techno rave.
Chicka booh. Chicka booh.
Each time we stop, we lose
half a million, you got that.
We'll make technical corrections
every three hours,
ink and offset, as well.
It's a party. I say have fun and enjoy it.
The best paid job in history:
2,400 billion euros, maybe more.
It'll depend on how
long we can hold the fort.
Oh my god! This is so wonderful, dude!
This is incredible!
Our money, dudes!
This is our money!
Can I get a decaf, please?
Hello. This is Mariví's
answering machine.
Leave a message after the beep.
Mom, I've just finished, it's six am...
Excuse me, do you have a
cellphone charger on hand?
No, sorry.
You want to use mine?
Really? You don't mind?
- No. No.
- Are you sure?
Thanks.
I have to make a few calls.
- That's all right.
- Thanks again.