Can I get a decaf, please?
Hello, this is Mariví's
answering machine.
Leave a message after the beep.
Mom, I just finished. It's 6 am...
Excuse me, do you have a
cellphone charger on hand?
No. Sorry.
You want to use mine?
20 hours into the robbery
- really? You don't mind?
- No, no.
Are you sure? Thanks.
I have to make a few calls.
- That's all right.
- Thanks again.
Saturday 6:25 am
mom, I just finished. I'm on my way.
Chief Sánchez, leave a message.
This is inspector Murillo.
It's late, but... I
wanted to tell you that
if this is being
handled by intelligence,
because of some sort of
diplomatic interests,
I'm not going to be your puppet inspector
while those gorillas storm the place.
So I feel obligated...
to step down. Good night, sir.
Good morning.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
The number of hostages is unknown...
The only information so
far is that Alison Parker...
Oh, but you're up there...
Are you...
If I started off telling
a kidnapping story.
It's because everyone remembers
those days under siege at the royal mint.
Streets in downtown
Madrid were closed,
television broadcasted
live 24 hours a day,
the police threw their operation
manuals out the window
and didn't know what to do
about the balls on those bastards
trying to print their own money.
But actually, lots of things
happened that no one remembers,
things that changed us all
to the point of not knowing
who were the bad guys...
And who were the good ones.
When you negotiate with those people,
do you give them
what they ask for,
or do you just go along
to buy time...?
- Well, you don't have to answer...
- Each case is different.
Of course, I'm sorry.
Though...
We buy some time.
We try to defuse the situation
and end it peacefully.
Thank you.
Actually, we were the ones buying time,
the phrase time is money
has never been so appropriate.
And what a load of money.
Each hour we printed
eight million Euros,
1,400 sheets of currency grade paper
each producing 140,000
50 Euro bank notes.
Everything was so calm at dawn
that it seemed like the
plan was right on track.
The professor was our big brother.
He controlled the police radio
and 18 cameras,
so if someone wanted
to screw us over,
we'd know well in advance.
We took shifts
watching the hostages,
all entryways and of
course the production.
After only 20 hours in
the printers had already
spit out 52 million Euros,
so at that point we all
thought it was gonna work.
But all that peace was only
the calm before the storm.
Things were about
to get so fucked up,
that we came very
close to losing it all.
And if you ask me why,
I'll say it was because
of a simple love story.
In the end,
love is a good reason
for everything to fall apart.
I would like to ask you a favor.
Alright?
All units on alert,
Deputy inspector,
they're opening the doors.
Several men are coming out,
armed with M-16s, sir.
Nobody moves, you got that?
This could be our break.
I said, nobody moves.
Take off the mask.
I ask you to please not shoot.
My name is Mónica Gaztambide.
She's a hostage.
I'm only here to
read a statement.
I'm speaking on behalf of the hijackers.
There are 67 hostages,
all of us are in perfect health
and are well taken care of.
There are no
casualties or wounded.
We're all dressed the same way
and it's impossible to tell
us apart from the hijackers,
so any attempt at a raid
- could cost many lives...
- The guy with the megaphone
is giving orders, sir.
Sir, I have the shot.
Should I take it?
Requesting green light, sir.
I have a clear shot.
They're going back in.
Last chance, sir.
They're going in, I repeat,
they're going in.
No, nobody fires.
Nobody fires, did you hear me?
Let them go in,
let them go back in.
You copy? Everyone stand down.
As we all just witnessed live,
the hijackers just read a statement
where they expressed regret
for wounding the policemen.
Apparently, all the
hostages are in good health
and the hijackers have
no intention of being violent.
Dear, I know that you don't like
it when Paula sleeps in your bed,
but she insisted and I
didn't want to argue with her.
Don't get upset.
We're locked in
and we don't know how
much longer this will last,
but as long as they don't shoot
me in the head, I'll take care of you.
As long as you don't trick me, or try
to communicate with the outside world,
everything will be fine.
From now on, we'll get organized.
You'll be assigned some tasks
so you don't get depressed.
What's your name?
Pablo.
Do you play sports?
Yeah, captain of the
track team at school.
One step forward, captain.
One step forward.
Hey.
Little Arturo.
How did you sleep?
Fine, fine.
Great.
Tell me, are you handy
around the house?
No, no. No, sir. I'm a mess.
Actually, when I get a flat,
my wife changes the tire.
So you're saying
you don't own a drill?
- No. No.
- Think hard,
because I have a fucking
lie detector right here.
Yes.
Second chance.
Are you handy around the house?
- I manage.
- One step forward.
Would you feel better if we
brought a sedative to you?
- Yes, please.
- Okay, very well.
- Anyone else need medication?
- I do. I'm diabetic.
- All right, come up here, then.
- I do too. I take Sertraline.
That's fine.
Anyone else?
I do.
I would like to have an abortion pill.
We don't know how
long we'll be here
and I want to solve
this as soon as possible.
You'll get that today.
All of you, come with me,
I'll take you to Mr Román's office,
it's more comfortable there.
Excuse me, I have a request too.
Yes?
I would like to go on the
internet to delete a photo.
Sorry, but that's not my responsibilty.
I was tricked,
someone took a photo of me naked earlier.
And now my parents, my teachers,
everybody can see it now.
You can send a message, a video,
so they don't worry.
We'll send it for you.
All of you can record
messages for your families.
Nairobi, they're all yours.
Alright, macho guys
hands behind your heads
and to the left in a straight line,
chest out
like the national soccer team.
Come on, athlete.
Do you guys see this dotted line?
You're going to break
the concrete here
remaining perfectly
within the line,
just like
cutting out paper dolls.
It's 160 feet straight
down to get to the collector.
We'll work in three hour shifts.
And when you're
done with your shift,
you go back with the hostages,
and not a fucking word about
what you're doing down here.
- Got any questions?
- No.
That's very good, that
means I explained it clearly.
Alright then, get to work.
You, put on those
hearing protectors
and grab the jackhammer.
I've never used one of those.
First time for everything.
Hey, careful.
Wouldn't be the first time
someone lost a foot doing this.
- Dad, mom, I'm fine.
- Just make it brief.
Hi, dad. Hi, mom.
I'm okay, they feed us
and we get to rest.
Mom, this is not horrible.
No one got hurt.
Mom, I'm fine.
I figure you've seen the
picture that's on the internet.
I didn't upload it, and it has nothing
to do with what's going on here,
it was a classmate who tricked me and...
I can't.
Don't give too much
weight to that picture.
It's like when you go
topless at the beach.
No one cares about it.
I'm not the type that goes topless.
Nor the kind that gets
with a guy in a restroom.
Breaking my arm at school was
my most exciting thing this year.
A robbery is more exciting.
Well, you think about what
you want to tell your parents.
And relax, take your time.
You're quiet.
What's the matter?
What the fuck do you care?
I'm just a kid,
your fuck partner for
the last five months.
The idot with the dog tags.
I said that you were a kid
and I'd never would be with you
so you wouldn't get shot
because I couldn't care less
- If they shot me.
- That's a load of shit,
you didn't do that for me.
What's wrong with all of you?
Ever since I came back in
everybody gives me grief.
A phone is on, sir.
It's Alison Parker's.
Hack it.
You know what's wrong with me?
That I'm completely
sure that you waited
till we left Toledo
to begin all this bullshit
about me being a kid.
She's trying to access her profile.
Come on, come on, come on.
If I was your fucking
gigolo, just tell me.
You were my gigolo.
And everything else.
- I'm in.
- Record it.
I can't talk about this.
You have the nerve to tell me
that you're mourning your boyfriend.
You didn't seem to
be mourning him
when you asked me to
fuck you against the wall.
I didn't see any rosaries
through your fingers.
You talk to me like that
again, I'll kick your ass.
Switch the camera to selfie mode.
Hey, hey!
What the hell are you doing?
No, no, no!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
We lost the signal.
Play it back.
Pause it. Improve the image.
We have it.
- They're going to kill us.
- What are you saying?
- Hush!
And then they'll escape through
the tunnel we're digging for them.
It's gonna be a
fucking bloodbath.
Be quiet, you
don't know anything.
Use your head.
You think these people
are stupid enough to let us go
so we can go to the
police and identify them?
Use your head, damn it.
We're fucked.
Twice. So far I've been told
twice that I'm a dead man.
- Go see what's under the canvas.
- Huh?
Go look. I'm not sitting
here like a guinea pig
waiting for them to kill
me without doing anything.
Do you understand?
Look under the tarp,
see if there's some guns
or something we can use, come on.
- Yes?
- Listen up Raquel.
You call me at 6 o'clock in the morning
and you leave a confusing message
saying something about a puppet inspector,
and gorillas and other bullshit.
Nothing I give a damn about.
Then you walk out and leave
the situation with 67 hostages.
So I'm just calling you so you
can tell me to my fucking face
that you're not taking care of this.
I'm taking care of it.
Raquel, this whole thing
is bigger than either of us.
Homeland security,
state, intelligence...
But, keep this in mind,
you're the only person
that I can really trust
who can solve this without violence.
I understand, thank you.
Get back to mobile
command and take charge.
We've got a photo of one of them.
I'll cover you.
Come on, grow a pair of balls.
Grow a pair, would you.
What's wrong?
- I don't want to do it.
- Aren't you the captain of a rugby team?
Track and field.
Then run.
Containers.
- It's gasoline.
- Seriously?
- And ammunition.
- Holy shit!
What's that?
Drugs?
This is heroin. Dude, it's heroin.
Leave that alone, leave it. It's plastic
explosive, for fucks sakes.
Come back here, come back, come on.
Why in the hell isn't
this machine working?
We're taking a break, chief.
You take a break when I tell you
to take one. Or when it's your turn.
Alright, alright. We're
coming. We're coming.
Inspector, is there a conflict
between intelligence and the police?
Did you step down from the negotiations
due to your domestic violence complaint?
Huh, what?
Alright, that's enough. Back off.
- How does this scum know everything?
- I don't know.
Back so soon?
Do you have a minute?
Of course.
Colonel Prieto.
Look, I've been a little
nervous these last hours, but...
I would like to establish a more
fluid communication between us.
I think we both have a lot
to contribute to this crisis.
I'm glad you realize your error.
I am here,
at your service.
But I want you to know,
before there's any
misunderstanding, I'm...
well, I'm a married man.
Raquel, Raquel.
Male, 25 at the most, we got him
with Alison Parker's cellphone.
Identity?
We're on it, the facial recognition team
are searching the police profiles.
I want to watch
the whole video.
Pull up the image.
We couldn't get more than six seconds.
Pause it there.
It looks like a makarov.
No, it's a strizh 9mm, it's also Russian.
It's actually rare to see them around here.
Talk to judicial.
Tell them to ask every informants with
ties to the Eastern European black market.
- What's that on the wall?
- Cellphones.
Pull up the images of the rear camera.
What's that on the tags? Zoom in.
The list?
Those are their cellphones.
Recognition team will have
his identity in one or two hours.
No, we're not
waiting that long.
You don't find this special
connection quite peculiar?
I was actually about
to call you, just now.
And here you are.
Well, considering that I'm the
negotiator and you're holding hostages...
Yes, but we shouldn't allow this
felony to interfere in our relationship.
I don't know you, but I
see an opportunity here.
A opportunity for what?
To get to know each other.
I'm sure you that if you
and I had met in a bar,
you'd have completely ignored me.
Tell me, inspector.
Have you ever faked an orgasm?
No.
Please, inspector,
don't lie to me.
Think about it, for
a bit, would you.
I might have. I might have done it, yes.
You see, a man is programmed to
ejaculate in the least time possible.
Whereas a women, to make
it last as long as possible.
And sometimes, that small license from
nature gets resolved with a fake orgasm.
Which is nothing more than a small scam.
A lie.
Like last night's intervention,
with a team of elite forces.
Inspector, I asked you
not to lie to me,
you're endangering innocent people.
I wouldn't lie. And now tell me,
why were you going to call me?
Look, we need food and several medication:
Insulin, Sertraline, Albuterol,
an abortion pill
- and some sedatives.
- An abortion pill?
These are requests from the hostages.
We all have personal problems,
don't you agree?
- You'll get your requests.
- Good.
Civil protection will make the delivery,
in clear bags to avoid
the use of weapons.
Now, you tell me,
- you were calling me for...
- For you to surrender immediately.
I have images from the inside,
I've found the identity of one of you.
And if I keep digging,
I'll get the identities of
everyone in your gang.
Inspector, it seems to me...
I'm offering you a
deal with the DA.
I can reduce your sentences
from 16 to 8 years,
only if you get out now.
No casualties yet,
so we can deal.
I don't believe that is
a fair deal on our part.
You've already lost.
Look, in the unlikely
event that you get out,
your faces will be all over the news,
police stations and borders.
You no longer have a plan b.
Then we'll activate plan c.
You think I'm bluffing, right?
Frankly, yes.
To show you that I'm not
lying, I'll give you some info.
You have 67 phones
stuck to the wall with velcro.
You have one hour to consider my deal.
Listen, inspector...
We need to let
the police know
and we must guide
them through the raid.
Listen to me. There's
a phone in my office,
inside a coat hanging
from a clothes rack.
Listen, you've got about 30 or
40 seconds. Don't waste any time...
No, you go!
I can't, you have to go.
You know what would
happen if someone's there?
They'd shoot me, dude.
They're gona shoot you anyway.
Hey, I said I want to hear
that machine working, dammit!
I'm not gonna say it again!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
please forgive me.
- He's very tired. Please.
- I can't.
I can't go on.
- I'm going to die, I'm sorry.
- Come on, get out of there.
Get out and rest.
Yes, professor?
They have an image of
all the phones on the wall.
There's no security
camera inside, right?
No, of course not, just
the ones we installed.
Then it was one of the hostages.
You missed one of the phones.
Find it or we're all screwed.
Give me the go-ahead
to punish them.
We shut them down with fear
or they'll continue to play the hero.
- Like what?
- Make an example.
- We execute one.
- No.
Just find the phone.
Are you really going to abort it?
Please forgive me for everything, Mónica.
I was way out of line, I was a prick to you
I've never been a
brave man, you know?
I've spent all my fucking life
doing what other people want,
never what I wanted.
And I end up in a
situation like this,
with bullets and bad guys,
so I now realise what I need.
It's no longer just me.
It's me and you.
And the child that you're carrying.
I love you, Mónica.
I love you, that I know.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
And I want you
to keep it, alright.
I want to be a parent.
We're having a baby.
And I want us to become a
family if we get out of here.
- What do you mean, if...?
- Quiet
- They're digging a tunnel.
- What?
Yes, they have a bunch of plastic
explosive and gasoline tanks.
- Stand up!
- It's gonna be a bloodbath, for sure.
But there's a way to contact the police
and guide them through the raid.
I have a cellphone in
my office, inside my coat.
I don't know how to get there, though.
- I'll go.
- No, no, no.
There's always a hero...
Who believes that he can save the others.
Who thinks that...
That no one will discover that
he's plotting a strategy to contact
the police.
Bravo.
Congratulations,
because one of you
already did it,
He recorded an image from inside
and he sent it to the police.
Aníbal Cortés, he's from Getafe.
He's an expert in alarm systems,
he worked for two
years in security firms.
He's been linked to the
robbery of a mansion in Geneva,
and has a warrant issued by Interpol.
So I would like
to give him or her the
chance to step forward
so you all of you can thank him or her.
And, while we're at it, give me the phone.
He must have scouted out the Royal Mint
to analyze the alarm systems.
See what's in the hard drives
of the security firm.
If we're lucky...
maybe he was there
with another member of the gang.
Helsinki.
Undress him.
- Come on.
- Are you crazy or what?
Pay attention.
The shirt, too.
Come on.
- The rest.
- It was one of you.
Anyone want to confess?
Denver, take her clothes off.
You recorded a video
in the phone's room, right?
- No, wait.
- Please no.
- What's wrong?
- I can't breathe.
Just take me with the girls.
Please can I go?
Berlin, I'm taking her.
- Berlin, wait.
- What is it now?
I know what happened.
I got distracted for a second, then I
saw Alison trying to delete the picture.
It was just a slipup.
What's wrong, are you ADHD?
Because if you're one of
those kids with problems,
I should know about it.
I don't have any problems.
Tokyo came in, all right?
And we exchanged a
few words, and that's it.
- It won't happen again.
- Now I get it.
Everything comes down, once
again, to an emotional matter.
You really remind me of myself.
I was...
18, she was 44, she
was my French teacher.
- I was her favorite.
- I don't know what's your point,
- Tokyo's not 44.
- She's older than you by 15 years.
And when you're young
and you're with a woman
that's about to hit her prime,
everything's incredible.
She has the experience
that the younger girls lack
and they're far more grateful
than the ugly ones.
My teacher surrendered
her mature flesh
every time like it was
my fucking birthday.
You know why?
Because with you
they can once again
taste the lost youth,
before throwing themselves
off the cliff of aging.
Of course...
there's a small difference
between your love
story and mine.
I wasn't involved in a hostage situation,
risking the lives of my partners.
Teach him a lesson.
A heist at the epicenter of money,
the biggest heist in history.
Strange robbery claims
international attention.
How about that?
- You want some coffee?
- Fuck.
We have a policeman in the ICU,
67 hostages, a load
of heavily armed guys
and for the media
this is like a circus.
Yeah, I don't care about that.
what worries me is that they
have too much information,
it doesn't help.
Are you alright?
I'm going out to get
something to eat, alright?
I'll be back
in a few minutes.
All right.
Attention, inspector out.
Clear the paparazzis.
Leave the packages on the ground
and move back slowly.
I have a cellphone in
my office, inside my coat.
It's hot in here.
The medication.
May I?
What?
Water.
Sit down.
Sit down!
We got the medication.
Distribute them.
- I'll go now.
- Wait.
I want you to come with me.
Come with me.
Look, you might not think it's
worth a shit what I'm about to tell you.
but I don't think it's a good
idea for you to have an abortion.
Thank you.
The lastest on the
hijackers at the Royal Mint...
They're not leaving, huh?
Those people...
must be desperate to do
something like that, right?
That's what makes them so dangerous.
Yeah, but they don't want to hurt anyone.
Well, that's what they're saying.
Then they wouldn't
carry guns, would they?
Of course, I guess you're right.
On the other hand, no one gets to
rob the Royal Mint with a slingshot.
The assailants were surprised by a patrol
while they were trying
to escape with bags of money
and they shot
the two officers who tried to...
The check, please.
And...? Do you know how many there are?
Because some say there are seven.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Yes?
Raquel, the kid was at the museum.
When was that?
Three months ago.
Cameras got them during a tour.
Was he alone?
No, no. You were right,
he was with someone.
Listen, we've identified
another hijacker.
I'm sending the
picture to you right now.
Ah!
- Where is it?
- What are you talking about?
- Where is the recorder?
- But what recorder?
It's just a coincidence
that you're here every day
- asking questions, right.
- I don't know...
What media outlet are you from?
What fucking media
outlet are you with?
I'm not a reporter, my
name is Salvador Martín.
- Please look my wallet. Right, Antonio.
- What's going on, sir?
Please.
I know him, he
comes here every day.
You need money for the kid, don't you?
- Yes.
- No, no...
Yes. Listen, we're in
the middle of a heist.
You can get
something for yourself.
No, really.
Go ahead and hide this in your bra.
20,000 bucks, enough to get the kid diapers
- until he graduates.
- Thanks.
It's not that, really.
I appreciate it, but...
Give me the pill
and I'll get back there.
Alright.
Then what is it?
- That he'll fuck up your life.
- Who?
Your son.
Better to have your life
fucked up by your son
than any of these
motherfuckers, or me.
- I don't see how...
- The life you choose is the life you lead.
One day you're at work,
minding your own business,
and assholes show up here just like Dali,
then one of those guys loses it, a
bullet flies, and everything goes to hell.
That... fucks your life up.
Not a kid.
What do you know about
what fucks me up? Nothing.
My mom was gonna abort me.
It's just...
She inhaled the heroin she
was gonna sell to pay for it all.
And in some shitty alleyway
she was caught by the police.
and with the drugs and jail
and the police and all, I was born.
What about you?
Because it seems like
this job isn't very exciting,
and when you leave,
it's not that great, either.
What is it?
- Do you do kilates?
- Pilates...
Well that's even better then.
And Friday night drinks, right.
What a fucking drag,
another plan ruined by the kid.
But who do you go out with?
Where are your friends?
You want to know?
At their homes, with their kids.
Are they fucked up?
No, right?
What do you do that's so crazy
that you can't do it with a child?
Look, if the father is stupid
enough to lose all of this, then fine.
All that kid's love can be for you.
What are you doing?
I'm giving her the abortion pill.
What's wrong?
She needs you to help her put
it in her mouth with some water?
An abortion is a private thing.
It's for a woman to decide,
but not in here in public.
Anyways...
I'll think about it
til we get out of here.
Very good news.
I'm glad you want to carry on
with the pregnancy. Really.
Now go back to the office with the rest.
You were just at a bachelor party?
Or on your way?
That wasn't the first time
that Berlin put his hands
inside the panties of an honest woman,
though that was the first time
he took them out so quickly.
Perhaps Mónica was hoping he
would get carried away by instinct
and forget about that phone
that rang between her legs,
but that was not the case.
Denver.
What's going to happen to our authority
when she tells all the others?
Because even Berlin
could tell the difference
between pleasure and duty.
Kill her.
And be quick
Let's see.
For the first time
I realised that in
all my love affairs,
there was one flaw.
I was the one being taken care.
But this time would be different.
What's happening? Tokyo, Tokyo!
Go, get Berlin.
No!
Listen to me.
If anyone lays a hand
him again, I swear to God
that the next bullet
will be for Helsinki,
for Berlin or for you.
You're out there, free,
we are risking our fucking lives
inside this rat trap,
don't you get that.
I suggest you put your
weapon on the table.
Put it down.
Put the fucking gun on the table.
Helsinki, stay out of this.
What the hell is going on?
Helsinki.
Put the gun down.
No!
Don't do it, please.
Why did you have to grab
that fucking cellphone?
Why the fuck did you have to fool me?
Rio, no!
Where do you think you're going?
You've done enough for today.
Helsinki.
Put it down. Do it.
You know what will
happen if I don't kill you?
No.
They're gonna kill me first.
And then they're gonna kill you.
And now what?
I couldn't even hear
what I was yelling,
I just wanted to write
a fucking love letter.
While shotguns and
knives were pointed at me,
reality bit like a
like a hungry wolf
and I knew that those the five months
where I believed in something
came to an end.
Your love story has sent
our escape plan to hell.
They have you.
And they also have Rio.
The police know who you are.
You're all over the news.
Holy fucking shit.
Fuck, come on, do it.
Come on, man.
On your knees.
No.
Don't look at me.
- Please.
- Don't look at my fucking face.
Don't look at my fucking face.