Son of a bitch.
You're dead, anyway.
Alright.
Get on your knees.
No. No.
SATURDAY
12:30 PM
Don't look at me.
- Please, don't.
- Don't fucking look at me.
Don't fucking look at me.
Oh my God!
Shut up!
26 HOURS OF ROBBERY
What happened?
Calm down, God damn it!
Calm down.
Keep it together, or
we won't get out alive.
You got to show
a little courage.
Thank you.
Shut up, shut up.
- Thank you.
- Be quiet.
Tell them you killed me and
got rid of the body. I'll hide.
And where the hell
are you gonna hide?
In the second safe.
I have access. They can't get
in. Pretend that you killed me.
- Tell them you killed me.
- There's no fucking blood anywhere, though.
- Not a single drop. Don't you get it?
- Shoot me here, come on.
- Just shoot me here.
- Don't say dumb shit like that.
You're fucking crazy!
Come on, do it.
- Shoot me in the shoulder.
- Your shoulder is too close to your lung.
Not happening.
In the thigh, then. It
bleeds a lot. I've seen it.
They stabbed my sister there,
she bled a lot. Let's go. Come on.
Bite my hand if you want to.
Two gunshots...
Do you have bad aim or do
blondes make you nervous?
It's not easy when she's
begging you not to kill her.
Why didn't you do it?
You're a fucking bitch, you know.
You don't want blood on
your hands, so you used mine.
If you ever put your hands on me
like that again, you're a dead man.
There's a coal furnace in the
basement. Throw her in there.
And afterwards, this mess needs cleaning.
Paula?
Paula, sweety?
Where are you?
Where are you, Paula?
Paula, sweety!
Paula...
"I don't live in Almazán but in Madrid."
"The bus that goes
downtown is the number 21."
"I have two daughters.
The keys are by the door."
I live with Raquel and Paula.
"I'll never go to a home."
"I have two daughters."
Paula always gets her way.
There's a restraining
order against Paula's father.
"Never let Paula go with her dad."
Yes?
Professor, I'm sorry.
Your time is up now.
I need to know
if you'll surrender.
What games did you
like to play as a girl?
Uh, jump rope,
kick the can,
pin the tail on the donkey...
I played with dolls.
I was good at that.
I used to play cops and robbers.
Do you know it?
The idea was the cops
had to catch everyone.
If you got caught,
then you were out.
But I don't remember
a single kid giving up
before getting caught.
The kids at the schoolyard
aren't risking going
to jail for 8 to 16 years.
You're right. You're absolutely right.
And that's why I've talked to my partners.
We voted, and you know what?
We're very confident here.
In fact, we think we'll go
to prison for zero years.
Hi, this is Raquel.
I can't answer right now.
Please leave a message after the tone.
A lot of people are suffering.
What are you gonna to do?
Grab a pen and paper.
I need a truck
with 3 axles,
and an 18 ton trailer,
two tank trucks,
with propane to escort it
and the Malaika ship
with the Saint Vincent flag.
Sound familiar?
You seized it eight months ago
with 6,173 tons of cocaine.
It's at the military base in Ferrol.
Getting the green light for
your requests won't be easy.
For... logistic reasons and
safety concerns...
Picture this:
a building collapses
and there are 67 people inside.
Do you really think the media would agree
that you should have saved those people?
Look, inspector, let's be frank.
You only have two choices. One:
you come after us. Or two...
You save lives.
But I'm afraid
you can't do both.
You have one new message.
Mom, I'm done. I'm on my way.
To call back, press 1.
I'll make you a promise.
If you don't come after us,
I'll hand over the 67 hostages
safe and sound, once we
get to international waters.
And I assure you, it wasn't
my first choice. I hate the ocean,
and basically
everything about it.
Life don't always give you
an easy way out, does it?
I got a voicemail from my daughter
this morning, from this phone.
And I don't... I'm
Raquel Murillo's mother.
And I can't reach her.
Please, do you
know where she is?
It's an emergency.
We'll bring the truck
to get them out of hiding.
It'll be a lot easier on an open field.
We'll fill the trucks
with sleeping gas.
They won't leave.
How do you know that?
They opened the safe,
but they didn't want the money.
They waited for the police.
They began shooting.
They casually dropped two open bags,
scattering the money on the streets.
- So?
- They pretended to be trapped
so they'd get two days to negotiate.
But they meant to go in.
With a Browning machine gun,
masks, red overalls and God's will.
They activated the alarm
a few hours after going in.
And that's when they first opened the safe.
They used the money inside to make it look
like a robbery.
It was intentional.
The ambassador's
daughter is in there.
That's why he's not hesitating.
He's confident, because
everything is going according to plan.
But what better plan than to leave with
the eight million that's inside the safe?
They're printing their own unmarked bills.
- It's here, right?
- Yes.
Careful.
- It won't open?
- There's blood.
You don't have to wait
like the other one?
No.
There. let's go.
You can't go in.
I have a call for inspector
Murillo, Raquel Murillo.
- Alright.
- It's urgent and personal.
- It's an emergency.
- Step in.
Stretch out your arms.
Alright, follow me.
- There's an incoming call on the repeater.
- Record it. Now.
It's recording.
A civilian is approaching mobile command.
He wants to see the inspector,
he says it's urgent.
I'm sorry, officer, but I have
your mother on the phone.
I guess you called her from my phone.
Excuse me.
But I think it has to
do with your daughter.
- Yes?
- Sweety.
- Mom, what is it?
- Stop recording.
Paula left with her dad.
- He took her to lunch.
- What?
- He said it would be quick.
- Mom, what did you do?
- "They're not back yet."
- Alberto has a restraining order.
He only sees Paula every 15 days
and he can't come in the house.
- I don't know what to say.
- Stop recording, god dammit!
- We can't.
- Then turn it down!
Mom, mom.
- When did they leave?
- Two hours ago, I think.
Alright, wait for me there.
- What a setup you've got here, huh?
- Almansa, please escort the gentleman out.
The shots you heard came from
an encounter with the police.
Caused by a hostage who
chose not to follow my rules
and tried to contact the outside
using this cellphone.
And I wonder...
Since I have Miss Gaztambide's phone...
Whose is this, then?
Anybody recognize this ringtone?
What happened?
What?
We all heard the gunshots.
I'm asking you what
the hell happened.
Not here.
We said no victims.
She had a cellphone.
What do you think I would do?
Scare her, damn it,
not kill her.
Cut her ear off, in the
movies they always do that.
If she had told the police
who and where we are,
you'd be the one dead right now.
But at least you'd have your ear.
Who pulled the trigger?
Denver.
He's too hot headed.
The Professor said there
wouldn't be any blood, it was a rule.
Yes, well, there's been a change in plans.
As to who controls the hostages.
Got it?
Don't get nervous, the public is on
our side and that won't change a bit.
We'll be gone by the time
they realize someone's missing.
We'll be very far away.
Does the Professor know? Huh?
Does he know that you broke
the main rule of the plan?
You're not one to talk here.
I mean, you almost kill an officer
cuz he shot the idiot you had sex with.
The Professor has to know.
Hush, boy.
Call him, Rio.
No answer.
He can't control
everything all day in here.
He has to eat, get sleep,
go to the bathroom.
That's why in here I'm in charge.
To escape, we have
to be professionals.
Hey, what the hell is going on in here?
I could hear you all outside.
Berlin ordered a hostage killed.
Who did it?
Your son.
A thief is, by definition,
an arrogant optimist.
They think everything will work out,
but Moscow was the first to fall.
He was one of those decent
men who are trustworthy,
and look after you
and tell you bad jokes.
I thought he was sweet.
Hey, what is that?
Great song.
Do you know how music was first invented?
- No.
- On a train.
I think it was a
dad and his son,
his name was Patxi.
And the boy was worried about whether
the train was gonna stop in the right town.
And Patxi was a fat kid.
And he would go:
"Will it stop, papa?"
It will, Patxi.
- Will it stop, papa?
- It will, Patxi.
Will it stop papa? Patxi, Patxi...
So you and Denver?
You're like family
and heist partners?
Yes, we're like the Sharpener Duo,
but we're burglars. You know.
That afternoon
Moscow told me how he got
his son to join this insane heist.
My son shouldn't be here, you know.
But when the Professor
told me the plan, well,
I dragged him along.
Hey!
Alright.
Hey.
Give me a hug.
You don't mind prison food, huh?
- Knock it off, this is just gas.
- Yeah, right.
And the saturated fat
they give you in there.
- Yeah.
- Give me a cigarette, huh.
I have it ready for you, pop.
What about you? How's life?
Pretty good. It's going.
What is it?
What are you talking about?
I'm excited to see you.
Alright, don't lie to me, son.
This is the sixth time and
you've never had that face before.
So what's going on?
I messed up.
Oh. What did you do?
It seems he'd lost 800 pills.
Of some Polish guy, a damned
drug dealer from Alcorcón.
Apparently, those bastards
stole them from his car.
And his boss.
He's a son of a bitch.
They start by breaking your legs,
and turning you into a cripple.
So everyone knows
you stole from the wrong guy.
Papa...
the deadline is tonight
and I don't have it.
I swear to God I don't have it,
they can look in my car,
They stole it, not me. I didn't
take it either. Pills make me sick.
And, since they were going
to smash his bones, you thought:
I'll just print the money.
We've done every other crappy job:
furriers, savings banks, cargo vans...
And now... we need a big one.
And, if it works out, I'm
taking my son to a country
well, one we can't even pronounce.
Without Polish men, without
debts, to start from scratch.
And with a mojito and a nice beaches.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You're sorry. Can't you
see that we're mopping here?
Well, I left my notes, dad.
You got your notes,
son. Go on, leave.
I'll just be a second.
Let me through.
- Would you stop already?
- I left my notes...
- I have to study. I'm going. I'm going.
- Hurry, come on.
Moscow!
Moscow, stop.
Last time, go back to your post.
What will you do?
Shoot me?
And who will be next?
Everyone?
Do that and you'll
be alone in this place?
Son.
You killed that woman?
Papa.
- I can't breathe.
- Papa.
Papa, what is it?
What is it? Is it
a heart attack?
Papa. Papa, what is it? No, no.
It's a panic attack.
Lay him down. Lay him down.
- Papa.
- That's it.
Laying on that bloody floor,
Moscow knew there wouldn't be any drinks
or a country they couldn't pronounce.
That he didn't save Denver from something,
He'd thrown him in a hole, from
which he would only escape in chains
or with a bullet in his chest.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Those gunshots that we heard...
Did they hurt anyone?
Just take it easy, all right?
Nobody got hurt. Okay?
We did it to prevent the
cops from coming in. That's all.
Ok, kids.
You heard him. Let's all stop
imagining the worst, alright?
Those men are...
they're thieves,
they're not jihad
or anything like that.
Mom.
Sweetheart, I'm so sorry.
- So, did you have a good time.
- I liked the rides.
Oh really, which one did you like?
I liked the boats. The boats that spin.
Oh, yeah. The boats that spin.
Look who's here.
Mommy! We went to the theme park.
It was so much fun, too.
Of course, sweety.
Mom, could you take her upstairs
to put the teddy bear in her room?
Of course.
Come here, honey.
I'll see you later.
You violated the restraining order.
Turn around. Up against the wall.
Raquel, I'm her father.
You can't keep me from Paula.
There's a restraining order. You're in
violation. Now, turn around and obey.
You already ruined my life.
Isn't that enough?
- I said turn around and face the wall!
- Hey!
Really?
You're gonna point a gun at me now?
Yes?
Raquel, this is Salva.
I'm calling you from the cafe.
You took my phone during all the commotion.
Raquel?
Papa. Papa.
How are you feeling?
It's cold.
Cold?
- Bring a blanket.
- Yes.
And something sweet.
Let's go, Helsinki,
go get sugar.
Don't just stand there.
I don't know what happened.
I guess it's because I've
been digging all day.
And all I had to eat was
one of those stale sandwiches.
You should rest, Papa. Rest.
You know what you need right now?
A nice stew, the kind you like.
With lots of chickpeas and pork.
Here you go, Moscow.
Four angels
watching over you bed.
Two at the foot
and two at the head.
Just relax, okay?
What are you doing here, Papa?
I wake up at 4:00 in the morning
and you're not in bed.
It was nothing, I couldn't sleep, so,
I came out to look at
the stars for a little bit.
The stars...
The sky is so big.
Where do you think it ends?
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- You know why I left the mine?
- Of course I do.
Because of what was eating your lungs.
The "synphilis."
The "synphilis"?
- What?
- You're so dumb.
- It's silicosis.
- Whatever.
But that's not why.
It's because I had claustrophobia.
- You?
- Yeah.
I couldn't stand
being in that little hole.
That's when I started with the
robberies to get out of that hole.
Then I ended up in jail. Trapped.
Like I've always been.
Are you alright, Papa? You seem weird.
Weird? No.
I feel amazing, outdoors,
here, in the country.
I'm not worth it.
I don't deserve all of this.
We're doing great here, right?
Yes.
And we'll be even better
when we leave. I know it.
Screw the Maserati and the gym, okay?
You know what we're gonna do?
We'll buy an island.
That way you can sleep
naked under the palm trees.
In a hut. Or you in
one, and me in another.
Yeah.
No more sleeping
together, because you snore.
What are you
saying? I don't snore.
Papa, you snore so much, I'm telling you.
- I do not snore.
- Oh yes, you do.
- I don't snore.
- You sound like a buzzsaw, Papa.
Here you go.
There. It's okay, Papa.
We'll let him rest.
Finish cleaning the bathroom.
And then trade with Helsinki
watching the hostages.
Hello.
I'm sorry. I'm a mess.
No, don't worry. Besides, I
don't think anyone called me.
Look, not even a sad text. See?
Of course not.
Forgive me, it's none
of my business, but...
is everything okay
with your daughter?
Okay.
I stole your cellphone,
I searched you, I nearly arrested you,
and you still worry about me?
Look...
you took the phone
accidentally, and...
you were nervous, and all that.
And as for the search...
It was fun. What can I say?
It was exciting.
"The recorder. Where is it?"
- My arm was like that...
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Antonio was petrified, I swear.
But then you turn around and
invite me here. So we're even.
Everything's fine, thank you.
Good. Yeah.
We worry about so many things
and we shouldn't, right?
In the end...
Actually...
nothing is fine.
No. Everything is bad.
In fact...
It couldn't be much worse. No.
I'm sorry, but... I...
It's just, the emergency...
my ex-husband had just taken my daughter...
There's a restraining order
against him due to abuse.
Thank you.
I got stuff to help you.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- A bit.
Let's fix that tourniquet, alright?
Alright.
Come on.
Maybe you should...
- Alright.
- Be better.
Need help?
Slowly.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
Okay.
There.
Careful.
Okay, that's it.
Oh, man.
What's that for?
We should really remove the bullet.
No. No, there's muscles and bones.
It's no good. You can't.
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
- How will you get it out?
- I'll use this.
- You can't use that.
- I'm telling you, we need to get it out.
No. Some people have bullets
in them and they're alright.
I saw it on TV.
It's fine.
- Alright, alright, alright.
- We leave it in.
Let's stop the bleeding
and then we'll see, okay?
- Alright?
- Yes.
That's it.
Easy. Easy.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm almost done. I'm
almost done. Hold on.
Just like when we were kids, right?
You know, playing doctor.
Alright.
Okay.
I have enough antibiotics
for a whole boarding party.
Painkillers, muscle relaxers...
Everything.
Isn't that bad?
See if it has any side effects.
Well, more side effects
than a gunshot wound?
The baby, you know.
Right.
Okay.
I'll uh...
read the instructions
then we'll decide from there.
Is that okay?
Let's see.
"Read the entire leaflet
before using this product."
"Save this leaflet in case
you need to refer to it again."
"If you have any questions,
ask your doctor or pharmacist."
"This medication has been..."
Oh man.
No.
Hey. Any more noodles?
Noodles, no. I have rice.
That's fine.
Moscow.
What's he doing?
Moscow!
Moscow, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Hey!
Where are you going?
Wait!
What is this? What's wrong?
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Don't open the door!
Moscow!
- The doors are opening.
- Alright. Heads up.
- Go, Go, Go!
- Go to the main entrance!
Stop!
Snipers on the ready.
- Alpha 1 ready.
- Alpha 2 ready.
Everyone! On the ground!
Get on the ground now!
I have a clear shot.
On my count.
- Three, two, one.
- Papa!
Cover your face! Cover your face!
- He's not wearing a mask.
- They're fighting.
- No, papa.
- I have to get out.
- Come on, tape it.
- I can't see their faces.
- I have to get out.
- What! Why?
Waiting for the green light!
It's my fault. You
shouldn't be here.
You shouldn't
have killed anyone.
- Awaiting orders.
- Give me the green light.
You were gonna surrender
to take the fall for me.
We don't know if it's a
fight. We're waiting, sir.
- I have to get out.
- I didn't kill her.
I didn't kill her.
She's alright.
The doors are closing, sir.
Three seconds.
Everybody stand down.
God dammit.
- I need some air.
- We'll go out, papa.
We'll go outside, so you
can get some fresh air.
- I need some air.
- Okay.
I'm so sorry you had to go through...
something like that.
I mean, uh...
Well, if there's anything
I can do to help you out,
I can get you a...
A new cellphone, or a
bodyguard with sunglasses...
Forgive me. I shouldn't
be making jokes like that.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't worry.
I look at you and...
it just doesn't add up.
It doesn't make sense.
You're not what
comes to mind when...
I know. A battered woman, is that it?
Why? Because I have a gun?
Yeah,
the reality is that...
it doesn't always
start with a hit.
If it did, no one would
be with a violent guy.
Actually,
You...
fall in love with a guy
who is sweet, intelligent...
you feel like you're
the center of the universe.
And when he asks you to change
the photo on your profile
for one of your daughter,
you think it's so cute.
And when he tells you not
to wear a miniskirt to work,
you think...
I'm a woman working
in a man's world,
he's actually being
protective, you know.
And then one day...
he yells at you...
- You don't have to tell me all this.
- Yes, yes. I have to.
I mean, it's like...
It's like going down one step at a time
Like in those scary movies
and when someone goes downstairs
and everyone goes:
"Don't go down. Don't."
Yeah.
But you do it.
That's when the hitting first started.
And then the second time,
and then the third...
And then we got a divorce.
But you didn't report it?
No. He's a cop and...
he was the most
popular guy in the district.
I thought I better just leave.
I suppose that
I was embarrassed of
sitting with my boss and
telling him about a year and a half
of humiliation and blows.
I have a 9mm out in the car, but...
the truth is I have no idea
how to take care of myself.
Don't say that.
But...
the real problem was
a few months later.
Because my sister
fell in love with the guy.
and they started
dating, and traveling.
And then I reported him,
late and without proof.
Because I didn't want my sister
to go through all that hell.
You know?
But, of course, I
ended up looking like
a jealous pyschopath
making false accusations
The agent who
didn't report him until..
after he started dating her sister.
But, Raquel, the police
or the judges have to believe
you, it's impossible not to.
I can feel your helplessness.
There must be someone who can help you.
- Yeah, right. Who can help me with this?
- Me.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what I can do, but...
Thank you.
Raquel.
- Raquel.
- Ángel.
There's been movement.
The door opened for a few seconds
and there was some kind of fight.
- We think it's a hostage.
- Let's go.
Look, I want you to know
this isn't a threat,
I'm asking you this as a
personal favor, not as a thief.
I want you to put your
masks and hoods on
and go out on the roof
without doing anything stupid.
Just for 10 minutes, alright?
Go out, get some air
and go back in, all right?
What do you want, to distract the cops?
They're already distracted,
so stop it and don't get everyone riled up.
The bait. They want us to be the bait.
What are you saying?
They'll throw us to the
lions while they escape.
We're doing this out
of kindness, got it?
One of our partners
needs some air,
and I won't tell you
again, motherfucker.
Relax, it'll be okay.
What kind of world
do we live in here?
Nobody's willing to do
anything for anyone?
Our partner had an
anxiety attack
and you're only thinking
about yourselves as bait.
It'll be alright.
Everything wil be fine,
because I'm coming with you.
Why did he have an attack?
It was because of the gunshots, right?
It was because of
the damn gunshots
Who did you kill?
Open your mouth, Arturo.
Open your damn mouth, Arturo.
Open it.
Now raise your left hand if you're
going to keep busting my balls.
And if you're going to shut the fuck up,
then raise your right hand instead.
Good.
Come on, put it down.
Put it down.
Stop fooling around, I'm begging you.
- Wasn't a hostage.
- Why do you say that?
Because, unless they're saints,
they wouldn't let them go to
the door without shooting them.
I'd say he wanted to surrender.
There you go, papa.
Get some air.
You don't have to do this for me.
I remember when mom left,
you had trouble breathing,
you would go out on the
balcony every night for air.
So pretend that you're
going out there right now.
You'll get some air and when
you're feeling alright, we'll come back.
Everyone put your
masks and hoods on.
Arturo, you're next to me.
This is Condor 3 to headquarters.
We have movement on the roof.
Suárez, tell your snipers
to get ready to act.
Condor 1, everyone ready?
Ready. We have a visual.
They're walking.
Dad, calm down.
How?
Look, at this beautiful day.
- Sure.
- Look at the sun.
Just breathe and relax.
It's a big group. They're still walking.
They're headed to the ledge.
Yes?
What are they doing out on the roof?
Moscow went out for some air
with hostages holding fake guns.
As you know, I never
would have permitted this,
but actually my
partners are all telling me
that it was a very good idea.
I don't want any
improvisations.
Keep me informed.
They're still moving. They're
getting closer to the ledge.
If you don't keep a cool head,
you can forget about the money
Acapulco and the kids,
because you'll ruin all of it.
You only had to do one thing:
act professionally.
This doesn't look professional, huh?
Well?
Beautiful.
No, not beautiful.
It's even better than
the ones the banks have.
You can't even trace it.
This is a work of art, okay?
And do you know why?
Enlighten me, Nairobi.
Because I was slow and purposeful.
Just like a professional.
What I don't know
is what to do when one of us
stresses out in the middle of it.
Act like you don't care.
Huh, Berlin?
Like you're not human.
Well, it's easy for an asshole like you
but I... wouldn't know.
- You didn't kill the girl, right?
- No.
- Tell me the truth.
- No!
Berlin found a phone,
he ordered me to kill her and I had
to shoot her, I didn't have a choice.
You're talking about Mónica.
Stay out of this.
What did you do to Mónica? Where is she?
Step back.
This is not a courtesy call, Professor.
If you want me to be honest
and not hide things from you,
you should do the same.
Everyone has a right to
stretch their legs, inspector.
Don't you think it's nice of me to
let the hostages out for some air?
I don't want to hurt
anyone or scare anyone.
I want to return them safe and sound.
As soon as I get what I want.
That's all.
They're armed, take cover.
I repeat, everyone take cover.
Requesting orders.
What the hell did you do?
- Calm down...
- Where is Mónica?
- Tell me what happened.
- Shut the fuck up.
Something's happening.
Requesting instructions.
You killed Mónica, God dammit.
She was innocent.
This is Condor 1. I have a
visual. Requesting permission.
- Get on your knees.
- What?
She was pregnant.
Dammit, snipers.
Let them think that
we're hostages. Hands up.
Don't mess with me, get up.
I'm talking to you.
Something is happening.
They're kneeling down, sir.
They're gonna
execute them up there.
I need orders.
There are snipers.
Get down. Get down.
Where is Mónica?
Tell me what happened to her.
- There's movement.
- This is Condor 3.
The suspect is pointing his weapon.
- I can see him clearly.
- Requesting instructions.
- I need authorization.
- They're still kneeling, sir.
- Awaiting orders.
- They're gonna execute them.
- I have a visual on the kidnapper.
- There are snipers.
- What have you done?
Tell me what happened to Mónica?
- What the fuck have you done?
- They're pointing at each other.
- Give me the green light.
- They're going to execute them, sir.
Requesting permission.
Get down!
Do it then.
Condor 3, open fire.
Arturo!
Target down, sir. Target down.
Target down.
We have a visual.
Damn it. He's the factory
director, Arturo Román.
- Hold your fire.
- Condor 3, hold your fire.
Tell all the units.
We hit a hostage.