(MONKS SINGING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Sergio.
(CHUCKLES)
You were up pretty late studying again.
Come on, get up.
We're waiting on you for breakfast.
Tatiana is here.
(EXHALES)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYS)
(LAUGHTER IN DISTANCE)
Good morning.
(TATIANA AND BERLIN LAUGHING)
Little Prince Hamlet.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Let me introduce Tatiana.
Hello.
TATIANA: Nice to meet you.
Isn't she the most beautiful woman
in the world?
- BERLIN: I didn't know that.
- TATIANA: No?
So, you work in, um…
Well, I'm a concert pianist.
You… You play classical piano?
Yes. Schumann, Chopin, Bach.
Those fingers are divine.
For the piano and for robberies as well.
- BERLIN: Mm.
- PALERMO: Mm.
Pardon?
She's a thief and apparently a good one.
TATIANA: Piano and jewels,
my two specialties.
By the way, she loves
the Bank of Spain heist.
I told her about it.
- You told her?
- BERLIN: Yes.
- We don't have secrets.
- (TATIANA CHUCKLES)
In fact, she thinks this job is much
better than yours at the Royal Mint.
Can we talk for a second, just us?
Are you crazy?
Could be.
Andrés, what'll happen when…
when they offer a reward of 1, 2, 3
million euros for that information?
Because in a heist like this,
that's what's going to happen.
- Don't do that.
- Do what?
You're insinuating that
the love of my life is going to betray me.
Look, I'm not insinuating.
I'm telling you.
Okay, fine, put blind faith in true love.
- Shit!
- Let's go inside.
"Let's put blind faith in true love,"
you were saying and I say, "Absolutely."
You think Tatiana won't sell you out?
Listen to me. She's a thief.
What happens when she has
to turn you in or go to prison?
You're only saying that
because you've never been in love.
I'm being objective. My thoughts
haven't been clouded by feelings.
Look, let me tell you about Tatiana.
I traveled Europe with her,
cracking safes.
You know how tensions run high during
a heist, there's always conflict.
"You place the charges wrong."
"Where's the diamond drill?" The slightest
mistake and it all goes to shit.
But not the two of us, nothing.
Nothing. We're on cloud nine.
We've spend 14 hours
in a disgusting basement digging a tunnel.
And we made love
like there was no tomorrow.
Couples argue when
they go to Marbella on vacation.
The two of us held up a Crédit Agricole
and it was like being on our honeymoon.
So, just like
your last four marriages then.
That was uncalled for.
Below the belt and completely beneath you
as a brother and as a man.
(SMIRKS)
- (IN ITALIAN) Morning, Giovanni.
- GIOVANNI: (IN ITALIAN) Good morning.
Mr. Andrés, I offer you
fruit from the vegetable garden.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you so much,
Abbot Giovanni.
(IN PORTUGUESE) How are you, Joao?
How are you doing with Gregorian chants?
(IN PORTUGUESE) Oh, heavenly, Mr. Andrés.
(IN ENGLISH) I'm very happy.
- (IN ITALIAN) I hope you have a good day!
- GIOVANNI: (IN ITALIAN) Thank you, you too.
Giovanni, next time bring limoncello.
Wait for it!
(DOOR CLOSES)
You even let these monks go to the kitchen
with all the plans on the walls.
(IN ENGLISH) Come on,
they call me "Mr. Engineer."
They think we're academics, not thieves.
Why are you such a pessimist?
How long have you known Tatiana? How long?
Why does it matter? You can't time love.
You have to live it.
You can't risk the entire plan
for a woman.
That's the first rule.
Andrés, rule number one.
"A job can't be tainted
by a romantic relationship."
Never.
It's not hard to understand.
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYS)
It's seven. We have to make
our check-up call.
Can you call Palermo, please?
Palermo, situation?
PALERMO: We've reached ten tons.
10,700 kilograms of granulated metal.
- Two percent more than we expected.
- Obliterating records.
Like Usain Bolt.
And the defenses?
- We're still welding. We got two so far.
- PROFESSOR: Anything else?
Everything's in order. How about there?
No complications. Over and out.
PRIETO: Come in. Don't be shy.
We're evaluating the risks.
Luis, look at me.
Let me tell you,
I've got every color of pill
sitting on my nightstand.
I never want to get out of my bed.
After the last two years,
I've had erectile dysfunction
because of those fucking bastards.
Post-traumatic stress.
I think it might be best
if you stop coming down here.
Take Mercedes out of town,
relax, look after yourself.
Just don't turn on the fucking TV.
Don't make the same mistake I did.
If you have to drop a 20-megaton bomb
on their heads, do it! Just do it!
Don't think about the consequences!
That's much better
than dropping shitty little bombs
every couple of hours.
If you don't hit them hard,
those sneaky bastards
will wipe their asses with us.
They can wipe their asses with me
or hang me out to dry
as long as
they don't reveal state secrets.
If we bust in there, Alfonso,
we'll all end up court-martialed.
- Or worse.
- SIERRA: So what then?
You wanna just stay here
with our hands tied?
We just have to neutralize his next move.
Look. Does the public know
what those secrets are?
No! Not even God knows.
Well, Intelligence knows
what they look like, right?
Which paper to use, which stamps.
Phenomenal.
So, we'll make our own secrets.
We'll infiltrate the news and every paper
and every TV in the country
as if we were the Professor.
Please, what you're saying--
Commissioners on drug lord's payrolls,
ministers taking bribes, orgies…
paid for by using
government funds, whatever.
Hold on, think about what you're saying.
We can't do that. We would shit all over
the credibility of the system.
That means the police, politics,
institutions. Everything.
It won't. The media…
They'll start checking the information.
They'll all have an alibi. Where was
what's his name? In his hometown!
Shit! Where else?
The Minister? In a meeting in Brussels.
So when the Professor,
our faithful shepherd,
reveals the true state secrets…
not even God
could separate the wheat from the chaff.
We've removed the ace up his sleeve.
You know the best part?
By the time he recovers,
we'll have been in the bank and out again.
And that's a promise.
("MY LIFE IS GOING ON"
CECILIA KRULL PLAYS)
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong
I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now but I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
DAY TWO
Are you all right?
Ah, my… my stomach hurts.
From the gunshot.
Here.
It's pretty sore from the impact.
Let me see.
AMANDA: Oh my God, I'm sorry.
And the constipation.
Given the situation,
you can imagine. Right?
Of course. Yeah.
Pass the coffee.
- DENVER: You, come with me.
- Me?
Of course you. Who the fuck else?
Come on, get up.
Let's go.
(HOSTAGES WHIMPER)
Come on, get in.
Stand over there, against the wall.
What the fuck were you doing?
Sorry!
Were you flirting
by talking about shitting?
I was trying to tell her
my stomach's a mess, I've got gas.
For fuck's sake!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Do you like that girl?
(WHIMPERING)
Yes.
- A lot.
A lot and you thought,
that talking about constipation,
your fucking clogged intestines,
and flirting like an idiot
would reel her in?
What the hell were you thinking?
From now on, you're a fucking hero.
A fucking hero. Nothing can hurt you.
You're gonna give her
some of your food every day.
Every single day.
And if I'm acting like a prick,
you're gonna stand up to me.
Starting now. Stand up to me.
Fucking stand up to me!
Yes, sir!
(WHIMPERING)
I'm sorry…
about, uh…
shooting you in the vest.
It wasn't my proudest moment.
Don't worry, Mr. Denver.
I know these things can happen in a heist.
It is not easy, Miguel. Not easy.
Let me tell you something.
I know
that with my intelligence
and that little smile of yours,
that grin right there, yeah…
We're gonna win Amanda over.
How about it?
Think you can give it a shot?
Well, I'll do my best, Mr. Denver.
Of course you will.
Now, get in there and don't come out
until you've taken a shit. Come on.
Okay.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
- MIGUEL: Mr. Denver?
- (SIGHS)
Yeah?
I can't concentrate
with you standing there.
(CLASSIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
REPORTER 1: We interrupt the program
to bring you the news
of the largest classified information leak
in our country's history.
This program has gained access
to more than 100 classified documents.
REPORTER 2: Spain sold cluster bombs
to Saddam Hussein
just six months prior
to the invasion of Iraq.
No, no.
REPORTER 2: This is just one
of the so-called "CNI papers."
A mass declassification of state secrets…
- It's all over the media.
- Those secrets are false.
They're deactivating the best plan
we have to negotiate for Rio.
No, that's not it.
They're taking away our shield
so they can go in.
I understand, Minister.
Gentlemen, we've been given a green light
from the president.
SUÁREZ: Get in formation!
We'll inject extremely high-pressure gas.
Halothane, strong narcotic.
That means they should be unconscious
in no more than 30 minutes,
but be alert for absolutely anything.
- Palermo, do you copy?
- PALERMO: I can hear you.
They're coming in. Get everybody together.
They're going to attack.
When? What type of attack?
I don't know yet. I'll call again soon.
Marseille, they're gonna enter.
We need to know where from.
Report any type of movement.
We need to get off the highway.
Find a road.
In 300 meters, take a left.
Farm to Market Road.
What's happening?
We passed that car yesterday,
90 kilometers from here.
(FAST ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS)
- How do you know it's the same one?
- M5354XX. It's the same!
Don't talk to me like that!
- Not now, not ever!
- Stop. Not now, please!
The antenna, fuck!
Palermo! Palermo, do you copy?
Stuck. We have to get it out.
Go!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MAN YELLS)
(MUMBLES IN SPANISH) Dad!
It's the Professor!
Dad! It's… the Professor! The Professor!
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
And the inspector!
Yes, that's right, I'm, ah…
the… the Professor and this…
is, ah… Inspector--
Lisbon.
- We didn't see any blimps around here.
- No.
So, you guys need a hand to get this
out of the mud or what?
Come on, let's go!
We'll have this thing out in no time!
All at once.
Wait for it to get in. Wait. Okay, wait.
Now, give it some juice.
Come on! Back it in.
Come on guys, come on.
Get it out, come on. Keep pushing.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
MAN: Go, keep going!
Come on.
Something's not right.
I thought they were hostages.
Hey, kid!
Weren't you a hostage?
I was recruited, all right?
Now all of you shut the fuck up!
Ladies and gentlemen, they're coming in.
We all know what that means, don't we?
I'd love to give you more information.
Sadly, we don't have it.
So there's only one thing to do.
To use violence as a deterrent.
What?
We see an armored unit
and we'll riddle it with bullets.
We'll push them back.
- Did that order come from the Professor?
- We lost contact with the Professor.
I don't know if it's a technical glitch
or something serious.
The fact is, we're alone.
So I'm in charge now.
Wait, wait, wait just a moment. Hmm?
We don't know where they'll enter
or if they have an armored unit.
If they'll come through the windows
or the fucking sewer.
Tell me.
Where the fuck will you launch missiles?
Have we all gone crazy or what?
Are you fucking kidding?
Those are our people outside.
We came in here dropping money.
Not bombs.
This would never be the Professor's plan.
He'd try to buy time.
So now Miss Trigger-Happy wants
to buy more time. That's interesting.
- You know what I think?
- What do you think?
That you know if we pull out the big guns
they're not gonna give you Rio back.
They're gonna burn us with napalm!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Let's go! Wake up for fuck's sake!
(SIGHS)
- I'm so sorry.
- No.
Sorry, Tokyo.
You knew this might happen, Tokyo.
- NAIROBI: Honey.
- No.
My heart goes out to you, it really does.
But we need to defend ourselves.
HELSINKI: Bogotá.
DENVER: Take that one.
PALERMO: Time is of the essence, people.
Let's go!
- It's gonna work.
- Let's do it.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Stop fucking around. Right now
this is the only friend you've got.
(YELLS)
- MÓNICA: Where is everyone?
- NAIROBI: Probably eating a pig.
DENVER: This could use a little more oil.
(HELSINKI MIMICKING GUNFIRE)
No, no, no, please don't!
Please don't! Oh! Oh! Oh!
He's one of the gang!
Cincinnati is part of the gang.
- DENVER: Don't kill me yet!
- No, big guy!
- Kill police.
- Hey no, no!
This is a guitar. Can you play?
(IMITATES GUITAR)
- DENVER: I'll be on drums.
- NAIROBI: Get 'em.
- HELSINKI: Guitar!
- (MIMICS DRUMS)
(LAUGHING)
- HELSINKI: Cincinnati, give me five.
- MÓNICA: No…
- NAIROBI: No.
- MÓNICA: See?
Listen.
Whatever you're thinking right now,
let it go.
Hmm?
What is this? So you can read my mind now?
I don't need to be a psychic
to read your mind.
Ever since we got back together,
you've just been… (IMITATES MACHINE)…
running that guilt machine.
So quit it.
You were all having
fucking good time, man.
And you gave it all up to come here.
Of course I'm gonna start
that machine sometimes.
You're gonna listen to me
and you are gonna listen to me good.
And it's all gonna sink
into that beautiful little head of yours.
You are a free woman.
You're free to go partying,
you're free to go to a deserted island,
you're free to leave
this planet if you feel like it.
Got it?
You know who screwed up first?
The Professor.
Yeah. He should've known you'd never
be happy stuck out there on an island.
Who are you, Bin Laden?
You know I'm right. Your name is Tokyo.
The second screw-up came from Rio.
He bought the phones. He couldn't
control himself and he called you.
You wanna know the truth?
We didn't come here
just to do you a little favor.
- Look at that giant slab of cake.
- DENVER: Look at that.
We're all here
because we can't get enough.
We love this shit.
So stop looking at Cincinnati
like he's already an orphan.
Get over it. Let's have some fun.
Because this is a fucking party.
(ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
Party time, sister.
(UPLIFTING PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
Yeah!
DENVER: Everybody sit down.
Let's go to the table.
- Come on.
- NAIROBI: I'm so excited.
Oh, I'm so hungry. I made a salad.
What the fuck is this?
- Artichokes.
- Artichokes?
Ran out of rabbit food?
Come on, we got a load of vegetables
from the monks.
And I'm a vegan if you haven't noticed.
So today, on my birthday. It's vegan.
We don't listen
because vegans are the new Taliban.
They're terrorists!
- NAIROBI: Hold on.
- You won't stop until we die of boredom!
What do you mean "boredom?"
BOGOTÁ: Everything healthy is boring.
Who calls their friends and says,
"Come to my place,
I've got some beautiful artichokes."
Because eating artichokes
is just not fun.
Fun is going to a friend's place
and eating a nice goat or roast pig.
Or getting 50 guys together
in a country house to eat a cow.
Now, that's fun.
I'm sorry for the cow
but it brings people together.
Meat unites, the cow unites.
The artichokes…
divide.
Ah. Well, you know what they say,
"Eat vegan now, eat vegan pussy later."
(ALL CHUCKLE)
- I can be vegan for you, my love.
- Not even with the ten-foot pole, honey.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- She wants it.
HELSINKI: My ten-foot pole…
Professor?
What are the chances of us getting
out of the bank alive?
(INHALES)
At this moment, I would say…
probably less than 50 percent.
In that case, I'd like to say a few words.
Well, they're not my words
but let's pretend they are.
("MARÍA, MI VIDA, MI AMOR"
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ Missing your lips ♪
♪ I cried for the first time ♪
♪ And I cursed meeting you ♪
♪ Because I can't stop loving you ♪
♪ I wanted to make you my wife ♪
♪ With no love, I searched for luck ♪
♪ I started to use guns ♪
♪ And fate brought me death ♪
♪ María, my life, my love ♪
♪ I won't ever stop ♪
♪ Loving you ♪
♪ With bullets, I lost you ♪
♪ You won't ever see me again ♪
♪ María, my life, my love ♪
♪ I won't ever stop ♪
♪ Loving you♪
(ALL EXCLAIM AND HOLLER WITH MUSIC)
(SONG ENDS)
What's going on, Manolo?
The damn thing's gone
and got stuck in the mud.
And where is that from?
My cousin Antonio from Madrid.
(IN SPANISH) It's… It's the Professor's.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
What did you say, Perico?
My cousin Antonio.
He's a professor in Madrid.
Oh, yeah?
Juan and I are going
to take it to Portugal, you know?
- For seven days.
- Just stay quiet, huh?
MANOLO: Eating salted codfish like kings.
- (BANGING ON PANEL)
- CIVIL GUARD: This thing's enormous, huh?
And inside is like a house, right?
Yeah, a little apartment.
- Can I go in?
- No!
It's just that more shit on your boots
than a cow's ass.
I mean, you'd stain it,
the carpet and everything.
Relax, man.
Here we go.
A kitchen and everything.
A fridge.
Unbelievable.
Every comfort.
Professors don't live too bad.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll get one of these for my retirement.
Yeah?
Let me start the car
and help get this out.
Thanks, Paco.
- CIVIL GUARD: No problem.
- (BOTH SIGH)
(CLASSIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
MANOLO: Push!
- (ALL GRUNTING)
- MANOLO: Push, come on.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(IN SPANISH) Wow!
Give me a hug, Professor!
PROFESSOR: Thank you.
(ALL CHEERING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- RAQUEL: How's it going, Marseille?
- They've got a tanker truck.
They're putting some tubes
the ventilation ducts.
RAQUEL: Anything else?
That's all.
Thanks.
Narcotic gas. Probably halothane.
I know Sierra.
She's gonna do it like Putin
in the Dubrovka Theater siege in Moscow.
How far to the transfer point?
Twelve kilometers.
(GAS HISSING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(GRUNTS)
MIGUEL: Hello? Anyone there?
- Turn the volume.
- I know them well.
For example, we should use
harsher interrogation techniques
on terrorists. Wh… What do you think?
Are his rights being violated?
Shouldn't an innocent life be worth more
than the life of a terrorist?
What you're saying here, Mr. Román,
is that the police
have been practicing torture?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Can I go home yet?
No, you can't go home.
Your statements are
putting everyone at risk.
You'll stay here until you learn
to keep your mouth shut.
Where were you during the last heist?
Sorry?
Because I was inside.
Standing up to the terrorists,
saving the lives of 19 hostages.
You brought me in here as an expert. Hmm?
Maybe I'm wrong,
but I'd say you got no fucking idea.
Now all of this is out of your league.
You know what your problem is?
ARTURO: No.
Your life is shit.
You go around speaking to your fans,
they applaud,
and you cum in your pants, am I right?
But when you get home every night,
there's nobody.
Your wife has left you.
You live in a flat
full of cardboard boxes.
You eat tuna from the can
and your kids don't speak to you.
You go on about the heist because it's
the only significant moment of your life,
and you long for it
because you're surrounded by shit.
So when you see a camera,
you cling to it like a baby on a tit.
You're a sad excuse for a man.
Tuna from a can?
(CHUCKLES)
You wish.
I have my life set up nicely.
I fill theater after theater
with people whose lives I help improve.
My book is an international bestseller.
And everyone…
absolutely everyone
considers me a hero in this country.
Tuna from a can.
That shows your ignorance!
Now, if you'll excuse me.
No, my friend.
You're not going anywhere.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
EMERGENCY ROOM
RAQUEL: Connected.
Palermo.
Palermo, do you copy?
(STATIC OVER RADIO)
SUÁREZ: The ventilation
ducts in the bathroom
are the only entrance
that might not have explosives.
They were installed
and widened 17 months ago.
Even so, it is a very narrow space.
Forty-five by eighty centimeters.
We'll confirm that the gas
is taking effect.
Halothane concentration 67 percent.
Gentlemen, we're going in.
This is an extremely high-risk mission.
They've got it covered. That vent shaft
will be a fucking bloodbath.
TOKYO: Halothane is a narcotic gas
which knocks you out ten seconds
when its concentration exceeds 50 percent.
SUÁREZ: Colonel, we've reached the vent.
Looks like someone's there.
He's not moving.
TOKYO: The police entered the bank and
found a room full of sleeping children.
There were five elite agents,
thirty magazines full of bullets
and one simple objective.
Slaughter us like lambs.
And to be honest,
I think we earned it.
SIERRA: We'll do what Putin would do.
We'll shoot first
and then we'll ask questions later.
Try to avoid it if at all possible, okay?
But we must accept
there may be civilian casualties.
Are we clear?
ALL: Yes, sir.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
SUÁREZ: Clear.
OFFICER: Clear.
Hostage.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
SUÁREZ: Hostage.
Hostage.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- SUÁREZ: Stay down! Get down. Get down!
(OFFICER SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
SUÁREZ: Exit left-hand door now!
Move! Come on! Now!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
SUÁREZ: Shield!
TOKYO: Surviving this kind of assault
is impossible,
but by this point in our lives,
we'd specialized in using the impossible
to our advantage.
Palermo.
TEN MINUTES EARLIER
PROFESSOR: Palermo, do you copy?
They're pumping in narcotic gas.
Professor. It's Tokyo.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
Professor, all entry points are covered.
We have to be sure
where they're going to enter.
They'll wait until it's full of gas.
We've ten minutes.
Change of plans.
SUÁREZ: Retreat!
TOKYO: Oxygen was the only thing
we needed to fight them.
And to neutralize them,
we just had to block their route
until there was no way out.
SUÁREZ: Smoke!
(MUSIC ENDS)
PALERMO: How are we doing, Suárez?
(BOMB BEEPING)
PALERMO: See the bars?
Gorgeous, aren't they?
OFFICER: It's RDX plastic explosive.
PALERMO: Precisely.
More than 40 kilograms
spread across seven charges.
I don't imagine I have to explain to you
what would happen if you dare to touch
one of these laser beams.
This is how it works,
the detonator is connected
to a photoelectric cell,
and if one charge explodes,
the others will be set off
in response.
Right, bomb experts?
SUÁREZ: Shit!
PALERMO: So, I would recommend
you relax
because your oxygen is running out
and you're about
to start inhaling halothane.
So,
get on the floor,
curl up
and give each other
a goodnight kiss, muchachos.
Thirty-five minutes without contact.
We're preparing a rescue mission.
General, we can't do that.
They'll trap them the same way.
We don't know what happened inside.
We know we heard the Browning machine gun
and then some return fire.
Then, nothing.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
It's him.
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYS ON EARPHONES)
Martínez.
Professor?
I imagine you're wondering
about Suárez and his four men.
Why don't you tell me about it?
Well, I think his actions were exemplary.
Let's say the operation was very
commendable.
But, how can I say this?
There were a few complications.
Don't worry, they are in perfect health.
Completely fine.
In fact, we're sending you a video
now so you can verify that.
Martínez!
It's better if you see it yourself.
I'm Inspector Suárez,
head of Special Operations.
We're being held captive.
But I can confirm
we're being treated well.
I urge the authorities
to maintain a permanent ceasefire.
PALERMO: Very good! Very good!
Now the next part.
Come on!
Do the rest, let's go.
(SINGING "BELLA CIAO" IN ITALIAN)
(ALL SINGING "BELLA CIAO")
How romantic.
But you're sending this to us,
not to the press.
(SINGS IN RHYTHM WITH SONG)
I deduct the Professor wants
to negotiate.
Wow, I can see you're quite the artist.
Listen, I can offer something better.
I'm offering you a way out.
The United Nations Committee
Against Torture
is currently investigating
the Cortés case.
In just a few hours,
they're going to send forensic experts
to examine him
and neither you
nor the president want that.
Son of a bitch.
So, you should give us Rio.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm not going to hand over a detainee.
The police don't just deliver criminals.
Of course, but there's another reason.
It's obvious,
as demonstrated by your operation,
you've already decided to kill us.
But in custody,
you can't kill Cortés. However…
inside the bank, during an escape,
or a pursuit,
that's different.
I'm offering you and the state
a better option than what you have now.
And third, I'll save you
the international ridicule
of releasing the video of your
lead commander singing "Bella Ciao."
Hand him over.
Tell him we accept the trade.
I want all the hostages and GEO agents.
I need to sell this as a victory.
I'll give you 40 hostages and your agents.
I'm sure you can sell that as a triumph.
- It's 8:00 p.m.
- SIERRA: No.
Daylight.
- The exchange will happen at 8:00 a.m.
- What are you doing?
I am not gonna take
40 civilians out of there
without being able to see what's going on.
Accepted.
(SOOTHING MUSIC PLAYS)
- Why don't you just take over?
- That's right. Martínez!
PROFESSOR: Tokyo, they've agreed.
(CHUCKLES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(WOMAN HUMMING)
Hello.
Did you get some rest?
How long have I been asleep?
Fourteen hours.
RIO: I feel like I'm floating.
(LAUGHS)
You wanted to take something.
So they gave you an elephant's dose.
Remember?
Remember.
Well, come on.
We have to make you look handsome for TV.
Come on.
Get up.
Where are you taking me?
To school.
Can I make you some cereal?
RIO: You're gonna be a mother?
You'll go to your son's school
to tell the kids stories?
Of course.
And we'll take them lollipops
just to fuck with those
sexually-frustrated mothers
who say candy's bad for kids.
Alicia.
Your son won't love you.
But you're gonna adore me.
Let's go.
RIO: Where are we going?
To school.
(CROWD DROWNED OUT BY MUSIC)
("BROKEN COASTLINE"
BY DOWN LIKE SILVER PLAYS)
♪ I've been driving ♪
♪ A broken coastline ♪
♪ Holding on to everything I want ♪
♪ I've been trying to make this all mine ♪
♪ Pushing faster
Before the light is gone ♪
♪ For a while now
Day's been breaking colder ♪
HOSTAGE SWAP AT THE BANK OF SPAIN
♪ There's a wild wind driving me on ♪
♪ Would you know me
If I walked through your doorway? ♪
♪ Would you hold me
Like you've done before? ♪
TOKYO: The impossible had happened.
We risked everything to get this far,
but none of that mattered
when I saw Rio get out of the car.
He was alive.
Disoriented
and unable to explain a thing.
(INAUDIBLE SCREAM)
TOKYO: But he was so handsome.
♪ Would you know me
If I walked through your doorway? ♪
♪ Would you hold me
Like you've done before? ♪
♪ Will there be a place for me ♪
♪ If I can't drive anymore? ♪
("ASALTO AL CAMIÓN"
BY IVÁN M. LACÁMARA PLAYS)