1
00:00:09,271 --> 00:00:10,437
Palermo...

2
00:00:10,521 --> 00:00:11,812
this is war.

3
00:00:12,312 --> 00:00:13,646
Act accordingly.

4
00:00:18,521 --> 00:00:19,604
Doors!

5
00:00:21,687 --> 00:00:22,979
Fire!

6
00:00:58,854 --> 00:01:01,479
Everything can go to shit
in a split second.

7
00:01:03,729 --> 00:01:06,604
The moment you feel
death creeping in,

8
00:01:07,396 --> 00:01:10,271
you know nothing will ever be the same...

9
00:01:12,937 --> 00:01:15,604
and that you need to try your best
to survive.

10
00:01:15,771 --> 00:01:17,729
Nairobi, hang in there!

11
00:01:21,687 --> 00:01:24,604
Hang in there. Hang in there, Nairobi.

12
00:01:25,687 --> 00:01:27,229
Come on.

13
00:01:27,729 --> 00:01:28,812
Let's go!

14
00:01:29,562 --> 00:01:32,646
We all have snipers aiming at our hearts.

15
00:01:33,812 --> 00:01:36,187
But the true terror arrives

16
00:01:36,271 --> 00:01:40,187
when that bullet doesn't hit you...
but takes out someone you love.

17
00:01:40,271 --> 00:01:41,104
Hurry up!

18
00:01:47,229 --> 00:01:48,271
Saline, Rio.

19
00:01:59,521 --> 00:02:00,521
Almost done.

20
00:02:06,146 --> 00:02:08,687
The Professor was feeling
that terror the most.

21
00:02:09,729 --> 00:02:14,521
Two words that should never go together
collided in his heart: "love" and "death."

22
00:02:15,562 --> 00:02:17,271
That made him freeze up.

23
00:02:18,021 --> 00:02:19,979
As he ran through the woods...

24
00:02:24,187 --> 00:02:26,146
he couldn't stop thinking,

25
00:02:27,146 --> 00:02:29,396
"They've killed the woman I love."

26
00:02:38,312 --> 00:02:39,687
But Lisbon was there.

27
00:02:40,896 --> 00:02:42,312
She wasn't gone.

28
00:02:43,271 --> 00:02:48,646
The shots of her fake execution
had sounded real enough to the Professor.

29
00:02:49,729 --> 00:02:52,687
Our mastermind was losing his head
like never before.

30
00:02:53,354 --> 00:02:54,604
And along with him,

31
00:02:55,937 --> 00:02:57,312
we were losing ours.

32
00:03:21,396 --> 00:03:23,396
Pulse: 155 and rising.

33
00:03:23,479 --> 00:03:25,771
Blood pressure: 85/40. It's dropping.

34
00:03:25,854 --> 00:03:29,312
- We need two units of blood and saline.
- Nairobi.

35
00:03:29,396 --> 00:03:30,979
Stay strong. I'm here.

36
00:03:38,229 --> 00:03:41,979
In the tent, Tamayo felt what I felt.

37
00:03:43,146 --> 00:03:45,271
We were staring death in the face.

38
00:03:49,062 --> 00:03:51,937
A dry mouth. The taste of metal.

39
00:03:52,562 --> 00:03:55,312
Tightness in the chest
and pain in the temples.

40
00:03:55,437 --> 00:03:59,229
But until it was game over,
we still had everything to play for.

41
00:04:07,021 --> 00:04:09,521
Blood at 30ºC, ready for transfusion.

42
00:04:26,896 --> 00:04:27,812
It's here.

43
00:04:28,396 --> 00:04:31,229
The bullet. Behind the seventh rib.

44
00:04:31,312 --> 00:04:33,479
It's in the lower part of the lung.

45
00:04:33,687 --> 00:04:35,979
That's good news, honey.

46
00:04:39,229 --> 00:04:41,479
She can't breathe. It's a collapsed lung.

47
00:04:41,562 --> 00:04:45,229
- We have to release air.
- Tokyo, surgical kit six.

48
00:04:45,312 --> 00:04:46,771
OK, surgical kit six.

49
00:04:46,854 --> 00:04:49,312
There's air between the lung
and chest wall.

50
00:04:49,396 --> 00:04:50,479
Hurry, Helsinki.

51
00:04:51,354 --> 00:04:53,146
- She can't breathe!
- Hurry up!

52
00:04:59,479 --> 00:05:00,437
There we go.

53
00:05:06,062 --> 00:05:07,187
Get me out of here.

54
00:05:09,812 --> 00:05:13,479
I'd rather be in prison alive.
I don't want to die.

55
00:05:15,771 --> 00:05:16,604
Tokyo...

56
00:05:18,521 --> 00:05:20,937
hand me over to the police, please.

57
00:05:23,021 --> 00:05:24,312
Please.

58
00:05:26,646 --> 00:05:27,854
Hand me over.

59
00:06:45,854 --> 00:06:48,521
STAGE 3

60
00:06:49,854 --> 00:06:51,479
RESISTANCE

61
00:06:53,687 --> 00:06:57,354
Once they hand over Rio,
we'll begin stage three of the plan:

62
00:06:58,396 --> 00:06:59,271
resistance.

63
00:07:03,937 --> 00:07:06,312
You can't get out
of the Bank of Spain alive.

64
00:07:08,271 --> 00:07:09,229
It's impossible.

65
00:07:10,937 --> 00:07:13,021
But I will get you out of there.

66
00:07:13,104 --> 00:07:15,937
Once we begin stage three,

67
00:07:16,521 --> 00:07:18,896
there'll only be one countdown:
the gold.

68
00:07:18,979 --> 00:07:21,479
And our only goal will be to melt it.

69
00:07:22,437 --> 00:07:24,937
Because the gold is the key.

70
00:07:25,354 --> 00:07:27,937
Without it,
I won't be able to get you out.

71
00:07:29,396 --> 00:07:30,521
The police...

72
00:07:31,771 --> 00:07:34,396
will react harshly, but it doesn't matter.

73
00:07:37,729 --> 00:07:38,854
Whatever happens,

74
00:07:39,937 --> 00:07:41,146
whatever they do...

75
00:07:43,562 --> 00:07:46,937
we need to be able to keep control.

76
00:07:49,937 --> 00:07:52,354
Otherwise, our lives will be in danger.

77
00:08:03,437 --> 00:08:05,229
Did we kill any officers?

78
00:08:05,687 --> 00:08:08,146
I don't know, but they were on fire.

79
00:08:08,229 --> 00:08:11,854
They'll come back all guns blazing.
We can't defend ourselves.

80
00:08:13,271 --> 00:08:15,104
And Nairobi needs a surgeon.

81
00:08:16,354 --> 00:08:19,104
We used an antitank gun.
They won't send one.

82
00:08:19,187 --> 00:08:21,396
She's got a bullet in her lung.

83
00:08:21,479 --> 00:08:24,771
We can't do it ourselves.
You've got to try.

84
00:08:25,812 --> 00:08:27,854
We need the Pakistani surgeon.

85
00:08:29,937 --> 00:08:32,187
- How much time do I have?
- She's dying.

86
00:08:33,312 --> 00:08:36,604
He has crampons, dog deterrent,
and camouflage clothes.

87
00:08:37,312 --> 00:08:41,646
He may be hiding among the branches.
Shoot up into the treetops.

88
00:08:57,146 --> 00:09:00,437
Raquel, don't let them get you alone.
Tell them I'll surrender.

89
00:09:01,271 --> 00:09:02,521
Raquel!

90
00:09:03,437 --> 00:09:04,771
Get out of there!

91
00:09:05,479 --> 00:09:06,646
Get out of there!

92
00:09:07,646 --> 00:09:08,812
Get out of there!

93
00:09:13,187 --> 00:09:14,437
I'm going to try.

94
00:09:52,521 --> 00:09:55,979
Easy.

95
00:09:57,396 --> 00:09:58,646
Easy.

96
00:10:00,687 --> 00:10:02,104
Good little bull.

97
00:10:04,146 --> 00:10:05,521
Easy.

98
00:10:06,687 --> 00:10:08,729
Easy.

99
00:10:09,104 --> 00:10:09,937
Eas...

100
00:10:21,562 --> 00:10:26,229
The Professor is attacking the police,
but nobody is leaving the Bank of Spain.

101
00:10:26,312 --> 00:10:28,979
Demonstrators are in a state of shock.

102
00:10:29,062 --> 00:10:32,187
Will this affect public support
for the Dalís?

103
00:10:32,271 --> 00:10:34,396
For the moment, nobody can say.

104
00:10:34,479 --> 00:10:38,479
But we may be witnessing
the Professor's first big problem.

105
00:10:39,312 --> 00:10:41,812
That was unreal,
the best we could hope for.

106
00:10:41,896 --> 00:10:44,771
Those men have
second- and third-degree burns.

107
00:10:44,854 --> 00:10:45,854
As expected.

108
00:10:45,937 --> 00:10:49,229
- We need another armored van.
- Don't you care about anything?

109
00:10:50,854 --> 00:10:54,271
I won't send more men
to be permanently disfigured!

110
00:10:54,354 --> 00:10:57,062
They fired rockets at us,
and everyone in Spain saw it.

111
00:10:57,146 --> 00:10:59,562
I'm not starting a war
in the center of Madrid.

112
00:10:59,646 --> 00:11:00,854
It's already started.

113
00:11:02,521 --> 00:11:03,604
Tamayo.

114
00:11:04,062 --> 00:11:06,646
Don't make
the biggest mistake of your life.

115
00:11:09,979 --> 00:11:12,271
My mistake was sending you
to torture that kid.

116
00:11:17,146 --> 00:11:19,812
If we'd taken him to court,
we wouldn't be here.

117
00:11:19,896 --> 00:11:22,771
We gave them strength and ammunition.
I won't do it again.

118
00:11:24,104 --> 00:11:24,937
You're scared.

119
00:11:31,354 --> 00:11:32,687
You're like Prieto.

120
00:11:33,354 --> 00:11:36,771
You've got pills on your nightstand
and erectile dysfunction.

121
00:11:37,021 --> 00:11:39,146
And you think the law will save you.

122
00:11:40,271 --> 00:11:41,812
The law can't help us now.

123
00:11:43,896 --> 00:11:45,187
I am the law.

124
00:11:46,021 --> 00:11:47,979
And erectile dysfunction, my ass!

125
00:11:49,687 --> 00:11:50,896
Maintain composure.

126
00:11:52,979 --> 00:11:58,354
Let's de-escalate the situation, OK?
Dialogue and truce. Truce and dialogue.

127
00:11:59,396 --> 00:12:00,312
Is that clear?

128
00:12:01,312 --> 00:12:03,062
Crystal clear, boss.

129
00:12:08,354 --> 00:12:11,979
Antoñanzas.

130
00:12:12,521 --> 00:12:13,646
Yes, Inspector?

131
00:12:13,729 --> 00:12:17,521
You heard that, right?
He is the law, like John Wayne.

132
00:12:19,771 --> 00:12:22,437
I want an ambulance and a surgeon.

133
00:12:23,312 --> 00:12:24,312
Now!

134
00:12:27,812 --> 00:12:30,479
Let's get them
to hand over their wounded.

135
00:12:36,979 --> 00:12:40,812
The governor studied medicine in the army.
He's going to help us.

136
00:12:40,896 --> 00:12:44,562
I didn't complete the course
or practice, obviously, but...

137
00:12:44,812 --> 00:12:46,479
I still know a few things.

138
00:12:46,687 --> 00:12:48,937
- Put on some scrubs.
- I'll go get them.

139
00:12:49,312 --> 00:12:50,812
Where's the damn surgeon?

140
00:12:50,896 --> 00:12:53,854
I'm trying to reach him,
but they have to give me access.

141
00:12:53,937 --> 00:12:55,271
Bogotá, anesthetic.

142
00:12:55,354 --> 00:12:59,812
- Nairobi, we're going to put you under.
- You're not putting me under. Tokyo.

143
00:13:01,354 --> 00:13:02,187
Tokyo...

144
00:13:02,979 --> 00:13:04,479
tell him it's my life...

145
00:13:05,104 --> 00:13:06,354
and I decide.

146
00:13:08,479 --> 00:13:11,604
That's exactly why
we're going to operate on you here.

147
00:13:11,687 --> 00:13:12,937
Tokyo, please.

148
00:13:13,812 --> 00:13:14,812
Please.

149
00:13:19,562 --> 00:13:20,396
She decides.

150
00:13:22,229 --> 00:13:23,396
Period.

151
00:13:26,062 --> 00:13:29,021
Helsinki, put her under.
That's a fucking order.

152
00:13:31,437 --> 00:13:34,562
You don't give me orders.
You're not my boss, asshole.

153
00:13:35,146 --> 00:13:36,604
You let the phone in.

154
00:13:37,396 --> 00:13:39,187
You're supposed to protect us.

155
00:13:39,687 --> 00:13:41,937
She can make mistakes, but you can't!

156
00:13:42,021 --> 00:13:44,687
Shut up, big man,
or I'll fucking kill you!

157
00:13:44,771 --> 00:13:45,771
Shut the fuck up.

158
00:13:46,354 --> 00:13:48,437
You're my little whore, not my mom.

159
00:13:48,521 --> 00:13:51,521
It's her fault she's in this state.
She's an idiot.

160
00:13:52,729 --> 00:13:55,812
If she says she's leaving,
I'll walk her to the door.

161
00:13:56,854 --> 00:14:00,229
And you'll keep your mouth shut,
you piece of shit,

162
00:14:00,312 --> 00:14:03,187
because from now on,
you're no longer my boss.

163
00:14:03,646 --> 00:14:04,771
Put the gun down.

164
00:14:04,854 --> 00:14:05,687
Denver.

165
00:14:06,021 --> 00:14:09,771
If she talks, they'll kill us all.
We're treating her in here.

166
00:14:12,896 --> 00:14:15,312
How are you going to treat her, dumbass?

167
00:14:15,396 --> 00:14:17,146
Nairobi needs a surgeon.

168
00:14:17,271 --> 00:14:19,104
Have you all gone nuts or what?

169
00:14:19,854 --> 00:14:23,646
I swear on my son's life...
I won't tell them anything.

170
00:14:23,729 --> 00:14:27,104
You think you won't,
but when they torture you, things change.

171
00:14:27,729 --> 00:14:28,937
I don't give a shit!

172
00:14:29,771 --> 00:14:31,021
She's leaving.

173
00:14:33,687 --> 00:14:34,687
I don't think so.

174
00:14:39,312 --> 00:14:42,354
Do you think
this is a good time for a rebellion?

175
00:14:42,437 --> 00:14:45,396
One of the gang is dying.
Stop fucking around!

176
00:14:47,854 --> 00:14:51,229
- Another one of the gang.
- What do you mean, another one?

177
00:14:55,979 --> 00:14:58,312
They killed Lisbon half an hour ago.

178
00:15:02,354 --> 00:15:04,854
I could show you my democratic side.

179
00:15:04,937 --> 00:15:08,146
We could vote and send her out,
but I'd be killing her.

180
00:15:08,229 --> 00:15:10,729
Lisbon was killed
on her knees and unarmed.

181
00:15:10,812 --> 00:15:12,354
They brought Nairobi's son

182
00:15:12,437 --> 00:15:15,437
with a teddy bear
to shoot her in the head.

183
00:15:15,521 --> 00:15:20,312
Do you think the Red Cross is outside?
You've got to be fucking kidding!

184
00:15:26,187 --> 00:15:27,354
Palermo is right.

185
00:15:29,479 --> 00:15:31,312
You'll have to open me up...

186
00:15:33,729 --> 00:15:35,104
and remove the bullet.

187
00:15:37,937 --> 00:15:38,812
Maybe...

188
00:15:39,771 --> 00:15:41,729
remove part of my lung.

189
00:15:42,521 --> 00:15:44,854
All that,
without me bleeding to death.

190
00:15:46,104 --> 00:15:47,562
You're going to kill me.

191
00:15:49,062 --> 00:15:50,479
You're going to kill me.

192
00:15:52,187 --> 00:15:53,271
Helsinki.

193
00:15:55,312 --> 00:15:56,604
It's too complicated.

194
00:15:57,812 --> 00:15:59,812
It's too complicated for you guys.

195
00:16:00,521 --> 00:16:01,729
Take me to the door.

196
00:16:01,812 --> 00:16:03,521
- Take me to the door.
- Relax.

197
00:16:04,104 --> 00:16:06,146
- Take me to the door.
- Calm down.

198
00:16:06,646 --> 00:16:08,646
- Calm down.
- Take me to the door.

199
00:16:08,729 --> 00:16:10,687
- I'm going.
- What are you doing?

200
00:16:12,021 --> 00:16:12,854
I'm going.

201
00:16:12,937 --> 00:16:16,937
No!

202
00:16:18,437 --> 00:16:20,646
No...

203
00:16:20,729 --> 00:16:23,562
No!

204
00:16:25,937 --> 00:16:27,937
No...

205
00:16:44,729 --> 00:16:48,312
Sorry, Professor. We had an argument.

206
00:16:49,604 --> 00:16:51,479
I was going to sleep in Tokyo's room.

207
00:16:59,021 --> 00:17:02,646
Are you sure you don't mind me sleeping
here with you?

208
00:17:04,354 --> 00:17:05,354
It's all right.

209
00:17:14,854 --> 00:17:18,187
But having someone in my bed
turns me on.

210
00:17:18,271 --> 00:17:19,312
Do you mind?

211
00:17:20,521 --> 00:17:22,104
Mind what?

212
00:17:22,187 --> 00:17:23,562
Releasing some stress.

213
00:17:24,604 --> 00:17:26,062
Rubbing our lamps.

214
00:17:31,562 --> 00:17:33,021
I knew you were joking.

215
00:17:35,729 --> 00:17:39,729
Can someone please tell me
why Palermo is in charge of the heist?

216
00:17:39,812 --> 00:17:41,521
Because it was his idea.

217
00:17:43,312 --> 00:17:45,312
- He's the mastermind.
- Mastermind?

218
00:17:45,437 --> 00:17:49,521
The guy who was grabbing his junk
in the hallway like an ape?

219
00:17:49,604 --> 00:17:51,146
Come on! Are you serious?

220
00:17:51,562 --> 00:17:53,646
You know who should be in charge?

221
00:17:56,062 --> 00:17:58,604
You. Yes, you.

222
00:17:59,521 --> 00:18:03,854
I agree. If anyone has a lot invested
in this going well, it's you.

223
00:18:05,937 --> 00:18:10,104
Don't egg me on.

224
00:18:10,729 --> 00:18:11,979
I'm going to sleep.

225
00:18:12,437 --> 00:18:13,479
Good night.

226
00:18:22,562 --> 00:18:26,062
I'm going to talk with the Professor.
You'll see.

227
00:18:30,437 --> 00:18:35,479
Professor, I want to be in charge...
of the heist. I'm better than Palermo.

228
00:18:35,562 --> 00:18:37,479
Can we talk about it tomorrow...

229
00:18:37,562 --> 00:18:39,437
No, not tomorrow, now.

230
00:18:40,146 --> 00:18:42,187
- Why's he in charge?
- Let's see.

231
00:18:42,271 --> 00:18:47,437
He... is in charge because this heist
has been in development for a long time.

232
00:18:47,521 --> 00:18:50,812
He's been involved since the start.
The plan's in his head.

233
00:18:50,896 --> 00:18:51,729
And?

234
00:18:53,396 --> 00:18:57,812
I can learn it. I'm a quick learner.
"Platero's a small, soft, hairy donkey,

235
00:18:57,896 --> 00:19:00,562
so soft you could say he's all cotton,
no bones."

236
00:19:03,937 --> 00:19:07,479
- Platero and I. By Juan Ramón Jiménez.
- We know.

237
00:19:07,729 --> 00:19:11,771
I don't know if you realize,
but you're spoiling an intimate moment.

238
00:19:18,479 --> 00:19:19,437
What is it?

239
00:19:20,937 --> 00:19:21,937
Are you horny?

240
00:19:22,021 --> 00:19:23,646
I was. Yes, I was.

241
00:19:24,229 --> 00:19:25,104
Oh, were you?

242
00:19:26,229 --> 00:19:28,437
I can't really imagine you two at it.

243
00:19:28,521 --> 00:19:30,021
You'd be quite surprised.

244
00:19:30,104 --> 00:19:31,271
Please...

245
00:19:31,354 --> 00:19:32,646
Wow, really?

246
00:19:36,479 --> 00:19:37,729
Want me to stay?

247
00:19:38,937 --> 00:19:39,771
No.

248
00:19:40,854 --> 00:19:41,771
What about you?

249
00:19:41,854 --> 00:19:43,771
Why are we talking about this?

250
00:19:43,854 --> 00:19:46,062
Because I'm proposing a threesome.

251
00:19:47,354 --> 00:19:48,937
Palermo, you, and me.

252
00:19:50,271 --> 00:19:54,187
He can do the numbers and calculations,
you can do the strategy.

253
00:19:54,771 --> 00:19:58,062
But I'm the best captain
you could have in there.

254
00:19:58,562 --> 00:20:01,812
Because when the going gets tough,
I react.

255
00:20:02,604 --> 00:20:05,854
That's not something you can study.
You're born with it.

256
00:20:12,437 --> 00:20:15,854
Ladies and gentlemen...
I'm taking command.

257
00:20:19,062 --> 00:20:20,104
Let's operate.

258
00:20:22,062 --> 00:20:26,271
She's taking charge, the mastermind,
the intelligent, level-headed one.

259
00:20:26,354 --> 00:20:30,646
The crazy bitch who brought us here
and cost some of us our lives. Great.

260
00:20:30,729 --> 00:20:33,146
I'll leave you all playing doctors.

261
00:20:34,062 --> 00:20:36,812
I'm going to think about my next move.
Careful.

262
00:20:48,979 --> 00:20:50,979
It was our darkest half hour.

263
00:20:52,062 --> 00:20:53,354
In 30 minutes,

264
00:20:53,646 --> 00:20:56,479
the police had come back
with guns blazing,

265
00:20:56,562 --> 00:20:58,687
and they had us on the ropes.

266
00:20:59,729 --> 00:21:04,687
The Professor, under the trough,
was only thinking of those 30 minutes.

267
00:21:06,021 --> 00:21:08,604
If he could've called
half an hour earlier,

268
00:21:09,312 --> 00:21:10,812
Lisbon would be alive.

269
00:21:31,312 --> 00:21:33,937
- Launch stage two of Hamelin.
- All right.

270
00:21:50,021 --> 00:21:51,521
PRIVATE NUMBER

271
00:21:54,021 --> 00:21:57,271
Alicia, empathy, dialogue, and truce.

272
00:22:01,312 --> 00:22:02,229
Professor.

273
00:22:02,312 --> 00:22:05,354
Five minutes as a widower,
and you're calling other women.

274
00:22:06,604 --> 00:22:09,104
Naughty boy. You're a ladies' man.

275
00:22:09,437 --> 00:22:13,437
- Did you order her execution?
- I didn't have time. She did it herself.

276
00:22:14,604 --> 00:22:16,896
Murillo violently resisted arrest,

277
00:22:16,979 --> 00:22:20,104
opening fire on her former colleagues,
like a traitor.

278
00:22:20,604 --> 00:22:21,437
Colonel.

279
00:22:24,354 --> 00:22:26,271
The cell tower isn't in Madrid.

280
00:22:33,437 --> 00:22:35,646
It's a national highway.

281
00:22:36,187 --> 00:22:37,229
In Huelva.

282
00:22:42,437 --> 00:22:44,604
He's gotten through the cordon.

283
00:22:44,687 --> 00:22:48,312
That bastard's on the move.
42 kilometers from your position.

284
00:22:48,396 --> 00:22:50,354
You sure? It may be another trap.

285
00:22:50,437 --> 00:22:53,396
I'm sure.
The signal bounced off three cell towers.

286
00:22:53,479 --> 00:22:56,437
Highway 435, northbound. Go get him.

287
00:22:56,521 --> 00:22:57,354
OK.

288
00:22:58,937 --> 00:23:01,521
Inspector Rubio to all units.
We're leaving.

289
00:23:01,604 --> 00:23:05,229
The target is escaping
on highway 435, northbound.

290
00:23:14,229 --> 00:23:15,562
Listen, Sierra.

291
00:23:16,771 --> 00:23:19,271
Before we're out of the Bank of Spain,

292
00:23:20,021 --> 00:23:21,854
we'll destroy you.

293
00:23:23,687 --> 00:23:24,687
So boring.

294
00:23:25,562 --> 00:23:27,812
You're not an ethics professor, right?

295
00:23:27,937 --> 00:23:30,854
No, you fired two rockets
in the center of Madrid,

296
00:23:30,937 --> 00:23:33,021
and now you're on Al-Qaeda's team.

297
00:23:33,104 --> 00:23:34,771
Bada bing, bada boom.

298
00:23:35,604 --> 00:23:40,062
I'll fix my mistakes. I'm offering you
the chance to do the same with yours.

299
00:23:40,229 --> 00:23:43,979
- Nairobi...
- No way! I won't send a surgeon in.

300
00:23:45,229 --> 00:23:48,646
But I can offer access to medical care.
Bring Nairobi out.

301
00:23:48,729 --> 00:23:50,937
I've got an ambulance waiting.

302
00:23:51,021 --> 00:23:54,896
I won't put her in the hands
of a torturer who tried to kill her.

303
00:23:56,312 --> 00:23:59,437
- Face the consequences.
- I'm trembling with fear.

304
00:24:02,354 --> 00:24:05,729
As a gesture of goodwill,
I'm offering you a truce.

305
00:24:05,812 --> 00:24:07,187
For the next 48 hours.

306
00:24:07,271 --> 00:24:10,896
That way, you can assess
how serious the wound is.

307
00:24:12,021 --> 00:24:13,229
Or let her die there.

308
00:24:13,312 --> 00:24:16,229
I accept the truce,
but let me tell you something.

309
00:24:17,062 --> 00:24:18,687
Nairobi will survive...

310
00:24:19,937 --> 00:24:21,479
with or without your help.

311
00:24:25,646 --> 00:24:26,812
Good.

312
00:24:29,104 --> 00:24:30,729
Let's catch that bastard.

313
00:25:25,854 --> 00:25:28,271
And how will we get out of the epicenter?

314
00:25:30,354 --> 00:25:32,062
Following the Hamelin plan.

315
00:25:35,896 --> 00:25:36,812
Tell me more.

316
00:25:40,646 --> 00:25:45,104
Marseille will play the pipe,
and all the rats will run after him.

317
00:25:48,271 --> 00:25:51,062
We'll make them believe we've escaped.

318
00:25:52,729 --> 00:25:53,896
Exactly.

319
00:25:53,979 --> 00:25:59,854
We'll leave a false trail, but...
a believable one, backed up with evidence,

320
00:25:59,937 --> 00:26:03,646
and they'll leave the place
where we're hiding.

321
00:26:03,729 --> 00:26:08,146
Then, when the predators have gone,
we'll climb down the trees like monkeys.

322
00:26:15,771 --> 00:26:18,604
Don't you think
it'll be the most beautiful reunion?

323
00:26:59,812 --> 00:27:01,562
Why'd you call me Mr. Potato Head?

324
00:27:02,687 --> 00:27:04,187
I don't know. Your gait.

325
00:27:04,271 --> 00:27:05,687
My gait? What gait?

326
00:27:05,771 --> 00:27:08,062
Because you're... sweet.

327
00:27:08,146 --> 00:27:10,562
Are you calling me sweet or fat?

328
00:27:10,646 --> 00:27:13,229
Don't answer.
I'd rather think I'm sweet.

329
00:27:14,437 --> 00:27:16,979
You really messed things up
calling me that.

330
00:27:17,062 --> 00:27:21,896
Word got around. Now Homicide,
Internal Affairs, and the court all know.

331
00:27:21,979 --> 00:27:24,896
I didn't know about memes
until I saw the Mr. Potato Head ones.

332
00:27:24,979 --> 00:27:26,646
I'm really sorry.

333
00:27:37,437 --> 00:27:41,021
Aren't you going to ask me...
why I got involved in this?

334
00:27:46,187 --> 00:27:47,104
No.

335
00:27:48,562 --> 00:27:50,479
I know you did it for love.

336
00:27:53,437 --> 00:27:56,937
When we get to Madrid,
they'll offer you a cooperation deal.

337
00:27:57,354 --> 00:27:58,187
I know.

338
00:28:00,312 --> 00:28:03,562
Armed robbery, breach of the peace,

339
00:28:03,646 --> 00:28:06,354
assaulting an officer,
possession of weapons,

340
00:28:06,437 --> 00:28:09,479
disclosure of secrets,
belonging to an armed group,

341
00:28:09,562 --> 00:28:10,646
and abduction.

342
00:28:11,437 --> 00:28:14,479
Abduction of the hostages
and of my own daughter.

343
00:28:18,854 --> 00:28:21,146
So, no matter what deal they offer me,

344
00:28:22,062 --> 00:28:25,271
even with the most
anti-establishment prosecutor,

345
00:28:25,354 --> 00:28:27,604
I'll do at least 30 years.

346
00:28:30,229 --> 00:28:32,312
So, I'm fucked,

347
00:28:33,271 --> 00:28:34,437
Mr. Potato Head.

348
00:28:38,771 --> 00:28:42,146
The instructions you give
must be clear and concise, OK?

349
00:28:42,229 --> 00:28:44,187
How many blood units do we need?

350
00:28:44,687 --> 00:28:46,896
Have three ready at room temperature.

351
00:28:47,312 --> 00:28:48,646
How many are there?

352
00:28:51,437 --> 00:28:53,271
- Three.
- OK, go and get more.

353
00:28:53,354 --> 00:28:54,896
O negative and A negative.

354
00:28:54,979 --> 00:28:58,396
Draw enough for three operations.
Ask if anyone's a doctor.

355
00:28:58,479 --> 00:28:59,896
Bogotá, go downstairs.

356
00:28:59,979 --> 00:29:02,521
It's our only way out of here.
Get melting.

357
00:29:09,104 --> 00:29:11,021
Being in charge suits you well.

358
00:29:11,104 --> 00:29:12,646
You lost the team's trust.

359
00:29:12,729 --> 00:29:16,271
Do you know what your only way out will be
once I'm not here?

360
00:29:18,979 --> 00:29:21,312
Walking out with your hands up, praying

361
00:29:21,396 --> 00:29:25,396
that there are so many cameras outside
that they won't shoot you.

362
00:29:25,479 --> 00:29:28,979
Messieurs... au revoir.

363
00:29:29,437 --> 00:29:30,271
Bye.

364
00:29:35,479 --> 00:29:36,604
Go ahead, Doctor.

365
00:29:37,146 --> 00:29:42,062
A 15-centimeter incision
between the sixth and seventh ribs.

366
00:29:42,146 --> 00:29:43,062
Scalpel.

367
00:29:45,729 --> 00:29:50,437
This time, if anyone gets injured,
we'll be ready to save their life.

368
00:29:51,146 --> 00:29:55,187
We'll learn the protocols
for the most common gunshot wound cases.

369
00:29:55,271 --> 00:29:58,354
In the truck,
apart from what we need for the heist,

370
00:29:59,854 --> 00:30:03,812
we'll also carry medical supplies
to carry out any kind of surgery.

371
00:30:05,521 --> 00:30:08,854
Dr. Ahmed will be the brains,
but he'll be 7,000 km away.

372
00:30:08,937 --> 00:30:10,187
You'll be the hands.

373
00:30:11,021 --> 00:30:12,312
And it won't be easy.

374
00:30:13,562 --> 00:30:15,021
You can't hesitate.

375
00:30:16,479 --> 00:30:17,437
You can't fail.

376
00:30:18,687 --> 00:30:21,229
Because it won't be
a dead pig on the table.

377
00:30:26,021 --> 00:30:27,396
It'll be one of you.

378
00:30:28,729 --> 00:30:31,937
- Suction. I can't see.
- Bring the camera closer.

379
00:30:32,021 --> 00:30:35,437
Always keep the surgical area clean.

380
00:30:35,854 --> 00:30:37,271
- I can see.
- Next step?

381
00:30:37,687 --> 00:30:39,479
We need to separate the ribs.

382
00:30:40,021 --> 00:30:43,271
You may have to remove part of the lung.

383
00:30:43,354 --> 00:30:45,021
Separate the ribs? Fuck me.

384
00:30:46,146 --> 00:30:47,687
The rib spreader.

385
00:30:54,354 --> 00:30:56,354
- Is this it?
- Yes, bring it here.

386
00:31:04,521 --> 00:31:08,937
Those with blood types O negative or
A negative, raise your hands.

387
00:31:14,021 --> 00:31:17,354
Are you going to make us
check your medical records?

388
00:31:21,437 --> 00:31:24,979
Paquita.
You were a nurse's aide, weren't you?

389
00:31:25,062 --> 00:31:26,646
Yes, sir. And a midwife.

390
00:31:26,729 --> 00:31:28,021
Come with me.

391
00:31:28,104 --> 00:31:31,521
Everyone with their hand raised,
come with me now!

392
00:32:01,479 --> 00:32:02,479
Hello.

393
00:32:03,021 --> 00:32:04,229
Professor.

394
00:32:04,312 --> 00:32:06,562
- Marseille!
- Yes, it's me. Don't worry.

395
00:32:10,687 --> 00:32:12,854
- The cops aren't here.
- Where's the bull?

396
00:32:13,437 --> 00:32:16,021
- What bull?
- Help me up. I'm stiff.

397
00:32:26,312 --> 00:32:27,604
That bull?

398
00:32:28,521 --> 00:32:29,604
That bull.

399
00:32:31,271 --> 00:32:34,021
Start walking backwards
very slowly, Marseille,

400
00:32:34,979 --> 00:32:37,187
and don't break eye contact.

401
00:32:38,729 --> 00:32:40,729
Does this remind you of something?

402
00:32:41,062 --> 00:32:42,062
San Fermín?

403
00:32:44,312 --> 00:32:45,187
Italy.

404
00:32:45,271 --> 00:32:47,854
When I met you, at the wedding.

405
00:32:47,937 --> 00:32:49,646
Come on, farther back.

406
00:32:50,812 --> 00:32:53,479
Isn't the bouquet thing for single women?

407
00:32:53,896 --> 00:32:56,062
Do you see any single women here?

408
00:32:56,146 --> 00:32:58,187
You're the closest thing we have.

409
00:32:58,896 --> 00:33:01,229
Tradition says the bride has to throw it,

410
00:33:01,312 --> 00:33:03,687
and that's what I'm doing.
Farther back.

411
00:33:03,771 --> 00:33:04,896
Come on, move.

412
00:33:05,646 --> 00:33:07,646
A welder, a gay guy,

413
00:33:08,229 --> 00:33:09,896
a mute, and a librarian.

414
00:33:10,854 --> 00:33:13,062
Fucking hell, this Italian wedding...

415
00:33:13,479 --> 00:33:15,687
I'm not a mute. I'm just quiet.

416
00:33:15,771 --> 00:33:17,979
I told you, I'm not a librarian.

417
00:33:18,062 --> 00:33:20,146
Please just call me Sergio.

418
00:33:20,229 --> 00:33:23,146
Ladies, the bride's throwing the bouquet.
Focus!

419
00:33:23,229 --> 00:33:26,229
Come on, farther back, girls!
Just a bit more.

420
00:33:26,979 --> 00:33:28,062
Farther back!

421
00:33:48,729 --> 00:33:49,562
Ready?

422
00:33:54,979 --> 00:33:56,646
My little brother!

423
00:33:56,729 --> 00:33:59,521
- Bravissimo, little brother.
- Congratulations.

424
00:34:00,646 --> 00:34:03,521
Mrs. Fonollosa,
it's time for the first dance.

425
00:34:03,604 --> 00:34:07,062
- But first... a little surprise.
- What is it?

426
00:35:41,062 --> 00:35:43,854
That's what I call a choir!

427
00:35:47,604 --> 00:35:50,271
Like anyone with no sense of rhythm,

428
00:35:50,354 --> 00:35:52,271
the Professor sat at the table.

429
00:35:52,604 --> 00:35:53,937
There he wondered,

430
00:35:54,562 --> 00:35:58,229
which carries more weight: love or death?

431
00:35:58,687 --> 00:36:00,521
Life carries the most weight.

432
00:36:01,604 --> 00:36:02,562
Life.

433
00:36:04,021 --> 00:36:06,854
Then there's me.
Dying but still getting married.

434
00:36:09,562 --> 00:36:11,729
Isn't it a beautiful contradiction?

435
00:36:16,146 --> 00:36:17,729
Does she know you're sick?

436
00:36:18,062 --> 00:36:19,771
Of course she does.

437
00:36:22,521 --> 00:36:23,646
She's very smart.

438
00:36:26,146 --> 00:36:28,937
And if you look on the bright side,
we're lucky.

439
00:36:30,354 --> 00:36:32,812
Most people don't know
when their time will come.

440
00:36:33,521 --> 00:36:36,521
We get to stay
in the honeymoon period forever.

441
00:36:39,437 --> 00:36:42,896
People buy a bottle of champagne
for a special occasion

442
00:36:42,979 --> 00:36:44,479
and go back to their routines.

443
00:36:44,562 --> 00:36:49,021
Tatiana and I will live life to the limit
with a barrel of French champagne.

444
00:36:57,146 --> 00:37:00,396
Death can be
the best opportunity of your life, Sergio.

445
00:37:19,104 --> 00:37:20,312
Sad, Professor?

446
00:37:24,229 --> 00:37:27,437
If you want,
you can talk to me about feelings.

447
00:37:28,396 --> 00:37:30,021
Should I put some music on?

448
00:37:31,146 --> 00:37:33,146
Music cheers you up.

449
00:37:43,729 --> 00:37:45,896
The car's stolen. The music isn't mine.

450
00:37:45,979 --> 00:37:48,646
It doesn't matter, Marseille.
Keep driving.

451
00:38:07,979 --> 00:38:09,021
Excuse me.

452
00:38:10,187 --> 00:38:11,729
Who is the blood for?

453
00:38:12,521 --> 00:38:14,479
Why the fuck do you care?

454
00:38:14,562 --> 00:38:18,521
Two of you went upstairs with the bear,
but only one of you is here.

455
00:38:18,604 --> 00:38:20,812
Then you already know who it's for.

456
00:38:21,437 --> 00:38:22,687
Now let's stay quiet.

457
00:38:31,271 --> 00:38:32,604
- Denver.
- What?

458
00:38:35,187 --> 00:38:36,021
Thank you.

459
00:38:37,062 --> 00:38:40,729
- What for?
- I came in just to tell you in person.

460
00:38:42,937 --> 00:38:45,854
I know we didn't start off
on the right foot,

461
00:38:45,937 --> 00:38:49,896
but what matters
is that you've raised my son.

462
00:38:49,979 --> 00:38:53,021
- Thank you.
- What are you talking about, jerk?

463
00:38:57,437 --> 00:38:59,729
That'll do, Paquita. Thank you.

464
00:39:02,271 --> 00:39:04,937
At your age and with all that money...

465
00:39:07,021 --> 00:39:09,979
changing diapers
probably wasn't part of your plan.

466
00:39:10,062 --> 00:39:11,312
That does you credit.

467
00:39:11,396 --> 00:39:13,354
Because it takes a real man

468
00:39:13,437 --> 00:39:17,604
to look after a kid who was born
from another man's sperm.

469
00:39:17,687 --> 00:39:19,187
Look, freak.

470
00:39:20,021 --> 00:39:21,646
Be quiet. Don't rile me up,

471
00:39:21,729 --> 00:39:23,896
or you'll be eating my fist
till Christmas.

472
00:39:24,854 --> 00:39:27,729
He isn't. He's not A negative.

473
00:39:27,812 --> 00:39:29,312
Arturo is A positive.

474
00:39:30,521 --> 00:39:31,771
What were you doing?

475
00:39:33,021 --> 00:39:35,229
What were you doing?
I tested them by chance.

476
00:39:35,312 --> 00:39:36,771
We could've killed her.

477
00:39:39,437 --> 00:39:40,479
I'm sorry.

478
00:39:40,562 --> 00:39:43,604
Sorry. Shit, I was wrong.
I didn't do it on purpose.

479
00:39:43,687 --> 00:39:47,479
I know I'm A something. I didn't know
if it was positive or negative.

480
00:39:47,562 --> 00:39:49,979
It's not something you use every day.
I'm sorry.

481
00:39:50,062 --> 00:39:52,187
You're confused now, is that it?

482
00:39:56,812 --> 00:39:59,312
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?

483
00:39:59,646 --> 00:40:01,562
Maybe he really was confused.

484
00:40:03,354 --> 00:40:06,896
- Help him, for Christ's sake!
- Get up. He's OK. Get up.

485
00:40:07,354 --> 00:40:10,312
You can't go around
punching people like that.

486
00:40:10,396 --> 00:40:15,187
- It's enough that they're trapped here.
- It's over. He's OK. I'm sorry.

487
00:40:15,896 --> 00:40:18,437
It's OK.

488
00:40:19,604 --> 00:40:20,437
Besides...

489
00:40:23,729 --> 00:40:26,187
I know exactly why you're so pissed off.

490
00:40:26,271 --> 00:40:28,479
- Why?
- I get it.

491
00:40:28,562 --> 00:40:31,187
Mónica told you about the bathroom,
right?

492
00:40:31,271 --> 00:40:32,354
What bathroom?

493
00:40:33,562 --> 00:40:35,937
What bathroom is he talking about?

494
00:40:36,021 --> 00:40:39,021
I apologize. For Christ's sake, I'm sorry.

495
00:40:39,104 --> 00:40:41,271
I don't know what I was thinking.

496
00:40:41,354 --> 00:40:44,771
I hadn't seen her or had her close
for such a long time...

497
00:40:44,854 --> 00:40:46,896
I don't know, I misread the signs.

498
00:40:46,979 --> 00:40:48,896
And she told me...

499
00:40:49,396 --> 00:40:52,521
that we could meet somewhere
so I could see my kid.

500
00:40:52,604 --> 00:40:55,354
One thing led to another,
and I went for it.

501
00:40:55,437 --> 00:40:56,646
He went for what?

502
00:40:57,229 --> 00:41:00,062
- What did he go for?
- Denver, nothing happened.

503
00:41:00,146 --> 00:41:02,479
Let it go.

504
00:41:03,479 --> 00:41:06,812
Were you going to meet this jerk
to show him our son?

505
00:41:06,896 --> 00:41:10,187
He confused me, saying he was his father.
He was upset...

506
00:41:10,271 --> 00:41:13,521
OK, but... what did he go for?
I don't get it.

507
00:41:13,604 --> 00:41:17,354
It wasn't her fault. 
Leave her out of it. I'm the one to blame.

508
00:41:17,437 --> 00:41:20,146
We hugged... I got aroused...

509
00:41:20,229 --> 00:41:21,687
- I held her...
- Shut up!

510
00:41:22,687 --> 00:41:23,604
Is that true?

511
00:41:25,854 --> 00:41:30,354
Did this son of a bitch
rub himself against you... with a hard-on?

512
00:41:30,437 --> 00:41:33,646
I pushed him off right away with the gun.

513
00:41:34,771 --> 00:41:37,187
Listen to me. I fought back, Denver.

514
00:41:38,187 --> 00:41:39,437
So it's true.

515
00:41:45,937 --> 00:41:47,771
Stop, Denver!

516
00:41:50,271 --> 00:41:53,937
Stop, you're going to kill him,
Denver! Stop!

517
00:42:14,312 --> 00:42:15,854
What the fuck is this?

518
00:42:18,437 --> 00:42:21,104
What the fuck do you have inside of you?

519
00:42:21,854 --> 00:42:23,312
All that rage...

520
00:42:25,437 --> 00:42:27,604
All that violence...

521
00:42:27,687 --> 00:42:30,396
You shot a hostage.

522
00:42:31,729 --> 00:42:33,312
And now you beat him up...

523
00:42:34,937 --> 00:42:36,021
like a maniac.

524
00:42:37,021 --> 00:42:37,979
I can't...

525
00:42:39,479 --> 00:42:44,521
I don't know what your trauma is
or where it came from,

526
00:42:44,604 --> 00:42:46,437
but I can't, Denver.

527
00:42:49,146 --> 00:42:51,104
I can't, and I don't want...

528
00:42:52,271 --> 00:42:55,521
I don't want my son...

529
00:42:56,187 --> 00:42:59,396
to feel that rage you carry inside.

530
00:43:01,229 --> 00:43:02,479
I don't want that.

531
00:43:20,354 --> 00:43:21,812
Correct. Continue.

532
00:43:29,687 --> 00:43:31,354
- Good morning.
- Good morning.

533
00:43:31,812 --> 00:43:34,354
- Is it him?
- The car rolled several times.

534
00:43:34,437 --> 00:43:37,687
There are traces of blood and no driver.
It must be him.

535
00:43:37,771 --> 00:43:39,771
Or a dealer, or someone undocumented...

536
00:43:39,854 --> 00:43:42,187
The car was stolen just hours ago
in Salvatierra,

537
00:43:42,271 --> 00:43:45,229
the town closest
to where we found Murillo.

538
00:43:45,729 --> 00:43:47,062
And they climb trees.

539
00:43:48,271 --> 00:43:49,104
I see.

540
00:43:50,604 --> 00:43:51,812
Excuse me.

541
00:43:58,146 --> 00:43:59,896
- Yes, Colonel?
- Was it him?

542
00:44:00,479 --> 00:44:03,812
I think so. He can't be far.
He's lost a lot of blood.

543
00:44:03,896 --> 00:44:07,229
Let Suárez deal with it.
I need you here with Murillo.

544
00:44:07,312 --> 00:44:10,146
Bring her to Madrid.
That's more important. OK?

545
00:44:10,229 --> 00:44:12,521
- Understood.
- Get Suárez to send units

546
00:44:12,604 --> 00:44:14,604
to all the hospitals in the area,

547
00:44:14,687 --> 00:44:17,854
to every vet,
to every nun with a first aid kit.

548
00:44:18,771 --> 00:44:23,271
I want everyone alert. If we lose him,
it'd better be because he's dead.

549
00:44:29,854 --> 00:44:30,979
Pamuk.

550
00:44:36,146 --> 00:44:36,979
What?

551
00:44:37,521 --> 00:44:39,062
My dog was called Pamuk.

552
00:44:39,896 --> 00:44:43,896
Pamuk was with me during the war.
I know how you feel.

553
00:44:43,979 --> 00:44:49,229
Are you making some kind of metaphor
with your dead dog and my partner?

554
00:44:49,312 --> 00:44:50,562
She was a female dog.

555
00:44:52,729 --> 00:44:57,104
After the war, all my friends were dead.

556
00:44:58,021 --> 00:45:02,021
And I... spent my nights in a bar.

557
00:45:02,521 --> 00:45:04,729
One day, another day...

558
00:45:05,771 --> 00:45:08,937
Pamuk was always outside waiting.

559
00:45:10,937 --> 00:45:14,312
Did you also fall in love
only to have her killed in front of you?

560
00:45:17,104 --> 00:45:17,937
Yes.

561
00:45:23,771 --> 00:45:25,229
What happened to Pamuk?

562
00:45:29,354 --> 00:45:33,146
The boys from the village...
liked to play war.

563
00:45:34,771 --> 00:45:36,646
After a while,

564
00:45:37,229 --> 00:45:41,479
without an enemy,
they got bored of playing war.

565
00:45:42,479 --> 00:45:45,604
One day... they found some stones.

566
00:45:47,479 --> 00:45:49,479
They broke bottles.

567
00:45:51,896 --> 00:45:55,146
And they said Pamuk was the enemy.

568
00:45:59,937 --> 00:46:00,854
I'm sorry.

569
00:46:05,271 --> 00:46:06,937
She was a good dog.

570
00:46:13,896 --> 00:46:17,104
Marseille, can you stop a minute?
I need to... urinate.

571
00:47:45,521 --> 00:47:46,562
Good piss?

572
00:47:51,146 --> 00:47:53,271
Peeing is a relief sometimes.

573
00:48:03,771 --> 00:48:08,146
However great the pain,
we could not lose sight of one thing.

574
00:48:09,021 --> 00:48:13,687
Our lives depended on what was happening
48 meters below the ground.

575
00:48:13,896 --> 00:48:15,979
The plan had a very simple rule:

576
00:48:17,021 --> 00:48:20,812
either we got all the gold out of there,
or we were all dead.

577
00:48:22,271 --> 00:48:25,937
No matter what was going on above,
we had to get the gold out.

578
00:48:26,187 --> 00:48:30,021
No matter what was going on above,
we had to get the gold out.

579
00:48:34,646 --> 00:48:37,437
Move the lung.
I want to see the lower part.

580
00:48:37,521 --> 00:48:38,479
Okay.

581
00:48:39,271 --> 00:48:40,562
Use your hand.

582
00:48:44,646 --> 00:48:45,479
Colonel!

583
00:48:48,229 --> 00:48:50,937
There's an increased flow
of electromagnetic signals

584
00:48:51,021 --> 00:48:52,771
going in and out of the bank.

585
00:48:52,854 --> 00:48:57,271
- Martínez, in layman's terms.
- They're communicating with the outside.

586
00:49:02,646 --> 00:49:05,229
Move the image closer. OK.

587
00:49:05,687 --> 00:49:08,562
OK, we need to remove
the lower part of the lung.

588
00:49:08,687 --> 00:49:10,812
Risk of infection and necrosis.

589
00:49:10,896 --> 00:49:12,021
It could kill her.

590
00:49:12,104 --> 00:49:14,687
How are we gonna cut
part of her lung out?

591
00:49:15,062 --> 00:49:17,104
- Do you have an electric scalpel?
- Yes.

592
00:49:17,187 --> 00:49:20,812
- From its size, I'd say it's a video call.
- Can we watch it?

593
00:49:21,146 --> 00:49:25,937
The signal is encrypted. I'd say
it's going through a Kazakh satellite...

594
00:49:27,854 --> 00:49:31,521
then probably through the deep web.
It's impossible to be sure.

595
00:49:34,146 --> 00:49:35,687
Let's take it down, then.

596
00:49:38,187 --> 00:49:40,396
Let's do it. No time to waste.

597
00:49:40,479 --> 00:49:43,187
Listen and follow my instructions closely.

598
00:49:44,146 --> 00:49:47,104
- We'll go slowly. Understood?
- Understood.

599
00:49:47,187 --> 00:49:51,437
Colonel... if it were
a Spanish phone company satellite,

600
00:49:51,521 --> 00:49:55,187
- we'd request a jam...
- Don't tell me what we can't do.

601
00:49:55,271 --> 00:49:57,437
I told you to cut off the damn call.

602
00:49:57,521 --> 00:50:00,771
If you cut a vein, we stop the scalpel

603
00:50:00,854 --> 00:50:04,021
- and close it with Kocher forceps.
- Understood.

604
00:50:04,104 --> 00:50:06,646
We'd have to jam the signals in the area,

605
00:50:06,729 --> 00:50:09,854
take down the Internet
and anything using satellite.

606
00:50:09,937 --> 00:50:13,229
Like in Egypt in 2011. Do it.

607
00:50:14,521 --> 00:50:16,604
Let's make the first incision.

608
00:50:16,687 --> 00:50:18,854
- See the lingula?
- What's that?

609
00:50:18,937 --> 00:50:20,437
Lower part...

610
00:50:22,896 --> 00:50:24,771
- What?
- You've gotta be kidding.

611
00:50:28,979 --> 00:50:29,812
What's wrong?

612
00:50:33,021 --> 00:50:34,771
- There's no return signal.
- What?

613
00:50:34,854 --> 00:50:35,937
Fuck!

614
00:50:38,812 --> 00:50:41,229
There's no signal. Everything is down.

615
00:50:42,104 --> 00:50:43,104
What do we do?

616
00:50:43,187 --> 00:50:45,979
Blood pressure is dropping.
We're losing her.

617
00:50:46,062 --> 00:50:47,104
No.

618
00:50:47,771 --> 00:50:49,646
No, fuck!

