MADRID, 77 DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
♪ Who's that, who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat? ♪
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ Who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat now? ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat? ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat now? ♪
He's here.
Come on! We're 15 minutes late.
We gotta hurry.
- Gemma, please.
- Just the brows.
Why mess with perfection, honey?
Hey!
♪ You wanna hear that wildcat
Cruel cat, cool cat growl ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat? ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat now? ♪
(CHEERING)
♪ Who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat now? ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat? ♪
♪ Who's that, who's that
Who's that cool cat now? ♪
Who's that cool cat now? Yeah ♪
(CROWD CHEERS)
For the last two and a half years,
many of you called me a hero.
- MAN: Hero!
- WOMAN: Hero!
- You're a hero!
- No, no, no. Make no mistake.
I'm no hero. I'm just an ordinary man.
A man had enough courage
to refuse to kneel
before a group of terrorists.
(CHEERING)
Let me tell you.
That's why I can be here today.
My dignity remains intact.
Meanwhile, those rats
are still hiding somewhere in their holes.
GUNA YALA ARCHIPELAGO
♪ Have you seen the tools
Hanging in the dark ♪
- (SHOUTS IN KUNA)
- (YELLS)
(LAUGHS)
♪ They're glowing in the dark ♪
♪ I've been working in the crib
'Til they making tunes ♪
(LAUGHING AND SHOUTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
There are some people who find
those terrorists charming and likable.
(AUDIENCE BOOS)
Yeah, believe me.
They think they're funny.
And I ask myself,
"Is it funny to be a criminal?"
- AUDIENCE: No!
- ARTURO: No!
Does a terrorist deserve
to be considered a hero?
AUDIENCE: No!
Is the so-called Professor
some kind of Robin Hood?
- AUDIENCE: No!
- No! Helsinki…
the monster from the Balkans.
For 24 hours straight,
this bum had a freaking bomb
strapped to my body.
- Can he be anyone's idol?
- AUDIENCE: No!
- ARTURO: No!
- MAN: No, never.
I can only hope
that he feels guilty
and this weighs on his conscious
for the rest of his miserable life.
(UPBEAT FOLK MUSIC PLAYS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
- (MUSIC ENDS)
- (AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
I attacked the so-called Denver
with a pair of blunt scissors. (CHUCKLES)
(AUDIENCE CHUCKLES)
He had an M16.
Suicidal?
Maybe, but thanks to that,
the first hostages could escape.
In exchange, he took what I loved most.
Mónica Gaztambide.
- WOMAN: Forget her!
- My mistress!
Because I've made mistakes along the way.
Yeah, I admit that I've been unfaithful.
I've also been selfish and despicable.
And as a result,
I lost absolutely everything in my life.
These days, when I wake up in the morning,
my only thought is
"What happened to my poor son?"
- (HORN HONKS)
- (MAN SHOUTS)
(LAUGHS)
(GIGGLES)
You know, that looks like shit
but I bet it's fresh.
Whoa! Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
(LAUGHS)
Love you, love you, love you!
You know, life…
Life is lost if you stop making decisions.
We get carried away
by that unstoppable inertia.
I was a hostage.
But at some point…
at some point,
we all become hostages to something.
AUDIENCE: Yes.
And when you accept that,
that's when you make your mind up.
- AUDIENCE: Yes!
- I make my own decisions!
I face my problems! Everyone!
EVERYONE: I make my own decisions!
I face my problems!
I make my own decisions!
ARTURO: Everyone, you got it!
AUDIENCE: I face my problems!
I make up my own decisions!
I face my problems!
GUNA YALA ARCHIPELAGO, PELICAN ISLAND
77 DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYS)
TOKYO: My name is Tokyo.
Remember me?
This is the Caribbean.
For over two years,
my life has been like a romantic movie.
We fish our own food.
Naked and wild.
But with some luxury.
(SIGHS)
But all of this is about to be fucked
because of a decision
that will enter my mind right now.
TOKYO: We've been here over two years.
RIO: Two years in paradise.
Paradise is wonderful
when your life is dull
and full of traffic and
as an escape every now and then.
You need a change of scenery, right?
And that doesn't include me,
does it?
(SIGHS)
This lasted a while. (CHUCKLES)
Rio…
I need to get out of here.
I need noise.
I need people.
To not know where I'll be tomorrow.
I understand.
I think I'll leave here too. (CHUCKLES)
An adventure will do us both good.
I'm not sure how long I'll be gone.
Better to think it's forever.
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKING IN KUNA)
RIO: Tokyo!
Tokyo!
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYS)
If you wanna talk.
It's a satellite phone. I bought it
off the black market with Helsinki.
- Rio…
- It's unregistered.
Turn it on at 6:00 p.m. every three days.
If one of us wants to talk,
just turn it on for five minutes
and then turn it off if I don't answer.
Okay?
My number's on the back.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Go on, it's gonna get dark soon.
Party time?
Party time!
(ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC PLAYS)
TOKYO: I can behave like a proper girl
for a long time.
But, little by little, the naughty girl
inside of me starts to take over.
Until I simply explode.
And when I transform into a satellite,
three days fly by.
PANAMA
Days pass so quickly,
you end up forgetting about
the only important thing you have to do.
(SALSA BAND PLAYING)
EUROPOL, THE HAGUE
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS)
MAN: The terminal you are trying to reach
is out of satellite…
Tokyo, turn on the phone…
Come on Tokyo, turn it on. Shit.
(LINE RINGS)
(CHEERING AND SHOUTING)
Fuck!
(MUSIC MUFFLES AND FADES)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Unidentified terminal
connecting with Aníbal Cortés.
TOKYO: Rio's position traveled from
the Guna Yala Islands in the Caribbean,
to Europol in one second.
(PHONE RINGING)
TOKYO: From Europol to the National
Center of Intelligence in 50 seconds.
Hello?
TOKYO: Less than a minute later,
Prieto was awake.
- Prieto.
- MAN 1: Colonel.
We've located Aníbal Cortés
on an island in Panama.
Inform the police in Panama now!
(ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
(SIRENS WAILING)
TOKYO: Mine reached them even faster.
Phones have a tap.
TOKYO: The phone was safe,
but the Libyan seller wasn't.
PILOT: Eagle to Fox 1, we're taking off.
Hello, Rio.
That's her.
Hey, Tokyo.
Confirmed. It's Tokyo.
Police is on the way.
(SIRENS WAILING)
I'm sorry for the wait.
How are you?
Well, I'm here. Three days
of doing nothing on this fucking island.
- MAN 1: Police are in Cinta Costera.
- Let's go.
(SIRENS WAILING)
RIO: I can't take it anymore.
I can't stand the Gunas' food.
Shit, in all my life, I only ate pizzas
and burgers, fries and packs of hot dogs…
That's what I fucking wanna eat.
I don't wanna be here
with these people anymore.
You can't get a laugh out of them.
(SIRENS WAILING)
MAN 1: Police are in
the Chorrillo neighborhood.
Come on, come on, come on!
(SIRENS WAILING)
I wanna party with you
to chunda chunda.
And we get wasted and our pupils
look like fucking raccoons'.
- That's what I want, Tokyo, fuck!
- (LAUGHS)
Even for just one date.
Ah, you wanna go on a date?
Of course I wanna go on a date.
Then why don't you pick a city?
And I'll be there.
Rio de Janeiro.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
Shit.
What?
Patrol boats.
Patrol boats!
(SUSPENSEFUL ACTION MUSIC PLAYS)
Run, Tokyo! They found us.
- We're about to reach the plaza.
- Okay.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Alpha team, move through the alley.
Go back. Surround the building.
Alpha team,
through the Pedro Barrio passage.
- OFFICER 1: We're inside.
- OFFICER 2: Move! Move!
(PANTS)
(SIGHS)
PILOT: Eagle to Fox 1,
we can't see the target.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
OFFICER 1: Clear.
MAN 2: Cubeta, go through
Bodegón alley. It's a shortcut.
Come on, come on, come on!
Listen Cubeta, she's in the courtyard.
We are surrounding her, Colonel.
I got you now, bitch! I got you!
- OFFICER 2: Bravo 2 in position.
- OFFICER 3: Bravo 1 in position.
(OFFICER OVER MEGAPHONE) Drop the weapon!
We have you surrounded. Drop it!
Drop your gun. Drop it!
(PANTING)
OFFICERS: Go, go!
(YELLING)
- OFFICER 1: Lower your weapons!
- OFFICER 2: Easy. Guns down.
Negative. It's not her.
- Shit!
- Fucking bitch.
(DOG PANTS)
(MUSIC BUILDS)
(MUSIC ENDS)
(PANTING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
That way, that way!
Go, go, go!
Let's go, come on!
TOKYO: Guilty.
Guilty.
That's how I felt
while thinking about every moment
of happiness I'd spent with Rio…
since we got our freedom.
PORTUGAL'S MARITIME BORDER
THREE YEARS UNTIL D-DAY
(SHIP HORNS BLOW)
Everyone.
Two hundred nautical miles.
We just entered international waters.
(EVERYONE CHEERS AND SHOUTS)
- NAIROBI: Yes! We did it, Helsi!
- (HELSINKI AND NAIRIBI LAUGH)
NAIROBI: Yes, that's it! (SHOUTS)
Professor!
(NAIROBI SHOUTS AND LAUGHS)
RIO: Come on!
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYS)
Rich!
(EVERYONE LAUGHS AND CHEERS)
(CLAPS) Finish the champagne.
We have some new concepts to look at.
Professor…
Come on.
We have ten fucking billion now.
You think I'm gonna go back to class?
We've escaped,
but now comes the most difficult part.
Managing to survive.
Don't open them yet.
Wait until you're alone.
What's this?
Safe houses. Every couple has their own.
I gather you and Helsinki
will stay together.
Huh?
(LAUGHS)
- Why the hell not. (CHUCKLES)
- Great.
You'll be safe,
under protection and surveillance.
Interpol won't be able to do anything.
Denver, not now.
What did I do?
I said open them when you're on your own.
I'm the only one who should know
where you are at every moment.
What are those numbers?
AUSTRALIA, AFRICA, ASIA, LATIN AMERICA
Each number corresponds to a continent.
A continent where you could go
in case you need help.
So memorize them.
Now.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
COLOMBIA, 72 DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYS)
PROFESSOR: These are phone numbers.
In case of an emergency,
dial the number that matches your location
and you'll be connected to a transporter.
These transporters are inactive units
that will bring you to me
safely.
MAN: Yes?
My name is Tokyo,
I'm looking for my transporter.
Aren't you going with them?
Yeah, I'm going.
(SHIP ENGINES HUM)
(SHIP CREAKS)
TOKYO: And you?
PROFESSOR: Me?
Where are you going?
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS)
I hope the day never comes
when you need to find out.
TOKYO: But the day came.
THAILAND, 62 DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
TOKYO: I imagine in every paradise,
the same thing happens.
In the end, someone always bites the apple
and everything goes to shit.
Come on.
(HORN HONKS)
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETS)
Enter the temple and they'll come for you.
(CEREMONIAL MUSIC PLAYS)
TOKYO: It took me 11 days to reach
the temple where my transporter left me.
After an oil tanker, two cargo planes
and who knows how many buses…
PROFESSOR: Miss Tokyo.
…my guardian angel appeared.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
Welcome to Thailand.
(CRIES AND LAUGHS)
I don't think
I've ever been so happy to see someone.
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYS)
Professor…
Have you heard from Rio?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE STARTS)
RAQUEL: Mama!
Mama!
PALAWAN, 62 DAYS UNTIL D-DAY
(LAUGHS)
Mom, are you okay? You good?
Are you cold?
(LAUGHS)
Come out of the water. Okay?
Come on. Let's get out. Okay?
Yes, yes.
- PAULA: Mommy, what happened?
- It's okay. Grandma's fine.
Adorable.
Mom went into the water again
with her clothes on.
I fell in the water. (CHUCKLES)
Raquel.
My love, how did your trip go?
Pack your bags.
But why?
Tokyo's here.
Raquel, Raquel…
Until we find out what happened,
it's best if you leave
with your daughter and mother to Mindanao.
Even though this place is not safe,
you're gonna stay?
It's for the best.
Because you have to solve Tokyo's problem.
On your own.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS)
If you are thinking of hiding me from her,
you need to think of a better plan.
(INSTRUMENTAL ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
Hey.
- Why is this bitch here?
- Calm down. She's one of us now.
Let's say I changed.
You know who changes sides in wars?
- Fucking traitors.
- Tokyo.
- Only absolute shit.
You know what happens to those rats?
They change sides once, twice,
a hundred million times.
- Tokyo, please.
- She'll turn against you.
She's gonna betray you
like she betrayed them.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Oh no?
How do you know? Tell me!
- I know.
- TOKYO: Yeah?
- I have absolute certainty.
- "Absolute certainty"?
You think with your dick now?
(MUSIC ENDS)
If the Professor says
I'm one of you, then I am.
Is that clear?
Oh, tough bitch.
We won't get along like that, Inspector.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS AGAIN)
Lisbon.
My name is Lisbon.
Well, now, after that very…
endearing reunion, let's go have some tea.
Please.
OFFICER 1: Hands up! Get down!
I told you to get down!
OFFICER 2: Get down!
Hands behind your back!
- OFFICER 3: Don't move!
- (YELLS)
PROFESSOR: How long ago was that?
Eleven days.
PROFESSOR: Where did you get
the satellite phones?
When we split into two ships,
we went to Casablanca for 24 hours.
We got them off the black market.
From a Libyan.
- Casablanca…
- They weren't registered.
Well, it looks like they were.
Not only that…
That person reported you.
And most likely got paid
for the information.
Professor…
Are you positive that Rio was caught?
If not, he would have called
his transporter like you did.
No one's published anything.
It's been 11 days already.
It's the biggest news
the government could release.
Why would they keep it a secret?
It's a mother fucking bombshell. And…
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
How long can they keep him incommunicado?
Seventy-two hours.
Where do they have him?
They're not torturing him.
I don't know, Tokyo. I don't know.
You can bet he's being tortured.
All democratic countries
have a backyard to play dirty
if things get ugly.
And we've made things very ugly.
Well, you have.
They can't torture him.
It's the 21st century.
Of course they can.
At a height of 35,000 feet
above jurisdiction,
on CIA flights or in Guantanamo…
Even Spain organized a terrorist commando.
Tokyo, are you fucking serious?
Professor.
We need to get Rio out.
Are you listening?
We need to rescue Rio.
Did anyone else buy phones?
Yeah, Helsinki.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
We need to get the gang back.
Professor!
Tell me you're gonna save Rio.
And how, Tokyo?
We don't even know what country,
prison or goddamn hole he's in right now.
We know nothing.
Nothing.
(TREMBLES)
(BONE SNAPS)
(SCREAMS)
- (ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
- (DENVER LAUGHS)
Professor!
Professor! (LAUGHS)
I'm happy to see you. Very happy.
- Miss Gaztambide.
- You can call her "Mrs."
We got married.
A Balinese ceremony on an elephant.
(IMITATES ELECTRONIC MUSIC AND LAUGHS)
Tokyo!
Tokyo! (LAUGHS)
(CHANTS) Tokyo! Tokyo!
TOKYO: Come here.
(LAUGHS)
♪ Hidden right this way
Twist of fate, hope and tragedy ♪
♪ I have lived a most certain stance ♪
HELSINKI: Professor!
(LAUGHS)
Professor!
Slow down, Helsinki!
Slow down! What are you, nuts?
- Helsinki!
- (SCREAMING)
♪ They broke 'til they come down
I'm never gonna let go ♪
♪ No, no ♪
(LAUGHS)
You fucking idiot!
Oh, my dress!
NAIROBI: What's up?
You gonna hug me or what?
- Cheers to the baby.
- Be quiet or the baby will wake up.
Say it with an Argentinian accent.
(IN ARGENTINEAN ACCENT)
Che, boludo. Congratulations.
(LAUGHS)
That is the worst Argentinian accent
I've heard in my life.
- Your house is beautiful.
- DENVER: It feels like heaven here.
- And Rio?
- DENVER: He knows it.
Rio isn't coming.
He was arrested.
When?
17 days ago on an island in the Caribbean.
It hasn't been made public yet.
He's in some shit hole being tortured.
How did they find him?
He was using a satellite phone.
Was he in trouble?
No.
(SIGHS) There were rules.
No Europe.
No access to phones.
What the fuck are we doing here?
You're here for safety reasons.
What safety reasons?
Rio didn't know where we were.
TOKYO: Guys…
we have to help him.
Come on, come on, come on.
What the fuck are we doing here?
Are you actually thinking
we're gonna rescue Rio?
Yes, Denver.
That's what I'm thinking.
(BANGS TABLE)
(SIGHS)
Mother fucker.
You made me cross the world
with a small baby to tell me this shit?
- Are you smoking opium, Professor?
- Denver, sit down.
What do you think this is? A video game?
- You're not my fucking boss!
- Sit down.
You owe me this fucking life!
Do you understand that?!
You owe me all of this.
That fucking backyard.
Even that fucking sea
because you can't bring my father back.
Do you get that?
I have a son.
I fucking swear I'm not gonna let him
suffer as much as I did.
Go and ask him
if he wants his father's body
to be full of bullets.
- Ask him.
- Denver.
They have him in a bathtub
with a bag over his head.
- Do you understand?
- I am sorry but that's his problem.
PROFESSOR: That face
you're looking at right now
is the same face your dad was looking at
while you were trying to open the tunnel.
She didn't leave his side for a second.
Tokyo was there.
Rio made a mistake.
You also made mistakes.
You took your father up to the roof.
You two could've been killed.
But the gang was there.
Helsinki, you took the car
to the scrapyard, but didn't crush it.
We fixed it.
The gang was there.
You were late to stop the machines,
Nairobi.
And the police came in.
You escaped through the tunnel
because Berlin…
stayed there to hold them back.
He gave us the seconds we needed.
The gang was there.
The one who isn't here…
is Berlin…
and Oslo…
and Moscow.
What the fuck?
She's one of us.
I made a mistake.
I lost control.
The gang was there.
Now Rio's made a mistake
like the rest of us.
I can't ask you to feel what I feel, but…
But I really feel responsible
that some
son of a bitch
is giving him electric shocks
as he hangs from his ankles.
(SIGHS)
I'm going!
Not alone, Nairobi.
Because if you're going, I'm going too.
Here we fucking go.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
TOKYO: How will we rescue Rio?
PROFESSOR: With a robbery.
That's what we're good at.
TOKYO: Rescue him with a robbery?
PROFESSOR: We will begin
with a robbery.
TOKYO: But…
But actually we're gonna
defy the establishment.
This time, we won't be those guys
who take hostages to make their own money.
We'll be the ones who take a stand.
The ones who say, "Enough is enough."
What they're doing to Rio
is a declaration of war.
And we're the resistance.
No?
TOKYO: What are we gonna rob?
The gold.
Gold?
Not just gold.
The gold.
The only gold that matters.
The National Reserve at the Bank of Spain.
Isn't that gonna be a big mess?
Never been a bigger one.
You just thought of this now,
while watching the sunrise?
PROFESSOR: No, it's not my plan.
TOKYO: Your father's?
("BELLA CIAO" PLAYS)
PROFESSOR: No, not my father's.
FLORENCE, FIVE YEARS UNTIL D-DAY
(CHURCH BELLS RING)
PROFESSOR: Andrés.
(UPBEAT ITALIAN MUSIC PLAYS)
(LAUGHS) Little brother.
(CHUCKLES)
(IN ITALIAN) Welcome to Italy.
(IN ENGLISH) A country
full of art and class…
where everyone dresses with style.
Unlike you.
You look like a salesman.
Come with me. (CHUCKLES)
Off to my humble abode.
I have so many things I wanna tell you.
This is your home?
"The abode in the country"?
You begin by looking for something
with two bathrooms and a garden,
and you end up renovating a monastery.
- I know how to break into the Royal Mint.
- Through the front door?
The back.
On the truck with the currency paper.
Andrés, there's people here.
Relax, we don't bother each other.
They're the perfect neighbors.
- PROFESSOR: They're monks.
- Cistercians.
They live on one wing
and we're on the other.
Besides, they're sworn to silence.
They've taken a vow of silence,
not at gunpoint or before a judge,
but before God Almighty.
Makes things much more interesting, right?
PROFESSOR: And…
um… what did you tell them?
BERLIN: That I'm an intellectual
in need of austerity and solitude,
so I can write a treatise
on theological philosophy.
And they believed you?
I also paid for the renovations
so they didn't have to turn
this beautiful place into a hotel.
They don't need much. They love me.
Sometimes I sing
Gregorian chants with them.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- BERLIN: Watch your head.
Andrés, do you sleep in a cell?
Well, I intended to, but I fell in love…
with this chapel.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
Look at this beauty.
(CELESTIAL MUSIC PLAYS)
Sergio, my dear friend. How are you?
Long time no see. Come here.
What is this?
Do you remember that old plan
to steal gold from the Bank of Spain?
It's remarkable. We can obtain up to
90 tons of gold from the inside there.
We found a way to do it
and I think you're gonna love it.
It's the most brilliant civil engineering
since the Panama Canal. I guarantee it.
No. Wait a minute. Wait.
I've told you a million times.
You can get the gold, but, Andrés,
there's no way you'll leave
the Bank of Spain alive.
Well, that's just a small detail.
The gold comes first.
- Then the people, right Andrés?
- That's right.
- What do you mean "small detail"?
- Let's think about all that later.
Brother, do you notice
something different about me?
- No.
- I have to tell you about a woman. Come.
Take a look.
My sweetheart.
May I present Tatiana.
She's very beautiful.
She's madly in love with me.
- (CHUCKLES)
- She's a goddess.
BERLIN: I think he's gonna like her.
TOKYO: What the Professor never imagined
was that one day
he would have to make
that suicidal plan his own.
(ROCK VERSION OF "MY LIFE IS GOING ON"
BY CELIA KRULL PLAYS)
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
WELCOME
AGAIN
(CHUCKLES)
Well, most of you already know the rules,
but since there are some new faces,
I'll remind you.
First of all, there will be
no personal relationships.
- All right, that rule's been…
- (LAUGHS)
The second rule is that we're not allowed
to use first or last names.
NAIROBI: Professor.
Let's cut the bullshit. How will we
be breaking into the Bank of Spain?
By making a lot of noise.
MADRID, D-DAY
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
TOKYO: Nowadays,
wars start with bombings.
So did ours.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
TOKYO: That day, in Madrid,
it rained over 140 million euros.
(CROWD CLAMORING AND YELLING)
TOKYO: That was our way of saying
"We're back."
("ASALTO AL CAMIÓN"
BY IVÁN M. LACÁMARA PLAYS)