LIVE, HEIST AT THE BANK OF SPAIN
Thanks.
Walk towards the music, Cristoff.
Towards the music.
Music.
Music... music.
This is Bear 3.
Emergency in Room 1.
I need immediate replacement in Room 1.
Copy, Bear 3. On my way.
Music.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'm a doctor.
I think this gentleman doesn't feel well.
He's disoriented.
It's nothing serious. Thanks.
Come on, Dad.
Excuse me. Out there...
He crossed the line with some ladies.
What?
The president of the foundation
almost called the police.
What did he do?
He said
inappropriate things.
What things?
About...
genitals.
Did you see if he was
with someone or how he got here?
Move aside.
Come here, Dad.
Excuse me.
UNKNOWN NUMBER