Good God!
No, it's not going down.
Give me another one. Another!
- Come on!
- Another!
Another shot!
Please, please, please.
What's happening?
Okay, that's it.
That's it, that's it.
How long?
Five seconds.
Doors are unlocked.
Everyone, get ready. Come on!
Get ready!
You need to put on your mask, now!
Ready! Now!
Quiet!
Be quiet, fuck!
It's only smoke.
Don't do it yet. Hold on.
Helicopters, I need you ready
in 30 seconds.
Now! Everyone outside. Let's go!
Out! Now. Quick. Everybody out.
Come on, come on, come on. Get out.
Everybody out, let's go.
Move, move, move!
Get out! Come on!
Come on, come on! Outside!
Move it!
What the fuck?
Son of a bitch.
We have to abort.
I don't give a shit about the balconies.
If the hostages are there,
we knock down the main door.
Armored unit, advance now!
Let's go, let's go! Tie poles to the door.
I'm gonna open the door and you go out
holding up these boxes.
Is that right, little orphan?
Motherfucker.
They're opening the doors.
That's better. Everybody go in. Now!
Get out there now.
Nobody is moving.
I said get the fuck out there!
Special forces are about to arrive.
No one move.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna shoot us,
like we shot your papa?
Don't move!
Denver! Denver, what are you doing?
Denver!
Denver, stop!
And here's the beauty of the surprise.
It's just like you're thinking.
We surrender!
What?
PROFESSOR: What's he doing?
What's he doing?
We surrender!
Target in sight.
Denver!
I have a shot at him.
Target in the crosshairs.
Requesting permission to fire, sir.
Permission to shoot.
I repeat, permission to shoot.
The state will permit you
to provoke the army out into the streets.
The state will permit you to enter
the national reserve and steal their gold,
but there is one thing they cannot abide.
There is something they will not allow.
They cannot allow you
to find out their secrets.
If we remove those little red boxes
and they see them,
it'll take less than a second
to know what we have
and we will bone them.
Those motherfuckers.
Because those 24 boxes
hold the secrets
of the Ministry of the Interior,
Foreign Affairs, Intelligence…
How they spend the state reserve funds.
Bowel movements of the state!
Everything that the system
can't allow to be made public,
otherwise, they'll get sucked
down the drain
to float among their own excrement.
♪ Dealers keep dealing ♪
Sons of bitches!
♪ Whores keep whoring ♪
♪ Junkies keep scoring ♪
Stop the attack!
I repeat. Abort.
Accept the surrender and retreat.
It's impossible these bastards
are diving inside the vault?
I don't know, Colonel.
- I don't know.
- Fuck!
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
Yes!
Hey!
♪ Creeps keep crawlin'
Drunks keep fallin' ♪
♪ Teasers keep teasin'
Holy Joes are preachin' ♪
♪ Cops keep bustin'
Hustlers keep hustlin' ♪
♪ Death keeps knockin'
Souls are up for auction ♪
♪ Ain't no use in prayin'
That's the way it's stayin', baby ♪
♪ Johnny ain't so crazy
He's always got a line for the ladies ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ Shake it now, now
Get 'em off downtown ♪
♪ Get your rocks off
Get your rocks off, honey ♪
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now ♪
♪ But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on♪
The best sex in the world is gay.
Do you know why?
It's obvious.
There are no women.
You're not a homosexual,
you're a misogynist.
You were brewed in a cauldron, not a womb.
No, señorita.
Don't confuse misogyny with biology.
It's about facts. It's simple.
Look, men need
to expel their poison. Okay?
Every few hours, we need to boom boom.
And after, we feel such repulsion
for the body we dumped in.
It doesn't matter who it is,
we feel repulsion.
So, we say, "Ciao."
Boom, boom, ciao.
- Precious.
- Homosexual sex.
Sex between women is also homosexual.
Boom, boom, ciao. Two men meet
each other and relieve one another.
Boom, boom, ciao. They don't even
share names. It's marvelous.
Do you know what's marvelous?
The incredible fucking women can do.
And we can do it ten times in a row.
- Or more.
- Multi-orgasmically.
We can go for hours,
not just five seconds.
I'm not saying God didn't provide you
with the possibility of pleasure,
that would be misogyny.
I am simply saying it's not a necessity.
Oh, sure.
It's not an organic need for you
like it is for men. Think about it, okay?
- The world is full of saunas…
- Sure.
…where men meet up and relieve each other.
Public parks and restrooms,
where we meet and boom boom and ciao.
Fundamentally selfish.
- Where are the women's saunas?
- We don't need them.
- Oh, no.
- Of course not.
There aren't any. Where can you find
restrooms where you can rub beavers?
Where are they? They don't exist.
I'll tell you why. And it's controversial.
It's that sex for females
is conditioned by procreation.
Really.
In one way or another,
you are ultimately looking
for a man to exchange genes with.
To form a family. Ugh, repulsive.
You have too many things in your head.
We only have one. Ejaculation.
So, we have the boom, boom, ciao.
Boom, boom, ciao. Boom, boom, ciao.
Homosexual sex!
Boom, boom, ciao.
Look, your theory is complete bullshit,
but it's got a nice ring to it.
I'm done.
- Boom, boom, ciao.
- I'm out.
Boom, boom, ciao.
- Professor!
- Boom, boom, ciao.
- Come on.
The Professor!
Boom, boom, ciao.
- Boom, boom, ciao.
- Na, na, na…
- Loosen up, Professor!
- MEN: Boom, boom, ciao.
Boom, boom, ciao.
Boom, boom, ciao…
Goodnight. All right?
If you want that. No problem.
All right.
Look, we have
to be practical, Helsinki. Okay?
You're great. You're a titan, it's true.
I acknowledge that.
But we're professionals, you and I.
Unlike the rest of the morons
in the gang, right?
You're right.
Can you really imagine going in there
with emotional baggage?
It's absurd, right? We got our poison out.
We made boom, boom. And now…
And now, ciao.
No baggage.
Well, now we're blood brothers.
Brothers, comrades, isn't that right, huh?
Yeah.
Hmm?
Yeah, brothers.
What's wrong?
Better I sleep here.
Tomorrow is a big day.
He fucked you and then tossed you out.
Fucking disgusting!
- It's like this between men.
- You're not like that.
We've been everywhere together
for the past two years
and you're a teddy bear, my love.
You're the type to spend 12 hours
latched to someone, like a koala,
and good for you.
We're comrades. Brothers.
How can you be his brother?
Helsinki!
You have to love yourself more.
Forget this fuck boy,
he treats you like shit.
The next time he tells you "Boom, boom,"
you have to say "Ciao."
And he can boom, boom
in someone else's asshole.
Okay, okay.
Helsi.
Are you in love?
Men take care of men.
Fuck my life.
Some days are strange.
You're supposed to be
in a very important meeting,
instead, a second ago you
were clinically dead, dressed as a diver.
You're wearing a wet suit and you
aren't sure if you're dead or alive.
You feel like you have all the
hangovers in the world, and you wonder,
"Is this hell?"
"What have I done wrong?" Nothing.
You've done nothing wrong.
Not any more than anyone else anyway.
You were just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Governor?
Mr. Governor, your heart almost burst.
We've injected you with enough Diazepam
for a whole family. Please, lie down.
I'm perfectly fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
Be careful. Please.
Take it easy.
Well, I guess, if you're okay…
Come on. Let me show you
this little number we've set up.
Come, Mr. Governor. Look here.
What does it smell like?
Do you smell that?
What's that smell?
That's right! Nothing!
Industrial extractors.
We take the gases,
then we pass them through the machine
and we liquefy them and then…
…all the way to the vault.
Currently, our carbon footprint is zero.
We have to be a little careful
because tomorrow the zinc
and the carbon dioxide
will probably be crazy.
Right here
we're currently melting 52 bars per hour.
I mean, we are flying right now.
♪ Be my, be my baby ♪
That's the patrimony of the state.
And we're not missing a drop of it.
We've melted 1,600 kilograms
so far. Heaven.
How many days was I unconscious?
Four hours.
Come on, Mr. Governor,
here's the best part.
Look here, look here.
Take a look, Mr. Governor.
Watch as the magic happens.
Come here, come here, look.
Look, look, look.
Watch it come out.
Ay, yai, yai. Oh, marvelous.
How marvelous!
♪ You know I will adore you
'Til eternity ♪
Good afternoon, Governor. Sausage?
In here, we turn the liquid gold
into little granules.
Small pellets, you know,
like little grains of rice.
And we do it all with bubbles, you see?
It's hypnotic.
Look, look, look!
Top-quality birdseed, Governor.
Listen to me, what you're doing
will have many, many consequences.
And that's the lesson,
nothing is free.
Everything you do has consequences.
Almost a million people
surround the Bank of Spain.
The pressure on the government
is overwhelming.
And the big question, Sara Solomando,
what was in those boxes
that caused the police and army
to stop the attack?
At the moment Cristina,
the only official response is silence.
But since the attack
was brought to a halt,
official cars at the highest level
have not stopped arriving.
Among them are
the Minister of the Interior,
the Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs
and the Chief of Staff of Defense.
Each car has been subjected to…
♪ Be my, be my baby ♪
And so, the consequences
began to arrive.
The Minister of the Interior,
the defense staff,
all showed up at the tent
in the four hours
the governor had been unconscious.
The president wants the crowd
dispersed immediately.
You tell the president
if we go in with water cannons tomorrow
instead of one million people,
it'll be two.
The European Union
is demanding information.
Do the contents of the boxes involve them?
Of course it involves them,
can't they deduce that?
Your job is to lower diplomatic pressure.
Because if you don't, I can't do my job.
The problem is
they know this is really big.
They saw how the Spanish forces aborted
an offensive against seven criminals.
Colonel Tamayo tried his best,
but Berlin and the Professor's plan
drastically changed the chess game.
One move
and all our enemies were in check.
The king and the rest
of the state institutions threatened.
The content of those 24 boxes took
less than an hour to reach Pakistan.
Our legion of hackers opened
a secure, undetectable back door
through a clear satellite.
If we published that information,
they were dead.
And they knew it.
What's the actual size of this leak?
Colonel?
Minister?
The size of this leak…
Europe provoking a war in Libya
for private interests.
Payments to Morocco to abandon
immigrants in the desert.
A confidential agreement to
look the other way in the Mediterranean.
Seventy-four shipwrecks that could've
been avoided, hundreds of drownings.
Old news, but all the details
on the creation of a group of terrorists
in the south of France. Want me to go on?
The contents of these boxes condemn
the government and those before it.
It will fill Spain,
the European Union and NATO up with shit.
And what's worse,
we shoot ourselves in the head.
You, you, you and me.
Are we ready
to end up standing before a judge?
Is that what this president wants?
Is there a prime minister in Europe
who wants to go to jail? Huh?
That's the fucking size of this leak.
We can't negotiate with that man.
As long as he has secrets,
he'll continue to be a threat.
Okay, then.
What do you suggest?
There's only one thing to do.
And you're fully aware of that.
Good afternoon, I'm Alicia Sierra,
for those of you who don't know me.
And I'll be taking over the negotiation
of the heist.
Let's get this party started.
I want three little teeny tiny things
that I know you all can handle.
To know how much gasoline they have
in there to feed the emergency generator.
Secondly,
bring the underground equipment.
Tell me exactly what's down there.
Tunnels, galleries, sewers. Yeah?
And third,
Antoñanzas.
Antoñanzas?
Inspector?
Great.
Donuts, licorice, lollipops and gum.
Melon flavored. Burns your tongue.
My hormones are fired up.
I need to look like a sweet woman while
dealing with that emasculated Professor.
Everything okay?
Absolutely perfect. You're in command.
Okay. Let's go.
Martínez.
Inspector, we're trying
to triangulate the calls.
Inspector.
In what country
was he being held?
Why was he brought into Spain
on a secret plane?
The pregnant woman who tortures.
Even the monkeys in Madagascar
will recognize me.
He dropped like a rag doll.
Go on and get me gum.
ALLEGED ILLEGAL INTERROGATION
I look fat.
Well, yesterday
we were looking at ways
to stall for time
if they stop us here in Spain.
But what happens
if we manage to rob the Mint,
flee with the money and after some time,
Interpol stops us in a foreign country?
In all likelihood, they will want
to detain us in another country to…
Well, to apply what they consider
improved interrogation techniques.
Torture.
The only good news is that
at any given time,
we can use that to our advantage.
Torture to our advantage? Great.
Why didn't I think of that?
Even if they ignore the law,
and the rights
and guarantees of law are waived,
sooner or later,
they have to bring us back to Spain.
There will be transfers,
there will be vans.
That is when you have to show yourself
as being completely destroyed,
because there's always going
to be someone watching.
And if people see and feel that brutality…
That's when we have
an opportunity to negotiate.
Where you in the bathroom?
Yes.
You went at noon to deposit
your solid waste in the shared bathroom?
To shit. Yeah, I went to shit.
What about it?
In the one we all use,
what happens I have to go in there now?
Then light a match, I mean…
Or you plug your nose with that finger
you always got up your ass.
In other words, you got options.
Do you know what that smell is?
It's made up of particles.
Your particles were in the sludge
of your intestines,
floating around peacefully.
Now they've departed
along with your waste through
your filthy anus, devastating everything!
And now I must accept that
entering my lungs?
So, cover your fucking nose.
Why? You don't poop?
Every day, religiously,
like clockwork, but at dawn.
First, for privacy,
but fundamentally out of respect.
- Respect, really?
- Out of respect.
Because I don't think anyone should have
to inhale the particles of my shit.
Let's not get all high and mighty.
It starts with a turd taboo and ends with
you addressing each other as "my liege."
- I don't mind being called "liege."
- You don't say.
Look, uh…
I know I'm not an elegant man like you.
And I don't know as many things as you.
I only know how to open holes
where even God wouldn't be able to.
Most importantly,
I know how to lay my life on the line
for my team, if needed.
The question is whether
you are on my team or not.
The question is
whether I'd risk my life for you.
That's my question.
The answer is that,
despite your crude living habits
and your fondness for crossword puzzles,
if the two of us go in together…
we come out together.
Great, are we friends again? Yes?
Good.
Because what we were talking about
is very important.
All of us, we're all at risk
of being arrested.
Let's see.
Palermo?
Can you see anything with this eye?
I see your Russian Orthodox beard,
you fucking Serbian.
Or is it Jeremiah Johnson?
I don't see the fucking mule though,
where is she? Huh?
- I can see, fat man.
- Let's check the other.
How about this?
It's all right, just has to heal.
Tomorrow you'll see better.
We'll put a patch on.
I'll go find a cane.
ALLEGED ILLEGAL INTERROGATION
Palermo, are you there?
- The all-seeing eye is here, Professor.
- Is Tokyo close?
Yeah, she's here.
Professor.
Tokyo,
Rio is in Spain.
Thank you.
I hope I'll be able to hug you
and thank you in person really soon.
Of course you will.
Tokyo, the hardest part
is still ahead of us, but we'll get there.
We're gonna do it.
All actions,
all of them, have consequences.
And for the police…
Colonel!
…in the darkest moment,
a light would appear.
- We've started to triangulate the signal.
- Like for a cell phone?
It's not precise, not even close.
But ITU has receivers throughout Spain.
The signal is reaching Galicia,
Alicante and even the rest of Europe.
But the important thing is that
it's stronger south of the peninsula.
- I think they're broadcasting from there.
- How precise is this?
This is the radius.
He's directing the robbery from a beach?
While on vacation with his cousin Rosita?
Come on, man!
Colonel, just think about it. It doesn't
make sense for them to be close.
He did that last time. He knows we'll scan
the buildings near the bank.
So they could be in Portugal,
Andalusia or Morocco?
Anywhere is safer than Madrid…
All they need is a phone and a radio.
Colonel, they know our protocols.
And they know that we're incapable
of investigating a robbery
600 kilometers away from a hostage crisis.
I think you better head out there.
- Sure, that's a large area…
- What the fuck, Ángel!
- Let's at least narrow it down first.
- You're going down there now.
I need your absolute discretion. Got it?
If you find there's something to this,
I'd prefer you're there
and not a couple of hick Civil Guards
who will scare them off.
- Martínez, come here!
- Yes.
You're going to give him support.
I want you to study
this signal exclusively. Nothing else.
All right.
Don't say anything to anyone.
I'd love to travel somewhere with you,
like a weekend trip.
But without having to rob something.
- Oh, yes, it could be our honeymoon.
- Yeah.
Well, we would have to get married first.
I already live with your mother.
Marrying you isn't a big deal.
Excuse me?
- What the fuck are you saying?
- Pardon?
Marrying me isn't such a big deal for you?
What is that?
The marriage proposal of a pussy?
Why buy a cow
if you can get the milk for free, right?
I didn't mean anything by it.
Forget it, you're making it worse.
Call Marseille now.
Of course.
And listen,
if you wanna marry me,
make sure next time
you ask me the right away.
Find somewhere to stop, come on.
Inspector. It's him.
Professor.
Inspector Sierra, how nice.
I was looking forward to speaking to you.
Yeah, I know how much you like negotiating
with female police officers.
Aren't you gonna ask me
about what I'm wearing?
Maternity clothes, I presume.
Oh, you're so antiquated!
Are you the kind of guy
that wears a wifebeater?
Well, to be honest, I do, but…
Inspector, you can't go wrong
with a classic. Don't you agree?
Plus, you know, an undershirt
can make you feel like Pablo Escobar
or Marlon Brando in
Streetcar Named Desire.
Touché.
Tell me something.
Have you ever
recorded yourself making love?
Let me think about that…
No, the truth is I haven't.
I imagine that's because I haven't
suggested it, I'm a timid man.
If that's the case, perhaps I can help.
Raquel!
You're listening to me, right?
Raquel?
Hello, Alicia. Been a long time.
A long time, yeah.
Seems like your Professor
has reservations about
asking you to make a sex tape.
But you did that in your second year
of academy with Hortigosa.
Fuck me! Well…
Alicia, you disappoint me.
Look,
I'm gonna tell you
what you're trying to do.
You're trying hard to take control
over the conversation
with nice words and then
drop a bomb trying to divide us.
Negotiation 101.
Not at all. I was just having fun.
The bomb comes now.
Since you're classified as terrorists,
I've got the CIA, Europol,
and Christ himself looking
for your mother and your daughter.
I don't know where they are,
but I'm guessing
you didn't escape to Norway,
probably some tropical paradise
with useless, ineffective police.
Southeast Asia, for example.
I would do the same.
Do you know what the bad part is
about those countries, Raquel?
You tell me, Alicia.
The jails there.
So foul.
Overcrowding, infections,
drugs, murders.
Everything
And your mother in there…
With her age and how confused she gets.
And Paula?
Oh, Paulita.
Considering I could stall the extradition,
I can't imagine how she'd feel.
Well, I can imagine it.
Crying every night
in an orphanage in Jakarta.
Shit, that poor baby.
My congrats, Raquel. You've done great.
You won a little puppet man.
And I'm sure you get
at least one screw a month.
But you lost a family.
If you give me the Professor,
I'll leave them alone.
Why did you say that to her?
Because this is a game of cards,
and I just played a flush.
Hmm? And now they'll be fucked
for a little bit. That's what's is about.
Fucking with them.
No?
Calm down.
- She's bluffing.
- You called her and lost control.
You took control from me.
- And she beat you. Manipulated you.
- She manipulated you.
- She manipulated you!
- She played you like a puppet!
She hung up
and we didn't even play our hand.
She went after you
because you're the weakest link.
Hey, mongrels! Get me some water.
What'd you just call me?
Mongrel.
But I could also call you kebab,
fortune teller or melon-peddler.
Do you really think you're in the position
to bust my balls?
Nah.
I don't wanna be anywhere close
to your foul-smelling cunt.
Gandía. Correct?
Is it just me or is there
a certain negativity in the air?
Very bad vibrations.
Bring me to him, I wanna talk.
And leave me alone with him.
He's sitting on the ground
in front of you.
Smells like shit.
I can't see well…
but I'm developing my other senses.
And my intuition tells me
you don't respect us.
When clowns put on masks
that's what they get.
They don't deserve respect.
A very logical thought coming
from someone of your rank,
but you're wrong my skinny friend.
Or you watched too much TV
and you think we're Robin Hood?
That we're lovable stuffed animals
with a Dalí mask.
Is that it?
No, I think
you're just a mother fucking faggot,
one-eyed, piece of shit, worthless sudaca.
Sudaca.
From South America, that's right.
But from a German school.
The school of Berlin.
Stay there.
Oh, how I love piñatas.
Quiet.
Son of a bitch!
- Palermo!
- Don't move! Stay still.
The sudaca who has come to reclaim
the gold you looted, you son of a bitch.
- Denver, stop him!
- Stay where you are.
Palermo! Denver, stop him!
Gold bathed in the blood
of South Americans! Satanic rites!
- Fucking reptile!
- That's enough!
You better fucking try and kill me,
or I'll use pliers to pull your guts
out of your ass, you motherfucker!
You mother fucker! Come on!
- I'm gonna kill him!
- Nobody move! Stay still!
Come fucking hit me, come hit me!
You motherfucker!
Motherfucker! Come on!
You've brought us all down
to the same fucking level as the Taliban.
What were you trying to demonstrate?
Authority?
Beating the crap out of
a guy who's all tied up?
The only thing that demonstrates
is you're a piece of shit!
Let him go and send him over.
I'll take him on with one hand.
I will fuck him up. Bring him in!
Professor put a crazy person in charge.
We can't keep listening to this psycho.
No, no, no. Listen to me, Palermo.
We've got a plan and this plan has rules.
Implemented by the Professor.
And we don't break them.
Oh, yeah? Where is the Professor?
Where is Mr. Professor?
He's never around, Mr. Professor!
Raise your hand if you have
the scepter of command!
I have the scepter! I'm in charge!
- I'm the boss. Silence!
- Hey.
I'll explain one thing about the laws
that govern in here now.
For any mother fucker here
who fucking dares to insult one of us,
I will break his head open.
And you, mongrel,
better learn to shut your mouth.
Unless you wanna open your mouth
to thank me for the fact
that I stepped in to defend you
for instance, no?
I do not need a piece of trash like you
to defend me.
Haven't you been paying attention?
The same way you hit a defenseless guy,
I could take my gun,
smack you in the head, knock you out
and take command.
Oh, yeah?
Helsinki, tie her up.
Tie her hands and her feet and take her
down to the forge for mutiny. Right now.
Don't even think about it. Helsi, Helsi!
- Nairobi.
- Helsi.
"Helsi?"
"Ay, Helsi."
Excuse me.
Is it just me? Or are you speaking to him
from your emotional baggage, is that it?
Do you secretly
wanna be Ms. Helsinki?
Why, Nairobi…
Why chase an impossible love?
Why would you do that? Huh?
Aren't you cheating yourself, genius?
Huh? Or are you just playing mama?
I'm sorry to say that
the only thing you can do now
is to assume the role
of the faggot's friend.
You're the fucking straight friend.
I'm sorry,
but Helsinki loves me. Doesn't he?
I apologize.
Look, I'll tell you a couple of things
that you probably already know.
You're certainly old enough.
In matters of the heart,
there is the lover
and the beloved.
The lover lives with passion,
with full commitment and romanticism.
The beloved
is limited to being idolized.
I'm not saying that being a lover is bad.
Don't get me wrong.
But you have to know what happens.
You suffer a lot, my dear.
Hmm?
I'm the one having the better time.
In our relationship, the only thing
I get out of it is sexual.
It's the law of love.
I'm sorry. That's the way it is.
The only pathetic one in this entire story
is you.
With your talk about love,
about "Boom, boom, ciao." Wow.
Could it be
because you'll never admit the truth?
The only truth is what is real.
Let me explain.
Look. You love the fat guy.
The fat guy loves me.
And I love no one.
And that's precisely why
you hate me.
Oh, really? You love no one?
Of course not, honey.
You don't have the balls.
You need courage to love.
And as for me? Watch.
Helsinki…
I love you. I love you so much…
that I would build a family with you.
You see? That's bravery.
I feel it and I say it.
That's what
you're not capable of.
Because how long has it been?
Ten years
that you've been in love with Berlin?
And you never dared to open your mouth.
You worshiped him like a god.
You followed him around like a little dog.
But you said nothing.
And now what?
You're stuck with nothing.
He's gone forever.
And you're empty.
The only thing you can do now
is hide behind bullshit speeches…
"Boom, boom, ciao" because…
Because you know
that you've been
left behind forever, my friend.
Let's get back to work.