They think we're academics, not thieves.
Why are you such a pessimist?
How long have you known Tatiana?
Why does it matter?
You can't time love.
You have to live it.
You can't risk this entire plan
for a woman.
That's the first rule, Andrés. The first.
"A job can't be tainted
by a romantic relationship."
Never.
It's not hard to understand.
You're so sweet.
No loose ends.
You're going to put your life at risk.
Your life is already at risk in there.
You need to understand that.
Dying is a possibility.
- Only if there are mistakes.
- No.
No. That's the funny thing.
You're hurtling towards chaos,
absolute chaos,
yet you insist
on maintaining control at all costs.
With a perfect plan,
there wouldn't be any chaos.
For the love of God,
of course there's chaos.
Chaos interferes in life all the time.
You don't need to make mistakes to
be killed. How long do I have left? Huh?
Three years? What mistake did I make?!
Did I make mistakes?
I didn't?
Realize
you can't prevent it.
What mistake did Dad make?
- He must have made a mistake.
- No, it's much simpler than that.
It's possible the police were too close.
Or someone saw him enter,
or his gun jammed.
Little brother, you're smart.
But accidents
are the mystery of life.
Which is why
how you live doesn't make sense.
- And how was that, Andrés?
- Without Tatiana.
What I mean is…
Without enjoyment.
Because in the end,
that's the only thing that matters.
We're here.
You have to understand that, okay?
Before I…
Thank you very much, Joao.
Ah, quick question.
Where are you from, Joao?
From São Paulo.
Brazil. How marvelous.
Our father loved Brazil.
Hmm? Our father
was in love with your country.
The parties, the magic,
the soccer.
I'm not really into soccer or party.
Sure, but I bet you know
soccer is played in Brazil.
- Beautiful.
- Exactly.
They play beautifully.
They're fearless.
They don't think about
every little thing that could go wrong.
They enjoy it.
They dance.
They play while they dance.
That's what makes them different,
little brother.
The best.
During the World Cup,
I always pray a lot for our national team.
Thank you, Joao.
Have a good day.
Thanks.
And there you have it.
They enjoy it.
Cherish it, little brother.
Every step.
Because someday,
something bad's gonna happen
that might cost you your life
or something much worse.
And on that day, you can't begin to think
that you are to blame for something
that you could never control. Understand?
Your life is here.
Enjoy it…
until the party's over.
Tamayo, I need the emergency military now.
You don't have enough personnel?
No, we have 420-hectare of forest
and 183 houses.
Farms, sheds, wells, and a perimeter that
needs to expand 20 kilometers every hour.
- Give me the unit.
- I'll talk to defense and send them.
Great.
- Suárez, let's take a look at those farms.
- I'll take care of it.
Let's go!
Marseille will be here in three hours.
- Received.
- How are you?
Well, scared.
And pissed.
And surrounded by chicken shit.
Sorry, Raquel.
I'm truly sorry.
Look, I've
lived many years and you're my first love.
I don't know how to do this.
I don't know how to talk about this.
I just know that I need you in my life.
I've cherished everything
that you shared with me.
Um, cooking
together in our filthy boat.
Um, swimming fully-clothed in the sea.
And letting me know that
Van Morrison is very good, really.
I like him a lot.
Everything is better now
that I'm with you.
Because I'm in love with you.
You should have told me once
that you loved me.
I don't know to say this to your face.
And forgive me because
when we were arguing,
I was talking as
the misanthrope who doesn't enjoy life,
the Professor.
But as Sergio, I…
I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
I feel so stupid.
Crying.
While a chicken stares at me.
They say hens are good luck.
Yeah, I don't know. Because it's not
in the Chinese horoscope.
I think I can wait three hours
after everything you said to me.
Let's touch base in 15 minutes.
Frequency 144, hmm?
Received. Cut.
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong
I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now but I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
♪ I've had time to unfold ♪
♪ And see my face in other lives ♪
♪ I already threw the stone
At the center of the pond ♪
I brought that bottle
to drink with Rio.
♪ A den will have to be created ♪
As I danced,
I realized there are two types of people.
Those who break up
and feel the need to wish you the best.
Like, "Take care, be happy."
♪ Everyone who takes their measurements ♪
Rio is one of them.
And then there's people like me,
who can be a fucking bitch about it.
Excuse me. Should I wait outside?
No, there's nothing
you haven't seen before.
Rio, I wanted to tell you…
You did what we should have done
a long time ago.
Hey. Not a long time ago.
We had fun together.
Even though I'm sure
you're pissed right now,
you haven't beat the shit out of me yet.
Yeah, we had our fun.
We had good moments.
But that wasn't enough.
We got wrapped up in all this.
Wrapped up in what?
What the fuck are you talking about?
The heist. The pressure.
Being millionaires.
Hello, Denver.
- I didn't hear anything.
- Hmm?
- See you later.
- Where are you going?
- Don't go, don't go.
- What?
Rio, did you know
I almost hooked up with Denver?
Tokyo, what the fuck are you doing?
- Hmm? In Toledo. After the festival.
- What are you doing, Tokyo?
You were drunk.
Fine. Fine. He was drunk.
And you were also drunk
and so was I, okay?
Mm, no. Actually,
Moscow ruined everything.
Coming into the room…
What we had together was casual.
Anything…
Anything could have happened back then.
Now I'm wondering the same thing as you.
How were we able
to stay together for so long?
Hmm?
Thank you.
Rio, nothing happened. Nothing.
Love is like two people
on a seesaw.
When one goes up, the other goes down.
The balance is always fucked.
Thanks to time, monotony…
And sometimes, because of people like me,
who only know one way
to get over the pain,
give a little back.
Rio was implanted
with a microphone and GPS.
We extracted it. No problem.
Did you manage to get the chips placed?
But of course, my dear.
They're in a little box,
in a symphony of dreams.
The police have been basking in a melody
of sleep for some time now.
It's time
to give them something more. Palermo.
It's time for Plan Alcatraz.
Initiate as soon as possible.
Plan Alcatraz?
Sergio, what the fuck
is going on out there?
Our situation
is extreme.
Lisbon and I may be faced
with pressure at some point
that we won't be able
to handle by ourselves.
We'll have the army on top of us.
The police.
And some things may go wrong.
But that's why
we have Plan Alcatraz.
If Lisbon and I find ourselves
in a critical situation,
we'll need you to create
the largest diversion possible.
The objective is
for the police to be looking
at two places at the same time.
And there's only one thing more powerful
than capturing the two of us.
Capturing all of us?
If all of you were to escape,
that would be
the biggest distraction we could create.
This will drive them crazy.
Any update?
Colonel.
The seismometers are picking up movement.
They could be drilling
with industrial equipment.
Bernardo!
You've conducted exhaustive research
on the subject.
Tell me. Are they capable
of escaping down there?
I'd say no, sir.
That is a very unlikely scenario.
Unlikely or impossible, Bernardo?
This is an engineering project that needs
tunnel-boring machines
100 meters below the ground.
So what?
These people can do anything.
Don't underestimate them.
They could build anything
without anyone noticing.
- How many of your men are down there?
- 25 men.
25 men? What, were there budgets cuts?
Fifty meters, 100.
I want a policeman in every puddle.
They can't take a step without
being spotted. Get it together, Bernardo.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Get me an expert
that knows every rock in this subsurface.
Georadars, seismologists,
engineers, whatever is necessary!
This is fucking unbelievable! Come on!
What are you doing here?
I was hiking. I got lost, sir.
I came here to rest. I'm very sorry.
You were resting in there
with the chickens?
Listen… I knocked on the door, sir,
but nobody came up. Please.
And those spurs?
Climbing.
There's no mountains here.
Or ice.
You think I'm an idiot?
I know who you are.
Raquel Murillo.
Okay.
I'll tell you the whole truth.
- Don't do that!
- Easy.
- Don't aim it! Put down the gun!
What's your name?
- Put down the gun!
- Your name.
What's your name?
Tell me your name.
- Justino.
- Justino. Justino, easy.
Look at me. Look at me.
Now…
Now you have two guns pointing at you.
You only have a little shotgun
to kill birds with.
You can hurt me.
But if you shoot me, you're dead.
So lower your weapon.
Lower it, Justino.
Easy.
Easy. That's it.
You have no chance.
If I were you, I wouldn't risk my life.
They asked for help from civilians.
And they're offering ten million euros
as a reward, miss.
You put down your guns.
It's okay.
Relax!
- Be careful!
- Relax!
Throw your weapons.
Back up, now!
Renata, back off!
- Quiet, Justino.
- Back off!
Calm down, Justino.
Throw your weapons.
I know how to play this, you don't.
Does it look
like we're playing here, Inspector?
You're a police officer.
I've seen you on TV.
And you won't shoot us.
But we can shoot you.
You're on our property.
Now you really need
to have good aim with both hands.
This shotgun is for big game,
not little birdies.
It'll make a big hole.
Drop the fucking guns now!
It's okay.
We're gonna do something. Okay?
- Hey!
How about we do some negotiation?
Wow, this is nice.
Really pretty.
Very nice.
It's hot in here. Look.
Here it is.
What are you doing?
- Nairobi! Nairobi!
- Ooh, ooh.
- What…?
- Now we're both single, aren't we?
Mm, yeah.
Yeah, now we can go
get some little kitties.
Okay. What happened?
Nothing, girl. But, you know…
Love en… ends, right?
- It just ends.
- All right, come on. Come on.
Fellas!
- Come on, let's go.
- We all stormed in here with the cavalry.
- Eh?
- Tokyo!
- What are you doing?
- And I stepped in horse shit.
The oven!
- All right, come here.
- What?
You're gonna go upstairs
and drink a little coffee.
Then I'm gonna come and we'll talk.
- No. Coffee, no. I'll throw up.
- My love, then throw up.
- No.
- Throw up.
What?
I'm gonna take a shower.
- What shower? You're drunk as fuck.
- Yes.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna take a shower.
I need to be in water
and be in the darkness.
- Floating!
- Relax!
Why don't we both go upstairs
and have a little talk.
- Just you and me.
- Of course.
Since you're in love
with the big fat guy in our gang, right?
But look I…
I had a really good story.
Good. When love…
I'm taking a shower.
Okay. Hey! Hey!
Radio!
Hey!
Denver, get your ass down here
and grab Tokyo.
- Giddyap, cowboy!
- Let her go, man. She's really funny.
Shut the fuck up, Matías.
If she wants to snorkel, I'll teach her.
Get back to work. You're on the clock.
Whatever, all right.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
These ovens are set to 1,500 degrees.
We're not here to deal with drunk girls.
The macho alpha. Hmm?
You're like a big buffalo, Bogotá.
- Quit screwing around.
- Oh, I get it.
You love Nairobi.
Like a lady on top, huh?
Quit screwing around.
Fine. How about this one? Ready for this?
If I can't dive in the water,
let me dive in gold like Scrooge McDuck.
Denver, you're back?
Denver… here again?
Take her away.
Tokyo, what the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
You're putting us all in danger.
- Sorry.
- Don't fucking apologize.
This is total bullshit.
We're here because of you
and you're fucking drunk?
If you're not gonna help,
then the least you can do
is try to not get us all killed.
I'm pathetic.
It's no surprise you told me to fuck off.
Listen Tokyo, wait a second.
Wait a second.
We came here to get Rio.
Right? That's why we're here.
Not to save your relationship.
And you did it.
Because you are incredible.
Now it's time to move on.
Mm-hmm.
I can't move on.
You think you can't but…
But yes you can.
Repeat after me.
"I gonna move on
because I'm the fucking boss."
I…
What? Um… Tokyo!
- What was that?
- I don't know.
You don't know.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter. Okay?
- Okay.
- Doesn't matter.
No. I'm not here for this. Okay?
- No. Fine.
- Stay over there.
- Stay there. Please
- I won't do anything.
- I'm not doing anything.
- Okay.
- We're not gonna move.
- Not gonna move.
No, not the elevator.
We… We're going up. No.
Cut it out.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Just stop it.
It's not funny.
You wanted it once.
Get out.
Get out. Right now.
Motherfucker.
With Rio, they'll try to sneak in at least
one microphone and GPS tracker,
which we'll use to our advantage
in Plan Alcatraz.
So, they'll think we're escaping.
We'll allow them to hear it,
which is much more powerful.
Stop. Stop, Helsinki!
The seismometer stopped working.
There's the opening.
Our sense of hearing combined with
fear is the best way to cause paranoia.
We'll be able
to make them believe anything.
It's the tunnel.
Get Palermo, hurry.
A tunnel?
Are there tunnels that far down there?
No.
None from before.
There has to be something. Find it!
- There aren't any tunnels.
- Search for it!
You see…
An escape is about tension,
excitement, darkness.
It's about the echo within space.
It's the moist subsurface.
They need to hear all of that.
And they will.
They're in a flooded tunnel.
Turn up the volume.
There's an echo.
Where's Nairobi?
She's finishing smelting the gold.
Get everyone down here. We have enough.
We've gotta get out of here!
Sierra, can they smelt 90 tons of gold
in two days?
No. That's impossible.
Tell me, can you or can you not
to smelt 90 tons of gold in only two days?
You need at least 150 to 200 ovens.
I'd have to crunch the numbers.
Technically, it's possible, but…
Very unlikely.
If they did things that were likely,
they'd steal from your local bank.
Their ears will create so many doubts
they'll need confirmation
through a different sense.
Through sight.
And that's exactly when the new member
of the gang will come into play.
Behave yourself, Sofía. You're up.
Sofía.
We'll plant on Sofía the GPS tracker chip
and get her ready
while we continue to bombard their ears
with aural hallucinations.
What the hell is that?
- It sounds like some kind of boat engine.
- An engine?
Actually, it could be
an outboard motor with a…
recoil start.
Who gives a shit about the recoil start?
They're on the move.
They're fucking escaping!
There's only one conclusion they'll reach
and it'll be very clear.
And they are not gonna like it.
It's just like El Chapo's modus operandi.
The escape from Altiplano Prison.
Okay, I'm ready.
We're all here, let's go.
What is that?
They have wagons.
Then comes the moment for us
to send them into a frenzy.
We'll release Sofía.
We have confirmation from the satellite.
They're moving.
How fast are they going?
18 kilometers per hour.
Holy… At that pace,
they'll be gone in half an hour.
What is it, Ángel?
Tamayo, I need
the Emergency Military Unit.
- Quickly.
- Quickly, my ass.
They're getting the gold out
through a tunnel.
The national reserve is in wagons
with a fucking recoil starter.
The unit is staying in Madrid.
We'll cut the signals from the microphones
and the satellite will be all that's left.
So their only option
will be to watch the GPS.
They'll follow Sofía.
We've lost audio.
The signal is out of range.
They're too far down.
Connect me to the unit
we have underground.
I want a full detail done
outside the sewers.
Send every single unit right now!
Suárez.
We only have two farms left.
We're almost there.
Okay.
Gentlemen!
Let's move.
40 meters.
Come on, come on, come on.
Move.
That's right. We got 'em.
We got 'em, Bernardo. We got 'em!
Thirty meters.
They're right next to you, Bernardo.
You're close.
Come on!
Fifteen meters.
They're right around the corner from you.
They stopped.
Let's move.
Everyone ready. Stay sharp.
Five meters.
Bernardo!
Three meters.
Two.
They're here.
Bernardo, what's happening there?
- Where are they?
- Here.
One meter away.
What the fuck is this?
Colonel.
It's a ferret.
It's dressed like a Dalí.
Sons of bitches.
All units on alert
until perimeter is secured.
It's not that bad,
if you know how to read the situation.
Oh, yeah? Enlighten me.
They faked an escape.
It's just an extreme maneuver
to distract us.
He's fucked.
He wants you to look somewhere else.
You stepped in shit, right?
But I assure you
he's on the verge of collapse.
It's all part of this bastards' plan.
Yes, but he's not
the only one who has plans.
This is the moment to hit them
where it hurts the most.
We attack.
We go directly for the heart.
We destroy them from within.
And I know how to do it.
Tell me.
It's already happening.
Everything.
I have money.
The police do as well.
Ten million.
Are you sure that you've heard my name
in the news?
- Oh yeah.
- Because…
they say that they're offering ten million
for the Professor.
And even that's not sure.
Those rewards have a lot of fine print.
We may be farmers,
but we are not complete idiots.
It was on the television, the news.
It's everywhere.
And I've been police,
they don't get paid, never.
Never. Ever.
Tom Lee, a man from Michigan.
He gave crucial information
about Bin Laden's whereabouts.
They offered 25 million dollars.
He's still trying to claim it.
I'm not lying. You can check the internet.
I can give you guys the money.
Today.
And much more than
the police are offering.
How much?
How does 15 million sound to you?
Fifteen?
Watch for any movement on the perimeter.
Stay sharp, everyone.
Perimeter covered.
The windows.
Keep your eyes on the windows.
Copy.
Keeping an eye on the third floor.
Inspector?
Covered.
Motherfucker.
Come here.
You're the biggest piece of shit
in the world.
We came here to rescue you
and the first thing you do
is break up with Tokyo?
Denver, that's a personal thing.
Personal my ass.
Tokyo is a bomb ready to go off.
You know that as well as I do.
You're gonna apologize to her.
Get back together.
Hell, ask her to get married.
I don't give a fuck,
just do what you have to do.
When you get out of here,
you can leave her. Not now.
Maybe for once
you can stop acting like a child.
There's a pregnant woman
coming a stuffed animal.
Did you guys order a circus?
Someone wanna tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Watching left flank.
Entering maximum security perimeter.
- Lower sector?
- Perimeter covered.
Get the windows.
Affirmative.
She's crazy.
We have to go outside for that bear.
That's exactly what we're doing, genius.
I'm going.
Nairobi!
- No way, Nairobi.
- What do you want?
We're sticking to the protocol.
What crawled up your ass, Nairobi?
Nothing.
Denver.
Choose a volunteer.
I got one.
What are you looking at?
Miguel.
Come here. Listen.
You're gonna go out there
and get a stuffed bear.
Um… But won't that be dangerous?
"Danger" is your middle name.
Get out there.
Stop it!
Don't do it, kid. You don't
wanna be a hero. It's not worth it.
If you send him out there,
it'll look like an attack.
It's practically suicide!
Listen to me, kid.
Going out there is certain death.
You're sending him to the slaughterhouse.
What if it's a fucking bomb?
If it was a bomb, I'd send you!
Shut up!
Hey. Hey, this is your moment.
We talked about this. Remember?
Listen, hey.
I believe in you. Remember to
stay calm and keep it together.
Just think of Amanda.
Let's go, come on. Come on!
Masks on!
Rio!
The doors are opening, sir.
There are ten hostages
with assault rifles.
No fucking shit, Antoñanzas!
I'm watching it too.
Don't shoot, I'm a hostage.
My name's Miguel Fernández Talanilla,
from Totana, Murcia. I'm a systems intern.
Keep an eye on the Dalís,
some of them might be the terrorists.
Copy that, sir. We're alert.
Standing by for orders.
He's picking up the bear.
The bomb is inside.
Mission accomplished, Mr. Denver.
Good job, Miguel.
Now, hand it to me slowly.
Don't make any sudden movements.
Take it to the x-ray.
You can send me out whenever you need,
Mr. Palermo.
There's a phone, but it's not a bomb.
And there's something else.
Open it, Helsinki.
Just a cell phone.
Mother fucking cock sucker.
What the hell do you want?
I can make you an offer.
Go fuck yourself!
Okay.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't be an idiot.
Get off me.
Can someone tell me
what the hell's going on?
I don't know what is going on,
but get her back here now.
I said now!
No. No.
"No" what?
- Let me.
- Stay out of this.
I said let me.
Between the police and the thieves,
I trust the police more.
These thieves have released
140 million euros in the center of Madrid.
Do you think they won't have 15 million
or 20 to give you in case you help me?
Yeah, yeah, but that's dirty money.
- The money from the police is legal.
- It's legal.
If you turn me in,
it will turn you into a plague.
As soon as they have me,
they'll disappear.
But guys?
You're gonna be on all the televisions.
"The couple who turned in Lisbon."
Everyone will hate you.
Because the whole world loves us.
Do you know why?
Because we came back to rescue
our friend who they were torturing.
The torturers are the same people
who are offering you ten million euros.
So really think about it.
And take the money.
You can have it in two hours.
And nobody will ever know about this.
I give you my word.
Agreed.
Shit.
The police. It's the police, Justino.
That's your son's, isn't it?
It doesn't smell like him.
Nairobi.
- They did this to hurt you. You know that.
- Yeah. I know.
And they really fucked me good…
…now the only thing I want
is to smell my son.
I'm a bad mom.
No.
No, Nairobi.
You did everything that you could.
And you paid for it.
So much. And you're still paying.
You have no fucking idea.
Do you know what I did with this bear?
I'm so embarrassed,
I couldn't even tell Helsinki.
When they used to call me
to pick up drugs,
I'd take my son and go to the park.
I'd get him dressed up.
And I'd sit him in his seat.
And I'd give him his little bear.
And Mama would open the bear
and put Molly,
cocaine,
heroin,
whatever I had to.
And that's how my son went to the park.
I used him
like a mule.
They took him away.
And they did it for a good reason.
I have your son.
What?
Axel.
He's here with me.
I don't believe you.
Yeah, yeah.
I have him here, right next to me.
Just as adorable as always.
And he's only nine.
- What do you want to be when you grow up?
- A chef.
- What?
What?
A chef!
- You wanna be a cook?
- You're lying. I'm gonna hang up.
Don't hang up.
I wanna offer you a deal.
But first and foremost,
I'll show you that I'm telling the truth.
I don't trust lying cunts.
Yeah, the feeling's mutual.
Let's go, Axel.
Look, let's do this.
I'm gonna go outside
with him.
And you'll see that I'm telling the truth.
Then we'll talk.
It's important that we trust each other.
- I have a clear shot.
- My baby.
- Fire.
- Nairobi, get back!
Nairobi. Nairobi. Stay still. Stay still.
- No!
- Stay still.
I need help!
Please! Help in here!
Please, hide me somewhere.
Please, I'm telling you. Hide me.
Please. Hide me somewhere, please!
Twenty million.
Yes, that's okay. That's okay.
I have two in my bag.
When I'm out, I'll give you the rest.
- I swear.
- Don't listen to her.
There's no time, Justino!
Hey, hands up! Hands up!
Easy. It's a radio.
I want you to hear this.
Professor. It's Lisbon. I'm surrounded.
I need to give 18 million to some people
so they can help me. Is that possible?
We'll deliver it to them
as soon as possible.
He never goes back on his word.
Neither do I. Twenty million.
Do you accept?
Sniff.
They have a dog.
They're gonna find her.
We will go to jail, Justino.
We have a trapdoor in the basement.
We can cover her in fertilizer.
- The dogs won't smell anything.
- There's no time!
- Please, Reni.
- Please!
No.
Ah… Help us, please!
What happened? Nairobi!
You have to hold on, please, Nairobi.
You have to hold on. It's gonna be okay.
I'm really fucked, Helsi.
It's okay.
It's inside. It's not that bad.
We'll take it out.
It's okay. Gauze! Gauze!
Give me the fucking gauze!
You're gonna be okay.
Now that they're playing doctor…
Go in with everything, right?
It's finally time.
Ladies and gentlemen, launch the attack!
Armored cars, advance.
We're gonna break down that fucking door.
Raquel.
Come on.
They're going to hide me in the basement.
Stop right there!
Raquel Murillo is in there!
She's talking to the Professor.
Move it.
What the fuck?
Easy, tiger.
- It still inside?
- Yeah.
- Morphine!
- They fucked me up.
My insides are destroyed.
No.
Put the weapon on the ground.
Drop your weapon.
Against the tree!
- Against the tree!
- I didn't do anything.
Sierra, do you copy?
- Talk to me.
- We got Murillo.
She's communicating with the Professor.
What do you wanna do?
- Hands up!
- No, Justino, no.
- Get back!
- Hide me. Hide me.
Quiet!
On your knees!
I'm gonna give you morphine.
We have to take out the bullet.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Morphine!
- Stay still.
We have to get it out. Hold on.
Justino, help me.
I can't.
Velasco, Solana, with me.
The rest of you surround the structure.
Police!
I don't know what to do.
Guys!
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys!
The bastards are coming
with armored fucking cars! Fuck!
Police! Police!
Drop your weapon!
Put your hands where I can see them!
On your head!
You, get out of here.
Raquel.
Why are you sending him out?
Don't leave. Justino, don't leave!
She's dangerous. You need to leave.
- What are you gonna do?
- Suárez.
I'm turning myself in. I'm unarmed.
What are you doing?
Velasco, get this civilian out of here!
- What are you gonna do?!
- Don't leave, Justino. Don't leave!
What are you gonna do?!
Against the tree.
I said against the tree! Don't move!
Suárez. Suárez, I'm not a threat.
You're the biggest threat, traitor.
You sold us all out, you fucking bitch!
Suárez, lower your weapon.
Where is the Professor?
Raquel, give them my surrender.
Buy some time until I get there.
Raquel, tell them.
Where is the Professor?!
I don't know where the Professor is.
Tell them I'm almost there. Raquel.
Where is the Professor?!
I don't know!
Are you sure?
I'm only going to ask you one more time.
Get out of there!
I don't know where the Professor is.
I don't.
That's the wrong answer.
I'm almost there.
Just get out. Just get out!
This was self-defense, you understand?
You got me, Solana?
She shot first.
Take the gun. Clean off the prints.
Put it in her hand.
Professor, it's Palermo.
Everyone, stand by to enter the bank.
After we break that goddamn door down,
we go inside immediately with all units.
Professor, it's Palermo. Do you copy?
Sergio! Are you there?!
Sergio!
They executed Lisbon.
In here, they shot Nairobi.
A sniper. It's very bad.
- Nairobi.
- Helsi.
Hold on.
I saw my son.
My son.
And he's okay. He's okay.
He's okay.
Palermo! Palermo! They're coming in
with fucking armored cars!
They're gonna bust down the door.
They're going to attack.
Palermo…
this is no longer a heist
or taking down the system.
This is a war.
Act accordingly.
Sir…
it's been an honor to serve with you.
DEFCON two!
Denver!
Positions.
When he turns 18,
you give him the money
and you tell him who his mother was.
- Promise me.
- Yeah.
Look at me. Look.
Give it to him yourself.
Okay?
You're gonna get out of here.
And out there, you can do it.
- Helsinki! DEFCON two now!
- Palermo!
Not now! I need to stay
with Nairobi, Palermo.
I'll go!
We're ready for the assault.
Now!
Attention! Get out of the way.
Two groups in the corners. Now!
On your knees holding your head!
Hurry up!
Rio, let's go.
Come on, Rio. Let's go.
In position.
Hold it.
Hold it!
Denver!
Fire!
The Professor had fallen
for his own trap.
The ear has a unique ability
to cause paranoia.
It was the card that Sierra played…
Fake her execution.
He'll be listening.
…to destroy us.
And that's how the war began.
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If my choice is wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now, but I win later on ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ Whatever happens in the future ♪
♪ Trust in destiny ♪
♪ Don't try to do anything else ♪
♪ No matter what you feel ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Waste my time, my life is going ♪
♪ On ♪