1
00:00:42,021 --> 00:00:46,604
BANK OF SPAIN
5 YEARS BEFORE D-DAY

2
00:00:49,979 --> 00:00:50,896
Hello.

3
00:01:24,646 --> 00:01:26,146
Good morning, miss.

4
00:01:26,354 --> 00:01:29,062
I have an appointment
with Mr. Mario Urbaneja,

5
00:01:29,229 --> 00:01:31,021
governor of the Bank of Spain.

6
00:01:33,896 --> 00:01:36,604
Alfredo Kesmann,
from Rating Trust Corporation.

7
00:01:45,479 --> 00:01:46,354
Take a seat.

8
00:01:50,146 --> 00:01:51,854
You're very kind. Thank you.

9
00:02:22,979 --> 00:02:25,312
- Excuse me, where are you going?
- Hello.

10
00:02:26,146 --> 00:02:27,021
And you?

11
00:02:28,479 --> 00:02:32,062
- Have we met before?
- I'm asking you where you're going.

12
00:02:32,479 --> 00:02:34,187
I'm here to see the governor.

13
00:02:35,437 --> 00:02:39,271
Where are you going? For a walk?
It's a beautiful day.

14
00:02:39,979 --> 00:02:42,937
They'll have told you to wait there.
They'll come for you.

15
00:02:43,021 --> 00:02:45,812
No one was coming,
so I came up. I know the way.

16
00:02:45,896 --> 00:02:47,687
- Mr. Kesmann.
- That's me.

17
00:02:47,771 --> 00:02:49,687
- Nice to meet you.
- How are you?

18
00:02:49,771 --> 00:02:51,104
Sorry about the wait.

19
00:02:51,187 --> 00:02:53,271
- He'll be right with you.
- Great.

20
00:02:53,354 --> 00:02:54,979
- Come with me.
- Thank you.

21
00:02:55,979 --> 00:02:58,271
- Have a good day.
- I'll come with you.

22
00:02:59,771 --> 00:03:00,771
Please do.

23
00:03:23,521 --> 00:03:24,729
Rest, dear.

24
00:03:27,687 --> 00:03:28,687
You?

25
00:03:29,396 --> 00:03:31,396
I'm in charge of intensive care.

26
00:03:31,562 --> 00:03:33,729
Don't worry, I was a nurse.

27
00:03:34,271 --> 00:03:36,479
I'm going to the bathroom,
but I'll be here.

28
00:03:36,562 --> 00:03:37,771
Thank you.

29
00:03:44,562 --> 00:03:45,521
Mutt.

30
00:03:47,146 --> 00:03:49,354
I told you I was going to kill you.

31
00:04:53,896 --> 00:04:55,187
Which way did he go?

32
00:04:57,812 --> 00:04:59,521
Rio, which way did he go?

33
00:05:00,104 --> 00:05:01,312
For fuck's sake.

34
00:05:03,021 --> 00:05:04,021
Where did he go?

35
00:05:04,771 --> 00:05:05,729
Up the stairs.

36
00:05:08,021 --> 00:05:09,771
Stockholm, Denver, stay here.

37
00:05:09,854 --> 00:05:13,604
Don't let him get near the door.
If the hostages escape, we're fucked.

38
00:05:13,687 --> 00:05:15,229
- Understood.
- Let's go.

39
00:05:15,396 --> 00:05:18,104
- Helsinki, Bogotá, come with me.
- Let's go.

40
00:05:19,479 --> 00:05:22,187
Everyone, stand the fuck up, now!

41
00:05:24,312 --> 00:05:25,521
What's happening?

42
00:05:26,854 --> 00:05:29,354
Nairobi. Something's wrong. Run!

43
00:05:29,437 --> 00:05:30,521
Nairobi!

44
00:05:51,187 --> 00:05:52,937
- Nairobi, hold on!
- Nairobi!

45
00:06:06,937 --> 00:06:08,979
Nairobi!

46
00:06:09,062 --> 00:06:10,396
Nairobi, hold on!

47
00:06:26,854 --> 00:06:29,354
He tried to smother her.
Her pulse was 162 bpm.

48
00:06:29,437 --> 00:06:30,937
- Nairobi.
- Nairobi.

49
00:06:31,354 --> 00:06:32,229
Easy.

50
00:06:32,646 --> 00:06:33,937
Easy, breathe.

51
00:06:34,021 --> 00:06:36,687
- Breathe, Nairobi.
- Gandía is on the loose.

52
00:06:39,729 --> 00:06:41,646
Bogotá!

53
00:06:42,687 --> 00:06:44,021
You stay with Nairobi.

54
00:06:44,604 --> 00:06:48,187
If he comes back in,
blow his brains out, understood?

55
00:06:48,854 --> 00:06:51,229
Helsinki, go after him.

56
00:06:52,354 --> 00:06:54,146
- Look after her.
- My friend...

57
00:07:07,271 --> 00:07:10,354
From now on, the rules have changed.
Nobody gets up,

58
00:07:10,646 --> 00:07:14,521
nobody moves, nobody eats
without direct fucking orders.

59
00:07:14,604 --> 00:07:16,229
You're fucked, Denver.

60
00:07:16,937 --> 00:07:18,396
Really fucked.

61
00:07:18,479 --> 00:07:20,854
- I don't believe it.
- Did you say something?

62
00:07:20,937 --> 00:07:21,771
Yes.

63
00:07:22,479 --> 00:07:24,521
You're not invincible anymore.

64
00:07:24,604 --> 00:07:26,312
No. You're not invincible.

65
00:07:26,396 --> 00:07:28,229
They're not invincible!

66
00:07:28,312 --> 00:07:29,646
Arturo, shut up!

67
00:07:30,021 --> 00:07:30,896
Or what?

68
00:07:30,979 --> 00:07:33,812
Or I'll empty the gun
into your fucking head.

69
00:07:33,896 --> 00:07:36,146
- Things have changed around here.
- Yes.

70
00:07:37,021 --> 00:07:41,021
We're here, and now we're the Resistance.

71
00:07:42,812 --> 00:07:46,062
Amanda, Miguel, we're the Resistance, hey?

72
00:07:46,896 --> 00:07:49,729
We're the Resistance. Resistance!

73
00:07:49,812 --> 00:07:52,479
Resistance!

74
00:07:53,062 --> 00:08:01,187
Resistance!

75
00:08:07,812 --> 00:08:09,854
Resistance, my ass.

76
00:08:12,104 --> 00:08:14,687
Everyone, on the fucking ground now!

77
00:08:27,146 --> 00:08:28,521
That's right, Sergio.

78
00:08:28,854 --> 00:08:31,729
We need to know
how the bodyguards will react.

79
00:08:32,312 --> 00:08:33,646
How they react,

80
00:08:33,729 --> 00:08:36,604
how long they'll take
to get the governor to safety,

81
00:08:36,687 --> 00:08:38,187
how they'll spread out...

82
00:08:39,521 --> 00:08:42,521
- It's all in the protocols.
- We have the protocols,

83
00:08:42,687 --> 00:08:43,854
we have the theory,

84
00:08:44,187 --> 00:08:46,562
but we could do with a bit of practice.

85
00:08:48,062 --> 00:08:50,646
And how do you propose
we get that practice?

86
00:08:51,604 --> 00:08:55,521
By creating a minor security crisis
and watching it from inside.

87
00:08:57,521 --> 00:09:01,479
- You're going into the lion's den?
- And the lion will protect me.

88
00:09:08,896 --> 00:09:10,437
Who will you impersonate?

89
00:09:12,521 --> 00:09:14,562
They'll think he's a genius, a big name.

90
00:09:15,437 --> 00:09:17,062
A risk analyst

91
00:09:17,146 --> 00:09:18,979
from Rating Trust Corporation.

92
00:09:19,396 --> 00:09:23,979
Before that, he was at Bacher & Bacher,
and at Standard and Risk before that.

93
00:09:24,729 --> 00:09:29,521
We're going to steal the identity
of someone truly brilliant.

94
00:09:30,521 --> 00:09:34,812
A Spanish guy who has been living
in New York for more than 20 years.

95
00:09:35,312 --> 00:09:36,479
Alfredo Kesmann.

96
00:09:37,062 --> 00:09:38,354
A real genius.

97
00:09:38,812 --> 00:09:42,729
And we have a few great suggestions
for the country's economy.

98
00:09:42,812 --> 00:09:45,146
- The governor will appreciate them.
- Right.

99
00:09:57,729 --> 00:09:59,604
- May I sit down?
- Of course.

100
00:10:00,229 --> 00:10:03,187
But you could also
remain standing for the governor.

101
00:10:05,562 --> 00:10:09,104
- You're the governor's head of security?
- Affirmative.

102
00:10:21,354 --> 00:10:24,937
In a way, you and I do the same thing.

103
00:10:25,812 --> 00:10:27,646
We're both risk analysts.

104
00:10:29,062 --> 00:10:32,396
- We're very similar, don't you think?
- No.

105
00:10:33,104 --> 00:10:34,604
We're not at all alike.

106
00:10:35,729 --> 00:10:38,271
I analyze risks to save lives.

107
00:10:39,396 --> 00:10:40,812
You do it to make money.

108
00:10:42,729 --> 00:10:43,604
It's not the same.

109
00:10:45,271 --> 00:10:46,437
Yes, we're similar.

110
00:10:46,521 --> 00:10:50,229
What's more,
you're very clearheaded and... observant.

111
00:10:57,062 --> 00:11:00,729
What risks do you see
here and now in this office?

112
00:11:00,812 --> 00:11:02,146
Just out of curiosity.

113
00:11:02,229 --> 00:11:07,729
If I could see any risks in this room,
they would no longer exist.

114
00:11:08,729 --> 00:11:09,771
Don't you think?

115
00:11:13,104 --> 00:11:13,937
Mr. Kesmann.

116
00:11:14,021 --> 00:11:15,812
- Good morning.
- How are you?

117
00:11:15,896 --> 00:11:17,729
- Good, thank you.
- Shall we sit down?

118
00:11:17,812 --> 00:11:18,646
Let's.

119
00:11:19,021 --> 00:11:20,979
Would you like some coffee, sir?

120
00:11:21,354 --> 00:11:24,479
A Ceylon tea
with cardamom would be great.

121
00:11:24,562 --> 00:11:27,771
- If not, any black tea is fine. Thanks.
- Of course.

122
00:11:30,104 --> 00:11:32,479
If I had a coffee now, I would go crazy.

123
00:11:39,187 --> 00:11:41,896
You can start your statement. Go ahead.

124
00:11:46,687 --> 00:11:49,354
Before I start,
I'd like to clarify something.

125
00:11:51,271 --> 00:11:53,646
I don't know if it's important, but...

126
00:11:53,937 --> 00:11:57,354
I've been thinking,
and I wanted to ask you something.

127
00:11:58,062 --> 00:12:01,021
- Shoot.
- What's it like when you get home?

128
00:12:02,312 --> 00:12:05,604
I mean, you get home from work,

129
00:12:06,146 --> 00:12:09,021
after torturing a kid like Rio,

130
00:12:09,687 --> 00:12:12,354
who you've had standing up
for days and days

131
00:12:12,729 --> 00:12:15,146
in a cell that's smaller than a closet,

132
00:12:15,229 --> 00:12:16,937
shitting and pissing himself.

133
00:12:18,937 --> 00:12:21,146
And then you go back home, to Germán.

134
00:12:23,854 --> 00:12:24,854
I don't get it.

135
00:12:26,229 --> 00:12:28,979
You don't mind
being called a torturer in the press.

136
00:12:30,354 --> 00:12:31,396
But Germán...

137
00:12:34,437 --> 00:12:36,146
Germán is a good person.

138
00:12:37,062 --> 00:12:39,271
What does he say when you get home?

139
00:12:39,354 --> 00:12:42,271
Does he ask you,
"How was your day, darling?"

140
00:12:43,104 --> 00:12:44,271
And you kiss him...

141
00:12:46,146 --> 00:12:47,187
and you hug him.

142
00:12:47,729 --> 00:12:50,312
What about him?
Does he kiss and hug you back?

143
00:12:50,729 --> 00:12:51,604
Do you fuck?

144
00:12:53,312 --> 00:12:55,521
I think you must make him sick.

145
00:13:06,896 --> 00:13:11,021
The truth is, it has been two months
since Germán hugged me.

146
00:13:12,604 --> 00:13:15,562
He doesn't hug me, or kiss me,
or make love to me.

147
00:13:17,479 --> 00:13:19,521
Not since I had him cremated.

148
00:13:22,062 --> 00:13:26,937
They covered him with a white sheet
and took him down to the hospital morgue,

149
00:13:27,937 --> 00:13:30,187
and that's when the embraces stopped.

150
00:13:33,021 --> 00:13:34,771
What are you talking about?

151
00:13:44,312 --> 00:13:45,271
He's dead.

152
00:13:56,187 --> 00:13:57,062
Cancer...

153
00:13:58,729 --> 00:13:59,771
of the pancreas.

154
00:14:03,479 --> 00:14:07,187
The kind where they give you two months,
and it is two months.

155
00:14:11,104 --> 00:14:14,021
I put on weight, and he lost it.

156
00:14:15,729 --> 00:14:17,854
I was pink, and he was yellow.

157
00:14:22,021 --> 00:14:23,021
It consumed him.

158
00:14:25,062 --> 00:14:26,562
Life grew in me.

159
00:14:27,896 --> 00:14:29,104
Death grew in him.

160
00:14:32,687 --> 00:14:33,854
That's cancer.

161
00:14:36,229 --> 00:14:41,396
Do you know the last thing he said to me?
Can you believe his last words were...

162
00:14:44,771 --> 00:14:45,979
"Turn on the news?"

163
00:14:54,271 --> 00:14:57,271
I thought he was going to give me
one of those talks of his

164
00:14:57,354 --> 00:15:01,312
because, as you know,
he was quite eloquent and so imaginative.

165
00:15:01,562 --> 00:15:05,771
And he said, "Turn on the news."
He was high as a kite on morphine.

166
00:15:05,854 --> 00:15:08,146
So I guess he just lost it.

167
00:15:09,979 --> 00:15:11,062
Then he just died.

168
00:15:26,437 --> 00:15:27,521
I'm really sorry.

169
00:15:31,271 --> 00:15:34,854
- Alicia, let's go outside for a second.
- Yes, coming.

170
00:15:54,187 --> 00:15:57,979
Antoñanzas, stay and watch Murillo.
Don't let anyone in.

171
00:16:10,771 --> 00:16:13,979
For God's sake,
why didn't you say anything before?

172
00:16:15,479 --> 00:16:18,729
What would I have gained? A bit of pity?

173
00:16:20,437 --> 00:16:21,646
Oh, Alicia...

174
00:16:24,646 --> 00:16:28,271
I'm sorry, but I don't think
you're up to leading this case.

175
00:17:59,062 --> 00:18:00,354
I'll take this.

176
00:18:01,271 --> 00:18:02,479
This too.

177
00:18:02,562 --> 00:18:04,062
Easy.

178
00:18:04,146 --> 00:18:05,937
Try and die quietly.

179
00:18:16,979 --> 00:18:19,187
Helsinki!

180
00:18:21,479 --> 00:18:23,187
Hold on! Bogotá!

181
00:18:23,521 --> 00:18:26,396
Bogotá, come to the library!

182
00:18:26,896 --> 00:18:29,021
Helsinki, hold on, please.

183
00:18:29,104 --> 00:18:31,104
- Hold on. Bogotá.
- Go!

184
00:18:37,729 --> 00:18:39,562
Bogotá! Hold on, please.

185
00:18:40,396 --> 00:18:42,146
The library, Bogotá!

186
00:18:44,187 --> 00:18:46,187
Bogotá, quickly!

187
00:18:46,562 --> 00:18:47,396
Help me!

188
00:18:48,062 --> 00:18:50,271
Hold on, Helsinki.

189
00:18:50,687 --> 00:18:53,021
- Quick.
- Come on.

190
00:18:54,104 --> 00:18:56,021
Hold on. Come on!

191
00:18:56,604 --> 00:18:57,521
Hold on!

192
00:18:57,604 --> 00:18:59,396
Cut the rope!

193
00:18:59,479 --> 00:19:00,521
Hold on!

194
00:19:01,729 --> 00:19:05,062
Come on! Cut the rope, dammit!

195
00:19:05,812 --> 00:19:06,687
Hold on.

196
00:19:20,062 --> 00:19:22,646
Gandía!

197
00:19:22,729 --> 00:19:24,687
You son of a bitch!

198
00:19:25,937 --> 00:19:30,437
Silence, for fuck's sake!
I said, nobody talk! Nobody talk!

199
00:19:42,854 --> 00:19:43,979
Amanda.

200
00:19:44,979 --> 00:19:47,104
- How are you feeling?
- Better.

201
00:19:48,021 --> 00:19:49,854
- I feel a bit calmer now.
- Good.

202
00:19:52,312 --> 00:19:54,979
If you want,
we can go back with the others.

203
00:19:55,062 --> 00:19:57,854
There's no rush.
The main thing is for you to get well.

204
00:19:57,937 --> 00:20:00,062
- OK.
- Let me take your pulse.

205
00:20:02,354 --> 00:20:04,479
No, it's still really fast, Amanda.

206
00:20:04,562 --> 00:20:06,479
This is a major anxiety attack.

207
00:20:06,562 --> 00:20:09,021
Do you have fluttering in your chest?

208
00:20:09,104 --> 00:20:12,979
- Well, a little bit.
- That's normal. It's one of the symptoms.

209
00:20:14,104 --> 00:20:15,562
Luckily...

210
00:20:16,604 --> 00:20:18,146
I got something for you.

211
00:20:19,979 --> 00:20:20,854
Here.

212
00:20:20,937 --> 00:20:22,271
This works wonders.

213
00:20:22,854 --> 00:20:24,271
Take three.

214
00:20:24,479 --> 00:20:28,437
- It's not too strong, is it?
- No. A bit stronger than valerian.

215
00:20:28,521 --> 00:20:31,604
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure. I've taken four.

216
00:20:33,271 --> 00:20:34,437
- OK.
- Go ahead.

217
00:20:34,521 --> 00:20:36,104
One at a time.

218
00:20:38,354 --> 00:20:39,521
- Thanks.
- It's OK.

219
00:20:44,437 --> 00:20:47,354
Everyone, listen up, please.

220
00:20:49,021 --> 00:20:49,896
Let's see.

221
00:20:50,979 --> 00:20:55,354
Many of you didn't know my husband,

222
00:20:56,604 --> 00:20:57,562
Germán.

223
00:20:58,604 --> 00:21:01,021
But the colonel thinks this concerns you:

224
00:21:03,104 --> 00:21:04,104
he's passed away.

225
00:21:08,271 --> 00:21:12,354
Tamayo thinks I'm not up to this task.

226
00:21:14,521 --> 00:21:17,729
But the truth is,
there's no one better than me for this.

227
00:21:17,812 --> 00:21:19,479
No one.

228
00:21:23,021 --> 00:21:27,229
Because I don't fucking want to go home.
Or open the fridge.

229
00:21:29,312 --> 00:21:30,312
Or the mailbox...

230
00:21:31,021 --> 00:21:32,479
in case I see his name.

231
00:21:33,354 --> 00:21:34,896
Or the boxes of photos.

232
00:21:38,812 --> 00:21:41,312
So, I'm like fucking Deep Blue,

233
00:21:41,396 --> 00:21:45,062
calculating 200 million moves a minute
against the Professor.

234
00:21:47,854 --> 00:21:49,937
That's what this heist needs.

235
00:21:51,271 --> 00:21:52,854
And it's what I need.

236
00:21:55,771 --> 00:21:57,479
Anyone got anything to say?

237
00:21:59,187 --> 00:22:00,104
No?

238
00:22:00,354 --> 00:22:03,104
Then let's all cheer up a bit.
Back to work.

239
00:22:18,146 --> 00:22:18,979
Rio.

240
00:22:20,146 --> 00:22:21,979
Why the hell didn't you shoot?

241
00:22:23,937 --> 00:22:24,771
I don't know.

242
00:22:28,104 --> 00:22:29,187
I froze.

243
00:22:31,771 --> 00:22:35,479
- And why did you freeze, Rio?
- Because I'm not a fucking killer.

244
00:22:40,562 --> 00:22:42,479
You don't need to be a killer.

245
00:22:43,437 --> 00:22:47,146
I couldn't shoot him in the chest
and pretend nothing happened.

246
00:22:47,229 --> 00:22:48,312
Then shoot his leg!

247
00:22:48,396 --> 00:22:50,521
- I can't!
- Then shoot at the ceiling!

248
00:22:50,604 --> 00:22:53,646
Or the floor!
Wherever it takes to keep him still!

249
00:22:53,729 --> 00:22:56,229
I'm telling you, I couldn't. I froze!

250
00:22:59,771 --> 00:23:01,271
He said he had a family.

251
00:23:02,146 --> 00:23:05,187
He was unarmed. I couldn't.

252
00:23:08,146 --> 00:23:09,312
Why couldn't you?

253
00:23:11,521 --> 00:23:12,646
Tell us why.

254
00:23:15,271 --> 00:23:18,354
He couldn't, because he is traumatized.

255
00:23:18,437 --> 00:23:20,771
I told you, and you fucking ignored me.

256
00:23:20,854 --> 00:23:24,729
And now, because of you,
Helsinki and Nairobi were nearly killed.

257
00:23:24,812 --> 00:23:26,146
Denver, enough!

258
00:23:27,437 --> 00:23:28,687
Rio raised the alarm.

259
00:23:28,771 --> 00:23:31,354
Helsinki and Nairobi are alive.
That's what matters.

260
00:23:31,437 --> 00:23:33,354
You know what matters more?

261
00:23:34,312 --> 00:23:35,437
How did he get free?

262
00:23:36,854 --> 00:23:39,146
- You took Gandía to the bathroom.
- Yes.

263
00:23:39,229 --> 00:23:41,771
- Did you put the cuffs on right?
- Obviously.

264
00:23:41,854 --> 00:23:44,521
"Obviously."

265
00:23:44,604 --> 00:23:47,687
Then obviously,
something doesn't fucking add up.

266
00:23:47,771 --> 00:23:50,729
Tokyo, how does
a guy who is handcuffed escape?

267
00:23:51,729 --> 00:23:53,562
Any ideas, Nairobi?

268
00:23:54,062 --> 00:23:56,062
Any ideas? What?

269
00:23:56,604 --> 00:24:00,771
Nothing, right?
Something smells very fishy to me.

270
00:24:04,229 --> 00:24:05,687
Are you saying I'm a traitor?

271
00:24:05,771 --> 00:24:08,479
- I don't know. You tell me.
- No. You tell me.

272
00:24:09,771 --> 00:24:11,062
It's our fault.

273
00:24:13,604 --> 00:24:18,146
We shouldn't have left
the kid on guard with PTSD.

274
00:24:19,146 --> 00:24:20,437
Rio is no traitor.

275
00:24:22,104 --> 00:24:24,896
We have a more urgent problem.
Listen to me.

276
00:24:24,979 --> 00:24:28,104
The biggest risk is Gandía making contact
with the outside...

277
00:24:28,646 --> 00:24:32,229
and them launching a coordinated attack,
from inside and outside.

278
00:24:32,562 --> 00:24:34,021
What's the plan?

279
00:24:36,354 --> 00:24:37,562
He has to be killed.

280
00:24:40,521 --> 00:24:41,354
Who?

281
00:24:42,729 --> 00:24:43,562
That guy.

282
00:24:45,812 --> 00:24:47,187
We are not murderers.

283
00:24:47,271 --> 00:24:48,771
Then we'll be corpses.

284
00:24:48,854 --> 00:24:52,521
We'll get rid of the bodyguards
during the first hour.

285
00:24:53,062 --> 00:24:56,187
They'll be the ones
who leave with the state secrets.

286
00:24:57,604 --> 00:24:58,937
Problem solved.

287
00:24:59,021 --> 00:25:01,062
Get the fuck out!

288
00:25:01,146 --> 00:25:03,271
That bastard won't go out
with the secrets.

289
00:25:03,354 --> 00:25:04,687
Nobody move.

290
00:25:04,771 --> 00:25:06,312
He won't follow orders.

291
00:25:13,562 --> 00:25:14,521
And Santiago?

292
00:25:16,271 --> 00:25:19,187
- Did he get out after raising hell?
- Yes.

293
00:25:19,896 --> 00:25:23,437
- It looked like an accident.
- The blast was magnificent.

294
00:25:27,562 --> 00:25:30,854
I've brought my agency's
latest reports on country risk.

295
00:25:32,521 --> 00:25:36,312
But...
they don't come out until next month.

296
00:25:36,396 --> 00:25:39,687
We're still working on them,
but these are practically final.

297
00:25:40,812 --> 00:25:42,187
And not encouraging.

298
00:25:42,271 --> 00:25:45,021
They'll damage the risk premium
on your public debt.

299
00:25:45,104 --> 00:25:48,812
- Any suggestions?
- Officially, liquid assets in the bank,

300
00:25:49,437 --> 00:25:51,854
anti-inflationary measures, the usual.

301
00:25:52,771 --> 00:25:56,937
But if I may give you my opinion,
which won't appear in the report...

302
00:25:58,062 --> 00:25:58,896
Gold.

303
00:26:02,604 --> 00:26:05,687
- Excuse me?
- Increase your gold reserves.

304
00:26:05,771 --> 00:26:08,646
It's the only safe-haven asset.
And bring it here...

305
00:26:09,396 --> 00:26:11,146
to the vault in the Bank of Spain.

306
00:26:11,229 --> 00:26:13,604
Only that will support you in the market.

307
00:26:15,146 --> 00:26:16,104
Look...

308
00:26:16,854 --> 00:26:18,812
what happened in 2008 was a joke.

309
00:26:20,312 --> 00:26:22,062
The real debt crisis is coming.

310
00:26:25,687 --> 00:26:27,021
Are you telling me...

311
00:26:28,104 --> 00:26:31,854
to bet the entire national reserve...
on a single color?

312
00:26:32,562 --> 00:26:37,146
No, I'm telling you
to bet on the winning horse: gold.

313
00:26:42,521 --> 00:26:43,562
What's happening?

314
00:26:44,437 --> 00:26:47,146
- Don't worry.
- Was that an explosion?

315
00:26:47,229 --> 00:26:48,979
Security to the governor's office.

316
00:26:49,937 --> 00:26:51,396
Exterior security, it's Gandía.

317
00:26:51,479 --> 00:26:55,812
Activate protocol red. Close the building.

318
00:26:55,896 --> 00:26:57,896
- Anything outside?
- I can't see anything.

319
00:26:57,979 --> 00:26:58,979
Where was the blast?

320
00:26:59,062 --> 00:27:02,187
In the basement, sir.
It may have been a gas pocket.

321
00:27:02,271 --> 00:27:06,146
Copy that. Don't close anything.
We may need to evacuate.

322
00:27:06,229 --> 00:27:09,437
Maximum security alert!
Everyone with their vests on!

323
00:27:09,521 --> 00:27:10,646
Everyone!

324
00:27:24,896 --> 00:27:26,771
They have military weapons in there.

325
00:27:26,854 --> 00:27:30,646
I think he caresses them in the evenings,
longing to pull the trigger.

326
00:27:30,729 --> 00:27:34,479
He was a green beret.
He's been on the job for three years.

327
00:27:34,562 --> 00:27:38,646
He was the minister of the interior's
personal bodyguard before that.

328
00:27:38,937 --> 00:27:41,771
He was deployed on special ops
in Iraq and Lebanon.

329
00:27:41,854 --> 00:27:43,854
Those are just the official ones

330
00:27:43,937 --> 00:27:47,604
because during the six years
he was in special ops,

331
00:27:47,812 --> 00:27:50,812
there are no records of his movements.
That means...

332
00:27:52,354 --> 00:27:54,896
clandestine operations, secret missions...

333
00:27:55,979 --> 00:27:57,812
He's a killer, Sergio.

334
00:27:58,937 --> 00:27:59,854
He's a killer.

335
00:28:05,479 --> 00:28:08,687
- Have you found the gun rack?
- We can't find it.

336
00:28:08,771 --> 00:28:11,812
We've looked everywhere,
but there's no sign of weapons.

337
00:28:11,896 --> 00:28:15,062
I don't know about the guns,
but his cuffs were in the library.

338
00:28:17,312 --> 00:28:19,562
The bastard escaped from them by himself.

339
00:28:19,646 --> 00:28:21,187
Like a child at Disneyland.

340
00:28:22,187 --> 00:28:24,021
We kill him, or he kills us.

341
00:28:25,646 --> 00:28:26,937
I saw him too.

342
00:28:28,312 --> 00:28:30,312
I could see right through him.

343
00:28:31,562 --> 00:28:35,354
If he gets the chance,
it'll be like he's playing a shoot-'em-up.

344
00:28:47,979 --> 00:28:50,896
Faced with the slightest risk,
act decisively.

345
00:28:51,354 --> 00:28:52,729
In self-defense...

346
00:28:54,104 --> 00:28:55,479
but without hesitation.

347
00:28:57,146 --> 00:28:58,687
Because he won't hesitate.

348
00:29:00,812 --> 00:29:02,937
He's an unscrupulous ex-combatant.

349
00:29:04,729 --> 00:29:08,229
He's merciless.
And he's trying to kill you.

350
00:29:08,937 --> 00:29:10,729
What about the command center?

351
00:29:11,021 --> 00:29:13,896
I'll make sure their hands are tied
so they respect the truce.

352
00:29:15,271 --> 00:29:16,104
And also...

353
00:29:19,854 --> 00:29:22,604
I'll make them see
that we're better than ever.

354
00:29:30,104 --> 00:29:30,937
Right.

355
00:29:31,271 --> 00:29:34,979
You need to take long, deep breaths.

356
00:29:39,104 --> 00:29:41,812
Very good. Tell me something you love.

357
00:29:42,229 --> 00:29:43,062
The sea.

358
00:29:43,521 --> 00:29:47,271
The sea is perfect for this exercise.
Close your eyes.

359
00:29:48,646 --> 00:29:50,646
Good. Now, Amanda,

360
00:29:50,729 --> 00:29:53,104
imagine it's a hot summer's day.

361
00:29:54,021 --> 00:29:55,521
You're on the beach,

362
00:29:55,854 --> 00:29:59,687
at the water's edge,
with the waves lapping at your feet.

363
00:30:00,271 --> 00:30:02,937
- Can you feel it?
- Yes, I can.

364
00:30:03,021 --> 00:30:06,104
Now we're floating
on an air mattress in the water.

365
00:30:06,729 --> 00:30:07,896
The sea breeze...

366
00:30:09,979 --> 00:30:11,604
on the shore.

367
00:30:13,771 --> 00:30:15,354
And the smell of summer.

368
00:30:15,437 --> 00:30:17,354
I'm getting sleepy.

369
00:30:17,437 --> 00:30:20,062
Let the sound of the sea carry you away.

370
00:30:20,146 --> 00:30:22,229
Let the sea rock you to sleep.

371
00:30:22,896 --> 00:30:24,271
The sea...

372
00:30:24,354 --> 00:30:25,979
Amanda...

373
00:30:26,354 --> 00:30:27,312
Amanda...

374
00:30:28,479 --> 00:30:29,312
Come.

375
00:31:24,312 --> 00:31:26,812
If you're calling to negotiate, press one.

376
00:31:27,146 --> 00:31:29,646
If you're calling to surrender, press two.

377
00:31:29,896 --> 00:31:33,354
If you're calling to ask what I'm wearing,
press pound.

378
00:31:33,437 --> 00:31:35,312
- I caught you at a good time.
- Yes.

379
00:31:35,396 --> 00:31:37,229
It's a beautiful day.

380
00:31:37,646 --> 00:31:41,146
I'm glad. I wasn't sure how
you'd take the news I'm about to give you.

381
00:31:41,229 --> 00:31:43,979
I just sent an exclusive
to a national newspaper.

382
00:31:44,771 --> 00:31:48,729
They'll call asking you to confirm
that there's a truce. I hope you do.

383
00:31:49,979 --> 00:31:51,729
Why would I do that?

384
00:31:51,812 --> 00:31:55,896
Because if you don't, I'll leak
that you pretended to kill Lisbon,

385
00:31:56,396 --> 00:32:00,937
that she's been illegally held since then,
and you're refusing to take her to court.

386
00:32:01,021 --> 00:32:02,312
Those are trifles.

387
00:32:04,187 --> 00:32:07,187
I also have a recording
of the supposed execution.

388
00:32:07,271 --> 00:32:08,104
Bastard.

389
00:32:08,562 --> 00:32:11,896
I can also tell them you're negotiating
by threatening to arrest

390
00:32:12,729 --> 00:32:14,437
her daughter and mother.

391
00:32:14,521 --> 00:32:16,521
But between you and me...

392
00:32:17,604 --> 00:32:19,146
you're too late for that.

393
00:32:20,604 --> 00:32:23,896
Those three CNI agents
at Katipunan police HQ in Mindanao,

394
00:32:23,979 --> 00:32:26,771
and the Spanish consul,
Mr. Leopoldo Gis Bornay,

395
00:32:26,854 --> 00:32:29,854
arriving in Manila
to coordinate the operation...

396
00:32:30,979 --> 00:32:33,396
Save the taxpayers' money,
and while you're at it,

397
00:32:33,479 --> 00:32:37,604
- save yourselves the embarrassment.
- You love hearing yourself talk.

398
00:32:37,687 --> 00:32:40,521
You're like a radio host.
Get to the point.

399
00:32:41,187 --> 00:32:42,312
What do you want?

400
00:32:43,479 --> 00:32:48,271
I need to be sure about the truce.
I have someone fighting for their life.

401
00:32:51,396 --> 00:32:53,229
Your word isn't enough anymore.

402
00:32:57,271 --> 00:32:59,104
Confirm it with the press.

403
00:33:00,396 --> 00:33:04,729
And in order to prove your goodwill
and boost the morale of everyone inside,

404
00:33:04,812 --> 00:33:06,187
including the hostages,

405
00:33:06,271 --> 00:33:08,854
I'd like to ask for one more thing.

406
00:33:22,979 --> 00:33:26,396
News of the truce
was all over the press in minutes.

407
00:33:29,479 --> 00:33:30,979
The headline was good.

408
00:33:32,229 --> 00:33:33,771
But the photo was better:

409
00:33:38,021 --> 00:33:40,729
the police leaving us eight paellas,

410
00:33:41,021 --> 00:33:43,604
14 loaves of bread
and two cases of wine.

411
00:33:44,021 --> 00:33:46,146
It looked like the start of a party.

412
00:33:46,354 --> 00:33:47,771
This smells so good.

413
00:33:54,604 --> 00:33:57,521
But inside,
it felt like the buildup to a funeral.

414
00:34:05,521 --> 00:34:08,812
What you don't see is usually
more important than what you do see.

415
00:34:08,896 --> 00:34:12,146
And Gandía,
on the verge of screwing our lives up,

416
00:34:12,937 --> 00:34:13,979
was invisible.

417
00:34:14,187 --> 00:34:17,979
Stockholm and Rio swept the first floor.
There's no sign of him. Listen.

418
00:34:18,062 --> 00:34:19,979
The basements are my blind spots.

419
00:34:20,479 --> 00:34:22,896
Helsinki to the east basement,
you to the west.

420
00:35:36,021 --> 00:35:36,854
Tokyo.

421
00:35:37,729 --> 00:35:41,396
I've just lost
the cameras inside the bank. All of them.

422
00:35:44,646 --> 00:35:45,771
You're on your own.

423
00:35:52,729 --> 00:35:56,229
What we don't see affects our lives
much more than it seems.

424
00:36:04,729 --> 00:36:05,979
Nurse.

425
00:36:09,562 --> 00:36:11,187
Let's see how you're doing.

426
00:36:16,021 --> 00:36:18,646
And to think I didn't trust you before.

427
00:36:21,146 --> 00:36:22,021
Why not?

428
00:36:23,521 --> 00:36:26,854
Because you're
from Palermo and Berlin's gang.

429
00:36:29,229 --> 00:36:31,937
And because you act like an Iberian male.

430
00:36:33,646 --> 00:36:35,646
Macho, but a big, strong fellow.

431
00:36:35,979 --> 00:36:37,521
Built like a castle.

432
00:36:38,812 --> 00:36:40,562
He's sensitive is what he is.

433
00:36:42,021 --> 00:36:44,687
I'm going to give you a shot,
Nairobi, honey.

434
00:36:44,937 --> 00:36:45,812
Another one?

435
00:36:46,312 --> 00:36:49,187
- Can't you give her a break?
- They're antibiotics.

436
00:36:49,521 --> 00:36:51,521
She's at risk of infection.

437
00:36:52,812 --> 00:36:54,437
You're awesome, Paquita.

438
00:36:54,979 --> 00:36:57,062
I told her to give me another shot.

439
00:36:58,354 --> 00:37:01,021
Well, if it's on the patient's orders...

440
00:37:06,062 --> 00:37:10,937
You know how I said...
I wouldn't touch you with a ten-foot pole?

441
00:37:14,771 --> 00:37:16,146
I'm reconsidering.

442
00:37:22,521 --> 00:37:25,854
That was a very clear
declaration of your intentions.

443
00:37:26,271 --> 00:37:27,479
Am I wrong, Paquita?

444
00:37:34,562 --> 00:37:38,062
When you said that...
ten-foot pole thing...

445
00:37:41,104 --> 00:37:42,271
you already had me.

446
00:37:45,146 --> 00:37:47,437
Now I can picture you...

447
00:37:48,104 --> 00:37:50,312
all dressed in white.

448
00:37:50,396 --> 00:37:51,979
"I do."

449
00:37:52,062 --> 00:37:54,271
- Wait...
- The reception, the friends,

450
00:37:54,354 --> 00:37:57,062
- the boozing...
- Don't get your hopes up.

451
00:37:57,479 --> 00:38:00,229
You're not having your eighth kid with me.

452
00:38:16,854 --> 00:38:19,854
What we don't see is also
what haunts us the most.

453
00:38:20,812 --> 00:38:21,896
He's not here.

454
00:38:22,271 --> 00:38:27,271
Because once the doubts start...
it's not easy to stop them.

455
00:38:27,354 --> 00:38:28,187
Rio.

456
00:38:30,437 --> 00:38:32,937
Why don't you have scars from the torture?

457
00:38:39,104 --> 00:38:40,854
You haven't even lost weight.

458
00:38:44,312 --> 00:38:45,896
How did Gandía break free?

459
00:38:50,354 --> 00:38:51,979
Why are you asking me that?

460
00:38:58,896 --> 00:39:00,271
Because you lied.

461
00:39:02,021 --> 00:39:06,229
You didn't tell the Professor everything,
and he said to be precise.

462
00:39:10,771 --> 00:39:12,354
Why did you only tell me?

463
00:39:12,896 --> 00:39:13,729
Why?

464
00:39:14,771 --> 00:39:15,604
Why?

465
00:39:19,104 --> 00:39:19,979
Why me?

466
00:39:21,396 --> 00:39:24,187
Because there's so much shit in my head,
I can't sleep.

467
00:39:24,271 --> 00:39:27,104
I didn't want to remember it
or be pitied even more.

468
00:39:27,187 --> 00:39:28,771
I didn't want to describe

469
00:39:28,854 --> 00:39:31,146
how I cried hopelessly in that coffin

470
00:39:31,229 --> 00:39:35,062
and that the only thing I wanted
was to be in my bedroom

471
00:39:35,396 --> 00:39:36,646
and to hug my mother,

472
00:39:36,729 --> 00:39:39,229
who I thought would never know
what happened to me

473
00:39:39,312 --> 00:39:41,521
because she wouldn't have
a grave to visit.

474
00:39:41,604 --> 00:39:42,896
- Rio...
- I cried so much

475
00:39:42,979 --> 00:39:46,104
that I had spasms
and hit my head on the coffin lid.

476
00:39:46,187 --> 00:39:47,521
Sand fell into my eyes,

477
00:39:47,604 --> 00:39:49,062
- and I kept crying.
- Stop.

478
00:39:49,312 --> 00:39:52,271
Is that it?
Is that what you wanted me to tell you?

479
00:39:56,437 --> 00:39:58,937
Forgive me. I'm sorry.

480
00:40:02,312 --> 00:40:04,146
It's OK.

481
00:40:05,812 --> 00:40:06,646
I'm sorry.

482
00:40:08,187 --> 00:40:09,437
Easy.

483
00:40:13,187 --> 00:40:14,229
It's all right.

484
00:40:15,021 --> 00:40:15,979
No, it's not.

485
00:40:16,437 --> 00:40:19,271
Sorry. I'm scared.
I don't know what I'm saying.

486
00:40:21,562 --> 00:40:23,021
I'll make you trust me.

487
00:40:24,854 --> 00:40:25,729
Rio.

488
00:40:28,604 --> 00:40:29,979
What are you gonna do?

489
00:40:33,312 --> 00:40:34,854
I'm going to kill Gandía.

490
00:40:37,521 --> 00:40:39,521
You look for what you don't see.

491
00:40:39,687 --> 00:40:43,396
But sometimes, you forget
the invisible might be watching you.

492
00:40:44,146 --> 00:40:45,979
And then you're in trouble.

493
00:41:12,646 --> 00:41:14,646
Yeah, that's better. Right, babe?

494
00:41:14,729 --> 00:41:17,021
Now we're all cheered up.

495
00:41:17,104 --> 00:41:18,646
Look at those faces.

496
00:41:18,729 --> 00:41:21,729
No one else is going to rebel now, babe.

497
00:41:21,812 --> 00:41:24,812
How wonderful!
What an amazing transformation

498
00:41:24,896 --> 00:41:26,937
with a simple paella and a beer.

499
00:41:27,021 --> 00:41:29,604
A round of applause for the bank robbers.

500
00:41:29,687 --> 00:41:32,396
Stop screwing around
and shut the fuck up, now!

501
00:41:33,396 --> 00:41:34,896
You have to let me go.

502
00:41:35,687 --> 00:41:37,437
I smashed his head in.

503
00:41:37,521 --> 00:41:39,146
Leave me here, tied up,

504
00:41:39,229 --> 00:41:41,771
and it'll be worse than murder.
Free me.

505
00:41:43,896 --> 00:41:46,229
Why would he kill you now?
He didn't before.

506
00:41:47,687 --> 00:41:48,646
Don't worry.

507
00:41:49,021 --> 00:41:50,937
We're looking for him now.

508
00:41:51,604 --> 00:41:55,354
Great. You're looking for him.
That's good to know. Very good.

509
00:41:55,854 --> 00:41:57,521
And it's also good to know

510
00:41:57,854 --> 00:42:00,854
that they put you in charge
of the kids in the nursery.

511
00:42:03,062 --> 00:42:06,729
What a wise decision, huh?
Who made that decision?

512
00:42:12,812 --> 00:42:14,396
She chose Rio.

513
00:42:16,021 --> 00:42:18,854
She chose the IT genius

514
00:42:18,937 --> 00:42:23,021
to go hunt the most dangerous
professional killer in all Spain.

515
00:42:23,687 --> 00:42:24,729
That's brilliant.

516
00:42:26,812 --> 00:42:30,479
A traumatized little boy
who can't even bring himself to shoot.

517
00:42:31,521 --> 00:42:35,646
And he's hand in hand with your ex,
crying in corners around the bank.

518
00:42:35,729 --> 00:42:37,146
What a beautiful story.

519
00:42:39,604 --> 00:42:41,521
He'll kill them, one by one.

520
00:42:41,604 --> 00:42:44,812
When are you going to understand
that Tokyo's in charge?

521
00:42:44,896 --> 00:42:49,062
This isn't about operating on Nairobi.
This is about survival, brother.

522
00:42:50,104 --> 00:42:53,854
- Come here, moron, come here.
- What is it? What do you want now?

523
00:42:56,146 --> 00:42:59,021
Listen, I know you really love Tokyo.

524
00:43:00,521 --> 00:43:02,479
You've been through a lot together.

525
00:43:04,896 --> 00:43:08,479
But do you think
she's the leader we deserve right now?

526
00:43:09,104 --> 00:43:10,937
With your hand on your heart...

527
00:43:15,354 --> 00:43:16,854
do you trust Tokyo?

528
00:43:26,437 --> 00:43:31,062
You have to free me, brother.
You know it's the right thing to do.

529
00:43:31,354 --> 00:43:34,604
You have to take me upstairs.
You have to free me.

530
00:43:36,729 --> 00:43:38,104
Come on. Hey.

531
00:43:38,187 --> 00:43:39,646
Shut up!

532
00:43:40,021 --> 00:43:41,521
Matías, you're in charge.

533
00:43:47,896 --> 00:43:48,771
Almost.

534
00:43:49,479 --> 00:43:52,354
Rio!

535
00:43:52,437 --> 00:43:55,437
- Where are you going?
- To kill that son of a bitch.

536
00:43:55,521 --> 00:43:57,687
Rio, stop. I said stop!

537
00:44:03,979 --> 00:44:05,396
Sorry about before.

538
00:44:06,771 --> 00:44:08,396
I've got a lot going on.

539
00:44:09,396 --> 00:44:12,521
But let me be clear:
I know you're an honorable man.

540
00:44:13,187 --> 00:44:15,021
I know you'd never betray us.

541
00:44:19,562 --> 00:44:22,312
Let's get that bastard together. Let's go.

542
00:45:52,437 --> 00:45:53,771
Hello, National Police.

543
00:45:53,854 --> 00:45:57,604
This is César Gandía, head of security
for the governor of the Bank of Spain.

544
00:45:57,687 --> 00:46:00,396
I'm calling
on a Ministry of the Interior secure line.

545
00:46:00,479 --> 00:46:01,937
Can you see that?

546
00:46:02,021 --> 00:46:04,896
- Yes, it's a line from the Bank of Spain.
- Yes.

547
00:46:04,979 --> 00:46:07,812
Get me the command center
outside the bank.

548
00:46:07,896 --> 00:46:09,271
Top priority.

549
00:46:14,104 --> 00:46:16,062
- Hello?
- This is a top-priority call.

550
00:46:16,146 --> 00:46:17,687
- This is César Gandía.
- Who?

551
00:46:17,771 --> 00:46:21,437
The governor's head of security.
Let me speak to Colonel Tamayo.

552
00:46:21,521 --> 00:46:23,312
Yes, of course. Colonel!

553
00:46:27,187 --> 00:46:29,354
It's the governor's head of security.

554
00:46:29,437 --> 00:46:31,812
- Clear the room.
- Clear the area, please.

555
00:46:32,937 --> 00:46:34,396
Colonel Tamayo speaking.

556
00:46:34,771 --> 00:46:37,521
Colonel, I managed to break free.
It's Gandía.

557
00:46:37,604 --> 00:46:41,604
- Where are you calling from?
- From the panic room.

558
00:46:41,687 --> 00:46:45,146
I can monitor all their movements
with the internal CCTV.

559
00:46:45,229 --> 00:46:48,896
I've cut all external connections
so they can't see us from outside.

560
00:46:48,979 --> 00:46:50,687
I'm awaiting your instructions.

561
00:46:52,646 --> 00:46:56,604
For now, remain inactive.
We have a truce.

562
00:46:56,979 --> 00:46:59,562
What truce, Colonel?
How long is the truce?

563
00:47:01,104 --> 00:47:04,021
There are more than 24 hours left.
I can't get out of it.

564
00:47:04,104 --> 00:47:05,354
It's in the news.

565
00:47:05,437 --> 00:47:08,479
In 24 hours,
these bastards will be in Singapore.

566
00:47:08,562 --> 00:47:11,687
Let's launch a coordinated attack.
We'll take them by surprise.

567
00:47:11,771 --> 00:47:13,646
It'll be over in ten minutes.

568
00:47:14,146 --> 00:47:15,812
My hands are tied.

569
00:47:15,896 --> 00:47:18,896
The Presidency doesn't want
more battles in Madrid.

570
00:47:20,937 --> 00:47:22,896
Sir, I've got automatic weapons,

571
00:47:22,979 --> 00:47:24,312
grenades, everything.

572
00:47:24,396 --> 00:47:27,979
I won't wait for them to escape.
I haven't signed any truce.

573
00:47:28,062 --> 00:47:30,146
Do you understand what I'm saying?

574
00:47:39,604 --> 00:47:43,354
Officially,
I can only command you to wait...

575
00:47:44,187 --> 00:47:46,729
even if that's not
what I'd like you to do.

576
00:47:47,437 --> 00:47:48,854
What does that mean?

577
00:47:49,437 --> 00:47:52,604
Whatever you do
will be considered self-defense.

578
00:47:52,687 --> 00:47:54,437
There will be no legal issues.

579
00:47:54,521 --> 00:47:57,437
If you eliminate them all,
you'd be a hero to me,

580
00:47:57,521 --> 00:48:00,146
to the investigators,
and to the government.

581
00:48:00,687 --> 00:48:01,771
Copy that.

582
00:48:03,021 --> 00:48:03,896
Good luck.

583
00:48:04,562 --> 00:48:06,312
The most important moments

584
00:48:06,396 --> 00:48:09,104
are when we realize there's no going back.

585
00:48:09,687 --> 00:48:12,896
That you've crossed a line,
and there's no way back.

586
00:48:13,646 --> 00:48:15,021
The point of no return.

587
00:48:16,521 --> 00:48:20,562
Everything is about to change,
and you cling to the present...

588
00:48:20,896 --> 00:48:23,104
as if you could stop the disaster.

589
00:48:25,604 --> 00:48:27,187
How are you doing?

590
00:48:27,771 --> 00:48:29,854
I guess it won't come as a surprise...

591
00:48:32,229 --> 00:48:33,729
but we arrived in Mindanao,

592
00:48:33,812 --> 00:48:37,187
and your mother and daughter
were no longer there. Ta-da!

593
00:48:39,187 --> 00:48:43,896
I'd congratulate you... but you know what?

594
00:48:46,062 --> 00:48:46,896
I won't.

595
00:48:47,437 --> 00:48:51,229
Because Rio,
before he went into the bank,

596
00:48:52,021 --> 00:48:54,396
gave up all the carriers.

597
00:49:01,396 --> 00:49:03,646
He didn't tell the Professor.

598
00:49:04,604 --> 00:49:06,146
I was listening.

599
00:49:21,021 --> 00:49:24,687
How quickly do you think
he'll give me your mom and daughter?

600
00:49:41,937 --> 00:49:43,937
- Professor.
- Yes, Antoñanzas?

601
00:49:44,729 --> 00:49:47,104
I know I shouldn't tell you this, but...

602
00:49:49,979 --> 00:49:50,812
But what?

603
00:50:03,979 --> 00:50:06,271
There will be casualties,
Tamayo's orders.

604
00:50:06,354 --> 00:50:08,896
- In cold blood. It's a crime.
- What's going on?

605
00:50:09,396 --> 00:50:12,312
Gandía, the head of security,
called the tent.

606
00:50:12,396 --> 00:50:16,229
- He has a panic room and military weapons.
- Where is the room?

607
00:50:17,146 --> 00:50:20,312
I don't know, but it has cameras.
He can see everything.

608
00:50:34,104 --> 00:50:34,979
Tokyo.

609
00:50:36,729 --> 00:50:38,521
- Tokyo.
- Professor.

610
00:50:38,604 --> 00:50:42,396
Listen to me.
Gandía is armed. He has a panic room.

611
00:50:43,521 --> 00:50:46,271
- What?
- He has a panic room.

612
00:50:46,354 --> 00:50:50,312
He's watching. He knows where you all are.
Get everyone together.

613
00:50:53,396 --> 00:50:54,229
Tokyo?

614
00:51:05,062 --> 00:51:05,937
Tokyo?

615
00:51:08,729 --> 00:51:10,854
Tokyo?

