["Friday I'm in Love"
by Phoebe Bridgers playing]
♪ I don't care if Monday's blue ♪
♪ Tuesday's gray and Wednesday too ♪
♪ Thursday, I don't care about you
It's Friday, I'm in love ♪
♪ Monday you can fall apart ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday, break my heart ♪
♪ Thursday doesn't even start... ♪
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ ...I'm in love ♪
♪ Saturday, wait ♪
♪ Sunday always comes too late ♪
♪ Friday, never hesitate ♪
♪ I don't care if Monday's black ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday, heart attack
Oh, Thursday never... ♪
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ It's Friday, I'm in love ♪
[song continues]
♪ Monday you can hold your head ♪
♪ Tuesday, Wednesday... ♪
[Tokyo] Locked up for 100 hours,
trapped, about to be killed,
and having lost a best friend,
it feels like 100 years have gone by.
♪ Saturday, wait... ♪
And just going outside
feels like the biggest freedom
in the world.
It doesn't matter
that thousands of guns are pointed at you.
Unarmed,
barefoot,
with the sun on your face,
wrapped in silence,
you feel free.
♪ Smile at the sound ♪
♪ As sleek as a shriek
Spinning round and round ♪
♪ Always take a big bite... ♪
We were sending a message of hope.
There she was,
Lisbon, walking out of the bank with us.
She wasn't at the National Court
or in prison like everyone thought.
Colonel Tamayo!
We have a white flag!
[Tokyo] We were showing them
if we were capable of doing that,
we could do anything.
And the people
began to believe in miracles.
[song ends abruptly]
["My Life Is Going On"
by Cecilia Krull playing]
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong
I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
[breathes angrily]
One minute, Suárez! In one minute
I want your whole team ready.
I want a clean operation!
Priority is those three bitches.
Then worry about the hostages.
I want them here!
I don't care how you do it!
[Suárez] You heard him.
Everyone get ready to go in. Make sure...
- We can't do that, Tamayo.
- She pissed in our faces, Ángel.
I have to take them out,
no matter what the cost.
30 seconds, Suárez!
They're waving a white flag. It's been
a symbol of peace since the Punic Wars.
Even the Nazis respected it.
Are we gonna pretend we didn't see it
in front of the whole world?
Sir, prepped and ready.
[background chatter]
- Colonel, your orders.
- I heard you! I'm trying to think here.
- If we go to talk, we look like shitheads.
- No.
What we have to do is show everyone
who the good guys
and bad guys are in this war.
It's an opportunity for them
but for us as well.
We have to project a positive image.
No tie. No jacket. No bullet-proof vest.
And roll up your sleeves.
But I'll look like a total bitch.
You'll look solid as a rock, Tamayo.
You gotta be tough, all right?
Give them an ultimatum.
We go in in two minutes.
We need to make sure
they're panicking in there.
They gotta know they're fucked.
You've given me a hard-on, Angelito.
Get me a security detail so I can go out
and negotiate with those three.
[crowd boos]
- [soldier 1] Go get them.
- [soldier 2] Good luck.
[whispers] Governor.
What's the deal with the military?
[governor] This is not
a civil conflict anymore.
Two battalions, strike forces...
They're coming in.
[sighs] It's about time.
[governor] No, this isn't good.
The police see us as hostages.
But to the army, we're collateral damage.
[crowd boos and whistles]
[soldier] Leaving security perimeter.
What's that supposed to mean exactly?
That means they'll shoot anyone
wearing a mask.
[tense music playing]
Their priority is to kill them,
not to rescue any of us.
[tense music builds]
[music ends abruptly]
It looks like
The Three Graces have arrived
to give a gentle touch to the heist.
We're out here without masks
so everyone can see
that I'm not at the National Court,
and I'm not being held in a tent
for questioning or in jail.
- Okay, what the fuck do you want?
- Gandía's injured.
I need to show you this.
- [guns cock]
- [call to alert]
[tense music plays]
Raise your hand.
Let's see if they'll follow your orders.
[crowd chanting in background]
Palermo.
Showtime, my precious reptile.
- Come on, come on.
- [Gandía grunts, pants]
There's a shard lodged
between cervical vertebrae C3, 4, and 5.
One wrong move
and his arm will stop moving forever.
Or maybe his lungs.
It's a thing called the phrenic nerve.
He needs a neurosurgeon
as soon as possible.
Maybe one from the army.
You've got someone here.
Come on, what are we waiting for?
Let's make a run for the tent. Right now!
Nobody's gonna shoot us.
We can't risk going back inside the bank.
- Of course we have to go back.
- Huh?
The other hostages have no idea.
Well, they're gonna find out.
It's every man for himself
over here, Mr. Governor.
We have to. We have a moral obligation.
You came in here to be a hero, didn't you?
Well, now's your moment.
If I send a doctor in, I'll have to wait
three or four hours to send the army,
which is something
you know I'm going to do.
That's why you're pulling
the only card you have. Gandía's injury.
You're gonna let a man
who's been loyal to you be paralyzed?
Mmm. Let him out. I'll take care of him.
I get nothing out of that, Tamayo.
Yes, you do.
Allow me to explain.
If you don't let him out,
I go in immediately.
But if you do let him out,
I could wait for an hour while he tells me
the details of your little shit show.
Your decision.
Give me a minute to discuss this
with the rest of my team.
[Tamayo] Of course.
Looks like I'm leaving
before you do, Sandokan.
[tense music builds]
What the fuck are you doing, Bogotá?
[Tokyo] At that moment...
We gotta release Gandía.
We really need that hour.
...Lisbon was the only one
who noticed a small detail...
Lisbon?
...something that would radically change
how we played the game.
They don't have the Professor.
- What?
He came here to give us an ultimatum
but he didn't even use his best move.
If you had the option to checkmate
in one move and you don't do it...
Then it's because you don't know
that you can.
Exactly.
Sierra's working alone.
I'm beginning to like
that fucking nutcase.
Get Gandía ready.
[sinister music plays]
[music booms]
I'm gonna throw a couple punches
at this piece of shit.
[Palermo] Bogotá, stop!
Even with these shards in my back,
I'm going to kick your ass.
For fuck's sake, Bogotá!
We're releasing him.
He can't be beat to shit.
We're not, we're releasing his corpse.
Go on, the minister's gonna be waiting
for me with a medal.
Shut up, you son of a bitch!
Every time you hit him, you're hitting us.
You're gonna screw us
'cause of your pride.
We're already screwed.
This won't change a thing.
All we have left is our dignity.
You wanna get your revenge.
Revenge is an act of selfishness,
you know that.
It's respect.
It's respect for ourselves.
It's respect for the person he executed.
- That's what it is.
- [Rio] I'm with him!
Are you all fucking crazy or what?
Lisbon told us she's letting him go.
She's out there buying us time.
I don't know Lisbon,
but I did know Nairobi.
They're about to kill us,
but we're getting rid of him before that.
Oh, now you're killing him? Now, huh?
Now you're the piece of shit
yelling in the back "Kill him"?
When you had the chance, you couldn't.
You didn't have the balls.
You just stood there, trembling.
Cut the fucking bullshit!
You're gonna
beat each other up now too? [laughs]
Okay, asshole, now you're accusing me?
The only one to blame here is him.
He pulled the trigger.
That bastard over there did it
because he wanted to.
So leave me the fuck alone.
Do you want me
to take some flowers to the morgue?
I'm sure your little friend
is still nice and warm.
And still plenty tight.
What would you do if he killed Stockholm?
You beat the shit out of Arturo
and he just teased you.
That motherfucker over there killed her.
What, so you get a free pass
but no one else does?
Do whatever the fuck you want.
Is it that important to you?
Palermo,
I have to do it
or I can't look you in the eyes.
He's all yours.
[tense music plays]
[Gandía screams]
[grunts and exhales]
Let's enjoy recess
before the girls come back.
[laughs]
- Let's find out.
- Okay.
We will release Gandía.
Before I do, I need to ask the Professor.
You go ahead and ask
whatever you need to ask.
You've got four minutes.
And what do you propose we do?
We need to organize an escape.
With 10, 15, or 20 hostages.
We have a deal.
We take them somewhere secure.
[crowd boos and shouts in background]
[tense action music plays]
You know there's no such thing
as somewhere secure in there.
Of course there is.
[whispers] Come on, come on.
For example, any of the four vaults
that only open with my fingerprints.
- [tense music plays]
- Hit me.
I said hit me.
[yells] Come on, hit me!
[strident music plays]
You know why I'm gonna kill you?
Because I groped
your girlfriend's nice ass?
[whispers] No.
Because you're a fascist.
[strident music plays]
As soon as you lift a gun
to defend your country,
every dumbass
is ready to call you a fascist.
[Lisbon] Doors!
[Bogotá] Because you called her "mutt."
"Gypsy."
Oh shit!
- Close the doors! Make a line!
- Get back! Come on!
- I said get back!
- "Melon seller!"
- [Tokyo] Against the wall! Hands up!
- Stop now!
Because you called Palermo
"one-eyed queer."
[grunting]
Right now!
- [Palermo] Stay out of it!
- Stop it!
And "sudaca!"
- What are you doing?
- You're racist!
We're trying to come up with a miracle
and you start a fight?
You're sexist!
- Make them stop!
- No!
You're a homophobe!
[grunts]
And this one is for Nairobi.
Bogotá, Bogotá, hey.
[whispers] Bogotá.
He killed Nairobi.
The police don't have the Professor.
[tense music playing]
Nairobi wouldn't want this.
[Gandía grunts]
Tamayo doesn't know
about the Professor. It's not checkmate.
We still have a chance.
- He killed her.
- Let him go.
- [Bogotá sobs]
[grunts]
I still make you horny, don't I?
Tokyo...
you missed it.
Boom.
[tense music builds]
[Tokyo screams]
Come on, children. Playtime is over!
- Stitch him up.
- I'll rip you apart, motherfucker!
She was the one that knocked me down,
fucking Sandokan!
Not you! Not you!
[Arturo] On the ground,
you fucking terrorists!
[panicked screaming]
[yelling]
[crying and screaming]
- Let's go, come on! Hurry!
- Get 'em the hell out of here!
[screaming]
- Denver! Are you okay?
- Denver!
- [shooting]
- [screaming]
That son of a bitch.
[glass shatters]
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Stay calm.
Let me see the wound.
- [hostage panting]
- Don't worry.
It's okay.
There's an exit wound,
I need the surgical kit!
- Get it now!
- Okay.
- Go get the kit. Your gun, come on!
- [hostage grunts]
Helsinki, Manila, the hostages escaped.
They hit Denver and some of their own.
They're armed!
Copy that.
Come on!
Matías, you stay here,
don't let anyone move.
[action music plays]
Let's go!
Let me see.
Fucker!
Wait, Denver. Denver.
Take care of Gandía, he's our priority!
Denver!
Shit!
I want a medical unit by the entrance now!
The head of security of the Bank of Spain
is coming out and his prognosis is grave.
Let's go!
After that, I want you to go into action.
- You're in charge of the intervention.
- Mm-hmm. With which team?
Special Forces Unit III.
You know most of them. They're the best.
- Cañizo!
- At your order, sir!
- Get your men ready to go fucking dancing.
- Yes, sir.
- Anything from the recording?
- [Martínez] Sounds like a gunfight.
I told you I'd go in with my team.
That's who I want.
The guys you demanded
are completely out of the question.
[clears throat]
Colonel,
this is going to be a massacre.
I need men
who won't ask who's behind the mask
when they have to pull the trigger.
Special Forces will ask questions
because somewhere in their brains
hides the deep-seated notion
of rescuing hostages.
I need people who are gonna get in there
to conquer territory, not to save lives.
How many civilian casualties
are we talking about?
Well, if I were you,
I wouldn't count on more than...
30% survivors.
Either I go in with my team, or I won't.
Your team?
Mateo Canalejas,
arrested for playing Russian roulette
with his service weapon
in a bar in Tbilisi.
Arantxa Arteche organized
illegal monkey fights in Gibraltar.
For fuck's sake.
Salvador Torrecilla
pretended to be kidnapped by Boko Haram
after spending six days copulating
with the chancellor's daughter in Mali.
Want some more? Because your trusted
bomb expert, Ramiro Vázquez,
is in a mental hospital in Mondragón.
I'm informed about every detail.
They're outside if you wanna meet them.
I reached out to them
when the Professor started dropping money.
Should I go get them,
Colonel?
[soft rock music plays]
Sagasta!
Stop trying to piss me off.
- [rock music plays]
- [dramatic laughter]
[sighs]
[governor] Go to the right!
Palermo! Let's see those balls you've got!
[screaming and crying]
[action music plays]
[Arturo yelling]
Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
- Shoot their vests, go!
- Move fast!
- Get down.
- Helsinki, they're coming.
On the ground now!
Do you copy, fatty?
[hostages yelling]
Cover me!
Lisbon!
[grunts]
We're trapped!
There's nowhere we can escape.
I can't die!
We're not gonna be able
to make it to the vaults,
but we can get them out
through the loading dock.
- Okay, how?
- It's just through the next door.
Covering fire! Let's go!
[hostages yelling]
- [Denver] Motherfucker!
- Damn it!
[speaking Serbian]
- They're heading to the loading docks.
- Tokyo, Denver, Manila, follow them!
Palermo, with me.
We'll go through the other door.
Helsinki, go to the top floor.
Report any kind of troop movement,
weapons, ammo, men, all of it.
- I wanna know when they're coming.
- Let's go.
Come on.
Matías, take five of the hostages!
Let's go!
[Helsinki] Let's go!
- Library, now!
- [hostages scream]
Let's go!
Inspector.
We were correct.
It's confirmed, it was a shooting.
[tense music plays]
- [unintelligible chatter]
- [crying]
Here.
Fuck!
[tense music continues]
Get down, get down.
Okay, let's go.
Get back!
- Shoot the vests.
- Okay.
Get inside!
Come on!
[shouting and grunting]
Damn it.
We're so fucked.
Come on guys, with me.
[music builds and ends abruptly]
- They blocked off the exit with steel...
- [Arturo] Shit.
...and with explosives.
No, they're the ones
that are fucked here, Mr. Governor.
It looks like we've got all their arsenal.
[music intensifies and ends abruptly]
[camera clicks]
My name is Alicia Sierra.
I'm an inspector for the National Police.
And there's a warrant out for my arrest.
I'm forced to record this video
in case the police or the CNI
try to hide, distort, or misrepresent
the reality of the situation.
That's not gonna bring me down,
because today is a day of celebration.
We are here. Let's see who's here with me.
I can't believe it.
Right now, we're in the hiding hole
of this smart little animal,
the Professor.
Señor Marquina, say "hi" to the camera.
Señor Marquina?
- I don't think it's necessary.
- [Alicia] It is.
Okay, tell us, señor Professor,
who arrested you?
- You did.
- You, who?
I need you to do your part here.
I've been arrested
by Inspector Alicia Sierra.
[sighs] Exactly right.
I swear on the baby Jesus.
Me, Alicia Sierra,
at 9:50 a.m., April 8th,
located the Professor's
abandoned stormwater tank.
At kilometer 21,
I simply got off the highway...
Can I tell you the truth?
I'd like to tell you the truth.
Absolutely.
[suspenseful music plays]
As a part of our Plan Paris,
I recruited someone from the police.
And the person we recruited
was Mr. Benito Antoñanzas.
Officer Antoñanzas jumped
into his building's swimming pool
out of one of the windows
of his apartment,
specifically, the bathroom window.
Um... and that
is when he began to work with us.
In his defense,
we made him fear for his life
and that of his family.
Shut up for fuck's sake. Really?
What did you have for lunch, a parrot?
Why are you running your mouth?
[Professor] I'm trying to
get the facts straight and tell the truth.
[Alicia] The truth? What truth?
You weren't even honest with your brother,
you piece of shit.
- What are you doing?
- That's why now's the right moment...
Oh, you bastard.
Keep your fucking mouth shut!
Marseille!
Listen, I'll blow your fucking head off.
Shut your mouth.
Hey, Marseille!
I'm in here, it's a code red!
Marseille and Benjamín!
Marseille, here!
[Alicia grunts]
[threatening music plays]
[chains rattle]
Ah, fuck.
[Alicia] Here we go.
Marseille, it's the police!
Marseille, the police are here!
I'm not the fucking police, four-eyes.
[music ends]
Marseille... [pants]
Mars... [pants] Mar... [pants]
[tense music plays]
- You need a tourniquet.
- I'm fine.
Amanda, Miguel, rifles. Get the rifles!
Come on, you can do it.
You two, let's go!
[gun loads]
The windows.
You two, you two.
Cover the windows.
- Do you even know what you're doing?
- Perfectly well. What has to be done.
I don't think so.
[tense music builds]
The window!
[shouts]
Get back! Cover!
[pants]
Stop this now.
You got two people injured here.
Yeah, but I saved another four,
and now we have their arsenal.
Look at me!
They're both fathers.
They both have families.
It wasn't my fault.
It was that Goddamn recoil.
It's just collateral damage.
We're in the middle of a Goddamn war!
Churchill would see it as a victory.
Ammunition?
[dramatic music plays]
- Only two clips.
- [Tokyo] What?
We can't cover this entire corridor
with two fucking clips.
For fuck's sake.
We gotta blow one of the charges.
If you blow the arsenal from the inside,
the entire building will collapse.
[Palermo] Not a great idea.
We need some grenades.
Where the fuck do we get grenades?
[grunts in pain]
I know where to find grenades.
And a lot more.
Palermo, distract them.
Don't let them suspect we're gone. Lisbon...
[Palermo] Good luck!
[uplifting music plays]
There's been a shooting
inside the building.
Something critical is going on.
I'll tell you what's going on.
The Plan Valencia or Beijing.
They're putting on a show.
They're throwing firecrackers
so we change our strategy.
It's battle rifles. Windows have been hit.
There are civilians in there.
- Suárez, please.
- Colonel.
Are you setting up
an intervention behind my back?
- What if I was? Would that be a problem?
- This is a civil conflict.
I demand to be part of any intervention.
You demand?
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Sir, I'm the inspector in charge
of this country's special operations.
And though you try to diminish us,
let me remind you
we're the team that took down Berlin.
We got him when he had a Browning.
[sighs]
[Tamayo] Sagasta!
Sagasta, go in with your men. Right now!
[action music plays]
[pants]
It's okay.
Rio! Come with me.
[yells]
- [grunts] God damn it!
- [Manila] Hold on, hold on, hold on!
You are really
a colossal son of a bitch, Denver.
Huh?
The other heist, the good one...
I can't believe you kicked me out of that.
Suddenly, you felt like inviting me
to this one, this fucking disaster!
I'm doing this because I'm a good person.
We both know
I should be kicking you in the balls!
- [laughs and grunts]
- [laughs]
Get the fuck away from me!
[shooting in background]
[pants]
Denver!
When you left you were bleeding
like a pig. You gotta come back.
Okay. Your arm's gonna go a little numb,
but it's nothing, okay?
Come on, go.
- What are you doing with that?
- I'm gonna make them dance.
Didn't you say we needed to be heroes?
That's exactly what I'm gonna do here now.
We have the hostages in the armory,
and we've got two fucking clips left.
I'm not going anywhere.
There's no point in attacking them now.
We have all their weapons.
It's a matter of time
before the army gets here.
Sweetie. Dani, sweetie,
you need to come back here.
I'm fine, okay? I'm honestly fine.
You're not fine.
[static]
Our task now is to defend this position
using our intelligence.
[laughs]
Defend? Like the Italians? Huh?
Even though we have
little Messi on our team? [pants]
And Neymar?
And Cristiano Ronaldo?
No, Governor.
We're not defending here. God no.
We're playing tiki-taka!
Come on, kids. Take cover.
Your turn.
[tense music plays]
[crying]
- [Palermo] Grenade!
- It's a grenade!
[suspenseful music builds
and ends abruptly]
[high-pitched ringing]
[muffled audio]
[Denver] Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Bad!
Arturo!
I'm going to rip your fucking balls off!
- They're right here, come and get 'em!
- [pants angrily]
Why don't you come and see me sometime?
[raucous music plays]
[shooting]
[action music plays]
Oh shit.
- [Lisbon] Are you okay?
- No!
They've got enough ammo for five wars!
We're fucked!
What is this?
What are you doing? That's a flamethrower.
A flamethrower, huh?
Everything in this room
is flammable and explosive!
Don't worry, Mr. Governor.
The barbecue's gonna be outside.
[Professor] ...is for all of you
who see this mask
as a symbol of resistance.
We need you.
The State has declared war on us.
- A filthy war.
- [gate squeaks]
[quiet suspenseful music plays]
Professor?
[Professor] We've decided
to stand up to them.
[grunts]
[Professor] The police have arrested
one of us in a foreign country.
Aníbal Cortés.
It's been more than two months
since his arrest.
And no formal charges have been made.
Professor?
They haven't requested extradition.
Marseille. The toilet.
- They haven't provided a lawyer.
- Go and look.
He's being held captive...
Hello? Anyone in there?
...in some unknown place.
And in all likelihood,
they are torturing him.
So we are demanding
that his illegal detention
be brought to an end right now.
And that he's brought to justice
while respecting legal standards.
- The State began this war...
- Benjamín.
...and we're not going to hide.
He's sleeping.
- [shushes]
- We're going to fight...
[sighs in relief]
...blow
by blow.
And this time...
[door squeaks]
...the heist will be even bigger.
[whispering] You did
a good job, Professor.
[suspenseful music plays]
[music booms]
[Marseille groans]
- [metal thuds]
- [glass shatters]
[suspenseful music continues]
[discreet footsteps approaching]
[music intensifies]
[Alicia] Next I'm gonna unload
the entire clip through the door.
I suggest you slide your gun to me
and come out.
Very well.
Three, two,
one.
[door squeaks]
Who the fuck are you?
- Logroño?
- No...
No city name [hesitates]. No...
I don't have one.
[action music plays]
Shit! The cylinder's out of oxygen. On it.
Okay, so...
[oxygen flows]
It's filling up. It'll take a minute.
[silence]
You know that I let you break up with me.
You didn't get to hear what I had to say.
You're not leaving this place without me.
You know that, right?
[soft music plays]
You might have to kidnap me.
[chuckles quietly]
That's not a cool way
to restart a relationship.
It'd be kinda fun though.
I just learned
new tricks about kidnapping.
You know, tying people up.
[oxygen tank clicks]
Are you gonna cut the steel
or flirt with me?
I can do two things at the same time.
Hell, maybe even three.
[chuckles]
[tense music plays]
You three, in the front jeep, come on!
Let's go, go, go, go, go!
This is Helsinki.
There's some movement outside.
Looks like Special Forces.
They're going in heavy, lots of guns.
A C90 rocket launcher,
grenade launchers, machine guns,
shotguns, rifles.
[soldier] Come on, let's go!
They're getting in two jeeps.
Shit, they're going in right now.
Bogotá, this is Lisbon.
Release Gandía immediately.
If we get him out now, he'll tell them
we're chasing the hostages.
If we don't, they'll just waltz in here!
We don't have any weapons.
The hostages took them all.
[tense music plays]
Hey! Cover me! All of you!
[Lisbon] Shit!
[Denver] God!
[Denver] Fuck!
[Arturo] Denver!
I'm the father of Cincinnati!
Motherfucker.
[Arturo] I got a little present for ya!
- Who's the father? I don't get it.
- Shut it or I'll staple your mouth.
[Arturo] Come here!
[Arturo screams]
- [soldier 1] Area secured.
- [soldier 2] All clear.
- [Tamayo] Prepare to enter.
- We're clear, Colonel.
[Suárez] Green light. We can proceed.
Right now!
[hard rock music plays]
- [stapler clicks]
- Ready.
Come on.
[Arturo screams]
[crowd clamors]
[grunts]
Son of a bitch!
Arturito!
Do you believe in reincarnation?
If you don't, you should be negotiating.
How long can you hold your breath?
I can hold my breath as long as it takes
to fuck the cunt of your whore mother.
[laughs] Let's see if that's sufficient.
[raucous music plays]
Fentanyl.
They're opening the doors.
Let's see if this knocks you out, champ.
The hostages! [coughs] The hostages!
- What the fuck is going on?
- The hostages are... [coughs]
The hostages...
Abort the intervention!
The hostages are...
Confirmed, Colonel.
It's Gandía.
It's Gandía, Colonel. It's Gandía.
Sagasta, abort the operation
until further notice.
[music ends]
[gasps for air] The hostages...
[Arturo] Denver.
I know you're listening.
Do you think she loves you?
Denver?
No.
You're not man enough for that woman.
She would always say
that I taught her what love is.
Did she ever tell you
something like that? No.
You know why?
'Cause you don't have
half the brains I have.
And you can never get where I got.
This is revenge, it's personal.
You're just putting all of us at risk!
Shut it!
I know that kid
like I gave birth to him myself.
[pants] I know where I have to poke him
so that he loses his cool.
That's what I'm gonna do.
And when he comes out,
I'll turn him into ashes.
With me...
With me she never wondered,
"What am I doing with this guy?"
Never.
And I was married, you know?
And she knew that.
But we couldn't stay apart,
not even for a minute.
You could literally see
the sparks fly, man.
Right there, between us,
every time we met by the coffee machine.
I need you to give me your gun.
We were doing it all the time.
In every single corner.
One year...
and another.
I mean, we made love everywhere, Denver.
It didn't matter where it was.
Under the money-printing machine,
or in the cafeteria restroom,
or in my own office. [laughs]
Or on top of the coin displays.
[dramatic music plays]
It didn't matter.
And every night...
Every night, as soon as she got home,
she would send me these beautiful texts,
she would send pictures...
[sobs]
...and she would say, she would swear to me
that she never felt like that before
and she couldn't live without me.
Denver,
did she ever say
anything like that about you?
Huh? I know she hasn't.
- Give me the walkie.
- Leave it.
[Arturo] Why didn't you have
another child, huh? Your own child!
You stole her from me, you son of a bitch!
You had to fucking kidnap her!
And when she came to her senses,
she was in the middle of nowhere,
condemned to spend her entire life
with a fucking moron!
[Denver yells]
Are you fucking crazy?
[both scream]
Come on!
- Keep your fucking cool, Denver!
- [Arturo] Fuck!
[pants]
Tokyo is about to come here
with a grenade.
Calm down.
Sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[pants]
Weapons!
They have more weapons.
Fuck!
Change of plans!
You two, get those shields
and put the Browning
on top of that forklift. Come on!
[Tokyo exhales]
There's no military logic
in choosing to abandon our position.
[machine clicks]
We have no chance
of beating them if we leave.
Listen carefully
because I'm not gonna say it twice.
They're counterattacking,
you heard them yourself.
They have more weapons.
[tense music plays]
As soon as they bring them here,
this will turn into a rattrap.
We'll be totally fucked!
[tense music plays]
[metal rattles]
I already told you, let's act now.
Right now!
- Let's do it.
- [gun cocks]
[frenetic music plays]
They're not covering the windows.
We can't wait any longer.
We have to go in right now, let's go!
[engine roars]
- What the fuck is this?
- [Palermo] Take cover!
[Arturo] Open!
[shooting]
- [yelling]
- Close!
Open!
[music intensifies]
I'm on my last clip!
[yelling]
Close!
Open!
[Lisbon] Shit!
I'm out of ammo!
[Stockholm grunts]
Arturo!
[music ends]
[Stockholm pants]
Mónica...
Calm down.
Huh? [pants]
[Stockholm] Don't move or I'll kill him!
On your knees!
Come on, get down.
[Arturo] Don't do
something stupid you're gonna regret.
[pants] Put the gun down, please.
[gun cocks]
'Cause you're not gonna shoot me,
right?
You would never shoot
the father of your child.
Do you know how I know?
I'm the only one who will
be able to be there for your child
when this thing is all over.
- The only one who's not gonna shame him.
- Lie down on the floor!
Don't you understand? [pants]
Don't you realize it?
Stop trying to be someone you're not.
You'll never be one of them.
- You'll always be a secret...
- [gun fires]
[grunts]
- [grunts]
[body hits ground]
[dramatic music plays]
[music builds]
[music ends abruptly]
[mysterious music plays]