1
00:00:19,854 --> 00:00:21,396
Any news on the rooftop?

2
00:00:22,104 --> 00:00:23,896
All in order here, sir.

3
00:00:30,521 --> 00:00:31,354
Suárez.

4
00:00:32,896 --> 00:00:33,979
Martínez!

5
00:00:35,646 --> 00:00:37,562
Colonel, it's Gandía.

6
00:00:38,854 --> 00:00:40,104
Gandía, I'm here.

7
00:00:40,187 --> 00:00:41,187
Colonel,

8
00:00:41,812 --> 00:00:44,104
I've eliminated Nairobi and Tokyo.

9
00:00:44,896 --> 00:00:46,646
I'm launching another attack.

10
00:00:46,729 --> 00:00:49,229
- I'll take a radio. This is the frequency.
- Radio!

11
00:00:51,979 --> 00:00:55,437
- I want all units on alert.
- Alpha and Beta units, get ready.

12
00:00:55,521 --> 00:00:58,146
- Everyone ready and on alert.
- Go.

13
00:01:01,229 --> 00:01:02,562
Everyone ready.

14
00:01:04,479 --> 00:01:06,021
Colonel, they're shooting!

15
00:01:07,896 --> 00:01:10,687
Gandía, answer me.

16
00:01:10,771 --> 00:01:12,021
Gandía, do you copy?

17
00:01:12,104 --> 00:01:13,312
Gandía here.

18
00:01:13,396 --> 00:01:16,604
They're closing in on me.
I'm caught in the cross fire.

19
00:01:16,896 --> 00:01:19,146
Where are you? Can we give cover fire?

20
00:01:19,229 --> 00:01:22,021
Negative, Colonel. I'm going to the roof.

21
00:01:22,104 --> 00:01:23,312
I request evacuation!

22
00:01:23,396 --> 00:01:25,729
Suárez, send a helicopter, now.

23
00:01:25,812 --> 00:01:27,854
- Come on!
- Delta 1, prepare for takeoff.

24
00:01:27,937 --> 00:01:29,979
Rescue operation
at the Bank of Spain, now!

25
00:01:33,479 --> 00:01:34,312
Taking off.

26
00:01:37,646 --> 00:01:40,021
They're starting a fire. I can't see!

27
00:01:40,104 --> 00:01:41,729
Colonel.

28
00:01:42,562 --> 00:01:45,562
Smoke! There's smoke on the roof, sir.

29
00:01:46,729 --> 00:01:49,062
Hold on. The helicopter's coming.

30
00:01:49,687 --> 00:01:51,312
Go to the roof. We'll cover you.

31
00:01:51,396 --> 00:01:55,187
Exiting now. I'm wearing black
and a ski mask. Hold fire.

32
00:01:55,687 --> 00:01:59,479
Our man's in black. Cover him.
Be ready for possible cross fire.

33
00:01:59,562 --> 00:02:00,646
Come on!

34
00:02:04,896 --> 00:02:05,937
Go!

35
00:02:06,437 --> 00:02:08,146
Let's go!

36
00:02:11,812 --> 00:02:13,687
They're on the roof. They're firing!

37
00:02:16,896 --> 00:02:18,771
Cover fire!

38
00:02:18,854 --> 00:02:20,854
No visual. There's too much smoke.

39
00:02:23,937 --> 00:02:26,437
- Where's the helicopter?
- Delta, position.

40
00:02:26,521 --> 00:02:28,771
Two minutes, fifty seconds, sir.

41
00:02:36,396 --> 00:02:38,854
Delta, begin approach maneuver.

42
00:02:38,937 --> 00:02:40,521
Rescue protocol.

43
00:02:40,604 --> 00:02:42,979
I want a quick, clean extraction.

44
00:02:56,521 --> 00:02:57,771
Helicopter in position.

45
00:02:57,854 --> 00:02:59,646
Get it down there!

46
00:02:59,729 --> 00:03:01,604
Go ahead, proceed.

47
00:03:11,354 --> 00:03:12,896
Target in sight.

48
00:03:13,896 --> 00:03:17,854
I have one in my line of fire.
Permission to shoot.

49
00:03:22,604 --> 00:03:27,312
45 HOURS EARLIER

50
00:03:27,396 --> 00:03:30,104
Mutt, I said I was going to kill you.

51
00:03:32,062 --> 00:03:33,187
No!

52
00:03:38,896 --> 00:03:40,854
Ten, nine,

53
00:03:41,687 --> 00:03:43,896
eight, seven,

54
00:03:44,479 --> 00:03:46,479
six, five,

55
00:03:47,021 --> 00:03:49,104
four, three,

56
00:03:49,896 --> 00:03:52,021
two, one...

57
00:03:53,646 --> 00:03:54,562
zero!

58
00:04:14,937 --> 00:04:15,979
What happened?

59
00:04:16,062 --> 00:04:18,604
Your friend Nairobi threw a grenade at me.

60
00:04:18,687 --> 00:04:20,062
Is Nairobi OK?

61
00:04:21,396 --> 00:04:23,104
I asked if Nairobi is OK!

62
00:04:23,187 --> 00:04:24,937
I don't know if she's OK,

63
00:04:25,687 --> 00:04:28,312
but she can certainly get up, the bitch.

64
00:04:29,396 --> 00:04:30,854
Is she recovering?

65
00:04:31,854 --> 00:04:33,187
I think so.

66
00:04:33,854 --> 00:04:35,771
You were an awesome surgeon.

67
00:04:50,354 --> 00:04:53,104
Are you aware
you're bleeding like a stuck pig?

68
00:06:16,271 --> 00:06:19,646
Do you have to change your suit
in front of all these people?

69
00:06:19,771 --> 00:06:22,187
This isn't a suit. It's the uniform

70
00:06:22,271 --> 00:06:25,604
of a filthy executive
who checks stocks during dinner.

71
00:06:25,687 --> 00:06:28,854
It got you an interview
with the governor of the Bank of Spain.

72
00:06:28,937 --> 00:06:31,062
Isn't it good enough for a cocktail?

73
00:06:31,146 --> 00:06:34,771
You should have parked the car.
Martín complains much less.

74
00:06:34,854 --> 00:06:35,729
Of course.

75
00:06:37,312 --> 00:06:39,312
Now what's wrong with Martín?

76
00:06:40,354 --> 00:06:41,687
He follows you everywhere.

77
00:06:42,521 --> 00:06:43,396
So?

78
00:06:44,812 --> 00:06:46,229
He's in love with you.

79
00:06:48,312 --> 00:06:49,896
In love with me.

80
00:06:50,562 --> 00:06:52,729
Does he write my name in his notebooks?

81
00:06:52,812 --> 00:06:56,604
- Or did he confess in drunken tears?
- I see how he looks at you.

82
00:06:56,687 --> 00:06:59,604
How he smiles at all of your crazy ideas.

83
00:06:59,687 --> 00:07:02,062
How he agrees with what you say
about the plan.

84
00:07:02,146 --> 00:07:04,354
He can't formulate a critical opinion.

85
00:07:04,437 --> 00:07:06,896
He's in love.
That stops him being objective.

86
00:07:06,979 --> 00:07:10,312
He's totally objective.
He's an engineer. He doesn't weigh in.

87
00:07:10,396 --> 00:07:12,187
He does equations,

88
00:07:12,271 --> 00:07:15,771
and no feelings are involved
in any of those calculations.

89
00:07:15,854 --> 00:07:19,687
- We both know the plan's a disaster.
- The plan is fantastic.

90
00:07:19,771 --> 00:07:21,937
It has some fantastic details,

91
00:07:22,021 --> 00:07:25,812
but it doesn't work as a plan.
It doesn't work.

92
00:07:26,771 --> 00:07:29,771
- Why did you call me?
- I want to share it with you.

93
00:07:30,687 --> 00:07:33,854
It's the biggest job of my life.
I want my brother there.

94
00:07:34,312 --> 00:07:37,604
You want me to be the brains
that he's not providing.

95
00:07:38,562 --> 00:07:39,396
And you...

96
00:07:40,479 --> 00:07:43,104
you know how to get the gold out,
not yourselves.

97
00:07:43,187 --> 00:07:46,146
And you have no idea
how you'll live the rest of your lives

98
00:07:46,229 --> 00:07:48,521
with 90 tons of gold
without being found out.

99
00:07:48,604 --> 00:07:52,687
An analytical mind, however small,
would work that out straightaway.

100
00:07:52,771 --> 00:07:53,771
But not you guys.

101
00:07:54,354 --> 00:07:56,687
Because you're in love with the plan...

102
00:07:57,479 --> 00:07:59,312
and he's just in love with you.

103
00:07:59,771 --> 00:08:02,812
We're guided by passion.
You're blinded by hatred.

104
00:08:02,896 --> 00:08:04,062
Hatred for romanticism.

105
00:08:04,146 --> 00:08:07,562
Maybe because suicide
is one of its main characteristics.

106
00:08:07,646 --> 00:08:09,229
This plan is suicide.

107
00:08:09,312 --> 00:08:10,812
Still finding faults?

108
00:08:10,896 --> 00:08:14,562
He'll get over it. When he's stressed,
he's all doom and gloom.

109
00:08:14,646 --> 00:08:18,396
Well... I'm going to the bathroom.

110
00:08:18,479 --> 00:08:20,646
Do you want to come with me, Sergio?

111
00:08:21,646 --> 00:08:27,229
Have you ever had the privilege
of an experienced man giving you fellatio?

112
00:08:30,604 --> 00:08:31,812
I'm joking.

113
00:08:43,854 --> 00:08:47,354
Freezing up,
disorientation, a blank stare...

114
00:08:48,354 --> 00:08:51,979
and, above all,
the feeling of floating outside reality.

115
00:08:53,729 --> 00:08:56,396
Those are the consequences
of emotional shock.

116
00:08:57,937 --> 00:08:59,979
But you can also go the other way.

117
00:09:03,354 --> 00:09:04,812
An unbridled rage

118
00:09:05,354 --> 00:09:06,729
that only seeks...

119
00:09:08,562 --> 00:09:09,437
revenge.

120
00:09:13,354 --> 00:09:14,521
It's open.

121
00:09:26,979 --> 00:09:27,937
Clear.

122
00:09:30,312 --> 00:09:31,146
Blood.

123
00:09:34,437 --> 00:09:35,479
Fuck.

124
00:09:38,729 --> 00:09:39,604
Clear.

125
00:09:59,271 --> 00:10:01,187
We've found the panic room, sir.

126
00:10:01,271 --> 00:10:04,854
Gandía is shut up inside.
He's injured and he has Tokyo.

127
00:10:04,937 --> 00:10:06,604
Is he badly injured?

128
00:10:07,687 --> 00:10:09,812
A grenade exploded on his back.

129
00:10:10,062 --> 00:10:12,479
He'll try to negotiate.
Time's on our side.

130
00:10:12,562 --> 00:10:15,729
- If he wants to live, he can't harm Tokyo.
- I'm not so sure.

131
00:10:17,604 --> 00:10:18,604
Professor...

132
00:10:20,812 --> 00:10:22,229
he killed Nairobi.

133
00:10:31,354 --> 00:10:33,187
Is that a yes?

134
00:11:11,354 --> 00:11:15,104
We'll pay them back 100 times over
for what they did to Nairobi.

135
00:11:20,812 --> 00:11:23,562
The Professor no longer felt any pain.

136
00:11:24,021 --> 00:11:27,479
He was detached from his emotions
and was operating like a machine.

137
00:11:27,562 --> 00:11:29,979
We'll destroy that tent in seven steps.

138
00:11:30,062 --> 00:11:34,312
- All he could think of was his next move.
- It starts with the truth.

139
00:11:34,396 --> 00:11:38,062
If you want to tell the truth,
you need to speak to Rio first.

140
00:11:39,229 --> 00:11:40,937
There are things you don't know.

141
00:11:42,021 --> 00:11:42,854
Professor.

142
00:11:42,937 --> 00:11:44,354
From that moment,

143
00:11:44,437 --> 00:11:47,687
absolutely everything
would become a plan of attack.

144
00:11:47,771 --> 00:11:49,771
- Professor.
- In the hours that followed,

145
00:11:49,854 --> 00:11:51,396
he'd launch missiles.

146
00:11:51,479 --> 00:11:56,187
You said getting out was impossible,
but we'd get out. Keep your word.

147
00:11:56,979 --> 00:12:01,271
I said when we'd melted
and extracted the gold, I'd get you out.

148
00:12:02,104 --> 00:12:03,521
And I stand by that.

149
00:12:05,562 --> 00:12:07,896
Palermo, get Tokyo out.

150
00:12:08,312 --> 00:12:10,771
I'll go to the foundry.
Denver, come with me.

151
00:12:14,104 --> 00:12:15,646
Everyone on alert.

152
00:12:16,646 --> 00:12:18,646
Bomb disposal robot is advancing.

153
00:12:18,729 --> 00:12:20,229
Go ahead. Let's go.

154
00:12:26,021 --> 00:12:28,729
Ready to deactivate
the bombs at the entrance.

155
00:12:44,979 --> 00:12:46,021
Nairobi is dead.

156
00:12:48,479 --> 00:12:50,521
From now on, I'm in charge.

157
00:12:50,896 --> 00:12:54,187
We're going to be efficient.
How many tons have we done?

158
00:12:55,104 --> 00:12:56,146
Forty-four.

159
00:12:56,229 --> 00:12:59,896
- What is this, recess?
- That's three less than the target.

160
00:12:59,979 --> 00:13:04,146
Raise the temperature to 1,750ºC.
We need to increase the production rate.

161
00:13:04,229 --> 00:13:05,812
- Is there no one inside?
- No.

162
00:13:05,896 --> 00:13:10,104
There should be. Let's get moving.
We have to get this gold out.

163
00:13:10,187 --> 00:13:11,062
Denver.

164
00:13:12,062 --> 00:13:13,729
Get every last gram of gold.

165
00:13:13,812 --> 00:13:15,896
I want to get the hell out of here.

166
00:13:17,187 --> 00:13:18,479
Now! Quick! Come on!

167
00:13:29,479 --> 00:13:30,396
Professor.

168
00:13:30,479 --> 00:13:32,854
No, we have a problem.
I'll create a firewall.

169
00:13:32,937 --> 00:13:35,229
- I'll put you through.
- OK, hurry up.

170
00:13:39,687 --> 00:13:40,812
Out!

171
00:13:40,896 --> 00:13:42,146
Shame on you!

172
00:13:42,229 --> 00:13:45,312
Beginning procedure to defuse
the first explosive. Take cover.

173
00:13:46,354 --> 00:13:50,062
Units one and two, ready to advance
once the devices are disconnected.

174
00:13:58,229 --> 00:13:59,687
Fucking firewall.

175
00:14:06,187 --> 00:14:07,354
- Professor.
- Yes.

176
00:14:07,437 --> 00:14:10,104
I shouldn't tell you,
but they're planning a massacre.

177
00:14:10,187 --> 00:14:12,104
They're going to storm the bank.

178
00:14:12,187 --> 00:14:15,187
They're trying to contact Gandía
to work together.

179
00:14:16,021 --> 00:14:19,354
Understood.
Did you give Lisbon my message?

180
00:14:19,437 --> 00:14:20,562
Yes.

181
00:14:21,021 --> 00:14:23,104
Antoñanzas, stay and watch Murillo.

182
00:14:23,646 --> 00:14:24,937
Don't let anyone in.

183
00:14:28,604 --> 00:14:31,437
For God's sake,
why didn't you say anything?

184
00:14:33,021 --> 00:14:35,729
What would I have gained? A bit of pity?

185
00:14:38,354 --> 00:14:39,396
Oh, Alicia...

186
00:14:42,646 --> 00:14:43,771
Paris.

187
00:14:46,646 --> 00:14:51,062
She got very emotional.
She went all doe-eyed.

188
00:14:52,604 --> 00:14:53,979
If you had seen her...

189
00:14:58,312 --> 00:14:59,479
Thank you, Benito.

190
00:15:05,021 --> 00:15:06,729
- Listen.
- I'm listening.

191
00:15:06,812 --> 00:15:08,937
The cops and Gandía
are planning an attack.

192
00:15:09,021 --> 00:15:11,687
Knock out the phone in the panic room.
Cut it all off.

193
00:15:11,771 --> 00:15:16,229
One very important thing:
don't kill Gandía, I need him alive.

194
00:15:16,312 --> 00:15:20,854
- With Tokyo in there, it'll be difficult.
- I said alive. It's key to the plan.

195
00:15:22,396 --> 00:15:25,521
Search for electromagnetic waves
and cut the cables.

196
00:15:26,146 --> 00:15:29,771
When he's totally incommunicado,
without cameras, start opening the door.

197
00:15:29,854 --> 00:15:32,979
Use angle grinders, hammers...
Make lots of noise.

198
00:15:33,062 --> 00:15:35,437
Make sure he knows about it
and won't look elsewhere.

199
00:15:35,521 --> 00:15:39,771
Meanwhile, we drill a small hole
through the back wall

200
00:15:39,854 --> 00:15:41,979
and pump in sleeping gas.

201
00:15:43,562 --> 00:15:45,562
When he's asleep, knock the door down.

202
00:15:45,646 --> 00:15:47,687
- Understood?
- Understood.

203
00:15:52,854 --> 00:15:54,646
Bombs defused, sir.

204
00:15:54,729 --> 00:15:56,396
Good. Get me Gandía.

205
00:16:12,187 --> 00:16:13,021
Bingo.

206
00:16:27,771 --> 00:16:28,687
Yoo-hoo.

207
00:16:37,854 --> 00:16:39,104
That'll be my friends.

208
00:16:59,937 --> 00:17:01,021
Colonel!

209
00:17:04,187 --> 00:17:05,396
Colonel!

210
00:17:06,312 --> 00:17:07,312
Colonel!

211
00:17:09,979 --> 00:17:12,646
Now you really are fucked, you bastard.

212
00:17:16,187 --> 00:17:18,979
Of course I'll do it, however tough it is.

213
00:17:19,062 --> 00:17:21,896
- Are you sure?
- You can count on me.

214
00:17:23,729 --> 00:17:25,812
Thank you, Rio. Thank you.

215
00:17:26,979 --> 00:17:31,271
THE ALGERIAN DESERT

216
00:17:32,271 --> 00:17:36,021
- Did you find anything?
- Find anything where?

217
00:17:36,729 --> 00:17:37,979
This is a desert.

218
00:17:38,062 --> 00:17:42,021
You can't call a cab and say,
"Take me to the torturers' house."

219
00:17:42,104 --> 00:17:43,521
I gave you local backup.

220
00:17:46,021 --> 00:17:47,979
I speak Spanish, I speak German,

221
00:17:48,062 --> 00:17:51,271
Italian, French,
English, Croatian, Serbian...

222
00:17:51,354 --> 00:17:53,312
But I don't speak fucking Berber.

223
00:17:53,396 --> 00:17:54,854
I need coordinates.

224
00:17:54,937 --> 00:17:56,146
Give me ten minutes.

225
00:18:03,021 --> 00:18:06,271
Shakir, I need those satellite images.

226
00:18:06,354 --> 00:18:08,229
You have ten minutes.

227
00:18:18,771 --> 00:18:20,437
Palermo, they're coming in.

228
00:18:27,562 --> 00:18:29,937
...special operations have been deployed

229
00:18:30,021 --> 00:18:34,229
and armored cars
and assault vehicles are on the move.

230
00:18:38,812 --> 00:18:42,646
Just as the police
were about to close in on us,

231
00:18:43,104 --> 00:18:45,562
the Professor launched the first missile.

232
00:18:45,687 --> 00:18:47,104
Open the doors.

233
00:18:49,062 --> 00:18:49,979
Hold position!

234
00:19:17,562 --> 00:19:19,354
What the hell is that?

235
00:19:22,521 --> 00:19:25,937
A missile which was
a salute of honor in memory of Nairobi.

236
00:19:37,354 --> 00:19:39,479
They're the governor's bodyguards.

237
00:19:40,396 --> 00:19:41,396
A funeral.

238
00:19:57,729 --> 00:19:59,021
THE FUCKING BOSS

239
00:20:04,062 --> 00:20:06,562
The tent came to a standstill.

240
00:20:11,271 --> 00:20:12,521
What's happening?

241
00:20:12,604 --> 00:20:13,812
Get her back inside!

242
00:20:14,021 --> 00:20:16,146
Let her. Out of respect.

243
00:20:21,062 --> 00:20:24,312
Nairobi's departure filled the air
with a heavy silence.

244
00:20:28,187 --> 00:20:31,854
It was the disappointment of those
who had believed the Dalí story...

245
00:20:37,062 --> 00:20:38,812
would have a happy ending.

246
00:20:45,604 --> 00:20:47,271
But it was just a war.

247
00:21:24,979 --> 00:21:28,187
And then, the Professor launched
his second missile.

248
00:21:31,687 --> 00:21:32,771
BURIED ALIVE

249
00:21:32,854 --> 00:21:36,271
He covered Madrid with posters of Rio
and sent his story

250
00:21:36,354 --> 00:21:39,229
to the entire national
and international press.

251
00:21:41,521 --> 00:21:44,771
I was illegally detained on January 20
by Panamanian police...

252
00:21:44,854 --> 00:21:46,479
Colonel, Inspector.

253
00:21:47,687 --> 00:21:51,021
...and transferred on a secret flight
with the CNI colonel...

254
00:21:52,146 --> 00:21:53,062
Luis Prieto.

255
00:21:53,146 --> 00:21:58,271
We landed somewhere in the Maghreb,
and they tortured me until April 4.

256
00:21:58,729 --> 00:22:01,646
They put me in a cell that was so small...

257
00:22:02,812 --> 00:22:04,396
that I could only stand.

258
00:22:05,271 --> 00:22:08,437
They left me to shit and piss myself.

259
00:22:10,146 --> 00:22:13,479
And they left me there,
living in my own shit.

260
00:22:15,812 --> 00:22:16,812
One night...

261
00:22:18,062 --> 00:22:21,812
they took me out of my cell,
they took me to the desert...

262
00:22:22,937 --> 00:22:25,271
and they forced me to dig my own grave.

263
00:22:27,146 --> 00:22:30,562
They put me in a box,
and they buried me alive...

264
00:22:31,646 --> 00:22:35,146
until I lost consciousness,
believing that I had died.

265
00:22:38,771 --> 00:22:42,187
- You buried the boy alive?
- Of course we buried him alive.

266
00:22:42,271 --> 00:22:43,979
What the hell gave you that idea?

267
00:22:44,062 --> 00:22:47,396
Why do you think we sent him to Algeria?
For a slap on the wrist?

268
00:22:47,479 --> 00:22:51,146
I would've preferred you put him
in a ditch, in quicklime, in cement...

269
00:22:51,229 --> 00:22:52,771
But buried alive?

270
00:22:52,854 --> 00:22:56,771
A guy describing how he was buried alive
is a fucking horror movie.

271
00:22:56,854 --> 00:22:59,396
In PR terms, it's like suicide.

272
00:22:59,479 --> 00:23:01,312
The New York Times published the video.

273
00:23:01,771 --> 00:23:04,354
Some are calling for
a commission in Strasbourg.

274
00:23:04,437 --> 00:23:07,896
Even Amnesty International
is filing a private prosecution.

275
00:23:07,979 --> 00:23:09,062
We're fucked.

276
00:23:09,146 --> 00:23:12,021
Did that fucking place
have phones, CCTV, Wi-Fi,

277
00:23:12,104 --> 00:23:14,646
or anything they may have used
to get proof?

278
00:23:14,729 --> 00:23:16,146
It was an abandoned hovel.

279
00:23:16,229 --> 00:23:19,062
There were no cameras, internet,
or roads.

280
00:23:19,146 --> 00:23:21,604
- That's why we went.
- It's the middle of nowhere.

281
00:23:21,687 --> 00:23:23,812
Not even Algerian intelligence
knows about it.

282
00:23:23,896 --> 00:23:27,979
And there isn't a scratch on him.
No bruising or internal bleeding.

283
00:23:28,062 --> 00:23:29,146
We were careful.

284
00:23:29,229 --> 00:23:30,146
OK.

285
00:23:31,896 --> 00:23:36,354
We're going to deny it like crazy.
It's his word against ours.

286
00:23:36,687 --> 00:23:38,812
- And you're going to do it.
- Me?

287
00:23:38,896 --> 00:23:39,729
Yes, you.

288
00:23:39,812 --> 00:23:44,687
Give it your all. The full works.
Press conference and urgent announcement.

289
00:23:45,354 --> 00:23:47,562
Transparency, Luis.

290
00:23:48,812 --> 00:23:50,437
My sugar levels are down.

291
00:23:50,521 --> 00:23:52,854
Where are the damn cookies?

292
00:24:36,854 --> 00:24:37,687
Darko.

293
00:24:41,604 --> 00:24:42,854
Benjamín.

294
00:24:43,812 --> 00:24:44,896
Thanks for coming.

295
00:24:46,521 --> 00:24:50,479
If Agustín, Moscow, trusted you...

296
00:24:51,646 --> 00:24:53,437
consider me your friend.

297
00:24:56,812 --> 00:24:58,854
And my daughter, is she well?

298
00:24:59,437 --> 00:25:01,354
Manila is fine.

299
00:25:02,687 --> 00:25:05,187
- Are they all miners?
- All of them.

300
00:25:05,354 --> 00:25:07,021
And all trustworthy.

301
00:25:07,354 --> 00:25:08,312
Asturians.

302
00:25:08,729 --> 00:25:09,771
Except...

303
00:25:11,104 --> 00:25:12,271
this guy.

304
00:25:12,979 --> 00:25:14,062
He's Polish.

305
00:25:14,896 --> 00:25:15,729
Captain.

306
00:25:16,146 --> 00:25:17,104
Thank you.

307
00:25:19,312 --> 00:25:20,854
Welcome, everyone.

308
00:25:21,854 --> 00:25:22,937
Follow me, please.

309
00:25:23,562 --> 00:25:24,937
Where are we going?

310
00:25:25,021 --> 00:25:25,937
To class.

311
00:25:26,271 --> 00:25:29,437
I'll explain what we're going to do
in the next 30 hours.

312
00:25:36,479 --> 00:25:41,729
This plan would be written off as madness
by anyone with any sense.

313
00:25:43,062 --> 00:25:44,896
So forget about sense.

314
00:25:49,937 --> 00:25:54,021
- Fucking sauna, Christ.
- Do you go to saunas?

315
00:25:56,687 --> 00:26:01,021
You're one of those repressed guys
who get horny in the locker room.

316
00:26:01,729 --> 00:26:03,104
Isn't that right?

317
00:26:08,104 --> 00:26:09,896
Did you know we're the same?

318
00:26:13,187 --> 00:26:15,437
We're just on opposite sides.

319
00:26:19,437 --> 00:26:21,354
I can offer you a job.

320
00:26:26,937 --> 00:26:27,896
Honestly...

321
00:26:30,187 --> 00:26:32,521
I'd rather you offered me a fuck.

322
00:26:36,979 --> 00:26:40,896
Is there a rule that forbids
soldiers from different sides fucking?

323
00:26:42,521 --> 00:26:44,229
That's not treason, right?

324
00:26:45,479 --> 00:26:48,104
They should put it
in the Geneva Convention.

325
00:26:48,896 --> 00:26:50,521
"Cease-fire!

326
00:26:51,604 --> 00:26:54,812
Time to fuck!"

327
00:27:03,437 --> 00:27:04,937
What is it that you want?

328
00:27:06,562 --> 00:27:08,062
I don't want anything.

329
00:27:10,646 --> 00:27:12,187
You turn me on.

330
00:27:54,437 --> 00:27:56,646
I was doing a lot of thinking.

331
00:27:57,687 --> 00:28:00,229
I don't really know
what's going on with me.

332
00:28:01,479 --> 00:28:04,312
Or what's going on with you,
but I love you.

333
00:28:05,562 --> 00:28:08,771
And whether we're together or not,
I'll look after you.

334
00:28:09,187 --> 00:28:10,187
What do you mean?

335
00:28:11,021 --> 00:28:12,104
What do you mean?

336
00:28:12,187 --> 00:28:13,687
Nairobi is dead.

337
00:28:14,979 --> 00:28:17,521
Things happen here
you think could never happen.

338
00:28:17,604 --> 00:28:18,479
But they do.

339
00:28:19,146 --> 00:28:21,604
It was easy in Indonesia because...

340
00:28:21,687 --> 00:28:24,479
you were with the only guy
who wasn't a local.

341
00:28:24,562 --> 00:28:27,646
But it's different here,
and I'll put up with that.

342
00:28:28,354 --> 00:28:29,312
And I love you.

343
00:28:30,687 --> 00:28:33,646
You got here, started comparing,
and I was the loser.

344
00:28:33,729 --> 00:28:36,521
- That's OK.
- No one's comparing you to anyone.

345
00:28:37,312 --> 00:28:40,521
Honestly.
And with Rio... it's not like that.

346
00:28:41,187 --> 00:28:43,604
I want you to know
that if you need that,

347
00:28:44,187 --> 00:28:46,229
if you need to be with Rio...

348
00:28:47,604 --> 00:28:48,604
go ahead.

349
00:28:48,896 --> 00:28:50,937
That's not what I need.

350
00:28:53,479 --> 00:28:56,604
I don't even know what I need.
Not right now.

351
00:28:57,979 --> 00:29:02,187
We're in the middle of all this,
and I can't think or make decisions.

352
00:29:02,271 --> 00:29:05,021
But you and I met each other
during a heist.

353
00:29:06,312 --> 00:29:08,437
And we made loads of decisions.

354
00:29:09,396 --> 00:29:10,354
Together.

355
00:29:34,812 --> 00:29:36,604
Arturo, what did you do to me?

356
00:29:39,646 --> 00:29:41,729
What did you do when I was asleep?

357
00:29:42,437 --> 00:29:46,354
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You took advantage of me.

358
00:29:46,437 --> 00:29:49,146
I don't know what you mean,
but now's not the time.

359
00:29:49,229 --> 00:29:50,187
You drugged me.

360
00:29:50,771 --> 00:29:53,729
You made me take
more sedatives than I should have,

361
00:29:53,812 --> 00:29:55,562
and I basically passed out.

362
00:29:55,646 --> 00:29:59,979
But before I did, I felt you up close,
touching my neck, my breast.

363
00:30:00,062 --> 00:30:03,604
I was drugged,
but I felt you lowering my zipper, and...

364
00:30:04,146 --> 00:30:05,604
you kept on touching me.

365
00:30:05,687 --> 00:30:07,687
You lifted my panties, Arturo.

366
00:30:08,479 --> 00:30:10,479
I woke up, I drifted back off...

367
00:30:12,062 --> 00:30:15,229
But I keep seeing images,
and my bra was broken when I woke up.

368
00:30:15,312 --> 00:30:16,354
Amanda.

369
00:30:17,979 --> 00:30:21,437
You're just very anxious. It's normal.

370
00:30:21,729 --> 00:30:23,354
With all this circus, OK?

371
00:30:24,062 --> 00:30:25,937
You must be confused

372
00:30:26,021 --> 00:30:29,521
and seeing and believing things
that didn't really happen.

373
00:30:29,604 --> 00:30:31,229
Or maybe...

374
00:30:31,854 --> 00:30:34,437
you had an erotic dream about me.

375
00:30:34,521 --> 00:30:37,187
I don't mind being
the object of your desire,

376
00:30:37,271 --> 00:30:40,312
but to go from that
to accusing me of something...

377
00:30:41,604 --> 00:30:43,062
You raped me, Arturo.

378
00:30:43,479 --> 00:30:45,562
You drugged me and you raped me.

379
00:30:45,646 --> 00:30:46,479
Listen to me.

380
00:30:48,521 --> 00:30:49,687
You brat.

381
00:30:49,771 --> 00:30:51,271
I didn't rape you.

382
00:30:51,854 --> 00:30:53,687
I didn't take advantage of you.

383
00:30:53,771 --> 00:30:57,229
You're accusing me
of something really very serious.

384
00:30:57,312 --> 00:30:59,021
Something I loathe.

385
00:30:59,104 --> 00:31:00,354
Something I detest.

386
00:31:00,437 --> 00:31:03,479
I've always been
a defender of women's rights.

387
00:31:03,562 --> 00:31:07,687
I've always advocated respect for women.
I won't allow this.

388
00:31:11,146 --> 00:31:12,187
Nothing happened.

389
00:31:12,271 --> 00:31:14,896
You were scared, you had a panic attack...

390
00:31:14,979 --> 00:31:16,854
It's normal, OK?

391
00:31:19,979 --> 00:31:23,021
Can you believe it?

392
00:31:31,979 --> 00:31:33,312
That's Bogotá.

393
00:31:44,604 --> 00:31:49,604
Now you really are fucked.
It's the shrapnel in your neck.

394
00:31:50,104 --> 00:31:52,062
Brachial plexus.

395
00:31:52,979 --> 00:31:55,354
It controls muscles in your arm...

396
00:31:55,604 --> 00:31:58,729
in your hand... in your shoulder.

397
00:31:59,396 --> 00:32:00,646
You know all that?

398
00:32:03,104 --> 00:32:05,812
- I learn this stuff with the Professor.
- Yeah?

399
00:32:08,937 --> 00:32:10,271
Is it hard to breathe?

400
00:32:11,187 --> 00:32:12,146
That's normal.

401
00:32:13,687 --> 00:32:15,104
It's your diaphragm.

402
00:32:17,021 --> 00:32:19,729
- Tough break.
- Do you want me to release you?

403
00:32:23,521 --> 00:32:25,521
If you don't release me, you're dead.

404
00:32:27,604 --> 00:32:28,896
If you release me...

405
00:32:31,562 --> 00:32:32,896
I'll treat your wounds.

406
00:32:34,104 --> 00:32:37,521
I'll undo your hands
so you can remove the shrapnel for me.

407
00:32:41,229 --> 00:32:42,771
But you'll still...

408
00:32:44,729 --> 00:32:46,729
be tied at the neck.

409
00:32:47,687 --> 00:32:49,271
I'll have my back to you,

410
00:32:50,812 --> 00:32:52,854
but I only have to do this...

411
00:32:53,896 --> 00:32:57,521
to blow your clever little head off.

412
00:33:00,521 --> 00:33:03,562
MINISTRY OF THE INTERIOR
19:45 HOURS

413
00:33:04,771 --> 00:33:06,146
Good morning, everyone.

414
00:33:06,229 --> 00:33:08,021
My name is Luis Prieto.

415
00:33:08,271 --> 00:33:11,479
I'm a colonel
from the National Center of Intelligence.

416
00:33:11,562 --> 00:33:15,312
I stand before you at the request
of the Minister of the Interior

417
00:33:15,396 --> 00:33:20,562
to firmly deny the accusations
about the alleged torture of Aníbal Cortés

418
00:33:21,479 --> 00:33:25,146
and to clear up any doubts
you may have about his arrest.

419
00:33:25,229 --> 00:33:27,062
- Yes, here, please.
- Colonel.

420
00:33:27,146 --> 00:33:29,687
How did Ágata Jiménez, alias Nairobi, die?

421
00:33:29,771 --> 00:33:32,396
We are currently
still gathering information.

422
00:33:32,479 --> 00:33:35,687
All I can say
is that she was killed in a skirmish

423
00:33:35,771 --> 00:33:38,896
with the Bank of Spain's head of security,
who broke free.

424
00:33:39,771 --> 00:33:42,396
Was Cortés illegally arrested in Panama?

425
00:33:42,479 --> 00:33:44,854
The arrest was made legally

426
00:33:44,937 --> 00:33:48,562
in accordance
with an arrest warrant issued by Europol.

427
00:33:48,646 --> 00:33:49,812
- Excuse me.
- You.

428
00:33:54,854 --> 00:33:58,062
No democratic country in the world
respecting the rule of law

429
00:33:58,146 --> 00:33:59,271
would do such a thing.

430
00:34:00,979 --> 00:34:03,146
He claims to have been buried alive.

431
00:34:03,229 --> 00:34:06,771
Do you deny that too?
That he was left to defecate himself?

432
00:34:06,854 --> 00:34:12,771
That they gave him 40 coffees
and cold showers?

433
00:34:14,146 --> 00:34:17,479
Those statements
are as ridiculous as they are grotesque.

434
00:34:18,479 --> 00:34:21,271
Prieto did what the Professor
expected him to:

435
00:34:21,354 --> 00:34:24,479
lie, lie, and lie again.

436
00:34:24,562 --> 00:34:28,354
He did it better than the Professor
could ever have imagined.

437
00:34:28,812 --> 00:34:31,187
With sarcasm and arrogance.

438
00:34:31,271 --> 00:34:33,104
They'll be confident.

439
00:34:33,229 --> 00:34:38,062
They'll be confident because they think
it's our word against theirs.

440
00:34:38,146 --> 00:34:42,979
And that's what will make them drown
in the quicksand of their own dirt.

441
00:34:43,062 --> 00:34:47,479
Because what the CNI
could never imagine...

442
00:34:49,354 --> 00:34:51,437
is that our intelligence could be better.

443
00:34:54,021 --> 00:34:55,271
But we'll show them.

444
00:34:56,896 --> 00:34:58,812
We're going to show them...

445
00:35:02,854 --> 00:35:04,312
because we'll be there.

446
00:35:20,271 --> 00:35:22,979
This is the same old
conspiracy theory as always:

447
00:35:23,062 --> 00:35:25,062
that the police use torture.

448
00:35:25,521 --> 00:35:27,521
We won't accept this kind of talk.

449
00:35:33,021 --> 00:35:33,896
Talk.

450
00:35:37,437 --> 00:35:41,854
We tortured Aníbal Cortés
for around two months.

451
00:35:41,937 --> 00:35:44,854
We were paid 200,000 euros to do it,

452
00:35:44,937 --> 00:35:47,812
by Colonel Prieto
from Spanish Intelligence.

453
00:35:47,896 --> 00:35:50,687
And that was his third missile.

454
00:35:50,771 --> 00:35:51,687
Colonel Prieto.

455
00:35:51,771 --> 00:35:52,854
Excuse me.

456
00:35:52,937 --> 00:35:57,896
We're receiving documentary evidence
that contradicts your words.

457
00:35:57,979 --> 00:36:00,854
Do you know a Turkish citizen named Osman?

458
00:36:01,604 --> 00:36:03,187
I don't know who that is.

459
00:36:03,854 --> 00:36:07,604
This e-mail sent from your account
to this Osman

460
00:36:07,687 --> 00:36:09,521
in which you order,

461
00:36:09,604 --> 00:36:12,979
"Use any means necessary
to obtain the information."

462
00:36:13,062 --> 00:36:15,646
- Did you send this?
- I don't know what you mean.

463
00:36:18,104 --> 00:36:20,729
Maybe these images
will refresh your memory.

464
00:36:21,729 --> 00:36:24,771
This is
where we buried Aníbal Cortés alive.

465
00:36:24,854 --> 00:36:26,479
You can see the wooden box.

466
00:36:26,562 --> 00:36:29,229
We had him in there
for two or three hours.

467
00:36:29,437 --> 00:36:31,521
He dug the hole himself.

468
00:36:32,062 --> 00:36:34,146
Do you deny this evidence too?

469
00:36:34,854 --> 00:36:39,771
Do you still claim that this grave
in a place called Timimoun, in Algeria,

470
00:36:39,854 --> 00:36:43,271
that you refer to in several e-mails,
is a setup?

471
00:36:43,354 --> 00:36:44,979
Of course it is.

472
00:36:45,062 --> 00:36:46,771
Colonel, please.

473
00:36:46,854 --> 00:36:48,271
Colonel, here, please.

474
00:36:49,146 --> 00:36:50,854
I have nothing more to say.

475
00:36:55,646 --> 00:36:59,021
Tamayo will be like a tennis player
in the middle of the court,

476
00:36:59,104 --> 00:37:03,979
trying to return all the balls
that a machine is firing at him nonstop.

477
00:37:09,146 --> 00:37:10,437
They put me in a box.

478
00:37:11,312 --> 00:37:13,271
...€200,000 to do it.

479
00:37:13,354 --> 00:37:16,812
He'll be so focused
on stopping the balls we're firing

480
00:37:16,896 --> 00:37:21,104
that he won't have the time or energy
to think about the heist.

481
00:37:21,187 --> 00:37:24,146
Because his whole world
will be falling apart.

482
00:37:24,229 --> 00:37:26,479
We're ready to resume the attack.

483
00:37:26,562 --> 00:37:28,646
- We're not attacking.
- Colonel!

484
00:37:28,729 --> 00:37:32,604
Can't you see what's happening?
They want to take us all down.

485
00:37:32,979 --> 00:37:37,021
The finishing touch
would be killing a hostage on our way in.

486
00:37:37,104 --> 00:37:39,979
- They're weakened.
- No, it's out of the question.

487
00:37:40,062 --> 00:37:43,437
Do I have to remind you
that you've tried to go in 4 times?

488
00:37:43,521 --> 00:37:45,979
What's going on in there?
Is there an open bar?

489
00:37:46,062 --> 00:37:51,687
When you have a fire of such magnitude,
you can only think about one thing.

490
00:37:51,854 --> 00:37:55,229
- Putting it out.
- Putting it out.

491
00:37:55,312 --> 00:37:59,437
Not for Spain's credibility,
nor for the integrity of the CNI...

492
00:38:00,854 --> 00:38:02,521
but for your own freedom.

493
00:38:02,937 --> 00:38:04,521
Listen, everyone.

494
00:38:04,604 --> 00:38:07,812
I need all non-essential personnel
to step outside.

495
00:38:07,896 --> 00:38:11,562
Take a breather, have a coffee,
and back to work in 5 minutes.

496
00:38:17,562 --> 00:38:19,437
Oh, Alicia...

497
00:38:20,396 --> 00:38:22,646
We tried to get out there and deny it,

498
00:38:24,187 --> 00:38:28,729
but that son of a bitch, the Professor,
was waiting with the evidence in hand.

499
00:38:31,062 --> 00:38:33,812
Now the only way out is to take the blame.

500
00:38:35,021 --> 00:38:36,646
And who's going to do that?

501
00:38:37,396 --> 00:38:39,146
For the CNI, Prieto.

502
00:38:42,979 --> 00:38:44,562
For the police, you.

503
00:38:46,646 --> 00:38:50,812
We need you to create a firewall
so the institutions come out clean.

504
00:38:56,437 --> 00:38:57,729
What should I say?

505
00:38:58,646 --> 00:39:01,187
That I did it all without telling anyone?

506
00:39:01,562 --> 00:39:05,062
That I did it...
out of professional ambition?

507
00:39:05,896 --> 00:39:08,937
To see if they'd give me
the police medal of merit?

508
00:39:09,562 --> 00:39:12,729
They have Prieto's e-mails.
I'm sure they have yours.

509
00:39:13,812 --> 00:39:16,437
You have to resign,
leave the negotiations...

510
00:39:17,312 --> 00:39:21,604
and take the blame for acting illegally.

511
00:39:21,729 --> 00:39:26,229
If I'm taking the blame,
why don't you add that I killed Manolete,

512
00:39:26,312 --> 00:39:29,062
the Kennedy thing,
the attempted coup in '81...

513
00:39:29,604 --> 00:39:31,187
shooting the pope...

514
00:39:31,687 --> 00:39:33,979
I'm getting blamed for it all, right?

515
00:39:34,062 --> 00:39:37,021
You're going to take the rap anyway,

516
00:39:37,396 --> 00:39:40,479
but if you help us,
we won't leave you hanging.

517
00:39:41,312 --> 00:39:43,729
I'll have the CNI discredit the evidence.

518
00:39:43,812 --> 00:39:47,062
The state attorney
and the prosecution are on our side.

519
00:39:47,146 --> 00:39:49,479
You'll get a friendly judge.

520
00:39:50,062 --> 00:39:54,312
Someone who we've got by the balls.
You'll be suspended without pay.

521
00:39:54,396 --> 00:39:58,312
But don't worry,
you'll be paid from reserve funds.

522
00:40:02,646 --> 00:40:05,479
I promise you won't set foot in prison.

523
00:40:05,562 --> 00:40:06,979
I don't care about that.

524
00:40:14,604 --> 00:40:15,479
Well.

525
00:40:17,479 --> 00:40:19,437
It's not like I have much choice.

526
00:40:21,604 --> 00:40:22,437
Right?

527
00:40:23,937 --> 00:40:24,896
Alicia...

528
00:40:25,979 --> 00:40:26,812
be strong.

529
00:40:28,229 --> 00:40:29,729
We're with you.

530
00:40:41,854 --> 00:40:45,521
Sierra... and Colonel Prieto.

531
00:40:47,312 --> 00:40:50,521
They will be the first to fall.

532
00:40:51,104 --> 00:40:51,937
Why?

533
00:40:52,896 --> 00:40:55,396
Because that's how
we'll paralyze the tent,

534
00:40:55,479 --> 00:40:58,437
and by doing so,
protect our crew inside the bank.

535
00:40:58,521 --> 00:41:01,354
Tamayo will have difficulty
maintaining control.

536
00:41:01,437 --> 00:41:05,396
Once everyone in the bank is protected,
what do we do, Benjamín?

537
00:41:05,479 --> 00:41:08,604
Huh? Well... you tell me.

538
00:41:09,312 --> 00:41:13,062
Rescue another member of the gang.

539
00:41:14,771 --> 00:41:16,562
We're going to rescue someone

540
00:41:17,021 --> 00:41:20,187
who is being guarded
by a group of 26 police officers.

541
00:41:20,271 --> 00:41:22,021
That's impossible, Professor.

542
00:41:23,021 --> 00:41:25,354
It's almost impossible,

543
00:41:25,437 --> 00:41:28,521
but there is a possibility

544
00:41:29,062 --> 00:41:30,771
if you know these details:

545
00:41:31,521 --> 00:41:35,687
where they are going to take her
and when.

546
00:41:35,771 --> 00:41:38,771
And we will know that information...

547
00:41:40,812 --> 00:41:43,312
because I'll make them transfer her.

548
00:42:33,771 --> 00:42:35,937
Now just the one in your neck.

549
00:42:38,104 --> 00:42:39,062
How's it look?

550
00:42:40,687 --> 00:42:46,104
It doesn't look good.
If I do it wrong, you could be paralyzed.

551
00:42:46,771 --> 00:42:49,687
Pull it out.
Pull upwards, without hesitation.

552
00:42:58,687 --> 00:43:00,687
Put your head down a bit.

553
00:43:04,687 --> 00:43:05,771
The camera.

554
00:43:27,021 --> 00:43:29,104
For fuck's sake, Gandía's dead!

555
00:43:29,187 --> 00:43:31,937
Bogotá, Tokyo killed Gandía!
Knock the door down!

556
00:43:32,479 --> 00:43:33,396
Fuck!

557
00:43:35,604 --> 00:43:37,604
Then came the fourth missile.

558
00:43:40,521 --> 00:43:42,937
Look at the screens.
Is that the Professor?

559
00:43:43,021 --> 00:43:44,604
Is that the Professor?

560
00:43:49,062 --> 00:43:52,062
Our colleague Lisbon
has been illegally detained.

561
00:43:52,229 --> 00:43:56,271
She was captured and is being held
at the command post in front of the bank.

562
00:43:56,854 --> 00:43:58,854
Without a judge being informed.

563
00:43:59,771 --> 00:44:02,312
- With no right to a defense.
- What the hell?

564
00:44:02,396 --> 00:44:04,937
And after the police faked her execution.

565
00:44:05,521 --> 00:44:06,812
Here's the proof.

566
00:44:07,562 --> 00:44:09,271
The recording of that moment.

567
00:44:09,854 --> 00:44:11,437
Suárez, put down the gun.

568
00:44:11,896 --> 00:44:13,229
Where's the Professor?

569
00:44:13,312 --> 00:44:15,937
Tell them I'll surrender.
Buy time.

570
00:44:16,562 --> 00:44:17,562
Raquel, tell him.

571
00:44:17,646 --> 00:44:20,312
- Where's the Professor?
- I don't know.

572
00:44:20,396 --> 00:44:22,396
Tell him, I'm on my way. Raquel!

573
00:44:22,479 --> 00:44:24,729
- Where's the Professor?
- I don't know!

574
00:44:24,812 --> 00:44:25,687
Get them out.

575
00:44:26,229 --> 00:44:28,687
Get out of there!

576
00:44:28,771 --> 00:44:30,604
I don't know where he is.

577
00:44:31,021 --> 00:44:32,396
Wrong answer.

578
00:44:32,479 --> 00:44:34,396
I'm on my way. Get out of there.

579
00:44:34,479 --> 00:44:35,937
Get out of there!

580
00:44:39,521 --> 00:44:41,187
It was self-defense.

581
00:44:41,646 --> 00:44:44,521
Do you understand, Solana? She shot first.

582
00:44:45,187 --> 00:44:48,146
Take the gun, clean the prints,
put it in her hand.

583
00:44:50,021 --> 00:44:52,396
I implore the authorities to investigate

584
00:44:52,812 --> 00:44:55,312
and to confirm
the accuracy of these facts.

585
00:45:07,604 --> 00:45:10,062
Tied up, and you still took him out.

586
00:45:10,146 --> 00:45:12,146
Great. See if he has a pulse.

587
00:45:12,229 --> 00:45:13,812
Yes, I have a pulse.

588
00:45:14,062 --> 00:45:16,521
Sorry, you're more interested in Gandía.

589
00:45:17,312 --> 00:45:19,687
There he is.
A bit under the weather.

590
00:45:21,771 --> 00:45:23,771
- He's alive.
- Good.

591
00:45:23,854 --> 00:45:25,229
Are you going to untie me?

592
00:45:29,896 --> 00:45:30,812
How are you?

593
00:45:56,646 --> 00:45:57,896
How's Nairobi?

594
00:46:34,229 --> 00:46:38,146
The last missile
arrived at the tent in an official car,

595
00:46:38,229 --> 00:46:41,229
with a badge and a judge's order.

596
00:46:41,729 --> 00:46:42,604
Attention.

597
00:46:44,271 --> 00:46:45,646
Stop what you're doing.

598
00:46:49,562 --> 00:46:52,604
- I'm Colonel Tamayo. I'm in charge.
- I don't care.

599
00:46:52,687 --> 00:46:54,229
Internal Affairs Unit.

600
00:46:54,312 --> 00:46:57,812
- What's going on?
- Where's Raquel Murillo being held?

601
00:47:12,979 --> 00:47:14,062
Raquel Murillo,

602
00:47:14,354 --> 00:47:17,729
you're under arrest for the crimes
of belonging to an armed group,

603
00:47:17,812 --> 00:47:21,771
abduction, attacking an officer
and the institutions of the state.

604
00:47:22,396 --> 00:47:24,521
You have the right to remain silent.

605
00:47:24,812 --> 00:47:27,896
You have the right
to an attorney of your choice.

606
00:47:28,521 --> 00:47:31,021
You have the right to medical care.

607
00:47:31,354 --> 00:47:33,354
You have the right to make a call.

