Nobody move!
No!
My name is Tokyo.
But when this story began,
that wasn't my name.
That was me.
SUSPECT'S WHEREABOUTS UNKNOWN
And that was the love of my life.
ROBBER GETS SHOT DEAD
The last time I saw him
I left him in a puddle of blood
his eyes wide open.
We pulled off 15 perfect heists,
but mixing love and
business is never a good idea.
So, when the security guard fired,
I had to switch careers.
From thief to murderer.
And that's when I had to run away.
In a way, I was dead too.
Well, almost dead.
I had been hiding for 11 days
and my picture was in
every police precint in Spain.
I'd get 30 years
And to be honest,
growing old in a prison cell
is not my thing
I'd rather run.
In body and soul.
And if I can't take my body with me,
"at least let my soul should run."
I was running out of time, and
there were important things to do.
Only one, really.
Hello?
Mom?
Oh, my girl.
How are you, sweetheart?
What's happening?
You've heard what they said about me?
On all the news reports.
Of course I've seen them.
So, uh...
I'm thinking about going on a trip.
Maybe get a job on a Chinese boat.
As a cook.
Didn't you say that
I couldn't even fry an egg?
Now I can learn. What do you think?
I don't know, dear.
What if they only eat Chinese food?
What does this trip mean,
that I won't see you again?
Of course not.
We'll see each other.
I'll buy you a ticket so
you can come and visit me.
And where is that?
The cemetery?
Are you alone?
Mom, are you alone?
Yes.
Then go down to the street,
go toward the grocery store.
I'll find you.
And that day, the day I was going to be slaughtered,
my guardian angel showed up.
You can never know be sure
what a guardian angel will look like,
but what you'd never expect
is for him to show up
in a '92 SEAT Ibiza.
I'm sorry, do you have a second?
No.
There's an upside to
cooking on a Chinese boat.
You don't have to wash dishes.
For a minute I thought to myself
He's got a point.
- Who are you, a cop?
- Wait, wait.
You're heading into a slaughter,
a police task force is waiting for you
and the UIT has been
following you for six days...
Why should I believe you?
"And that's how I met the Professor,"
"by pointing a gun at his balls."
May I?
The good thing about relationships
is that we end up forgetting
how they started.
May I?
They're already at your mother's house.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
I have a business proposal,
a heist,
a heist that's...
unique.
I'm looking for people that...
Well, with not much to lose.
How woud stealing...
about 2.4 billion euros sound?
No one has ever hit that hard,
Not even in New York,
London, or Monte Carlo.
So if my picture needs
to be in the news again,
at least it'll be for
to the greatest in history.
WELCOME
Welcome everyone
and... I wanted to
thank you all for...
agreeing to this offer.
We'll live here,
away from the maddening crowd.
For five months,
we'll spend studying
- how to pull off this heist.
- What do you mean, five months?
Are you nuts, or what?
There are those,
who spend years at school
to get a salary,
which, in even the best scenario,
is just a salary, a shitty one.
What's five months?
I've been thinking about this...
for much longer.
So I don't have to work ever again.
Nor will you
and nor your children.
Alright.
Currently, you don't know each other
and I want to keep it like that.
I don't want to use names,
or personal questions,
And, obviously, no personal relationships.
I want each of you to pick a name,
something simple.
It can be numbers, planets, cities...
- Like "Lord 17, Lady 23."
- We already got a problem.
- I can't even remember my phone number.
- You can't even use your phone.
- Planets?
- I'll be Mars, he's Uranus.
I'm not Uranus, so just forget it.
- What's wrong with Uranus?
- It sounds like an asshole.
- We'll use cities. Cities.
- Cities, it's all agreed.
Good.
And, that's how I started
calling myself Tokyo.
The one looking at
my ass is Mr. Berlin.
There's a warrant for his arrest.
27 robberies.
Jewelry stores, auction houses
and armored vehicles.
His biggest score,
Champs Elysees, in Paris.
434 diamonds.
He's like a shark inside a pool.
You can swim with him,
but you're always nervous.
He was in charge of the heist.
The one coughing is Mr Moscow.
The first thing he dug was a mine,
in Asturias.
Later on, he figured out that
he'd go further by digging up.
Six fur shops, three watch shops
and the Royal Credit Union of Avilés.
He's an expert with the thermal lance
and any industrial tool.
The one behind Moscow is Denver, his son.
Drugs, busted teeth, broken ribs.
He's the king of bar fights.
Pure hot blooded.
Perfect for a heist,
but, a time bomb.
Rio. He's my weakness.
He's the Mozart of computers.
He's been coding since he was six and knows
everything about alarms and electronics.
As for everthing else
it's like he was been born yesterday.
And there you have the twins,
Helsinki and Oslo.
Even with the most bulletproof plan
soldiers are neceesary.
And what's better than two Serbs.
It's possible they can think,
but, frankly, we'll never know.
Nairobi,
hopeless optimist.
She's been counterfeiting
banknotes since age 13.
And now she's our quality control manager.
It's possible that she's nuts,
but she's so damned funny.
To think that every day
the news will be talking about us.
And every family in this
country will be asking
what are they doing now.
And you know what they'll be thinking?
Those Motherfuckers!
I wish I thought of that first.
The Professor:
no criminal record.
Hasn't renewed his ID since he was 19.
For all intents and purposes, a ghost,
but a very smart ghost.
Because we're not stealing their money...
It's not theirs.
And for that very reason alone
they're gonna like us.
And that's imperative.
It's absolutely critical that we
have positive public opinion.
We'll be the fucking heroes
of the entire nation.
But be very careful,
because the second any blood
is shed, and this is very important,
if there's one single victim,
we'll no longer be Robin Hoods but
just a bunch of plain motherfucking punks
Professor.
Yes, Tokyo.
What are we robbing?
The Royal Mint of Spain.
DAY OF THE ROBBERY
FRIDAY 8:35 A.M.
Who chose these?
- What's wrong with the masks?
- They're not scary.
In every movie the
robbers wear scary masks.
Zombies, skeletons,
Angel of death, I mean...
I assure you that a nutjob with
a gun is scarier than a skeleton.
- That's enough.
- Who's the dude with the mustache?
Dalí, son, he was a Spanish painter.
A very good one.
- A painter.
- Yes.
- A painter that paints.
Do you know what's really scary?
Little kids dolls.
Those are scary.
What dolls?
Goofy, Pluto, Mickey Mouse, all of those.
So a mouse with big ears is scarier,
that's what you're saying?
Yes, bastard.
Do you want a kick in the nuts?
- Hey!
- I'm right. Listen.
If a some clown with a gun goes anywhere
wearing a Mickey Mouse mask
people will think he's a pyscho
and he want's a bloodbath.
And you know why?
Because weapons and children
are two things
you never put together, dad.
Right?
Well, if you see it that
way it's, more dangerous,
more twisted.
Then a Jesus mask would be
terrifying, he's even more innocent.
That's like the old saying "Better
two guns than a crucifix", right?
- Like a saint with two guns.
- What's the difference?
It was obvious that this
gang needed more women.
A woman can spend two days
choosing shoes for a wedding,
but wouldn't spend a minute
arguing over masks for a robbery.
Everything we had planned was starting now
and in those microseconds
I thought of all the
innocent people
whose lives will come to a
sudden stop because of us.
E-80 LOCAL ROAD
The Professor knew
there was only one way
to enter the Royal Mint
with a three ton arsenal
And it was through the truck
that came in each week
with the new rolls of
currency paper ready to print.
And that was exactly what we were doing,
get all the way in,
escorted by the National Police.
"In Spain, anything that has a double
escort means it's heavily protected."
"But if you prevent any radio or
phone communication from happening"
Center...
"and you point five assault rifles
into the heads of two 26-year-old kids,"
Get out of the car!
"regardless of how well armed they are,"
"they will do exactly the same
that any of us would do."
I told you get out, damn it!
Out of the fucking car!
"They'll shit ther pants."
You'll do what I tell
you, you understand!
"Courage and heroism come with a price,"
"and it's much higher than the
1,600 euros made each month"
- "by a guy in a uniform..."
- Open the door, do you hear me?
"...or by a truck driver."
For fucks sake, open it!
If those men had their daughters
inside the back of the truck,
they would never have opened it,
but who cares about some
rolls of watermarked paper?
Hurry!
Hurry! Move, dude! Come on!
Get your ass in there.
Close your eyes. Go.
Go. Go. Go.
Sit there. Now the three of you
keep quiet or I'll smash your heads.
You'll be driving with a
gun pointed to your kidneys.
So when they call you on the radio
to check how everything is going,
you'll answer calmly,
and say everything is going well.
Is that clear?
And in the middle of
the chaos with the guns
I remembered that the night before
I got a marriage proposal
and that I decided to
focus on other things.
Of course, if you think about it,
you'll never find a good day for a heist.
Alright, you know what you have to do.
Don't take your eyes off the girl.
There can be no mistakes, are we clear?
She's 17.
I think I can handle her.
Can I sit next to you?
Sure.
Hello.
Hi.
You want to hang out?
Yeah, right. I get it. I'll go.
No, no.
I don't have to think it over.
Yeah.
Alright kids, we've arrived at the Mint.
We'll go directly to the museum lobby,
where we'll wait for the rest of the class.
Everyone be careful getting
off the bus and stay together.
And this is the front entrance
of the Royal Mint. Go on inside.
The little lamb just entered.
Perfect.
Berlin, it's your turn.
Now, be very careful with what you do next.
What's up, Javi? Where's Rafa?
He changed his shift.
That's very good. Relax.
Alright, everyone come through.
Your credentials must
be visible at all times.
This let's security know that you
have permission to be on the premises.
So put them around your necks, and save
your questions until we're inside, please.
Everyone stay together and make
sure you're on your best behavior.
Don't turn around.
When you're this close,
I can barely stand to breathe.
Well, breathe,
because in nine months
you won't be able to breathe at all.
Go ahead.
These must be visible
at all times, alright kids.
Credentials around the neck.
Lower your voice.
Berlin, camera on your left.
You have nothing to say?
I tell you that I'm pregnant,
and you don't say anything?
What should I do Monica,
call my wife, tell her
to go pick up the kids
and we can all go celebrate together?
For God's sakes!
Go, go, go. Okay,
okay, that's it.
Keep going. Okay. Go, go.
ACCESS TO SECURITY SYSTEM
Ready, Tokyo?
ACCESS TO ALARM SYSTEM
Yes!
- Alarms disconnected.
- Now.
Just yesterday you were saying
that you couldn't stand her any longer,
you were having problems.
Yes, like any other
couple, Mónica,
Same problems as any
marriage that has three kids,
not that I was leaving her.
Mónica, I have three kids,
all through artificial
insemination.
For more than 20 years I've been
having infertile sex with my wife
and now you're telling me this.
Who are you, Shiva,
the goddess of fertility.
What are you implying?
I'm not here looking for child support.
Nor a divorce,
or any kind of paternity test, either.
I thought we were in love.
And...
And I was happy with that.
I realize that this won't be easy
but I'm sure it's what I want.
Hold on!
What? You want to know what
I'm going to do with your child?
That's it, isn't it?
Listen to me, don't
get carried away.
Don't move!
Don't do it.
Don't move or I'll blow you in half!
Stay calm! Stay calm!
Let's go, let's go.
Hurry!
Quiet!
Stay there!
Go. This way.
Let's go.
As you can see, this wonderful
stairway is made of marble and granite...
Don't move!
Stop! Go back!
Come on!
Professor, we have a problem.
I can't find the little lamb.
I don't see her! Fuck!
Alright, Miss Parker,
where did you go?
Come on! Hurry! Let's go!
Wait.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
I'm going too fast. I know.
We should capture this moment, right?
Come on. Let's take a picture of this.
In here? It's kind of gross?
This is our first date.
You're beautiful, you know that?
I can't find the girl.
I can't fucking find her.
Unbutton your shirt to make it sexier.
It's on your phone.
You can delete it, if you want.
Do it. This is just for us.
Come on, this is great.
Ready?
With this photo you'll be
killing it on the Internet.
Give it back! Give me the phone!
Give me the phone!
Give me the fucking phone!
First things first...
Greetings.
I am the man in charge.
And I want to start...
by offering my apologies.
This is not a good way
to end your week.
But you're here as our hostages.
Cellphone.
Follow our instructions and you'll be safe.
- Name.
- Alison Parker.
- PIN.
- 2018.
Cellphone.
It's okay, it's okay.
PIN.
But, why do you need the PIN?
Give the fucking PIN or I
beat it out of you. You decide.
How many months?
Eight.
Eight months.
- PIN.
- 1234.
You think that you're clever,
but that's your shitty PIN number.
What an idiot. Name.
- Arturo.
- Arturo what?
- Arturo Román.
- Arturo Román, got it. Arturito.
Arturito.
You're our safe passage,
so I will protect you.
Hey...
Give me your hands. Relax.
Relax. Relax.
What's your name?
Ariadna.
Come with me, dear.
It's okay.
Feel my hands.
Are these the
hands of a monster?
- No.
Because I'm not a monster.
I know exactly how you feel.
Dry mouth, out of breath...
You need to try to calm down. Breathe.
Breathe.
That's it, please. Everybody breathe now.
Slowly.
Everybody.
Take control of your breathing.
Trust me, you'll be alright.
That's it.
Miss Mónica Gaztambide, please?
Don't move. Please, don't move.
They won't touch us.
Stay very still.
- Stay quiet.
- Okay.
Miss Mónica Gaztambide, would
you be so kind as to step forward?
Right here.
You're the man, Papa!
You're the bomb!
You could sleep great in here, papa.
Like a king.
Papa, papa papa.
To fuck a chick. Right here, boom!
Boom, boom...
Stop fooling around like that
and let's get to work. Come on.
This smells fucking great.
Better than roasted lamb,
like you used to cook.
- Come lie down here.
- Quit it, will you!
When have you had
a bed like this before?
Not in your jail cell.
You see where we are, papa?
We're the on top now.
- We're very big.
- Listen, kid. Don't be mistaken.
We're very small.
What else can you do?
Have you ever had a proper job?
Have you ever put together
a resume and sent it out?
Exactly. Come on.
You said a resume.
Why would I need that?
To get you out of jail, old man?
And do you think that I'm proud of that?
Of being in and out of prison for 12 years.
Want to know why?
Alright.
Because I'm not too smart, son.
And neither are you.
But on this job, someone
else is putting up the brains.
And if we're lucky
and you don't fool around,
you'll get out of here
with your life sorted out.
- I don't fool around.
- Come on, damn it. Let's go.
Fill them up.
Answer the phone and
convince whoever is calling that
we are shut down due to
a technical problem. Got it?
Yes.
I have no choice but
to point a gun at you.
- Can you feel it?
- Yes.
Alright.
Now.
Royal Mint, can I help you?
I'm sorry, Arturo can't
be reached at the moment.
The system is down.
No, I can't leave right now.
No, he's not able
to answer the phone.
No, it's not possible.
No...
Look, I don't know
where he is right now,
I don't know if he's
somewhere in the Mint,
the museum, or the cafeteria,
anywhere! We're busy around here, lady!
That performance deserves
an Oscar, Miss Gaztambide.
20 minutes in,
we started wiring our
analogue communication
system to talk to the Professor.
Cellphone free, no radio frequencies,
so no one can hear us.
We sealed all doors
and the alarms hadn't gone off yet.
We were in a time limbo,
without anyone knowing
that we seized the Royal Mint.
And during that sweet
calm before the storm,
it simply seemed like
just another day.
You're a handsome guy.
Who is it?
It's me, let me in.
What are you doing, Rio? If the Professor
catches us, he'll kill us, you know?
I know, Come here.
I have to talk to you. Come here.
- What's going on?
- Sit down.
What is it?
The heist is tomorrow.
And we have no fucking
idea what will happen.
I want you to know
I'm serious about you
and...
I completely understand that,
that you're a little older, and...
and it's possible you want
something more serious.
That's why I want to give you this.
I didn't get you a ring
because we're stuck in here,
but when we get out of here
I'll get you a big-ass ring.
You'll carry your hand
in a wheelbarrow. You'll see.
Is that right?
What's this?
An engagement dog tag?
Now at least you'll know my real name.
But we're not allowed
to know each other's names.
Well, don't look at it.
But it's yours.
How do I tell you this?
What we've got has been
very good, okay? Awesome.
We've been together a few nights...
A few nights? Every night...
Except for what, four or five...
Yeah, well.
I don't think we're
meant for each other.
- Isn't the sex good?
- Yes, the sex is very good.
Well, that's a start, right?
But it takes more than
good sex for it to work.
Is this because I'm 12
years younger than you?
I'm getting
300 million euros.
I'm not a kid, my life is all set.
Really, Rio, I wish
there was love, but...
Hey. Don't say that. There was
love, really. I was there, I saw.
There's someone else?
He's gone.
Look, Rio,
when this is all over,
We'll go together to Tahiti
and we'll see how that works, tomorrow
I need to focus on only one thing:
staying alive.
Rio.
Rio, no. No, no.
One of the phones is on.
Turn it off.
Okay, the vault is open.
Put on your vest and be ready to go out.
Then we'll activate the alarm.
Berlin, get ready to open up the doors.
Hostages, for your own safety,
move three steps to the back!
A little bit more. Here. That's it.
There you go. Everything will be all right.
A little bit closer.
Everything's going to be okay.
Shh. Relax
Relax. I'm looking at the bags.
They're filled with cash.
They're gonna clear out of here in no time.
We have a 10-33 at the Royal Mint.
Z24 on our way.
We'll be there in two minutes."
Two minutes.
- Why is the alarm on?
- I don't know.
They're just standing there,
not doing anything.
- Why don't they just leave?
- I can't tell!
One minute, 40 seconds.
One minute and...
What's your name?
Arturo.
Arturo, is it?
Yes. No, I haven't
seen anything!
I haven't seen anything, I swear,
I haven't seen anything!
- Look at me.
- Please.
Arturo, come on. Look at me.
- Look at me, look at me.
- I haven't seen anything!
Hey, hey, come on. Hey.
Do you like movies?
Do you?
Yes, I'm fond of movies.
Okay. Have you noticed
how in horror movies
in the beginning, there
is always a nice guy,
and you say: "He's
going to get himself killed",
Yes.
- and then it happens.
- No...
The man's killed.
Arturo, trust me, you're
gonna get yourself killed.
- Z24 to central, we're 30 seconds away.
- 30 seconds.
30 seconds.
Listen. It's absolutely imperative
that the police don't have
any idea what we're doing.
We'll have them think it's just a robbery,
that we were caught fleeing with
the money and everything went south,
that we pulled our guns, and opened fire
at point-blank range, we had no choice...
but retreat.
And then, without having hurt
anyone,
we go back inside.
Let them think that we're cornered.
Let them think we're improvising.
Now!
Tokyo! Tokyo, wait, damn it!
Tokyo!
Go out, toss the
money in the air,
fire toward the ground
and get back inside.
I'd heard that more than 30 times.
But what the Professor never told us
is that they would also fire back
Rio, Rio!
Damn it to hell!
Holy shit!
You know it! It was
the first fucking rule!
Fuck!
Rio.
Fuckers!
requesting immediate
backup at the Royal Mint.
We've received hostile fire. Man down.
I repeat, man down.
The bullet of an M16 bullet
shoots out at 2,100 MPH
Faster than the speed of sound.
So if they shot you in the heart,
you won't even hear
the bullet that killed you.
That's how I knew that I fucked it all up,
in one microsecond
and the same way as always.