I need authorization. I don't see.
What have you done?
Tell me what happened to Monica
What the fuck have you done?
They're pointing at each other.
- Give me the green light.
- They're going to execute them, sir.
You fucking assholes, tell me!
Get down!
- Get down now!
- They're going to kill them.
Do it, then.
Condor 3, open fire.
Arturo!
SATURDAY
6:00 PM
Yes! Great work, Torres. Pure perfection.
Now we're changing the series.
As well as the lettering, got it?
Another country, ok?
So get on it.
Come on, hurry up. Move it.
Get ahead of me.
Come on quickly, let's go.
Filthy sons of bitches!
Come on, let's go. Quickly.
Easy.
Water.
Water, please. Water.
Arturo, wait.
Don't give him any more water.
Take your hand away.
Alright. Here we go.
Raquel.
We have breaking news to report.
We have just learned
the identity of the man
who was shot and
wounded by the police.
He is Arturo Román,
director of operations where
the situatiuon has been unfolding.
Román was wounded
by a police sniper
while he was on the roof
with the attackers.
The incident occurred 32 hours
after the standoff began.
32 HOURS INTO ROBBERY
I need to talk to my wife right away.
I have to see her. Please let me.
They say that when we
stand at the threshold of Death
we can finally see
our lives clearly.
As Arturo Román laid
bleeding out on the table,
he waited for the
clarity of death
to reveal to him who the
true love of his life was.
What would the answer be?
Would it be Laura,
his loving and devoted
wife of 14 years?
Or Mónica,
his secretary and lover, who made
him feel like a young man again?
Sadly, the only
certainty for Arturo
is that we'll either
dig the bullet out,
or he'll die before finding
the answer to his question
And frankly,
our minimal amount of medical training
offers little hope for his survival.
Inferior vein,
both of the kidneys, the
right one and the left one.
Mesenteric organ.
Then we have the lungs.
The right one and the left.
From the heart, we have the veins.
Subclavian, right and left.
Brachial.
Humeral.
Internal jugular.
And external jugular.
Red lines are main arteries.
Hold on a minute. Wait, wait.
You want us...
to learn basic surgery
skills with some markers?
If someone gets shot,
you don't go to the hospital.
You handle it yourselves.
- This is suicide.
- Son, that's enough.
Being confined in that
mouse trap is one thing.
- Getting killed is another.
- Denver.
He's just teaching you
how to remove a bullet.
you're not learning brain surgery.
- It's not that hard, really.
- Yeah, no big deal.
You just gotta take the pliers,
get the bullet and take it out.
Hey, if I end up taking a bullet...
please rush me to a
hospital and a real doctor.
Yeah, and then to jail.
I'd rather be free without legs
than be in jail and healthy.
No one gets out.
We act as a single unit
and if anyone wants to walk away,
then now is the moment.
You'll stay inside
for as long as it takes.
So, we done?
I'm cold and shriveled
up, like Helsinki's dick.
Our dick's bigger than you are.
That's enough everyone.
- Really.
- Please.
- I bet it's tiny.
- Get dressed.
Someone else now.
- Fuck you.
- Pull it out.
Come on.
No?
-  No, no, no...
- Coward.
- At last. This is worth watching.
- Do it, Nairobi.
- It's no big deal.
- Look at this hottie!
What a sexy lady.
Very sexy.
- Your turn.
- Oh!
Let's see what you've learned.
Well, this is the carotid artery...
"I realized that as we played doctor."
"There was much more to
Nairobi than met the eye."
The heart is right here.
The aorta...
"Even though none of
us knew each other..."
The abdominal...
"I would not have guessed
that Nairobi had given birth."
"She had a scar along her belly."
"It was evidence of a C-section."
- Get out of there.
- Okay, okay!
What the hell do you
think you are doing, huh?
What's wrong?
- What were you looking for?
- Why? What happened?
- Nothing.
- No. You're a perv, that's what.
- Hey. Hey.
- She tried to get between my legs.
I'll shove that marker
up your ass, you bitch.
From what I saw, I'm pretty sure
nobody would want what's down there.
"That's where our friendship began."
I have them on the phone.
What should I tell them, Raquel?
- Raquel! They're holding.
- What?
They'll ask who gave
the order to take the shot.
I gave the order.
Just say... the hostage was wounded.
Hang up the damn phone!
I asked for the green light.
He looked like one
of them. I insisted.
Inspector, I'll share the
responsibility for this.
Inspector, the ambulance is here.
I'm ready to talk with him now.
Now patching through
the call to the kidnapper.
Can you explain to
me how this happened?
We were forced to
make a tough choice.
It looked like they were
gonna start shooting
and we had no
time to deliberate.
Silence, please!
Professor?
You shot a hostage.
He's in danger of dying.
I suppose that's why you called.
We have an
ambulance ready to go.
No one leaves here.
- That man is bleeding out.
- From a bullet shot by one of yours.
You would let him die?
Let us at least send
in a medical team.
Professor, I'm...
aware it's my fault.
It was my mistake,
and mine alone.
But if one of the hostages dies,
things will go very
badly for both of us.
The public will immediately
think that he died
because neither of us gave enough
of a damn to save the man's life.
Two surgeons and a nurse
with surgical tools.
- Let me know when you're here.
- Thank you.
Also, the man has a request.
He'd like to talk to his wife.
Of course. I...
Find Mr Román's wife.
How soon could a
medical team get here?
If we fly them in from La Paz,
20 minutes or so.
- Get them. Now!
- Alright.
Excuse me.
Can you drive?
Yes, yes.
I need to get out of here, now.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Raquel. Hey.
What's wrong?
I have to think.
Let's go.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not leaving you alone.
Where the hell is she?
God damn bitch has bolted!
There we go.
All right.
Answer the phone.
Hello, darling.
Are you coming home tonight?
I don't know, mom.
What's the matter?
Mum...
I made...
a huge mistake at work.
Well, it's not like you don't
have a difficult job, darling.
Listen. Why don't you
tell me what happened.
Things don't seem as bad as
they are, if you talk about them.
I was um...
drinking wine with...
with...
Oh, you had a date.
Is he someone I know?
No, mom. Even I
don't know who he is.
What happened was...
When I returned to the command post,
there was
a high risk situation
on the factory's roof
and I felt that the
hostages were in danger
I gave the order to shoot.
And because of that
order, a hostage was shot.
Yes. I saw that
on the television.
I don't know what to do now.
Should I call his wife,
Or...
should I issue a
press release, or quit.
I don't know what to do, mom.
Blaming yourself is really the last
thing you should ever do, sweetheart.
I mean, weren't those people all
wearing masks and holding guns?
It had to be confusing for you.
You were looking
out for the hostages,
isn't that right?
And... what if you had saved
someone's life?"
Then, I doubt you'd
even be having
this conversation with
your mother right now.
But, there was an upside to this.
I learnt something new about my daughter.
She's finally starting
to meet other men.
Good God!
Can we not talk about this?
Darling, we have a
short time in this world...
Yeah, mom. I know. But...
That's not the issue here.
The issue is that I'm in a
really tough position at work.
Then screw your job. Go forward.
Just tell them you want to
stamp passports instead.
Then you can enjoy life,
instead of stressing about this.
Do you want to end up in a retirement home
still obsessing over this case?
But...
what about that stranger, hmm...
Go ahead and laugh, I
know what I'm talking about.
I've been a widow for 20 years.
but...
Time always moves on.
If only we could turn it back.
We're entering the perimeter.
I'll think about it, mom.
If I'm not home early,
go to bed, alright?
Fine.
You should sleep with
someone too, you know.
RACHEL LIKES A STRANGER
Well, look who it is?
I saw your stomach scar.
and...
I was nosy.
I didn't know what it was.
Sorry.
Fine. You're forgiven.
Okay. Now, go away.
What the hell?
Get out!
I don't want company!
So, how old?
Your kid.
Seven.
He's seven.
Who's he with?
The boy's dad?
With the dad? Yeah, right.
No. He's not with his father.
That guy is long gone.
What's his name?
Axel.
His name's Axel.
You know, like an axe.
Axe.
Yeah.
Fits him, too.
Like his mother.
That kid is a survivor, you know?
He's gone through a lot.
He's like a cork on the sea,
defying the water.
he won't sink.
He's strong.
He was three years old.
We'd been living at
my mother's place.
We left, though.
Her husband, when I was out,
would give the boy some alcohol.
He couldn't stand
my son's crying.
So, I took Axel away. Just him and me.
No one else.
Us two. We did great by ourselves.
But...
I fucked up.
One day...
I went to make
a sale... of pills.
And...
He was alone.
Just five minutes.
I was only gone five minutes.
That's all it took.
He was getting into mischief,
always pretending
that he was Spider-Man!
It's why I hate Spider-Man today.
Axel was always having
fun as a superhero.
He would climb on everything.
Especially, when
you weren't looking.
He stood on a chair and then began yelling.
He screamed: "Mommy!"
"Mommy!"
He was three and a half.
Well, it was reported, so...
Then all the cops,
firemen, EMTs in the area...
arrived in a hurry.
Everyone.
They booked me on
possesion with intent.
I had no job.
Had priors.
Went to jail.
My child was thrown
into foster care.
And they passed him
around from family to family.
And me, nothing.
Nothing, huh?
No visits.
No calls.
No letters No contact of any kind.
I got out of jail.
and nothing.
They've got my son.
- You've seen him?
- They won't let me.
Although...
I know where he is.
- Where?
- Canarys.
He's with a family
that has a hotel.
He's well.
So, now what?
I'll get my boy.
That's all there is to it.
We'll go far away.
And I'm gonna tell
you something else.
No one in this group
is gonna screw
up this job, no one.
Because I swear, if anyone does,
I am going to kill them.
Out of everyone's plans,
yours...
is the best.
One last question.
Like tequila?
Um...
Hello there.
It's 4:03 am. You both know that.
We have class this morning.
Plastic explosives.
Sorry.
Get some rest
before then, alright?
It's past our bedtime?
Go to bed.
- All three of us?
- Go to bed!
The jammies look
nice on you, Professor.
Now.
Right now.
You're still... you're still
wearing the stupid lights.
You know, I want that man so much.
He makes me feel so horny.
I can't even stand it!
- Wow, I can't tell.
- You can't?
No...
I bet he can.
Mónica. Hey... Hey, hey hey.
Hey.
You shouldn't be here.
I don't feel well.
I think it's just a reaction to the meds.
The meds, huh.
Yeah.
That would explain
why you're feeling lousy.
Well, she's really burning up.
- We have to get her out of here now.
- Stop
- Come one. Let's go.
- I'm gonna be sick.
Leave me alone for a minute.
Please.
What is it?
She isn't so good.
She's worse.
We've got to extract that bullet
or that woman's gona die.
Take it easy, papa.
She'll be alright.
Damn it! Why the
hell did you shoot her?
Berlin would have killed her.
What else could I do?
Son of a bitch.
Let him pull the trigger
next time, not you.
We're here for a robbery.
Not to kill. Or save lives.
Why the hell did we
get ourselves involved
- in this fucking mess?
- Papa, relax. Come on, relax.
Don't worry.
Mónica, are you finished?
Yes.
Let's go.
Raquel, wait a minute.
I want to talk to you.
I'm going to go in
with the medical unit.
No.
I can't let you go.
Yeah right.
I guess there's
always someone better.
Raquel, I'm a firearms expert.
I would be able to go in, assess
how many guns they have,
and whether or not they're fake.
and I can spot the real attackers.
Alright.
You can go in with
the medical unit.
I'll go over it with you.
I heard a shot.
It was the police.
They shot a hostage.
- Really?
- Yes.
Who got shot?
Who was it?
The hostage, who was it?
The factory director.
Arturo?
The police killed Arturo?
No. He wasn't killed.
- You mean it?
- Yes.
Swear to me.
- Arturo's alive?
- I swear to you.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure.
They're sending a surgeon
with his team.
They'll operate and
he'll be fine, okay?
- Operate?
- Yes.
Here.
Tell him that I'm alive.
You have to tell Arturo.
- You have to.
- No one is telling anyone anything.
Because you'll be fine
and so will he, okay?
Now, let's just take
a look at that wound.
Just relax.
He is going to think
this was all his fault.
He asked me to take the phone.
He'll think I've been
killed because of him.
He need to know
that I'm alive. Please.
And his son, as well.
Are you pregnant?
That's great.
Congratulations.
- Have a pen, Denver? Please?
- Of course.
When?
Thanks.
Ángel!
I've decided to send a
group inside to help out.
Ángel will be going in
with the medical unit.
Did you decide that while joyriding
in the ambulance, inspector?
At least I'm here to make sure
that no further outbreaks of violence
occur under your watch, okay?
Well.
Pacifism is new for the CNI.
You wanted to roll
in tanks, yesterday.
I wanted to surprise them
and finish all of this quickly.
Now my priority is zero casualties.
I advise that you
negotiate and wait.
I guess it must drive you up a wall
to be in charge of us,
but not have an ounce of power.
You're just a pawn
who can't call the shots.
I'm not getting into this,
because I know how hormones
can affect your thinking.
Especially a woman of your age.
Just like my mother.
You're leaving?
I'm sure you know, this
has to be reported, right?
Of course.
Until now, they've been two
steps ahead of us the entire way.
They planned out
everything. Except for this.
The one thing they hadn't planned.
This is our only chance.
The one way in without being
detected by their cameras
is through this underground access tunnel.
It leads to the basement.
Which connects to
the ventilation shafts.
And that tunnel was added on
only about seven months ago.
It's still under construction.
They probably don't have
any idea that it's even there.
I need two men to
enter through there.
In that case, Officer Lobo
here, and I will go.
Good.
Assistant Inspector Rubio will go
in as a nurse with the two doctors
It's 18:09 right now.
Set your watches.
At 18:15, the team will move in.
According to the doctors,
the operation shouldn't
take more than 30 minutes.
But you can't go in until
precisely 19:00 hours.
After the surgery, when the
doctors are ready to leave,
the kidnappers will
be on their guard.
That's when Suárez and Lobo
will enter through the tunnel.
You'll both be wearing the same
overalls and masks as the kidnappers.
That way, you'll blend in.
We need precision timing
in order for this to work.
Inspector!
Arturo Román's wife is here.
One moment, please.
Suárez, move out.
Protect the doctors. Good luck.
All units to the front.
Is he alright? Tell me the truth.
Your husband's awake and he's stable.
He's suffered a gunshot wound.
- He was shot? How badly?
- No. He's wounded, but he'll make it.
Relax. Relax.
The suspects have allowed
a medical team to go inside
and perform an operation on your husband.
I'm sorry, but...
I didn't hear what you
were saying. I'm too upset.
Yes, I know.
Everything will be okay.
- Have a seat, won't you.
- Thanks.
- I'll let you talk to him right now.
- Okay.
Put this on.
- Go on.
- Thank you.
Almansa, start recording.
That bullet needs to come out.
Can you do it?
Your hands are steadier.
Well...
What happened to the
medical kit that we brought in?
- It had a scalpel.
- Berlin has it.
Shit.
And I wouldn't
ask him for it either.
The surgeons!
Go and get one
from them. Hurry it up.
- Okay.
- Wait! Wait!
Give this to Arturo, please.
I'm going to clean
your wound up, okay?
You just relax.
It'll be alright.
Yes?
Professor, we have
Arturo Román's wife here.
Okay.
Arturo.
Arturo!
Your wife's name is...
Laura.
Pretty name.
You may talk to her now.
Wives are meant
for these moments.
They comfort us.
Yet a husband will ignore
the fact that he's married
and doesn't think about his
wife when he's out carousing.
But...
When there's a problem,
or an accident...
or he's afraid of something...
things change.
Or are you thinking
of your secretary?
You are.
No.
Who has time to
think about lovers or...
those pesky abortions...
- or anything?
- Spare me your speech, you...
Listen up.
If you say anything
stupid, I'll shoot you
so that your wife
will listen as you die.
Got it?
Inspector!
They're calling the cellphone.
We have to hack the cellphone.
I want to see through the
front and back cameras.
Here you go. talk.
Hello, sweetheart.
Arturo, how are you, my love?
Fine, fine. I'm okay.
- I was shot in the shoulder so the bullet...
- No image.
There's nothing on either camera.
They're black.
I hear they're bringing in
some doctors to operate on me.
I know.
I've been worried...
about us for a long while now.
And everything we did wrong.
Don't think about that,
sweetheart. Not now.
Not now.
Besides, it's my own fault.
I know we're not okay.
And we haven't been for some time.
I've been distant
from you and the kids.
I've been very selfish.
But I promise things are
going to be better, okay?
I promise you, they'll change.
You've been saying
for 10 years how much
you want to see your
sister in Australia.
Once this is all over,
maybe the kids can
finally get to go there and
see some kangaroos.
That's the first thing
we'll do when I get home.
You deserve more.
But I promise I love you.
And I'd do anything for you.
All of these years I wasted,
chasing stupid things
like money and status.
I realize now, those
things were never important.
It's always been you.
Since the first day I met you.
There are some times when...
I sit there thinking
about that day...
And I'm still wondering what
the hell you saw in me, Mónica.
Laura.
Just think about
getting out of there.
Just think about that.
I love you.
I love you, my dear.
Are you alright?
It's okay.
Relax.
You're a piece of work, Arturo.
Your secretary is pregnant
with your baby.
The wifey is waiting for
you in the SUV with the kids.
And you, wallowing cash,
you're a living legend.
Berlin!
The doctors are outside!
If you'll excuse me.
Everyone knows their jobs?
Of course. They
all know their parts.
Are you ready?
Yes.
They're ready.
Mercedes.
Are you ready?
- Yes, sir.
- I want her out of here.
Rio, take her to the office.
Nairobi.
Everybody, put your masks on!
And follow me! Rock and roll!
Walk forward.
Leave everything on the floor.
Close the doors.
Follow us.
Hands on your heads
and spread your legs.
We're gonna pat you down.
Please escort the gentleman out.
Listen to me.
One of those doctors
is with the police.
- Which one?
- The one with glasses.
You know what to do.
- Absolutely. We're on it.
- Berlin!
This has to be
handled flawlessly.
I know.
Apparently
The man wearing
glasses is an officer.
They'll get in.
I don't know if it
wil be a breach,
or forced entry, or...
a Red Cross volunteer,
or a pizza guy.
but they are going
to infiltrate somehow.
And that will be our opportunity
to employ a Trojan horse.
What's that?
- I don't know, but it rhymes with...
- No!
- The Trojan horse is...
- Rhymes with hoarse!
Shut up and pay
attention, smart-ass.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
The Greeks were at
war with the Trojans.
One day, the Trojans
saw a wooden horse
a giant wooden horse.
at their gates.
Their vanity led them to think
the Greeks had surrendered
and that this was a gift.
So the Trojans
opened the city gates...
and pulled it inside.
They didn't know that
the horse was hollow
and filled with Greek soldiers.
The Trojans were
easily defeated.
And that's the strategy
we're going to use.
When they're inside
and believe that they're
winning the battle...
Place all metal
objects in this bin.
That goes for watches and glasses.
If you have weapons, or
anything that emits a signal
I urge you to place them here.
We're tracing every signal.
Remove your shoes too, please.
Now lie face down on the floor.
That's it.
Like roaches.
On your feet.
Put your shoes on.
Take the glasses only.
You'll need those.
Okay... welcome.
Grab your things
and come with me.
Thank you.