No, no. There is no damn way
I'm going in there.
Go get the tank.
This is a fucking rattrap.
We won't get out.
You come out the way you go in. Simple.
What the fuck is that smell?
They must have put pesticides,
bleach and shit that's toxic.
I'm not going in there.
- It's just water.
- Yeah, toxic water.
Go sit down.
I'll sit, but I'm not going in.
Fine.
It would be easier to train in a pool,
but we're not gonna be in a pool.
It's gonna be way scarier
than getting in here.
And you can't go in scared.
That's good because I'm not scared.
You're fucked, kid.
Thanks.
You're scared because you're a father.
Look.
I think you actually have a point, Bogotá.
Before you had your son,
you'd have jumped in an open grave.
Now you've got something to lose.
Before, if something happened,
it was just me that was fucked. You know?
Now, there's things I don't want to do.
Like get in a fucking sewage tank.
I don't want to.
Do you how to be a good father?
No, I don't.
Behave like you did before
you were a father.
Sure, go to the clubs
and crawl home fucked up on a Wednesday.
If you like getting fucked up
on Wednesdays, then keep doing it.
I don't know.
You gotta stay consistent
or you'll end up hating your son.
That's what makes a bad father.
Believe me.
Jesus Christ. Do you know
what you should do, Bogotá?
You should write a book.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
How to Be a Father Without Quitting Drugs.
You don't have kids, do you?
Seven.
- You serious?
- This it look like I'm lying?
Emilio, my oldest, lives in Venezuela.
Julián, he's in Mexico City.
He almost has a mustache now.
He calls me "güey."
Erik's a tough bastard, he's in Iceland.
Hanna, in Finland. Violinist.
She's gorgeous.
Drazen in Montenegro. He's dumb as fuck.
Yaris, in Greece, she's a character.
Ivanna, she's got a temper,
but she's an artist.
Lives in Ukraine.
Seven.
So I guess you weren't lying.
But I still feel ashamed just to know you.
Look, I take care of all of them.
But I'm still me.
I don't go see the school play,
or his games,
or whatever they do in… in Iceland.
I don't.
I show up after six months or a year
and I don't ask for anything.
Not a hug or their love.
But they throw their arms around my neck.
Why?
- Huh?
- I don't know. Why?
'Cause I'm their fucking father.
Their father.
You can't give up DNA.
Never.
If you are a thief, keep being one.
And if you risked your life,
then keep risking it.
Sweeties, honeys, darlings…
Look what I brought you.
Look at these little earrings
that I found. Look at them, huh?
All shiny and golden! Can I pull this off?
Check this out.
What? You wanna hold them?
- Come on!
- Here, take them, kid.
It's like you've never seen gold before.
Come on, get to work.
There's a lot more where that came from.
Open for Bogotá.
♪ And it's plain to see ♪
Come on, gentleman.
The worst is over.
This is where the fun starts.
The wet suit
doesn't look bad on you, Nairobi.
Excuse me?
That little ass could warm up my balls.
Why don't you go warm your balls
with your own fat ass?
You weird fuck.
It's not funny.
Why would you talk to me like that? Huh?
Here on this heist, I'm your boss.
Yes, boss. Excuse me.
How about you show me some respect.
Change his tank!
And you guys,
move it, people.
I wanna see these ovens working yesterday.
Get the smoke extractors connected.
We're gonna melt
this fucking national reserve down.
And you! The lance and the bathyscaphe.
Highest priority.
You've got me feeling so pleased.
Let's go, gentlemen!
And one, and two, and one, and two…
Smile!
Let's earn our lunch! Come on!
♪ Oh, whoa, oh ♪
♪ I got a love that keeps me waiting ♪
♪ I'm a lonely boy ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, oh ♪
The first time I heard
fire would burn underwater
was at the Monastery of San Giovanni.
It seemed as unlikely
as me being in a monastery
listening to Gregorian chants.
But when they told me
that the fire's wrapped bubbles of oxygen…
It seemed like a beautiful way
of getting what we came for.
A way to break into a safe
that no one would've noticed was there
next to all that gold.
They got in by pretending to be the first
platoon of the sixth company of BRIPAC.
The real unit arrived a few minutes later.
Those mother fuckers.
We've been compromised.
They probably bugged the fucking pope.
Get every device they can hack
out of the tent.
Anything that connects to a network,
all the phones!
Colonel, let's think.
Why don't we start by doing a sweep?
- They can't hack everything.
- They can hack whatever they want.
They have one billion euros.
Do you know what ITU's budget is?
Sixteen million.
And the whole CNI? 282 million!
282 million against a billion.
They've even tapped the janitor.
We only have evidence that they tapped
communications at the--
These guys even have pictures of your dick
and photos of the mole on your left nut.
Do you want to say hi?
Because they've got your mic…
Colonel, the protocol
is to do a sweep. Listen to me.
Attention everyone!
Nobody turn on any devices unless it's
been in a box for the last six months.
Not even a typewriter.
There are no secure networks,
not the army's or the ministry's.
Total blackout.
I want all your phones in this trash can.
Now!
If you wanna call your mom,
go find a phone booth.
In less than one minute,
we'll be deaf and blind.
Come on.
They just fucked us up.
He's bypassing all the protocols.
It's completely illegal,
taking the phones without a warrant.
Fuck!
This changes everything.
The technicians
will analyze them…
Let me think.
Antoñanzas, what didn't you get?
Just deleting a few private things.
Thirty seconds, Colonel.
Fuck me! We all know you have a thing
for Marisol. Quit fucking around.
- 20 seconds.
- Listen to me. We're in alert level five.
All the NIC security system
has been hijacked,
staff bugged and computers
infected by Christ knows what.
The last thing the ITU are gonna do
is read your texts.
Give me the fucking phone!
Goddamn it!
Put the countdown until the security lock
at the bank is open on that screen.
Let's go!
You!
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong
I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now but I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
There we go. That's it.
That's it.
All done.
- Saline.
- Thank you.
Stay still.
That's it. There we go.
Okay. You're okay.
Okay, that's it.
Palermo.
Palermo, it's urgent.
Professor. It's Tokyo.
How is Palermo?
Operational, señor.
They found out
we had them bugged.
We had to speed everything up.
But keep calm.
Keep calm?
Calm is what you can be
in your van, sweetheart.
In here, we're surrounded by the army.
We don't know when they'll enter.
And we don't know where.
Has Bogotá already started?
Yeah, he's slaving away down there.
Cutting that door will take more
than an hour. Maybe more than two.
Professor, how much time do we have?
- Fourteen minutes.
- What?
They really fucked us and they know it.
Let's go for another move.
I even have doubts about Prieto.
That fucker Tamayo
is gonna ignore rules and protocols.
What does that mean?
It means they're gonna enter as soon
as they unblock the doors.
Fine.
I guess the only alternative
is to use the dolphin. Isn't that right?
Exactly. You have it?
Yes.
Flipper is in here with us.
Colonel, radio waves
are coming in and out of the bank.
Shortwave signals.
Put them on the speaker,
I wanna hear them.
What the fuck is this?
It looks like an encrypted radio system.
Once inside, the big question is,
how do we communicate with each other?
Palermo.
Boom!
A bomb exploded.
We're all dead.
Laser sensors.
Technology is fantastic, huh?
Internet, hidden IP clones.
With the money we have,
we could buy a satellite in Kazakhstan.
But it all leads us to the same place.
The exact same shit.
Because technology
is fought with technology.
And the state can win that battle. Now…
There's something
that they can't compete with,
a trip back in time, hmm?
1941.
Made in England.
With gadgets like this,
the BBC broadcasted
from Great Britain to the whole world.
Shortwave, ladies and gentlemen.
No technology can stop this frequency.
We'll talk with this.
With that thing, anyone can listen to us.
Yes, Nairobi, that's true. Any asshole
with a walkie-talkie can listen.
However,
actually understanding us
is a different story.
Cyber encryption, huh?
Used for the broadcast and reception.
It's not simple.
It's going to be encoded in 2,300 layers.
Even 200 million Chinese hackers
wouldn't be able to decipher it.
Synchronicity.
The monks. "The Spirit of the Creator."
Mentes tuorum visita.
Imple superna gratia.
They will be there,
peeling back layer after layer,
cursing our mothers.
Their tech team
will be desperate.
They'll waste tons
of government funds for nothing.
Because for every call we make,
we will encode 2,300 more layers.
Call,
encrypt.
If it is an encryption system,
what do we do? Decipher it.
Have entire technological research unit
come if necessary.
And start working on it, now!
Okay then.
I want everyone to get their vests
and masks on in two minutes.
We're also giving you weapons.
Fake ones. Don't get too excited.
Amanda, right?
- I'm--
- Miguel.
You knew?
Well, I knew
because I heard you say to the robber.
I put away your lunch once.
Do you remember that?
You know?
Not really.
Put on your vest now!
You're going to need it.
Don't put it on.
Huh?
- No.
- Do not put it on. Don't put your vest on!
They wanna use us as human shields.
It's true. Don't put it on.
We found him.
The head of the class.
The honor student.
- It's not like that.
- It's not?
What's your name, Einstein?
- Miguel, Miguel.
Miguel, I'm Mr. Denver.
Yes, Mr. Denver. Miguel.
Good. You like movies?
No, sir. I watch TV.
I want you to get suited up
because we're gonna play a little game.
Put on your vest!
Give me that.
It's backwards, Miguel. Other way.
Good.
You're gonna put this on, too.
If you don't, this will hurt.
Faster!
Good.
I'm gonna take seven steps
and then I'm gonna shoot. Okay?
If you guess the movie
before I turn around,
maybe I won't shoot you.
Sir, please.
Miguel is a robot.
One.
Two.
Three. Nothing Miguel? Come on.
I'll give you another clue.
I am also a robot.
Four.
WALL-E. WALL-E.
I come from the future
with no clothes on, Miguel.
- WALL-E.
- No, no, no.
WALL-E.
WALL-E?
You calling me WALL-E, Miguel?
No. No, Mr. Denver.
Terminator.
I'm the Terminator.
Hasta la vista, baby.
The show's over! Come on!
Let's go! I want two lines.
Get along.
Let's go.
- Come on.
- Come on, masks on.
Put them on, I'm not kidding.
Who the fuck forgot
to turn off their phone?
Forgive me, it's mine.
HIDDEN NUMBER
Yes?
Colonel Prieto, it's
Professor. I hope you're feeling better.
Hello, Professor.
Sorry I disrupted
your dental appointment.
I hope that I'm not causing you
too much trouble.
You are never any bother, Professor.
Help me out.
I'm a little confused.
Are you in charge of this operation?
Or is it Tamayo?
Colonel Tamayo speaking.
- From this moment, I'm in charge.
- Nice to meet you, Colonel Tamayo.
NEGOTIATION
If that happens, we will call them.
Never the reverse.
And we'll call on the telephone but
they will not be able to track our calls.
And why?
Here, we're also going
to travel back in time.
I had that phone for five years
and only charged it once.
Second-generation cell phones.
Without Internet and,
most importantly, without GPS.
With each of these phones,
we will make one call.
Only one, no more,
to an outside operative.
Marseille.
So the mute isn't going in?
- I'm not mute.
- Sure. Does your rat do the talking?
Something like…
She's not a rat.
Her name is Sofía.
Marseille
will have two terminals.
The first will receive my call
and the second
will dial the only number
saved in its contacts.
Our friend Colonel Prieto.
Those two phones will be our firewall.
Archaic.
Rudimentary.
But effective.
The police can locate
the phone that's calling
at the exact moment of the call.
But that's it, nothing else.
There is no technology
that can track two cell phones
stuck in a box
and constantly moving.
Besides, without GPS,
without Internet…
The only thing
they will have is the repeater
the phone connects to
when making the call.
A repeater located
in the center of Madrid.
Right in front of their noses.
And that's the only thing they'll have.
Which is…
nothing.
Pardon me, since we don't know each other,
I wanted to ask you something.
Are you in love?
I've been married for more than 17 years,
something that is no longer in style.
That is an irrefutable
proof of love, Professor.
Yes, I understand.
However, forgive me, but…
I don't believe you're actually in love.
When someone is in love,
they look through rose-colored glasses.
Everything is wonderful,
they transform into a soft teddy bear
that's smiling all the time.
And they do not shout and lose
their tempers and harass their coworkers.
That's why I was asking.
I know you've been listening to us,
you piece of shit.
Colonel,
do you remember
the last time you made love?
Professor… You and your titillating
conversations, you can go fuck yourselves.
Colonel, since you've only just arrived,
let me remind you
of the first lines of the NIC's manual
on hostage negotiation.
They say verbatim,
"Listen actively and understand
the psychology of the abductor."
"Show, you feel empathy towards him
and you understand his feelings."
You know what?
I think you've gone blind and deaf.
That's why Prieto's phone rang a second
before he left.
I'm beginning to think
you are fucked, Professor.
This isn't the same as that tropical beach
you must have been on
after the Mint, is it?
By the way, how did that getaway go?
How is Murillo?
Hello, Colonel Tamayo.
Colonel Prieto.
Ángel.
I imagine you're there listening.
Okay, were you able to track…
Just don't lose them.
Hello, Raquel. How are you?
We've missed you here in the command tent.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry for leaving like that,
without a word.
How are you?
Well, you know me. I…
I can put up with a lot.
And Mari Carmen is she okay?
Mari Carmen…
She left me.
A long time coming, don't you think?
I'm very sorry, Ángel.
Colonel, they're on
the Princesa Street repeater.
Look at those mother fuckers!
They're right next to us.
Raquel, can you tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Are you sure this is what you really want?
Listen…
This is my life now.
And do you know what?
It's a thousand times better than before.
Why, do you think
you're in a movie or something?
Listen to me, Raquel.
Movies are fantasy, this is real life.
You know I'm gonna
have to chase you, right?
Well, that's nothing new.
You've always chased me.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Colonel, are you still there?
Listen, I'll call you in an hour
and I anticipate that, by then,
I'll have released five hostages.
We're going to do things right this time.
In an hour, I'll be smoking a cigar
in your honor in the governor's office.
Colonel, I'm recording this conversation.
It sounds like you don't care
about the hostages lives.
Well, since it's recording,
I'm going to give you a quick warning.
Take your little mask,
your Browning machine gun
and get ready.
Because the sky is about to fall.
What did we get on this phone call?
The call must be coming from an old phone.
It was impossible
to access their location,
but the conversation was picked up
on repeaters on Princesa and Callao.
- What does that mean?
- There's a lot of people on phones.
The signal jumps from one repeater
to another or they're moving.
You telling me that while we were talking
they were taking a walk,
holding hands, having ice cream?
I want all available units deployed
to identify every motherfucker out there.
Colonel, we're talking about more
than 400,000 people.
People are probably out there
spending the bills they dumped.
The lack of noise in the metallic voice
indicates they weren't on the street.
Maybe they're in a basement
or in a subway tunnel.
It's impossible to know.
Four hours.
Look at her, so innocent,
like she couldn't even hurt a fly.
- I want a child like him.
- Mm.
And those guys?
- What are they doing?
- How would I know?
They're trying to break a record.
I'm telling you, that guy
must do some freaky boyfriend shit.
Ooh.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You have doubts, right? That's it?
You thinking about turning back?
In order to make it perfect…
the plan.
It'd take… It'd take at least four months.
- Four months?
- Four months.
And what will you say to Tokyo?
That the next time she sees Rio,
he'll be a vegetable?
We cannot help Rio
with a plan that doesn't work.
It doesn't work?
We've studied it together.
It's a perfect plan.
No, it isn't. No, it isn't.
You know what your problem is?
You're turning into an egomaniac.
You don't believe in the plan
because it's not yours.
It's your brother's,
but your brother believed in you.
Why are you suddenly so interested
in doing a robbery?
This deep need to be there.
I'm telling you, it's exactly the same
as the people who quit smoking.
They start to hate tobacco
and people who smoke…
and they become
the biggest anti-smoking Taliban.
That's like you with the police.
You hate the police
because they destroyed your life,
because they tried
to take away your daughter,
because there's a warrant out for you
and what you want this revenge.
You want revenge.
You're not thinking about Tokyo, or Rio
or Berlin. You're thinking about yourself.
And if that's the case,
I don't think it's a good idea
for you to be part of the plan.
I need more time.
Relax, I'll take care of this.
Hello.
This way, please.
Of course.
At your service, Inspector.
We know you know them well.
Uh-huh.
In the absence of Fonollosa, AKA Berlin,
who do you think has assumed command?
For what?
What do you mean?
What the hell do you care what it's for?
If we kill the boss first,
we might not have to kill them all.
Got it?
Denver.
No doubt. He's the most seasoned.
Moscow's son.
- Denver. I'm telling you.
- Are you sure?
Absolutely. I know them well.
Look, look, Helsinki is a war criminal.
He only obeys orders.
And Nairobi.
Nairobi staged a coup at the Royal Mint
and took power from Fonollosa.
- Professor would never put her in charge.
- And Tokyo?
Tokyo… Too unstable.
She's a hothead.
It was her fault that Moscow died. No.
Tokyo couldn't command shit.
Listen to me. It's Denver.
Denver.
What was that about?
To get you to talk to me.
And look, it worked.
You're not doing well, Denver.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know. But it's not…
It's not even about all that shit you said
about me being a sexist.
It's something else.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Come on, tell me.
- I know how this will end.
- No.
- There are a lot of ways it can end.
- My father was shot.
You know why?
Because somebody wanted to ride
on a motorcycle. Right, Tokyo?
He was a good man.
And he started acting like a father
in front of 200 policemen
with an M16 and no vest.
And now he's dead.
You understand what I'm saying?
If you're here,
the exact same thing
is gonna happen to me.
If I had to stand in front of
a bullet for you, I would…
in a heartbeat.
Because you are my family, Mónica.
You are my family.
That's why I didn't want you here.
Do you understand that?
Move.
Keep going. Come on. Step, step. Move.
Okay, I'll deal with the Browning.
Very good idea, Helsinki. Much luck.
Let's go. In you go.
You, too.
You have no idea what you're doing.
As soon as I touch the door,
the security system
will flood it in just minutes.
It's gonna flood? No.
It'll bring in more than
100,000 liters of water.
More than 100,000 liters of water?
Nairobi, listen to this guy.
Well, I hope you learned how to snorkel.
You're mistaken if you think I'm bluffing.
I know where you're taking me.
And for what?
I'm telling you now,
I don't plan on doing it.
Come on.
Put it on right now.
Please.
Madam,
step out of the line.
No, I can do it, I can do it.
I have strong hands. I'm okay.
Madam.
Step out of the line, please.
And the rest of you, keep working!
Thank you very much.
Tokyo.
The other heist, I was glued to the TV.
I know all of you.
Hmm?
Sit down.
Get the helicopters in the air.
Now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Hurry up with those bags.
We gotta keep them moving.
If things go wrong,
then we end up
in the worst-case scenario possible,
which is the police is entering
before we've had time
to open that little door.
And opening that door… It'll take
a lot longer than the first one.
And he's the only one who can do it.
Two hours minimum.
Two hours.
And if we haven't opened it
before they come in, then…
Then we're dead.
But I'm sure we have a solution.
There's always a solution.
We have this tiny guy. Huh?
A dolphin.
Yeah, well, we ran out of toy divers.
We named him Flipper.
You remember Flipper, right?
The trained dolphin that gave high fives
and also saved lives.
In case we need it,
it would have to save ours.
The governor of the Bank of Spain
is the only person able to open that door
in three seconds.
This button will regulate the buoyancy.
I'll do it. Don't touch it
or you will end up stuck on the ceiling.
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
We have an emergency respirator.
Hopefully, you won't need to use it.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me!
Once in there,
you'll notice the change in pressure.
Don't panic and most important,
don't stop breathing.
But we've got a problem.
He won't do it.
His entire biography
shows he has principles.
Everybody has principles.
The question the governor
has to ask himself is "What's worth more?"
"My principles
or my life?"
We're running out of time.
Come on. Come on, let's fucking go.
Okay Governor, any questions?
I'm not going in.
I think you are.
- Into the tiny submarine.
- Let's go.
Teams in position.
Locked and loaded, sir.
Gentlemen,
two minutes and thirty seconds.
All right.
"Hasta la vista baby" with Stockholm.
The others with me. Now!
Come on. You heard her. Quickly.
- Move it!
All right, come on.
All the way to the back.
Let's go, come on.
If I have to put the mask on you,
it's gonna be fused to your face.
Put it on, Governor. Put it on.
Huh?
- The hard way, then.
- Let go of me!
I'm not going in there.
He's 60 years old
and has coronary heart disease.
Brilliant.
That works for us.
That's exactly right, coronary disease,
the bathyscaphe, the water pressure…
All of that collides in his head
and gives him extreme lucidity.
The whole plan depends
on the decision of one man.
And I can already say
with absolute certainty it'll be a "no."
And do you know when it will become
definitively clear for him?
Hmm? When he enters that flooded chamber
and understands that he has no escape.
When he realizes that his life depends on
whether we open
or we shut off the oxygen valve.
So Sergio, if you had to pick between
your integrity and oxygen,
what would you choose?
He won't go in.
He will go in.
With a little push.
He'll go in.
You're gonna regret that.
Matías, the bolt cutters.
Let's cut 'em off.
Either you give me the fucking key now
or you'll be counting bills
with your fucking stumps.
You're fucking kidding.
You're a brave man.
- Oh, fuck!
- Denver!
Denver, what the fuck did you do?
For Christ's sake!
Somebody tell me what's happening!
Take this.
Are you okay, Governor?
Governor? Mr. Governor?
Oh, shit! Motherfucker!
What's happening, Nairobi?
- He lost consciousness.
- Goddamn it!
Pulse is 130.
This guy's gonna have a heart attack.
- How much time do we have?
- One minute and 20 seconds.
That much?
Matías, the first-aid kit and the staples.
We have to close the wound.
- Come on!
- Denver!
Direct pressure on the wound!
Yeah, yeah.
Over here, Denver!
Fuck!
Okay, and what happens if,
for whatever reason,
he decides not to open that door?
There's always risks.
Little brother, please.
What would life be
without a tiny bit of risk?
Little brother,
that's what makes it exciting.
And, if something goes wrong,
we always have the C-4.
Bogotá.
Be careful, brother. Okay?
Come on, come on, come on. Ah…
That's it, come on.
Don't be a pussy, goddamn it. Go, go, go.
Come on, come on, come on.
150 beats per minute.
This guy's about to explode.
- C-4 inside there?
- Cyclonite, also called RDX.
- Popularly known as plastic explosives.
- You are crazy.
Well, it's unpredictable.
It would be crude, but so exciting.
It'll shake the whole world.
Gentlemen, we're going in.
We know the primary objective.
We have the green light to open fire
against any member of the gang.
At least 100 hostages have been confirmed,
among which is the governor of the bank.
Streets have been closed and the whole
country is watching the Bank of Spain.
Reports are now coming
in that the governor…
…and assault vehicles are moving in.
For the last few minutes,
helicopters have been circling the area.
Stay tuned for…
Ten milligrams of Diazepam.
You goddamn
motherfucking son of a bitch.
No, no, no.
Come on, kid.
Okay.
An expanding underwater wave,
50 meters deep,
releasing a pressure of 40 atmospheres,
not even our Lord knows
what's gonna happen then.
Denver, remind me to beat
the shit out of you when this is all over.
You stupid son of a bitch.
A little big bang that'll create life.
No, it isn't going down.
Give me another one.
- Another!
- Come on, come on!
Okay, okay, okay. Come on.
It's true it might damage part
of what's inside the box,
but I assure you right now,
we're going to open it.
Oh, God!