Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Core Contents Media Presents
In association with Showbox
A Core Contents Media Production
Co-produced by
Goldenthumb & Poibos
Hey, Jung-sik?
How is it?
What do you think.
I need it for the drama next week
so tell him it's great!
Like Seung-chul ever listens to me.
Then make him. He's gotta do this song.
But the lyrics are weak, man.
What the suits say
goes. That's show biz.
Whatever, man!
- Hold up!
- What is it?
You like this song?
Of course! Why?
Singing about a girl to
come back to me at my age?
My heart this and tears that...
Isn't it childish?
No! It's perfect! Don't you think?
It's great.
Make your fans really
feel the song, man!
But I don't feel anything!
You can do it, man. Feel me?
- It's great!
- No.
It's not working for me.
Seung-chul! Come on!
Get him!
Seung-chul!
Yes, director.
I see.
KWON Sang-woo
Next Tuesday?
The song's a killer.
LEE Bo-young
Nothing but the best from LEE Seung-chul.
Of course.
LEE Beom-soo
No problems whatsoever.
Yes, sir. Take care.
JUNG Ae-yeon, LEE Han-wui
See? He's asking for the song. Do it for me?
Executive Producer KIM Gwang-soo
You always do this to me.
Please?
So get me a good song and I'll sing it!
Producer HONG Jung-pyo
Damn!
What about 'Hee-ya'?
'Hee-ya, please look at me.'
Give me a break.
That was a hit only cuz you sang it.
Wanna hear this song I got?
What is it?
It's off a flopped album.
Forget it, kid!
Let's hear it.
Really? Turn it on.
To give you everything
and all my love...
Who wrote this? The lyrics are great.
Really? Then let's ask
them to write our lyrics.
Who wrote this?
Not sure. I got this off someone.
Who?
Min-chul. He used to
work for KIM Gap-sik.
Gap-sik? I know him well.
Hey, didn't he leave the biz?
Who does your friend work for now?
He left the biz, too.
What does he do?
He runs a cafe in Chung-pyung.
Wanna go over, Seung-chul?
- Know where it is?
- Yes.
Lead the way.
Director WON
Got the album?
Ah, here.
What's the title?
It's the second track.
Second track?
'No one else like Thee' by Cream?
What's her real name?
I think it was EUN Won.
Yeah, that's it.
Got her number?
She's gone.
Gone? To where?
Right after KANG Chul-kyu left...
KANG knows her well?
Of course. He was
totally in love with her.
Do you have KANG's number?
- He died.
- He's dead?
When?
About a month after
he married off EUN Won.
Mr. KANG!
What was the name of his show?
'Ugly Ducklings in Love'.
Yeah, that's it!
He married off the woman he loved?
- What does that mean?
- Well...
Tell us what happened.
It's a long story.
Hi, Chul-kyu!
KANG said he saw stars
when he first met Cream.
Why you little punk!
Like he'd been slapped
on the back of his head.
He said it was love
at first sight.
Without even talking to her.
I asked,
'Shouldn't you at least
say a few words, first? '
Then he said...
If you need words,
then how can mutes love?
How did you know my name?
Isn't it a waste living
in this big place alone?
Want me to live with you?
Think of a name for me,
and I'll make one for you.
We can't change our names.
Why not?
Her name is Cream
and my name is K.
She was cold like ice cream,
- but also sweet like ice cream.
- The curtains won't do.
We're changing everything.
And she was soft like ice cream.
And I'm not A, B, C,
D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K...
But just K.
We had a lot in common.
We were the same age.
We both liked noodles.
We loved listening to
music on rainy days.
We loved coffee.
We hated school.
She liked me.
And I liked her.
And we were both orphans.
Prison and love...
Once you're stuck,
you can't get out.
I fell in love with Cream.
Even the very air she breathed.
Romeo must've been so worried...
loving Juliet, but
afraid he might lose her.
Why did he drink the poison?
Perhaps he knew.
To love someone
- is to give her everything.
- I'll visit often.
I received so much from her
like the catcher who gets the ball.
Love was like dry ice.
Sometimes cold, sometimes hot.
Wait!
Cream was so loveable.
But I couldn't tell her
that I loved her.
Cuz I had cancer cells in me
ready to strike at any time.
More than Blue
Thank you, Mr. KIM.
It's the least I can do.
Writers need to eat well
to do all that thinking.
Have some soup with the
Kimbap and chew carefully.
Is this your new singer?
Greet them, girl. They're
the best writers in SBC.
Hello, I'm Cat Girl. I
promise to sing my heart out.
Damn right you should.
Great outfit.
It's a new concept. She's a cat.
It's Cat Girl.
This gal's got brains.
She's a student at Seoul University.
Really?
It's Seoul University of Arts.
Who's side are you on?
You could get in trouble for
lying about schools these days.
If you're so holy, go be a cop instead.
Sorry.
Mr. Kang!
How are you?
Here's Seung-chul's
new album. It's deep.
- It's a sure hit.
- I'm sure it's great.
- Say hi.
- Hello.
Call me K.
Let's go for drinks some time.
- Sounds great.
- Bye.
Seoul Univ. of Arts. Same difference.
That's right.
Did you eat, sir?
Mr. Kang!
- How've you been?
- I waited so long for you.
She's Cats. Damn, I keep forgetting.
It's Cat Girl, sir.
Go on and introduce yourself, girl.
I'm Cat Girl. I promise
to sing my heart out.
Thank you.
Of course you should.
Let's go some place
quiet to talk, Mr. Kang.
See you folks later.
- Come on, what are pals for.
- I can't.
It's just a show of my appreciation.
The album's finished?
I put together all the
best songwriters around.
You know me, I get what I want.
How is she?
Oh, her? Not bad.
But she has trouble getting
along with the others.
Still she's got talent. Be nice.
Of course. Anything for you.
- But do this for me.
- I can't.
It's not much. Please, take it!
I can't sleep at the thought of you.
My dear love.
That part you just sang. Try
not to scream it this time.
You'll scare 'em off.
How, sir?
How would you feel if someone
screamed they loved you?
You know, softly and
tenderly? You're good at that.
What? Not that. Stop making me do it.
- That's not what I meant!
- Roll it!
What's she so good at?
Drop it will ya, man?
Come on. Just between us?
She's my future. That's
all I can tell ya, man.
Did you fix the second verse?
What?
The climax on the second verse.
'Always like yesterday'?
It's a little corny, isn't it?
'A world without love? ' How's that?
Like that's not corny?
It's just a suggestion.
Let's not get too excited here.
You two write it, then. I'm out.
What?
So feisty.
Do you have to become a singer?
What?
Got enough medication left?
My damn connection to your family.
First your father, now you.
There are too many illnesses
that can't be cured.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Don't cry.
Stop crying.
The bastards told me to rewrite it.
'If I could live again'.
How's that for the title?
'If I could live again? '
If you could, what would
you like to be reborn as?
Besides a person?
Anything.
Well...
If I could live again...
A ring?
Wait.
Start over.
If I could be born again...
A ring.
A pair of glasses.
A bed.
A diary.
Born again as things like
that? What fun is that?
You can buy me. It'll
always be fun at your side.
So sensible.
Did you eat?
Of course, I did.
Well, I didn't.
Then let's eat.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Like what?
A deep, dark secret?
Think of it as a confession
at a Catholic church.
I'll be the priest and listen.
A deep, dark secret?
Say anything. I'm ready to listen.
I like you.
I want to ask you something.
Do you have a wish?
A wish?
If you could have anything in the world?
First, hold up your spoon.
Then?
Eat all your food.
Meet a great guy and get married.
Can't I marry you?
I'm not a great guy.
It wasn't my choice, but heaven's will,
to fall in love with you.
I was born to love you.
Heaven sent me to love you.
ID: Little Mermaid.
Now, for the requested song.
Your second toe is longer
than the first one like mine.
That means your mom will outlive you.
Who says that?
I think I read it somewhere.
It's a lie.
Why?
Cuz my Mom and Dad died on the same day.
If you...
If you die before me, I'll kill you!
Here's another requested song.
Are you finished?
Excuse me?
The coffee.
Then can I have the cup?
Which side did you drink from?
Pardon?
This isn't kissing, is it?
- Hey.
- Yeah?
- You know the guest doctor?
What kind of doctor is he?
Huh?
We need to fill a cavity.
Amalgam is stronger than resin.
We kiss on the first day.
You see inside me, on the second day.
What should we do on the third day?
What?
We'll decide when the time comes.
I'm in love!
A guest on another show. He's a dentist.
Pass me the toothbrush?
You're listening to 'Happy Hour'.
- As you're out driving...
- Did you eat?
Oh, hi.
- Got a show to record, today?
- No.
The guest doctor on your show...
Who? You mean CHA Joo-hwan?
How is he?
He's a great guy. Why?
Just wondering.
His family's rich, he's nice,
and he makes a ton of money.
And he's a famous dentist.
You look a little sad today.
Good job, bro.
It was fun.
- Great show.
- Cut it short.
Hey, nice seeing you.
Let's go out for drinks.
Not if it's just a few drinks.
- How much then?
- All night?
All night! Alright!
What's his social
security number?
- 730313105...
- 730313...
Sure you can get his medical records?
Insurance companies
get everything.
But why do you want
to check out a guy?
I'll tell you later.
Bingo! He's got life
and medical insurance.
No record of family illness
or any operations.
He has an impeccable
health record.
You sure?
Insurance companies know
how to make money, man.
KANG!
If he has a hospital
record, we'll see it.
KANG!
Thanks. I owe you one.
Got a minute Mr. KIM?
For you, any time!
It's a gift.
Ah, thank you.
Just a thank you?
First my lips, then my insides...
Now, you're in my head.
Buy me a drink?
A drink?
I don't get it.
Who would've thought I'd use my
former dark roots to help you?
No need to worry. Now about Cats.
Man, I gotta change that name!
It's Cat Girl, sir.
I know! It's up here
but I can't say it right!
Call me whatever you want, hon.
Who cares if it's a cat or a dog?
That's my pretty.
My sweet Cats.
We're changing the name.
- Ah, sir?
- I said, I know!
Not that. The phone.
Sorry, Producer KANG! I checked and...
You kids scram for a sec.
I gotta take this call. Go!
CHA Joo-hwan's family's loaded!
He even has a hot fiancé.
He's got it made.
Fiancé?
Is something up?
Oh, you dropped your candy.
Let's put it in your pocket.
Have you ever been in love?
Like a rock thrown into the river.
Give me the ring.
Excuse me?
Your ring.
Like this.
Someone to pull you out. Like this.
I'm engaged.
It doesn't matter.
Let's keep drinking.
It's so cold.
Did you drink?
What do you like so much about him?
I feel like I'm being sterilized.
Sterilized?
Sterilized.
Perfect.
- Let's eat.
- Sorry, I gotta run.
- You're not eating?
- I can't.
What about all this food?
You eat it all.
I'll see you later.
ABCDEFGHIJK...
Hello?
Is this EUN Won's number?
Yes, it is.
May I speak to her, please?
She's not here.
My name's CHA Joo-hwan.
We were supposed to meet today
but something came
up at the clinic.
Is there any way
I can reach her?
Where were you going to meet?
So cold.
Hey.
He can't come.
Who?
Him.
The doc.
Where are you going?
I gotta go.
Sit down. The curry here is great.
You know I don't eat curry.
Then what do you want?
What else is there?
What do you want to eat?
Kimbap.
So boring.
Just eat curry.
You're buying.
Come on Producer KANG. Spill it.
Did he rip you off or something?
Then, why didn't you say so!
My boys can get the money
back before lunch in no time.
It's not that.
Then what is it?
Why would someone like you want
the dirt on some guy's fiancé even?
Are you interested in his fiancé?
Just find out, please.
Fine, then.
Anyway, Cats' album's
startin' to get noticed, now.
Let's cook up something with your show
and sell 'em like hot pancakes!
I'm sure it'll do well.
Of course.
Hey, Min-chul!
Did you like the house?
Mother said she liked it.
It's not bad.
I heard you stopped holding exhibitions.
I'm tired of putting on shows.
And there's nothing to take pictures of.
I'm sorry I'm not more fun to be around.
Don't worry. I like
to have fun by myself.
That's sad.
- Let's have fun together from now on.
- Sure.
Can I get an ashtray here?
I'm sorry. There's no smoking here.
The world's such a bore.
Get her an ashtray to
put that out, please.
Yes, sir.
Interesting.
Keep smoking.
Should've known. She's
really somethin' all right.
She's got men coming out of her ears.
I told 'em to take some good pics.
It won't be long.
How did you pose
for your album cover?
I posed like I practiced
with my boss last night.
Exactly how?
- Here?
- Pardon?
Men are all the same.
Okay, then.
First, I open my eyes like a cat.
Like this.
- Ah, Cat Girl?
- Then...
I hold my hands up and
open my mouth like this.
Look at her. She's a natural born star!
You can just tell us.
But my boss said a star
- has to speak with the body.
- See that?
Girls like her adjust so quickly.
That foxy babe. Who wouldn't love her?
- Ah, sir?
- KANG!
- What's wrong?
Where is he?
- Hey!
- I'm dead beat.
What's wrong with you!
What's with you!
Don't start.
Why does he keep fainting like this?
It's hereditary, but it could also be
not enough calcium in his diet.
We've been eating the same food
in the same house for years!
Why are you the only
one who keeps fainting!
You eat way more than I do.
You're only eating anchovies
from now on, got that!
You!
Yes?
What did he just say?
To break off your engagement...
- Stop! Please!
- Who are you!
What the hell are you trying to pull!
You don't wanna mess with me!
Get the hell out of my sight!
I said, get lost.
Why are you doing this?
Huh?
You're a successful radio show producer.
Trailing a woman and
getting slapped like that.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I don't have time to be embarrassed.
What are you talking about?
One mountain after
another. But no time to go.
Ow, my head.
Does it hurt?
I'm hurt, too.
What's with me today?
It's cuz we're sad.
Then cry instead of making jokes.
I don't want to cry.
Don't wanna make someone cry even more.
I'm dying. Just like my dad.
Chul-kyu!
Mom left me a year
after Dad died.
It probably wasn't
cuz she resented me.
She was sick of
everything cuz of Dad.
I understand. I was
sick of everything, too.
But when she left me all alone...
I was so lonely.
People...
should never be alone.
I'm sorry.
I want you to leave your fiancé.
The girl that I love is in love with him.
-Medical records-
I beg you.
Under one condition.
But...
But?
No, please! Tell me.
I want to take your pictures.
Your medical records said
you don't have much time left.
Now, that's an interesting model.
I think it'll be fun.
I don't think it'll be fun.
Then the deal's off.
Drink up, first!
Give me a drink, too!
- Hi! Hi!
- Hi! You're late!
Hello. I spoke to you on the phone.
Oh, hi.
I'm KANG Chul-kyu.
CHA Joo-hwan.
- Thanks again for that day.
- Anytime.
You know him?
The sterilizer?
- Did you eat?
- No, I'll eat now.
Why are you so late?
- Still recording a show.
- What?
You said you're done.
Not yet. I gotta go back.
- Here.
- Thank you.
The song's great.
'If I can live again'?
Of course, I wrote it.
Sorry, I gotta run.
- Come on.
- Don't go.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
- See you next time, then.
- Sure.
Be careful in the snow!
Why are you back so early?
Aren't you supposed
to be recording a show?
Change of plans.
Me, too.
Drink this.
Didn't you eat?
I did, but I'm still starving.
Why are you eating
noodles instead of rice?
Just wanted something simple.
It's good, huh?
If you could stop time,
what would you do first?
If everyone else is frozen
and only you can move?
If time stopped, you wouldn't die.
Don't you want to live?
Not talking to me?
Too sorry to die and leave
the girl you love alone.
Okay, I can understand that much.
But still...
How can you marry her
off to someone else?
Isn't that going overboard?
You're not dead, yet.
- How can you watch that?
- Ah, Jenna?
Let's just stick to our jobs.
What's love?
Like brushing your teeth.
Brushing your teeth?
But you do that alone.
Do you brush to show someone?
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Pardon?
I said, did you wait for me?
Well, just wondering
why you didn't come.
You fell in love with me, didn't you?
What?
Love makes you wonder
and wait for that person.
It's not that. If a patient
doesn't come, I wait.
Do you wonder about every patient?
Well...
You're blushing. It's love all right.
Hey, KANG Chul-kyu!
Yes, boss.
How much did you get from KIM Gap-sik?
Should've been more discreet!
Cat Girl's on your show 10 times a week!
Think people will stay still?
Someone wrote in to audit your show!
What's got into you all of a sudden?
You of all people!
When are you going to break it off?
In a rush?
You saw my medical records.
I want to keep playing.
But I guess you don't have that luxury.
Under one condition.
Now, what.
I'll tell you after I break it off.
A promise is a promise.
Since when was it no smoking in here.
No idea.
Our parents will be shocked.
I should be really angry
at a time like this, right?
Yell at you or something?
Funny, somehow I feel a little grateful.
I'm going out for a smoke.
So uncomfortable.
My engagement's off.
I don't have parents.
I was studying late at high
school in my senior year.
My homeroom teacher came
in and stared right at me.
Like someone who came
to take me on death row.
Like in the movies, you know?
Anyway, he told me
to go to the hospital right away.
When I asked why...
if he said my parents and
sister died in a car accident...
then I wouldn't have gone
and seen them like that.
I see...
K's been with me ever since.
K?
You saw him, Producer KANG Chul-kyu?
His name sounds too corny
so I just call him K.
At home, he's my Mom
At work, he's my Dad.
When I'm sad, he's my brother.
Sometimes he's like a lover.
Though he always chickens out.
Can I kiss you?
You wanna kiss me?
Stupid.
Let me see.
Oh, no.
That's right, I'm stupid!
Open the door. Are you okay?
Don't look! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I was born to love you.
Heaven sent me to love you.
Cat Girl's 'If
I could live again'
requested by
ID: Little Mermaid.
- You wrote this song, Cream?
- Yes.
Let's hear, 'If I could live again'.
(Did you eat?)
(I'm almost done!)
Yes, boss.
Come to my office, now.
Okay.
Producer KANG!
KANG!
I heard everything. I'm going to
speak with the boss, right now!
How can he fire a genius like you!
I'm not getting fired.
Same difference.
- You can't go like this!
- I'm taking a break.
Really? That's not what I heard.
I'm going to the States
to study for a while.
Really? Guess there's
no use going to the boss.
Thank you for everything, Mr. KIM.
- Anytime.
- You too, Min-chul.
Give him the demo tape, Min-chul.
Producer CHOI! Hold on! Wait!
Min-chul...
It's a ballad.
Write up a good song.
What's marriage?
Marriage?
Marriage.
- Marriage...
- Wait!
A toothbrush holder.
What?
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.
What's that got to do with marriage?
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.
Then I must be married, already.
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.
Really?
I gotta pee.
No one else but Thee.
'Thee' is a lucky person.
Wanna hear it?
EUN Won and I living
together probably got to you.
But there's nothing to worry about.
I'm okay with that.
I'm thankful for
everything you did for her.
Let's get together often.
Go on trips together and stuff.
Sounds good.
She says she wants to pick
out her wedding dress with you.
Gotta love her wild ideas.
Why me?
I want what she wants.
Please do it for her.
And I hope it's the last
thing you ever do for her.
Sure. Please take good care of her.
Of course. She's my woman, now.
Let's drink.
What do you think?
Very pretty.
It's time for the groom-to-be
to try on his suit.
I'm not the groom.
Try it on.
Come up here.
Come here. Can you take a picture of us?
On three. One, two, three!
Wait out there. I'll
try on something else.
Why are all the clocks stopped?
No reason.
Can I turn one on?
Why?
No reason.
No reason?
Sure.
Jenna? I have a big favor to ask.
What is it?
I need to send flowers on her
anniversary for a few years.
She'll get suspicious, if
I lose touch altogether.
I had one more condition. Remember?
What is it?
Please die at my side.
You booked the tickets?
I'm running low on battery.
Hey.
What are you making?
My phone battery ran out.
I'll charge it and call you back later.
Bye.
Hi.
Why'd you leave me there like that?
It's for you.
Who do you think you are!
What's with you?
Who says you can touch my phone!
The hell you...
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!
Can I help you?
Is K home?
K?
Someone's here.
She's pretty. I can
see why you love her.
You think she's happy?
What are you saying?
She didn't seem happy.
Can you send this for the next 3 years?
It's pretty.
Maybe too pretty.
It looks fake. Like your love.
Then what's real?
Real?
If you're hungry, you eat.
If you're hurting, you cry.
If you're having fun, you
laugh. Not hold it in like you.
You really wanna die like this?
No!
I don't want to die like this.
I want to live a happy life.
I want to be the one marrying EUN Won...
...instead of him, tomorrow.
But...
That's just a dream.
A sad dream.
I'm done with dreaming.
Sleep tight and sweet dreams.
Did you eat?
- Cream
Thanks.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For everything.
I'm sorry, too.
For what?
For everything.
I love you...
I like you.
Me, too.
That's some story.
KANG... amazing guy. I had no idea.
Is there anyway to reach
them? What about the dentist?
Wonder what happened to her.
Let's record it.
Really? I'll call right now.
No, the other song.
Oh, that song.
I gotta go, I'm late.
Get up and eat. I made breakfast.
What's this?
Ah, Vitamin ABC. It
helps me get smarter.
Where'd you get these pills?
They're my friends' pills.
Since when did your
friend start taking this?
Why?
The pain must've been
severe to take these pills.
What?
They're painkillers for
patients with cancer or leukemia.
Terminal patients.
Have you heard of
the hospice ward?
It's where dying patients stay...
with consent from their families.
Mom!
Watch the house while we're out.
See you later, sis!
No!
When I found out what
Vitamin ABC really was...
When I finally realized
what they were...
When my whole world
turned pitch dark before me...
What's wrong?
I died before K.
I met K a year after my
whole family passed away.
Though almost 3 hours passed...
he stood there frozen like stone.
Crying and looking in the
direction his mother went.
This will be enough to support you
till you're an adult, Chul-kyu.
He looked sadder
and more hurt than me.
He needed a hug more than me.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Like what?
A deep, dark secret?
Say anything. I'm ready to listen.
I like you.
Stupid idiot.
Do you have a wish?
What's with you?
Just curious all of a sudden.
If you could do anything
you want in the world.
K is dying.
Meet a great guy and get married.
Can't I marry you?
I'm not a great guy.
Then who is?
Someone who is healthy and nice.
Who knows how to take
care of his family.
I already met a great guy.
But K told me to
meet someone else.
He said that was his wish.
KANG Chul-kyu
When I heard K fainted...
I rushed over,
afraid I'll go crazy.
But I...
...couldn't even go crazy.
No, doc.
But she should know.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
It feels like a needle
stuck in my throat.
Right here.
It gets stuck right here.
I can't say it.
She'll live on. Think of yourself.
She's different.
She needs someone beside her.
- Hello.
- There goes Mr. Perfect.
Glowing from head to toe!
I picked a man.
Which side did you drink from?
Pardon?
I'm engaged.
Stupid. You think I care
whether you're engaged or not?
Just play along and
meet me. For K.
Am I a bitch?
I don't have time
to worry about that!
The man I love is dying!
If I could be born again...
A ring? A pair of glasses?
A bed? A diary?
Born again as things like
that? What fun is that?
You can buy me. It'll
always be fun at your side.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Let me see your hand.
Where are you going?
I made a deal with myself.
If he turns around,
I'd tell him everything.
If he turns around, I'd
hug him and stop everything.
But K didn't look back.
And there was nothing
I could do.
Why are you eating
noodles instead of rice?
Just wanted something simple.
- It's good, huh?
- Yeah.
As I sat eating the
noodles with him...
I'd think, 'Don't
die you bastard'
and drank some water instead.
'Tell me. Let me hold you!
I'll die with you! '
'I'll follow you and pay you back
for everything you did for me! '
Instead, I just drank the water.
And finished the noodles.
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.
What's that got to do with marriage?
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.
Then I must be married, already.
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.
Really?
Can we get married, soon?
Wait out there. I'll
try on something else.
The hell you...
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!
I'm sorry.
I want to tell him I love him.
I want to open my mouth
and say I love him.
But I knew tears will fall
before I could say it.
So I kept silent, again.
When are you going to talk to me?
Didn't you hear me screaming
at you all this time?
What?
Stupid.
I didn't hear anything.
Then how can mutes love?
I love you.
Me, too.
We became a real couple.
Cuz we made it down the aisle.
Heaven's Gate Resting Place
Wait!
You never learn!
How can you write
with a brain like that?
This isn't kissing, is it?
Can you take a picture of us?
On three. One, two, three!
I was born to love you.
Heaven send me to love you.
- EUN Won -
I'm making noodles.
Want some?
No, I gotta work.
You sure?
Yes, I'm working!
- Then I'm just making one!
- Okay.
Don't come beggin' later.
- Hey!
- What?
No eggs! Give me that.
Wonder who invented noodles.
You said you didn't want any.
Changed my mind.
Is there any rice?
Hold on. There's
some in the fridge.
Chul-kyu...
I'm coming to you.
Don't worry.
I trust you. You
were always my compass.
Remember when I said
I can see you
even when you're not with me?
Go wherever you want.
I'll find you, soon.
Don't get mad when you see me.
Don't ask me why I followed
you or get angry at me.
After everything to come to
you, if you get mad I'll cry.
When we meet again on the other
side, let's not cry again.
Wait for me.
I'll be right there.
Even if...
...Im reborn a thousand more times,
There will not be another one like you.
The one who...
...would warm up my sad life.
I'm really grateful for that person.
For that person, my heart could...
...be hurt indefinitely.
Even if
I can't tell you that I love you,
the fact that I'm able to...
...look at you from a distance,
give you everything and love you.
Even if I'm sad, I'm happy.
There is no other love
in this world...
...that could make my chest shiver
with such anticipation.
I've buried so deep
in my memories...
...my only love.
For someone like you,
all the painful tears,
I could endure it indefinitely.
Even if
I can't tell you that I love you,
the fact that I'm able to...
...look at you from a distance,
give you everything and love you.
Even if I'm sad, I'm happy.
I don't want anything else except...
...your laughter. With it, I'll be happy.
Because love is about giving everything,
just about giving.
So, even if I'm sad,
I'm happy.