"Lu snake is not love."
"When Love is Over"
"Premature shuttle"
"Missing in pulling stubborn."
"A person walking in the road."
"How to make baby weeping."
"Dumbfounded cat how to make up."
"Back in the scenery."
"No amount of sadness."
"Since the baby is passing."
How, East Columbia
Like it
This lyric was written an hour ago
Hot
"87 points is the kind of attitude to life" arranger Jonny Code was also full of popular
"87 points is the kind of attitude to life," the market will need to have the topic of the song
This is true it
But the company has been throwing money ride network drama
If this song does not cause topic
We just GG
Her back to basics yeah
What the audience will sing pay
really
"Baby profound love again," What's your worry
"Baby love again deep," I see you high count of money waiting to be soft it u
"Scared to eat from hand to hand."
Wait
I worry about this
Amanda
The lyrics
I can not put into
baby
Scared to eat hand in hand
How this sing
A-Lin, we do not record
Mixing will be too late
First thing you'll know you sing about
it is good
I do not sing
Sing your own
Hey, baby
Hey, not, A-Lin
Yeah I'm back to basics
A-Lin
When you'll know I do this for me, OK
I also want to help
But how I sing is no way to put the feelings
I know I know
The words above are very popular on the web
But with the first song
Entirely different tone
Whom you want to sing how I
Feel embarrassed
Why
I have a cell phone inside a song
It seems to have never been published
I do not want to say u boss
no need
Small tour, put, I want to hear
it is good
"I do not envy the sun."
"According to you in the past does not shine."
"Some of darkness"
"We are all the same." This song is called what
Word also is well written
There is a sad song called
Better to call him to help us write the words
Maybe this song have saved
Who wrote the word
I do not know
This song is one of my friends gave me Abang
You take me to find him now
"Do not open"
"There is no need."
"hide"
Abang
Small tour
How come
Hello, I'm Amanda
A-Lin brokerage
A-Lin
It is that A-Lin
Hello
I'm A-Lin
Come, come in please
I invite you to drink coffee
Small tour helped me shut the door
Abang
You know it lyricist
Because our company has a song
Want invited him to write
Know ah
She called Cream
It is face to face break up the Cream
Yuanyuan
Song Yuanyuan
Then you have the contact details Yuanyuan
Line, WeChat, Facebook, or what do
Now no one contacted her
She knew that other people do
People sing this song Demo
You should be able to contact her
People singing called Zhangzhe Kai
Zhangzhe Kai
He recognized it with Zhangzhe Kai Song Yuanyuan
understanding
They loved each other once before
Great
Zhe Kai goes phones can give me
please
This thing is really important
I'll find him, killed
He had died
died
I think of it
Zhangzhe Kai is the brother K
We share a record company
Prior to joining the company when
There he met
Later, it seems to leave the
Was his
How could so suddenly
Zhangzhe Kai's story
From the age of sixteen he began talking about
That year his family left him
He started alone a person's life
Live up in that left him a man
Father filled with relics
But unable to finish the old house
Was I, he became close
He just never seemed doomed to a lonely individual
Live is one of the most sad thing
Until that day, she met
Eh
You drink
Why
How u smoking
Hey
You which classes
Dare to smoke at school
Nah, instructors, instructor
not me
stand up
This is to have you
Instructors
Do not grab my hair instructors do not follow school rules
Not tried to stay pain
I do not know Honesty and Honor
Zhangzhe Kai for the first time in the playground met Song Yuanyuan
It is love at first sight
I asked him if he did not even introduce themselves
This can also love at first sight
He said
If you need to explain the words of love
That world no one therefore painful
Eh
go home together
Hey
U is causing me to remember too small
Do you care about
Just a little too
Otherwise, I invite you to read comics plus those days
Gone
Yeah those days
Oh, so you'll eat three bowls
Add the meat, add eggs, add vegetables
since that day
Song Yuanyuan into my life
It changed my life
Her sloppy
Her sunny
Zhangzhe Kai
I opened my heart had closed
Which room
The same school doing it
We admitted to the same university
We decided birthday together
happy Birthday
go
Wait
We have a lot in common
I like to watch cartoons
Like those days
Lose treat
Why it than this
Oh, Zhangzhe Kai, you big party right
In particular, to take me to Kyoto graduation photo shoot
Spend a lot of money now
There are cherry yeah
U are so good how people exaggerate yeah
To see here
Kyoto, a three hundred
Boss, it is not one hundred fifty
Two people ah
To see here
I just did not see
It's ok
I'm counting one two three
Twelve
Six hundred Hello
Too expensive
The most powerful came
She likes the challenge
but me
I followed her like the challenge together
Faster
We all like to eat ice in winter
Like rain
We have another season like
The other half we become indispensable to each other
Do you live ah
Sixteen start
I own it live
Come
, The clothes u
Oh, for
I like you how to change
Get out!
You're wet, you wipe it
Oh, you can not peek
We will not turn over peep
Eh
Well
naive
Allowed Kanwo
I'm looking at you oh
I did not see ah
Comfortably
Eh
I moved here with you now
The house is so big
I
I'm used to a person
I am alone
get up
What time the
From that day the family was admitted Cream
She opened a window for me
One that would otherwise be trapped in the solitude of my window
She took my sorrow
let me know
original
I deserve to have someone
Once people get used to loneliness
That is more than sad sad thing
Zhangzhe Kai
I think your name is not nice
I can help you get a new
What's your say
After you called K
K
Correct
K is a nickname right, but not the name
Anyway, I'll call you later K
So that's your name
Why is K
Because I was Cream
Ice Cream of the Cream
What about you Why is Cream
Because I like to eat Ice Cream
U like to eat Ice Cream
It should be called Ice Cream ah
Why is it called Cream
Cream, Cream cream
Milk is the meaning of
milk
Where do you see
grandmother
Ice Cream of the Cream
How can Cream Milk
you really are
Well, Cream
Cream
K
Eh
Roman feet of people heard
Mom will take longer to live
What is the Roman foot
This 像妳
Thumb foot long man
Not right
They are my parents died in a car accident together
My mother did not live quite long
But my mother was still alive ah
Your mother left the child in you
She had not in your life in the
So it is not
I do not Rome or feet
U help me look
Do not affect me watch movies
Hurry, help me see u
U think so do you like Roman foot annoying
Stink hurts
I warn you oh
If you dare to go earlier than I
You're dead hear no
I was not allowed to disturb the movies
Very poor
There are not looking you in the end
Everything I cherish along with her
But like prisoners confined to their cells
Once people caught in love
It is difficult to escape
I fell in love with Cream
She fell in love with everything
I want to live with her forever
But I can not
Do not dare confess Cream
because
I'm ready to wake up the body has cancer
Small K
Zhe Kai
Zhangzhe Kai
You're in the company to stay up late
Money to life, money to life ah
keep your voice down
How you sleep sleep sweating
Have it
There ah
Have wet clothes
Probably really tired of it
Recently our company to do a man named Lisa who want to get married
It made me really busy very hard
I say you have the nerve
Before you suddenly leave a whole week
I almost fainted
Young lady
I really collapsed
To roar
Really, this thing really can not let know Cream
I know
You've reminded me
Third Hello
U swear
I swear
It is all right
Thank you
Fast back
I'm not finished
Health First it
Be all right, super-healthy
Hello
Hello there
My name is Lisa, hello
Hello, I'm Amanda
Today, the new company
Exhibitions Ni Hao
I Zhangzhe Kai, call me K on it
K good brother
I am responsible for brokerage
Now with Feng Yi
Hello, I'm Feng Yi
how do you feel
Like it
well
Teach very well
Thank you, Brother K
Exhibitions
Well, I'll take him past
great, good luck
Excuse me, go
Lot of help
Too fake
You how to teach your child dad
Hey
Say hi to Bonnie
Small K
Bonnie's new look
How, good bar
K good brother
Bonnie is a cosmic system
US star small meow
I feel good
well
Jige sorry
You can put off the music
introduce
This is my execution broker
Abang
K Hello Brother
Hello there
Jige
Our meeting room Liaoba
Hey Good
this way please
"Do not open"
"Meow together is enough."
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug."
"I rely on you"
"Cat Bomb Bomb Bomb"
Pause
Eh
Bonnie
it's okay no problem
In front of you, all sing very well
Very delicate
Is that where u do the treble with a roar
Throat vulnerable to injuries
U will try to be
Kobara output
Ass clamping
it is good
She can - the
To continue the good
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug."
"I rely on you"
"Cat Bomb Bomb Bomb"
Wait
Bonnie wants to change you are my roc
You are mine for ever
May I
can
Bonnie love how to change on how to change
U random change what
Ouch, Bonnie a little thing like romantic
Where romantic forever
Pink bubble ah
What Pink Bubble
This song is not always the right attitude
What is the attitude ah u
Right ah, what attitude u
And off what u
This song is Jige gave Bonnie's
Bonnie like how to change, how to change it
Jige to see her friends
Young lady
He changed the lyrics
What u over there yelling at it
When did you get round here talk
Who says I can not speak
No, I mean she ...
This is what I wrote lyrics
Why can not I speak
Eh
Bonnie percent with Jige says you can not talk
U just can not speak
Who are you and
U must be changed is not
Correct
Bonnie is to change
I go u change
Feel embarrassed
I ask u once I said I want to change
U The over gas lyricist
What's your say, say who had gas lyricist
All right
stop fighting
Jige say the fight
Fight hit me
Do not hit
U really fight
Some people do at home
Cry cry
it's okay no problem
All right
Come
Cover like this
U are going to get married ah
Wow, your face
How hurt
What Bonnie female kitten
She deliberately changed forever my lyrics
Jesus is always very low
and then
Then I, beat
U too impulsive
I can help u say clearly
Jige still appreciate u talent
But u his beloved cat to catch female face took
This is the u talk to her to apologize
I do not want
I also spend it
You see my face
And my hand
I also really hurt
I did not hear
I'll go apologize
How are the lyrics changed
Not in the mood changed
Losing his temper
Come
I am, I Peini change
I do not like forever
Then do not forever
Replace
The next life
I can accept the next life
It feels like a convention
But never
As long as two people one of them is gone
It is not always the
Let me ask you
If my next life, then
What you want to be
people
When people who do not want to
When you pig
Well, seriously
If I had my next life, then I want to be
Ring
or it could be
You wait
Good to
Hi, I'm K
If my next life, then
I want to
Ring
glasses
bed
and also
notebook
When doing these
Can u around in
Hello nausea yeah you
What disgusting
Write the lyrics will inevitably nauseating little bar
right
Not to say that we wanted to change it forever.
How not to change it
Into the next life
Is it not good
in fact
Such a change is not re wrong
Glasses with key ring quilt
Expressed as companionship
Bonnie like
Forever word
If there is a missing person
It can not be established
But the next life
A bit like a
Promise
If there is a person to see
But you can still see the face
Bonnie felt like this good romantic
I want to express what it means
U completely understand
really
That is not a good chance to become Bonnie
Promising lyricist do
I think u very talented
It should be no problem
Bang Bang
Bonnie happy
Meow meow
The last thing
Really sorry
It's fine
Bonnie does not mind
Bonnie forgive u
Bonnie know it
Lyricist is a very difficult thing
But Yuanyuan Ni Zhen's well written
I'll call u Cream
Well, Cream
What about you call it Bonnie Chen Huijun
Who
Chen Huijun
U whose real name it
Bonnie is Chen Huijun
Chen Huijun is Bonnie
In order to make Bonnie later became well-known lyricist
starting today
Bonnie Chen Huijun good friends keep Cream
it is good
Bonnie friends
Jige is my friend
Jige friends with Bonnie percent
Abang is my friend
Jige with Bonnie percent Abang with friends
He is our friend
"Cats tears are pearls."
All right, then choose a good song lyric first hit
what about you
How it
Kitty Bomb吧
I think Kitty Bomb hit when very good
The first song is fast songs, then there is more of memory
And it is suitable for dancing and singing kitten
This song is very lovely friends
This is the word Cream
Ok
Yes
Long time no see her work the
But I still think the word a little too jump
But Bonnie liked
Bonnie is to go in front of it
Meow ~
I'll know you really go too in front of friends
I think this is a nice song
The song must beat MV
Because this song is very strong visual sense to shoot MV
If the MV looks good words
I believe that the young will love
it is good
That this song when the first hit
That second hit it
Do you have any comments
I have opinions clams
Bonnie is my baby
Each song should hit a lot of money to shoot MV
Bonnie felt moved
Bonnie moved to have to cry
clam
Cry it
This can be used when promotional spots
how about it
First hit
I will not because you
I can be selected as the first title bar
Tell your say how many times
This u own strength
Whether it is the last face to face break up
Or is this one, okay
Related to my business
I feel so too
U I dare you hit me
How, how do you like to play
Shame on you.
Bonnie is not
It bother you
No ah no ah
Oh
Ah, whom you want to doing
Celebrate ah
Just Cream songs
He was chosen the main
Let's go and eat
Bonnie treat
Well
Zhe Kai
I suggest you quit your job
Good recuperating at home body
So my illness
He began to attack
You and your dad had symptoms of
It is exactly the same
The biggest hope is a bone marrow transplant
Help him measure your blood pressure
Yes
Oh you ask
do you have
What to say to me
what's wrong
Naiyou looking for inspiration for the lyrics
Leave me alone
Say it
no
What I have to say
That is the kind of
You usually want to say
But only when no one
You dare to say it out loud kind words
How handsome I
This is not it
It is the kind of
If you go to church to keep the priest confession
You will say it's the kind of
That I will not tell your say
Niyou not God
Leave me alone
Well I want to hear
There yeah
I love u
I already know
I know u asked
I have another question
U yeah a lot of problems
Leave me alone
What you wish for
Longevity
This is not it
I'm talking about
Kind of
Is there anything you want to do
But you do not
Have
I hope u
Looking for a good man married
Did not you say you love me
You marry me ah
I am not a good man ah
What is the definition of a good man
have a job
A little money
Kind and loving family
then
Healthy body
what does it mean
It means nothing
Quickly eat, not hungry
Eh
Yeah good to eat
I do not eat eat Hello
Cream
K ah u like it or not
Why this sudden say
Because Bonnie could see
Do you have feelings for K
Do you have him say it
We are not the kind of relationship
Do not know
Although we live together
But we do not together
Cohabitation, no communication
How can this be
There is such a relationship in the world
We are
I'm used to it
How long have you so that
High school to now
Ten years now
ten years
That decade y'all doing what
What to do at home ah
Clothesline, laundry, eating, cooking
Do not go to bed
we…
several times
Fifth
Five years before
No
0. 5
what does it mean
It is
only
Kiss hug
Not that
what
We're not boyfriend and girlfriend
Is
U do not like him
Nor dislike
But we have no dealings
I do not want such a complex relationship
Cream u want to keep it that way right
Do u do not want to declare to him
in fact
He told me to find a good man to marry
are you crazy
I tell your say
Man is cheap
U do now
Immediately talk to someone else
If he knew
He will be back picking on the
Trust me
Behind
Forth
Gordon going to be sick
Who is the man
Oh vampire
That was my high school classmate ah
Oh is a dentist
Lisa, I'll get a drink
it is good
You run out of it
U Oh no cup
Ok
By me
Thank you
So it is not kissing
Count it
clam
Indifferent
He kissed all kissed
Thanks
Gordon, hitting
"Yang Youxian"
U teeth healthy
no problem
Yang, MD
We have met for two consecutive days Jesus
The first time we met we kiss
Second meeting
I'll show you inside my mouth
The third time that we have to do what
I wanted to meet you
You want to know me
Eh
I found a good man
clam
What's your say
I said, I find a good man
He is a dentist
Lisa is a high school classmate
That's fine ah
Bone marrow I've been waiting for seven years
I have so much time
You come back regularly visits
If the situation stabilized, then
Life can still be sustained
Uncle De
You do not comfort me
My illness
He has entered the accelerated phase
That way I can be much longer
probably
No more than one year
Jige
I would like you to help me investigate a person
survey
This thing I am most of the line
But small K
I also want you to do me a favor
The money is a little something
Bonnie publicity depend on you
It is half past four implant
34、35
CT help me open
Other equipment to help me get ready
it is good
Thank you
give you
I wrote it
It's the lyricist
Ok
so smart
Why do you want to commute
Why not
Make me a drink
I will give you CD
Well
Not all right
You can have a drink
Oh you ask
Boys are not very duplicity love it
As you obviously love a person
But only speak a little bit like it
To be honest it is difficult
You is not never been in love
I have engaged
By me
The results of only two fall in love
One do, it is like this
Fall in love inside
Another it
It is to fall into the trap of love to fish out
U know me say Naixiang
Ok
Why is my
If love can be explained, then
No one in the world and therefore painful it
Continued Cup
Yang Youxian
Doing business at home
Dentistry first graduation
Now with a friend and opened clinics
No criminal record
No bad habits
No specific diseases
Very healthy
Now there is a fiancee named Cindy
Life is simply set victory
So the next to him
Is his fiancee Oh
Ok
She was a very powerful photographer
Many big stars have to specify her photo
Then we Bonnie promotional photos
To find her a shot
Yes, immediately arrange
Oh so cold
Hello u go drinking
Ok
with him
What u like him
I do not know either
do not know
Do not talk, sleep
right
left
That hand is that right hand K brother
Cindy This woman is not simple
I think that Guaiguai Pai Yang Youxian
Certainly do not know his fiancee
On the outside so popular
You give us a little time
I can also take videos as evidence
no thanks
That's enough
Ok
Small K
You love a person
How so hard ah
Jige
What does it mean
Hey Hey hey
Which side put your hand, you court death ah
Jige
Bonnie teacher teaching dance
Why are you friends
He taught to dance, even if the
Why should touch the ass
I will not lie to jump, or I'll teach
How you teach Bonnie
You're not a professional
You do not care so much more attractive
What professional
Knives to injure my professional
He's fine not to immediately hacked him
This teacher is not good I'll give u for a better
Whether Bonnie is to teacher Michael
But I do not care
Jige, K brother fainted
张哲凯 it
How suddenly collapsed
I do not know either
Doctors like to say what I have
Congenital anemia bar
Congenital anemia
Ok
He would pass out mainly because
Too tired
There is also a little bit of calcium deficiency
Generally this anemia
There will not be much impact on the lives
Young lady
U do not worry
It's fine
Really nothing
Calcium deficiency
Strange as I eat with you every day
How I did not calcium deficiency
Because u eat more
Eh
妳是 bulimia Kai
Anyway, from today we are not allowed to work overtime
Hear no calcium every day
It's fine
All right
Archiving helps me look
it is good
Doctors
This is your letter
Oh
Why
You see it
Shit
Premarital investigation
I did not go to check the
Someone sent me
We were together for six years
I became a photographer funding u
I want to give u a home
This is my response to u
Yu Yin
Marriage is not me you want junction
This question we have long talked about the
Love was not actually my first priority
If not the first priority
It does not mean u can rightfully
I do not want to explain to you so much
Inside all I want to cherish the relationship
I have a clear conscience just fine
U This is just irresponsible
I need to create
So they argue with me but also to the creation of u
It was too hurt right
What about you these things do not hurt
Money is not every man for u
U have feelings
What do you mean your words
What about you what is meant
I've done things I will not deny
If you want my apology
I can say I'm sorry to tell you
What the fuck you think you are
Why do you investigate me
You think I did not address it will not adjust the monitor
Hey
Why u
enough
You let me go
and also
Will my life is none of your business
Hey
Bring
I am sorry
I just hope
U can break up with Yang Youxian
are you crazy
I do not know what your intentions are
But if I dare to continue to look for trouble
I told you endlessly
Zhangzhe Kai
K brother
I really do not understand what you're thinking
You to investigate the crazy woman
Then asked her to dissolve a marriage
what does it mean
You are not crazy
I'm crazy
I just want to find a good man to help Cream
How old is she
She will not find it
look at me
Do you think she will find it
She will not, not really
And I really do not have time
What no time
I was running out of time
Bonnie percent of the records listed
He did not sell more than ten thousand
Jige I will walk
Abang
At that time I did not need to bother the Abang
You just lose your job
Or are you going to die
K brother you look at me
If I appear just in time
You're really dead
Abang
Really thank you
Brothers
One of us
Thirty-eight
Well
Otherwise, this
I'll go with you to find Cindy
Once negotiations
how about it
Remember to close
Drink a little
No need to
Hey, you do not move the flower
I took a week
Oh
Eh
Why are you in the end come
This is to compensate for u
I hope u can leave Yang Youxian
And he broke off their engagement
You did not see my studio
He supported me photography is done
I reached this step
His half of the credit
If he does not take the initiative
I will not leave him
Understand
I please u
I have only less than a year's time
I'm going to die
"Certificate of chronic myelogenous leukemia."
High school that year, my dad died of cancer
Unfortunately
When my mother learned that I inherited leukemia
She could not bear the brunt
Money left
The money
Out of my life
It should be enough for you to live to adulthood
You need to take care of yourself
do not leave me
mom
In my most lonely time
Cream in my life
She became my family
And the people I love most
One, two
Come
birthday present
U not like rainy days
Songnai a cloud
Thanks, you too happy birthday
But today's not my birthday yeah
A few times a year to birthday ah
After your birthday is today
But my leukemia this year, entered the accelerated phase
I have the courage to tell Cream
In what happened to me
She may not Like my mother
Because of the pain, fear and leave me
But I do not know what Cream will make things
And such a blow
I really do not want her to bear
really sorry
I love the people fiance fell in love with u
I beg u
K brother
I am sorry
I may be in a hurry
this is my name card
If u change your mind
Please contact me immediately u
I can promise you
But you have to promise me one condition
I promise u
I am going to do a solo exhibition
Themes about death and maturity
Since you say you are all dead men
You've come to be my model
Let me take pictures
When I exhibited works
I would go broke
U will not be too exaggerated
Anyway, my condition was so
Do not you want to
K brother's gone
Late night
Why do you eat
They are cold
No la
Just suddenly thought
She never sent me over supper
Why think so much
Quickly eat
What would you like tomorrow
Texting told me
I will help you send
"Do not open"
"Meow together is enough."
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug."
"Next life also" Bonnie great jump
「Bonnie Bonnie」
"Meow meow hug" smoke, smoke it
"You have to stay with me."
「Never Let me go！」
Dance
"Bonnie hug."
"Spring flowers love summer fireworks."
U come ah
Now you tell us about
This is my dentist told you that
Yang Youxian
Hello there
Hello, Zhangzhe Kai
Welcome
I know, I often heard you mention Yuanyuan
To cut
The director can do
很好，Give me five
Give me five
Jige
Bonnie performance of how to
Not bad right
Very Good
Hey, Cream
How well do you think Bonnie jump
Great
Aw, that is, of course Hello
Bonnie small but international superstar it
you are
Oh Little America
He said that's what I tell your dentist
Hello
So you're Yang Youxian
Correct
Not bad
Meow ~
U Do not scare him this matter, again
Are you all right, do not look too comfortable
Nothing not to call it a day after a drink
I also can
Go ah
I almost have a trip back to the company
So disappointing
You do not care scene ah
on site
A small US-ah
Well, here to me
You quickly get busy now
Bonnie people do
coming
Hello I go first
Bye
Refuel
To each group Standby
going or not
Really too busy
Nice to meet you under music
me too
I'm leaving
Goodbye
吉哥 go Hello
Official to La
Action
To snow machine snow
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug."
"Next life also."
"Cat Bomb Bomb Bomb"
"Bonnie Bonnie meow hug."
"You have to stay with me."
「never let me go」
The first is when you know Song Yuanyuan
A high
High school, she is like
lovely
Lively
Beautiful eyes
You obviously can now cherish her
With her
Why do not you
Why do not you tell her the truth
I ask what the truth
U know the pain it
We then sixteen years old, there is no family
I was her only family now
Whom you want me to say how
And then I said
She let it no longer be an injury
I still say
U think she can make it go
No one does not survive
It was not too confident that you yourself
Song Yuanyuan she certainly stronger than you might think
Maybe
I am satisfied that you have outside of male chauvinism
Anyway, you do not want to help her find a cash machine is just right
Yes
I was looking for ATM
Then how about you
I'm bad, I'm selfish
I was her only family
I hope she good
May I
You want me to leave Yang Youxian can
But you promised me a request again
any request
After the death of the property you everything I
Not work
Everything I die of Cream
Do not you think it very contradictory
You want her to forget you
Should anything not to stay
I am sorry
let's break up
Together these days
I actually did not know u love me
Perhaps just as u said
Love is not so important in terms of u
But I have not let go
But you still put down
This is because I feel awake
Because the relationship between those pictures of it
We have been together now not because of love
Just habit
So for you
Our feeling is not love six years
Anyway, you have to mention breaking up
I also mentioned to break up
I recently met a woman
But there is no relationship between us now
I wish you happiness
I broke up
There are some things that I
I want to tell you
When I was in high school
Half the class
Class guided suddenly rushed
With a very strange expression told me that
U now immediately go to the hospital
I ask him why
He said that because
U u dad your mother as well as sister
In a car accident inside the tunnel
died
then
I just like to live with a K
K
K is Zhangzhe Kai
Because I think his name Tai Su
So he called K
He's a really strange
At home
Like Mom
When work like dad
Sometimes frustrated when he comforted me like a brother
Sometimes
He resembled wife
But the key moment
He any connection with a fool
Why so honest to me
Because you do not lie to me
So I'm not trying to cheat you
And I
Afraid you would care
You said K
Ok
will not
That's good
Christmas gifts
Thank you
Why do people want to get married
marry
Ok
Just when u old time
Or when needed to be taken care of
That person can justifiably has been by his side u
That I'm not married
clam
From the age of sixteen you to accompany me now
Am I getting old after you ignore me
Oh idiot
Not the same
Marriage is marriage
Marriage is a ceremony needs
Called marriage
Yes
Ok
Forget it
forget about it
Oh very hungry
There is nothing to eat
I do not eat this
It's good to eat
really tasty
Do not
I'm going to cooking
Then do not help you cook
"I do not envy the sun."
"According to you in the past does not shine."
"Some of darkness"
"we are the same"
And then a little fun
In this way you too sad
The more sad song, the more can not sing
"I'm so jealous of the time."
It need not be so happy
"To leave too generous."
"Do not open"
You have a good singing
"There is no need to hide."
I think you sing a little
Not serious
I sing very seriously
If you feel like you and sing Bonnie
How to do new songs sell well
Wait
Dear lyricist
Come on whom you want to know because u
That's why I sing the opening
Got it
Thank you
thank you
So take care of Yuanyuan
This is what I want to say
Thank you been with her since childhood
Good care of her
Then you should have heard
Stay with us
But you do not get
We really just friends
I have told Yuanyuan
You are good friends with her
To some extent also like family
So she ask for your help to pick the wedding
I think it is very reasonable
It's something I picked yarn
This is the hope of Yuanyuan
I want to go for what she meant to do
And it is also your Yuanyuan
The last to do one important thing
You should understand what I mean
how about it
is it beautiful
Looks great
Do not also try to groom dress
I'm not the groom
It does not matter, try Well
I want to see
Amby
Faster
I tried to why I want to see
handsome
Faster
So handsome thing
how is it going
I helped take a picture of two
Well
Oh look good here
One hundred twenty-three, a laugh
wait for me a while
I went for a set of clothes
Thank you
I've chosen a wedding
I resent photo to you
let me tell you
My phone seems almost out of power
I'm late
By me
Hey, I just phone battery died
Ok
correct
Well, I will charge late
Ok
Then you go to busy
I'll call you
worship
Which you go yesterday
You suddenly gone left me down there
I am so embarrassed
Which ran the
Did not go
Which did not go
Hey
Hey, Zhangzhe Kai, did not go out
Why u
Why mess u answer my calls
Not, ah, I thought it was
I think who u are
baffling
Dinner cooked
Where are you going ah
Out ah
Just inside the phone with the girl dating ah
U quit to do it
Well you want to eat dinner
Do not eat
You do not eat after I married you can not eat the
what are you worried about
She just hear my voice
I will not guess who it is
She knows You're the ex-girlfriend of Yang Youxian
I do not want to take the risk
What do you want me to call you
Posing as your date of
You will not mind too much opportunity
So she must give up before they can
Florid
Eternal love
Lonely strong
Next three years
You'll know you help me send it cactus
This is what you want
The final step
A year to send a
While supplies last three years
Over time she will not notice me gone
You do
She really happy it would be more
She'll be happy
Even now will not
Doubtless will
You almost died
Can not you live a little direct
Cry cry
Laugh
Angry, then you get angry
If you are hungry, then eat something
If you are afraid of words
Well it would help
There are some things you do not say you're too late
do you know
Or do you want to disappear without trace in this world
(I am sorry)
(Have you eaten)
Thank you
Oh you ask
Why do people get married ah
When you are older
Or when needed to be taken care of
That person can justifiably has been by his side u
Did not you say you love me
Yeah you marry me
I am not a good man
You do
She really happy it would be more
She'll be happy
Even now will not
Doubtless will
We then sixteen years old, there is no family
I was her only family
I hope she good
Or do you want as now
There is no trace of
He disappeared on in this world
I think I want to be dead
I think I want to just die ah
Who do not want to have a wonderful life
U think I could do
U think I have time to do
I hope she married the man of my
Not marry him
I hope we can grow old together
Accompany each other to take care of each other
But this is only wishful thinking
It was a sad dream
I do not want to dream
I really did not expect to have such a brother K Story
Unfortunately, gone
This is for A-Lin u
Thank you
This is their last album two cooperation
Memorial gave u do
correct
Tomorrow Record Bar
real or fake
Ok
I booked the studio Hello
but
I want to sing
There is a sadness
Yuanyuan, I'm back
Yuanyuan
Yu Yin
I am sorry
Really sorry
Earthly love
Not by hand can touch to
Mouth can say is clear
Eye can see the best of
my love
Know him from the start
It has existed in my life
No longer be separated
I thought my life
Do not have to experience separation
did not expect
Since that day
K shift away from me
Said I had gas lyricist
Le u u just tone deaf
Meow meow meow
pig
Kitten audience should all be boys
Boys, boys, boys
What boys love, love what boys
What is more important to them
Excuse me
Hello
Take this medicine is what to do with
This medicine where they come from
Home
This Glivec cancer or leukemia treatment drug
And this strong doses of painkillers
If you need to use the two words together
He should fill a serious condition
Bye
Goodbye Yuanyuan Yuanyuan good housekeeping
Hello sister we go
Oh good housekeeping Yuanyuan Yuanyuan bye
Not work
do not go
You can not be here
Can not go
Stop, stop
Some people do at home
I feel bad K refrained pain
Endure in silence all
I am very grateful to him
Even if the sick or for my sake
Perhaps this life I can not be together with the old K
But I look forward to my next life
We'll meet again next life
That day
I worry about things that happened
You really do not tell her
I can not really tell her
But now you need someone to take care of you
I'm fine.
I can take care of myself yourself
How long are you going to conceal her hiding
I do not know how long I can hide the truth
But if she knew the words
Everything is over
In the sake of someone else before you
Can you think about your own
I'm not important
But she is not the same
She is only one person
She needs someone with her
You are a person
Is not it
The first time I saw K
A month after the death of my family
Death took my family
K is alive but abandoned
Day he
He looked sad
Than I need hugs
since that day
I decided to call him K
And I own, called Cream
After all, two lonely people
There should be a name not so lonely
K u say brother dying
U think
I should have told him that I already know it
If he did not want to let u know
He should have his intention
Does he now split u
What can change it
I just want to be happy K
Regardless of anything
I will make every effort to meet his wishes
Do you have any desire
I hope u
Looking for a good man married
What is the definition of a good man
have a job
A little money
I wish K wish is to be with me
Then good health
But in order to coming away from me K
Even if I do not want to
I will try to give everything for him
Who is the man
Oh vampire
He was my high school classmate ah
Oh is a dentist
So it is not kissing
Count it
I wanted to meet you
I have engaged
therefore
Sorry, Yu Yin
I took advantage of you
If it is to be with you
K I think it should be very reassuring
I am sorry
I took advantage of your tender
Your thoughtfulness
I know that even if I was someone else
You will still accommodate me
Quietly waiting time
I'm impressed
Why do people want to get married
Because when u when old
Or when needed to be taken care of
That person could have been justifiably be with u around
That I'm not married
Marriage is a ceremony needs
Called marriage
When can we get married
I just love the Nizhen
anytime
please forgive me
People I love most is going to die
I really can not worry so much
Hi, I'm K
If my next life, then I want to be
Ring
glasses
I should not hate forever
bed
I want to stay forever beside K
One hundred twenty-three, a laugh
wait for me a while
I went for a set of clothes
Thank you
Contact me talk to you
it is good
I am sorry
It's ok
I was under tremendous sadness
I know the same K
I own and made an agreement
As long as he looked back
I'll tell him everything
If he looked back
I'll hold him deeply
(I love you)
I want to loudly say I love him
(Whom you want happiness)
But I know my tears will flow down a opening
Unsustainable
Thank you
To accompany me to practice my wedding process, OK
Song Yuanyuan
Whether rich or poor
Health or disease
U marry
The man standing in front of u
As his wife do
I am willing to
I and K become a real couple
I dream to achieve the happiest picture
I had thought we could go on holding hands
Just did not expect
In the real world
I personally K is handed over to another person
My feelings for K's
From the age of sixteen to now
It has been buried too deep
I never fished the way
Yu Yin
Thanks for everything you have done for me
Thank you love me
I have found a K
I want to see him
Hi
What are you ah
I'm looking for you for quite a while
Idiot
You have a fever you know
never mind
Well soon
I warn you oh
From now allowed to eat bubble
It was not allowed to rain
Not allowed to eat ice
Are not allowed to work overtime
Did you hear me
K
I'll take care of you
We have to go play baseball
You have to help me sing very difficult to listen to Demo
You must not leave me birthday
We said OK from the age of sixteen
Is not it to the birthday together
I am here
Will be fine
Will be good, be good
never mind
I accompany you
So there is a little better now
Home
Home all right
Sorry, Cream
Without the consent of u
He was scheduled to u love
Like it
We make another one right
Remember u ask me
To La
What I wish is that right
My greatest wish
Come
And u is
together forever
K
With Cream
We are a family
Has been ah
Take pictures
long time no see
Hi
How come so early
I'm afraid wait to start u will be busy
I show you around it
it is good
Hi, I'm K
If my next life, then I want to be
Ring
glasses
bed
I'm still not understand
This idiot like Zhangzhe Kai
Actually really live in this world
If love can be explained, then
This world no one therefore painful
I underestimated love
Before I even told Zhangzhe Kai said
Song Yuanyuan
She certainly stronger than you might think
It is not possible because you can not live dead
But I was wrong.
They had the eyes of love
It is to make each other happy life
"There is no need to hide."
"There is a sadness."
"Your name is stuck in my past."
"I decided to accompany my breath smile looks like."
"Can not forget"
K
do you know
After my family left
I think happiness will follow them away
Until I met you
I came to understand two lonely individuals
As long as accompany each other
But also to have the right to happiness
Our meeting was meant to be
No one would have alternatives to the
do you know
what I want
Not send me hot coffee in the winter people
But come with me to eat ice rain
People eat toothache
what I want
Not guard my people
But with someone to accompany me adventure
what I want
Not others
It's you
K
Thanks for everything you have done for me
As long as they stayed on your side
For me it has been the happiest thing
"I stay in the past."
I am sorry
"Can not forget"
I love you
"There is a sadness."
"Zhe Kai Yuanyuan tomb" "Yes you hesitate, let love be."
"My body of light."
"Give me warm."
"I was not allowed to."
I have been very curious
Why I called K
Because I called Cream
that's it
Because it
The two of us grew up without a family
And live together
K
With Cream
All k pronunciation
Do not you think this sounds
Much like a real family yet
"There is a sadness."
"You do not want to separate."
"I miss it and looked back to back."
"You are all"
"You are pictured."
"A"