I'm just glad we're
finally able to do this now.
How is it?
Will the mixing make
the release date?
Can we redo it? I feel
like it's missing something.
What? We don't need to do that.
We need to finish this.
Besides, that's Elaine.
She can even sing "Happy
Birthday" and make it a hit.
Cut! Cut!
What's the matter?
What is it?
I can't feel the song.
Something's wrong
with the lyrics.
Let's fix it then.
Which part is the problem?
All of it!
The song is fine.
Maybe it's the singer.
Did you say something?
Me? No.
Mark, pack up our stuff.
So, who do you want
to write the lyrics?
Someone with heart,
depth and sense!
Who?
Excuse me.
Not now.
What is it?
I have a song.
Are you a lyricist?
No, but I can assure you
it's great, ma'am.
Leave us alone.
Hold on. Let's listen to it.
Here. Listen to it.
Sad, but…it's beautiful.
The song doesn't suit you.
I want this!
Fine! Do you know the composer?
Let's call him.
I don't,
but my friend knows him.
He's just nearby.
We can visit him.
Let's go and see him.
Okay, I need my phone.
Hey, are you busy?
Not really.
Do you remember
the song, "Anytime"?
Miss Elaine and Miss Amanda
are interested in it.
You want anything? On the house!
A latte for me.
Me, too.
We'll make that three, please.
All right.
Ben, do you know
whose song it is?
Yes. It's K and Cream's.
Wait. You mean Charles
Keith and Sue Anne?
Yeah. You know them?
Well, I worked with them before
SA V Records.
Do you know how to
get in touch with them?
That's the problem. I don't.
Maybe with Keith, at least?
Keith is gone.
He's gone abroad?
Farther than that.
He passed away.
Gosh!
He's gone too soon.
Yes.
What about Sue Anne?
I don't know
where she is, either.
Let's look for her.
Sure.
Mom, wait!
Sorry.
Sorry, Keith.
Mom, Dad's already gone.
You're leaving me, too?
Mom!
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Mom, I need you.
You need to be independent.
I'm leaving everything to you.
Mom, please.
Please don't go.
Mom!
Keith!
I need you!
Mom!
Mom, please.
Sometimes, I want to run and run.
Till my head bursts.
Till my heart bursts, too.
That's how I want to feel.
Like everything's going to…
Boom!
And all will be gone.
Along with me.
Hey!
Macabuhay!
What? It's not mine.
Whose is it, then?
It's…
To the principal's office. Now.
Hey!
What?
They gave me a warning.
Just a warning!
Let's celebrate.
It's your treat. Come
on, I'm starving.
Hold on.
Don't be mad anymore.
Life is short!
Very good, Group 1.
What? You're getting me in trouble
again. I don't see it that way.
I'm keeping you on your toes.
So you'd be alive,
alert, and enthusiastic!
Let's go.
Can you just leave me alone?
If I did, you'd be miserable.
Your life would be sad.
I'm used to being sad.
Stop being mopey!
Are you scared?
Come on. The lesson's up
on YouTube anyway.
My bag!
Mr. Macabuhay,
where are you going?
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you!
Is it your birthday?
Nope.
It's a free cupcake.
Too good to pass up.
You better stop being like this.
You always get me in trouble.
It's you who needs to stop.
Your life is boring.
Well, that's true.
Let's change that.
Why not do something about it?
What funny ideas
are you getting now?
First, I wanna go to college.
I wanna get into a
music conservatory.
And then,
I want to be a composer.
And third,
I'm gonna finish
this pasta before you!
Wait, hold on!
I'm giving you two seconds.
One,
two, three.
Wait up!
Eat faster, I'm beating you!
Hurry! I'm soaked!
Can you hold this?
Come on!
Come on, hurry up!
Hold on!
Why are we even out in this rain?
We're gonna get sick.
You just had to take
me to your house!
Yeah, yeah. Keep complaining!
Hurry up!
Come in, come in.
This is beautiful.
It's huge! You live alone?
Why didn't you invite
me over sooner?
'Cause you'll make a mess.
And you'll eat
everything in my fridge.
Are there any ghosts in here?
What ghosts?
Who's this?
My mom.
Come on, this way.
Over here!
Do you have an extra shirt?
Here.
Thanks.
Why don't you change?
I'm doing it.
Hey!
Why did you look?
You were talking to me.
You could've answered
without looking!
Sorry.
I didn't see anything.
Give me your wet
clothes. I'll hang them.
Are we doing this?
Yeah.
You don't want to?
If we do this,
everything will change.
No.
Yes.
It will get complicated.
It won't get complicated.
But we're okay the
way we are now.
We're okay. I…
I need this more, not…
Okay.
I understand.
You're mad.
Frustrated.
But, whatever you want.
I will respect that.
You're really…
really lucky to have me.
It's true that I'm lucky
to be with Cream.
Sadness had been my default.
And then, she came along.
Woof!
Woof! Wake up!
Good morning!
Where did that come from?
You two have the same hair.
Outside. I found him.
He's so cute.
Someone probably owns that.
I didn't see anyone.
If they look for him,
we'll give him back.
But, for now, we'll name him…
Charles.
That's my name.
You go by Keith anyway.
Also, why are you
named Charles Keith?
It sounds like a shoe brand.
We have to change it.
Let's make it… K.
Kay? Sounds like a girl's name.
What? Not K-A-Y.
Just the letter "K"!
As in, "You're O-K!"
I thought we were naming the dog.
Because we're a family.
You're K.
This is Charles.
And I'm Cream.
What the hell?
So, I have to adjust for a dog.
Why are you "Cream"?
Because I like ice cream.
Ice cream?
You know what'll
suit you? "Pick".
Why?
Because that's what they'll use to
stab you with when the owner finds out.
No!
So, that's what you want, huh?
Gross!
Let go!
You're disgusting!
I didn't know you had Roman feet.
No, they're Filipino.
Smart-ass.
Your big toe is bigger
than the next toe.
That means you'll live longer.
What? That's not true. Fake news.
My mom and dad had the same feet,
but look what happened, still.
They're gone.
Sorry.
It's okay.
We're the same.
We're not.
Your parents were in an accident.
They had no choice.
My mom is alive but she left me.
She might as well be dead.
That hurts even more.
Come on.
When someone leaves, it hurts. Doesn't
matter if it's on purpose or not.
So, you…
You dummy. I'm telling you.
If you die first…
I'll kill you!
Right, Charles?
That's not allowed. No, no, no.
Come here.
Hey, Cream.
Eat up so you can
take your medicine.
I don't want to.
I don't have any appetite.
I made sure it isn't
too hot. Come on. No.
Come on.
I don't want it.
Cream, it's going to spill.
Jeez!
I want to die.
Do you mean that?
Just kidding.
I was just pretending
to scare you.
I wanna see how
important I am to you.
Do whatever you want.
You think too much.
Keep this on, okay? Stay still.
You are important to me, Cream.
I said, stay still.
What?
You're the most important person
in my life.
You're my reason to live.
Thanks.
Thank you for coming
into my life. Just rest.
I would do everything
to stay with you.
Let's go inside.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Why did you leave Keith?
I didn't want to leave my son.
You hurt him.
It hurts me more.
I am sick.
I know all too well that my son would
do anything to get me treatment.
Why wouldn't you want that?
There's no cure.
I may be able to
live a while longer…
But that's the most
that can be done.
I don't want him to spend everything
his dad left for his future on me.
That's more important to me.
I'm begging you.
I am feeling weaker each day.
I think my body and my
cancer cells are battling it out.
I hope they take a break.
Not this time, please?
Stay stable.
I don't want to let go yet.
Not yet.
Hey, Keith!
I fell asleep.
Are you sick?
No.
Why did you pass out?
It's happened a few times.
I'm probably anemic.
Lisa.
I hope you keep it between us.
I don't want to worry Cream.
Fine.
But see a doctor, okay?
Hi. Amanda, Bonnie's manager.
Keith, right?
Yeah.
I'm excited to work with you.
Likewise.
Bonnie is on her way.
She's here.
Hello, hello.
Bonnie is here.
Bonnie is your bomb.
Ready to explode.
Boom.
Hi.
My staff. Eman,
producer/bodyguard.
And Paul.
Keith.
To hope
Anytime
I'll be waiting till
our hearts meet
It's you that my heart beats for
My heart…
Cut! Cut, Bonnie!
Let's cut!
Why?
Bonnie. Relax.
No need to belt it out so much.
I was relaxed enough.
Well, we weren't.
That was my normal
key. Wasn't even high.
High enough to get on my nerves.
Why?
Is something wrong?
No.
Yes!
It's the lyrics that are bad.
They're not even romantic.
There should be
more romantic words.
Like, "death".
"Infinite".
"Everlasting" or "the end".
You call that romantic?
Stop making excuses.
Let's change it.
Yes.
I am the recording star.
I'm the one singing it.
She gets what she wants.
Okay!
Okay.
And that line? "Till
our hearts meet"?
It doesn't sound smooth.
Aw, is that so?
Yeah, so change it. Now.
I know what we need to change.
Change your voice.
It sounds like a road roller.
Oh, my God!
How dare you?
You are so rude!
You're ruining my work.
You bitch!
Bonnie!
Oh, my…
Stop!
Hey.
What happened?
You left all that drama.
What did you do?
I stood my ground.
Why did it look like you came out
of a boxing match?
Nothing like that.
She should be thankful
they held me back.
I've already talked to our boss.
Just apologize.
I'll think about it.
What are you going
to do without me?
And you? What will
you do when I'm gone?
Whoever goes first needs to find
a way to get reincarnated, okay?
Let's find each other.
Wait. I need proof.
Say it.
I don't believe in reincarnation.
Fine, since you're
being so pushy.
I'll come back as your pillow.
So you'd hold me
tight all the time.
I wouldn't want to be your
shoes, though. Your feet smell.
You promised, okay?
You've made a promise to me.
I wouldn't just search for you.
I would go to God
for you and beg.
I love it!
It's cheesy.
You're right to put "life after
death" instead of "death".
So morbid.
You're so brilliant!
Thanks.
Bonnie, why do they act
like they're mafia?
Eman?
He used to be an NBI agent.
He's the one who recruited the
team. They act like my bodyguards.
That explains it.
Bonnie, I'm sorry for what
happened at the recording.
Bonnie is able to move on.
Bonnie is happy.
Bonnie likes your lyrics.
So, Bonnie is now your friend!
You're funny when you speak like that.
You sound like a Facebook status.
Cream is funny.
Cream is happy.
And Cream is sorry.
"Boom, I Love You"
is the title track of choice.
Upbeat and catchy.
What do you think, K?
I think that's your usual.
Why not something
unexpected and different?
Why not choose "Waiting"?
Bonnie likes that, too!
No.
Yes!
This is not your sound.
Bonnie can have different sounds.
I like it.
It would sell.
Then we'll make a music video.
A sad, romantic one.
This will go viral.
Sad?
Yes, the song is sad.
I'll be emoting in
the music video.
It'll be great!
Is this the one by Cream?
Yes!
Cream.
How was it?
Did they say yes?
Tell me!
Congratulations!
Wait. Why are you
congratulating me?
Are you serious?
Your song is the
album title track!
Let's go.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Is there something
going on between you two?
Something?
Never mind.
You're not going to admit it.
Anyway, I want to
celebrate Cream.
It's my treat.
Let's eat out!
Where?
You guys have fun.
There's something I need to do.
What?
I have to sort something out.
Anyway, let's just go.
Bye, see you next time.
Have fun!
Doctor, am I okay?
No, you're not.
It's been a year since I
told you to quit your job.
I'm not going to make it
even if I quit anyway, right?
That's not the point.
We're trying to avoid infections.
You can get the common cough.
And it will cause complications.
Please take care of yourself.
Especially when we're still waiting
for a donor for your transplant.
You said that two years ago.
Still, nothing.
Don't lose hope.
Too bad K can't make it.
This is our favorite place.
What's going on
between you and him?
Nothing.
There is something.
We're just friends.
But you live together?
Live-in?
We have separate rooms.
What? Is he gay?
So, how come nothing happened?
Because we're not like
what you're thinking.
So, what are you?
Housemates?
Do you like him?
There we go.
Well, your boyfriend is weird.
He's not my boyfriend.
Okay. This is what
you're gonna do.
It'll get him to
come to his senses.
Look for a super cute guy.
And then, he'll get jealous.
That's when he'll
realize he loves you.
Is that how it works?
Trust Bonnie!
Bonnie has a
solution for everything.
Do you have something to tell me?
No?
Don't you have
any secrets to share with me?
Why are you being weird?
Say, I'm a priest and
you wanna confess.
What would you say to me?
Bless me, father,
for I have sinned.
Not that one!
Let's eat. You're just hungry.
You eat. Eat all you want, okay?
Let's put it this way.
What's your wish for me?
I want you to be
happy, of course.
And for you to find
someone who loves you.
Why? Don't you love me?
That's different.
What I mean is,
I want you to find someone…
you can spend your life with.
Someone smart,
nice,
devout…
healthy…
And…
will give you a comfortable life.
But we're comfortable
here, right?
I'm not marrying you.
Also,
when I get married,
I'll throw you out.
This is my classmate
in high school, Lisa.
This is my girlfriend, Cindy.
All right, you two
enjoy yourselves. Okay.
I should get back.
Nice seeing you again.
Who was that?
He was my schoolmate.
Valedictorian.
Smart?
Smart.
Rich.
Good-looking.
Nice.
But, he's taken.
I see another friend!
Sorry. Is it okay?
Of course!
Sure!
Just leave us!
No! I'm coming back. Wait.
Alan!
Lisa!
Hey!
What's up?
Go on then.
Hi!
Is it okay?
I'll be fine here.
Sorry, hon.
I wouldn't leave you here
if I could help it.
I know some girls
might hit on you here.
But I have to go.
Okay, but take care.
You've had a few.
Yes, yes. Thanks, hon!
Take care on your way home. Bye.
Bye.
Thanks.
Hey, sweetheart.
Get him to come to his senses.
Look for a super cute guy.
That's when he'll
realize he loves you.
Let me borrow this.
What?
Your glass.
There aren't any other ones left.
What?
Your choice if you
still wanna use it.
It's like we just kissed.
But only a quick smack!
In case you think I'm cheap.
What?
Messy, as always.
So, Cream, how long
have you known Lisa?
All right. Rinse first.
I met her at work.
You two met in high school?
Why is it taking so long?
To answer your first question,
we met in high school.
She used to copy
off me in our tests.
And to answer your
second question,
You have a cavity on your molar.
So I took it slow.
I hope you take it slow
when you fall for me.
Slow because it's deep.
Okay, um, you have a
follow-up appointment next week.
Because I need to
check on that cavity.
You're too much.
On our first meeting,
it's like you kissed me.
This meeting's more
like an intense kiss.
Deep in my esophagus.
Good news!
I met someone.
I wish you'd knock.
I wish you'd lock the door.
Anyway, you should be glad
because I met someone.
What do you mean?
Didn't you say you want
someone to love me?
Now, I found him.
Aren't you happy?
Where did you even meet him?
A bar?
What if he's a drug
dealer or an addict?
Neither. He's Lisa's classmate.
He's an approved
gentleman, for sure.
Move over.
Hey! You pushed me.
How is it, Doctor?
Is it getting better?
Is it stable, or is
it getting worse?
Even if you undergo chemotherapy,
you know that only a
transplant will cure you.
If there's no donor,
how long would I have?
This is the time to focus on
making your body stronger.
So that when a donor
comes, you're ready.
If there's no donor…
shouldn't I be ready
for something else?
Maybe.
More or less…
A year.
I'll just wait for the pastries.
Bro.
Shouldn't you be with Bonnie?
Nope.
She just asked for coffee.
Bro, can I ask you a favor?
You were a policeman,
right? Or NBI?
Dude, we don't kill people.
Dude, no. I don't
wanna kill someone.
Just wanted a background
check on someone.
All right, then.
"Compositions by Sue Anne."
Who's Sue Anne?
Me! AKA Cream.
So, you're a songwriter.
Congrats!
Impressive, huh?
Yeah. You're impressive.
Hang on.
You don't have an
appointment today.
Nope. Just here to drop that off.
Okay. Thank you.
Just "thank you"?
No congratulatory
blowout or a treat?
For what?
Because I gave you a CD!
CD. Right.
Actually, I don't
have a CD player.
You just don't want to treat me.
Come on, treat me.
Is that a guy thing?
When it's hard for you
to express your feelings?
Not really.
I mean…
Women are generally
more outspoken than men, right?
But what about you?
What do you mean, me?
If you like someone
or love someone,
is it easy for you to
say what you feel?
Yeah. I guess, yeah.
How can you tell?
Well…
I have a fiancée, so…
Do you love your fiancée?
Yeah. I love her.
I feel like you only think that.
I feel you two will break up.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! Sorry.
John Luis.
Top 10 in the dentist
licensure exam.
No criminal records.
No traffic violation.
Healthy?
He's perfect.
But… he has a girlfriend.
Cindy De Leon.
Professional photographer.
Here's what we'll do.
Let's hire her for
Bonnie's promo shoot.
This feels strange.
Are you a stalker?
No, um…
Let's just keep it
between us, okay?
Hey, you smell like alcohol.
Are you drunk?
Just a bit.
Come upstairs...
No, thanks.
I'll just sleep here on the sofa.
I might throw up on your bed.
Who were you drinking with?
John.
Did you enjoy yourself?
What do you like about him?
What's with the Q&A?
Am I on Miss Universe?
Okay, ready,
Bonnie? Let's do this.
Test shot, first.
Okay, start.
Give me that fierce look. Okay.
I love it!
Okay, let's hold that.
And then, look at the camera.
That's perfect.
Hold that one. Hold that one.
Just give me more
poses, all right?
Just a little bit
closer to each other.
Yes! I love that leg.
Just point your toes.
Gorgeous, Bonnie.
Just look at the camera.
One last.
Okay, let's do
some retouch first.
Glam team!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Where's the chart
for Anne Monson?
Here, sir.
Thank you.
Welcome.
You need to be hospitalized.
Or, at the very least, get a
private nurse to take care of you.
Doctor, I can still
take care of myself.
As long as Cream doesn't know.
You're still concerned about her
over yourself?
I'll have to run away
if she ever knows about this.
She should be able to decide.
Don't deprive her
of her right to do that.
Ma'am, Charles Keith
Macabuhay, please?
Cubicle 1.
K, what happened?
Did you freak out?
What happened to him?
Why were you feeling dizzy?
I'm pregnant.
Hey.
It's not funny!
His hemoglobin is very low.
He has anemia.
How did you get anemia?
Nutrition deficiency.
You eat a lot,
so I haven't been getting enough from
what little's left from our dinners.
Ow!
Ow! That hurts!
Stop it.
Cindy.
Hon!
Who's this?
It's not what you think.
Answer me, Cindy.
Who's this?
It's really nothing.
Cindy, this is not nothing.
I'm sorry! So I messed up.
You were always so busy!
What sort of excuse is that?
Busy?
I was busy working
for our future.
Where did you get even get those?
Does that even matter?
We're done.
Hon!
We can tone down this part here.
Hey!
What did I ever do to you?
What's this about?
Why did you get
me into this mess?
What do you mean?
You bastard!
I saw you on our security's CCTV.
You took pictures of us!
I can sue you!
Tell you what.
Instead of stalking…
why don't you just help me
with Bonnie's album?
Is that all you
really care about?
What?
What do you mean?
I'll lose my job.
It's easy to find another job.
But, Cream's future…
It's over for us now.
Not us.
Just me.
Are you drunk?
Or are you being serious?
I'm being serious.
Cindy might wreak havoc.
I don't want Cream
to find out about all this.
All right.
We'll fix it.
I want to apologize
for the mess I've made.
It's not just a mess you've made.
You've ruined everything.
So, what is this?
A consolation prize?
That was not my intention.
Everything you see here…
was all possible because of John.
He made me.
But you don't love him, right?
If you did, you wouldn't...
Why are you so
obsessed with John?
My friend likes him.
Bravo!
So, there are still guys like you
these days.
So I bet…
you're in love with her?
Is John a good person?
Yes.
Can I ask why you cheated on him?
I played around.
Harmless.
But you got into our business.
We'll still make up.
What will it take
for you to give up on him?
Nothing.
So, what's your story?
I'm dying.
I want to make sure…
that someone will
take care and love her.
Here's the calling
card of my doctor.
Just in case.
Sorry, I have to go.
Wait.
Here's the deal.
If I can really
verify your story…
I might consider it.
But you have to let
me cover your story.
How?
You'll be the subject
of my next exhibit.
I don't want to.
You don't get to decide.
I do.
Hello.
I didn't break in or anything.
The security guard let me in.
What are you doing here?
You said you'd be home late.
So, I thought I'd bring you
some congee, pork and tofu.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
It's not.
This is something.
You're the first
to have ever done this for me.
Next time, let me
know what you want.
I'll bring it to you.
You're sweet.
It's not sweet.
I'll have to charge you
for the delivery service.
Flat rate. Just 40 pesos.
Eat up.
Thank you.
Flirt with the camera, Bonnie!
I wanna see those flirty eyes.
Good!
K, meet John.
Hi.
K, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Okay, I'll leave you two to it.
Is it okay?
You know what, K?
I feel like I know you already.
Cream keeps talking about you.
Likewise.
Me too.
Yeah, Cream talks too much.
A little.
Bonnie, cut!
Why are you pouting like that?
Sorry, sir.
It's my fault.
Sorry, guys! Sorry.
Thank you for doing
what we'd agreed.
No choice. John and
I were over anyway.
Where did you meet Cream?
We met in high school.
One more. Left. Yeah.
But why is she such
a big deal to you?
Do I need to explain that?
She's important to me.
She's important to you…
But you will not
tell her the truth?
Yes.
Precisely because
she's important to me.
Why?
I don't want to hurt her.
Camera.
But, when you're gone…
you'll still hurt her.
So why would I want her to grieve
before that?
She's already been through a lot.
But…
What about you?
She's more important
to me than myself.
It shows that you love her a lot.
You chose my
boyfriend to make sure…
that she'll be taken care of
in the future.
I don't know John.
They chose each other.
Cindy and I are done.
Huh?
Well…
It would be stupid to stay
together at this point, right?
So…
We called off the engagement.
Are you gonna be okay?
That was six years.
Yeah.
I'll be fine.
Actually, I'm…
I'm relieved.
I can't see a future
for us anymore.
The trust is gone.
It's hard to gain it back.
She's not like you.
John, you should
know more about me.
I was in my fourth year in
high school when it happened.
My parents had just
dropped me off at school…
Then, there was a collision.
All of a sudden…
my whole family was gone.
I became an orphan.
Then, I met K.
He was also an orphan.
We became family. I
know it sounds weird.
No.
It isn't weird.
K is…
He's all-in-one.
He's like my mom
when I need some scolding.
He's like…
my dad too.
When I need
someone to protect me.
And, like a boyfriend…
when I need someone to hold me.
Thank you.
Thank you for opening up to me.
You make me
appreciate you even more.
And I understood you more, now.
Hi, baby.
For you.
You like them?
Yes.
Thanks.
Babe?
What is it?
My gift for you.
Sorry, I don't
have a gift for you.
It's okay.
You are more than enough.
Okay?
There's nothing else I need.
Only you.
I made you coffee.
It's over there.
I'll just finish up here.
Okay. I'll sit over there then.
Okay.
Is that from him?
K, why do people get married?
He proposed?
No.
I was just asking.
Maybe…
It gives meaning
to someone's life.
And it lets you experience it all
with someone else.
Joy.
Sadness.
Success.
Failure.
That's why it's "for
better or for worse", right?
Why aren't we married, then?
Isn't that us?
We're not that.
Hey!
It's to have someone by your side
for life and in your twilight years.
So, I'll just hire a nanny then.
Or a nurse.
Then marry someone
to have someone share the bills.
Is that what marriage is to you?
No.
I believe…
when two people
really love each other,
God wouldn't separate them.
It's "till death do
us part", right?
It's like my parents.
They died together.
Neither of them had to feel…
the pain of losing one another.
I'm starving.
Let's eat.
You're always hungry.
You should check for worms.
The mind seeks and
tries to comprehend
The feeling
You need to know
My heart is only yours
My only one…
K?
Don't smile.
What's wrong with smiling?
It doesn't make a sound.
Still.
If you smile, it
seems like there's joy.
It should be sad.
Okay.
Should doubts be entertained?
Expect my…
That's too sad, K.
One more time.
Should doubts…
be entertained?
Expect my everlasting promise
Anytime
I will be here
I won't be abandoning you
Anytime
Everlasting love
Is what your heart desires
And you want to possess it
I'm here
Ready to love you
Without…
end…
The song is beautiful.
Thanks.
I almost can't
believe you wrote it.
Stop it.
Would Bonnie like the song?
Will the song like Bonnie?
K.
I know how close
you are with Cream.
We're just friends.
It just so happens
that she lives with me.
She told me about it.
And I understand
the dynamic between you two.
I don't want us to feel
awkward around each other.
Okay? Especially because…
you're very important to her.
Family.
That's us.
Right.
I understand.
That's why I want
you to be with her
during the preparation
of our wedding.
If, of course, that's
okay with you.
Yeah, of course.
Why not?
But, K, I want you to
understand something.
After our wedding…
Cream is my responsibility.
No one else's.
I will take care of her.
Of course.
I'll respect that.
Okay.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Well, what do you think?
You look decent.
It suits you, ma'am.
Sir, would you want to try
your suit as well?
I'm not the groom.
Yes! Persuade him for me.
I want to see how it matches with my
gown when I am standing beside the groom.
Quick! Take him.
I don't want to.
Go!
Shall we take a selfie?
One,
two…
I'll just try on the
other gown, okay?
Stay here.
No. I don't want
to send it to you.
I want it to be a surprise
on the wedding day.
Hello?
Is the food ready? I'm starving.
Hold on, okay?
Hello.
My phone died. I'll call
you once I charge it, okay?
Okay, bye-bye!
This won't take long.
Then, we can dig in.
Where did you go?
You left me looking
silly back there.
Hello?
Hello, K?
Yes, K's here. May I
know who's calling?
Hello?
I'll call you later.
Okay. Bye.
What was that?
Huh?
What?
It's my phone!
It's not a landline!
Do you have any
sense of propriety?
You have no respect for privacy!
Who was that?
Are you seeing her?
Is she your girlfriend?
Don't wait for me.
Hey! You eat up first.
I'm full.
You'll miss my
cooking when I'm gone!
I'll get takeout!
You shouldn't have said anything.
Don't be paranoid.
I only said hello.
She won't recognize my voice.
She might associate
you with John.
I thought you'd want her to
think that you're seeing someone?
Yes.
So she can focus on John.
You really love her so much.
Don't you think she
deserves to know?
No.
Cindy.
Can you do me a favor?
On her birthdays,
can you send her flowers for me?
Are you sure?
Don't you think that would be…
torture for her?
You want her to
forget you, right?
You confuse me sometimes.
I just thought of it.
So it would feel less sudden
for her to lose me.
Here.
K.
You'll die anyway.
You should do
all the things you want in life.
Say everything you
want to say to her.
So that neither of you
would have regrets.
Just because you're about to die…
doesn't mean you're entitled
to do whatever you want.
If you love someone…
you'd do what's best for them.
Even if it hurts you.
I think you're just scared.
I'm not scared to die.
When my mom left me…
That was when I wanted to die.
But Cream changed everything.
Now, I want…
I really want to live.
I still want to love her.
I still want to be with her.
I'm really happy
when I'm with her.
But it's going to end soon.
I can't do anything about it.
HAVE YOU EATEN?
NOT YET.
GO TO THE KITCHEN
BUT DO NOT TALK TO ME.
THANK YOU
AND I'M SORRY.
FOR WHAT?
IT'S OKAY.
JUST DON'T DO IT AGAIN.
I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY
K. I want you to
understand something.
After our wedding,
Cream is my responsibility.
No one else's.
I will take care of her.
K, wait! K, where are you going?
Talk to me! Wait! Don't leave me!
K! Don't leave me, please!
K, don't leave me! K!
K!
Cream?
Cream.
John, I'm sorry.
All I can say to you is…
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the
love that you gave me.
Sorry for all my
faults and mistakes.
Why is it so hard for me
to write a song for you?
You ask for deep songs.
As if you have the voice for
them. You've got a screechy voice.
Sorry for all my
faults and mistakes.
The most painful thing…
wasn't discovering
that K was sick.
Hey.
What happened?
It was realizing that he
was going through it alone.
What did you do?
I stood my ground.
What are you going
to do without me?
And you? What will
you do when I'm gone?
I should be with him.
I realized he was pushing me away
to be with someone else
not because he doesn't love me,
but because he loves me so much.
You need to be hospitalized.
Or, at the very least, get a
private nurse to take care of you.
Doctor, I can still
take care of myself.
As long as Cream doesn't know.
You're still concerned about her
over yourself?
I'll have to run away…
if she ever knows about this.
She should be able to decide.
Don't deprive her
of her right to do that.
As long as I'm capable of fighting
this, I'll continue doing it.
I don't want to die…
before I see Cream
live a better life.
My family had just
passed away back then.
It was the most painful thing
I've ever felt.
Then, I saw K.
I didn't know what
had happened to him.
The only thing I knew…
was that he was sadder than me.
It made me curious about him.
Perhaps, it was my way
of distracting myself.
I want you to find someone…
you can spend your life with.
Someone smart, devout…
Healthy.
And will give you
a comfortable life.
But we're comfortable
here, right?
I'm not marrying you.
Also, when I get married,
I'll throw you out.
I hope you'll understand.
K needs me.
I'm the only family he has.
He only has me.
I don't believe in reincarnation.
Fine, since you're
being so pushy.
I'll come back as your pillow.
So you'd hold me
tight all the time.
I wouldn't want to be your
shoes, though. Your feet smell.
I'm sorry John, I didn't mean it.
I needed to have you
so K would see that…
it's okay for him to die.
Do you love me?
What about me? Do you love me?
I asked you first.
But I was the one who
made the first move.
You make me very happy.
Do you want to be
happy every day?
From morning to evening?
Are you proposing to me?
No.
I'm waiting for you to propose.
I've had the chance to love…
two such wonderful men.
If God would give me a chance
to fulfill my wish…
I hope you'll think over
everything I've said.
Don't be angry.
Don't be bitter.
And I hope…
I hope you won't be
afraid to love again.
Sorry.
Let's practice them.
Huh?
The, um…
wedding vows.
Okay.
Do you, Cream,
take John…
to be your husband?
Do you promise
to be faithful to him,
in good times and in bad?
In sickness and in health…
to love him and to honor him
in all the days of your life?
I take you…
to be my lawful wedded husband.
To have and to hold.
From this day forward…
for better or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness and health…
'till death do us part.
Actually, they used to be
our regular customers.
I even have a copy of their CD.
You might want to check it out.
Thank you.
I want to record Cream's songs.
You look stupid.
You thought I wouldn't find you?
It's okay.
I'm here now. You'll get better.
We promised each other.
If you leave me,
I'm really going to kill you.
Don't be afraid.
You'll be okay.
Everything will be okay.
We're going home, okay?
I'll take care of you.
We're going home.
I'm here.
Just here.
Eat a little.
There.
Cream?
I'm sorry.
I messed up your life.
What are you talking about?
We're even.
I'm the one who
messed up your life first.
Messy is better, right?
Better than boring?
I'm okay.
Of course, you're okay!
Because I'm here now.
Right?
Remember? That's
why I named you K.
Look.
Look at this.
Cream?
I'm not afraid anymore.
You asked me before
what my wish was.
My wish…
is to be with you always.
K! K!
Look here, K.
Look. See?
We're so cute here.
Selfie?
Let's take a selfie?
I want it to be wacky, okay?
K, my wish…
I wish you wouldn't leave me.
K, I love you so much.
I believe…
that when two people really love
each other,
God wouldn't separate them.
It's "till death do
us part", right?
John!
Glad you could come!
You invited me, remember?
Come.
He really was different.
They're both different.
If I hadn't met K,
I wouldn't have believed
that true love exists.
He said to me once,
"Just because you're dying,
doesn't mean you're entitled
to do whatever you want.
If you love someone,
you'd do what's best for them.
Even if it hurts you."
He loved with everything he had
and didn't have.
How are you doing?
I'm coping.
I'll be okay one day.
What about Cream?
Like I said…
they're both different.
A few days after K died…
her heart stopped.
Maybe because it'd
been beating for him.
I'm sorry.
It hurts, but…
I carry everything I
learned from them.
And I hope we will be
better human beings
because of them.
Bye, Mom!
Bye, Dad.
Bye-bye!
Take care!
Mom?
Mom!
Mom! The car that let
us through just got hit!
What do you want me to do?
You want me to worry about them?
Your father is dying!
Hang on, sweetheart!
I take you…
to be my lawful wedded husband.
To have and to hold.
From this day forward…
for better
or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness
and in health,
till life…
after death.