Core Contents Media Presents
In association with Shoebox
A Core Contents Media Production
(Io-produced by
Goldemhumb 8- Poibos
Hey, Jung-sik?
How is it?
What do you think.
I need it for
the drama next week
so tell him it's great!
Like Seung-chul ever listens to me.
Then make him.
He's gotta do this song.
But the lyrics are weak, man.
What the suits say goes.
That's show biz.
Whatever, man!
- Hold up!
- What is it?
You like this song?
Of course! Why?
Singing about a girl
to come back to me at my age?
My heart this and
tears that...
Isn't it childish?
No! It's perfect!
Don't you think?
It's great.
Make your fans
really feel the song, man!
But I don't feel anything!
You can do it, man.
Feel me?
- It's great!
- No.
It's not working for me.
Seung-chul! Come on!
Get him!
Seung-chul!
Yes, director.
I see.
KWON Sang-woo
Next Tuesday?
The song's a killer.
LEE Bo-young
LEE Bo-young Nothing but the
best from LEE Seung-chul.
Nothing but the best
from LEE Seung-chul.
Of course.
LEE Beom-soo
No problems whatsoever.
Yes, sir. Take care.
JUNG Ae-yeon, LEE Han-wui
See? He's asking for the song.
Do it for me?
Executive Producer KIM Gwang-soo See?
He's asking for the song. Do it for me?
You always do this to me.
Please?
So get me a good song
and I'll sing it! Damn!
Producer HONG Jung-pyo So get me a
good song and I'll sing it! Damn!
What about 'Hee-ya'?
'Hee-ya, please look at me.'
Give me a break.
That was a hit
only because you sang it.
Wanna hear this song I got?
What is it?
It's off a flopped album.
Forget it, kid!
Let's hear it.
Really? Turn it on.
To give you everything
and all my love...
Who wrote this?
The lyrics are great.
Really? Then let's ask them
to write our lyrics.
Who wrote this?
Not sure.
I got this off someone.
Who?
Min-chul. He used to work for
KIM Gap-sik.
Gap-sik?
I know him well.
Hey, didn't he leave the biz?
Who does your friend
work for now?
He left the biz, too.
What does he do?
He runs a cafe in Chung-pyung.
Wanna go over, Seung-chul?
- Know where it is?
- Yes.
Lead the way.
Director WON
Got the album?
Ah, here.
What's the title?
It's the second track.
Second track?
'No one else like Thee'
by Cream?
What's her real name?
I think it was EUN Won.
Yeah, that' s it.
Got her number?
She's gone.
Gone? To where?
Right after KANG Chul-kyu left...
KANG knows her well?
Of course.
He was totally in love with her.
Do you have KANG's number?
- He died.
- He's dead?
When?
About a month after
he married off EUN Won.
Mr. KANG!
What was the name of his show?
'Ugly Ducklings in Love'.
Yeah, that's it!
He married off
the woman he loved?
- What does that mean?
- Well...
Tell us what happened.
It's a long story.
Hi, Chul-kyu!
KANG said he saw stars
when he first met Cream.
Why you little punk!
Like he'd been slapped
on the back of his head.
He said it was love
at first sight.
Without even talking to her.
I asked,
'Shouldn't you at least
say a few words, first?'
Then he said...
If you need words,
then how can mutes love?
How did you know my name?
Isn't it a waste living
in this big place alone?
Want me to live with you?
Think of a name for me,
and I'll make one for you.
We can't change our names.
Why not?
Her name is Cream
and my name is K.
She was cold like ice cream,
- but also sweet like ice cream.
- The curtains won't do.
We're changing everything.
And she was
soft like ice cream.
And I'm not
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K...
But just K.
We had a lot in common.
We were the same age.
We both liked noodles.
We loved listening to music
on rainy days.
We loved coffee.
We hated school.
She liked me.
And I liked her.
And we were both orphans.
Prison and love...
Once you're stuck,
you can't get out.
I fell in love with Cream.
Even the very air she breathed.
Romeo must've been so worried...
loving Juliet,
but afraid he might lose her.
Why did he drink the poison?
Perhaps he knew.
To love someone
- is to give her everything.
- I'll visit often.
I received so much from her
like the catcher who gets the ball'.
Love was like dry ice.
Sometimes cold, sometimes hot.
Wait!
Cream was so loveable.
But I couldn't tell her
that I loved her.
Because I had cancer cells in me
ready to strike at any time.
More than Blue
Thank you, Mr. KIM.
It's the least I can do.
Writers need to eat well
to do all that thinking.
Have some soup with the Kimbap
and chew carefully.
Is this your new singer?
Greet them, girl.
They're the best writers in SBC.
Hello, I'm Cat Girl.
I promise to sing my heart out.
Damn right you should.
Great outfit.
It's a new concept.
She's a cat.
It's Cat Girl.
This gal's got brains.
She's a student
at Seoul University.
Really?
It's Seoul University of Arts.
Whose side are you on?
You could get in trouble
for lying about schools these days.
If you're so holy,
go be a cop instead.
Sorry.
Mr. Kang!
How are you?
Here's Seung-chuFs new album.
It's deep.
- It's a sure hit.
- I'm sure it's great.
- Say hi.
- Hello.
Call me K.
Let's go for drinks some time.
- Sounds great.
- Bye.
Seoul Univ. of Arts.
Same difference.
That's right.
Did you eat, sir?
Mr. Kang!
- How've you been?
- I waited so long for you.
She's Cats.
Damn, I keep forgetting.
It's Cat Girl, sir.
Go on and
introduce yourself, girl.
I'm Cat Girl.
I promise to sing my heart out.
Thank you.
Of course you should.
Let's go some place quiet
to talk, Mr. Kang.
See you folks later.
- Come on, what are pals for.
- I can't.
It's just a show
of my appreciation.
The album's finished?
I put together all the best
songwriters around.
You know me,
I get what I want.
How is she?
Oh, her?
Not bad.
But she has trouble
getting along with the others.
Still she's got talent.
Be nice.
Of course.
Anything for you.
- But do this for me.
- I can't.
It's not much.
Please, take it!
I can't sleep
at the thought of you.
My dear love.
That part you just sang.
Try not to scream it this time.
You'll scare 'em off.
How, sir?
How would you feel
if someone screamed they loved you?
You know, softly and tenderly?
You're good at that.
What? Not that.
Stop making me do it.
- That's not what I meant!
- Roll it!
What's she so good at?
Drop it will ya, man?
Come on.
Just between us?
She's my future.
That's all I can tell ya, man.
Did you fix the second verse?
What?
The climax on the second verse.
'Always like yesterday'?
It's a little corny,
isn't it?
'A world without love?'
How's that?
Like that's not corny?
It's just a suggestion.
Let's not get too excited here.
You two write it, then.
I'm out.
What?
So feisty.
Do you have to become a singer?
What?
Got enough medication left?
My damn connection
to your family.
First your father, now you.
There are too many illnesses
that can't be cured.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Don't cry.
Stop crying-
The bastards told me
to rewrite it.
'If I could live again'.
How's that for the title?
'If I could live again?'
If you could,
what would you like to be reborn as?
Besides a person?
Anything.
Well...
lf l could live again...
A ring?
Wait.
Start over.
If I could be born again...
A ring.
A pair of glasses.
A bed.
A diary.
Born again as things like that?
What fun is that?
You can buy me.
It'll always be right at your side.
So sensible.
Did you eat?
Of course, I did.
Well, I didn't.
Then let's eat.
Is there anything
you want to tell me?
Like what?
A deep, dark secret?
Think of it as a confession
at a Catholic church.
I'll be the priest and listen.
A deep, dark secret?
Say anything.
I'm ready to listen.
I like you.
I want to ask you something.
Do you have a wish?
A wish?
If you could have
anything in the world?
First, hold up your spoon.
Then?
Eat all your food.
Meet a great guy
and get married.
Can't I marry you?
I'm not a great guy.
It wasn't my choice,
but heaven's will,
to fall in love with you.
I was born to love you.
Heaven sent me to love you.
Now, for the requested song.
Your second toe is longer than
the first one like mine.
That means your mom
will outlive you.
Who says that?
I think I read it somewhere.
It's a lie.
Why?
Because my Mom and Dad died
on the same day.
If you...
If you die before me,
I'll kill you!
Here's another requested song.
Are you finished?
Excuse me?
The coffee.
Then can I have the cup?
Which side did you drink from?
Pardon?
This isn't kissing, is it?
- Hey.
- Yeah?
- You know the guest doctor?
What kind of doctor is he?
Huh?
We need to fill a cavity.
Amalgam is stronger than resin.
We kiss on the first day.
You see inside me,
on the second day.
What should we do
on the third day?
What?
We'll decide when the time comes.
I'm in love!
A guest on another show.
He's a dentist.
Pass me the toothbrush?
You're listening to 'Happy Hour'.
- As you're out driving...
- Did you eat?
Oh, hi.
- Got a show to record, today?
- No.
The guest doctor
on your show...
Who? You mean CHA Joo-hwan?
How is he?
He's a great guy.
Why?
Just wondering.
His family's rich, he's nice,
and he makes a ton of money.
And he's a famous dentist.
You look a little sad today.
Good job, bro.
It was fun.
- Great show.
- Cut it short.
Hey, nice seeing you.
Let's go out for drinks.
Not if it's just a few drinks.
- How much then?
- All night?
All night! Alright!
What's his social security number?
- 730313105...
- 730313...
Sure you can get
his medical records?
Insurance companies get everything.
Bu! why do you want
to check out a guy?
I'll tell you later.
Bingo! He's got life
and medical insurance.
No record of family illness
or any operations.
He has an impeccable
health record.
You sure?
Insurance companies know
how to make money, man.
KANG!
If he has a hospital record,
we'll see it.
KANG!
Thanks. I owe you one.
Got a minute Mr. KIM?
For you, any time!
It's a gift.
Ah, thank you.
Just a thank you?
First my lips,
then my insides...
Now, you're in my head.
Buy me a drink?
A drink'!?
I don't get it.
Who would've thought I'd use
my former dark roots to help you?
No need to worry.
Now about Cats.
Man, I gotta change
that name!
It's Cat Girl, sir.
I know! It's up here
but I can't say it right!
Call me whatever you want, hon.
Who cares if it's a cat
or a dog?
That's my pretty-
My sweet Cats.
We're changing the name.
- Ah, sir?
- I said, I know!
Not that.
The phone.
Sorry, Producer KANG!
I checked and...
You kids scram for a sec.
I gotta take this call.
Go!
CHA Joo-hwan's family's loaded!
He even has a hot fiancé.
He's got it made.
Fiancé?
ls something up?
Oh, you dropped your candy.
Let's put it in your pocket.
Have you ever been in love?
Like a rock
thrown into the river.
Give me the ring.
Excuse me?
Your ring.
Like this.
Someone to pull you out.
I'm engaged.
It doesn't matter.
Let's keep drinking.
It's so cold.
Did you drink?
What do you like
so much about him?
I feel like I'm being sterilized.
Sterilized?
Sterilized.
Perfect.
- Let's eat.
- Sorry, I gotta run.
- You're not eating?
- I can't.
What about all this food?
You eat it all.
I'll see you later.
ABCDEFGHIJK...
Hello?
Is this EUN Won's number?
Yes, it is.
May I speak to her, please?
She's not here.
My name's CHA Joo-hwan.
We were supposed to
meet today
but something came up
at the clinic.
ls there any way
I can reach her?
Where were you going to meet?
So cold.
Hey.
He can't come.
Who?
Him.
The doc.
Where are you going?
L gotta go-
Sit down.
The curry here is great.
You know I don't eat curry.
Then what do you want?
What else is there?
What do you want to eat?
Kimbap.
So boring.
Just eat curry.
You're buying.
Come on Producer KANG.
Spill it.
Did he rip you off
or something?
Then, why didn't you say so!
My boys can get the money back
before lunch in no time.
It's not that.
Then what is it?
Why would someone like you want
the dirt on some guy's fiancé even?
Are you interested in his fiancé?
Just find out, please.
Fine, then.
Anyway, Cat's albums are
starting to get noticed, now.
Let's cook up something
with your show
and sell 'em like hotcakes!
I'm sure it'll do well.
Of course.
Hey, Min-chul!
Did you like the house?
Mother said she liked it.
It's not bad.
I heard you stopped
holding exhibitions.
I'm tired of putting on shows.
And there's nothing
to take pictures of.
I'm sorry I'm not more fun
to be around.
Don't worry.
I like to have fun by myself.
That's sad.
- Let's have fun together from now on.
- Sure.
Can I get an ashtray here?
I'm sorry.
There's no smoking here.
The world's such a bore.
Get her an ashtray
to put that out, please.
Yes, sir.
Interesting.
Keep smoking.
Should've known.
She's really somethin' all right.
She's got men
coming out of her ears.
I told 'em to take
some good pics.
It won't be long.
How did you pose
for your album cover?
I posed like I practiced
with my boss last night.
Exactly how?
- Here?
- Pardon?
Men are all the same.
Okay, then.
First, I open my eyes
like a cat.
Like this.
- Ah, Cat Girl?
- Then...
I hold my hands up
and open my mouth like this.
Look at her.
She's a natural born star!
You can just tell us.
But my boss said a star
- has to speak with the body.
- See that?
Girls like her adjust so quickly.
That foxy babe.
Who wouldn't love her?
- Ah, sir?
- KANG!
- What's wrong?
Where is he?
- Hey!
- I'm dead beat.
What's wrong with you!
What's with you!
Don't start.
Why does he keep fainting
like this?
It's hereditary,
but it could also be
not enough calcium
in his diet.
We've been eating the same food
in the same house for years!
Why are you the only one
who keeps fainting!
You eat way more than I do.
You're only eating anchovies
from now on, got that!
You!
Yes?
What did he just say?
To break off your engagement...
- Stop! Please!
- Who are you!
What the hell
are you trying to pull!
You don't wanna mess with me!
Get the hell out of my sight!
I said, get lost.
Why are you doing this?
Huh?
You're a successful
radio show producer.
Trailing a woman and
getting slapped like that.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I don't have time
to be embarrassed.
What are you talking about?
One mountain after another.
But no time to go.
Ow, my head.
Does it hurt?
I'm hurt, too.
What's with me today?
It's because we're sad.
Then cry instead of making jokes.
I don't want to cry.
Don't wanna make
someone cry even more.
I'm dying.
Just like my dad.
Chul-kyu!
Mom left me a year after
Dad died.
It probably wasn't
because she resented me.
She was sick of everything
because of Dad.
I understand.
I was sick of everything, too.
But when she left me all alone...
I was so lonely.
People...
should never be alone.
I'm sorry.
I want you to leave your fiancé.
The girl that I love is
in love with him.
- Medical records
I beg you.
Under one condition.
But...
But?
No, please!
Tell me.
I want to take your pictures.
Your medical records said
you don't have much time left.
Now, that's an interesting model.
I think it'll be fun.
I don't think it'll be fun.
Then the deal's off.
Drink up, first!
Give me a drink, too!
- Hi! Hi!
- Hi! You're late!
Hello.
I spoke to you on the phone.
Oh, hi.
I'm KANG Chul-kyu.
CHA Joo-hwan.
- Thanks again for that day.
- Anytime.
You know him?
The sterilizer?
- Did you eat?
- No, I'll eat now.
Why are you so late?
- Still recording a show.
- What?
You said you're done.
Not yet.
I gotta go back.
- Here.
- Thank you.
The song's great.
'If I can live again'?
Of course, I wrote it.
Sorry, I gotta run.
- Come on.
- Don't go.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
- See you next time, then.
- Sure.
Be careful in the snow!