"No love for the losers"
"When love is over"
"Morning bound train"
"Thoughts are having a tug-of-war"
"A lonely path"
"making the babe weep"
"How the stunned kitty make up to it"
"Scenaries that flashing by"
"how unwillingly to let it go"
"babe would become a passenger"
So Tung
Do you like it?
The lyrics are done an hour ago
Hot and fresh
- "Being a happy fool is a way of life as well"
- Jonny made the tune pretty catchy
- The market can use a song with a fuss
Well, that's true
But we invested a lotto work it in the web series
If the song doesn't go viral
It's GG for our company
She is a natural born diva
the fans will buy whatever she performs
Is that so?
- "How deep is babe's love"
- What are you worrying about?
- Just wait for the money to pour in
"scared the pants off"
Hold on a second
This is what I am worried about
Amanda
The lyrics
I can't really relate to it
Babe
scared the pants off
How should I sing it?
A-Lin, if we don't do the recording now
it would be too late for the mixing
Just give it a try
Ok
I am not doing it
You can sing the song on your own
Hey,babe
Uh no, A-Lin
I am a natural born diva
A-Lin
Can you do me this favor?
I would like to help
But I just can't sing it with my emotions
I know, I know
These phrases are very popular on the internet
But they are totally unrelated
to the tone of the song
How am I supposed to convey that?
Excuse me
What?
There is a song in my phone
It has not been published yet
I wonder if you can use it
No need
Play it, Hsiao-Yu, I want to hear it
Sure
"I don't envy the sun"
"it can't illuminate your past"
"there are certain darkness"
- "in both of us"
- What is the title of the song?
The lyrics are well-written too
The song is called A Kind of Sorrow
Maybe we can hire him to write the lyrics
so the song would still have a chance
Who wrote the lyrics?
I have no idea
A friend of mine, A-Pang gave it to me
Take me to him now
"If there is no need to speak up"
"then there is no need to"
"hide"
A-Pang
Hsiao-Yu
What brings you here?
Hi, I am Amanda
A-Lin's manager
A-Lin
The A-Lin?
Hi, how are you?
I am A-Lin
Here, come in please
Coffee on the house
Close the door for me, Hsiao-Yu
A-Pang
Do you know the lyric writer?
There is a song from our company
We would like to hire him to write the lyrics
do
She is called Cream
The Cream that did Face-to-face Breakup?
Yuan-Yuan
Yuan-Yuan Sung
Do you have her contact information?
Line, WeChat, or facebook?
No one can reach her now
Or anyone she knew?
Like the one that sang this Demo
He could probably reach her
The singer is Che-Kai Chang
Che-Kai Chang
- Does he know Yuan-Yuan Sung?
- Che-Kai Chang
Yes, he does
They fell in love with each other before
Great
Can you give me his phone number?
Please
This is really important
I need to find him no matter what
He passed away
He's dead
I remember it now
Che-Kai is K
We worked in the same record company
When I first joined the company
I met him once
then later he left the company
So it was him
It's really much too sudden
The story of Che-Kai Chang
began when he was 16 years old
His family left him that year
He began living on his own
in the old house that was piled
with his father's heirlooms
that he was too frustrated to organize
He kept everything to himself back then
as if he was destined to be alone
as if living itself is a painful thing
Until the day he met her
Eh
My treat
What are you doing?
You're smoking?
Hey
What class are you from?
How dare you smoke in school?
No, ma'am
it wasn't me
Get up
There's always student like you
Ma'am
- Don't grab my hair, ma'am
- breaking the rules
- with no discipline
- it hurts
No shame and manners
When Che-Kai Chang first met Yuan-Yuan Sung
it's love at first sight
I asked him how can it be love at first sight
since he didn't even introduce himself
He said
If love can be explained
no one in the world would suffer from it
Eh
Let's go home together
Hey
I got a minor demerit because of you
Don't be a square
It's just a minor demerit
I'll repay you with comics and instant noodle
Let's go
- Instant noodle
- that's right
- Three cups please
- you sure can eat
extra meet, egg, and vegetables
Since that day
Yuan-Yuan Sung has entered my life
and changed it too
Her free spirit
Her cheerful personality
Che-Kai Chang
opens up my heart
Which college?
- The same one
- What?
We got into the same college
We decided to celebrate our birthdays
Happy Birthday
Let's go
Wait
We have a lot in common
Enjoy reading comic books
Enjoy eating instant noodles
The one who loses will pay
Why are we competing over this?
Oh Che-Kai Chang, you are so generous
taking me to Kyoto for graduation photos
It costs you a lot right?
There are cherry blossoms
- You're so dramatic
- How nice of you
Ok, look over here
300 dollars for the Kyoto shot
I thought it's 150, master
There's two of you
Look over here
I just looked the other way
It's all right
I will count to three
one two
that's 600 dollars
That's a rip off
Here comes the best one
She likes challenges
And I
like to do the challenges with her
Hurry
We both enjoy eating popcicles in winter
We like the rain
like the seasons that we share
We became inseparable with each other
You live alone?
Since I was 16
I started living alone
Here
Here, clothes for you
Oh, right
I can't change with you being here
Go away
You're drenched, go dry it off
No peeking
- I won't peek
- Turn around
Eh
Fine
Childish
No peeking
I am watching you
I am not peeking
That's more comfortable
Eh
I should move in with you
This is a big house
I
I am used to living alone
I am alone
Get up
Look at the hours
Since that day, Cream moved in here
She opened up a window for me
a window that trapped me in loneliness
She dispels my sadness
and let me realize
after all
I deserve to have someone here for me
when people get used to loneliness
that is much sadder than sadness itself
Che-Kai Chang
I don't like the sound of it
Let me give you a new name
What are you talking about?
You should be called K
K
Right
That's a nickname, not a proper name
I will just call you K anyway
so it will be your name
Why K then?
Well because I am Cream
As in cream from ice cream
Then why are you Cream?
Because I like to eat ice cream
You like to eat ice cream
then you should be called ice cream
Why just Cream?
Cream is buttermilk
It means milk
milk
Where are you looking at?
Your boobs
Cream from Ice Cream
There's no milk in cream
You're talking nonsense
Fine, Cream
Cream
k
Eh
They said that people with Roman feet
their moms would live longer
What's Roman feet?
Like yours
Thumb of the foot is longer
That's not right
My parents died in a car accident together
She didn't live longer
But my mom is still alive
She left you when you're a kid
She is not in your life anymore
That doesn't count
Or maybe I don't have Roman feet
Check it out for me
Don't block the movie
Come on, check it out for me
- Do you think it's Roman feet
- You're really annoying
- It stinks
- that hurts
I am warning you
If you dare to die before me
you are so dead you hear me
Stop interrupting the movie
It's really sad
Are you watching it or not?
I cherish the moment I spent with her
but just like a prisoner sitting in a cell
when one fell in love
it is hard to get out
I fall in love with Cream
I love everything about her
I want to live with her forever
But I can't
I wouldn't dare to tell her my feelings either
because
something inside me is about to
act up the cancer cells
K
Che-Kai
Che-Kai Chang
You stayed up all night in the office again
You want the money more than your life
Keep it down
You are sweating all over in your sleep
Did I?
Yes
Your clothes are all soaked
I am probably too tired
One of the employee Lisa is getting married
I have to work so hard to cover her
I beg your pardon
You suddenly took a leave for a week last time
I nearly passed out trying to cover you
Lady
I really did pass out
Right
Seriously, Cream can't know about this
I know
You have already reminded me
the thrid time
You swear?
I swear
Ok?
Thanks
Go home already
I am not finished
Health comes first
No problem, I am really healthy
Hello
Hi, I am Lisa
Hi
Hi, I am Amanda
I start working today
- Looking forward to working with you
- Hi
I am Che-Kai Chang, just call me K
Hi, K
I am a manager
I am managing Feng-Yi now
Hi, I am Feng-Yi
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Very well
You coached him well
Thank you, K
Looking forward to working with you
Ok, we should get going
Sure, keep up the good work
Sorry to bother you
Thank you for your time
That's too fake
Didn't your father school you as a kid?
Hey
Say hi to Bonnie
K
Bonnie's new style
How is it? Looks great right?
Hi, K
Bonnie is the Galaxy idol
Supernova pretty kitty
I think it's pretty good
Not bad
Sorry, Chi
Can you turn off the music first?
Let me introduce you
This is my talent manager
A-Pang
Hi, K
Hi
Chi
Let's talk in the conference room
- Good
- Eh
This way
"You don't have to speak"
"Just meow with me together"
"Meow Meow Meow Meow"
"Bonnie hug"
"You are the one I rely on"
"Kitty bomb Bomb Bomb"
Time out
Eh
Bonnie
It's all right
You did good at the beginning
Very subtle
Don't try to yell at the high pitch part
Your throat might get hurt
Try it later
Use your strength from the belly
Hold your bottom
Ok
She can do it
- Ok, go on
- Ok
"Meow Meow Meow Meow"
"Bonnie Hug"
"You are the one I rely on"
"Kitty bomb Bomb Bomb"
Hold on
Bonnie wants to change You are the one I rely on
into You are my eternity
Is that all right?
Sure
Bonnie can do whatever you like
What are you doing?
Come on, Bonnie likes it to be more romantic
What's so romantic about eternity?
It has pink bubbles
What pink bubbles?
Eternity is not the theme of this song
Why are you acting like this?
Yeah, why are you acting like this?
It's none of your business anyway
This song is given to Bonnie by Chi
Bonnie can do whatever she likes to it
Chi, look at her
Lady
she wants to change one line of the lyrics
You are making too big a deal out of it
You have no right to tell her what to do
Who said I have no right to speak up?
No, I mean her
I wrote the lyrics
Why don't I have the right?
Eh
Bonnie and Chi said that you can't
then you can't
Who the hell are you?
You really want to change it?
Yes
Bonnie wants to change it
I will change it for you
Sorry about that
- Let me ask you again
- I told you I want to change it
You has-been lyric writer
What did you say? Calling me a has-been?
Hey
Stop it
Chi said stop it
You can hit me if you want
Stop it
You really hit me
Is there anyone home?
Don't cry
It's fine
Here
What's with the veil?
Are you getting married?
Wow, your face
Why are you injured?
Some kitty girl Bonnie
She wanted to change my lyrics to eternity
Eternity sounds so low
Then?
Then I beat her
You're too impulsive
I have straighten it out for you
Chi still appreciates your talent
but you scratched his favorite kitty girl's face
You should apologize to her
I don't want to
My face is screwed too
Look at my face
and my hands
I got hurt as well
You hear me?
I will go apologize
How is the lyrics working?
I am not in the mood
Throwing a fit now?
Come on
I am here, I can work it with you
I don't like eternity
Then throw it away
Change it
Next life
I can accept next life
It feels like an appointment
but eternity is not
if one of the two people is gone
it won't be eternity
Then tell me
If there is a next life
what would you want to be
A human being
Who wouldn't want to be a human being?
You can be a pig
Fine, seriously
If I have a next life, I want to be
a ring
Ring?
Or maybe
Hold on a second
Ok, go
Hi, I am K
If I have a next life
I want to be
a ring
a pair of glasses
a bed
and
a notebook
Why would you want to be these things?
So I can accompany you
You're so gross
Gross, how?
The lyrics can be a bit cheeky
Right?
Isn't it supposed to be eternity?
Why didn't you change it?
I changed it to the next life
is it ok?
Actually
it doesn't sound that bad
Glasses, key, comforter and ring
can be expressed as companionship
Bonnie likes it
The word eternity
if one person is gone
it would not sustain
But the next life
it sounds like
an appointment
if one person is gone first
they could still have a chance to meet
Bonnie thinks it's so romantic
That is exactly what I want to express
You totally get it
Really?
Then Bonnie has the potential
to become a great lyric writer?
I think you are very talented
It should be a piece of cake
Wonderful
Bonnie happy
Meow meow
About the incident last time
I am really sorry
It's fine
Bonnie doesn't mind
Bonnie forgives you
Bonnie knows that
writing is very difficult
But Yuan-Yuan you are doing really well
You can call me Cream
Ok, Cream
You can call Bonnie Hui-Chun Chen
Who?
Hui-Chun Chen
Oh your real name?
Bonnie is Hui-Chun Chen
Hui-Chun Chen is Bonnie
In order to make Bonnie a famous lyric writer
Starting today
Bonnie Hui-Chun Chen will be friends with Cream
Good
Bonnie's friend
is me Chi's friend
Chi and Bonnie's friend
is me A-Pang's friend
Chi and Bonnie and A-Pang's friend
is our friend
"Cat's tears are like pearls"
Ok, this love song will be the first hit
What do you guys think?
What's wrong?
What about Kitty Bomb ?
I think Kitty Bomb is a good first hit
Starting with a fast song will be more impressive
and Kitty is great for singing and dancing
The song is pretty cute
Cream wrote the lyrics?
Hmm
Yeah
Haven't seen her work for a while
But I still think the lyrics are a bit off tone
But Bonnie likes it very much
Bonnie wants to stay ahead in the trend
Meow
You are way too ahead in the trend
I think the song is great
You definitely need a Music Video for it
- It has strong visuals
- Music Video?
If the MV is well-produced
I think the young people would love it
Fine
Then this song will be the title track
What about the second one?
Anyone has any ideas?
- I do
- Huh
Bonnie is my babe
We need MV for every song at all costs
Bonnie is so touched
Bonnie is going to cry
Huh
You're crying
This can be a promotion material
What?
It's the title track
Does it mean that because of you
my song get to be the title track
I told you many times
It is your own skills that did it
Whether Face-to-face Breakup
or this song, OK?
I have nothing to do with it
I think so too
- How dare you hit me
- You hit me first
So? So what if I hit you?
This is embarassing
Did Bonnie
come at a bad time?
- Not at all
Oh
Uh, what do you want?
To celebrate
Cream's song
has just been picked as the title track
Let's go to the karaoke
Bonnie's treat
Sure
Che-Kai
I suggest you quit your job
and rest yourself at home
So my disease
is starting to break out
Your symptoms
are the same as your dad's
A bone marrow transplant is your best hope
Take his blood pressure again
Ok
Tell me
Do you have anything
you want to say to me?
What's going on?
Looking for inspirations for songs again?
Don't avoid my question
Come on
I mean
What am I supposed to say?
Just tell me things that
you would like to say
but you can only say it
when there is no one around you
Why am I so good looking?
Not that
It's like the things
you would confess to a priest in a church
those kind of things
Well, then I am not going to tell you
you are not a priest
Don't avoid my question
I want to hear it
Well, there is one
I like you
I knew that already
Then why are you asking me?
I have another question then
You certainly have a lotto ask
So what?
What is your wish?
To live long and happy
Not this kind of wish
I mean
that
Is there anything you really want to do
but you haven't done it yet
Yes
I wish you
can find a nice guy and get married
I thought you said you like me
You can marry me
I am not a nice guy
What is the definition of a nice guy?
Got a job
Some money
Who is kind and loves his family
and
with good health
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing really
Have your meal, I thought you're hungry
Eh
This is really delicious
You don't want it, I'll have it all
Cream
Do you like K?
Why would you say that all of sudden?
Because Bonnie can tell
there is something going on with you and K
Have you told him that before?
We are not like that
I don't get it
We live together
but we are not together
So roomates but not a couple
How is that possible?
Well, some people still do that
That's what we are doing
I am used to it
How long have you been like this?
Ever since high school
over a decade I think
10 years?
So what are you doing in those 10 years?
What can we do at home?
Doing laundries, cooking, having dinners
No sex?
We...
How many times?
5 times
Only 5 times in 10 years?
No
0.5
What does that mean?
It means
only
kisses and hugs
but not that
What?
We are not in a relationship
So
You don't like him?
It's not that I don't like him
but we are not in a relationship
I don't want it to be too complicated
Cream, you want to keep living like this?
Don't you want to tell him how you feels?
Actually
He told me to marry someone nice
Is he sick?
I am telling you
Men are so bitchy
You should
go find someone and be with him
If he finds out about it
he will try to win you back
Trust me
Behind you
Go forward
Gordon is about to puke
Who is that guy?
The vampire?
That's one of my high school classmates
He is a dentist
Lisa, I'll go grab a drink
Sure
Are you done with that?
You don't have a glass?
Hmm
Can I borrow it?
Thanks
This doesn't count as a kiss right?
Does it?
Huh
Nevermind
Just a kiss
Thanks
Gordon hit it
"Yu-Hsien Yang"
You have great dental health
Nothing serious
Doctor Yang
We have seen each other 2 days in a row
We kissed in the first time
and the second time
I showed you inside my mouth for cavity
What are we doing for the thrid time?
I want to know you more
Do you want to do that?
Eh
I found a nice guy
Huh
What did you say?
I said, I found a nice guy
He is a dentist
Lisa's high school classmate
That's great
I've been waiting for the transplant for 7 years
How much time do I have now?
You need to come back regularly
If the status is stable
you can still live on with your life
Uncle Te
Stop trying to comfort me
My disease
is in accelerated phase now right?
How long do I have left?
Probably
no more than a year
Chi
I want you to investigate someone for me
Investigate
That is my specialty
But K
I want you to do me a favor too
This is a token of my gratitude
Bonnie's promotion is counting on you
Dental implant for Mr. Chen at 16:30
34, 35
Turn on the CT for me
and get the other equipments ready
Ok
Thanks
This is for you
Thank you
I wrote it
You are a lyric writer
Hmm
That's impressive
What are you doing after work?
Nothing
Buy me a drink
I got you a CD
Come on
You have nothing to do, right?
Can we have a drink?
Can I ask you something?
Guys don't like to tell the truth, right?
Like when you clearly love someone
but would just say you like her a bit
How hard is it to tell the truth?
You have no romance before, right?
I am engaged
Can I borrow it?
Only two things would happen in a romance
one would be like this
falling deep in love
the other one
is dredging up the sunken love
You said you want to know me more
Hmm
Why me?
If love can be explained
no one in the world would suffer from it
One more shot
Yu-Hsien Yang
His family does business for a living
He graduated top in the class of a dental school
Now runs a clinic with his friend
No criminal records
No vices
No special diseases
with perfect health
He has a fiancee called Cindy
Simply put, a winner in life
So the one next to him
that is his fiancee
Hmm
She is a professional photographer
often works with celebrities
Then the promotion photos of Bonnie
we should get her to do it
Yes, I will arrange that right away
It's so cold
You went drinking?
Hmm
With him?
What do you like about him?
I have no idea
No idea
Stop talking, go to sleep
Right
Left
- So the hands should be like this?
- K
Cindy is quite a gal
An honest man like Yu-Hsien Yang
would have no idea that his fiancee
is such a popular figure out there
Give us some more time
I can prove it with videos
No need
This is enough
Ok
k
Why is loving someone
so freaking hard?
Chi
What do you mean?
Hey hey hey
Watch your hands, you want trouble?
Chi
He is teaching Bonnie how to dance
What are you doing?
Just give your instructions
No need to grope her ass
I can dance too, maybe I should do it
How can you teach Bonnie?
You are not professional
Stay out of this
What do you mean professional?
I am good at cutting people up
- He is great
- Should I cut him up now?
He sucks, I can hire someone better
Bonnie don't care, I want Michael
I don't care
Chi, K passed out
Where's Che-Kai Chang?
Why did you pass out suddenly?
I don't know
The doctor told me that
I have Congenital anemia
Congenital anemia
Hmm
The reason he passed out is
that he was too exhausted
and lacking a bit of calcium
Usually, this kind of anemia
would not affect your daily life
Miss
you don't have to worry
I'm fine
Really, it's fine
Lacking calcium
That's weird, I eat the same with you everyday
Why am I not lacking calcium?
Because you eat more than I do
Eh
You are the gobbling monster
Anyway, stop working overtime from now on
And take your calcium everyday
It'll be fine
Fine
Help me store this to the archive
Ok
Doc
Your mail
Oh
What's up?
Take a look at this
Shit
Premarital investigation?
I didn't do the investigation
someone sent it to me
We have been together for 6 years
I funded you to become a photographer
I want to give you a home
And this is how you repay me?
Yu-Hsien
You are the one that wants to get married
We have been through this a longtime ago
Love is never my first priority
Even if it's not your first priority
doesn't mean you can take it for granted
I don't want to explain everything to you
As long as I have a clear conscience
in the relationships that I want to cherish
You're saying that to avoid any consequences
I need creative works
So being with me is for your creation
That is a very mean thing to say
So the things you did isn't mean?
Does anyone that can fund you
is your love interest?
What is that supposed to mean?
Then what are your actions mean?
I won't deny what I did
If you just want my apology
I can tell you I am sorry
Who the fuck do you think you are?
You have no right to investigate me
I can find the surveillance camera
even without an address
Hey
What are you doing?
That's enough
Let go of me
And
My life doesn't concern you
Hey
Give me that
Sorry
I am just hoping
You can break up with Yu-Hsien Yang
Are you nuts?
I don't know what is your purpose
But if you dare come bothering me again
I will get back to you with all I got
Che-Kai Chang
K
I don't know what you are thinking
investigating that crazy woman
And ask her to call off her engagement
What do you want?
Are you insane?
I am insane
I just want Cream to find a nice guy
How old is she?
Can't she find it on her own?
Look at me
Do you think she can?
She can't, really can't
And I am really running out of time
What do you mean out of time?
I am running out of time
If Bonnie's record hits the market
and sells less than 10 thousand copies
Chi is going to fire me
A-Pang
- I would have nothing to worry about then
- A-Pang
You are just going to lose the job
or are you going to die
Look at me K
If I didn't show up in time
you were really going to die
A-Pang
Thank you so much
What a bro
My man
Come on
Fine
Tell you what
I will go to Cindy with you tomorrow
to negotiate with her
What'd you say?
Remember to close the door
Do you want a drink?
No
Hey, don't touch the flower
I have been shooting it for a week
Oh
Eh
What are you guys doing here?
This is to compensate you
I hope you can leave Yu-Hsien Yang
and call off the engagement with him
Did you see my studio?
He funded me to do the photography
I can get where I am now
I have to give him half the credits
If he didn't make a move first
I won't leave him
You understand?
I still want to ask you
I have less than a year to live
I am dying
"Diagnosis: chronic myelogenous leukemia"
First year in high school, my dad died of cancer
Unfortunately
When my mom knew I got leukemia too
She couldn't take it anymore
She gave me some money
The savings
and left me
should support you to adulthood
Take good care of yourself
Don't leave me
Mom
In my loneliest moment
Cream appeared in my life
and she became my family
and the one I love the dearest
One Two
Here
Birthday gift
You like rainy days, right?
A black cloud for you
Thanks, happy birthday to you too
But today is not my birthday
How many birthdays do you want?
From now on this day will be your birthday
but my leukemia has entered the accelerated phase
I can't tell Cream...
...what happened to me
She might not do what my mom did
just leave me because of pain and fear
but I don't know what she would do
and a blow like this
I don't want her to take it
I am really sorry
my love one falls for your fiance
I am begging you
k
Sorry
I am probably pushing it too hard
This is my business card
If you change your mind
Please contact me right away
I can agree to your deal
only under one condition
I promise you
I am going to present an exhibition
the theme is about Death and Deadline
Since you said you are going to die
then you should be my model
let me take your photos
as my work for the exhibition
I will go break up with him
You're being ridiculous
Anyway, this is my deal
take it or leave it
Let's go K
Night snack time
Why aren't you eating?
The food is getting cold
Well
It just occurred to me
She never brought me night snack before
Don't think too much about it
Just eat
What do you want to eat tomorrow?
Text me and let me know
I will bring it to you again
"You don't have to speak"
"Just meow with me together"
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug"
- "Next life again"
- Bonnie did great
"Bonnie Bonnie"
- Meow meow hug hug
- Shoot the smoke, Where is the smoke?
"You are here with me"
"Never let me go!"
Dance
"Bonnie hug"
"Spring blossom loves the summer firework"
- You're here
- Hmm
Let me introduce you
This is the dentist I told you about
Yu-Hsien Yang
Hi
Hi, I'm Che-Kai Chang
Welcome
I know, I heard lot about you from Yuan-Yuan
Ok, cut
Director, is it ok?
Great, give me five
Give me five
Chi
How did Bonnie do?
Pretty good?
Very good
Hey Cream
What do you think about Bonnie's dance?
Very good
Oh well, that's for sure
Bonnie is an international star
And you are?
- Oh
- Mei
He is the dentist I told you about
Hi
So you are Yu-Hsien Yang
Yes
Not bad
Meow
- Don't frighten him
- Here, reshoot it
Are you ok? You don't look too good
- I'm fine
- Have a drink after work?
Fine by me
Let's go together
I need to get back to the office
What a bummer
Don't you need to look after the scene?
The scene
Mei can handle it
Sure, I got it here
Just go do your thing
Where is Bonnie?
I am here
I should go now
Bye
Go for it
Ok, everyone standby
Are you coming?
I really have to work
- Nice to meet you
- Music go
Me too
Bye
Chi, I'm leaving
Ready to roll
Action
Ok, start the snow now
"Meow meow meow meow"
"Bonnie hug"
"Next life again"
"Kitty bomb Bomb Bomb"
"Bonnie Bonnie Meow meow hug hug"
"You are here with me"
"Never let me go!"
When did you first meet Yuan-Yuan Sung?
High school freshman year
What was she like in high school?
Cute
Outgoing
Pretty eyes
You have the chance to cherish her now
and be with her
Why don't you want to?
Why don't you tell her the truth?
What kind of truth?
Do you know the pain?
We lost our family when we were 16
I am her only family now
What do you want me to say?
And what then if I said it
To let her suffer once more
Even if I told her
you think she can live with that?
We can all learn to live with it
You think too less of yourself
Yuan-Yuan Sung can be tougher than you think
Perhaps
I am surprised you have male chauvinism
You are just finding her a cash cow
Right
I am finding her a cash cow
So what?
I suck, I am selfish
I am her only family now
I wish her to be well
Ok?
I can leave Yang like you asked
but you need to promise me one more thing
What is that?
I get all your belongings after you died
No way
All my belongings go to Cream
You see the paradox here?
You want her to forget you
Then you should leave her nothing
Sorry
Let's break up
All these days we been together
I know you don't love me that much
Maybe it's like what you said
Love is not that important to you
But I just can't let it go
But you do now
I think it's time for me to wake up
It's about those photos I guess
We are not together for love anymore
It's just a habit now
So you're saying
The 6 years we had is not about love
Anyway, since you want to break up
I am here to break up with you too
I met a girl recently
but that has nothing to do with us
Hope you will be happy
I broke up with her
Then I have something
I want to tell you
When I was a freshman in high school
I was in the middle of a class
the teacher rushed in suddenly
and spoke to me with a weird look
You should go to the hospital now
I asked him why
He said it's because
your parents and your sister
had a car crash in a tunnel
and were all dead
Afterwards
I started living with K
K
K is Che-Kai Chang
I thought his name is too tacky
so I called him K
He is really a weird guy
When we're at home
he's like a mother
when he's at work, he's like a father
when he comforts me he's like a brother
sometimes
he's like a lover
but when the important moment comes
he acts like a fool
Why are you so honest to me?
Because you didn't lie to me
so I don't want to lie to you
and
am
afraid you would mind
You mean K
Hmm
Not at all
Good then
A gift for Christmas
Thanks
Why do people get married?
Married?
Hmm
So when you're old
or you need someone to take care of you
he can accompany you no reason asked
Then I don't want to get married
What?
You have been with me since 16
You're going to leave me when I get old?
You idiot
That's different
Marriage is marriage
It needs a ceremony
to become a marriage
Is it?
Yes
Nevermind
I don't want to think about it
I am so hungry
Is there anything to eat?
I don't want to eat this
This is really good
It really is
No
I'll go make some noodles
Not for you
"I don't envy the sun"
"it can't illuminate your past"
"there are certain darkness"
"in both of us"
Be merrier
You are making it too sad
It's a sad song already
"I am too jealous of the time"
That's too cheerful
"it can leave in poise"
"If there is no need to speak up"
Do it right
"then there is no need to hide"
I think you are singing it
a bit careless
I am singing it very seriously
What if Bonnie sings it like you do
and the new song fails
Wait
Dear lyric writer
You should know that I did this
only because you asked me to
I know
Thanks
Thank you
Taking care of Yuan-Yuan so much
That should be my line
Thank you for being there with her for so long
You took good care of her
Then you probably know
that we live together
But make no mistake
we really are just friends
Yuan-Yuan told me about it
You two are great friends
sort of like a family in a sense
So she asks you to help pick the wedding dress
sounds pretty reasonable to me
About the wedding dress, I...
This is what Yuan-Yuan wants
I want to do as she asks
And this would also be the last
important thing you did for Yuan-Yuan
You get what I am talking about right?
What do you think?
Is it pretty?
It's beyond pretty
Do the groom like to try on the suit?
I am not the groom
It's ok, give it a try
I want to see it
Go
Hurry up
- Why would I try it on?
- I want to see it
Very handsome
Come on
It's looks great
How is it?
Let me take a photo for you
Sure
Ok, look over here
One two three, cheese
Wait me here
I will go put on another dress
Thanks
I have picked the wedding dress
I'll send you the photo
Hey listen
I think my phone is running out of battery
Later I will
Borrow me
Hello, my phone ran out of battery
Hmm
Right
Ok, I will charge it later
Hmm
Get back to work
I will call you later
Bye
Where have you been yesterday?
You left me there by myself
I felt so awkward
Where did you go?
Nowhere
What do you mean nowhere?
Hello?
Hello, Che-Kai Chang, are you out?
What are you doing?
Why did you answer my phone?
No, I thought it was
Who do you think you are?
This is ridiculous
The dinner is ready
Where are you going?
I am going out
You're dating that girl on the phone?
It's none of your business
So do you want to have the dinner or not?
No
You will never have it once I get married
What are you worrying about?
She only heard my voice
She can't possibly know who I am
She knows you are Yu-Hsien Yang's ex girlfriend
I don't want to take that risk
They why do you ask me to call you
and pretend dating with you
Pretty scheming of you
I have to let her give up on me
Floriography
Everlasting love
Solitarily powerful
In the next three years
you can help me give her cactus
This is the last step
that you are hoping for
One for each year
after three years
she won't notice I am gone
Doing this
you sure it will make her happier?
She will be happy
if not right now
but in the end she will be
You are dying
can't you live it more straightforward
Cry when you want to
Laugh when you want to
Get angry when you want to
And eat when you're hungry
And if you are getting scared
just call for help
Something needs to be said before it's too late
You know?
Or do you want to be gone without a trace?
"Sorry"
"Have you ate?"
Thanks
"I don't want to talk to you today"
"Sorry for all what I've done"
"I am sorry too"
"For what?"
"For all what I've done"
"I love you"
"Hope you will be happy"
Thanks
Tell me
Why do people get married?
So when you are old
or when you need to be taken care of
he can accompany you no reason asked
I thought you said you like me
You can marry me
I am not a nice guy
Doing this
will she really be happier?
She will be happy
if not right now
but in the end she will be
We lost our family since we're 16
I am her only family
I hope she will be well
Or do you want things to be like this
Leaving no trace
and just gone from the world
You think I want to die
You think I want to die like this
Who wouldn't want a wonderful life?
You think it is possible for me
You think I still have time
I wish she will be marrying me
Not him
I wish we can grow old together
taking care of each other
but it's just an illusion
a sad dream
I don't want to dream anymore
I didn't know K had such a story
Too bad he's gone
This is for you, A-Lin
Thanks
The last album they collaborated
Keep this as a remembrance of them
Oh right
Let's do the recording tomorrow
Seriously?
Yes
Then I will book the studio
But
I want to record
A Kind of Sorrow
I am home, Yuan-Yuan
Yuan-Yuan
Yu-Hsien
I am sorry
I am really sorry
The love between mortals
can't be reached by hands
be explained by words
be seen by eyes
My love
started from meeting him
and has been in my life
and will never part
I thought I don't have to suffer the loss again
but it didn't occur to me
from that day on
K will be leaving me
calling me a has-been lyric writer
you are the out-of-tune singer
Meow Meow Meow
Pig
Kitty's target audience must all be guys
Men
What do men like?
What is more important for them?
Excuse me
May I help you?
What does this mediccation treat?
Where did this come from?
From my home
Glivec treats cancer or leukemia patients
And that is a strong dose of painkiller
Using these two meds together
means he is in pretty bad condition
Bye
- Bye Yuan-Yuan
- Take care of the house
We are leaving sis
- Bye Yuan-Yuan
No
Don't leave me
You can't be here
You can't leave me
Don't you leave me
Stop
Is anyone home?
I feel sorry for K to have endured the pain
dealing it all quietly
I thank him very much
Thinking about me even when he's sick
maybe I can't grow old with K in this life
But I look forward to the next life
that we can meet again then
That day
The thing I was worried about has happened
You really can't tell her
really can't tell her
But you need someone to look after you
am fine
I can take care of myself
How long you think you can keep it from her?
I don't know for how long
But if she finds out
everything is over
Before think about other people
you should think about yourself first
I am not important
But she's different
She is all alone
She needs someone to be there for her
You are all alone too
aren't you?
The first time I met K
is a month after my family died
Death has taken my family
But K was abandoned by his family
That day
he looked pretty sad
and needed a hug more than I do
From that day on
I decided to call him K
As for me, I am Cream
After all, two lonely people
should have a name feeling less lonely
You said that K is about to die
You think
I should tell him I already knew
If he didn't want you to know
he probably has his reasons
Would expose him now
make any difference?
I only want K to be happy
No matter what happened
I will do anything to fulfill his wish
Do you have any wishes?
I hope you
find a nice guy and get married
What is the definition of a nice guy?
Got a job
some money
I wanted so bad that his wish is to be with me
and with good health
but for K who is about to leave me
even though I don't want to
I will do everything for him
Who is that guy?
The vampire?
He is my high school classmate
He is a dentist
This doesn't count as a kiss, right?
Does it?
I want to know you more
I am engaged
Therefore,
sorry, Yu-Hsien
I used you
If I am with you
I think K would be relieved
Sorry
I used your kindness for me
Your consideration for me
I know even if I am thinking of someone else
you will still take me in
Waiting quietly for the time
to move me
Why do people get married?
Because when you are old
or need to be taken care of
he can accompany you with no reason asked
Then I won't get married
Marriage needs a ceremony
to be called a marriage
When can we get married?
If you really love me
we can do it anytime
Please forgive me
My love one is about to die
I really can't think it all through
Hi, I am K
If I have a next life, I want to be
a ring
a pair of glasses
I shouldn't detest eternity
a bed
I want to stay beside K forever
One two Three, cheese
Wait me here
I will go put on another dress
Thanks
I will call you back
Ok
Sorry
It's all right
I am suffering from the great pain
I know K is too
I made a promise to myself
If he turned around
I would confess everything to him
I would give him a big hug
"I love you"
I wanted to say I love him out loud
"Hope you will be happy"
but I knew I would burst into tears once I said it
I couldn't hold on anymore
Thanks
Can you do the wedding rehearsal with me?
Yuan-Yuan Sung
for richer or for poorer
in sickness and in health
Will you take
the man in front of you
to be your husband?
I do
K and I became really husband and wife
the happiest moment in my dream is fulfilled
I thought we can go on together forever
But
in the real world
K gives my hand to another man
The feelings I have for K
from 16 years old until now
has gone so deep
it can never be dredged up again
Yu-Hisen
Thank you for everything you did
Thank you for loving me
I have found K
I want to go see him
Hi
Here you are
I have been looking all over for you
Silly
You know you're having a fever
It's fine
It will be fine soon
I am warning you
No more instant noodles from now on
no more walking in the rain
no more popsicles
no more extra shifts
you hear me?
K
I will look after you
We are going to play baseball together
You need to sing the terrible demo for me
Don't leave me alone in my birthday
We had a deal when we were 16
We would spend the birthdays together
I am right here
It will be fine
It's ok
I am here with you
Feeling better now?
We're home
It'll be fine here
Sorry Cream
I arranged your romance
without your approval
Do you like it?
Let's take another picture
You asked me once before
Let's take the photo
about my wish
My biggest wish
Here
is to be with you
together forever
K
and Cream
We are a family
We always have been
Take the photo now
Long time no see
Hi
Why are you here so early?
I thought you might get busy later
Let me show you around
Sure
Hi,I am K
If I have a next life, I want to be
a ring
a pair of glasses
a bed
I still can't understand now
An idiot like Che-Kai Chang
really existed in the world
If love can be explained
no one in the world will suffer from it
I underestimated love
I told Che-Kai Chang before
Yuan-Yuan Sung
She could be tougher than you think
She will do fine even if you're gone
But I was wrong
The love in their point of views
is based on each other's happiness
"Then there is no need to hide"
"a kind of sorrow"
"is your name staying in my past"
"breathing with me, shaping my smile"
"Can't seem to forget"
k
Do you know?
After my family left
I thought happiness left with them
until I met you
I realized that two lonely souls
as long as they can stay with each other
can have the right to be happy
We are destined to meet each other
No one can replace that
Do you know?
What I want
is not someone that brings me
hot coffee in the cold winter
but someone who eats popsicles with me in the rain
so much so that our teeth hurt
What I want
is not a guardian
but someone who would do the adventures with me
I don't want anyone else
I want you
K
Thank you for everything you did
As long as I get to stay with you
it would be the happiest thing for me
"and stay in my past"
Sorry
"Can't seem to be forgotten"
I love you
"a kind of sorrow"
"Che-Kai Yuan-Yuan's grave"
"Is your determination to let love become"
"the light that shines on me"
"giving me warmth"
"but not permitting me"
I keep wondering
why call me K?
Because I am Cream
That's it?
Because
we have no family since we were kids
and we live together
K
and Cream
all have the same consonant K
Don't you think it sounds
like a real family?
"A kind of sorrow"
"Don't want to be apart"
"and miss you so back to back we look around"
"You are everything"
"you are an eternal figure in a photo"
"to be remembered"
"2002-2015
What we share every day defines Eternity"