1
00:00:24,190 --> 00:00:26,522
<i>Core Contents Media Presents</i>

2
00:00:30,497 --> 00:00:32,897
<i>In association with Showbox</i>

3
00:00:33,633 --> 00:00:36,193
<i>A Core Contents Media Production</i>

4
00:00:36,703 --> 00:00:39,194
<i>Co-produced by</i>
<i>Goldenthumb & Poibos</i>

5
00:00:44,644 --> 00:00:46,737
Hey, Jung-sik?

6
00:00:47,180 --> 00:00:47,981
How is it?

7
00:00:47,981 --> 00:00:49,516
What do you think.

8
00:00:49,516 --> 00:00:51,851
I need it for the drama next week

9
00:00:51,851 --> 00:00:53,286
so tell him it's great! Okay?

10
00:00:53,286 --> 00:00:55,121
Like Seung-chul ever listens to me.

11
00:00:55,121 --> 00:00:58,424
Then make him. He's gotta do this song.

12
00:00:58,424 --> 00:01:01,723
But the lyrics are weak, man.

13
00:01:01,861 --> 00:01:04,330
What the suits say goes. That's show biz.

14
00:01:04,330 --> 00:01:06,321
Whatever, man!

15
00:01:06,499 --> 00:01:08,201
- Hold up!
- What is it?

16
00:01:08,201 --> 00:01:09,335
You like this song?

17
00:01:09,335 --> 00:01:10,570
Of course! Why?

18
00:01:10,570 --> 00:01:14,174
Singing about a girl to
come back to me at my age?

19
00:01:14,174 --> 00:01:16,876
My heart this and tears that...

20
00:01:16,876 --> 00:01:17,877
Isn't it childish?

21
00:01:17,877 --> 00:01:21,147
No! It's perfect! Don't you think?

22
00:01:21,147 --> 00:01:21,848
It's great.

23
00:01:21,848 --> 00:01:24,083
Make your fans really feel the song, man!

24
00:01:24,083 --> 00:01:26,085
But I don't feel anything!

25
00:01:26,085 --> 00:01:29,789
You can do it, man. Feel me?

26
00:01:29,789 --> 00:01:30,790
- It's great!
- No.

27
00:01:30,790 --> 00:01:32,781
It's not working for me.

28
00:01:35,361 --> 00:01:37,197
Hey, Seung-chul! Come on!

29
00:01:37,197 --> 00:01:39,529
Get him!

30
00:01:39,632 --> 00:01:40,929
Seung-chul!

31
00:01:41,201 --> 00:01:42,600
Yes, director.

32
00:01:42,969 --> 00:01:44,402
I see.

33
00:01:45,672 --> 00:01:47,731
Next Tuesday?

34
00:01:48,875 --> 00:01:50,577
The song's a killer.

35
00:01:51,211 --> 00:01:54,441
Nothing but the best from Lee Seung-chul.

36
00:01:54,847 --> 00:01:56,382
Of course.

37
00:01:57,317 --> 00:02:00,411
No problems whatsoever.

38
00:02:01,788 --> 00:02:04,357
Yes, sir. Take care.

39
00:02:07,093 --> 00:02:11,588
See? He's asking for
the song. Do it for me?

40
00:02:11,898 --> 00:02:15,268
You always do this to me.

41
00:02:15,268 --> 00:02:16,970
Please?

42
00:02:16,970 --> 00:02:22,840
So get me a good song
and I'll sing it! Damn!

43
00:02:22,942 --> 00:02:24,911
What about 'Hee-ya'?

44
00:02:24,911 --> 00:02:26,546
'Hee-ya, please look at me.'

45
00:02:26,546 --> 00:02:28,181
Give me a break.

46
00:02:28,181 --> 00:02:30,817
That was a hit only because you sang it.

47
00:02:30,817 --> 00:02:33,353
Wanna hear this song I got?

48
00:02:33,353 --> 00:02:34,454
What is it?

49
00:02:34,454 --> 00:02:36,856
It's off from a flopped album.

50
00:02:36,856 --> 00:02:39,058
Forget it, kid!

51
00:02:39,058 --> 00:02:41,361
Hey, let's hear it.

52
00:02:41,361 --> 00:02:43,625
Really? Turn it on.

53
00:02:45,698 --> 00:02:51,534
<i>To give you everything</i>
<i>and all my love...</i>

54
00:02:51,638 --> 00:02:54,440
Who wrote this? The lyrics are great.

55
00:02:54,440 --> 00:02:58,137
Really? Then let's ask
them to write our lyrics.

56
00:02:58,378 --> 00:02:59,746
Who wrote this?

57
00:02:59,746 --> 00:03:03,216
Not sure. I got this off someone.

58
00:03:03,216 --> 00:03:04,017
Who?

59
00:03:04,017 --> 00:03:06,552
Min-chul. He used to
work for Kim Gap-sik.

60
00:03:06,552 --> 00:03:08,782
Gap-sik? I know him well.

61
00:03:09,889 --> 00:03:13,825
Hey, didn't he leave the biz?

62
00:03:13,960 --> 00:03:15,094
Who does your friend work for now?

63
00:03:15,094 --> 00:03:17,363
He left the biz, too.

64
00:03:17,363 --> 00:03:18,398
What does he do?

65
00:03:18,398 --> 00:03:20,593
He runs a cafe in Chung-pyung.

66
00:03:21,401 --> 00:03:23,494
Wanna go over, Seung-chul?

67
00:03:23,636 --> 00:03:25,968
- Know where it is?
- Yes.

68
00:03:26,072 --> 00:03:26,773
Lead the way.

69
00:03:26,773 --> 00:03:29,333
<i>Directed by Won Tae-Yeon</i>

70
00:03:33,112 --> 00:03:34,204
Got the album?

71
00:03:34,314 --> 00:03:35,542
Ah, here.

72
00:03:38,184 --> 00:03:39,617
What's the title?

73
00:03:39,752 --> 00:03:41,515
It's the second track.

74
00:03:42,322 --> 00:03:44,085
Second track?

75
00:03:47,427 --> 00:03:51,631
'No one else like Thee' by Cream?

76
00:03:51,631 --> 00:03:53,030
What's her real name?

77
00:03:53,132 --> 00:03:57,967
I think it was Eun Won.
Yeah, that's it.

78
00:03:58,204 --> 00:03:59,967
Got her number?

79
00:04:00,606 --> 00:04:01,607
She's gone.

80
00:04:01,607 --> 00:04:03,910
Gone? To where?

81
00:04:03,910 --> 00:04:06,579
Right after Kang Chul-kyu left...

82
00:04:06,579 --> 00:04:10,743
Kang knows her well?

83
00:04:11,651 --> 00:04:15,712
Of course. He was totally in love with her.

84
00:04:16,589 --> 00:04:19,217
Do you have Kang's number?

85
00:04:19,992 --> 00:04:21,857
- He died.
- He's dead?

86
00:04:21,928 --> 00:04:23,229
When?

87
00:04:23,229 --> 00:04:26,721
About a month after he married Eun Won off.

88
00:04:27,100 --> 00:04:29,864
Mr. Kang!

89
00:04:30,370 --> 00:04:33,430
What was the name of his show?

90
00:04:33,539 --> 00:04:35,508
'Ugly Ducklings in Love'.

91
00:04:35,508 --> 00:04:37,844
Yeah, that's it!

92
00:04:37,844 --> 00:04:41,047
He married off the woman he loved?

93
00:04:41,047 --> 00:04:43,914
- What does that mean?
- Well...

94
00:04:44,851 --> 00:04:48,150
Tell us what happened.

95
00:04:48,788 --> 00:04:51,518
It's a long story.

96
00:05:41,941 --> 00:05:43,238
Hi, Chul-kyu!

97
00:05:56,889 --> 00:05:59,323
<i>Kang said he saw stars</i>

98
00:05:59,425 --> 00:06:00,693
<i>when he first met Cream.</i>

99
00:06:00,693 --> 00:06:02,684
Why you little punk!

100
00:06:08,668 --> 00:06:11,136
<i>Like he'd been slapped</i>
<i>on the back of his head.</i>

101
00:06:11,370 --> 00:06:14,362
<i>He said it was love at first sight.</i>

102
00:06:15,274 --> 00:06:17,208
<i>Without even talking to her.</i>

103
00:06:18,311 --> 00:06:19,903
<i>I asked,</i>

104
00:06:20,079 --> 00:06:22,877
<i>'Shouldn't you at least</i>
<i>say a few words, first?'</i>

105
00:06:23,049 --> 00:06:24,573
<i>Then he said...</i>

106
00:06:25,451 --> 00:06:29,478
<i>"If you need words,</i>
<i>then how can mutes love?"</i>

107
00:06:43,369 --> 00:06:46,806
How did you know my name?

108
00:06:46,806 --> 00:06:51,038
Isn't it a waste living
in this big place alone?

109
00:06:53,613 --> 00:06:55,843
Want me to live with you?

110
00:07:12,365 --> 00:07:16,502
Think of a name for me,
and I'll make one for you.

111
00:07:16,502 --> 00:07:18,595
We can't change our names.

112
00:07:19,472 --> 00:07:20,496
Why not?

113
00:07:20,573 --> 00:07:23,974
<i>Her name is Cream</i>
<i>and my name is K.</i>

114
00:07:24,143 --> 00:07:26,879
<i>She was cold like ice cream,</i>

115
00:07:26,879 --> 00:07:29,682
<i>- but also sweet like ice cream.</i>
- The curtains won't do.

116
00:07:29,682 --> 00:07:30,883
We're changing everything.

117
00:07:30,883 --> 00:07:33,477
<i>And she was soft like ice cream.</i>

118
00:07:34,520 --> 00:07:39,787
<i>And I'm not A, B, C,</i>
<i>D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K...</i>

119
00:07:40,159 --> 00:07:41,854
<i>But just 'K'.</i>

120
00:07:55,675 --> 00:07:57,802
<i>We had a lot in common.</i>

121
00:07:58,210 --> 00:08:02,237
<i>We were the same age.</i>
<i>We both liked noodles.</i>

122
00:08:04,216 --> 00:08:06,912
<i>We loved listening to</i>
<i>music on rainy days.</i>

123
00:08:08,621 --> 00:08:10,816
<i>We loved coffee.</i>

124
00:08:13,793 --> 00:08:15,590
<i>We hated school.</i>

125
00:08:20,099 --> 00:08:21,896
<i>She liked me.</i>

126
00:08:23,002 --> 00:08:24,902
<i>And I liked her.</i>

127
00:08:27,073 --> 00:08:28,973
<i>And we were both orphans.</i>

128
00:08:32,378 --> 00:08:34,413
<i>Prison and love...</i>

129
00:08:34,413 --> 00:08:37,280
<i>Once you're stuck, you can't get out.</i>

130
00:08:41,887 --> 00:08:45,448
<i>I fell in love with Cream.</i>

131
00:08:48,427 --> 00:08:51,260
<i>Even the very air she breathed.</i>

132
00:08:57,837 --> 00:09:00,670
<i>Romeo must've been so worried...</i>

133
00:09:00,906 --> 00:09:05,707
<i>Loving Juliet, but</i>
<i>afraid he might lose her.</i>

134
00:09:10,483 --> 00:09:13,884
<i>Why did he drink the poison?</i>

135
00:09:14,320 --> 00:09:18,450
<i>Perhaps he knew.</i>

136
00:09:19,692 --> 00:09:22,261
<i>To love someone</i>

137
00:09:22,261 --> 00:09:24,491
<i>- is to give her everything.</i>
- I'll visit often.

138
00:09:27,333 --> 00:09:34,000
<i>I received so much from her</i>
<i>like the catcher who gets the ball.</i>

139
00:09:35,508 --> 00:09:38,377
<i>Love was like dry ice.</i>
<i>Sometimes cold, sometimes hot.</i>

140
00:09:38,377 --> 00:09:39,435
Wait!

141
00:09:39,578 --> 00:09:41,375
<i>Cream was so loveable.</i>

142
00:09:42,948 --> 00:09:49,148
<i>But I couldn't tell her</i>
<i>that I loved her.</i>

143
00:09:50,556 --> 00:09:57,792
<i>Because I had cancer cells in me</i>
<i>ready to strike at any time.</i>

144
00:10:00,566 --> 00:10:06,300
MORE THAN BLUE

145
00:10:43,709 --> 00:10:45,277
Thank you, Mr. Kim.

146
00:10:45,277 --> 00:10:48,748
It's the least I can do.

147
00:10:48,748 --> 00:10:52,118
Writers need to eat well
to do all that thinking.

148
00:10:52,118 --> 00:10:57,656
Have some soup with the
Kimbap and chew carefully.

149
00:10:57,656 --> 00:10:59,759
Is this your new singer?

150
00:10:59,759 --> 00:11:06,187
Greet them, girl. They're
the best writers in SBC.

151
00:11:06,932 --> 00:11:11,504
Hello, I'm Cat Girl.
I promise to sing my heart out.

152
00:11:11,504 --> 00:11:13,699
Damn right you should.

153
00:11:14,206 --> 00:11:16,041
Great outfit.

154
00:11:16,041 --> 00:11:19,135
It's a new concept. She's a cat.

155
00:11:20,079 --> 00:11:21,447
It's Cat Girl.

156
00:11:21,447 --> 00:11:25,918
This girl got brains.

157
00:11:25,918 --> 00:11:29,021
She's a student at Seoul University.

158
00:11:29,021 --> 00:11:30,682
Really?

159
00:11:31,390 --> 00:11:34,026
It's Seoul University of Arts.

160
00:11:34,026 --> 00:11:36,051
Who's side are you on?

161
00:11:36,195 --> 00:11:38,831
You could get in trouble for
lying about schools these days.

162
00:11:38,831 --> 00:11:43,335
If you're so holy, go be a cop instead.

163
00:11:43,335 --> 00:11:44,393
Sorry.

164
00:11:47,706 --> 00:11:49,071
Mr. Kang!

165
00:11:49,175 --> 00:11:50,075
How are you?

166
00:11:50,075 --> 00:11:54,273
Here's Seung-chul's new album. It's deep.

167
00:11:54,747 --> 00:11:57,883
- It's a sure hit.
- I'm sure it's great.

168
00:11:57,883 --> 00:11:58,951
- Say hi.
- Hello.

169
00:11:58,951 --> 00:12:00,213
Call me K.

170
00:12:00,820 --> 00:12:02,588
Let's go for drinks some time.

171
00:12:02,588 --> 00:12:04,317
- Sounds great.
- Bye.

172
00:12:05,858 --> 00:12:08,194
Seoul University of Arts...
Same difference.

173
00:12:08,194 --> 00:12:09,495
That's right.

174
00:12:09,495 --> 00:12:10,928
Did you eat, sir?

175
00:12:11,564 --> 00:12:12,932
Mr. Kang!

176
00:12:12,932 --> 00:12:15,234
- How've you been?
- I waited so long for you.

177
00:12:15,234 --> 00:12:18,904
She's Cats. Damn, I keep forgetting.

178
00:12:18,904 --> 00:12:20,997
It's Cat Girl, sir.

179
00:12:21,173 --> 00:12:24,904
Go on and introduce yourself.

180
00:12:25,044 --> 00:12:29,815
I'm Cat Girl. I promise
to sing my heart out.

181
00:12:29,815 --> 00:12:30,983
Thank you.

182
00:12:30,983 --> 00:12:33,645
Of course you should.

183
00:12:33,919 --> 00:12:36,889
Let's go some place
quiet to talk, Mr. Kang.

184
00:12:36,889 --> 00:12:39,221
See you folks later.

185
00:12:40,726 --> 00:12:44,029
- Come on, what are pals for.
- I can't.

186
00:12:44,029 --> 00:12:47,965
It's just a show of my appreciation.

187
00:12:48,067 --> 00:12:49,768
The album's finished?

188
00:12:49,768 --> 00:12:53,472
I put together all the
best songwriters around.

189
00:12:53,472 --> 00:12:56,703
You know me, I get what I want.

190
00:12:57,042 --> 00:12:58,377
How is she?

191
00:12:58,377 --> 00:13:01,881
Oh, her? Not bad.

192
00:13:01,881 --> 00:13:05,885
But she has trouble getting
along with the others.

193
00:13:05,885 --> 00:13:08,220
Still she's got talent. Be nice.

194
00:13:08,220 --> 00:13:11,815
Of course. Anything for you.

195
00:13:13,392 --> 00:13:16,061
- But do this for me.
- I can't.

196
00:13:16,061 --> 00:13:18,552
It's not much. Please, take it!

197
00:13:18,964 --> 00:13:25,804
I can't sleep at the thought of you.

198
00:13:25,804 --> 00:13:31,174
My dear love.

199
00:13:33,212 --> 00:13:38,684
That part you just sang. Try
not to scream it this time.

200
00:13:38,684 --> 00:13:40,675
You'll scare them off.

201
00:13:41,553 --> 00:13:44,317
How, sir?

202
00:13:45,591 --> 00:13:51,029
How would you feel if someone
screamed they loved you?

203
00:13:51,330 --> 00:13:56,700
You know, softly and
tenderly? You're good at that.

204
00:13:56,802 --> 00:14:01,398
What? Not that. Stop making me do it.

205
00:14:01,540 --> 00:14:06,136
- That's not what I meant!
- Roll it!

206
00:14:15,154 --> 00:14:17,520
What's she so good at?

207
00:14:17,957 --> 00:14:21,518
Drop it will you, man?

208
00:14:21,660 --> 00:14:24,959
Come on. Just between us?

209
00:14:28,133 --> 00:14:33,400
She's my future. That's
all I can tell you, man.

210
00:14:35,708 --> 00:14:39,075
Did you fix the second verse?

211
00:14:39,211 --> 00:14:40,678
What?

212
00:14:41,013 --> 00:14:43,413
The climax on the second verse.

213
00:14:43,582 --> 00:14:45,846
'Always like yesterday'?

214
00:14:46,018 --> 00:14:49,112
It's a little corny, isn't it?

215
00:14:50,356 --> 00:14:54,019
'A world without love?'
How's that?

216
00:14:56,996 --> 00:15:00,022
Like that's not corny?

217
00:15:02,568 --> 00:15:05,867
It's just a suggestion.

218
00:15:05,971 --> 00:15:12,968
Let's not get too excited here.

219
00:15:17,249 --> 00:15:20,616
You two write it, then. I'm out.

220
00:15:21,320 --> 00:15:22,685
What?

221
00:15:27,092 --> 00:15:28,923
So feisty.

222
00:15:52,818 --> 00:15:54,683
Do you have to become a singer?

223
00:15:55,654 --> 00:15:57,178
What?

224
00:16:02,261 --> 00:16:04,593
Got enough medication left?

225
00:16:18,677 --> 00:16:22,272
My damn connection to your family.

226
00:16:26,552 --> 00:16:29,612
First your father, now you.

227
00:16:31,423 --> 00:16:34,517
There are too many illnesses
that can't be cured.

228
00:16:53,479 --> 00:16:54,776
What's wrong?

229
00:16:59,852 --> 00:17:01,149
What is it?

230
00:17:03,889 --> 00:17:05,356
Don't cry.

231
00:17:06,358 --> 00:17:07,882
Stop crying.

232
00:17:09,328 --> 00:17:12,320
The bastards told me to rewrite it.

233
00:17:18,036 --> 00:17:22,029
'If I could live again'.
How's that for the title?

234
00:17:22,841 --> 00:17:25,173
'If I could live again?'

235
00:17:25,944 --> 00:17:31,177
If you could, what would
you like to be reborn as?

236
00:17:32,451 --> 00:17:34,316
Besides a person?

237
00:17:35,354 --> 00:17:37,049
Anything.

238
00:17:39,324 --> 00:17:41,224
Well...

239
00:17:42,861 --> 00:17:45,125
If I could live again...

240
00:17:48,066 --> 00:17:49,368
A ring?

241
00:17:49,368 --> 00:17:50,767
Wait.

242
00:17:58,510 --> 00:18:00,102
Start over.

243
00:18:02,648 --> 00:18:04,843
If I could be born again...

244
00:18:05,584 --> 00:18:07,415
A ring.

245
00:18:08,954 --> 00:18:10,512
A pair of glasses.

246
00:18:11,990 --> 00:18:13,651
A bed.

247
00:18:15,427 --> 00:18:17,190
A diary.

248
00:18:17,396 --> 00:18:20,832
Born again as things like
that? What fun is that?

249
00:18:20,832 --> 00:18:25,394
You can buy me. It'll
always be fun at your side.

250
00:18:27,239 --> 00:18:29,173
So sensible.

251
00:18:30,075 --> 00:18:31,599
Did you eat?

252
00:18:31,877 --> 00:18:33,504
Of course, I did.

253
00:18:34,513 --> 00:18:36,344
Well, I didn't.

254
00:18:38,450 --> 00:18:40,281
Then let's eat.

255
00:18:45,224 --> 00:18:47,692
Is there anything you want to tell me?

256
00:18:48,093 --> 00:18:49,424
Like what?

257
00:18:49,761 --> 00:18:53,298
A deep, dark secret?

258
00:18:53,298 --> 00:18:57,564
Think of it as a confession
at a Catholic church.

259
00:18:58,670 --> 00:19:01,366
I'll be the priest and listen.

260
00:19:02,341 --> 00:19:04,309
A deep, dark secret?

261
00:19:05,644 --> 00:19:08,914
Say anything. I'm ready to listen.

262
00:19:08,914 --> 00:19:10,541
I like you.

263
00:19:15,254 --> 00:19:17,688
I want to ask you something.

264
00:19:18,924 --> 00:19:20,619
Do you have a wish?

265
00:19:20,826 --> 00:19:22,418
A wish?

266
00:19:22,628 --> 00:19:26,325
If you could have anything in the world?

267
00:19:27,199 --> 00:19:29,190
First, hold up your spoon.

268
00:19:33,538 --> 00:19:35,199
Then?

269
00:19:35,741 --> 00:19:37,902
Eat all your food.

270
00:19:46,785 --> 00:19:48,377
Then?

271
00:19:48,587 --> 00:19:50,885
Meet a great guy and get married.

272
00:19:51,590 --> 00:19:53,353
Can't I marry you?

273
00:19:53,458 --> 00:19:55,517
I'm not a great guy.

274
00:19:58,830 --> 00:20:02,701
<i>It wasn't my choice,</i>
<i>but heaven's will,</i>

275
00:20:02,701 --> 00:20:06,071
<i>to fall in love with you.</i>

276
00:20:06,071 --> 00:20:13,500
<i>I was born to love you.</i>
<i>Heaven sent me to love you.</i>

277
00:20:13,812 --> 00:20:15,905
<i>ID: Little Mermaid.</i>

278
00:20:16,048 --> 00:20:20,747
<i>Now, for the requested song.</i>

279
00:20:31,263 --> 00:20:34,858
Your second toe is longer
than the first one like mine.

280
00:20:35,634 --> 00:20:38,432
That means your mom will outlive you.

281
00:20:41,506 --> 00:20:43,167
Who says that?

282
00:20:45,344 --> 00:20:49,405
I think I read it somewhere.

283
00:20:49,881 --> 00:20:51,405
It's a lie.

284
00:20:52,050 --> 00:20:53,278
Why?

285
00:20:53,285 --> 00:20:56,982
Because my Mom and Dad died on the same day.

286
00:21:00,192 --> 00:21:01,716
If you...

287
00:21:01,860 --> 00:21:04,556
If you die before me, I'll kill you!

288
00:21:10,969 --> 00:21:15,429
<i>Here's another requested song.</i>

289
00:21:49,074 --> 00:21:50,837
Are you finished?

290
00:21:53,211 --> 00:21:54,803
Excuse me?

291
00:21:55,147 --> 00:21:56,637
The coffee.

292
00:22:01,720 --> 00:22:03,654
Then can I have the cup?

293
00:22:29,381 --> 00:22:31,315
Which side did you drink from?

294
00:22:32,050 --> 00:22:33,415
Pardon?

295
00:22:41,460 --> 00:22:43,360
This isn't kissing, is it?

296
00:22:57,609 --> 00:23:00,442
- Hey.
- Yeah?

297
00:23:03,448 --> 00:23:07,578
- You know the guest doctor?
- Yeah?

298
00:23:09,054 --> 00:23:11,022
What kind of doctor is he?

299
00:23:12,657 --> 00:23:13,783
Huh?

300
00:23:18,663 --> 00:23:22,463
We need to fill a cavity.
Amalgam is stronger than resin.

301
00:23:28,340 --> 00:23:30,672
We kissed on the first day.

302
00:23:36,882 --> 00:23:39,316
You saw inside me, on the second day.

303
00:23:45,257 --> 00:23:47,282
What should we do on the third day?

304
00:23:53,131 --> 00:23:54,564
What?

305
00:23:54,933 --> 00:23:58,596
We'll decide when the time comes.

306
00:24:07,612 --> 00:24:09,671
I'm in love!

307
00:24:11,116 --> 00:24:15,075
A guest on another show. He's a dentist.

308
00:24:21,226 --> 00:24:23,023
Can you pass me the toothbrush?

309
00:25:31,596 --> 00:25:34,499
<i>You're listening to 'Happy Hour'.</i>

310
00:25:34,499 --> 00:25:37,936
<i>- As you're out driving...</i>
- Did you eat?

311
00:25:37,936 --> 00:25:40,372
Oh, hi.

312
00:25:40,372 --> 00:25:43,000
- Got a show to record, today?
- No.

313
00:25:45,010 --> 00:25:48,241
The guest doctor on your show...

314
00:25:48,446 --> 00:25:52,212
Who? You mean Cha Joo-hwan?

315
00:25:52,817 --> 00:25:54,285
How is he?

316
00:25:54,285 --> 00:25:57,379
He's a great guy. Why?

317
00:25:57,689 --> 00:26:00,725
Just wondering.

318
00:26:00,725 --> 00:26:06,925
His family's rich. He's nice
and he makes a ton of money.

319
00:26:07,098 --> 00:26:09,965
And he's a famous dentist.

320
00:26:10,568 --> 00:26:13,435
You look a little sad today.

321
00:26:13,972 --> 00:26:16,241
Good job, bro.

322
00:26:16,241 --> 00:26:18,009
It was fun.

323
00:26:18,009 --> 00:26:21,746
- Great show.
- Cut it short.

324
00:26:21,746 --> 00:26:24,306
Hey, nice seeing you.

325
00:26:24,382 --> 00:26:26,284
Let's go out for drinks.

326
00:26:26,284 --> 00:26:28,687
Not if it's just a few drinks.

327
00:26:28,687 --> 00:26:32,646
- How much then?
- All night?

328
00:26:32,791 --> 00:26:34,224
All night! Alright!

329
00:26:36,194 --> 00:26:38,162
<i>What's his social</i>
<i>security number?</i>

330
00:26:38,930 --> 00:26:42,400
-730313105...
<i>-730313...</i>

331
00:26:44,803 --> 00:26:47,205
Are you sure you can
get his medical records?

332
00:26:47,205 --> 00:26:49,765
<i>Insurance companies</i>
<i>get everything.</i>

333
00:26:49,874 --> 00:26:52,243
<i>But why do you want</i>
<i>to check out a guy?</i>

334
00:26:52,243 --> 00:26:53,945
I'll tell you later.

335
00:26:53,945 --> 00:26:59,440
<i>Bingo! He's got life</i>
<i>and medical insurance.</i>

336
00:26:59,551 --> 00:27:02,987
<i>No record of family illness</i>
<i>or any operations.</i>

337
00:27:02,987 --> 00:27:06,858
<i>He has an impeccable health record.</i>

338
00:27:06,858 --> 00:27:08,193
Are you sure?

339
00:27:08,193 --> 00:27:10,595
<i>Insurance companies know</i>
<i>how to make money, man.</i>

340
00:27:10,595 --> 00:27:11,362
Kang!

341
00:27:11,362 --> 00:27:13,865
<i>If he has a hospital</i>
<i>record, we'll see it.</i>

342
00:27:13,865 --> 00:27:14,899
Kang!

343
00:27:14,899 --> 00:27:16,764
Thanks. I owe you one.

344
00:27:19,304 --> 00:27:21,005
Got a minute, Mr. Kim?

345
00:27:21,005 --> 00:27:23,872
For you, any time!

346
00:27:29,647 --> 00:27:31,137
It's a gift.

347
00:27:34,452 --> 00:27:37,353
Ah, thank you.

348
00:27:38,223 --> 00:27:40,384
Just a thank you?

349
00:27:42,460 --> 00:27:46,658
First my lips, then my insides...

350
00:27:47,198 --> 00:27:49,826
Now, you're in my head.

351
00:27:50,401 --> 00:27:52,266
Buy me a drink?

352
00:27:58,243 --> 00:27:59,642
A drink?

353
00:28:00,311 --> 00:28:03,576
I don't get it.

354
00:28:03,681 --> 00:28:11,053
Who would've thought I'd use my
former dark roots to help you?

355
00:28:12,157 --> 00:28:16,594
No need to worry. Now about Cats.

356
00:28:17,629 --> 00:28:20,899
Man, I gotta change that name!

357
00:28:20,899 --> 00:28:22,867
It's Cat Girl, sir.

358
00:28:22,867 --> 00:28:28,032
I know! It's up here
but I can't say it right!

359
00:28:29,541 --> 00:28:32,043
Call me whatever you want, hon.

360
00:28:32,043 --> 00:28:34,807
Who cares if it's a cat or a dog?

361
00:28:35,113 --> 00:28:38,947
That's my pretty.

362
00:28:40,218 --> 00:28:42,118
My sweet Cats.

363
00:28:43,121 --> 00:28:46,090
We're changing the name.

364
00:28:47,826 --> 00:28:51,196
- Ah, sir?
- I said, I know!

365
00:28:51,196 --> 00:28:53,391
Not that. The phone.

366
00:28:55,066 --> 00:28:58,832
Sorry, Producer Kang! I checked and...

367
00:29:00,371 --> 00:29:03,738
You kids scram for a sec.

368
00:29:04,742 --> 00:29:07,336
I gotta take this call. Go!

369
00:29:11,216 --> 00:29:14,919
Cha Joo-hwan's family's loaded!

370
00:29:14,919 --> 00:29:18,523
He even has a hot fiancé.

371
00:29:18,523 --> 00:29:21,890
He's got it made.

372
00:29:22,093 --> 00:29:23,294
<i>Fiancé?</i>

373
00:29:23,294 --> 00:29:26,195
Is something up?

374
00:29:32,103 --> 00:29:35,766
Oh, you dropped your candy.

375
00:29:36,941 --> 00:29:39,000
Let's put it in your pocket.

376
00:29:52,023 --> 00:29:54,116
Have you ever been in love?

377
00:29:56,194 --> 00:29:59,357
Like a rock thrown into the river.

378
00:30:03,801 --> 00:30:05,393
Give me the ring.

379
00:30:05,770 --> 00:30:06,828
Excuse me?

380
00:30:06,938 --> 00:30:08,599
Your ring.

381
00:30:22,987 --> 00:30:24,750
Like this.

382
00:30:39,137 --> 00:30:42,834
Someone to pull you out. Like this.

383
00:30:45,243 --> 00:30:47,473
I'm engaged.

384
00:30:57,422 --> 00:30:59,219
It doesn't matter.

385
00:30:59,524 --> 00:31:00,786
Let's keep drinking.

386
00:31:08,800 --> 00:31:10,893
It's so cold.

387
00:31:14,572 --> 00:31:16,540
Did you drink?

388
00:31:25,950 --> 00:31:29,408
What do you like so much about him?

389
00:31:31,723 --> 00:31:34,590
I feel like I'm being sterilized.

390
00:31:37,328 --> 00:31:39,421
Sterilized?

391
00:31:40,965 --> 00:31:42,489
Sterilized.

392
00:32:18,036 --> 00:32:19,264
Perfect.

393
00:32:32,183 --> 00:32:35,118
- Let's eat.
- Sorry, I gotta run.

394
00:32:36,354 --> 00:32:38,982
- You're not eating?
- I can't.

395
00:32:39,223 --> 00:32:41,214
What about all this food?

396
00:32:41,726 --> 00:32:43,193
You eat it all.

397
00:32:46,097 --> 00:32:47,587
I'll see you later.

398
00:33:11,022 --> 00:33:16,971
A, B, C, D, E, F, G...

399
00:33:18,600 --> 00:33:22,112
...H, I, J, K

400
00:33:57,702 --> 00:33:59,397
Hello?

401
00:33:59,804 --> 00:34:02,673
<i>Is this Eun Won's number?</i>

402
00:34:02,673 --> 00:34:06,370
Yes, it is.

403
00:34:06,811 --> 00:34:09,336
<i>May I speak to her, please?</i>

404
00:34:09,547 --> 00:34:11,344
She's not here.

405
00:34:13,751 --> 00:34:15,987
<i>My name's Cha Joo-hwan.</i>

406
00:34:15,987 --> 00:34:18,456
<i>We were supposed to meet today</i>

407
00:34:18,456 --> 00:34:22,660
<i>but something came up at the clinic.</i>

408
00:34:22,660 --> 00:34:25,396
<i>Is there any way I can reach her?</i>

409
00:34:25,396 --> 00:34:27,830
Where were you supposed to meet?

410
00:35:10,374 --> 00:35:11,807
So cold.

411
00:35:13,477 --> 00:35:14,637
Hey.

412
00:35:14,712 --> 00:35:16,145
He can't come.

413
00:35:16,547 --> 00:35:17,775
Who?

414
00:35:17,848 --> 00:35:19,338
Him.

415
00:35:23,087 --> 00:35:24,554
The doctor.

416
00:35:28,960 --> 00:35:30,661
Where are you going?

417
00:35:30,661 --> 00:35:32,322
I gotta go.

418
00:35:32,630 --> 00:35:36,122
Sit down. The curry here is great.

419
00:35:38,236 --> 00:35:40,004
You know I don't eat curry.

420
00:35:40,004 --> 00:35:41,138
Then what do you want?

421
00:35:41,138 --> 00:35:42,273
What else is there?

422
00:35:42,273 --> 00:35:44,264
What do you want to eat?

423
00:35:45,276 --> 00:35:46,937
Kimbap.

424
00:35:47,979 --> 00:35:49,674
So boring.

425
00:35:49,847 --> 00:35:51,678
Just eat curry.

426
00:35:54,952 --> 00:35:56,476
You're buying.

427
00:35:59,090 --> 00:36:03,754
Come on, Producer Kang. Spill it.

428
00:36:03,928 --> 00:36:06,192
Did he rip you off or something?

429
00:36:06,397 --> 00:36:09,833
Then, why didn't you say so!

430
00:36:10,568 --> 00:36:17,565
My boys can get the money
back before lunch in no time.

431
00:36:17,808 --> 00:36:19,332
It's not that.

432
00:36:19,443 --> 00:36:22,378
Then what is it?

433
00:36:22,580 --> 00:36:28,177
Why would someone like you want
the dirt on some guy's fiancé even?

434
00:36:29,920 --> 00:36:34,289
Are you interested in his fiancé?

435
00:36:34,892 --> 00:36:37,087
Just find out, please.

436
00:36:37,228 --> 00:36:38,855
Fine, then.

437
00:36:40,131 --> 00:36:46,331
Anyway, Cats' album is now
starting to get noticed.

438
00:36:46,904 --> 00:36:49,707
Let's cook up something with your show

439
00:36:49,707 --> 00:36:53,074
and sell them like hot pancakes!

440
00:36:53,878 --> 00:36:55,146
I'm sure it'll do well.

441
00:36:55,146 --> 00:36:56,909
Of course.

442
00:36:57,248 --> 00:36:58,613
Hey, Min-chul!

443
00:36:59,116 --> 00:37:00,811
Did you like the house?

444
00:37:01,252 --> 00:37:04,415
Mother said she liked it.

445
00:37:04,555 --> 00:37:06,455
It's not bad.

446
00:37:06,791 --> 00:37:09,021
I heard you stopped holding exhibitions.

447
00:37:09,593 --> 00:37:11,891
I'm tired of putting on shows.

448
00:37:13,597 --> 00:37:16,065
And there's nothing to take pictures of.

449
00:37:17,835 --> 00:37:23,102
I'm sorry I'm not more fun to be around.

450
00:37:23,274 --> 00:37:27,938
Don't worry. I like to have fun by myself.

451
00:37:28,746 --> 00:37:30,441
That's sad.

452
00:37:31,749 --> 00:37:36,311
- Let's have fun together from now on.
- Sure.

453
00:37:37,621 --> 00:37:40,954
Can I get an ashtray here?

454
00:37:41,325 --> 00:37:44,226
I'm sorry. There's no smoking here.

455
00:37:45,863 --> 00:37:48,457
The world's such a bore.

456
00:37:48,566 --> 00:37:51,433
Get her an ashtray to put that out, please.

457
00:37:51,535 --> 00:37:53,560
Yes, sir.

458
00:37:55,272 --> 00:37:56,899
Interesting.

459
00:37:57,241 --> 00:37:58,640
Keep smoking.

460
00:37:59,510 --> 00:38:05,176
Should've known. She's
really somethin' all right.

461
00:38:05,883 --> 00:38:09,148
She's got men coming out of her ears.

462
00:38:09,453 --> 00:38:12,823
I told them to take some good pics.

463
00:38:12,823 --> 00:38:14,024
It won't be long.

464
00:38:14,024 --> 00:38:17,661
<i>How did you pose for your album cover?</i>

465
00:38:17,661 --> 00:38:20,931
I posed like I practiced
with my boss last night.

466
00:38:20,931 --> 00:38:23,033
Exactly how?

467
00:38:23,033 --> 00:38:25,136
<i>- Here?</i>
<i>- Pardon?</i>

468
00:38:25,136 --> 00:38:28,697
Men are all the same.

469
00:38:30,107 --> 00:38:31,699
Okay, then.

470
00:38:34,011 --> 00:38:38,107
First, I open my eyes like a cat.

471
00:38:38,783 --> 00:38:39,750
Like this.

472
00:38:39,750 --> 00:38:42,319
- Ah, Cat Girl?
- Then...

473
00:38:42,319 --> 00:38:45,423
I hold my hands up and
open my mouth like this.

474
00:38:45,423 --> 00:38:48,392
Look at her. She's a natural born star!

475
00:38:48,392 --> 00:38:50,155
You can just tell us.

476
00:38:50,461 --> 00:38:53,063
But my boss said a star

477
00:38:53,063 --> 00:38:55,599
<i>- has to speak with the body.</i>
- See that?

478
00:38:55,599 --> 00:39:01,038
Girls like her adjust so quickly.

479
00:39:01,038 --> 00:39:04,633
That foxy babe. Who wouldn't love her?

480
00:39:07,411 --> 00:39:10,080
- Ah, sir?
- Producer Kang!

481
00:39:10,080 --> 00:39:12,048
- What's wrong?
- Producer Kang!

482
00:39:21,826 --> 00:39:23,657
Where is he?

483
00:39:26,597 --> 00:39:28,656
- Hey!
- I'm dead beat.

484
00:39:28,833 --> 00:39:30,494
What's wrong with you!

485
00:39:30,935 --> 00:39:32,459
What's with you!

486
00:39:34,004 --> 00:39:36,302
Don't start.

487
00:39:38,342 --> 00:39:42,142
Why does he keep fainting like this?

488
00:39:42,847 --> 00:39:47,451
It's hereditary, but it could also be

489
00:39:47,451 --> 00:39:50,054
not enough calcium in his diet.

490
00:39:50,054 --> 00:39:56,760
We've been eating the same food
in the same house for years!

491
00:39:56,760 --> 00:39:59,228
Why are you the only
one who keeps fainting!

492
00:40:01,332 --> 00:40:03,630
You eat way more than I do.

493
00:40:03,834 --> 00:40:08,100
Hey! You're only eating anchovies
from now on, got that!

494
00:40:27,157 --> 00:40:28,647
You!

495
00:40:29,193 --> 00:40:30,660
Yes?

496
00:40:30,761 --> 00:40:32,752
What did he just say?

497
00:40:34,164 --> 00:40:37,930
To break off your engagement...

498
00:40:39,103 --> 00:40:42,300
- Stop! Please!
- Who are you!

499
00:40:42,907 --> 00:40:46,673
What the hell are you trying to pull!

500
00:40:49,179 --> 00:40:52,876
You don't wanna mess with me!

501
00:40:53,150 --> 00:40:56,950
Hey! Get the hell out of my sight!

502
00:41:02,960 --> 00:41:04,723
I said, get lost.

503
00:41:26,717 --> 00:41:28,878
Why are you doing this?

504
00:41:30,287 --> 00:41:31,811
Huh?

505
00:41:33,290 --> 00:41:36,953
You're a successful radio show producer.

506
00:41:37,161 --> 00:41:40,528
Trailing a woman and
getting slapped like that.

507
00:41:41,765 --> 00:41:43,634
Aren't you embarrassed?

508
00:41:43,634 --> 00:41:46,102
I don't have time to be embarrassed.

509
00:41:47,504 --> 00:41:50,064
What are you talking about?

510
00:41:50,441 --> 00:41:55,208
One mountain after another.
But no time to go.

511
00:41:59,483 --> 00:42:01,644
Ow, my head.

512
00:42:04,121 --> 00:42:05,952
Does it hurt?

513
00:42:07,191 --> 00:42:08,988
I'm hurt, too.

514
00:42:13,063 --> 00:42:15,327
What's with me today?

515
00:42:16,266 --> 00:42:18,257
It's because we're sad.

516
00:42:19,503 --> 00:42:24,497
Then cry instead of making jokes.

517
00:42:25,142 --> 00:42:27,372
I don't want to cry.

518
00:42:29,079 --> 00:42:31,445
Don't wanna make someone cry even more.

519
00:42:36,420 --> 00:42:40,254
I'm dying. Just like my dad.

520
00:42:43,894 --> 00:42:45,589
Chul-kyu!

521
00:42:51,168 --> 00:42:55,764
<i>Mom left me a year after Dad died.</i>

522
00:42:59,276 --> 00:43:02,177
<i>It probably wasn't</i>
<i>because she resented me.</i>

523
00:43:03,080 --> 00:43:05,605
<i>She was sick of</i>
<i>everything because of Dad.</i>

524
00:43:07,584 --> 00:43:12,317
<i>I understand. I was</i>
<i>sick of everything too.</i>

525
00:43:13,424 --> 00:43:18,191
<i>But when Mom left me all alone...</i>

526
00:43:19,430 --> 00:43:21,625
<i>I was so lonely.</i>

527
00:43:25,335 --> 00:43:27,064
<i>People...</i>

528
00:43:28,272 --> 00:43:30,172
should never be alone.

529
00:43:59,436 --> 00:44:01,028
<i>I'm sorry.</i>

530
00:44:02,172 --> 00:44:04,231
<i>I want you to leave your fiancé.</i>

531
00:44:05,709 --> 00:44:10,238
<i>The girl that I love</i>
<i>is in love with him.</i>

532
00:44:12,082 --> 00:44:13,674
<i>I beg you.</i>

533
00:44:21,725 --> 00:44:23,590
Under one condition.

534
00:44:26,497 --> 00:44:28,098
But...

535
00:44:28,098 --> 00:44:29,656
But?

536
00:44:36,540 --> 00:44:39,202
No, please! Tell me.

537
00:44:50,587 --> 00:44:52,817
I want to take your picture.

538
00:44:55,959 --> 00:45:01,454
Your medical records said
you don't have much time left.

539
00:45:02,699 --> 00:45:07,500
Now, that's an interesting model.

540
00:45:11,308 --> 00:45:13,572
I think it'll be fun.

541
00:45:13,777 --> 00:45:16,371
I don't think it'll be fun.

542
00:45:18,849 --> 00:45:20,783
Then the deal's off.

543
00:45:24,888 --> 00:45:26,913
Drink up, first!

544
00:45:27,224 --> 00:45:30,887
Give me a drink, too!

545
00:45:38,001 --> 00:45:40,868
- Hi! Hi!
- Hi! You're late!

546
00:45:45,442 --> 00:45:49,208
Hello. I spoke to you on the phone.

547
00:45:49,880 --> 00:45:51,348
Oh, hi.

548
00:45:51,348 --> 00:45:52,610
I'm Kang Chul-kyu.

549
00:45:52,783 --> 00:45:54,045
Cha Joo-hwan.

550
00:45:54,151 --> 00:45:56,585
- Thanks again for that day.
- Anytime.

551
00:45:57,187 --> 00:45:58,552
You know him?

552
00:45:58,956 --> 00:46:00,321
The sterilizer?

553
00:46:03,393 --> 00:46:06,163
- Did you eat?
- No, I'll eat now.

554
00:46:06,163 --> 00:46:07,926
Why are you so late?

555
00:46:08,031 --> 00:46:10,465
- Still recording a show.
- What?

556
00:46:10,567 --> 00:46:12,035
You said you're done.

557
00:46:12,035 --> 00:46:14,560
Not yet. I gotta go back.

558
00:46:17,274 --> 00:46:18,935
- Here.
- Thank you.

559
00:46:22,379 --> 00:46:25,177
The song's great.

560
00:46:26,183 --> 00:46:27,650
'If I can live again'?

561
00:46:27,751 --> 00:46:29,810
Of course, I wrote it.

562
00:46:31,255 --> 00:46:33,655
Sorry, I gotta go.

563
00:46:33,724 --> 00:46:37,717
- Come on.
- Don't go.

564
00:46:37,828 --> 00:46:39,227
I'll see you later.

565
00:46:39,696 --> 00:46:40,822
Bye.

566
00:46:41,465 --> 00:46:44,161
- See you next time, then.
- Sure.

567
00:46:49,473 --> 00:46:51,031
Be careful in the snow!

568
00:47:35,809 --> 00:47:37,911
Why are you back so early?

569
00:47:38,053 --> 00:47:41,216
Aren't you supposed to be recording a show?

570
00:47:42,291 --> 00:47:44,259
Change of plans.

571
00:47:44,493 --> 00:47:47,360
Me, too.

572
00:47:52,402 --> 00:47:54,029
Drink this.

573
00:48:00,777 --> 00:48:02,369
Didn't you eat?

574
00:48:02,679 --> 00:48:06,775
I did, but I'm still starving.

575
00:48:12,655 --> 00:48:15,988
Why are you eating noodles instead of rice?

576
00:48:16,259 --> 00:48:20,218
Just wanted something simple.

577
00:48:21,464 --> 00:48:22,761
It's good, huh?

578
00:48:25,969 --> 00:48:29,166
If you could stop time,
what would you do first?

579
00:48:31,240 --> 00:48:36,234
If everyone else is frozen
and only you can move?

580
00:48:37,413 --> 00:48:40,712
If time stopped, you wouldn't die.

581
00:48:43,753 --> 00:48:45,550
Don't you want to live?

582
00:48:49,926 --> 00:48:51,689
Not talking to me?

583
00:48:54,230 --> 00:48:58,257
Too sorry to die and leave
the girl you love alone.

584
00:49:00,470 --> 00:49:03,268
Okay, I can understand that much.

585
00:49:04,841 --> 00:49:06,468
But still...

586
00:49:08,277 --> 00:49:11,838
How can you marry her off to someone else?

587
00:49:13,049 --> 00:49:16,143
Isn't that going overboard?

588
00:49:19,722 --> 00:49:22,122
You're not dead, yet.

589
00:49:24,293 --> 00:49:27,319
- How can you watch that?
- Excuse me.

590
00:49:28,498 --> 00:49:31,228
Let's just stick to our jobs.

591
00:49:31,634 --> 00:49:34,967
What's love?

592
00:49:42,345 --> 00:49:44,279
Like brushing your teeth.

593
00:49:44,580 --> 00:49:46,445
Brushing your teeth?

594
00:49:47,784 --> 00:49:49,886
But you do that alone.

595
00:49:49,886 --> 00:49:52,184
Do you brush to show someone?

596
00:49:55,825 --> 00:49:58,385
Why didn't you come yesterday?

597
00:50:03,199 --> 00:50:04,188
Pardon?

598
00:50:14,177 --> 00:50:16,668
I said, did you wait for me?

599
00:50:16,979 --> 00:50:24,010
Well, just wondering why you didn't come.

600
00:50:24,120 --> 00:50:27,214
You fell in love with me, didn't you?

601
00:50:27,557 --> 00:50:28,683
What?

602
00:50:28,691 --> 00:50:33,594
Love makes you wonder
and wait for that person.

603
00:50:34,897 --> 00:50:39,102
It's not that. If a patient
doesn't come, I wait.

604
00:50:39,102 --> 00:50:41,696
Do you wonder about every patient?

605
00:50:42,371 --> 00:50:43,895
Well...

606
00:50:45,141 --> 00:50:49,043
You're blushing. It's love all right.

607
00:50:51,047 --> 00:50:52,514
Hey, Kang Chul-kyu!

608
00:50:52,615 --> 00:50:54,173
Yes, boss.

609
00:50:54,383 --> 00:50:57,318
How much did you get from Kim Gap-sik?

610
00:50:58,721 --> 00:51:01,390
Should've been more discreet!

611
00:51:01,390 --> 00:51:03,950
Cat Girl's on your show 10 times a week!

612
00:51:04,060 --> 00:51:07,029
Think people will stay still?

613
00:51:07,463 --> 00:51:13,231
Someone wrote in to audit your show!

614
00:51:13,402 --> 00:51:16,997
What's got into you all of a sudden?

615
00:51:17,106 --> 00:51:21,099
You of all people!

616
00:51:25,448 --> 00:51:27,541
When are you going to break it off?

617
00:51:28,584 --> 00:51:30,108
In a rush?

618
00:51:31,154 --> 00:51:33,145
You saw my medical records.

619
00:51:35,792 --> 00:51:38,158
I want to keep playing.

620
00:51:39,695 --> 00:51:44,189
But I guess you don't have that luxury.

621
00:51:49,338 --> 00:51:51,363
Under one condition.

622
00:51:57,980 --> 00:51:59,914
Now, what.

623
00:52:00,750 --> 00:52:03,014
I'll tell you after I break it off.

624
00:52:03,519 --> 00:52:05,714
A promise is a promise.

625
00:52:20,837 --> 00:52:24,432
Since when was it no smoking in here.

626
00:52:27,610 --> 00:52:29,407
No idea.

627
00:52:38,454 --> 00:52:42,481
Our parents will be shocked.

628
00:52:53,035 --> 00:52:59,475
I should be really angry
at a time like this, right?

629
00:52:59,475 --> 00:53:03,809
Yell at you or something?

630
00:53:06,682 --> 00:53:14,885
Funny, somehow I feel a little grateful.

631
00:53:17,126 --> 00:53:19,219
I'm going out for a smoke.

632
00:53:22,598 --> 00:53:23,963
So uncomfortable.

633
00:53:28,004 --> 00:53:29,767
My engagement's off.

634
00:53:38,381 --> 00:53:40,781
I don't have parents.

635
00:53:43,719 --> 00:53:47,246
I was studying late at high
school in my senior year.

636
00:53:48,457 --> 00:53:51,858
My homeroom teacher came
in and stared right at me.

637
00:53:52,128 --> 00:54:00,832
Like someone who came
to take me on death row.

638
00:54:02,305 --> 00:54:04,899
Like in the movies, you know?

639
00:54:06,275 --> 00:54:10,041
Anyway, he told me

640
00:54:10,313 --> 00:54:14,647
to go to the hospital right away.

641
00:54:14,984 --> 00:54:17,953
When I asked why...

642
00:54:18,187 --> 00:54:21,257
if he said my parents and

643
00:54:21,257 --> 00:54:24,693
sister died in a car accident...

644
00:54:25,227 --> 00:54:30,494
then I wouldn't have gone
and seen them like that.

645
00:54:32,401 --> 00:54:35,734
I see...

646
00:54:36,238 --> 00:54:38,968
K's been with me ever since.

647
00:54:39,942 --> 00:54:41,409
K?

648
00:54:43,646 --> 00:54:47,742
You saw him, Producer Kang Chul-kyu?

649
00:54:48,584 --> 00:54:52,418
His name sounds too corny
so I just call him K.

650
00:54:56,192 --> 00:55:00,424
At home, he's my Mom
At work, he's my Dad.

651
00:55:00,663 --> 00:55:02,858
When I'm sad, he's my brother.

652
00:55:03,632 --> 00:55:07,591
Sometimes he's like a lover.
Though he always chickens out.

653
00:55:09,205 --> 00:55:12,368
Can I kiss you?

654
00:55:14,076 --> 00:55:16,567
You wanna kiss me?

655
00:55:25,187 --> 00:55:26,552
Stupid.

656
00:55:27,857 --> 00:55:30,257
Let me see.

657
00:55:32,728 --> 00:55:33,786
Oh, no.

658
00:55:33,896 --> 00:55:35,921
That's right. I'm stupid.

659
00:55:44,807 --> 00:55:47,833
Open the door. Are you okay?

660
00:55:58,788 --> 00:56:01,018
(Don't look!)
(Stupid!)

661
00:56:13,202 --> 00:56:15,295
(Really Stupid!!!)
(Stupid!)

662
00:56:43,265 --> 00:56:45,768
<i>I was born to love you.</i>

663
00:56:45,768 --> 00:56:49,829
<i>Heaven sent me to love you.</i>

664
00:56:51,774 --> 00:56:54,176
<i>Cat Girl's 'If I could live again'</i>

665
00:56:54,176 --> 00:56:56,337
<i>requested by ID: Little Mermaid.</i>

666
00:56:56,512 --> 00:56:58,514
- Cream. You wrote this song, right?
- Yes.

667
00:56:58,514 --> 00:57:01,074
Let's hear, 'If I could live again'.

668
00:57:10,359 --> 00:57:11,951
(Did you eat?)

669
00:57:14,063 --> 00:57:16,054
(I'm almost done!)

670
00:57:32,581 --> 00:57:34,150
Yes, boss.

671
00:57:34,150 --> 00:57:37,920
<i>Producer Kang. Come to my office now.</i>

672
00:57:37,920 --> 00:57:39,217
Okay.

673
00:57:47,229 --> 00:57:50,596
Producer Kang!

674
00:57:52,301 --> 00:57:53,427
Producer Kang!

675
00:57:53,736 --> 00:57:59,275
I heard everything. I'm going to
speak with the boss right now!

676
00:57:59,275 --> 00:58:04,269
How can he fire a genius like you!

677
00:58:04,446 --> 00:58:06,348
I'm not getting fired.

678
00:58:06,348 --> 00:58:09,151
Same difference.

679
00:58:09,151 --> 00:58:11,847
- You can't go like this!
- I'm taking a break.

680
00:58:11,921 --> 00:58:17,560
Really? That's not what I heard.

681
00:58:17,560 --> 00:58:21,189
I'm going to the States
to study for a while.

682
00:58:21,297 --> 00:58:28,465
Really? I guess there's
no use going to the boss.

683
00:58:29,238 --> 00:58:33,142
Thank you for everything, Mr. Kim.

684
00:58:33,142 --> 00:58:36,578
- Anytime.
- You too, Min-chul.

685
00:58:36,812 --> 00:58:40,077
Give him the demo tape, Min-chul.

686
00:58:41,317 --> 00:58:45,219
Producer Choi! Hold on! Wait!

687
00:58:53,229 --> 00:58:54,856
Min-chul...

688
00:59:20,923 --> 00:59:22,185
It's a ballad.

689
00:59:22,691 --> 00:59:24,124
Write up a good song.

690
00:59:32,835 --> 00:59:34,530
What's marriage?

691
00:59:36,839 --> 00:59:38,329
Marriage?

692
00:59:38,774 --> 00:59:40,139
Marriage.

693
00:59:44,546 --> 00:59:47,140
- Marriage...
- Wait!

694
00:59:59,595 --> 01:00:01,654
A toothbrush holder.

695
01:00:02,731 --> 01:00:04,494
What?

696
01:00:05,267 --> 01:00:09,704
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.

697
01:00:11,674 --> 01:00:14,074
What's that got to do with marriage?

698
01:00:14,343 --> 01:00:21,306
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.

699
01:00:24,887 --> 01:00:27,355
Then I must be married, already.

700
01:00:28,691 --> 01:00:32,183
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.

701
01:00:34,897 --> 01:00:36,364
Really?

702
01:00:38,667 --> 01:00:40,157
I gotta pee.

703
01:01:09,365 --> 01:01:11,265
(No one else but Thee.)

704
01:01:17,773 --> 01:01:19,900
'Thee' is a lucky person.

705
01:01:23,645 --> 01:01:25,545
Wanna listen to it?

706
01:01:59,681 --> 01:02:05,244
You probably heard about
Eun Won and I living together.

707
01:02:06,155 --> 01:02:07,856
But there's nothing to worry about.

708
01:02:07,856 --> 01:02:09,517
I'm okay with that.

709
01:02:10,192 --> 01:02:15,960
I'm thankful for everything you did for her.

710
01:02:16,231 --> 01:02:19,826
Let's get together often.

711
01:02:20,135 --> 01:02:22,467
Go on trips together and stuff.

712
01:02:23,138 --> 01:02:24,605
Sounds good.

713
01:02:26,442 --> 01:02:31,243
She says she wants to pick out
her wedding dress with you.

714
01:02:31,513 --> 01:02:33,242
Gotta love her wild ideas.

715
01:02:33,348 --> 01:02:35,373
Why me?

716
01:02:35,651 --> 01:02:39,382
I want what she wants.

717
01:02:42,291 --> 01:02:44,851
Please do it for her.

718
01:02:46,995 --> 01:02:55,733
And I hope it's the last
thing you ever do for her.

719
01:02:57,906 --> 01:03:01,569
Sure. Please take good care of her.

720
01:03:01,710 --> 01:03:05,806
Of course. She's my woman now.

721
01:03:06,114 --> 01:03:07,479
Let's drink.

722
01:03:23,165 --> 01:03:24,723
What do you think?

723
01:03:30,873 --> 01:03:32,363
Very pretty.

724
01:03:35,911 --> 01:03:40,143
It's time for the groom-to-be
to try on his suit.

725
01:03:42,017 --> 01:03:43,452
I'm not the groom.

726
01:03:43,452 --> 01:03:45,044
Try it on.

727
01:03:53,729 --> 01:03:54,991
Come up here.

728
01:03:58,267 --> 01:04:02,260
Come here. Can you take a picture of us?

729
01:04:02,404 --> 01:04:05,931
On three. One, two, three!

730
01:04:14,683 --> 01:04:17,516
Wait out there.
I'll try on something else.

731
01:06:53,275 --> 01:06:55,800
Why are all the clocks stopped?

732
01:06:56,211 --> 01:06:57,508
No reason.

733
01:07:01,016 --> 01:07:03,382
Can I turn one on?

734
01:07:07,489 --> 01:07:08,922
Why?

735
01:07:09,691 --> 01:07:10,988
No reason.

736
01:07:12,928 --> 01:07:14,486
No reason?

737
01:07:15,797 --> 01:07:17,059
Sure.

738
01:07:43,058 --> 01:07:47,722
I have a big favor to ask.

739
01:07:48,797 --> 01:07:50,264
What is it?

740
01:07:52,200 --> 01:07:58,070
I need to send flowers to her
anniversary for a few years.

741
01:08:01,209 --> 01:08:05,145
She'll get suspicious, if I
suddenly lose touch altogether.

742
01:08:08,784 --> 01:08:11,548
I had one more condition. Remember?

743
01:08:14,556 --> 01:08:16,353
What is it?

744
01:08:39,247 --> 01:08:41,374
Please die at my side.

745
01:08:48,824 --> 01:08:52,089
You booked the tickets?

746
01:08:55,263 --> 01:08:57,925
I'm running low on battery.

747
01:08:59,568 --> 01:09:00,762
Hey.

748
01:09:03,205 --> 01:09:04,502
What are you making?

749
01:09:09,277 --> 01:09:12,269
My phone battery ran out.

750
01:09:12,948 --> 01:09:19,217
I'll charge it and call you back later.

751
01:09:19,387 --> 01:09:20,789
Bye.

752
01:09:20,789 --> 01:09:22,086
Hi.

753
01:09:26,595 --> 01:09:30,224
Hey. Why'd you leave me there like that?

754
01:09:31,366 --> 01:09:32,833
It's for you.

755
01:09:43,478 --> 01:09:45,241
Who do you think you are!

756
01:09:45,847 --> 01:09:47,576
What's with you?

757
01:09:47,749 --> 01:09:50,582
Who says you can touch my phone!

758
01:09:52,854 --> 01:09:54,685
The hell you...

759
01:09:57,959 --> 01:10:00,553
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!

760
01:10:34,296 --> 01:10:35,593
Can I help you?

761
01:10:35,697 --> 01:10:37,324
Is K at home?

762
01:10:38,900 --> 01:10:40,527
K?

763
01:11:04,159 --> 01:11:05,922
Someone's here.

764
01:11:24,746 --> 01:11:29,240
She's pretty. I can see why you love her.

765
01:11:30,652 --> 01:11:35,646
You think she's happy?

766
01:11:36,725 --> 01:11:38,625
What are you saying?

767
01:11:39,394 --> 01:11:41,453
She didn't seem happy.

768
01:11:43,531 --> 01:11:46,898
Can you send this for the next 3 years?

769
01:11:48,737 --> 01:11:50,170
It's pretty.

770
01:11:51,539 --> 01:11:53,404
But maybe too pretty.

771
01:11:56,678 --> 01:11:59,806
It looks fake like your love.

772
01:12:00,882 --> 01:12:02,816
Then what's real?

773
01:12:06,888 --> 01:12:08,321
Real?

774
01:12:10,792 --> 01:12:14,785
If you're hungry, you eat.
If you're hurting, you cry.

775
01:12:15,163 --> 01:12:20,157
If you're having fun, you laugh.
Not hold it in like you.

776
01:12:21,603 --> 01:12:24,231
You really wanna die like this?

777
01:12:26,975 --> 01:12:28,465
No!

778
01:12:30,678 --> 01:12:32,543
I don't want to die like this.

779
01:12:33,948 --> 01:12:36,143
I want to live a happy life.

780
01:12:38,787 --> 01:12:41,051
I want to be the one marrying Eun Won...

781
01:12:42,190 --> 01:12:44,215
...instead of him, tomorrow.

782
01:12:48,563 --> 01:12:50,030
But...

783
01:12:51,299 --> 01:12:52,960
That's just a dream.

784
01:12:53,635 --> 01:12:55,330
A sad dream.

785
01:12:58,740 --> 01:13:01,903
I'm done with dreaming.

786
01:13:57,232 --> 01:13:59,792
<i>Sleep tight and sweet dreams.</i>

787
01:14:20,121 --> 01:14:23,181
<i>Did you eat? -Cream</i>

788
01:14:27,262 --> 01:14:28,593
Thanks for the food.

789
01:14:47,815 --> 01:14:49,874
<i>I'm not talking to you.</i>

790
01:14:58,326 --> 01:14:59,850
<i>I'm sorry.</i>

791
01:15:06,901 --> 01:15:08,334
<i>For what?</i>

792
01:15:11,206 --> 01:15:12,764
<i>For everything.</i>

793
01:15:19,480 --> 01:15:21,311
<i>I'm sorry, too.</i>

794
01:15:22,050 --> 01:15:23,347
<i>For what?</i>

795
01:15:24,452 --> 01:15:25,749
<i>For everything.</i>

796
01:15:29,057 --> 01:15:32,117
<i>I love you...</i>

797
01:15:36,231 --> 01:15:37,664
<i>I like you.</i>

798
01:15:39,000 --> 01:15:40,331
<i>Me, too.</i>

799
01:18:01,876 --> 01:18:03,741
That's some story.

800
01:18:06,013 --> 01:18:09,346
Kang... amazing guy. I had no idea.

801
01:18:10,985 --> 01:18:17,413
Is there anyway to reach
them? What about the dentist?

802
01:18:23,798 --> 01:18:27,097
Wonder what happened to her.

803
01:18:34,375 --> 01:18:37,674
Let's record it.

804
01:18:39,514 --> 01:18:42,210
Really? I'll call right now.

805
01:18:42,383 --> 01:18:45,580
No, the other song.

806
01:18:46,921 --> 01:18:49,446
Oh, that song.

807
01:20:14,909 --> 01:20:16,677
I gotta go, I'm late.

808
01:20:16,677 --> 01:20:20,044
Get up and eat. I made breakfast.

809
01:21:17,638 --> 01:21:19,003
<i>What's this?</i>

810
01:21:20,241 --> 01:21:24,610
<i>Ah, Vitamin ABC.</i>
<i>It helps me get smarter.</i>

811
01:22:11,692 --> 01:22:14,820
Where'd you get these pills?

812
01:22:15,296 --> 01:22:17,491
They're my friend's pills.

813
01:22:18,199 --> 01:22:22,659
Since when did your friend
started taking these?

814
01:22:23,571 --> 01:22:25,095
Why?

815
01:22:25,773 --> 01:22:30,073
The pain must've been
severe to take these pills.

816
01:22:31,545 --> 01:22:32,637
What?

817
01:22:33,180 --> 01:22:38,709
They're painkillers for
patients with cancer or leukemia.

818
01:22:39,020 --> 01:22:41,079
<i>Terminal patients.</i>

819
01:22:42,390 --> 01:22:46,121
<i>Have you heard of the hospice ward?</i>

820
01:22:47,061 --> 01:22:50,861
<i>It's where dying patients stay...</i>

821
01:22:51,298 --> 01:22:55,359
<i>with consent from their families.</i>

822
01:23:10,351 --> 01:23:11,613
Mom!

823
01:23:11,752 --> 01:23:14,355
Watch the house while we're out.

824
01:23:14,355 --> 01:23:16,755
See you later, sis!

825
01:23:22,930 --> 01:23:24,363
No!

826
01:23:49,090 --> 01:23:52,150
<i>When I found out what</i>
<i>Vitamin ABC really was...</i>

827
01:23:52,393 --> 01:23:56,261
<i>When I finally realized</i>
<i>what they were...</i>

828
01:23:56,497 --> 01:24:01,059
<i>When my whole world</i>
<i>turned pitch dark before me...</i>

829
01:24:01,502 --> 01:24:02,969
What's wrong?

830
01:24:03,204 --> 01:24:05,900
<i>I died before K.</i>

831
01:24:08,809 --> 01:24:16,545
<i>I met K a year after my</i>
<i>whole family passed away.</i>

832
01:24:18,285 --> 01:24:22,278
<i>Though almost 3 hours has passed...</i>

833
01:24:23,624 --> 01:24:26,718
<i>he stood there frozen like stone.</i>

834
01:24:26,961 --> 01:24:30,564
<i>Crying and looking in the</i>
<i>direction his mother went.</i>

835
01:24:30,564 --> 01:24:35,365
<i>This will be enough to support you</i>
<i>till you're an adult, Chul-kyu.</i>

836
01:24:36,437 --> 01:24:42,535
<i>He looked sadder</i>
<i>and more hurt than me.</i>

837
01:24:43,978 --> 01:24:46,776
<i>He needed a hug more than me.</i>

838
01:24:47,782 --> 01:24:50,046
Is there anything you want to tell me?

839
01:24:50,818 --> 01:24:52,342
Like what?

840
01:24:55,523 --> 01:24:59,220
A deep, dark secret?

841
01:25:01,896 --> 01:25:05,457
Say anything. I'm ready to listen.

842
01:25:07,067 --> 01:25:08,500
I like you.

843
01:25:08,803 --> 01:25:11,431
<i>Stupid idiot.</i>

844
01:25:12,039 --> 01:25:13,836
Do you have a wish?

845
01:25:13,941 --> 01:25:15,509
What's with you?

846
01:25:15,509 --> 01:25:18,637
Just curious all of a sudden.

847
01:25:20,381 --> 01:25:24,147
If you could do anything
you want in the world.

848
01:25:24,752 --> 01:25:26,743
<i>K is dying.</i>

849
01:25:27,087 --> 01:25:29,555
Meet a great guy and get married.

850
01:25:29,723 --> 01:25:31,592
Can't I marry you?

851
01:25:31,592 --> 01:25:33,787
I'm not a great guy.

852
01:25:33,961 --> 01:25:36,263
Then who is?

853
01:25:36,263 --> 01:25:40,165
Someone who is healthy and nice.

854
01:25:40,734 --> 01:25:43,225
Who knows how to take care of his family.

855
01:25:44,438 --> 01:25:47,635
<i>I already met a great man.</i>

856
01:25:48,475 --> 01:25:52,138
<i>But K told me to meet someone else.</i>

857
01:25:52,613 --> 01:25:56,105
<i>He said that was his wish.</i>

858
01:25:57,685 --> 01:26:01,621
(KANG CHUL-KYU)

859
01:26:05,292 --> 01:26:08,386
<i>When I heard K fainted...</i>

860
01:26:08,896 --> 01:26:12,662
<i>I rushed over,
afraid that I'll go crazy.</i>

861
01:26:14,335 --> 01:26:16,132
<i>But I...</i>

862
01:26:17,071 --> 01:26:18,672
<i>...couldn't even go crazy.</i>

863
01:26:18,672 --> 01:26:20,674
No, doctor.

864
01:26:20,674 --> 01:26:23,336
But she should know.

865
01:26:24,311 --> 01:26:26,802
What are you going to do?

866
01:26:27,514 --> 01:26:29,573
I don't know.

867
01:26:33,988 --> 01:26:36,889
It feels like a needle stuck in my throat.

868
01:26:40,227 --> 01:26:41,956
Right here.

869
01:26:43,731 --> 01:26:45,858
It gets stuck right here.

870
01:26:47,334 --> 01:26:49,962
I can't say it.

871
01:26:51,672 --> 01:26:58,475
She'll live on. Think of yourself.

872
01:26:59,280 --> 01:27:01,680
She's different.

873
01:27:03,017 --> 01:27:05,110
She needs someone beside her.

874
01:27:20,434 --> 01:27:22,925
- Hello.
- There goes Mr. Perfect.

875
01:27:24,238 --> 01:27:26,638
Glowing from head to toe!

876
01:27:31,478 --> 01:27:33,742
<i>I picked a man.</i>

877
01:27:43,524 --> 01:27:45,685
Which side did you drink from?

878
01:27:48,796 --> 01:27:50,030
Pardon?

879
01:27:50,030 --> 01:27:52,430
I'm engaged.

880
01:27:52,967 --> 01:28:00,339
<i>Stupid. You think I care</i>
<i>whether you're engaged or not?</i>

881
01:28:01,642 --> 01:28:05,237
<i>Just play along and meet me. For K.</i>

882
01:28:06,313 --> 01:28:08,338
<i>Am I a bitch?</i>

883
01:28:09,049 --> 01:28:11,552
<i>I don't have time to worry about that.</i>

884
01:28:11,552 --> 01:28:13,918
<i>The man I love is dying.</i>

885
01:28:24,798 --> 01:28:30,600
<i>If I could be born again...</i>
<i>A ring? A pair of glasses?</i>

886
01:28:32,306 --> 01:28:36,402
<i>A bed? A diary?</i>

887
01:28:36,877 --> 01:28:40,574
<i>Born again as things like</i>
<i>that? What fun is that?</i>

888
01:28:40,848 --> 01:28:45,478
<i>You can buy me. It'll</i>
<i>always be fun at your side.</i>

889
01:29:01,502 --> 01:29:05,302
What's wrong? Are you okay?

890
01:29:07,408 --> 01:29:08,670
Let me see your hand.

891
01:29:16,050 --> 01:29:17,540
Where are you going?

892
01:29:37,271 --> 01:29:39,239
<i>I made a deal with myself.</i>

893
01:29:39,973 --> 01:29:42,441
<i>If he turns around,</i>
<i>I'd tell him everything.</i>

894
01:29:43,977 --> 01:29:48,346
<i>If he turns around, I'd</i>
<i>hug him and stop everything.</i>

895
01:29:50,084 --> 01:29:53,076
<i>But K didn't look back.</i>

896
01:29:54,421 --> 01:29:57,879
<i>And there was nothing I could do.</i>

897
01:30:03,564 --> 01:30:06,032
Why are you eating noodles instead of rice?

898
01:30:07,000 --> 01:30:09,195
Just wanted something simple.

899
01:30:12,706 --> 01:30:15,300
- It's good, huh?
- Yeah.

900
01:30:19,379 --> 01:30:22,473
<i>As I sat eating the</i>
<i>noodles with him...</i>

901
01:30:23,650 --> 01:30:26,053
<i>I'd think, 'Don't die you bastard'</i>

902
01:30:26,053 --> 01:30:28,920
<i>and drank some water instead.</i>

903
01:30:29,423 --> 01:30:34,190
<i>'Tell me. Let me hold you!</i>
<i>I'll die with you!'</i>

904
01:30:34,528 --> 01:30:38,988
<i>'I'll follow you and pay you back</i>
<i>for everything you did for me!'</i>

905
01:30:39,800 --> 01:30:42,997
<i>Instead, I just drank the water.</i>

906
01:30:44,037 --> 01:30:46,665
<i>And finished the noodles.</i>

907
01:30:50,844 --> 01:30:56,476
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.

908
01:30:58,085 --> 01:31:00,883
What's that got to do with marriage?

909
01:31:01,755 --> 01:31:08,319
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.

910
01:31:12,099 --> 01:31:14,397
Then I must be married, already.

911
01:31:15,869 --> 01:31:19,737
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.

912
01:31:21,742 --> 01:31:23,232
Really?

913
01:31:53,440 --> 01:31:55,840
Can we get married, soon?

914
01:32:21,268 --> 01:32:23,998
Wait out there. I'll try on something else.

915
01:33:00,474 --> 01:33:02,567
The hell you...

916
01:33:05,579 --> 01:33:08,377
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!

917
01:33:18,725 --> 01:33:20,317
<i>I'm sorry.</i>

918
01:33:26,967 --> 01:33:29,993
<i>I want to tell him I love him.</i>

919
01:33:30,404 --> 01:33:34,773
<i>I want to open my mouth</i>
<i>and say I love him.</i>

920
01:33:36,243 --> 01:33:40,111
<i>But I knew tears will fall</i>
<i>before I could say it.</i>

921
01:33:40,447 --> 01:33:43,848
<i>So I kept silent, again.</i>

922
01:33:57,230 --> 01:33:59,425
When are you going to talk to me?

923
01:34:00,934 --> 01:34:05,428
Didn't you hear me screaming
at you all this time?

924
01:34:06,039 --> 01:34:07,472
What?

925
01:34:08,975 --> 01:34:10,636
Stupid.

926
01:34:11,378 --> 01:34:13,312
I didn't hear anything.

927
01:34:14,348 --> 01:34:16,646
Then how can mutes love?

928
01:34:28,895 --> 01:34:30,692
I love you.

929
01:34:35,635 --> 01:34:37,102
Me, too.

930
01:35:01,828 --> 01:35:04,422
<i>We became a real couple.</i>

931
01:35:04,664 --> 01:35:06,791
<i>Because we made it down the aisle.</i>

932
01:36:39,059 --> 01:36:41,254
(Heaven's Gate Resting Place)

933
01:37:00,213 --> 01:37:01,339
Wait!

934
01:37:01,414 --> 01:37:02,779
You never learn!

935
01:37:03,884 --> 01:37:05,749
How can you write with a brain like that?

936
01:37:14,995 --> 01:37:17,395
This isn't kissing, is it?

937
01:37:29,576 --> 01:37:31,134
Can you take a picture of us?

938
01:37:31,378 --> 01:37:33,812
On three. One, two, three!

939
01:37:35,715 --> 01:37:43,781
<i>I was born to love you.</i>
<i>Heaven sent me to love you.</i>

940
01:38:43,183 --> 01:38:46,152
(Eun Won)

941
01:38:46,319 --> 01:38:47,887
<i>I'm making noodles. Want some?</i>

942
01:38:47,887 --> 01:38:49,956
<i>No, I gotta work.</i>

943
01:38:49,956 --> 01:38:51,324
<i>You sure?</i>

944
01:38:51,324 --> 01:38:53,087
<i>Yes, I'm working!</i>

945
01:38:53,193 --> 01:38:57,186
<i>- Then I'm just making one!</i>
<i>- Okay.</i>

946
01:38:58,064 --> 01:38:59,895
<i>Don't come begging later.</i>

947
01:39:00,033 --> 01:39:02,035
<i>- Hey!</i>
<i>- What?</i>

948
01:39:02,035 --> 01:39:05,198
<i>No eggs! Give me that.</i>

949
01:39:07,641 --> 01:39:10,166
<i>I wonder who invented noodles.</i>

950
01:39:10,377 --> 01:39:12,879
<i>You said you didn't want any.</i>

951
01:39:12,879 --> 01:39:14,471
<i>Changed my mind.</i>

952
01:39:15,382 --> 01:39:16,906
<i>Is there any rice?</i>

953
01:39:18,718 --> 01:39:21,949
<i>Hold on. There's some in the fridge.</i>

954
01:39:23,156 --> 01:39:28,219
<i>Chul-kyu... I'm coming to you.</i>

955
01:39:29,562 --> 01:39:32,030
<i>Don't worry.</i>

956
01:39:33,133 --> 01:39:37,467
<i>I trust you.</i>
<i>You were always my compass.</i>

957
01:39:39,205 --> 01:39:44,310
<i>Remember when I said I can see you</i>

958
01:39:44,310 --> 01:39:47,507
<i>even when you're not with me?</i>

959
01:39:49,282 --> 01:39:51,614
<i>Go wherever you want.</i>

960
01:39:52,585 --> 01:39:55,418
<i>I'll find you, soon.</i>

961
01:39:57,323 --> 01:40:01,191
<i>Don't get mad when you see me.</i>

962
01:40:02,662 --> 01:40:10,262
<i>Don't ask me why I followed</i>
<i>you or get angry at me.</i>

963
01:40:11,638 --> 01:40:18,669
<i>After everything to come to</i>
<i>you, if you get mad I'll cry.</i>

964
01:40:20,013 --> 01:40:25,041
<i>When we meet again on the</i>
<i>other side, let's not cry again.</i>

965
01:40:25,218 --> 01:40:28,210
<i>Wait for me. I'll be right there.</i>

966
01:40:46,149 --> 01:40:49,284
<i>Even if</i>

967
01:40:49,437 --> 01:40:52,801
<i>I’m reborn a thousand more times,</i>

968
01:40:53,844 --> 01:40:58,544
<i>There will not be another one like you.</i>

969
01:41:00,138 --> 01:41:03,279
<i>The one who</i>

970
01:41:03,493 --> 01:41:06,902
<i>would warm up my sad life.</i>

971
01:41:06,926 --> 01:41:12,746
<i>I'm really grateful for that person.</i>

972
01:41:13,220 --> 01:41:21,079
<i>For that person, my heart could</i>

973
01:41:21,142 --> 01:41:28,190
<i>be hurt indefinitely.</i>

974
01:41:28,462 --> 01:41:34,487
<i>Even if I can't</i>
<i>tell you that I love you,</i>

975
01:41:34,555 --> 01:41:37,950
<i>the fact that I'm able to</i>

976
01:41:37,974 --> 01:41:42,565
<i>look at you from a distance,</i>

977
01:41:42,589 --> 01:41:50,372
<i>give you everything and love you.</i>

978
01:41:50,396 --> 01:42:00,536
<i>Even if I'm sad, I'm happy.</i>

979
01:42:09,809 --> 01:42:16,732
<i>There is no other love in this world</i>

980
01:42:17,233 --> 01:42:23,151
<i>that could make my chest</i>
<i>shiver with such anticipation.</i>

981
01:42:23,566 --> 01:42:30,070
<i>I've buried so deep in my memories</i>

982
01:42:30,070 --> 01:42:36,268
<i>my only love.</i>

983
01:42:36,292 --> 01:42:40,581
<i>For someone like you,</i>

984
01:42:40,792 --> 01:42:44,042
<i>all the painful tears,</i>

985
01:42:44,043 --> 01:42:49,923
<i>I could endure it indefinitely.</i>

986
01:42:50,138 --> 01:42:56,346
<i>Even if I can't</i>
<i>tell you that I love you,</i>

987
01:42:56,370 --> 01:42:59,778
<i>the fact that I'm able to</i>

988
01:42:59,802 --> 01:43:04,321
<i>look at you from a distance,</i>

989
01:43:04,345 --> 01:43:11,940
<i>give you everything and love you.</i>

990
01:43:11,964 --> 01:43:18,086
<i>Even if I'm sad, I'm happy.</i>

991
01:43:18,169 --> 01:43:24,138
<i>I don't want anything else except</i>

992
01:43:24,162 --> 01:43:32,084
<i>your laughter. With it, I'll be happy.</i>

993
01:43:32,108 --> 01:43:36,099
<i>Because love is about giving everything,</i>

994
01:43:36,123 --> 01:43:39,996
<i>just about giving.</i>

995
01:43:40,020 --> 01:43:49,861
<i>So even if I'm sad, I'm happy.</i>

996
01:44:16,022 --> 01:44:21,322
subtitle by @pyururuh


