Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Bava, these bank guys…
If we come on time,
they say it's tea break,
and if we're late,
they say it's lunch break.
Let's hurry up.
Here’s the money you asked for, sir.
- Hey!
- Hey, who are you guys?
Bava!
- Chalapathi!
- Four million, man. Hey, give me the bag!
Hand it over!
- Four million…
- Give it to me.
Bava…
The money…
I knew about 24-carat gold,
but he is a 24-carat character, Bava.
What a good time!
You're getting a son-in-law who can fight.
For the first time,
I'm feeling sad about being born as a man.
Had I been born as a woman…
He has done what even our own people
wouldn’t dare to do.
- Yes.
- He is our son-in-law.
- You can fix it.
- What?
Trust me!
How about caste, family, and status?
Bava, you can adjust all that
if you get a guy with talent and timing.
The money is safe.
I can’t believe
someone like you exists these days.
You helped us just in time, sir.
- Many thanks, sir…
- Never mind. I hate praises.
It’s easy to earn money,
but very difficult to protect it.
Please take care of it.
All that is fine, but what is your caste?
I know pancakes and dosas.
Now what is this?
- Never heard of it.
- Your full name, by the way?
Parvataneni Papa Rao.
They gave me my grandfather’s name.
He is our Parvataneni…
- So, Kammas?
- No, Chowdarys.
It’s all the same. We are all one.
See? My parents raised me
without even knowing what my caste was!
It’s okay, son.
Innocent parents.
- What do you do, son?
- I cleared the group exams.
Awaiting the posting.
My family is looking for a bride for me.
- Ask them to stop.
- Why?
Bava, we should catch the young
by the net.
Hello, man, you're coming over
for a match meeting at our house tomorrow.
Tomorrow? What about my family?
You are coming with all of them
to our house to see our girl.
Okay, as you wish.
Please come. Welcome.
Glad you're on time.
Of course, we came.
But why is this match meeting
arranged in an outhouse?
- Sister…
- No, ma’am. It’s our house.
Looks like our outhouse.
Are you sure they will match our status?
- Go in now…
- Please come in.
This house was built 100 years ago.
Couldn’t you buy another house
in the last 100 years?
Sister…
Brother, I'm checking about their assets.
Shouldn’t I?
Sister, not sure. For me, the smile
that never fades is the best property.
Looks like our son-in-law
has modern thoughts.
It’s not enough to have modern thoughts.
We should also check out financially.
That’s why we came.
What business are you in?
We have been in the
tobacco business for ages.
We are good until people stop smoking.
- How about you?
- We are in the incense business.
We are also good
until people stop inhaling, Uncle.
Why delay then?
Let’s call the girl. What do you say?
- Sister…
- Brother…
The girl.
I can see.
Oh, God!
- Sister, are you okay?
- What is this?
Steel glasses. New ones.
We just bought these for you.
Does steel glass look like this?
We only use silver glasses at home.
We gave steel glasses
to our servants 25 years ago.
Don’t counter, Bava. Rich people…
- Elder daughter-in-law, Suhasini.
- 85 kg.
- Second daughter-in-law, Paddu.
- 76 kg.
What about the younger daughter-in-law?
A total of 110 kg.
We are superior in this matter.
Don’t get confused, Mr. Chalapathi.
My sister wasn't just talking
about their weight,
but also the gold they brought as dowry.
- Sister, take over now.
- Brother, thanks.
Let me tell you all openly.
We are from Bezawada.
We are very particular
about customs and manners.
Of course, we know that!
Bezawada means the Goddess
on top of the hill. And below--
Bava! No controversies, Bava.
So, you were saying something.
Listen. As per our custom,
we weigh the girl
during the match meeting,
and she brings gold worth her weight.
God, save me.
She is already heavy.
On top of it, weighing her!
You have no choice, sir.
Anyway, you need to pay after the wedding.
Consider it an advance booking.
Trust me!
We are okay with your challenge!
Here’s a 22-carat gold coin.
Seven-week ornaments.
Gold biscuits from Bombay.
These all are from Bengal.
Forget about weighing her.
The needle isn’t even moving.
Hey, Mr. Gold?
Don’t you have more gold at home?
It’s okay.
We’ll make up the difference with cash.
Glad you said that.
Hey, bring the cash.
Here is the money my Bava earned
from the tobacco business.
Well done!
- Jhansi ma'am!
- Sir!
Seize everything and seal it.
- I will sign and stamp it.
- Okay, sir.
We’re from the Income Tax Department.
You said they were our people
and made them part of the family.
Now everything is ruined!
Bava!
Stop the car.
- Do you need a lift, my son?
- Yes, of course.
Please get in.
Politicians don’t give
anything even if we ask.
You’re giving a lift without even asking.
We’re not able to give anything
to the people after being in power,
so I thought I’d at least give a lift.
You drive.
What do you do, man?
Should we have tea somewhere?
I was an IT officer until yesterday, sir.
So, if you were
an income tax officer until yesterday,
something happened yesterday.
What was it?
Morning…
Good morning, Jhansi ma’am.
What happened, Murthy sir?
He could have become a son-in-law,
but now he’s getting insulted.
Just because you have power in hand,
do you think you can go to anyone’s house?
Do you know who Mr. Jagga Rao is?
Officer, don’t tell him anything about me.
He’ll understand on his own soon.
Sure, sir.
Apologize to him if you want to
at least keep your job.
After doing a few raids
and achieving success in his career,
he started seeing stars,
his head held high.
I’ll bring him down.
I’ll bring everything down today.
Okay, your wish.
Stop!
What happened to your manhood?
Are you ashamed to touch my feet
in front of everyone?
Not acceptable.
Everyone in your department should know
what happens if someone targets me.
What is this, sir?
A tribute to honesty.
Watch and learn.
Take off my sandal with your hand
and lean your head against my leg.
Then I’ll think about your job.
Oh, God!
How could you beat such a powerful man?
This is how.
Now you can wear them, sir. Wear them.
What? Powerful?
In what way?
No matter how many millions he has,
he got beaten with a sandal by a guy
earning four thousand rupees a month.
Is he powerful, or am I?
What did you say?
That I got an attitude
after a few successful raids?
Success and failures are visitors.
They come and go.
Attitude is like our surname.
It stays with us until we die.
Krishna Murthy sir, give me a cigarette.
Sir, in here?
Doesn’t matter where,
after getting suspended.
By the way,
my name isn’t Parvataneni Papa Rao.
Bachchan.
Mr. Bachchan.
You must have heard the name.
Now you’ll remember it.
It’s not poverty
that afflicts this country, sir.
It’s black money.
And if the poor man is suffering,
it’s because of black money.
Still, if the country is running fine,
it’s because of sincere officers like you.
Sincere officers aren’t enough, sir.
We need sincere politicians.
Noted, sir.
By the way, why is your name Mr. Bachchan?
- Are you North Indian?
- Nothing like that, sir.
We’re pure Telugu, from Andhra Pradesh.
Do you know what happened on August 15th?
I’m a politician, and you’re asking me?
You are talking about August 15th, 1947.
I’m talking about August 15th, 1975.
That day, Sholay released
in 70mm stereophonic sound.
- So?
- Our lives changed from that day.
My father is a big fan of Sholay.
It's time for the show.
He watched it at least 100 times.
LAKSHMI TOURING TALKIES
Sholay… what a movie!
And my father came home in that madness…
My son, from today,
your name is Amitabh Bachchan.
Daddy, my name is Anand,
not Amitabh Bachchan.
Then you’re Anand Bachchan.
- And your friend’s name is Veeru.
- Me?
- And you?
- Thakur. Thakur of Ramgarh.
- What kind of name is that?
- You shut up, Basanti.
Now, who is she?
It’s you!
He changed our surname to Ramgarh
and attached a sidecar to my scooter.
I don’t pick up money
that’s thrown, even today.
- Deewaar.
- I have my mother with me.
I love you, my son.
Bachchan. Mr. Bachchan.
You must have heard the name.
Bachchan. My Bachchan.
With that, my name got fixed.
Couldn’t you change it after growing up?
He gave me birth.
Can’t I give him that much happiness?
From today,
not only am I a fan of that Bachchan,
- but I’m also a fan of this Bachchan.
- Thank you, sir.
If everything goes well, we’ll meet again.
Sure, sir.
Hey, I’m not getting a good card.
You're so dead today!
Hey, look, after a long time,
the Joker is coming.
Hey, you gambler!
Hey, Bachchan! You kiddo!
I’m the rising hand in this place.
Be careful with your words.
Your hand might be rising
in playing cards.
My hand rises in any game.
I’m the care-of-address for sarcasm.
I’ll smack your head off
if you play with me.
If not for bad luck,
how could a guy singing
in an orchestra become an IT officer?
And a guy owning 500 acres of land
is playing cards with these five people?
- Time, man. Time.
- It’s 1 p.m., brother. It’s lunchtime.
I will kick you on your back. Play now.
Basanti, look who’s here!
Thakur Baldev Singh!
You're back!
My lovely son.
Fresh up and come. Have lunch.
Not sure when you last ate.
My Bhagyalaxmi!
- My Bachchan!
- Bachchan is back!
- Brother, it's been so long!
- How many days are you camping here?
Should we start the orchestra again?
If you say yes, we can accept
programs for all the villages around.
- Stay at least till Vinayaka Chavithi.
- I’ll sign up for all the Navaratris.
Why only Chavithi?
I’ll be here until Dasara,
Diwali, and Sankranti.
They suspended me.
Such good news, my son.
I expected something when
the phone got disconnected.
The government may be late
in giving us what we deserve.
But when they have to
throw us out, they do it fast.
You said it right, my son.
I’ll take advances
for all the festivals then.
Go ahead and take them.
This is Kotipalli's Kumar Sanu.
He’ll hold the mic again
and sing the songs.
- Come, Mr. Pankaj.
- Greetings.
No puja can start in this temple unless
you play a cassette.
Which song are you playing today?
Seetha Kalyanam.
Our daughter is on her way.
You’ll get what you need
for the puja soon.
Hail Lord Ram.
- It’s time for a card game.
- Brother…
- What?
- Sister-in-law, bro.
Jikki!
Oh, no.
This Dorababu is there
to take you to the temple, right?
Why these adventures?
Now see what happened.
Go away.
One minute.
He will break the chain.
Hey, gambler! Get up!
Is he pulling her half-sari,
or my queen as well?
Both, bro.
Thank you.
You're welcome for a lifetime.
Has Bachchan become even more glamorous?
No! Men should be dark
and women should be fair.
That’s the rule.
Look at him. He looks fair and pale.
HAIL LORD RAM
Why are you chasing
after the bicycle chain, dude?
DONATION BOX
Hail Lord Ram.
Look, he put in twenty rupees!
As if he did something great.
What’s the big deal
about donating twenty rupees?
I can put in a hundred rupees.
It’s a sin. God is watching.
Whether a note or a word,
once it slips, it belongs to Lord Krishna.
Why talk about Krishna
in the temple of Ram?
- I will take my ten thousand.
- Even then,
you can only put money
in the donation box.
You can’t take it away. It’s a sin.
- My ten thousand.
- It's a sin.
Ten thousand. This sin is yours.
As if you are a rising hand, right?
I've talked about the Ramayana.
What did you understand?
Summarize it in one word.
Wives should always
listen to their husbands.
Since she didn’t listen to her husband,
Goddess Sita faced many difficulties.
This is what women
should learn from the Ramayana.
You stop, man.
Just because the wife
asked for a golden deer
or a monkey on the mountain,
a husband shouldn’t venture out.
That’s why he kidnapped Goddess Sita.
Trust.
The Ramayana is about trust.
Sita trusted that Ram
would come to Ashoka Vanam.
It’s not good for you to run after me
after I thanked you for helping me.
When did I run after you?
I’m standing right in front of you.
It’s amazing if a guy like this
runs after or stands in front.
Yeah, girl.
Tell me if you aren’t interested.
I will try for myself.
The guy is showing his intelligence.
Yes.
You can’t love with intelligence.
You fall in love without being aware.
And I fell!
Let’s go!
Hey girl, I’m talking to you. Stop…
Why are you walking in reverse,
unlike others?
It is said in the ancient scriptures
that someone born facing in reverse
should also walk in reverse.
Why don’t you tell me your name?
I won’t.
- I will make you reveal it.
- My tongue won’t slip.
You will slip.
- Jikki!
- What happened, Jikki?
Are you okay, Jikki?
Jikki… What is your name, Jikki?
Say it, Jikki!
Was it necessary? Jikki, Jikki, Jikki!
Jikki, you are very lucky!
Naughtily, like a design
She knotted me with playful looks
Oh, my girl, because of you
Music is playing in my heart
My heart took an oath after seeing you
Crossed the barrier and beaten heavily
Held the girl’s hand with strong resolve
How to stop after getting ignited?
My heart caught by you
Refusing to get down from the cloud
Carved your idol
And worshiped you every day, Jikki
I’m emphasizing
If our acquaintance
Turns into love and makes us a couple
No one is luckier than you
My heart took an oath after seeing you
Crossed the barrier and beaten heavily
The waistline that breaks my bravery
Kills me totally
The lip-line that was filled with spirits
Makes me go crazy
The thoughts that are refusing to leave me
Fighting them with the help of the sleep
The body that knew the taste of pleasure
Embrace it with your kisses
Listening to your voice
Not sure why hurry
Watching everything
Is noise your way?
Will your tactic work?
Will your plan click?
Don’t say no to me anymore
My heart took an oath after seeing you
Crossed the barrier and beaten heavily
Held the girl’s hand with strong resolve
How to stop after getting ignited?
My lovely lady
Is it harmful to give a kiss?
Sulking great or what?
Not wrong giving intimacy
The flames that approach me
Are burning me alive
In the girl’s heart filled with memories
I hear many murmurs
Your heart is a poem
Your word is a melody
Your name is so novel
Looks good luckily
If you behave well
I will say yes happily
Don’t keep me at a distance
My heart took an oath after seeing you
Crossed the barrier and beaten heavily
Held the girl’s hand with strong resolve
How to stop after getting ignited?
Hello, mic testing! One, two, three…
What is this, brother?
At the wedding, as well?
Dumbo.
A wedding can happen without festivities
but not without a card game.
It’s a rule.
Is it? Then give me a card as well.
- Brother?
- Yes.
You're playing a card game here.
What about after the wedding?
Chess, man.
Chess after the wedding.
They take one step, and we take one.
Welcome to all the people of Kotipalli.
For all the weddings
and celebrations, contact A1 Orchestra.
The first song in this music
program is "Bhale Manchi Roju."
And the singer is our local Balu.
A1 ORCHESTRA
What is this nuisance?
I've been hearing the same song play
since my wedding.
I cannot change my wife.
Ask him to change the song, at least.
Wish I get a queen in this game.
Take it.
Haven’t your parents come, Jikki?
- They are coming, behind me.
- He came.
He doesn’t have any other work.
Everyone in this village
is getting married.
Except for me and you.
What do you think?
There is a thin line
between hope and greed.
However, in life, it is different.
The abyss.
The what?
Let’s go.
He got it nicely.
What happened now, brother?
She said even if it’s greed,
I kept all my hopes on you.
I will not leave you despite all odds.
I can give it in writing.
Silly girl. She dies for me.
Why did this cycle chain fellow come here?
It’s Marwari’s wedding, right?
Maybe he came to sing some Hindi songs.
Come, let’s sit.
Hey, you!
He is Kumar Sanu of Kotipalli, bro.
Sings Hindi songs well.
He is singing intentionally.
He keeps singing "pyaar" all the time.
What is this "pyaar," anyway?
- "Pyaar" means pigeon.
- Is it?
Yes, Prema Pavuralu movie.
Haven’t we watched it?
Hey, his singing is so bad.
People are shameless, dude.
They’re just clapping
despite not understanding anything.
Let’s go.
Mr. Bachchan. I’m sure you heard the song.
Why so much attitude, Mr. Bachchan?
Why don’t you give some to your friends?
Yes. Look at how dull they’re looking.
You're right.
By the way, Ms. Jikki,
why do you need so much beauty?
Can’t you share some with your friends?
Look at how pale and dull they’re looking.
If the caterer is a friend,
the food tastes good.
This proverb doesn’t
match with the original.
It’s a proverb, not the Bhagavad Gita.
It can be changed.
- What is this?
- Memories.
In fifty years, you'll be telling our
grandchildren about how I pursued you.
Such wonderful memories.
Please leave me. I’m not comfortable.
Please forgive me.
I will never come near you again.
If my love is truly genuine,
you will come searching for me.
Until then…
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning.
I’m Srinivas from the
Income Tax Department.
Please sit.
We’re going on a raid
and need police support.
Sure.
On whom?
Muthyam Jaghayya.
- Muthyam Jaghayya?!
- Yes, sir.
Muthyam Jaghayya may be
new to you, but not to this area.
Three months ago, an excise officer
named Rama Krishna raided his warehouse.
Come on!
Crush them!
Don't spare even a single bottle.
Sir, it seems that he's an excise officer.
He destroyed all our stock.
No, sir.
If any officers come to my home,
it should be either to beg
or to seek my blessing.
But I came to arrest you.
I like you!
That’s why I like you!
- Sambashiva…
- Brother.
Please felicitate him.
He came from very far.
- I’m not scared of your silly deeds.
- You should be scared!
If any fool dares to come
to my house from now on,
they should die of fear,
not of my strength.
I have the entire system behind me.
You can’t do anything to me.
System?
When you were born, you were alone.
When you die, you will be alone.
By the time you understand this,
it will be too late, Tayaramma.
Tayaramma…
You did your duty very well.
But what about my duty?
Let me go!
Where were you when the excise officer
raided the warehouse?
I went to the temple
to perform the ritual, sir.
Instead of treating your boss like a God,
if you went to the temple,
what does that mean?
Am I a god or a fool?
In my anger, I should have
sent you to meet that God as well.
But 30 years of companionship…
makes me forgive you.
Go and beg at that same temple. Go!
Even after hearing this,
if you still want to go--
SI sir, have you found
any information about my husband?
It’s not right to make me
come here so many times.
You filed a complaint, right? Be patient.
We’re working on it.
He’s a government officer like you.
Would you be so indifferent
if something happened to one of your own?
- Why aren’t you speaking?
- One minute.
Now tell me, why did you come?
Someone picked my pocket
at the bus stand, sir.
There’s nothing to worry about.
File a complaint,
and we’ll look into it.
- Thank you, sir.
- Tell me, ma'am.
How many times do I have to
come to the police station with this baby?
I don’t know what to tell her
when she keeps asking
for her father every day.
When will you find him?
Please, tell me, sir. Tell me.
- Please, Uncle.
- Please, sir.
- Aunty…
- Who is it?
It’s me, Aunty. Jikki.
Your daughter called
and said she’d call back in five minutes.
Oh, I’m busy, dear.
My son, it seems your sister called.
Go check.
The phone at our house got disconnected,
and you’re getting connected
in the form of a PP number!
It seems like it’s all written in fate.
Hello, what are you looking at?
Let's go.
My sister is waiting on the other side.
I don't even know
where your house is, right?
- This boy…
- Bhagyalaxmi Aunty’s son.
- A call came in.
- Greetings.
Please come in, son.
I liked what you said
about the Ramayana the other day.
Give that to me.
What else would a retiree
or a suspended officer do, Aunty,
other than pray to God?
- Phone.
- Thank you.
Hey, ACDC? What are you doing
in this house, idiot?
I’m the one who found this house
and arranged for them to buy it.
And I’m guarding it 24/7 like a watchdog.
Why? Doesn’t this house have any dogs?
Sis, hello. How are you?
I heard you’ve been free
for a while now. Mom told me.
So we looked for a girl for you.
No need. I’ve already found one.
The girl is right here looking at me.
This girl is gorgeous.
Even if she looks angry,
her eyes still shine.
Even if she pouts, she looks kissable.
No, listen.
Tell him they're filthy rich.
They’ll offer a large dowry.
Your brother-in-law says they're wealthy
and will provide a fat dowry.
Sister, what we don’t earn isn’t ours.
Marrying for dowry is like prostitution.
DELUXE CASSETTE CENTER
Where did you find this birdie?
Not a normal birdie.
She is a beautiful bird.
Very famous in the neighborhood.
Take this. TDK 120 Minutes.
A-side Amitabh. B-side Rajesh Khanna.
Load the songs.
Though you’re from the Marwari family,
you’re living in Telugu land,
eating Telugu rice and Telugu lentils--
Don’t overreact, dude.
- My father is a Kishore Kumar fan.
- And you?
Gaddar.
I’m a Gaddar fan.
I keep singing his songs.
Her father loves music.
Hence, he named her Jikki.
She sings better than all of you.
- Load A-side. Leave the B-side to me.
- No, dude.
- A-side Amitabh Bachchan--
- B-side also Bachchan.
Okay.
My first love letter
to my last lover, Jikki.
In cinema, they express love in songs.
But this is my life, right?
So, I’m saying it in my own words.
That day, what got knotted
was not just your sari,
but also my heart.
One knot yours. One knot mine.
And if the third knot is tied by God,
what more do I need?
From the moment I saw you there,
wherever I look, it’s you.
ROMANCE
I will keep you in my heart
like a Yandamuri novel.
I will preserve you in my heart
like Ilaiyaraaja songs.
Boiled peanuts.
It will come, see.
Here it is.
Thank you.
Green chilies! She will bring.
Onion fritters!
Oh, God! What is this?
You drink once in a lifetime,
but you're making too much out of it.
Just because it’s a street fight,
you can’t go unprepared, right, Aunty?
You shut up, man.
What is that comparison?
Enough…
Take it, Uncle.
- You have a soft drink, right?
- Yes, Uncle.
- Cheers!
I’ve got a soft drink,
but where’s your drinking manners?
You’re having a drink
and a soft drink for me?
Your rule of
not drinking in the presence of elders
is amazing, Dorababu.
We have something
called culture. Right, Uncle?
Well said!
- What happened?
- Chemicals.
They are adding chemicals
to soft drinks as well.
My favorite, Kishore Kumar…
My family is searching for a girl for me.
- You are also anyway for Jikki--
- Shouldn’t there be some sense?
Uncle!
Who is he?
Bachchan from next door, Uncle.
He got suspended for taking bribes.
And he started the orchestra as always.
He is shameless, Uncle.
How dare he?
Can there be a competition between
Kishore Kumar and Kumar Sanu?
- Should I go and kill him?
- Jikki, ask him to stop his nuisance.
What’s this, buddy?
Why always Hindi songs?
Uncle, C major!
Let’s show how
a Telugu mass song sounds.
Okay, show me.
Master, hello?
I’m talking to you.
What's with all this nuisance?
From 6 p.m. to 8 p.m.,
we sing songs requested by listeners.
Any requests from you?
My father downstairs is
enjoying Kishore Kumar's songs.
Wow, Jikki, see how lucky you are!
Songs at your parents' place,
orchestra at your in-laws' place.
Jikki, you're really lucky.
My father doesn't appreciate all of this.
Normally, one might have a caste problem,
but it seems her father
has a taste problem instead.
That's true.
Our friend is called
Kotipalli's Kumar Sanu.
He won’t sing Kishore Kumar's songs.
Pack everything in two minutes and leave.
Forget me.
If you don’t leave in a minute,
you will land in trouble.
What happened?
If your father turns to the B-side
after completing the A-side,
he will realize that you are on my side.
- What happened?
- Enough for the day, Father.
Okay.
- Good night, Uncle.
- Good night.
My god. I see a cassette in your blouse.
And there’s something in the cassette.
Jikki!
Jikki, there's something in your blouse
that I want to see right now, right here.
It’s okay for her to hit me…
At least Jikki has finally touched me.
Jikki, let’s come up with an excuse
at home and go to the movies this evening.
Okay, dear.
What happened, dude?
You walked in so suddenly.
I wanted to see you.
A-side Rama Rao Garu, B-side
Nageshwara Rao Garu, load the songs.
Ghantasala sang for both.
So, why differentiate
between A-side and B-side?
I know, but he sings differently
for Rama Rao and Nageshwara Rao.
That’s what I call knowledge.
Not spoiling the business
while sitting next to me.
- So, completely on A-side and B-side--
- Move!
Are you only concerned
about the A-side and B-side,
or do you have any
intention of joining my side?
Tell me.
Once you reach Delhi, I expect a call
that my brother got the ticket.
You should make that call.
You're an MP,
your younger brother
is the Youth President,
and now you're seeking an
MLA ticket for your elder brother.
How can one family get so many positions?
Can members of one family
become Prime Ministers?
I cannot tolerate it
if you criticize the high command.
What will you do besides staying silent?
First, you need to get past this place
before taking any action.
You must have seen
leaders who manipulate votes.
This is Muthyam Jaghayya's area.
People disappear here.
I won’t be at this meeting.
Speak highly of my brother.
Mom, what's up?
The house is in darkness.
It’s okay.
Can you get me some water?
The fuse has blown.
Your father is handling it.
But the neighborhood has power,
and our house--
What's wrong, Mom?
Nothing, my son.
I slipped in the bathroom and fell.
You come. I'll serve you dinner.
What's with these injuries?
Son, please fix this fuse.
Dad, what happened to you?
Jikki, what are you doing here?
How did you get hurt?
Yeah, your mom said it right.
Slipped in the bathroom…
Did all of you slip in the bathroom
at the same time?
Jikki, what happened?
Earlier, Muthyam Jaghayya’s men came.
What’s the matter?
What do you guys want?
Muthyam Jaghayya's
meeting is happening outside.
We are drawing power from your house.
In that case, it won't handle the load,
and the fuse will blow.
Hey, if you utter another word,
forget the fuse,
your life might just blow away.
Bro, I found it.
I congratulate the National Party workers
on my behalf and on behalf of our party.
Speaking of our young leader
Muthyam Sambashiva Rao,
he holds a lot of respect
for elders and the aged.
He has great affection for women.
He is not a man of words but of action.
Forget about fuses blowing.
Soon, all of their fuses will be blown.
- Where are you doing, my son?
- Don't stop him, Bhagyalaxmi.
They need to understand that they'll face
consequences if they mess with Bachchan.
In a nutshell, he is strict.
The future MLA, our youth leader
Sambashiva Rao, will speak now.
My greetings to the people of Kotipalli.
I was born here!
I was raised here!
I will represent this
place in the assembly.
- We will give our lives!
- We will give our lives for our brother!
They were saying something.
Did you take it seriously?
We will see during the elections, okay?
- Hey! Sit down!
- Sit down!
- Hey…
- Hey!
I like you guys.
I thought you were joking when
you said you'd give your lives.
Come on, then.
Give it.
Come, come, come…
Instead of asking for power,
you forcefully took it…
And you assaulted my
parents when they resisted.
You should apologize in front of everyone.
Or else…
So they've made their decision…
What's yours?
Apology? Or a cigarette?
- Sorry.
- What?
Sorry.
The entire street witnessed
my parents being assaulted.
Now, the entire town should
hear your apology to them.
Each and every one of them.
Indukuri Suryanarayana aka Thakur.
My apologies to Indukuri
Suryanarayana aka Thakur.
Indukuri Bhagyalaxmi aka Basanti.
My apologies to Indukuri
Bhagyalaxmi aka Basanti.
Jik…
Indukuri Jikki.
My apologies to Indukuri Jikki.
Thank you so much.
You know, right?
Since I didn't like his methods,
I resigned as a clerk to Muthyam Jaghayya
and started serving at the temple.
Why deal with such a person?
And you guys? At least you
should have intervened.
They announced her name on the microphone.
Once she steps out of her house,
the public will scrutinize her
and comment on her.
It's Bachchan who is at fault, Uncle.
He tried to impress the girl
and messed with them.
If I had known about the issue,
I could have easily
handled Muthyam Jaghayya.
A true man stands not just
by his parents but also by a girl.
Bachchan didn't do anything wrong, Dad.
He corrected the mistake.
- You are singing well. Don't feel bad.
- It's my training. What do you think?
These guys always stick around here.
Hey, all the ladies come to one side.
Our friend isn't able to breathe.
The entire women's group has
come for one cassette recording.
We should limit one person to
one cassette, just like a movie ticket.
- Correct.
- Why?
So that each one of you
can flirt with one girl?
We shouldn't allow girls like you,
who can't tell the difference
between a chocolate and a cassette.
- On the A-side, Chiranjeevi songs.
- Do you want Balakrishna on the B-side?
B-side… Leave that to him.
Aunty, there's a phone call for you!
Bava is always negative. Listen to me.
- It's just some sound.
- What happened, Jikki?
It slipped out of my hand.
It's okay if it slipped
out of your hand, ma'am.
You will be in trouble if your leg slips.
A phone call has come.
Aunty, a phone call for you.
I can't hear you, dear. Come in.
Where are you, Aunty?
Here…
A phone call for you.
- Turn this side.
- Who are you talking to, my son?
My sister.
Well, the phone has been
dead for the last three days.
Who are you talking to?
That's why, I'm not able to hear anything.
Sister, I will call you later,
the phone is dead.
Thank you.
My parents are looking
for potential matches for me.
- Let them.
- Tomorrow they are coming home to see me.
- Aren't you scared, man?
Not at all.
Unless they see a few matches,
how will your father know my specialty?
Yeah, big specialty.
You are a Kumar Sanu fan.
He is a Kishore Kumar fan.
I'm getting killed for playing
the orchestra between both of you.
Really?
Then, let's do something.
This time, I will play the
chorus to your orchestra, okay?
- What?
- It means…
Mr. Pankaj, your…
Everyone is saying that
the girl is good.
- If this match works out…
- Greetings.
He is Mr. Chandi Das, and his
son is in the diamond business.
Your daughter is like gold…
They make a perfect match. That's
why I approached them for an alliance.
Thanks for that.
After the priest has said okay,
what questions will I have?
We will come to see
the girl on an auspicious day.
- Okay.
- The priest manages every
celebration in our family.
His word is as trustworthy as an ISI mark.
While he performs the puja in the temple,
I hear the song belongs to you.
Nothing like that.
Jikki, you said that you would persuade
your father to arrange our marriage.
What happened?
This won't work out.
Let's get married first,
and then we can convince him.
Once we're married,
he'll have no choice but to accept it.
This cassette
doesn't belong to him, madam.
Yeah, from now on, the girl also
doesn't belong to him. Let's go, Son.
What kind of match
did your father arrange?
Such trouble for this match?
I went to hear Bhagavatam at the temple…
and her story was exposed. It's shameful!
While everyone respects me,
she dragged me down.
Why is Jikki being
blamed for this, Uncle?
She is as innocent
as a queen in a deck of cards.
It's him who messed everything up.
This is a matter between two families.
I will not tolerate any
outsider intervening.
Look how your son is behaving!
Forget their words.
I will look after Jikki
like my own daughter.
Please allow them to get married, brother.
How can we agree?
He doesn't even have a job.
- It's all because of this stupid phone.
- Correct, Uncle.
Hello…
Excuse me. I'm calling from
the Income Tax Department.
- Can I speak to Mr. Bachchan, please?
- Dorababu!
It's cards playing in the…
Hey, stop.
Uncle, this guy is talking in English.
Yes?
This is the Deputy Commissioner
of the Income Tax Department.
Mr. Bachchan's suspension
has been lifted. Please inform him.
Okay.
Bachchan, it's your call.
You said the phone was stupid, right?
Tell them that I'm not here.
You need to take this call.
- Yes, Bachchan speaking.
- Your suspension has been lifted.
Please return
and resume your duties urgently.
- Sure, sir. Thank you.
- Welcome.
You tell them yourself.
It's from the Income Tax Department.
My suspension has been lifted, Dad.
They asked me to join back immediately.
What great news, Son!
What do you say now?
Mr. Bachchan.
You must've heard the name.
You raised your daughter
with so much love.
I will cherish
and care for her as my life.
Please allow us to get married.
Alright.
Let's set the date.
Congratulations, dear!
- Uncle, have you gone mad?
- Keep the phone aside.
Brother…
What's happening, dude?
He has ruined your chances, bro.
A big fair in the girl's beauty
And Bappi Lahiri in Bachchan's voice
Just at a gesture
Disco starts playing
And the concert won't stop till dawn
A love duet
In Telugu, Tamil, and Hindi
The drop of sweat will play to the music
Eyelids should beat like the drums
My bangles will sing a ghazal
The noise of the cot should play a chorus
The audience will throw Jasmine flowers
Once more, more, more…
Close the door, door, door…
When kissing, the surrounding villages
Play on the mic
Till the sun rises
A big fair in the girl's beauty
And Bappi Lahiri in Bachchan's voice
Why the shyness on your pink cheeks?
Since you hid sharpness
In your sharp looks
When I pinch your waistline
Fingers learn music
And we get into…
Pillow business under full moon
Jhanak! Jhanak! Jhanak!
And we play Nattuvangam
Eyelids should beat like the drums
My bangles will sing a ghazal
The noise of the cot should play a chorus
The audience will throw Jasmine flowers
Once more, more, more…
Close the door, door, door…
When kissing, the surrounding villages
Play on the mic
Till the sun rises
A big fair in the girl's beauty
And Bappi Lahiri in Bachchan's voice
How you hold my life
At ransom at the edge of your sari
While I hold with my fingers
You are the world for me
I smelt like an ice cream
Filled with youth in mid-summer
Let the heat be cold
And Varanda hold it
Hug me and sing an Asha Bhosle tune
Eyelids should beat like the drums
My bangles will sing a ghazal
The noise of the cot should play a chorus
The audience will throw Jasmine flowers
Once more, more, more…
Close the door, door, door…
When kissing, the surrounding villages
Play on the mic
Till the sun rises
A big fair in the girl's beauty
And Bappi Lahiri in Bachchan's voice
Congratulations.
You are the first officer to join
on promotion after a suspension.
Thank you, sir.
You must conduct
an income tax raid on a big shot.
My wedding is in four days, sir.
The raid can be completed in a day.
You can return by the evening.
- Please try to understand, sir.
- Bachchan!
You've been taken back
into the department for this raid only.
I will assign the team. Get ready.
- By the way, sir, who should I raid?
- It's highly confidential.
They said they would inform me
an hour before informing you.
No problem, sir. For me,
the work is important. Not the name.
The king has been checkmated, Tayaramma!
- Hello?
- Delhi Party Office.
So, what's the news from Delhi?
Bad news. They are not
giving the MLA ticket to your brother.
- Are you in your senses?
- Yes.
I'm an MP overseeing seven MLAs.
Party offices could be burnt down
if anyone messes with me.
You're overestimating
yourself, Mr. Jaghayya.
An anonymous person came
to your brother's public meeting…
and tried to burn
everything down with petrol.
And you couldn't do anything about it.
How can you threaten us in Delhi?
Goodbye.
What happened at your meeting?
Brother…
What happened at your meeting that night?
I want him in front of me within
the next hour, no matter where he is.
Why are you just standing there? Go now!
We have our wedding
in the next four days--
I will come back in two days.
I'm scared.
Come on, silly girl.
Every girl gets butterflies
before their wedding.
At times like this, you should…
- Did it come down?
- You will come, right?
You will soon find out.
We searched everywhere, sir.
We couldn't find him.
I don't know. I need him.
We looked for him in the market
as well, brother. He is not there…
I don't want to hear anything. I need him!
We scanned the entire town,
brother. He is not to be seen.
I need him!
Brother, it seems
his name is Bachchan.
He is an income tax officer.
He has been singing in
an orchestra since he was suspended.
Coward.
How did you let him go
after what happened?
Had he been in front of me…
He is the guy.
While we are searching
for him all around…
why did he walk in himself
along with his battalion?
Sambashiva…
isn't it a miracle?
While we're searching for him all around…
why did he walk in
along with his battalion?
We're from the
Income Tax Department.
And a raid is scheduled to begin
at your house in a few minutes.
Furthermore, all our names are
registered at Ayakar Bhavan, New Delhi.
Any harm to us will come
at a steep cost to you.
Officers, please announce
the rules before we start the raid.
Until the raid is completed,
no one should leave the house.
And those outside cannot enter.
The searches will occur
daily from 6:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m.
You won't be disturbed after that.
Only female staff
will question the women.
All your phones will be disconnected.
We will only use them when necessary.
- Sujata Garu and team…
- Yes, sir!
Please go in and speak to the ladies.
Once they indicate they are comfortable,
let us know, and then we will enter.
Okay, sir.
- Subhash and team…
- Yes, sir!
Close all the doors around us.
No one should enter the house.
- Okay? Right.
- Okay, sir.
What are you watching, brother?
Are they really going
to come in and raid us?
Hey, officer. Enough of this circus.
A three-time MP.
A two-time MLA.
And former minister.
That's my history and track record.
Do you know
who you're messing around with?
With five years of service…
I've conducted 72 raids…
and seized over three billion
in black money.
I've put an end to
72 "histories" like you.
Maybe you haven't encountered
an officer like me in your career,
but I've dealt with
many politicians like you in mine.
This raid might be new for you,
but not for me.
Sir, the women in the house are
comfortable. We can proceed now.
Come on, let's start the search.
Hope the lady officers
have informed you about us.
We need to know who you all are.
Please introduce
yourselves with your names.
My name is Prabhavathi,
wife of Muthyam Jaghayya.
My name is Chennakesava.
I'm Muthyam Jaghayya's second brother.
She is my wife, name…
Sparsha, the touch.
Touch me, and you'll get a shock.
He is my elder brother.
Name…
I know him very well.
How are you, sir?
I'm Srilatha.
Muthyam Sambashiva's better half.
She is our elder sister…
Are these all the family members,
or is there anyone else?
There is, and he is coming.
Who are you?
Presenting, cine hero
Sisindri Chittibabu Garu.
I haven't seen him in any movie.
I haven't acted in any movie, yet.
- Officers!
- Yes, sir.
- You can begin the search.
- Okay, sir.
It's all a waste of time.
What will we get?
Searching in sir's house is like
putting our hand in God's treasures.
That's true.
My God!
This bedroom is so huge.
This is the first time I've come
for a raid to such a big house.
Me too.
Muthyam Jaghayya is like a pure gem, sir.
You are unnecessarily
suspecting and insulting him.
You are young.
And you have a bright future.
Why do you want to
mess with these big people?
I want people who work.
Not the ones who give bits of advice.
Please keep your advice
and opinions under Muthyam Jaghayya's…
Raja… Maharaja…
You can't find anything here, Raja.
Please, go back, Raja.
We've searched everywhere, sir.
Couldn't find anything.
We've searched everything, sir.
Neither could we, sir.
Looks like there is
a lot of heat in your body.
You won't find anything, Raja.
Have some buttermilk and then leave.
We've checked the racks and shelves
in all the rooms, sir.
We couldn't find anything.
Search again,
but this time, look meticulously
- in all the unusual places.
- Okay.
Sir, we searched the backyard,
haystack, and everywhere.
- Yes, sir.
- Everything is clean.
We didn't find anything.
Check the well, unused vessels,
and old cars if there are any.
- We need to find something, okay?
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
It seems like your fire
has died down, officer.
Should I give you some?
Thanks.
I have a habit of repaying
a hundred times over.
The government pays me a salary
in the thousands,
and I pay it back
by finding black money worth millions.
If you give me the fire…
I will set it ablaze.
You can say as many dialogues as you want,
but you won’t find anything here.
Listen to me and go back,
my cute little boy.
We searched the entire house, sir.
We couldn't find anything.
Yes, sir. They have receipts
for whatever we've found.
We can't seize them--
Govinda! Govinda!
Bachchan is now deflated,
and the people who came with him
turned out to be useless.
Tayaramma, thank you for your blessings.
Why don't you all do something?
Stand in line behind me
and lick my armpits!
What else can you do,
other than be the lost goat in a carnival?
There's nothing you can do.
You forgive the goat that lost its way,
and you sacrifice the goat
that made a mistake.
We have enough time for that.
They call it something in Delhi, right?
- Ayyagaru Bhavan.
- It's Ayakar Bhavan, Brother.
Whatever it is.
Call them…
and tell them that you have come to
the wrong address, and made a mistake.
You'll apologize by falling
at Muthyam Jaghayya's feet and then leave.
Call them at once!
- Hello.
- Good afternoon, sir.
- Bachchan speaking, sir.
- Yes?
We discovered a large amount
of cash and gold
at Mr. Muthyam Jaghayya's house, sir.
Hey!
We'll need more time
to recover everything.
Hey, what are you saying?
- Is everything okay?
- Everything is under control, sir.
- Is Mr. Jaghayya giving you trouble?
- Not really, sir.
He and his family are cooperating well.
We are expecting big numbers.
Continue the search.
- Thank you, sir.
- Take your own time.
Sure, sir.
What is this new drama?
Have you given up on your life?
Mr. Jaghayya, do you know
why a tongue slips often?
Because the tongue is wet.
If you were truly honest,
you would never tell us to leave.
You should say,
"Come in if you have the courage."
Similarly, you wouldn’t say,
"You won’t find anything."
You should say,
"There is nothing in this house."
You can hide the treasures,
but you can’t hide your words.
This guy wants to mess with us.
Show him what happens when
we start messing around, just once.
Throw him out!
Hey!
Sambashiva, take care of this guy.
We'll handle the consequences!
Sambashiva, as your brother mentioned,
fate has a great sense of humor.
You can't escape me,
no matter what you do.
I'll break every bone in the
body and extract everything.
The one who protects
the borders is not the only soldier.
The one who safeguards
wealth is also a soldier.
I'll show that the Income Tax Department
is as formidable as the Indian Army.
Everyone in the house can breathe
freely for the next five minutes.
After that, every breath
you take will be accounted for.
It seems the clothes have become tight.
You may want to loosen your buttons.
You'll be able to breathe.
- Officers…
- Yes, sir.
We will leave after we break
his track record and seal his history.
The true raid is going to start now.
And it's going to be a historic one.
- Officers…
- Sir.
Get ready to create history.
Please tell me, Mr. Jaghayya.
Why did you call me?
I will pay you half a million.
Stop the raid and leave.
I won't stop even if you
pay fifty million rupees.
You madman!
Do you know how many zeros
there are in half a million?
You can't buy me
by increasing the zeros in the bribe.
You need to bribe to get
your pension after retirement.
Happiness is only in zeros.
Your honesty won't earn you anything.
No matter the zeros in your bank account.
You can only eat off a golden plate,
not the golden plate itself.
A selfish person may enjoy a good meal,
but an honest one will
enjoy a good night's sleep.
Do you know what will
happen if I break free?
Break free, Mr. Jaghayya.
I want to see it happen once.
Please.
Listen, officers. Your boss
isn't agreeing to the truce.
So I'm talking to the soldiers now.
You can keep
whatever gold you find inside.
End the raid and go home.
Go on and live your life.
- What do we do now?
- What now?
No, everyone is hesitating.
However, my vote is for Mr. Jaghayya.
Yes, sir.
My father needs heart surgery
that costs 100,000 rupees.
My salary is only 3,500.
I'm afraid his heart might give out
before I can earn enough, sir.
I need to arrange my sister's marriage.
They are asking for a dowry of 200,000.
If dowry isn't a crime,
how can bribery be a crime, sir?
This is my first raid,
and already they're offering a bribe.
This is my first raid as well,
and life will be sorted
after just one raid.
Such opportunities won't come again.
I'm fine with it as well.
This could be my last raid.
I'm retiring next month.
I have never taken a bribe
and won't take one now.
Thank God, one less
person to share the loot.
What about you?
I don’t want to break my back over this.
I'm okay with this.
Okay.
Why should you get rich alone?
I feel the same.
Double okay.
I feel the same way as well.
Everyone has needs.
But only a few get opportunities.
One raid won't change the country.
But it can change our lives.
That's why we should prosper,
even if we're in the wrong.
Once we decide to become robbers,
we shouldn't settle for small change,
we should aim for the treasure chest.
We are prepared,
even if it's two billion.
If the ED offers the same,
and if they seize everything?
I didn't expect this twist.
My goodness! Mr. Bachchan.
Let's seize a substantial
amount and then make our offer.
- What do you guys say?
- Yes, sir.
- Don't leave a single corner untouched.
- Okay, sir.
Whatever one digs up belongs to them.
- Whatever one obtains is theirs.
- Yes, sir.
Break down the walls.
Break open the lockers.
If anyone interferes, break their bones.
Yes, sir!
I spoke to all the officers.
Don't worry. Don't be afraid.
You cannot buy us
with money, Mr. Jaghayya.
The raid will continue as it was planned.
What we wear isn't just pants
and shirts, but morality and honesty.
What is this nonsense, Dad?
What is happening, sir?
- Officers, attack!
- Sir! Yes, sir!
Move away!
Mr. Ram Murthy and Mr. Subba Rayudu…
The village headmaster
and the postmaster…
They will be our witnesses.
Sir, we have nothing against you.
You are like a God to us.
- Please forgive us.
- Greetings, brother.
Get up.
Grandma, how are you
related to Muthyam Jaghayya?
Grandma, I'm talking to you.
Hey, man. Who are you?
- We are from the Income Tax Department.
- Oh, really?
I thought so.
I knew something like this would
happen to our Jaghayya one day.
Ruined, right?
You've destroyed everything.
Why did you come into
my room in the first place?
I was happily listening to songs…
and reminiscing about my Sekhar.
And now this has been ruined.
And that wall has grown taller.
- Is Sekhar your husband?
- No.
My boyfriend.
He used to look like Nageshwara Rao.
In those days--
You mentioned that
the wall has gotten taller.
Which wall is that?
You ruined my songs, and now
you're asking me questions? I won't say!
Grandma, please tell me.
I will tell you only
if I listen to my song.
- No, please understand.
- What do you mean?
I haven't had any experiences with him.
Won't you allow me
to live in his memories?
I must listen to that song now.
That's a good one.
You did it exactly like Akkineni.
Can you dance like him as well?
- Dance?
- Don't you want to see the wall?
I do.
And I want to see Akkineni's dance moves.
Come on, dance!
- You want to see the wall, right?
- Yes.
- Come with me.
- Please.
The wall that covered
my mansion of dreams.
Should we destroy it?
- Naresh…
- Sir!
Brother, they should
stop the raid after 6:00 p.m.
- Little brother…
- Yes?
You can't continue
the raid after 6:00 p.m.
Those were your rules.
After 6:00 p.m. means dusk.
It's the time when demons come out.
And here, monsters roam freely.
And I'm that monster!
Hiranyakasupundaa!
- Action!
- Son, Prahlada…
Where is your Hari?
Hey, Guruji, I'm asking you,
where is he?
- Hey, Guruji, is your Hari in this?
- Yes.
- Is he there in that pillar?
- Then, show me.
- Don't wait. Kill him!
Hari!
- Is Hari in this as well?
- Yes.
Come out, man.
Why isn't he present here?
Where is your Hari?
Where does he exist?
He may be in this, my lord.
- Are you sure?
- Hundred percent.
Hey, Hari. Come out.
So much money?
Hey, Srimannarayana.
You are truly miraculous.
- Please include this in the account.
- Okay, sir.
All that's here is waste paper.
Where is your Sri Hari?
He might be in that, my Lord.
- Where?
- In the corner, near that wall.
- Then, let's go.
- Please, come.
I will not spare Sri Hari today.
Why did you bring me here?
- Is your Sri Hari present in this?
- Confirmed, my Lord. He is in this.
Really?
Do it again.
Come out, man!
You have such strength, my Lord.
Once more.
Hey, Hari, what are you doing inside?
Why is the "Goddess of Wealth" appearing
when I call for Hari?
Thanks, my Lord.
Take everything out
and add it to the account.
Yes, sir.
Open your mouth.
These big officers, who used to fear us,
have entered our house.
If they're left alone,
they might enter our bedrooms next.
Hey, why are you bothered?
Just eat and be quiet.
Father, how will you produce a film
with me as the hero
if they take all your money?
Of course, the sky is the limit for
our movie, and the budget is unlimited.
- Well said…
- Have your food.
Okay.
Why did you tell the
officer about the wall, Mom?
Why did you build that
wall so tall, my son?
You oldie, shut up and eat!
We should deal with this Guruji first.
He and his nonsensical guidance.
Brother, you can say anything to me.
But I won't tolerate it if you say
even a word against my Guruji.
Look at him, he hasn't even taken off
the crown after all that happened.
Apparently, Rama Rao Garu used to remove
the crown only at the end of the day.
I'm the same.
I'll remove it before sleeping.
Guruji…
Rama Rao Garu might accept
if you remove the crown, but I won't.
How can you blame us
when you have all the money?
If you don't like it, you can play
the role of a beggar or a dumb man.
Don't act funny during my training.
- Hey, Guruji…
- What?
- If you utter another word--
- Hey!
Stop now!
I want jalebi.
No, Mom. It has sugar.
If you don't give me jalebi now,
I will have a meeting with him tomorrow.
Mom!
What a funny family!
How can she eat after all this?
Because nothing is going to happen
from here on out!
Also, no one should step out
of their rooms tonight, no matter what.
Close the doors tightly and sleep well.
You eat, Mom.
Just a little bit, okay?
Raja… Maharaja!
Wake up, Raja.
You are sleeping peacefully
after keeping us sleepless.
Very true.
You sleep so well after
taking away all our money.
The seized money.
Tell us where you hid our money.
Why are you talking to him, Brother?
Let's complain to the
department and get him arrested.
Hey, the door is unlocked.
- Oh, no! Where's the money?
- Where is it?
Did Jaghayya steal it?
Sir, there's nothing left
in the place we stored it.
This is unjust, sir.
Why are you not talking?
What can he say after
hiding away all that money?
He made so many exaggerated claims.
What else? Work is worship.
A true form of honesty.
- And this is his real form.
- Yeah.
I've been saying this from the beginning.
But you all came here in the name of
a raid. Look at what's happened now.
Moreover, he kept saying,
"You must have heard my name"
once every ten minutes.
Now, he'll get a bad reputation.
Oh, God! Did you take
away my share as well?
What about all my dreams?
All the hopes that I had?
- I thought all those gold coins were mine.
- How could you think they were all yours?
I believed those gold coins were mine.
I had so many dreams. Now the coins
are gone and only the dreams remain.
You didn't listen when he
offered a share in the gold coins…
Instead, you fell into his trap. Look now!
- Well said.
- Thank you, sir.
Speaking about magic,
do you know any magic?
You made all the money
disappear overnight.
Looks like you're a magician.
Speak up.
They are asking, right? Speak.
Hey, where are you going
without giving an answer?
Will he get imprisoned for life
because of this?
He could receive a death sentence for
the robbery committed here.
Come.
Where are you going without answering?
Where are you going, man?
We will file a case against
you and put you on the streets.
You will go to Tihar Jail
directly from there.
We are asking you something.
Answer.
As you all said,
I will perform a magic trick.
I'll demonstrate it right now.
- It seems he will show something.
- Magic?
So, let's begin the magic show.
One of the enthusiastic men
should come ahead with a crowbar.
This will have only two bullets.
There are so many people here.
The first bullet will hit only one
person, but everyone will be afraid.
The second bullet can hit anyone.
What is this? Who are they?
Hey, who are all of you?
How did they get here?
Your reaction is not needed now.
We need my action.
Next item, from our department…
Me, me, me.
That enthusiastic young man is me.
Now go there, say the mantra
I told you, and move your hand.
Abracadabra magic.
Sir, all of our money is here.
The money, sir.
I thought of thrashing them immediately.
However, an audience should witness
and understand my capabilities, right?
It's best to watch a cricket match live
instead of reading about it
in the newspaper the next day.
As I mentioned before,
I'm making you an offer.
Neither the officers who came with me
nor the police will oppose you.
I alone will stand against you.
If they dare, tell your men to
cross me and take your money away.
If they dare touch even a penny…
I swear, I'll abandon everything.
- What is he saying?
- Oh, my…
I won't fight your men in the shadows.
I'll take them down right
in the heart of your home.
Send them.
Sir…
Clarity!
I hope you are getting clarity about me.
Have you got it?
I hope you are getting it.
Cricket match… live!
As you said, I'm a magician.
But not a magician who
plays tricks or just talks.
I'm a real magician.
My character is not to
do my duty for the shares.
I can't sacrifice
my life on the field.
But I won't leave a single rupee behind.
If you want to work with me,
you must be like me.
What, dear?
You asked me to come so urgently.
I left Chitralahari on the TV
for this and came.
Light it.
Me, smoking? Are you mad?
Have it once for me, please.
- I will be caught by its smell.
- You won't be caught.
Chew a few guava leaves while going home.
Light it.
This is not an incense stick.
It’s a cigarette. Keep it in your mouth.
Nothing will happen.
Inhale in…
I feel his presence next to me
when I inhale this.
I feel like this cigarette
will become a habit, dear.
I'm unable to live without him.
Stupid girl.
Why are you sad when your wedding
is just two days away?
Everything will be alright.
Please don't cry.
- How are the wedding preparations going?
- Everything is going well.
Are you okay with having
the wedding in Marwari style?
How does it matter which style we choose,
as long as they like each other?
If the wedding happens
at an auspicious time, it is good.
Not the wedding.
You should rather prepare for his funeral.
Shut up!
Why talk nonsense
when we are preparing for the wedding?
Set your emotions aside and listen.
I've heard that your Bachchan
led a raid on Muthyam Jaghayya,
taking our headmaster
and postmaster as witnesses.
That's how the news got out.
He is Muthyam Jaghayya.
You must have heard his name.
I don't know how he will handle your son.
Dad, you worked for him for 30 years.
Speak to him once.
I'm sure he will listen to you.
He may listen to your father,
but my son will not listen to anyone.
You may be sad today but
will be proud of him tomorrow.
Oh, no! What a build-up!
It’s difficult to deal with them.
Culture-less family.
YANDAMURI VEERENDRANATH
LADY IN THE MOONLIGHT
Jikki…
How are you, Jikki?
Master, how did you recognize me?
Not just your word…
I can hear your breath as well.
How are you?
I’m drowned in work all day
and floating in your memories at night.
I'm feeling very scared.
I’m not sure
what they are talking about here.
Oh, my darling,
most people are not afraid of problems
but of rumors and gossip.
Most of the jobless
would be busy with this work.
These guys may be paid to spread rumors
in the future.
It makes me want to laugh.
You don't know about Muthyam Jaghayya.
They don't know about this Bachchan.
By the way, Jikki,
what is the Ramayana about?
Trust.
The trust Sita had that Ram would come.
Then why are you scared?
It is not Sita
who is in Lanka right now. It is Ram.
That's why I'm scared.
Your logic always amazes me.
Isn't this why
I'm head over heels in love with you?
Why don't you shut me up
with your kisses…
instead of logic?
Jikki, please.
Hey, cutie pie, who looks like a dove
Wear a bindi and wrap a silk sari
Team up and wrap me like my own
Tell me where your secret mole is
Hey, cutie pie, who looks like a dove
Wear a bindi and wrap a silk sari
Team up and wrap me like my own
Tell me where your secret mole is
Like all your naughty acts
But told you that you have to wait
But I came even before you said
Should I wet your shining lips
With all the love?
Should I spend all my time
In your enchanting beauty?
Should I dive into the depths
Of the ocean of your beauty?
Should I touch the clouds of the music?
Should I signal you…
And raise hopes in you?
When the wind makes the noise
Should I be the reason for you
To change the clothes?
Should I sneak in like
A thief in the evening?
Should I play pillow fights
With your youth?
Should I hug the beauty
With the speed of love?
Should I quench the thirst
In your thoughts?
Should I shed inhibitions…
Under the blue sky?
Should I sing a tune in our union
And give you a new thrill?
What happened, Aunty?
You didn't ask for coffee today.
Are you not feeling well?
Aunty?
Sambashiva!
Why did you do this, Mom?
I wanted to see you one more time,
and now you've made it so
that I'll never see you again!
- You should cry as well.
- I can't produce any tears.
You inherit property only if you cry.
I can’t bear this, Aunty!
You wanted to see the necklace
you wear around my neck. Meanwhile…
You said your "seven-week ornaments"
belong to me.
You gave me your mother's name
and promised to transfer
the rice mill to me.
And then you left abruptly, Mom!
They aren't mourning her demise
but the loss of the properties.
- Guruji!
- Sishya.
It’s time to showcase my training
and your timing.
The more you cry,
the more properties you get.
Just say "action," Guruji,
and I’ll deliver
an Oscar-worthy performance.
Action.
Grandma!
Oh, my grandma…
You always said you’d
give me millions to make a movie.
And now we have to face
your sudden death, Grandma!
You joined the stars before
seeing my stardom, Grandma.
You called "pack up"
before I could put on my makeup, Grandma!
- Get up, Sishya…
- Your mother--
Mothers give birth to their children.
My mother gave me life through her death.
It's time for you to stop this raid.
Bad luck.
Once the doctor confirms it,
pack your bags.
Leave the sealed bags behind
and go from here.
Moreover, the party workers, leaders…
ministers, VIPs…
and even the CM will be arriving soon.
Grandma!
You wanted to see me on the silver
screen even if it meant selling your gold.
Wake up, Grandma!
Please look at your grandson once,
Grandma.
Wake up, Grandma!
Wake up!
Grandma woke up!
Doctor, it's a medical miracle.
Daddy, Grandma is alive.
It was a cardiac arrest,
but CPR was done at the right time.
Who did this?
My disciple struck her heart
at just the right moment and revived her.
Truly, your mother is extraordinary.
Not just for you, but for many others,
as she allowed this raid
to continue and potentially saved lives.
She's a great woman.
My heartfelt condolences to you
on your mother's recovery.
- Officers…
- Yes, sir!
- Get back to work!
- Okay, sir!
I told him to bring a character to life,
but he brought the dead back to life.
If your mother is alive today,
it's solely due to my training.
Yes, sir.
At least increase my
salary from this month, sir.
Expenses are at an all-time high--
- Grandma…
- What happened, Aunty?
How did I sleep as if I
had taken sleeping pills?
What, Guruji? What’s the news?
Officer Srinivas reporting, sir.
Why did you take so long to report?
Yes, sir. I arrived here three months ago.
Actually, what happened is…
What's wrong, dear?
While everyone else is celebrating
Karwa Chauth, you're sitting alone.
If everything had been fine, you would
have been with our son-in-law today.
It's okay.
They say that when the man is not around,
you can look at his picture.
But we perform Karwa Chauth for
the husband's well-being.
- How can she--
- He said a picture is enough, right?
We have a picture of our son
at home where he looks like a hero.
Come, I'll show you.
- Come… Come!
- Come, dear.
Jikki, what are you doing here?
Are you thinking of jumping just because
Bachchan didn't come to the wedding?
Life is precious, Jikki.
They say when God closes a door,
a window opens.
You should look at the windows.
Would you come with me?
Where?
Wherever I go!
Shouldn't we inform your dad before
making such a significant decision?
No need!
My life, my decision.
Will you come or not?
I will come anywhere, and do anything.
Forget about this house.
I have nothing to do with this world!
Nothing…
You for me
and me for you. Let's go.
Let's go.
What the hell!
You guys have turned my house
into a choultry.
Go ahead…
How many days, sir?
No matter how much we search,
we can't find anything.
Yes, sir.
- Hello!
- I need to meet Mr. Bachchan.
How are you coming in without permission?
Inform him that Jikki is here.
What brings you here?
I'm Mr. Bachchan's fiancée.
Sir is inside, ma'am. One minute.
Jikki. What happened?
Why did you come here?
Jikki!
What happened, dear?
Tell me what happened.
This is the last kiss to Bachchan.
Tomorrow Dorababu
will get his first kiss.
First kiss…
What happened, dear?
You can't come.
I can't stop myself from coming.
Today is our first Karva Chauth.
Everyone sees the moon.
I came to see you.
What should I do now?
My heart goes mad without your company…
Dorababu.
Yes, darling.
Take it.
Silly girl!
Where's the strainer?
The son-in-law is here.
My wedding is the day after tomorrow.
You should come.
Not possible.
My wedding is on the same day
and at the same time.
Should I leave?
You can leave without worry.
I'll come as well.
Who are you, dear?
It's me, Uncle.
I'm Mr. Pandey's daughter,
who used to work with you.
I'm getting married
to Bachchan the day after tomorrow.
I came here because
today is Karva Chauth--
It's okay, dear.
This is your home.
You can come and go anytime you want.
But your husband might not agree.
He might talk about rules.
No one really follows rules here anyway.
Jikki, please leave now.
You once sent me a nose pin as a
gift in my childhood, with my father.
Can you please send my husband
to my wedding, the day after tomorrow?
Please.
You silly girl.
This time, I'll send him along
with a marriage necklace.
May you have a blessed
and long married life.
I'm so fortunate, Tayaramma…
Tayaramma…
I'm very happy, Tayaramma…
I found him easily, Tayaramma…
Tayaramma…
Well, Mr. Jaghayya, you sing very well.
Anyway, from tomorrow you'll
have to make a living by singing.
Meet me after the raid is over.
I'll give you a chance in our band, okay?
And don't forget to bring your Tayaramma
with you. You can sing a duet with her.
A duet. Is that okay?
Why are you talking
to a stranger in the middle of the night?
I won't like this after our wedding.
Let's go!
Where?
- Home. Where else?
- Why home? I thought we both…
Yes, we both are going to my house.
Are you compromising in life, Jikki?
You are confused.
If you hurry, you can come on the bike.
Otherwise, you'll have to walk.
We have a long way to go. I'm leaving.
How can I go that far by walking?
Keep the cash account
and gold account separately.
- Check.
- After that, I'll tell you what to do.
Okay, sir.
Is that phone call for you or me?
Even if it's for you,
please give it to me.
I'll talk in your presence.
What? Jikki, is it?
Oh, Jikki!
Why did you guys go there?
Hey!
Not right. He's just doing his duty.
What did you say?
You’re also doing your duty, are you?
Why should I get involved?
Sort it out yourselves.
Here.
Bachchan, if you stay there,
we'll stay here.
If you leave that house within the
next 24 hours, we'll leave this house.
You don't have much time. Think about it!
Party workers.
In English, they also call them fans.
It's madness.
They're obsessed with me.
Crazy enough…
to kill for me.
Twenty-four hours.
Tayaramma, you're miraculous.
Who is that?
You’ll get to know when I come inside.
Say what you want from there.
- Matchbox.
- Go.
Who are you, man?
If we keep introductions, it will take
seven and a half hours, you dumbo.
I was very busy. I came
because my brother asked me to come.
Simply speaking, I’m the Youth Yuvaraj
sent by Mass Maharaaj.
Presenting today’s entertainment
by Siddhu Jonnalagadda,
Junior Income Tax Officer,
Ayakar Bhavan, Hyderabad, 500032.
Brother breaks the bones
and I break the nerves.
What are you guys eating?
You guys look like double-decker buses.
My shoulder was going
to dislocate, sister.
Double-decker buses
should be parked on the road.
If they enter the house
and park here, we won't spare them.
Hey, according to the
constitution of this country,
indulging in black money
is a punishable offense.
If I do not eradicate this
kind of cancer from society,
the nation will go into depression,
and I will have to resign
from my bloody designation.
How did I say, dude?
You didn't understand?
Try to understand.
Meanwhile, I have to make a call.
Even if that call is for you,
give it to me. Please.
Hey, bro.
What? You broke their arms and legs?
I hope you haven't killed them yet.
What's that?
You're planning to kill them now?
Well, I'm staying out of it.
Sort it out among yourselves.
Hey, Jaggu Kaka!
Your BP will rise
once you hear what I'm saying.
So keep the tablets next to you.
I have thrashed the men
sent by you in ten minutes flat.
If you have more, send them.
I will stay here,
and Bachchan will stay there.
If it itches down under,
you should scratch your top.
We’ll both be on duty,
keeping a close eye on you going forward!
The wedding is planned here.
All the stuff should be set
in its own place. Do it quickly!
Excuse me, Jikki madam.
If you don't mind, please.
- Do you have any sisters?
- No, why?
Just fitting the map into the gap.
The younger brother's procession
at the elder brother's wedding.
Check and search. Find someone for me.
I don’t have many requirements.
If she is shorter than me, that's enough.
Please, if you don't mind.
Thank you. Take care.
It seems Uncle is upset because he doesn't
have a younger daughter.
Buddies.
They also call them friends in English.
If you have fans, I have friends
who are willing to give their lives
or take a life for me if needed.
You're playing with fire
by locking the lion in its den.
The moment I step out of this
house, you'll have to deal with it.
Why wait for one day?
You can step out now.
Use your position,
power, might, and people
to stop me if you dare.
I will.
I will give you hell.
If you do that,
I will resign and sit at home.
Or else, I will ensure that
you sit in Tihar Jail.
I don't think it is correct
to send him out currently, sir.
You can’t break into the snake’s den
unless it comes out.
We can’t get the people in the household
to talk unless he steps out.
Sir, the CM is calling you inside.
Hey, tell him to come out.
Today, I want to make or break things.
Bloody hell…
What's up, Jaghayya?
Everything alright?
Why would I come here
if everything were alright?
The Income Tax Department
is governed by the central government.
You would know the rules
if you were educated.
The guy in the ruling party
doesn't follow the rules.
Call him immediately
and stop all the raids!
- Hello.
- Am I speaking to Mr. Bachchan?
Yes, Mr. Bachchan speaking.
This call is from the CM's office.
The Chief Minister would
like to speak with you.
The Chief Minister?
Yes. One second.
Sir.
Is it true that raids are being conducted
at Muthyam Jaghayya's house?
You…
Yes, sir.
Stop them immediately and leave at once.
Sorry, sir. Our department operates under
the authority of the central government.
You are challenging the Chief Minister.
No, sir. I'm reminding you.
I’m reminding a Chief Minister
of his limitations.
The state officials, ministers,
and even the Chief Minister
cannot stop us.
What do you hope to achieve
by challenging influential people?
Want to demonstrate
the power of the system
when there's an officer
capable of cleaning it up.
- If I decide now, immediately--
- Please do.
- Shall we make the PM office call once?
- Hey!
Shame on you!
He calls himself a CM? How sad!
He's like a pure gem, right?
Hello!
Hello? Hello…
We won't face any trouble because
of this witness's signature, right?
Your sir is like a God to you, right?
Why would you have trouble with God?
- Raju Garu,
- Sir.
please make three copies of this,
prepare an order, and send them to me.
Okay, sir.
- Hello.
- This is the Prime Minister speaking.
Good morning, Mr. Prime Minister.
Even God cannot save him this time.
Is there any possibility
to stop the raids?
Yes, sir.
We can stop with your order, sir.
- Please stop the raids right now.
- Sure, sir.
When can I expect the orders?
What do you mean?
PRIME MINISTER
I need written orders from you, sir,
and I mean it.
This is my personal order.
If you’re calling it a personal order,
it suggests there’s something wrong here
or that you have
a personal connection with me.
I neither engage in wrongdoing
nor allow anyone to get close to me.
My office will get in touch
with you later.
This raid will not cease
until I receive a written order.
We’ve heard everything you’ve said so far.
Everyone has cooperated with you.
Please ensure
that no disaster occurs in the house.
He’s requesting a written order
that we cannot provide.
- Why is that not possible?!
- Excuse me!
I also belong to your party.
It's your responsibility to protect me.
Without me, neither you
nor your party will survive in our area.
Is there any other appointment today?
Delegates have arrived
from Italy to discuss the defense deal.
Call them.
Okay, sir.
Recheck everything
and arrange for the vehicle.
- Okay, sir.
- Yes, sir.
Hello?
Bachchan's duty here
is a resounding success.
Now, only the husband’s role remains.
Are you okay?
Hello, this is Mr. Bachchan.
Master, in a few hours,
I will become Mrs. Bachchan.
Suvvaala Suvvi!
Suvvi!
You gave a piercing look
And created a stir with your smile
Hey, oh, my boy…
Can I trust your word?
Can praise be given like this?
Can the cheek be pinched?
Oh my…
You can cause confusion
And shout at everyone, overcoming shyness
The white sari with the black border
Has caused chaos
In the smoother waistline
Affairs become turbulent
Your makeup has ignited a fire
Hey, oh, my boy…
Can I trust your word?
Can praise be given like this?
Can the cheek be pinched?
Oh my…
You can cause confusion
And shout at everyone, overcoming shyness
The white sari with the black border
Has caused chaos
In the smoother waistline
Affairs become turbulent
Your makeup has ignited a fire
Hey, oh, my boy…
Can I trust your word?
Can praise be given like this?
Can the cheek be pinched?
Oh my…
You can cause confusion
And shout at everyone, overcoming shyness
The mole that you hid…
Can I see it?
Hey, oh, my boy…
You shouldn't ask me everything
There is heat in the body
So I pinched you with my nail
Can you stir up a quarrel
Between youth and beauty?
Fuss in the hearts
Your passion has gotten to me
Can there be any limits to beauty?
You came like a bee…
Trying to steal honey from my lips
Hey, oh, my boy…
You shouldn't ask me everything
Your nose pin is green…
And you wore something very lovely
Is it fair to hang
With hair like electric wires?
I’ve seen all the weights
Can I weigh some
Sensitive and solo heart
Here I come
Hey, oh, my boy…
Can I trust your word?
Can praise be given like this?
Can the cheek be pinched?
Oh my…
You can cause confusion
And shout at everyone, overcoming shyness
We’ve sealed everything
that was confiscated.
Please sign here.
If I’m taking so much from you,
I should give something back, right?
That’s why,
here’s a small piece of advice.
Wealth isn’t just about
accumulating money.
It also means gaining people
who genuinely care for us.
None of those you trusted stood by you,
but these officers,
who are unrelated to me, did.
In this way, I’ve gained more than you.
Goodbye.
How long until my son-in-law arrives?
He must be tied up with some work.
He will come. Let me go check.
Okay.
- This is the best raid of our careers.
- I haven't seen a raid
like this in my long career.
Drive faster.
I need to get married.
My wife is waiting.
Brother, why did you let him go?
Sambashiva, fate is very ironic.
For me, this house
is just like this place.
He can leave the house,
but not this place.
The entire country knows
what happened in our house.
We can’t take any action against him here.
Drive faster! Faster…
It’s a hassle. Only the name
of the victim gets mentioned,
not the name of the killer.
That's India's history…
and future.
Please continue chanting the mantras.
Meanwhile, he will arrive.
He'll be here.
Mr. Suryan,
the auspicious time is approaching.
- Time is running out.
- Where is the groom?
- He hasn't arrived yet.
- Sister-in-law, he will come.
- Dear…
- Come here.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Isn’t he here yet? What happened?
Don't worry. He must've gone
to the office. He'll be here soon.
- Find out where he is. Go!
- Okay.
He is coming.
Sir!
Sir.
Where is the money?
Confiscate all the money!
- Go.
- Take all the money out.
Yes, sir.
Jikki…
I'm here!
Shall we get married?
Jaghayya threatened to kill me
if I didn't secure an MLA ticket
for his brother.
What makes him think
that he's so powerful?
Simple. Financial and muscle power, sir.
Alright. Let’s hit him with the same.
- What do you mean?
- An income tax raid.
He can bribe and buy out anyone, sir.
There's one officer
who can't be bought.
He is Mr. Bachchan.
You started from the interval,
and now we’re at the climax.
Have you ever wondered
what gives me such courage?
It's honesty. Courage comes from honesty.
Otherwise, think about it and let me know,
now that you have plenty of time.
I’ve heard that a cart
can become a ship and vice versa.
But I never thought
it could happen in life.
Give me a cigarette, please.
I’m craving one.
Wealth isn’t just about
accumulating money.
It also means gaining people
who genuinely care for us.
The wealth accumulated has slipped away
I’ve ended up in a place
I never imagined I’d reach
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
I’ve lost everything
By the time I realized this
By the time I realized this, Tayaramma…
Tayaramma…
Why are Amitabh Bachchan’s pictures
here too, Dad?
If it happens in his presence,
maybe I’ll get a grandson
like Amitabh Bachchan.
I’m Bachchan myself.
If one is born,
it could be Abhishek Bachchan.
- Even better. Goodbye. Bye.
- Now go. Shut the door.
Don't come back.
It's already too late. Come here…