Look at the stars.
Whenever you feel alone...
the great kings of the past...
will always be up there to guide you.
And so will I.
My friends, the time of my family's growth
is upon us.
This home we share is the fulfillment
of my father's vision.
How wonderful is it that Nala and I
get to continue his dream...
and make even greater the Circle of Life?
Nala, my love, I'm on my way.
Simba...
I'm here.
Security detail has arrived!
One gentle reminder: we are not food.
No, no, no. We are just two guys...
walking to work
through a pride of hungry lions.
Which is perfectly normal.
I'm not terrified.
Security detail reporting for duty,
Your Grace, Your Highness...
Ruler of all four-legged creatures.
And that one three-legged zebra.
Oh, right, Ron. That was tragic.
- It was an eat-and-Ron.
- Yeah.
Ron has three legs.
That's still one more than me.
- Well, are those arms or legs?
- Guys.
- I don't know. I think they're paws.
- I consider all those legs.
- Guys! This is serious.
I need you to stay with Kiara
until I get back.
Are you saying that your security detail
has been called on to do babysitting?
Pumbaa, we should really discuss this
because I don't really love...
Guys, I promised her
everything would be okay.
Well, that's one way to parent.
She's gonna have to grow up sometime.
What else did you tell her, that she
could be whatever she wants to be?
That life is fair?
I need you two to try
and act like adults, okay?
Don't scare Kiara.
And most of all, no stories.
- No stories?
- Wait a second.
I know where your head goes.
I grew up with you two. Promise me.
Okay. You know what, you know what,
you know what? Fine. No stories.
Speak for yourself, Pumbaa.
No. We'll tell a story anyway.
Okay, we'll tell him that
we're not gonna tell a story and then...
- we're gonna tell a story.
- Are you guys serious?
- He can't stop us.
- I'm clearly within earshot.
Dad.
Hey, little one.
Dad, the storm's coming, and I'm scared.
I wanna go with you and Mom.
Don't be scared, my love.
Timon and Pumbaa
will watch you while I'm gone.
Be brave now, Kiara.
Be brave.
Okay! We've prepared a story.
Scar looked at us.
He knew it was the end of the line.
I could smell the fear.
That was actually me, but yes.
So you two defeated Scar?
And then you ate him?
Honestly, one of the best meals I ever had.
My dad told me he defeated Scar.
Well, okay. But your dad,
as we all know, is a pathological liar.
He's always lyin'. Get it?
I'm scared. I want Mom and Dad.
Look, look, look.
Don't be scared, Kiara.
How about we sing you a song?
And, a-one...
Pumbaa, no, it is way too early for the song.
It worked on Simba.
He thought he had murdered his own father.
He was singin' and dancin' around in seconds.
I can't just turn it on like that.
I have to be in the moment.
He sang that song for six years straight.
Well, who didn't?
- Look!
- No!
It's Ron, the three-legged zebra.
- Run for your lives!
- He heard what we've been sayin' about him.
We're sorry, Ron. They were jokes.
They were just jokes!
It's Rafiki.
Rafiki! Rafiki!
Little one, there's no reason to cry.
My parents...
they're gone.
Look out there, mdogo.
You see those baobab trees
blowing in the wind?
The roots of those trees are very strong,
like your family.
And, just as they did for you...
your parents have gone
to the ceremonial birthing grounds.
And when they return, the Circle of Life
will bring a blessing to you, Kiara...
that you will never forget.
Man, he's good.
He's such a visual storyteller.
Yet it makes sense that he lives alone.
I just want the storm to pass,
and then I promise to be brave.
I'll tell you a secret.
When your father Simba was your age...
he was afraid of the thunder
and would hide behind the king.
When did he stop hiding?
One day, during a big storm...
your grandfather Mufasa took your father
to the very top of Pride Rock...
told him to stand with him...
and howl into the wind.
And Simba slowly stepped out with the king.
And together, they roared into the night.
But I'm not brave like my dad.
And I could never be like Mufasa.
Is that so?
Then maybe it's time I tell you a story.
A story of a cub, not much bigger than you.
A lion born without a drop
of nobility in his blood.
A lion who would change our lives forever.
A story! So glad I brought some crickets.
But go easy. We're in a cave.
This story begins far beyond...
the mountains and the shadows.
On the other side of the light.
In this place,
everything was dying of thirst...
as 20 full moons had passed
without a single drop of water.
But when the skies finally opened...
destiny would reign.
Mufasa.
Mufasa! Come see.
Mom, what is that light way out there?
Oh, that's very special.
Beyond the horizon...
beyond the last cloud in the sky...
that's a place we call Milele.
Milele?
It means, "forever."
Imagine a kingdom full of life...
water and food...
grass and sky as far as the eye can see.
Will we ever go there?
Oh, yes, Mufasa.
That's exactly where we're headed.
But we can also be there right now.
We can close our eyes.
Let our dreams take us.
Beyond the horizon
Beyond the last cloud in the sky
There's a place I know
Imagine a kingdom
The water flows, the grass is high
It's not a dream
Someday we'll go
We call it Milele
It's always there
Milele
It lives in you, it lives in me
You'll see
- Life, great and small
- The Circle of Life is not small
- We know that there's enough for all
- There's enough for all
There is always more
- Can you feel it?
- We're on your side
- We'll wander no longer
- We carry ancestors inside
- Like a constant tide
- It's not a dream, can you see it?
- On an endless shore
- And as you grow, can you find your way?
- Can you see it?
We call it
Milele
It's always there
We call it
Milele
It's always there
It lives in you, it lives in me
We're free
Milele
Wow.
What is this?
Rain. Rain!
Oh, finally we have rain!
Dad, race you to the light!
You're too fast.
I've never beaten you.
Nobody has ever beaten you.
I know!
Mufasa! Fastest cub in the world.
Thank you.
Mufasa...
that's enough.
Mufasa, come back now.
Mufasa, stay there! I'm coming, son.
- Father!
- Mufasa!
Mufasa?
I'll catch you on the turn.
Find my voice.
Find my voice!
Mom!
Mufasa, the cliff is too high,
but you can cross at the dam.
Come on, Mufasa, you can do this.
Find your mother's voice.
Listen to your father, Mufasa!
Listen to us!
Afia, he's there.
- Mom!
- He's there!
- Mother!
- Mufasa!
Find your footing one step at a time.
- I can't.
- You can do this. I'm right here.
Mufasa!
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
Mom?
Dad?
Can you hear me?
Is anyone out there?
Mom?
Please.
I'm scared.
The floodwaters joined a distant river...
carried Mufasa far
from his mother and father.
Beyond all that he knew.
Hello.
I'm Taka, son of Obasi.
What's your name?
Mufasa.
I'm not allowed to talk to Outsiders...
but I have a secret...
and I really want to tell you.
- What's the secret?
- I'll get in trouble.
Please, just tell me.
I don't know.
Just tell me!
Okay. You're about to be eaten.
I hate secrets!
- Swim!
- But I can't!
- You have to swim.
- I don't know how!
All right. Chin up,
then walk underwater really fast.
I can't!
Come on, Mufasa. Faster!
Help me, Taka! Help me!
I told you to wait for me.
It's not my fault, Mum.
I came down for a drink
and saw him floating by.
I'd like you to meet Mufasa.
You're lucky those crocs were young
and afraid to fight. Let's go!
We can't just leave him here.
Rules are rules, Taka.
Obasi will never accept a stray.
I'm not a stray. I'm just... lost.
See?
He's just lost.
There was a flood.
My parents, they tried to save me.
Do you know which way is home?
Home?
To be lost is to learn the way.
Call me Eshe.
I'm tired, Eshe.
Come on, it's this way.
Come on, Mufasa.
Is this Milele?
No, my love.
I was trying to nap, Eshe.
The all-important nap of kings...
only to be awoken by the disgusting...
hideous, revolting stench of a stray.
When we come upon an Outsider...
tell me, what do we do?
Obasi, I know.
Eat it.
But I found him, Dad. I saved his life.
Taka, we do not associate with Outsiders.
The only true bond is blood.
I've heard stories of lions twice our size.
These Outsiders...
will devour everything in their path.
Does he look like he's going to devour you?
That smell is disgusting.
I'm not even sure I could eat this kibeti!
I'm not a kibeti. I'm a Mufasa.
- Do you even know what "Mufasa" means?
- No.
It means, "king."
And that's me.
You better start running, little Mufasa...
for your life.
If I run, you'll never catch me.
I'm the fastest cub that ever lived.
My father told me so.
Taka, you have a challenge.
They will race to the dead tree and back.
And when the prince defeats him...
I will finish him in one bite.
What if Mufasa wins?
If he wins, he lives, Obasi.
He stays with me.
You have my word.
Let the race begin!
Clumsy little stray.
Run, Mufasa!
You did not have to do that.
Taka is the future king.
He has to win his first challenge.
No, Obasi. To be a true king,
he must earn it.
Don't take that away from him.
Better hurry.
I have one more secret, Mufasa.
I always wanted a brother.
Cheater!
Obasi!
You will keep him with the females.
Taka, how could you lose to a stray?
Well done, Taka.
Well done.
I thought you said you were fast.
I had to let you win.
Well, I did just go days with no sleep
while riding the waves of...
Anyway, come on, Mufasa.
Let's get in some trouble.
When I am king
No other animal will break my stride
Break my stride
- And my brother
- My brother
When I'm king, you'll always take my side
- Ha! Yeah, right
- That's right
- When I am king
- When you are king
No other animal will break our pride
Break our pride
- And my brother
- My brother
Our prey may run away,
but they can't hide
Watch your hide
Let's go, let's go
Let's go
Hey, did your mama say
you could be up this late?
Okay, she didn't say either way
Hide away, let's go
Hey, did your father say
you could be out this far?
Okay, we're on our way
On our way, run away
Let's go
Hey, did your mama say
you could be up this late?
Ha ha, you're very sharp
Yes, you are,
yes, you are, let's go
Hey, did your father say
you could be out this far?
Make a wish on the brightest star
And I say
I always wanted a brother
just like you
And I always wanted a brother
I always wanted a brother
just like you
You see that tree?
Those birds are watching the world unfold
The world unfold
- Oh, brother
- My brother
When I'm king, they will do as they're told
You may look down on them
- But they are free
- You can't catch me
And where they go
cannot be controlled
No one looks down on me
They look down on us, brother
Some things you chase
but you cannot hold
- Okay, it's getting old, let's go
- Let's go
Hey, did your mama say
that you could learn this way?
I've got to find a way, find our prey
- Fine, I'll wait
- Let's go
- Hey
- I heard his father say
He doesn't want this stray
I dare you to say that again to my face
What did you say 'bout my brother?
That's not a stray, that's my brother
You stay away from my brother
'cause I say so
If you put your paws on my brother
You'll meet the jaws of his brother
Those are the laws for my brother
Where'd he go?
I always wanted a brother
I still remember my mother
One season after another
- Everyone sing for my brother
- Hey
- I'd do anything for my brother
- Soon I'll be king with my brother
- Hey
- By my side
- I always wanted a brother
- Hey
- Now we rely on each other
- One season after another
- Hey
- Hey, Mufasa
- Yes, Taka?
- I'll race you to the other side
- Hey
- Race you to the other side
Race you to the other side
Ha!
Elephant stampede!
Run for your lives!
Chigaru jumped, like, 20 feet.
Oh, that's a new record.
Obasi, they did it again.
Your sons are nothing but trouble.
That one is not my son.
They're heathens, the both of them.
This stray is forbidden
to be near the Shade Tree.
Mufasa and I were just playing.
You two will never be brothers.
Now go back to the females...
and stay away from my son.
Oh, your mother, she adopts every lizard...
speaks to passing grasshoppers.
I want to go with him.
You want to be with the females?
You belong with the males.
He gets to hunt with Mother.
One day, he will betray you.
That is what strays do.
Mufasa would never betray me.
Hey, hey.
This will all be yours, my son.
You will be king.
So pay attention.
Study every move I make.
Sleeping again.
That is what males do.
We protect the pride as we nap.
That's...
Well, that's power.
Power?
Why are we stopping?
Close your eyes.
And tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
There's a herd of antelope
heading across the dry lakebed.
About half a day from here?
And how do you know they're not gazelles?
Their steps are too heavy.
- Moving way too slow.
- What else?
Come on. You can do it.
When the wind hits their horns,
it moves up...
instead of across.
So, definitely antelope horns.
Very good.
What is it, Mufasa? What's wrong?
Sometimes I get a scent.
It's barely a trace on the wind.
And it smells like home.
Then it's gone.
Mufasa, your parents are still out there.
We can keep looking.
I lost them, Eshe.
You're wasting your time
training me like this.
But these skills you have,
no other male has them.
Obasi will never accept me.
I'll never be his blood. His family.
But you are my family.
And if Obasi could see how gifted you are...
Well, maybe I like being a stray, you know.
No rules, no responsibility.
I'm the lucky one, Eshe.
What do you mean, Mufasa?
I never have to be like Taka.
I never have to be king.
Did he say, "no rules and no responsibility"?
An outcast, afraid of water,
never takes a bath.
Which means he smells like me.
Which is not good.
Well, either way,
I think that means that he's one of us.
- This is it.
- It's our time!
- This is our moment.
- And a-one, and a-two and a-one, two...
Hakuna Mufasa
What a wonderful name
He ain't no passin' craze
It means no...
- Stop!
- What?
Don't go there.
All right, all right, Rafiki's right.
We'll get letters from legal.
Those vultures will take everything we have.
Which, technically, is nothing.
Look at us. We're naked animals.
No wonder I'm always freezing.
- They want this!
- Come on, Pumbaa.
Let's bring it home.
Hakuna Mufasa
Quiet!
Kiara's a music snob.
Rafiki, keep going.
Later that day, Eshe was teaching Mufasa
how to hunt in pairs.
But, as Taka was secretly watching...
something terrible was hunting them.
Mufasa, run!
Eshe!
Mother.
Mother!
Eshe!
Keep moving, Mufasa.
They go for the neck!
It's okay, Mufasa.
It's okay.
That was very brave of you, Mufasa.
Thank you.
Eshe...
What has happened?
Are you hurt?
They were huge. White as ghosts.
Like nothing I've seen before.
Obasi.
Had Mufasa not been there, I...
Taka.
I owe you a great debt, Mufasa.
We need to prepare.
They're downwind less than a day away.
No.
You couldn't possibly know this.
Send a scout and you'll see...
they'll be coming for us.
Chigaru.
Father, please, let me explain.
No. Not now.
Taka, come.
Where is my son?
There was a young lion, Majesty.
He fought Shaju.
And yet you came back.
You survived.
I was badly hurt. I promise, Majesty.
This is the truth.
- The truth?
- Yes, the truth.
The truth is standing behind you.
- There were others, Majesty.
- No, no, no.
But only one left blood on his mane.
Which means he left Shaju to die.
Saved himself.
This young lion, was he their king?
His blood is common. Ordinary.
Answer me!
Was he their king?
No, Kiros, you are the only king.
An ordinary lion?
And you left my son to die?
I was injured. There was no choice.
Please, Majesty, you have to believe me.
There's no reason to fear me.
I would never harm one of my own.
Thank you, Majesty.
I'll leave that pleasure...
to them.
Majesty! No. Kiros!
Kiros!
No one can ever know you ran.
That you ran from your mother.
It never happened, Taka.
Do you understand?
But I didn't know.
I was just... I was just scared.
It doesn't matter.
We must protect the bloodline.
Protect it with a lie?
Father, that's deceitful.
Deceit is a tool of a great king.
Taka...
it's what kings must do.
But I'm not a king.
I'm just your son.
Obasi!
Chigaru.
Chigaru, I'm here. What did you see?
They're coming this way, Obasi.
Two lions for every one of ours.
Each one bigger than the next...
but none as mighty as Kiros,
their terrifying king.
Outsiders.
The stories were all true.
I must protect the bloodline, Eshe.
The future of this pride.
Taka, you are that future.
Future? Dad, what do you mean?
I'm sending you away.
Far from here.
You will leave and start a new life,
a new beginning.
I need you to go with him, Mufasa...
to pledge your loyalty.
They'll arrive with the sunrise.
Where will we go, Eshe?
Without you, I have no home.
Mufasa, you and Taka together. That...
- That is home.
- Eshe...
Mufasa, look out there.
Beyond the light...
You know what I see?
I see the place your mother told you about,
a place beyond the river's end.
Across the deepest canyon
on the other side of the mountains...
a place beyond the horizon itself.
A pride land so green...
so perfect...
that to see it is to see...
Milele.
Yes. Forever.
My parents spoke of Milele often.
My mother told me it was where we were going.
And don't you see, Mufasa?
You must keep going.
You must continue your journey
toward the light.
Please, Eshe. I can't lose you.
You have my love always, Mufasa.
But your family is still out there,
waiting for you.
I can feel their presence.
And I know you can, too.
Go.
Go, Mufasa. Find your way home.
Mother, please forgive me. I beg you.
There's no need, my love.
Taka, your moment of courage will come.
Now both of you go.
Go and find your place...
in the Circle of Life.
They left their family
never to see them again?
This story is killing me.
It's toying with my emotions.
And here is the worst part.
- What's that?
- I'm out of crickets.
Oh, maybe that's for the best.
I need a bathroom break
before the second act.
Everyone wait for me.
I am back.
- Pumbaa, did you wash your hooves?
- Mm-hmm.
- Pumbaa?
- I did. I did.
- I'm just gonna...
- walk on them again right after.
- Pumbaa?
Rafiki, did the Outsiders come?
Yes.
And as the hunters led Kiros
into the Valley of Kings...
Obasi and Eshe stood their ground.
Which one of you is king?
You have no reason to challenge me.
Does this look like a challenge, King?
There are rules among lions.
Not anymore.
While you ruled this pride,
I've built my army.
Yours is the last pride...
in the Valley of Kings, which means...
everything the light touches belongs to me.
There will be one ruler.
One Lion King.
You say you're the king,
but you lie around in the shade
Out of shape, unafraid
The moon cuts a path through the sky
By night or by day
It doesn't obey
And neither do I
You took my son
I hope you can run
'Cause I'm going to be
the last thing you see
Before you go bye-bye
There you go, bye-bye
Climb every tree
Cross land and sea
I'll make you go bye-bye
Everything in my clutches, ha!
Bye-bye
Everything the light touches
The Circle of Life is a lie
A pretty way to say
There are predators and prey
That circle of vultures up high
They keep stealing glances
They don't like your chances
And neither do I
I run my pride
You run and hide
'Cause I'm going to be
the last thing you see
Before you go bye-bye
There you go, bye-bye
Climb every tree
Cross land and sea
Until you go bye-bye
Will you go bye-bye?
Bye-bye, for vengeance is mine
If I'm the last of my line
I must be strong
Gotta go bye-bye
I'll make you go bye-bye
Bye-bye
We have to move. They'll be tracking us.
- Taka!
- What if you're wrong?
What if they're okay?
They live in you now.
Follow me, brother.
We have to move...
together.
Run, Mufasa.
Run!
Hunters.
What's the plan?
Run! Very fast!
This way!
Back to the trees.
We're trapped. We have to swim.
No, we have to fight.
If we fight, we die.
But if we swim, we drown.
Okay, I didn't want to do this...
- but I command you to swim!
- You what?
You pledged your loyalty.
I command you to swim.
Taka, this is not the time for jokes.
Which one of you killed my son?
I did. This lion with me
is nothing but a stray. Let him go.
Kiros, the other is no stray.
He holds the blood of the pride.
The last blood of the king?
Blood for blood.
They're coming!
What do we do?
We find the advantage?
What advantage?
We're on a rock in the middle of the water!
Taka, this is it. We go for the king.
Mufasa, I'm ready.
Just one last thing.
- What?
- Chin up!
Taka!
This was a bad idea.
Mufasa!
- Mufasa, we're alive.
- Yeah!
I did it. I saved us.
You were saying?
Okay. Okay.
No more water.
Tell me you can track them down river.
We can track them anywhere.
They can run, but they can't hide.
So just to be clear, we're not in this story?
It feels a little bit like
Kiros is stealing my thunder here.
Yeah. You know, I don't feel seen.
No. There's a lotta stories with all of us.
Tell one of those!
Can I make one small suggestion?
Less childhood trauma, more meerkat.
Rafiki, I know who Taka's gonna be.
Me too. It's so obvious.
But maybe,
just so we're on the same page, tell me?
- Is it Simba? Is it me?
- Pumbaa.
Oh, wait. Am I Obasi?
That makes no sense.
But seriously, I have one question.
Am I Taka?
I did it again. I did it again.
Not that I'm counting,
but I saved your hide. Again!
As much as it kills you to say it,
let's hear a little, "Thank you, Taka."
You want me to thank you
for pushing me off a waterfall?
Yes, and you're welcome.
Look, it's not my fault
crocodiles are simply attracted to you.
Don't say that.
I did it again. I did it...
Mufasa.
Is it them? Is it the Outsiders?
No. She's right there.
"She"?
There's no place to run.
We have your scent.
My scent?
I've been stalking you two all night.
That's not possible.
Then why did I circle you
three times in this wood...
while you two
were chasing each other's tails?
That's embarrassing.
Yeah, well, I meant to do that, so...
Still think I'm afraid?
- Why are you following us?
- I was hoping to find my pride.
- What happened to them?
- The Outsiders happened.
A few of us got away,
but you're the only other lions I've seen.
You two better keep moving.
Wait! Please.
My name is Taka.
Son of Obasi.
I know what it's like to lose everything.
Come with us. We can help you.
I don't need any help.
But you don't have anyone.
She does indeed have someone.
Thank you very much.
That's Zazu. Don't eat him.
You heard her. Do not eat me.
As a recent addition
to the King's Royal Guard...
I must kindly ask you both to move on.
Thank you for stopping by.
Your king hired a bird to protect you?
How high can you fly?
Look, I needed a scout.
Zazu was the last option.
Well, next to last.
Between Albert the Iguana and I...
His Majesty
decided on the underling with wings.
And thus, I became the lead scout
for the princess.
It's my third day, going swimmingly,
if I may say so myself.
Sarabi, you can say so as well.
How far do you think you'll get with a bird?
How far do you two geniuses think you'll get
stumbling around, running into each other?
All the way to Milele.
- Milele is nothing but a myth.
- It's not a myth.
Circle of Life and fairy tale herds.
- You're chasing something that doesn't exist.
- Honestly. As If.
I don't know that Milele exists,
but right now...
it's the only hope we have.
We don't need hope. We need food.
Good job, brother. Real nice.
There's trouble in the trees.
My first real trouble...
and I am going to pass. Not going.
I am staying right here, thank you.
Come on, Sarabi.
Looks like there's dinner headed our way.
Sarabi, if I may.
He makes a valid point, Your Highness.
But, on the other hand,
he's a starving lion, he wants to eat me...
so I am slightly torn.
I think that went quite well,
all things considered.
And now, Kiara, this is where I come in.
Rafiki.
Order! We will have order
in the Congress of Baboons.
Tonight, a cheetah came into our trees
for the third night in a row.
Almost took one of our own.
It was Rafiki's fault.
He summoned the beast with his dreams.
Rafiki and his visions
must be banished once and for all.
Rafiki tried to warn you.
His dreams conjure our enemies.
He talks to the spirits, summons the devil.
- What are you talking about?
- He's done it before.
His brother was chased
from these very trees...
never to be seen again.
Rafiki was just a child.
A child born with a leg that does not work.
Yet somehow, he survived?
It was Rafiki who found water
in the dry season.
Who healed you, Inaki, when you were sick.
He speaks to the insects,
converses with the moon.
Zala, you know what will happen
if you send him down from the trees.
He is amelaaniwa!
A curse to us all.
- That's not true.
- He doesn't belong here.
All in favor of banishment, cover one eye.
How can you trust him?
Don't trust him, and I don't trust his magic!
He doesn't belong here.
He's not a baboon.
And he never will be.
He's not one of us.
And so, it is time.
No, wait.
Where will you go?
Where I should have gone long ago.
To find all that was lost.
My family.
You can't survive on your own.
Nobody can.
And yet, here we are.
Oh, Rafiki.
The eye never forgets
what the heart has seen.
It's all right.
You can try to run,
but I'm afraid you won't get very far.
And why would I run from you?
Because we're lions.
As in lions!
A flea can trouble a lion
more than a lion can trouble a flea.
I don't think you understand
what's about to happen.
There's no place for you to go.
I am going forward.
I seriously doubt that.
It is easy to doubt everything
when you know nothing.
Can we get on with this, please?
If you take my life,
you will never find Milele.
Wait, did you say Milele?
That is where I'm going. Toward the light.
I have been there many times in my dreams.
My brother waits for me there.
I've seen the tree.
Can picture it. The two of us...
together again.
And why would anyone trust a baboon's dream?
Sometimes, a dream is all you have.
The only truth that lives in you.
Like the memory of a great king.
How did you know?
Okay. Help us get to Milele,
and we will let you live.
- Do we have a deal?
- No.
What? Why?
Rafiki will let you live.
I've had enough of this!
Taka, do not eat him.
Wonderful. Another misfit stray
we're not supposed to eat.
So, you expect us to follow this baboon...
to a place nobody has ever seen?
I'll be better off alone.
A single stick may smoke...
but it will never burn.
Okay, now that there's five of us...
why don't we all go around
and say a fun fact about ourselves?
I'll go first.
I once had a crush on a flamingo.
I've never said that out loud.
And they're walking away.
Yeah, places to go, kingdoms to see.
We're busy. Let's hustle.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now you're the star of this thing?
Someone's a little tired
of bein' second banana, huh?
All of a sudden,
there's a lotta Rafiki in this story.
You even gave yourself a long-lost brother.
- Yeah.
- What's next? A funny catchphrase?
You gonna be fartin' next?
'Cause that's my thing.
You cannot tell the story of Mufasa...
without the story of Rafiki.
Oh, now he's even talkin' about himself
in the third person.
Pretty soon, he'll have his own fragrance.
And I'm the only one
with a fragrance around here.
It's called "Pumbaa by Pumbaa"...
and from what I hear, it's pretty gross.
Mom? Dad?
If you can hear me, come home.
Please.
Come home.
Mother?
Milele.
Mother!
Rafiki.
- What are you doing?
- I am fishing.
You're sitting on a rock
with your eyes closed.
My eyes are open.
It is my lids that are closed.
Why am I talking to a baboon?
I am not a baboon.
I am a mandrill.
No offense, but a monkey is a monkey.
And a stray is a stray.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means we are very much the same.
We are nothing alike.
Take a good look. I am a lion.
A lion who fears water,
fears his own reflection.
Who can't sleep because of what he sees
when he closes his eyes.
You are afraid of your dreams, Mufasa.
Afraid of what you see in them.
I see my parents.
I feel them everywhere.
Of course you do, Mufasa.
You will feel them forever.
My mother, I hear her voice.
She tells me that
we are on a journey to Milele...
but I feel so lost without her.
Your journey is not a dream, Mufasa.
Your mother is guiding you...
and where you are going,
a family awaits.
What are you doing?
We're starving.
'Twas not its time.
Instead, the fish has agreed
to let us share the water.
I have a report.
It's morning.
End of report.
The earth divided is now a choice.
Around or down?
The decision is yours.
Look out there, beyond the light.
Across the deepest canyon.
"Across the deepest canyon."
We should go down.
Why? Because of some fairy tale?
The rocks will hide our tracks.
It's safer to go around.
I picked up their scents.
The only thing you picked up
is a hallucinating baboon.
I am a mandrill.
This is a waste of time.
Close your eyes.
What?
Tell me what you see. What you feel.
There's nothing on the wind.
- No, they're moving through the bush willow.
- They, who?
The females, out front. Come on.
Clear your thoughts. Concentrate.
I am concentrating.
He's right.
We have to go down.
Wow. Wow, wow, wow.
Now the many sticks will make fire as one.
Come on. We have places to go.
And kingdoms to see.
And kingdoms to see!
If you wanna go fast, go alone
There's the road
Off you go
But if you wanna go far
We go together
So good, so far
Your father left you in my care
And now we're running who knows where
Sometimes you need a bird's-eye view
And I've got you to see me through
By land, by air
If you wanna go fast, go alone
Day and night
- There's the road
- I just might
- Off you go
- Yeah, right
If you wanna go far
We go together
So good, so far
I will find my family again
I will walk with you until then
I will walk with you till the end
It's much easier with a friend
I will find my family again
I will walk with you until then
- I will walk with you till the end
- Flying through
It's much easier with a friend
Like the clouds and rain
Like a meal in a field of grain
Like the flecks of gold in your mane
Sarabi, you and me, we go together
- Like clouds and rain
- We will find our family again
- Like a meal in a field of grain
- We will walk together till then
- Like the flecks of gold in your mane, Sarabi
- We will find our way to the end
- You and me, we go together
- It's much easier with a friend
- My brother waits for me to find him
- We will find our family again
- My brother knows I'm right behind him
- We will walk together till then
- My brother tends to lose his way
- We will find our way
- And go astray, say
- To the end
- If you see my brother, please remind him
- It's much easier with a friend
It's much easier with a friend
It's much easier
- We won't go alone
- Not alone
- Here we go
- Down the road
- 'Cause we're gonna go far
- Hey, hey, hey, hey
We go together
- So good, so far
- Hey, hey, hey, hey
We go together
As we headed across the Great Valley...
the hunters tracked our every move.
Kiros. They are not alone.
They've collected a lioness.
And a monkey.
Mufasa.
Mufasa. You have to help me.
Help you how?
It's Sarabi, Mufasa.
She is the light my mother spoke of.
- What?
- She's special.
The most amazing female
I've ever met in my life.
I don't know what to say to her.
You've spent your life with females.
Please, tell me what to say.
Just talk to her. Be yourself.
No, Mufasa.
You don't understand.
Myself isn't good enough.
You...
just know things.
Fine. Fine.
Keep it simple. Ask her a question.
Right. A question. This is good.
Yeah, try to be confident. Disinterested.
But I'm very interested.
- Tell her about the flowers.
- What flowers?
The valley she comes from.
There's flowers everywhere.
They're called duck flowers.
Long stems.
It's absolutely beautiful.
How do you know that?
When she passes, I can smell them on her fur.
Okay.
Flowers. Disinterested.
- Flowers. And disinterested. Flowers.
- And here's the most important thing, okay?
- And disinterested.
- Listen...
- Flowers and disinterested.
- ...when she speaks.
- Males have trouble with that one.
- Flowers...
Sorry. What did you say?
Really?
I heard you, brother.
I'm gonna make you proud.
It's very hot, isn't it?
Yep.
I love listening.
Okay.
- I'm listening right now.
- To what?
- What you just said.
- You're the one that's talking.
I am.
- You smell like a duck.
- What?
Flower.
A duck flower.
How do you know about those flowers?
Well, I inhaled you with my nose.
I can smell them.
That's amazing.
Our valley was full of those flowers...
thousands of them
as far as the eye could see.
It was the most beautiful place, Taka.
Did he just say she smells like a duck?
And you call me a baboon?
They shouldn't be here.
The migration patterns are broken.
- I don't understand...
- Outsiders!
This is not a drill! Just to be clear...
I never signed up for this.
It's okay. We're safe.
They're on the other side.
Nope!
They can just jump across!
We are trapped!
What do we do?
The elephants will fight with us.
And why would they do that?
Because I'm going to ask them.
Got a better idea?
Yes, Mr. Ask-Questions-First.
Get ready to run.
Where is she going?
Hello? Listen to me, please.
We need your help.
Can you talk with me?
We need your help. Please.
They're coming!
Sarabi! Sarabi, wait!
Sarabi! Sarabi, wait. Wait!
Where is she going?
She's going for the hive!
Like I said, get ready to run!
Run!
Get to the trees!
Why am I running?
Your Highness, hold on!
Zazu!
Sarabi!
Stand your ground!
Do not retreat!
I got you.
Sarabi, I got you.
That's right. Run along, little kitty cats.
Thank you, my friend.
Over here.
Sarabi.
Alive. She's alive!
Why are you all looking at me?
You were thrown from the tree.
He saved your life.
Who?
Taka.
Taka saved you.
Isn't that right, brother?
You saved me?
Well, I had to do something.
Thank you.
We're lucky.
Those bees almost killed us all.
Those bees saved our lives.
- Mufasa.
- Really?
Because it felt like an elephant stampede.
- We're alive, aren't we?
- The elephants would have fought with us.
We're lions.
Nobody will fight with us.
Not out here.
Where's he going?
Beyond the horizon itself.
Mufasa, thank you.
Rafiki...
Who are the Outsiders?
Well, the Outsiders come from many prides.
But, when they are born...
they are hated
because they are different from their tribe.
Like you and your tribe?
Yes, just like me.
- But, Rafiki?
- Yes?
Why do they wanna hurt everybody?
Sometimes, when the people most like you
don't love you...
it is a hurt
that can cause the greatest pain.
And this pain...
can lead you to hate everything.
I'm glad that didn't happen to you, Rafiki.
Yes, my child. I'm glad too.
Hi. We're here, too.
Yeah, why are you leavin' us
outside this story...
when I'm pretty sure
we are the ultimate outsiders.
- Come on!
- Yeah, we've always been misunderstood.
I contain multitudes.
There are many ways to Milele.
But this will be ours.
Go. Go, Mufasa.
Find your forever.
I got you.
Sarabi, I got you.
Hey, Rafiki?
What are you doing?
I am confirming my vision, Mufasa.
Can I ask you something, Rafiki?
How many of your visions have come true?
- So far, none.
- None?
But it's not what I see. It's what I feel.
But how do you...
How do you know
when you should follow a feeling?
Milele exists.
I feel it in here.
The question is...
what do you feel, Mufasa...
in there?
The weather's shifted.
There's not enough fresh snow.
Hey, if the Outsiders find our tracks,
they'll follow them to Milele.
Zazu, only you can help us now.
Are you quite sure about that?
No, I was actually thinking...
that Rafiki looks pretty handy,
and with the stick...
Zazu, you can use your wings...
to cover our tracks
as we head up the mountain...
without leaving a trace.
Hey, you can do this.
Yeah.
Yes, sir. You're right. I've got this.
Okay. It's just me against a frozen mountain.
One hornbill
charged with saving the future...
Mummy!
Man alive, that's cold.
Now what's happening?
We can't keep stopping.
Somehow, they have covered their tracks.
In the snow?
It's not possible.
Majesty, they could be anywhere
on this mountain...
Then find them!
Now.
Zazu, Zazu, Zazu
Zazu, Zazu!
I have a report.
The Outsiders are completely lost.
Well played, Mufasa.
Great job, Zazu.
And as per usual.
I knew you could do it.
We did it. We did it.
No, you did it.
Great thinking, Mufasa.
We're all rubbing off on each other.
Perfectly normal thing to do.
Who wants to rub against Zazu?
No one. I'm leaving now.
I'll scout ahead.
I got you, Rafiki.
- Hey.
- I got you.
Ho monate, Mufasa.
Yeah, I got you.
Mufasa...
"I got you."
Hidden in the shadows,
downwind, light of foot.
Interesting hunting style, Mufasa.
We have to eat something
before we take on that descent.
Unfortunately,
there's nothing to hunt up here.
See under that rock?
There's a civet about to leave his den.
Of course you can smell a civet
hidden in the snow.
You, the lion who can do anything.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I see you, Mufasa.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Now, that part, I believe.
Because, smart as you are...
you have a way of seeing
everything but yourself.
What is this?
What is this, Sarabi?
There is a civet in the snow
right where you said it would be.
And you smelled the Outsiders
on the wind...
which means you're the one
who smelled the flowers on my fur.
It was a lucky guess.
You can smell the exact flower
from my valley.
No, that's not possible.
You saved me.
Held me, covered me in the stampede,
comforted me.
No, it was Taka.
"I got you. I got you, Sarabi."
- I'm here to protect him.
- That was you.
I was lost in the water, and he found me.
My brother saved me.
I sensed it from the beginning.
- His blood is the blood of the king.
- Mufasa.
- That is his destiny.
- No!
His destiny was to save you.
Now tell me it's you.
Ever since you appeared
I've been running from something
deep inside
And it's worse than I feared
'Cause I look in your eyes
and I can't hide
- I push you away
- Don't push me away
But the feelings come back
just twice as strong
- I don't know what to say
- You know just what to say
But I know that I'm right where I belong
The way you know just where to be
- I don't know
- The way you move, the way you see
- You see me
- The way you feel when you're with me
- Beside me
- Don't hide from me anymore
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
What do I say?
Where do I go?
How do I know you feel the same?
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
Quiet and low, letting it go,
letting you know it's in me
Ev'rywhere that I roam
I remind myself not to overstay
Ev'ry time I find home
Something happens to take that home away
But you've seen what I've seen
- I see you
- As you lead with
A strength that shines right through
You move like a queen, a true queen
Don't let anything take me away from you
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
Say it again, say it again
Tell me I'll always be with you
- Tell me it's you
- I know it's you
Say it again, say it again
Tell me you're always with me
- The way you know just where to be
- Now I know
- The way you move, the way you see
- I see you
The love I feel when you're with me
Beside me, beside me
Say it again, say it again, say it again
Tell me the world won't interfere
Say it again, say it again
Tell me the words I wanna hear
Open your eyes and here we go
I know it's you
You know I love her, my brother
There's nothing we keep from each other
I saved your life
This is how you repay me?
What do I do?
What does it mean?
How do I ever unsee
what I've seen?
He was my kin
She was my queen
Now it's broken forever and...
"Tell her it's you!
She knows it's you!"
What did you say to her?
What did you do?
I'm next in line
She should be mine, ha!
Are the ancestors laughing, I...
What would they say?
Father is gone
Not before giving me strength to go on
He never trusted you!
Did he know
you'd betray me so?
When you were drowning
I pulled you out
I gave you life
which you lived in my debt!
Now I'm the one drowning
Tumbling down
Trying to escape what I cannot forget
I have a brother no longer
It's over and done
Now all I have is this shame
and this rage that I can't...
Out...
...run
Deceit is a tool of a great king.
There wasn't much to eat on this mountain...
until now.
Tell me, how did you cover your tracks
in the snow?
A bird helped us.
Lions getting help from a bird?
Just as I will help you.
You will help us?
You think we need help from a wounded coward?
I may hold the blood of a king...
but it was Mufasa who killed your son.
It was Mufasa...
who trapped you up here...
outsmarted you at every turn.
Now I will lead you to him and to Milele.
Milele!
Milele is nothing but a dream,
a vision sold to cubs.
Well, tell that to the monkey.
He leads them to it.
Look at you.
A pack of starving wolves...
clinging to the side of a mountain.
No tracks to follow.
Only one chance at revenge.
Me!
Revenge...
What about your father?
Because of Mufasa...
I have no father.
He did this.
Yes.
You lost a father...
and I, a son.
Taka, will you join us?
Together, we can both have our revenge.
It will be my pleasure...
King.
Taka!
Taka, where have you been?
Hunting.
I couldn't find anything...
but I was never as good as you.
Or my mother.
- There's something I need to tell you.
- No.
There's something I need to tell you.
I need to thank you.
You kept your word to Eshe and Obasi.
- Taka...
- You saved me, Mufasa.
And I...
will never forget what you've done,
my brother.
Guys! I have found a way down
just beyond those near peaks.
Was it something I said?
Hey, Rafiki?
Yes.
We are nearing destiny, Mufasa.
And so, the earth must shake.
Okay, now I am 100 million percent sure
who Taka is.
Just be honest. Is it me?
In case you missed it,
we're not featured in this.
I think the civet has more screen time.
- Hey, maybe they'll put us in the play.
- No, no, please don't mention the play again.
I went to see it.
I'm nothing but a giant sock puppet.
You went to see it?
You didn't bring me?
Rafiki, Mufasa and Sarabi are in love?
Love?
That sounds gross and not something like
I constantly think about and really want.
What is Taka gonna do to them?
Little one, Taka's heart was broken.
And now his trap was set.
Mufasa. Do you see?
I don't believe it.
The other side of the light.
Home.
Milele.
I can't believe it.
We found it. We found Milele.
Yes.
You found it, brother.
You always do.
Rafiki.
This is the tree from your visions.
I have seen this tree many times...
and, in each vision,
there was always a brother...
standing right here.
But there's no one here, Rafiki...
and you came here to find your twin.
He was taken from me long ago.
What I saw in my dreams was a brother.
Standing right here.
A friend, family.
What I saw was you.
The unseeable.
I saw Mufasa.
Me?
Yes, you.
My brother.
Mufasa.
How do you know who I am?
We know the Outsiders are hunting you,
and we fear you'll bring danger.
No. No. We covered our tracks.
I promise you Milele is a safe place...
and I would never do anything
to jeopardize that.
Do not run.
You have nothing to fear.
We are not here for you.
We have come for Mufasa.
Oh, no, no. How did they get here?
Do not let him divide us.
It's no use, Mufasa.
The Circle...
The Circle is broken.
No!
Mufasa, what are you doing?
I'm going to fight, and I'm going
to show them that they can fight, too.
Rafiki, when you hear my signal,
help me call them together.
Yes, my brother.
There are other lions here.
Find them.
With pleasure, Your Majesty.
Mufasa, you're not alone.
It's my turn to go ask questions first.
This is where the hunt ends, Mufasa.
Thanks to your brother.
He left a trail of scars for us to follow.
He made a deal to save himself.
- Gave us this kingdom.
- Tell me he's lying.
Asked us to kill the stray.
Taka, please!
I'm the son of a king.
But Sarabi chose you.
Just like Mother.
Just like my own father.
I saved you and you betrayed me!
What have you done?
I'm your brother, fight with me!
You stole my destiny.
Now this is yours.
He's one of us now.
My son's name...
was Shaju.
Shaju!
All of this should have been his.
And now I will rule it without mercy.
This one is mine.
Please. We can't wage this battle alone.
There's nothing we can do.
They've chased us
from our pride lands before.
- They're too strong.
- Fight with us.
Fight for your young.
For your future.
What future?
They've taken all we have.
And they will always take more.
I am Mufasa, a stray with no pride...
and yet I stand before you.
Head unbowed.
I know you're afraid, but trust me.
Nothing will change
if we remain isolated to our own tribes...
without concern for the fate of others.
But why should we stand with you?
This is your fight.
Today, they are here for us lions,
but I assure you...
as you let them walk among you
in search of us now...
they are plotting to come for you tomorrow.
One lion's hope cannot change
the fate of Milele.
There is no lion as large as an elephant,
as strong as an oxen...
fast as a cheetah or tall as a giraffe...
who can soar and scout as wide and far...
as the cranes and hawks in the sky.
So, can't you see...
Every being has a place
in the Circle of Life.
My breath is your breath.
Your fight is my fight.
I will not bend to evil,
and neither should you.
Mufasa is right.
Milele is home.
We must stand with Mufasa!
Together we shall stand strong for Milele!
Here comes the lion!
From this moment on...
everything the light touches belongs to me.
You'll have to take it.
Bye-bye.
You've messed with the wrong hornbill!
Lunch is served.
Stand down! I am highly trained
and occasionally a...
This is so embarrassing.
I do have wings, you know.
Taka!
Taka, please. Please!
Mufasa.
You dare...
to challenge me?
You took my son.
My future.
Taka, your moment of courage will come.
Blood for blood.
Please. Don't kill him.
I didn't kill him.
You did.
They're coming.
The last lions.
Time for their extinction...
and we'll start with the youngest.
The earth will shake.
Attack!
Mufasa.
Close your eyes...
and tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
Mufasa!
He defeated the Outsiders.
- The king of Milele!
Is that him? Our king?
Your Highness.
- The King of Milele.
The King of Milele.
- My king.
- Your Highness.
- Your Majesty.
- My king.
Defeated Kiros!
- King?
No, no, I'm not king.
Raise your heads.
No. I'm just... No, no!
No more kings.
We are all one. Please.
Please. Raise your heads.
But, Mufasa...
you have brought them together.
You helped them see in themselves
what they considered unseeable.
Nothing is more kingly.
No, Rafiki.
I'm not king.
I'm not royal blood.
Don't you see, my brother?
It is not what you were...
it is what you have become.
The King of Milele.
My brother...
something beautiful awaits you.
Is this real?
But it can't be.
It can't be.
Mufasa.
But how can it be?
I had a son named Mufasa.
Taken from me by a great flood.
Mother?
I never stopped hoping.
Believing.
My son.
I've dreamt of this moment.
And now it's come true.
Oh, Mufasa.
But Father?
Where's Father?
He lives in you now.
He lives in you.
I always dreamed we'd be together again.
And I knew it would be in Milele.
My son.
Mufasa.
Mufasa, please forgive me.
You must banish him, Sire.
As long as I am king...
my brother will have a place here.
Brother, I am so...
But I won't ever...
say your name again.
I can't.
I won't.
Then call me Scar.
So I will never forget what I have done.
Scar.
Your Majesty.
Welcome home.
So, Mufasa...
I see your family has been awaiting you
in Milele after all.
Yes, Rafiki.
Yes, they were.
It is your time, Mufasa.
Rafiki, I wish I could see him.
I wish I could meet my grandfather.
As Mufasa once told your father...
look into the heavens, Kiara.
The great kings of the past
will always be there...
waiting for you.
I don't want him to go, Rafiki.
I don't want it to end.
Don't you see, Kiara?
Mufasa lives in you.
He lives in you.
Dad!
- Rafiki.
- It was unbelievable.
- It was perfect.
- You could not improve on it.
That said, I do have notes.
Some suggestions.
Take 'em or leave 'em. But take 'em.
- Dad!
- Kiara!
Kiara.
Dad.
Where's Mom?
Well, love, there's something
you need to know.
What? Did something happen to Mom?
Baby, I'm right here, and I'm fine.
Where were you?
Kiara...
this is your new brother.
Brother?
I have a brother?
Hi there. I'm Kiara.
I will take care of you.
Forever.
Little one...
let me tell you a story.
A story of a great king.