Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Look at the stars,
whenever you feel alone,
the great kings of the past
will always be prepared to guide you.
And so will I.
My friends, the time of
my family's growth is upon us.
This home we share is the
fulfillment of my father's vision.
How wonderful is it
that Nala and I get to continue
his dream and make
even greater the circle of life.
Nala my love, I'm on my way.
Nala, I'm here.
I'm here.
Security detail has arrived.
One gentle reminder, we are not food.
No, no, no, no, no.
We are just two guys walking to
work through a pride of hungry lion.
Which is perfectly
normal, I'm not terrified.
Security detail reporting
for due to your grace, your highness.
Ruler of all four legged creatures.
And that one three legged zebra.
Oh right, Ron.
That was tragic.
It was an Eden Ron.
Yeah.
Ron has three legs,
that's the one more than me.
Well, are those arms or legs?
I don't know, I think they're paws.
I consider all those legs.
Guys, this is serious.
I need you to stay
with Kiara until I get back.
Are you saying that your security
detail has been called on to do babysitting?
Pumba, we should really discuss
this because I don't really love children.
Guys, I promise her
everything would be okay.
Well, that's one way to parent.
You're gonna have to grow up sometime.
What else did you tell her?
That she could be
whatever she wants to be?
That life is fair?
I need you two to try
and act like adults, okay?
Don't scare Kiara.
And most of all, no stories.
No stories?
Wait a second.
I know where your head goes.
I grew up with you two. Promise me.
Okay, you know what?
You know what?
Fine.
No stories.
Speak for yourself, Pumba.
No.
Shh.
We'll tell a story anyway.
Okay, well, Tom,
we're not gonna tell a story.
We're never gonna tell a story.
Are you serious?
I'm clearly within earshot.
Dad.
Hey, little one.
Dad, the storm's coming and I'm scared.
I want to go with you and Mom.
Well, don't be scared, my love.
Timon and Pumba will
watch you while I'm gone.
Be brave now, Kiara.
Be brave.
Okay!
We've prepared a story!
Sky looked at us.
He knew it was the end of the line.
I could smell the fear.
That was actually me, but yes.
So you two defeated
Scar and then you ate him?
Honestly, one of
the best meals I ever had.
My dad told me he defeated Scar.
Well, okay, but your dad, as
we all know, is a pathological liar.
He's always lying.
Get it?
I'm scared.
I want Mom and Dad.
Look, look, look,
look, don't be scared, Kiara.
How about...
He sent you a song.
And a what? Pumba, no, it
is way too early for the song.
It worked on Simba.
He thought he had
murdered his own father.
He was singing and
dancing around in seconds.
I can't just turn it on like
that. I have to be in the moment.
He sang that song for six years straight.
Well, who didn't?
It's Ron, the
three-legged zebra. Run for your life!
He didn't even say anything about it.
We're sorry, Ron. They were jokes.
They were just jokes.
It's Rafiki.
Rafiki! Rafiki!
Little one, there's no reason to cry.
My parents, they're gone.
Hey, look out there, Mdugle.
You see those
bough-bough trees blowing in the wind?
The roots of those trees
are very strong, like your family.
And just as they did for you,
your parents have gone to
the ceremony of birth in grounds.
And when they return, the circle of
life will bring a blessing to you, Kiara,
that you will never forget.
Man, he's good.
He's such a visual story to him.
Yet it makes sense that he lives alone.
I just want the storm to
pass, and then I promise to be brave.
I tell you a secret.
When your father Simba was your age,
he was afraid of the
thunder and would hide behind the king.
When did he stop hiding?
One day during a big stop, your
grandfather Mufasa took your father to the lake.
He was the very top of Bright Rock,
taught him to stand
with him and howl into the wind.
And Simba slowly
stepped out with the king,
and together they roared into the night.
But I'm not brave like my dad.
I could never be like Mufasa.
He's not so.
And maybe it's time I tell you a story.
A story of a cub,
not much bigger than you.
A lion born without a
drop of nobility in his blood.
A lion who would
change over lives forever.
A story!
So glad I brought some presents.
But go easy, we're in a cave.
This story begins far
beyond the mountains and the shadows,
on the other side of the light.
In this place,
everything was dying of this.
As twenty-full moons have
passed without a single drop of water.
But when the skies
finally opened, destiny would rain.
Mufasa.
Mufasa! Come see!
Mom, what is that light way out there?
Oh, that's very special.
Beyond the horizon,
beyond the last cloud in the sky,
that's a place we call "Milele".
Milele?
Well, it means "forever".
Imagine a kingdom
full of life, water and food,
grass and sky as far as the eye can see.
Will we ever go there?
Oh, yes, Mufasa.
That's exactly where we're headed.
But we can also be there right now.
We can close our
eyes, let our dreams take us.
Beyond the horizon,
beyond the last cloud in the sky,
there's a place I know.
Imagine a kingdom, the water
flows, the grass and sky as not a dream.
They will grow, call it Milele.
We know that there is
nothing wrong, there is always more.
Can you feel it?
We'll wander, no
longer, we carry answers.
We'll find a way, can you see it?
And can you see it?
Can you find a way?
We'll wander, no
longer, we carry answers.
We will bring Milele.
What is this?
Rain, rain! Finally we have rain!
Dad, race it to the light!
You're too fast, I've never
beaten you, nobody has ever beaten you.
I know!
Mufasa, fastest cup in the world!
Mufasa, come back now!
Mufasa, stay there! I'm coming, son!
Father! Mufasa!
Mufasa! I'll catch you on the turn!
Find my voice!
Mufasa!
The clippers do have
but you can cross it to them!
Come on, Mufasa, you can do this.
Find my voice!
Mufasa! Mufasa!
Mufasa!
You can cross it to them!
Come on, Mufasa, you can do this.
Find your mother's voice!
Listen to your
father, Mufasa, listen to us!
Come here, he's there!
Mom!
He's there!
Mother! Mother!
Find your footing one step at a time!
I can't!
You can do this, I'm right here!
Mufasa! Mom?
Dad?
Can you hear me?
Is anyone out there?
Mom!
Please.
Mom, he's there.
The floodwaters joined the distant river,
carried Mufasa far
from his mother and father,
beyond all that he knew.
Mufasa!
Hello!
I'm Taka, son of a barsee.
What's your name?
Mufasa.
I'm not allowed to talk to outsiders,
but I have a secret,
and I really want to tell you.
What's the secret?
I'll get in trouble.
Please, just tell me.
I don't know.
Just tell me!
OK.
You're about to be eaten!
I hate secrets!
Swim!
You have to swim! I don't know how!
All right, chin up, then walk underwater.
Really fast!
I can't!
Come on, you faster!
Faster!
Help me, Taka!
Help me!
[growling]
I told you to wait for me.
It's not my fault, Mum.
I came down for a
drink and saw him floating by.
I'd like you to meet Mufasa.
You're lucky those crocs
were young and afraid to fight.
Let's go.
We can't just leave him here.
Rules are rules, Taka.
Obasi will never accept a stray.
I'm not a stray.
I'm just lost.
See?
He's just lost.
There was a flood.
My parents, they tried to save me.
Do you know which way is home?
Home.
To be lost is to learn the way.
Call me Eshe.
I'm tired, Eshe.
Come on, it's this way.
Come on, Rufasa.
Is this Malaylin? No, my love.
I was trying to nap, Eshe.
The all-important nap of kings,
only to be awoken by the
disgusting, hideous, revolting stench of a stray.
Will we come upon an outsider?
Tell me, what do we do?
Obasi, I know.
Eat it.
But I found him, Dad.
I saved his life.
Baka, we do not associate with outsiders.
The only true bond is blood.
I've heard stories
of lions twice our size.
These outsiders will
devour everything in their path.
Does he look like
he's going to devour you?
Oh, that smell is disgusting.
I'm not even sure
I could eat this kepete.
I'm not a kepete.
I'm a Mufasa.
Do you even know what Mufasa means?
No.
It means king.
And that's me.
You better start
running, little Mufasa, for your life.
If I run, you'll never catch me.
I'm the fastest kapa I ever lived.
My father taught me so.
Oh, Taka, you have a challenge.
They will race to the dead tree and back.
And when the prince defeats
him, I will finish him in one battle.
What if Mufasa wins?
If he wins, he lives, Obasi.
He stays with me.
You have my word.
Let the race begin.
Ooh, clumsy little stray.
Run, Mufasa.
You did not have to do that.
Taka is the future king.
He has to win his first challenge.
No, Obasi.
To be a true king, he must earn it.
Don't take that away from him.
[barking]
[grunting]
I'm sorry.
[barking]
[screaming]
[music playing]
I have one more secret, Professor.
I always wanted a brother.
[music playing]
[laughing]
Zeta! Obasi!
You will keep him with the females.
Tucker, how could you lose to a stray?
Well done, Tucker. Well done.
I thought you said you
were fast. I had to let you in.
Well, I did just go
gaze with no sleep, all right?
Anyway, come on, me
fusser. Let's get some trouble.
[music playing]
Where'd he go?
I always wanted a brother.
I still remember my
mother one season after another.
One season after another.
Season after season
after season after another.
Who would sing for my brother?
Who would do anything for my brother?
I'll be king with my brother on my side.
I always wanted a brother.
Now we rely on each other.
Season after another.
He moved faster.
His and Tucker are
anxious to the other side.
They're anxious to the other side.
[music playing]
(suspenseful music)
Emma, please stand here!
(screaming)
(growling)
(laughing)
Togaro jumped like 20 feet!
Oh, that's a new record!
Obasi, they did it again!
Your sons are nothing but trouble.
That one is not my son.
They're heathens, the both of them.
This stray is
forbidden to be near the shade tree.
Mufos and I were just playing.
You two will never be brothers.
Go back to the
females and stay away from my son.
Oh, your mother, she adopts every lizard.
Speaks to passing grasshoppers.
I want to go with him.
You want to be with the females.
You belong with the males.
He gets to hunt with mother.
One day, he will betray you.
That is what strays do.
Mufos and we'll never betray me.
Hey, hey, this will all be yours, my son.
You will be king.
So pay attention.
Study every move I make.
Sleeping again.
That is what males do.
We protect the pride as we nap.
That's, well, that's power.
Power.
Why are we stopping?
Close your eyes
and tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
There's a herd of antelope
heading across the dry lake bed.
Half a day from here.
And how do you know they're not gazelles?
Their steps are too
heavy, moving way too slow.
What else?
Come on, you can do it.
When the wind hits their horns,
it moves up instead of across.
So definitely animal horns.
Very good.
What is it, Mufasa?
What's wrong?
Sometimes I get a sin.
It's barely a trace on the wind.
It smells like home.
And it's gone.
Mufasa, your parents are still out there.
We can keep looking.
I've lost them, Eshe.
You're wasting your
time training me like this.
But these skills you
have, no other male has them.
Obasi will never accept me.
I'll never be his blood, his family.
But you are my family.
And if Obasi could
see how gifted you are.
Well, maybe I like being a stray.
You know, no rules, no responsibility.
I'm the lucky one, Eshe.
What do you mean, Mufasa?
I never have to be like Taka.
I never have to be King.
Ay-ay-ay.
Did he say no
rules and no responsibility?
An outcast afraid of
water never takes a bath.
Which means he smells like me?
Which is not good.
Well, either way, I think
that means that he's one of us.
This is it?
It's our time.
And a one, and a two, and a one, two.
Hakuna Mufasa
What a wonderful name
He ain't no passing craze
It means no wrong.
What?
Don't you go, man.
All right, all right.
Rafiki's right,
we'll get letters from legal.
Faltres will take everything we have.
Which technically is nothing.
Look at us, we're naked animals.
It's the wonder I'm always freezing.
They want this.
Come on, Pumbaa.
Let's bring it home.
Hakuna Mufasa
Quiet!
Here is a music snob.
Rafiki, keep going.
Later that day, Eshe was teaching Mufasa
how to hunt in pairs.
But as Taka was secretly watching,
something terrible was hunting them.
(suspenseful music)
Quiet.
Mufasa, run!
Ashwin!
(grunting)
(suspenseful music)
Keep moving, Mufasa.
Hey, go for the net!
(suspenseful music)
(growling)
It's okay, Mufasa.
It's okay.
I was very brave of you, Mufasa.
Thank you.
Eshe, what has happened?
Are you hurt?
They were huge, white as ghosts,
like nothing I've seen before.
Oh, Vasi.
Had Mufasa not been there, I...
(growling)
Taka.
(suspenseful music)
(growling)
I owe you a great debt, Mufasa.
We need to prepare.
They're downwind, less than a day away.
No, you couldn't possibly know this.
Send a scout and you'll see.
They'll be coming for us.
J'Aril.
Father, please, let me explain.
Not now.
Not now?
Taka, come.
(growling)
Where is my son?
There was a young lion, Majesty.
He fought Sha'ju.
And yet, you came back.
You survived.
I was badly hurt.
I promise, Majesty, this is the truth.
The truth.
Yes, the truth.
The truth is standing behind you.
(growling)
There were others.
He's Majesty.
But only one left blood on his name.
Which means he left Sha'ju to die.
Saved himself.
This young lion will see him their king.
His blood is common, ordinary.
I was here there.
King.
No, Kiritos.
You are the only king.
An ordinary lion.
And you left my son to die.
I was injured.
There was no choice, please, Majesty.
You have to believe me.
There's no reason to fear me.
I would never harm one of my own.
Thank you, Majesty.
I'll leave that pleasure to them.
Majesty!
(growling)
No one can ever know you ran,
that you ran for your mother.
It never happened,
Taka, do you understand?
But I didn't know, I
was just, I was just scared.
It doesn't matter.
We must protect the bloodline.
Protect them with the lie?
Father, that's deceitful.
Deceit is a tool of a great king.
Taka, it's what kings must do.
But I'm not a king.
I'm just your son.
Obashek.
Shigaru.
Obasii.
Shigaru, I'm here.
What did you see?
They're coming this way, Obasii.
Two lions for every one of ours,
each one bigger than the next,
but none as mighty as Kirops.
They're terrifying king.
Outsiders, stories were all true.
I must protect the bloodline, Eshei.
The future of this pride.
Taka, you are that future.
Did you?
Dad, what do you mean?
I'm sending you away, far from here.
You will leave and
start a new life, a new beginning.
I need you to go with him,
Mofasa, to pledge your loyalty.
They'll arrive with the sunrise.
(birds chirping)
Where will we go, Eshei?
Without you, I have no home.
Mofasa, you and Taka
together, that, that is home.
Eshei?
Mofasa, look out there, beyond the light.
You know what I see?
I see the place
your mother told you about.
A place beyond the river's end,
across the deepest
canyon on the other side
of the mountains, a
place beyond the horizon itself.
A bright land so green, so perfect
that to see it is to see--
Malaylei?
Yes, forever.
My parents spoke of Malaylei often.
My mother told me
it was where we were going.
And don't you see, Mofasa?
You must keep going.
You must continue
your journey toward the light.
Please, Eshei, I can't lose you.
You have my love always, Mofasa.
But your family is still out there.
Waiting for you.
I can feel their
presence, and I know you can too.
Go, go, Mofasa.
Find your way home.
(birds chirping)
Mother, please forgive me.
I beg you.
There's no need, my love.
Daga, your moment of courage will come.
Now both of you go.
Go and find your
place in the circle of love.
(dramatic music)
They left their
family never to see them again?
This story is killing me.
It's toying with my emotion.
Here is the worst part.
What's that?
A man of crickets.
Oh, maybe that's for the best.
I need a bathroom
break before the second act.
Everyone wait for me.
(dramatic music)
I am back.
Tumba, did you wash your hooves?
Mm-hmm.
Tumba.
I did, I did.
I'm just gonna walk
on them again right after.
Tumba.
(grunts)
Rafiki, did the outsiders come?
Yes, and as the hunters led Kirus
into the Valley of Kings,
Oubasi and Asher stood their ground.
(dramatic music)
(roaring)
What one of you is king?
You have no reason to challenge me.
Does this look like a challenge king?
There are rooms among lions.
Not anymore.
While you rule
this, try to build my army.
Yours is the last
pride in the Valley of Kings,
which means everything the light touches
belongs to thee.
There will be one ruler, one lion king.
(roaring)
You say you are the king
But you lie around in the shade
Out of shame unafraid
The moon cuts the path through the sky
By night or by day
It doesn't obey
And I let you run
You to my son
I hope you can run
But I'm gonna be the last thing you see
Before you go bye bye
There you go bye bye
Climb every tree across land and sea
I make you go bye bye
I sing in my glottals
Bye bye
Everything the light touches
The circle of life is a lie
A pretty way to say
there are predators and prey
That circle of order's a pie
They keep stealing glands
They don't like your chances
And neither do I
You are my pride
And I'm gonna be the last thing you see
Before you go bye bye
There you go bye bye
Climb every tree across land and sea
Until you go bye bye
Where you go bye bye
Bye bye for vengeance is mine
And I'm the last of my line
I must be soon
Bye bye
I make you go bye bye
(grunting)
Bye bye
We have to move.
They'll be tracking us.
Parker!
What if you're wrong?
What if they're okay?
Live in you now.
Follow me, brother.
We have to move.
Together.
(grunting)
Run real faster.
Run!
Butters.
What's the plan?
Run very fast.
(grunting)
This way!
Back to the trees.
We're trapped.
We have to swim.
No, we have to fight.
We fight, we die.
What if we swim, we drown?
Okay, I didn't want to do this,
but I command you to swim.
What?
You've led your
loyalty, I command you to swim.
Parker, this is not the time to jump.
Wait, so what have you killed, my son?
I did.
This lion with me is nothing but a stray.
Let him go.
You see, the other is no stray.
He holds the blood of the problem.
The last blood of the king.
We are ten for blood.
They're coming.
What do we do?
Find the advantage.
We'll have five kids, we're on a rock
in the middle of the warcraft.
Parker, this is it.
We go for the king.
New barter, I'm ready.
Stop, one last thing.
You won't.
Get up.
Parker, this was a bad idea.
What was that?
(laughing)
We're alive.
I did it.
I said don't.
You understand what I'm saying?
( Due arrest! )
( This is why I care about you. )
( I promise! )
(explosion)
Okay, okay.
No, no more water.
Tell me you can track them down river.
We can track them anywhere.
They can run, but they can't hide.
(ominous music)
So just to be
clear, we're not in this story.
It feels a little bit like Giros
is stealing my thunder here.
Yeah, you know, I don't feel seen.
No, there's a lot
of stories with all of us.
Tell one of those.
One small
suggestion, less childhood drama,
more mere catch.
Well, Ziggy, I
know who Chaka is gonna be.
Oh, me too.
It's so obvious, but maybe
just so we're on the same page.
Tell me, is it Simba?
Is it me? Oh, Simba.
Am I your bossy?
That makes no sense, but
seriously, I have one question.
Am I Chaka?
I did it again.
Not that I'm counting,
but I saved your heart again.
As much as it cues you
to say it, let's hear a little
thank you, you are the one of me.
The thank you for
pushing me off a waterfall.
Yes, and you're welcome.
Look, it's not my fault.
Crocodile's are simply attracted to you.
Don't, don't say that.
(laughing)
I did it again.
(growling)
Mufasa. Shh.
Is it, is it them?
Is it the outsiders?
No, she's right there.
Gee.
(suspenseful music)
There's no place to run.
We have your scent.
My scent.
I've been stalking you two all night.
That's not possible.
Then why did I circle
you three times in this wood
while you two were
chasing each other's tails?
(growling)
(screaming)
Not too bad, I said.
Yeah, well, I meant to do that.
So. Still think I'm afraid?
Why are you following us?
I was hoping to find my pride.
What happened? The outsiders happened.
A few of us got away,
but you're the only other lions
I've seen.
You two better keep moving.
Wait, please.
My name is Taka, son of Obasi.
I know what it's like to lose everything.
Come with us, we can help you.
I don't need any help.
But you don't have anyone.
He does indeed have
someone, thank you very much.
That's Zazu, don't eat him.
You heard her, do not eat me.
As a recent addition
to the king's royal guard,
I must kindly ask you both to move on.
Thank you for stopping by.
How can your king
hide a bird to protect you?
How high can you fly?
Look, I needed a scout.
Zazu was the last option.
Well, next to last.
Between Albert, the iguana, and I,
his majesty decided
on the underling with wings,
and thus, I became the
lead scout for the princess.
It's my third day going swimmingly,
if I may say so myself.
Zorabi, you can say so as well.
How far do you
think you'll get with a bird?
How far do you two
geniuses think you'll get
stumbling around running into each other?
All the way to Malayle.
Malayle is nothing but a myth.
It's not a myth.
A circle of life and fairy tale herds.
You're chasing
something that doesn't exist.
I don't know that Malayle exists,
but right now,
it's the only hope we have.
We don't need hope.
We need food.
Good job, brother.
Oh, real nice.
(dramatic music)
There's trouble in the trees.
My first tree was
trouble, and I am going to pass.
You're going?
I am staying right here.
Thank you.
It's yours, Zorabi.
I think it's like
there's dinner headed our way.
Zorabi, if I may, he
makes a valid point, your highness.
But on the other
hand, he's a starving lion.
He wants to eat
me, so I am slightly torn.
I think that went quite
well, all things considered.
(dramatic music)
(crowd cheering)
And now, Kiara, this is where I come in.
(dramatic music)
Thank you.
Order!
We will have order
in the Congress of Baboons.
Tonight, a cheetah came into our trees
for the third night in a row.
Almost took one of our own.
He was a rafiki for.
He summoned a beast with his dreams.
Rafiki and his visions
must be banished once and for all.
Rafiki tried to warn you.
His dreams conjure our enemies.
He talks to the
spirits, summons the devil.
What are you talking about?
He's done it before.
His brother was
chased from these very trees,
never to be seen again.
Rafiki was just a child.
A child born with
a leg that does not work,
yet somehow he survived?
It was Rafiki who
found water in the dry season.
Who healed you,
Enaki, when you were sick?
He speaks to the insects.
He converses with the moon.
Mzala, you know what will happen
if you send him down from the trees.
Here's Amalani,
you are, a curse to us all.
That's not true.
He doesn't belong here.
All in favor of
banishment, cover one eye.
(people chattering)
And so, it is time.
No, wait.
Where will you go?
The way I should have gone long ago,
to find all that was lost, my family.
You can't survive on your own.
Nobody can.
And yet, here we are.
Oh, Rafiki.
But I never forget
what the heart has seen.
(suspenseful music)
(slizing)
( INTENSE MUSIC)
(pAnne laughs)
I don't think you
understand what's about to happen.
There's no place for you to go.
I am going forward.
I seriously doubt that.
It is easy to doubt
everything when you know nothing.
Can we get on with this, please?
If you take my life,
you will never find Melele.
Wait, did you say Melele?
That is where I am going.
To ward the light.
I've been there many times in my dreams.
My brother waits for me there.
I've seen the tree, can picture it.
The two of us together again.
And why would
anyone trust a baboon's dream?
Sometimes a dream is all you have.
The only truth that lives in you,
like the memory of a great king.
How did you know?
Okay, help us get to
Melele and we will let you live.
Do we have a deal?
No.
What?
Why?
Rafiki will let you live.
I've had enough of this, Parker.
Do not eat.
Wonderful.
Other misfits
straight were not supposed to eat.
So you expect us to follow this baboon
to a place nobody has ever seen?
Ha, I'll be better off alone.
Hey, dumbassan.
A single stick may
smoke, but it will never burn.
Okay, now that there's five of us,
why don't we all go around
and say a fun fact about ourselves?
I'll go first.
I once had a crush on a flamingo.
We've never said that out loud.
And they're walking away.
Yeah, places to go, kingdoms to see.
We're busy, let's hustle.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now you're the star of this thing?
Someone's a little tired
of being sick of banana, huh?
All of a sudden there's
a lot of Rafiki in the story.
You even gave
yourself a long lost brother.
What's next, a funny catch break?
Are you gonna be farting next?
That's my thing.
You cannot tell the story of Mofapa.
We have the story of Rafiki.
Now he's even talking
about himself in the third person.
Pretty soon he'll have his own fragrance.
And I'm the only one
with a fragrance around here.
It's called Poba by Poba.
From what I hear, it's pretty gross.
Mom, Dad, if you can hear me, come home.
Please, come home.
(dramatic music)
Okay.
Where?
Me lately.
(burping)
(soft music)
Rafiki.
Hi, Suga.
What are you doing?
I am fishing.
You're sitting on a
rock with your eyes closed.
My eyes are open.
It is my lids that are closed.
Why am I talking to a bad girl?
I am not a baboon.
I am a mandrel.
No offense, but a monkey is a monkey.
And a stray is a stray.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means we are very much the same.
(speaking foreign language)
We are nothing alike.
Take a good look.
I am a lion.
The lion who sears water,
fears his own reflection,
who can't sleep because of what he sees
when he closes his eyes.
Huh?
You are afraid of your dreams, Mufasa.
Afraid of what you see in them.
I see my parents.
I feel them everywhere.
Of course you do, Mufasa.
You will feel them forever.
My mother, I hear her voice.
She tells me that we
are on a journey to Malaylay,
but I feel so lost without her.
Your journey is not a dream, Mufasa.
Your mother is guiding you.
And where you are going, a family awaits.
(grunts)
(speaking foreign language)
What are you doing?
We're starving.
Because not it's time.
Instead, the fish has
agreed to let us share the water.
(sighs)
(speaking foreign language)
Take your smile.
I have a report.
It's morning.
End of report.
The Earth divided is now a choice,
around or down.
The decision is yours.
Look out there.
Beyond the light,
across the deepest canyon.
Across the deepest canyon.
We should go down.
Why?
Because of some fairy tale.
The rocks will hide our tracks.
It's safer to go around.
I pick up their scent.
The only thing you
picked up is a hallucinating baboon.
I am a mentor.
This is a waste of time.
Close your eyes.
What?
Tell me what you see, what you feel.
There's nothing on the land.
No, they're moving
through the bush wallow.
They who?
The females, out front.
Come on, clear
your thoughts, concentrate.
I am concentrating.
(dramatic music)
He's right.
We have to go down.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
We are more than one.
Now the many
sticks will make fire as one.
Come on, we have places to go.
And kingdoms to say.
What's our plan?
You wanna go fast, go alone
There's the road, off you go
But if you wanna go far
We go together
So good, so far
If your father left you in my care
Whoa, whoa, whoa
And now we're running who knows where
Sometimes you need a bird
Like you and I
I want you to see me through
I land my hair
You wanna go fast, go alone
Day and night
There's the road
And just like
Off you go
Yeah, all right
If you wanna go far
We go together
So good, so far
I will find my family again
I will walk with you until then
I will walk with you till the end
It's much easier with a friend
I will find my family again
I will walk with you until then
I will walk with you till the end
It's much easier
Like a cloud and rain
Like a meal in a field of rain
Like a flex of gold in your main shrub
You and me
Go together
Cloud and rain
We are living in a great world
The peace of gold in your main shrub
You and me
Go together
My brother waits for a reason to sign
Down anywhere
My brother knows the word
He's like the devil
My brother tends to play decorate
It's big, it's nice to meet you
It's like a man
It's a man
It's a man No, no, no, no
There we go
No, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no
We go together
So good, so far
(cheering)
(laughing)
As we headed across the great valley,
the hunters tracked our every move.
Heroes, they are not alone.
They've connected a lioness.
And a monkey.
(roaring)
Mufasa?
Mufasa, you have to help me.
Help you how?
It's Sarabi, Mufasa.
She is the light my mother spoke of.
What? She's special.
The most amazing
female I've ever met in my life.
I don't know what to say to her.
You've spent your life with females.
Please, tell me what to say.
Just talk to her. Be yourself.
Mufasa, you don't understand.
Myself isn't good enough.
You just know things.
Fine, fine.
Keep it simple.
Ask her a question.
Right, a question?
This is good.
Yeah, try to be confident, disinterested.
But I'm very interested.
Tell her about the flowers.
What flowers?
The valley she comes from.
There's flowers everywhere.
Duck flowers, long stems.
It's absolutely beautiful.
How do you know that?
When she passes, I
can smell them on her fur.
Okay.
Flowers, disinterested.
And here's the
most important thing, okay?
Listen when she speaks.
Males have trouble with that one.
Sorry.
What did you say?
Really?
You know what I mean?
I heard you, brother.
I'm gonna make you proud.
Oh.
It's very hard, isn't it?
Yep.
Oh.
I love listening.
Okay.
I'm listening right now.
To what?
What you just said.
I am.
You smell like a duck.
What?
Flower.
A duck flower.
How do you know about those flowers?
I...
Well, I inhaled you with my nose.
I can smell them.
That's amazing.
Our valley was full of those flowers,
thousands of them,
as far as the eye could see.
It was the most beautiful place, Taka.
Did he just say she smells like a duck?
And you call me a baboon.
I shouldn't be here.
The migration patterns are broken.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry, sir.
This is not a drill.
Just to be clear, I
never signed up for this.
It's okay.
It's safe.
They're on the other side.
No!
They can just jump across.
We're trapped.
What do we do?
The elephants will fight with us.
And why would they do that?
Because I'm going to ask them.
Got a better idea?
Yes, Mr. Ask questions first.
Get ready to run.
Um...
Where is she going?
Hello?
Listen to me, please.
We need your help.
Can you talk with me?
Please.
They're coming!
Trombie!
Trombie wait!
Wait wait!
Just go for the hide!
Like I said, get ready to run!
Run!
Get to the trees!
Why are you running?
Run!
You are behind us!
Hold on!
I found you!
Trombie!
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Egypt.
Ex Industriaan!
Do not reach me.
(screaming)
I got you, I got you.
Sarabi, I got you.
That's right, run
along little kitty cats.
Meow, meow.
Thank you, my friend.
(crashing)
(somber music)
(groaning)
Over here.
(somber music)
(speaking foreign language)
Alive, she's alive.
Why are you all looking at me?
You were thrown from the tree.
She saved your life.
Who?
Taka, Taka saved you.
Isn't that right, brother?
You saved me?
Well, I had had to do something.
Thank you.
We're lucky.
Those bees almost killed us all.
Those bees saved our lives.
Ah, really?
Because it felt
like an elephant stampede.
We're alive, aren't we?
The elephants would have fought with us.
We're lions, nobody
will fight with us, not out here.
(speaking foreign language)
Where's it going?
Beyond the horizon itself.
(speaking foreign language)
Mufasa, thank you.
(thunder rumbling)
Rafiki, who, who are the outsiders?
Well, the
outsiders come from many prides,
but when they are born, they are hated
because they are
different from their tribe.
Like you mean your tribe?
Yes, just like me.
But Rafiki?
Yes.
Why do they want to hurt everybody?
Sometimes when the
people most like you don't love you,
it is a hurt that
can cause the greatest pain.
And this pain can
lead you to hate everything.
I'm glad that
didn't happen to you, Rafiki.
Yes, my child, I'm glad too.
Um, hi, we're here too.
Yeah, why are you
leaving us outside this story?
Well, I'm pretty sure
we are the ultimate outtiles.
Come on.
Yeah, we've always been misunderstood.
I contain both of you.
(dramatic music)
There are many ways to be there,
but this, for us.
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music) Go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hey, Rafiki?
What are you doing?
I am confirming my vision, Fasa.
Can I ask you something, Rafiki?
Hmm?
How many of your visions have come true?
So far, none.
None?
But it's not what I see.
It's what I feel.
But how do you know
when you should follow a feeling?
Millele exists.
I feel it in here.
The question is,
what do you feel, Mufasa?
In they.
(dramatic music)
Weather is shifting.
There's not enough fresh snow.
Hey, if the outsiders find our tracks,
they'll follow them to Millele.
Zazu, only you can help us.
Are you quite sure about that?
Now, I was actually
thinking that Rafiki looks
all pretty handy and with the stick--
Zazu, you can use
your wings to cover our tracks
as we head up the
mountain without leaving a trace.
Hey, you can do this.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, sir, you're right.
I've got this.
(dramatic music)
Okay, this is me.
Getting to the frozen mountain.
And the one horned
field charge with saving future.
Oh, mummy!
Oh, oh, my life, that's cold.
(dramatic music) (thunder rumbling)
(thunder rumbling)
What's happening?
We can't keep stopping.
Somehow, they have
covered their tracks in the snow.
It's not possible.
Majesty, they could
be anywhere on this mountain.
Then find them now.
Zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu.
(dramatic music)
I have a report.
The outsiders are completely lost.
Well played, Mufasa.
Great job, Zazu.
And as per usual.
I knew you could do it.
We did it.
No, you did it.
Great thinking, Mufasa.
Now, we're all rubbing off on each other.
Partly normal thing to do.
Who wants to rub against us?
No one.
I'm leaving now.
Scout ahead.
(dramatic music)
(thunder rumbling)
(grunting)
(laughing)
I got you, Rufasa.
Hey.
I got you.
Do not do that.
Yeah, I got you.
(dramatic music)
Mufasa.
I got you.
(dramatic music)
I'm sorry.
Heading in the
shadows, downwind, right afoot.
Interesting hunting style, Mufasa.
We have to eat something
before we take on that descent.
Unfortunately,
there's nothing to hunt up here.
See under that rock?
There's a sieve about to leave his den.
Of course you can
smell a sieve hidden in the snow.
You, the lion who can do anything.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I see you, Mufasa.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Now that part I
believe, because smart as you are,
you have a way of
seeing everything but yourself.
What is this?
What is this, Sarabi?
There is a sievet in the
snow right where you said it would be,
and you smelled
the outsiders in the wind,
which means you're the one
who smelled the flowers on my fur.
It was a lucky guess.
You can smell the
exact flower from my valley.
No, that's not possible.
You saved me.
Held me, covered me
in a stamp, he comforted me.
No, it was talking.
I got you.
I got you, Sarabi.
I'm here to protect him.
That was you?
I was lost in the water and he found me.
My brother saved her.
I sensed it from the beginning.
His blood is the blood of the king.
Mufasa.
That is his destiny.
No, his destiny was to save you.
Okay.
Now tell me it's you.
Ever since you appeared,
I've been running
through something deep inside,
and it's worse than I feared.
Cause I look in
your eyes and I can't hide
I push you away
Don't push me away
But the feelings
come back just twice as strong
I don't know what to say
I know just what to say
But I know that I'm right where I belong
Way you know just where to be
I don't know
Move the way you see
You see me
The way you feel when you're near
Beside me, don't hide me in court
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
What do I say, where do I go
How do I know you feel the same
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
Quiet and low, letting it go
Letting you know it's in me
Every year that I roll
I remind myself not to overstay
Every time I find home
Something happens to take that home away
Don't you see what I've seen
I see you
As you meet with the
strength that shines right through
Move like a queen, true queen
Don't let anything take me away from you
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
Say it again, say it again
Tell me I'll always be with you
Tell me it's you, I know it's you
Say it again, say it again
Tell me you're always with me
You know just where to be
Now I know
Move the way you see
I see you
As you feel like you and you and me
Beside me, beside me
Say it again, say it again, say it again
Tell me the world won't end again
Say it again, say it again
Tell me the words I wanna hear
Open your eyes and here we come
I know it's you
You know I love her, my brother
There's nothing we keep from each other
Save your life, this is how you behave
What do I do, what does it mean
How do I ever wanna see what I see
He was my kin, she was my queen
Now it's broken
forever and now it's broken forever
And the caller is you, she knows it's you
What did you say to her, what did you do
I'm next in line, now she should be mine
Ha, are the answers
laughing? I believe them
What would they say, father is gone
Not before giving me strength, Lord
He never trusted you, didn't know
You've been training me sir
For when you were drowning I could die
I can do life with you lived in my day
Behind you and round me, tumbling down
Trying to escape what I cannot forget
I am a brother no
longer, it's over in time
Now all I have is
shame and it's way that I can't
Out
This is a tool of a grateful king.
There wasn't much
to eat on this mountain.
Until now.
Tell me, how did
you cut me attractions, no?
A bird helped us.
Life is getting help from me, bitch.
Just as I will help you.
You will help us.
You think we need
help from a wounded coward.
I may hold the blood of a king.
But it was Mufasa who killed your son.
It was Mufasa who trapped you up here.
Outspotted you at every turn.
Now I will lead you to him and to Malele.
Malele.
Malele is nothing but a dream.
A vision, souls of cops.
Ah, well, tell that to the monkey.
He leads them to it.
Look at you.
A rock of starving wolves
clinging to the side of a mountain.
No tracks to follow.
Only one chance at revenge.
Lead.
Revenge.
What about your father?
Because of Mufasa, I have no father.
He did this.
Yes. You lost a father.
And I, a son.
Daga, will you join us?
Together we can both have our revenge.
It will be my pleasure.
King.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Taco.
Taco, where have you been?
Hunting.
I couldn't find anything,
but I was never as good as you.
All my mother.
There's something I need to tell you.
No.
I need to thank you.
You kept your word to Ece and Hobasi.
Taco, you saved me, Mufasa.
And I will never forget what you've done.
My brother.
Oh, guys, I have found a way
down just beyond those near peaks.
Is it something I said?
Hey, Rafiki.
Yes.
We are nearing destiny, Mufasa.
And so the earth must shake.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OK, now I am 100
million percent sure who Taco is.
Just be honest, is it me?
In case you missed it,
we're not featured in this.
I think the sit-it has more screen time.
Hey, maybe they'll put us in the play?
No, no, please
don't mention the play again.
I went to see it on
nothing but a giant sock puppet.
You went to see it? You didn't bring me?
Rafiki, Mufasa and Sarabia are in love?
Ew, love.
That sounds gross and not something
like I constantly think about and really want.
What is Taco going to do to them?
Little one.
Taco's heart was
broken, and now his trap was set.
[THUNDER]
Mufasa, do you see?
I don't believe it.
The other side of the line.
Oh, fuck.
You need a day, me.
[LAUGHING]
The dog.
I can't believe it.
We found it.
We found Malayla.
Yes.
You found it, brother.
You always do.
[SCREAMING]
Rafiki.
This is the train.
From your visions.
I have seen this
train many times, and in each
vision there was always
a brother standing right here.
But there's no one here,
Rafiki, and you came here to find your twin.
He was taken from me long ago.
What I saw in my dreams
was a brother standing right here.
A friend.
Family.
What I saw was you.
The unseeable.
I saw Mufasa.
Me?
This? You?
My brother?
Mufasa.
How do you know who I am?
We know the outsiders are
hunting you, and we fear you'll bring danger.
No, no, no. We covered our tracks.
I promise you,
Malayla is a safe place, and
I would never do
anything to jeopardize them.
Do not run!
You have nothing to fear.
We are not here to move.
We have come from Mufasa.
How did they get here?
Do not let him divide us!
Esmere, you lose, Mufasa.
The Circle...
The Circle is broken.
No!
Mufasa, what are you doing?
I'm going to fight, and I'm
going to show them that they can fight too.
Rafiki, when you hear my
signal, help me call them together.
Yes, my brother.
There are other lines here.
Find them.
With pleasure, your majesty.
Mufasa, you're not alone.
It's my turn to go ask questions first.
This is where the hunt ends, Mufasa.
Thanks to your brother.
He left a trail of
scars for us to follow.
He made a deal to save himself.
He gave us this kingdom.
Tell me he's lying.
Ask us to kill the stray.
Faka, please!
I, the son of a king, a Seravi chose you.
Just like mother,
just like my own father.
I saved him, and you betrayed me.
What have you done?
And your brother fight with me?
You stole my destiny.
Now this is yours.
He's one or less now.
My son's name.
Saku.
All of this should have been
his, and now I will rule it without mercy.
This one is mine.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
Please, we can't
wait for this battle alone.
There's nothing we can do.
They chased us
from our pride lands before.
They're too strong.
Fight with us.
Fight for your young, for your future.
What future?
They've taken all we have,
and they will always take more.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I am the possum, a stray with no
pride, and yet I stand before you, head unbound.
I know you're afraid, but trust me,
nothing will change if we remain isolated to
our own tribes without
concern for the fate of others.
But why should we stand with you?
This is your fight.
Today they are here for us lions, but
I assure you, as you let them walk among you
in search of us now, they are
plotting to come for you tomorrow.
One lion's hope cannot
change the fate of Malayle.
There is no lion as large as an
elephant, as strong as an oxen, fast as a cheetah,
or tall as a
giraffe, who can soar and scout as
wide and far as the
cranes and hawks in the sky.
So can't you see?
Every being is a
place in the circle of life.
My breath is your breath.
Your fight is my fight.
I will not bend to
evil, and neither should you.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Rufasa is right.
Malayle is home.
We must stand with Rufasa!
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Together we shall stand strong.
Come, Malayle!
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Together is the lion!
From this moment on,
everything the light touches belongs to me.
You have to take it.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Bye-bye.
Oh!
You messed with the wrong on-bill.
[LAUGHTER]
The launch is set.
Stand down.
I am highly trained
and occasionally effective.
This is so embarrassing.
I do have weight, you know.
[THUNDER]
Taka.
Taka, please.
Please!
This was her.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
[THUNDER]
You did challenge me.
You took my son, my future.
Taka, Taka, your
moment of courage will come.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
Please, don't kill him.
I didn't kill him.
You did.
[THUNDER]
They're coming!
The last lion.
Time for their extinction
and we'll start with the youngest.
The earth will shake.
Taka!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Orasa.
Close your eyes
and tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Kupata.
No, no, I'm not.
King, raise your heads.
I'm just-- no, no, no more kings.
We are all one.
Please, please, raise your heads.
But Mufasa, you
have brought them together.
You held them seeing
themselves, what they considered unseeable.
Nothing is more kingly.
No, Rafiqihi.
I'm not king, not royal blood.
Don't you see, my
brother, it is not what you were.
It is what you have become.
The king of Milene.
My brother,
something beautiful awaits you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this real?
But it can't be.
It can't be.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Mufasa.
But how can it be?
I had a son named Mufasa
taken from me by a great flood.
Mother?
I never stopped hoping, believing my son.
I dreamt of this moment.
And now it's come true.
Oh, Mufasa.
But father?
Where's father?
He lives in you now.
He lives in you.
I always dreamed we'd be together again.
And I knew it would be in Milele.
My son.
Mufasa.
Mufasa, please forgive me.
You must banish him, Saya.
As long as I'm king, my
brother will have a place here.
Oh, brother, I'm so sorry.
But Saya won't ever say your name again.
I can't. I won't.
Then call me Scar, so I
will never forget what I have done.
Scar.
Your Majesty.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Welcome home.
[MUSIC PLAYING] [MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING] [MUSIC PLAYING] Welcome home.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Your Majesty.
So, Mufasa, I see your family has
been awaiting you in Milele after all.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Mufike.
Yes, they were.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It is your time, Mufasa.
Mufike, I wish I could see him.
I wish I could meet my grandfather.
As Mufasa once told your
father, look into the heavens, Kiara.
The great gains of
the past will always be there.
Waiting for you.
[MUSIC PLAYING] [MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't want him to go, Prithi.
I don't want it to end.
Don't you see, Kiara?
Mufasa lives in you.
He lives in you.
Whoever, whoever, I will guide you.
Dad!
Rupiki, it was unbelievable.
It was perfect.
You could not improve on it.
That said, I do have no suggestions.
Take him or leave him, but take him.
Dad!
Kiara!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Kiara.
Dad, where's Mom?
Well, love, there's
something you need to know.
What?
Does something happen to Mom?
Baby, I'm right here, and I'm fine.
Where were you?
Kiara, this is your new brother.
Brother?
I have a brother?
Hi there.
Kiara.
I will take care of you forever.
But a what?
Let me tell you a story.
A story of a great king.
[MUSIC PLAYING]