Look at the stars.
Whenever you feel alone,
the great kings of the past
will always be up there
to guide you.
And so will I.
My friends, the time of
my family's growth is upon us.
This home we share
is the fulfillment
of my father's vision.
How wonderful is it
that Nala and I
get to continue his dream
and make even greater
the Circle of Life?
Nala, my love, I'm on my way.
Simba...
I'm here.
Security detail
has arrived!
One gentle reminder:
we are not food.
No, no, no, no, no.
We are just two guys
walking to work through
a pride of hungry lions.
Which is perfectly
normal. I'm not terrified.
Security detail
reporting for duty,
Your Grace, Your Highness...
Ruler of all
four-legged creatures.
And that one
three-legged zebra.
Oh, right, Ron.
That was tragic.
-It was an eat-and-Ron.
-Yeah.
Ron has three legs.
That's still one more than me.
-Well, are those arms or legs?
-Guys.
I don't know.
I think they're paws.
Guys.
-I consider all those legs.
-Guys! This is serious.
I need you to stay with Kiara
until I get back.
Are you saying
that your security detail
has been called on
to do babysitting?
Pumbaa, we should
really discuss this
because I don't really love...
Guys, I promised her
everything would be okay.
Well, that's one way
to parent.
She's gonna
have to grow up sometime.
What else did you tell her,
that she could be
whatever she wants to be?
That life is fair?
I need you two to try
and act like adults, okay?
Don't scare Kiara.
And most of all, no stories.
-No stories?
-Wait a second.
I know where your head goes.
I grew up with you two.
Promise me.
Okay. You know what,
you know what, you know what?
Fine. No stories.
Speak for yourself, Pumbaa.
No. Pssh.
We'll tell a story anyway.
Okay, we'll tell
him that we're not gonna
tell a story and then
we're gonna tell a story.
-He can't stop us.
-Are you guys serious?
I'm clearly within earshot.
Dad.
Hey, little one.
Dad, the storm's coming,
and I'm scared.
I wanna go with you and Mom.
-Don't be scared, my love.
-Mmm.
Timon and Pumbaa
will watch you while I'm gone.
Be brave now, Kiara.
Be brave.
Okay!
We've prepared a story.
Scar looked at us.
He knew it was
the end of the line.
I could smell the fear.
That was actually me,
but yes.
So you two
defeated Scar?
And then you ate him?
Honestly, one of the best
meals I ever had.
My dad told me
he defeated Scar.
Well, okay. But your dad,
as we all know,
is a pathological liar.
He's always lyin'. Get it?
I'm scared.
I want Mom and Dad.
Look, look, look
look, look.
Don't be scared, Kiara.
How about we sing you a song?
And, a-one...
Pumbaa, no, it is
way too early for the song.
It worked on Simba.
He thought he had
murdered his own father.
He was singin' and dancin'
around in seconds.
I can't just
turn it on like that.
I have to be in the moment.
He sang that song
for six years straight.
Well, who didn't?
Look!
-No!
-It's Ron,
the three-legged zebra.
Run for your lives!
He heard what we've been
sayin' about him.
We're sorry, Ron. They were
jokes. They were just jokes!
It's Rafiki.
Rafiki! Rafiki!
Little one,
there's no reason to cry.
My parents...
they're gone.
Hey. Look out there, mdogo.
You see those baobab trees
blowing in the wind?
The roots of those trees are
very strong, like your family.
And, just as they did for you,
your parents have gone to the
ceremonial birthing grounds.
And when they return,
the Circle of Life
will bring a blessing
to you, Kiara,
that you will never forget.
Man, he's good.
He's such
a visual storyteller.
Yet it makes sense
that he lives alone.
I just want the storm to pass,
and then I promise
to be brave.
I'll tell you a secret.
When your father Simba
was your age,
he was afraid of the thunder
and would hide
behind the king.
When did he stop hiding?
One day, during a big storm,
your grandfather Mufasa
took your father
to the very top of Pride Rock,
told him to stand with him
and howl into the wind.
And Simba slowly stepped out
with the king.
And together,
they roared into the night.
But I'm not brave like my dad.
And I could never be
like Mufasa.
Is that so?
Then maybe it's time
I tell you a story.
A story of a cub,
not much bigger than you.
A lion born without a drop
of nobility in his blood.
A lion who would change
our lives forever.
A story! So glad
I brought some crickets.
But go easy. We're in a cave.
This story
begins far beyond
the mountains and the shadows.
On the other side
of the light.
In this place, everything
was dying of thirst
as 20 full moons
had passed without
a single drop of water.
But when the skies
finally opened,
destiny would reign.
Mufasa.
Mufasa! Come see.
Mom, what is that light
way out there?
Oh, that's very special.
Beyond the horizon,
beyond the last cloud
in the sky,
that's a place we call Milele.
Milele?
Hmm. It means, "forever."
Imagine
a kingdom full of life,
water and food,
grass and sky
as far as the eye can see.
Will we ever go there?
Oh, yes, Mufasa.
That's exactly
where we're headed.
But we can also
be there right now.
We can close our eyes.
Let our dreams take us.
♪ Sekuseduzani ♪
♪ Empumalanga ♪
♪ Entshonalanga
Sala ngoxolo ♪
♪ Beyond
the horizon ♪
♪ Beyond the last cloud
in the sky♪
♪ There's a place I know♪
♪ Siqhubek'ekhaya
s'ofika ♪
-♪ Ngothando ♪
-♪ Imagine ♪
-♪ A kingdom ♪
- ♪ Ngothando ♪
♪ The water flows ♪
-♪ The grass is high ♪
-♪ S'ofika ♪
-♪ It's not a dream♪
- ♪ Ngothando! ♪
♪ Someday we'll go♪
-♪ We call it ♪
- ♪ Tunaita ♪
-♪ Milele ♪
-♪ Sivulele indlela ♪
♪ S'yacela Milele ♪
-♪ It's always there ♪
-♪ Sivulele indlela ♪
♪ Somandla!
Daimaiko ♪
-♪ Milele ♪
-♪ Sivulele indlela ♪
-♪ S'yacela Milele ♪
-♪ It lives in you ♪
-♪ It lives in me ♪
-♪ Siqonde Phambile ♪
-♪ You'll see ♪
-♪ Milele! ♪
♪ Life, great and small ♪
♪ The Circle of Life
is not small ♪
♪ We know that
there's enough for all ♪
♪ There's enough
for all ♪
♪ There
is always more♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
-♪ We're on your side ♪
-♪ We'll wander no longer ♪
♪ We carry ancestors inside ♪
-♪ Like a constant tide ♪
- ♪ S'ofika ♪
♪ It's not a dream,
can you see it? ♪
-♪ On an endless shore ♪
-♪ Ngothando! ♪
-♪ And as you grow ♪
-♪ Iyhooo! ♪
-♪ Can you find your way? ♪
-♪ Can you see it? ♪
-♪ We call it ♪
-♪ Sekuseduzani ♪
♪ Tunaita ♪
-♪ Milele♪
-♪ Sekuseduzani ♪
♪ Milele! ♪
-♪ It's always there ♪
-♪ Sekuseduzani daimaiko ♪
-♪ Milele ♪
-♪ Empumalanga entshonalanga ♪
♪ Sala ngoxolo
Milele! ♪
-♪ We call it ♪
-♪ Sekuseduzani tunaita ♪
-♪ Empumalanga entshonalanga ♪
-♪ Milele ♪
♪ Sala ngoxolo
Milele! ♪
-♪ It's always there♪
-♪ Sekuseduzani daimaiko ♪
-♪ Milele ♪
-♪ Milele! ♪
♪ Empumalanga entshonalanga
Sala ngoxolo ♪
-♪ Milele! ♪
-♪ It lives in you ♪
-♪ It lives in me ♪
-♪ Sala ngoxolo ♪
-♪ We're free ♪
-♪ Ngoxolo ♪
-♪ Milele♪
-♪ Milele! ♪
Wow.
What is this?
Rain. Rain!
Oh, finally we have rain!
Dad, race you to the light!
You're too fast.
I've never beaten you.
Nobody has ever beaten you.
I know!
Mufasa!
Fastest cub in the world.
Thank you.
Mufasa...
that's enough.
Mufasa, come back now.
Mufasa, stay there!
I'm coming, son.
-Father!
-Mufasa!
Mufasa?
I'll catch you on the turn.
Find my voice.
Find my voice!
Mom!
Mufasa, the cliff is too high,
but you can cross at the dam.
Come on, Mufasa,
you can do this.
Find your mother's voice.
Listen
to your father, Mufasa!
Listen to us!
Afia, he's there.
-Mom!
-He's there!
-Mother!
-Mufasa!
Find your footing
one step at a time.
-I can't.
-You can do this.
I'm right here.
Mufasa!
Mom?
Dad?
Can you hear me?
Is anyone out there?
Mom?
Please.
I'm scared.
The floodwaters
joined a distant river,
carried Mufasa far
from his mother and father.
Beyond all that he knew.
Hello.
I'm Taka, son of Obasi.
What's your name?
Mufasa.
I'm not allowed
to talk to Outsiders,
but I have a secret...
...and I really
want to tell you.
-What's the secret?
-I'll get in trouble.
Please, just tell me.
Uh... I don't know.
Just tell me!
Okay.
You're about to be eaten.
I hate secrets!
-Swim!
-But I can't!
-You have to swim.
-I don't know how!
All right. Chin up, then walk
underwater really fast.
I can't!
Come on, Mufasa. Faster!
Help me, Taka! Help me!
I told you to wait for me.
It's not my fault, Mum.
I came down for a drink
and saw him floating by.
I'd like you to meet Mufasa.
You're lucky
those crocs were young
and afraid to fight. Let's go!
We can't just leave him here.
Rules are rules, Taka.
Obasi will never accept
a stray.
I'm not a stray.
I'm just... lost.
See?
He's just lost.
There was a...
a flood.
My parents,
they tried to save me.
Do you know which way is home?
Home?
To be lost
is to learn the way.
Call me Eshe.
I'm tired, Eshe.
Come on, it's this way.
Come on, Mufasa.
Is this Milele?
No, my love.
I was trying to nap, Eshe.
The all-important nap
of kings,
only to be awoken
by the disgusting,
hideous, revolting stench
of a stray.
When we come upon an Outsider,
tell me, what do we do?
Obasi, I know.
Eat it.
But I found him, Dad.
I saved his life.
Taka, we do not associate
with Outsiders.
The only true bond is blood.
I've heard stories of lions
twice our size.
These Outsiders
will devour everything
in their path.
Does he look like he's going
to devour you?
Whoa, that smell
is disgusting.
I'm not even sure I could eat
this kibeti!
I'm not a kibeti.
I'm a Mufasa.
Do you even know
what "Mufasa" means?
-No.
-It means, "king."
And that's me.
You better start running,
little Mufasa,
for your life.
If I run,
you'll never catch me.
I'm the fastest cub
that ever lived.
My father told me so.
Ooh, Taka,
you have a challenge.
They will race
to the dead tree and back.
And when the prince
defeats him,
I will finish him in one bite.
What if Mufasa wins?
If he wins, he lives, Obasi.
He stays with me.
You have my word.
Let the race begin!
Ooh, clumsy little stray.
Run, Mufasa!
You did not have to do that.
Taka
is the future king.
He has to win
his first challenge.
No, Obasi. To be a true king,
he must earn it.
Don't take that away from him.
Better hurry.
I have one more secret,
Mufasa.
I always wanted a brother.
-Cheater!
-Obasi!
You will keep him
with the females.
Taka, how could you lose
to a stray?
Well done, Taka.
Well done.
I thought you said
you were fast.
I had to let you win.
Well, I did just go days
with no sleep
while riding the waves of...
Anyway, come on, Mufasa.
Let's get in some trouble.
♪ When I am king♪
♪ No other animal will break
my stride♪
♪ Break my stride♪
-♪ And my brother ♪
-♪ My brother ♪
♪ When I'm king,
you'll always take my side ♪
-♪ Ha! Yeah, right ♪
-♪ That's right ♪
-♪ When I am king ♪
-♪ When you are king ♪
♪ No other animal will break
our pride♪
♪ Break our pride♪
-♪ And my brother ♪
-♪ My brother ♪
♪ Our prey may run away,
but they can't hide♪
♪ Watch your hide♪
♪ Let's go, let's go♪
♪ Let's go♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say
you could be up this late? ♪
♪ Okay, she didn't say
either way ♪
♪ Hide away, let's go♪
♪ Hey, did your father say
you could be out this far?♪
♪ Okay, we're on our way♪
♪ On our way, run away
Let's go♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say
you could be up this late?♪
♪ Ha ha,
you're very sharp♪
♪ Yes, you are,
yes, you are, let's go♪
♪ Hey, did your father say
you could be out this far?♪
♪ Make a wish
on the brightest star ♪
♪ And I say ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother
I always wanted a brother♪
just like you♪
♪ And I always wanted
a brother ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother♪
♪ I always wanted a brother
just like you♪
♪ You see
that tree?♪
♪ Those birds are watching
the world unfold♪
♪ The world unfold♪
-♪ Oh, brother ♪
-♪ My brother ♪
♪ When I'm king,
they will do as they're told ♪
♪ You may look down on them♪
-♪ But they are free ♪
-♪ You can't catch me ♪
♪ And where they go
cannot be controlled♪
♪ No one looks down on me♪
♪ They look down on us,
brother♪
♪ Some things you chase
but you cannot hold♪
♪ Okay, it's getting old,
let's go ♪
♪ Let's go♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say ♪
♪ That you could
learn this way?♪
♪ I've got to find a way,
find our prey♪
-♪ Fine, I'll wait ♪
-♪ Let's go ♪
-♪ Hey♪
- ♪ I heard his father say♪
♪ He doesn't want this stray♪
♪ I dare you to say
that again to my face ♪
♪ What did you say
'bout my brother? ♪
♪ That's not a stray,
that's my brother ♪
♪ You stay away from my
brother 'cause I say so ♪
♪ If you put your paws
on my brother ♪
♪ You'll meet the jaws
of his brother ♪
♪ Those are the laws
for my brother ♪
♪ Where'd he go?♪
♪ I always wanted a brother♪
♪ I still remember my mother♪
♪ One season after another♪
♪ One season
after another♪
♪ One season after another♪
♪ Everyone sing
for my brother ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
-♪ I'd do anything ♪
-♪ For my brother ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
♪ Soon I'll be king
with my brother ♪
♪ Hey ♪
-♪ By my side ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
-♪ I always wanted a brother ♪
-♪ Now we rely on each other ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
-♪ One season after another ♪
-♪ Hey, Mufasa ♪
-♪ Yes, Taka? ♪
♪ I'll race you
to the other side ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
-♪ Race you ♪
-♪ To the other side ♪
-♪ Hey ♪
♪ Race you to the other side
Ha!♪
Elephant stampede!
Run for your lives!
Chigaru jumped,
like, 20 feet.
Oh, that's a new record.
Obasi,
they did it again.
Your sons are nothing
but trouble.
That one is not my son.
They're heathens,
the both of them.
This stray is forbidden
to be near the Shade Tree.
Mufasa and I were
just playing.
You two will
never be brothers.
Now go back to the females
and stay away from my son.
Oh, your mother,
she adopts every lizard,
speaks to passing
grasshoppers.
I want to go with him.
You want to be
with the females?
You belong with the males.
He gets to hunt with Mother.
One day, he will betray you.
That is what strays do.
Mufasa would never betray me.
Hey, hey.
This will all be yours,
my son.
You will be king.
So pay attention.
Study every move I make.
Sleeping again.
That is what males do.
We protect the pride
as we nap.
That's...
Well, that's power.
Power?
Why are we stopping?
Close your eyes.
And tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
There's
a herd of antelope
heading across
the dry lakebed.
About half a day from here?
And how do you know
they're not gazelles?
Their steps
are too heavy.
-Moving way too slow.
-What else?
Come on. You can do it.
When the wind
hits their horns, it moves up
instead of across.
So, definitely antelope horns.
Very good.
What is it, Mufasa?
What's wrong?
Sometimes I get a scent.
It's barely a trace
on the wind.
And it smells like home.
Then it's gone.
Mufasa, your parents
are still out there.
We can keep looking.
I lost them, Eshe.
You're wasting your time
training me like this.
But these skills you have,
no other male has them.
Obasi will never accept me.
I'll never be his blood.
His family.
But you are my family.
And if Obasi could see
how gifted you are...
Well, maybe I like being
a stray, you know.
No rules, no responsibility.
I'm the lucky one,
Eshe.
What do you mean, Mufasa?
I never have to be like Taka.
I never have to be king.
Did he say, "no rules
and no responsibility"?
An outcast, afraid of water,
never takes a bath.
Which means he smells like me.
Which is not good.
Well, either way, I think that
means that he's one of us.
-This is it.
-It's our time!
This is our moment.
And a-one,
and a-two and a-one, two...
♪ Hakuna Mufasa♪
♪ What a wonderful name♪
♪ He ain't no passin' craze♪
♪ It means no...♪
-Stop!
-What?
Don't go there.
All right, all right,
Rafiki's right.
We'll get letters from legal.
Those vultures will take
everything we have.
Which, technically,
is nothing.
Look at us.
We're naked animals.
No wonder I'm always freezing.
They want this!
Come on, Pumbaa.
Let's bring it home.
♪ Hakuna Mufasa♪
Quiet!
Kiara's a music snob.
Rafiki, keep going.
Later that day,
Eshe was teaching Mufasa
how to hunt in pairs.
But, as Taka was
secretly watching,
something terrible
was hunting them.
Mufasa, run!
Eshe!
Mother.
Mother!
Eshe!
Keep moving, Mufasa.
They go for the neck!
It's okay, Mufasa.
It's okay.
That was very brave of you,
Mufasa.
Thank you.
Eshe...
What has happened?
Are you hurt?
They were huge.
White as ghosts.
Like nothing I've seen before.
Oh, Obasi.
Had Mufasa
not been there, I...
Taka.
I owe you
a great debt, Mufasa.
We need to prepare.
They're downwind
less than a day away.
No.
You couldn't possibly
know this.
Send a scout and you'll see...
they'll be coming for us.
Chigaru.
Father, please,
let me explain.
No. Not now.
Taka, come.
Where is my son?
There was a young lion,
Majesty.
He fought Shaju.
And yet you came back.
You survived.
I was badly hurt. I promise,
Majesty. This is the truth.
-The truth?
-Yes, the truth.
The truth is standing
behind you.
-There were others, Majesty.
-No, no, no.
But only one left blood
on his mane.
Which means
he left Shaju to die.
Saved himself.
This young lion,
was he their king?
His blood is common. Ordinary.
Answer me!
Was he their king?
No, Kiros,
you are the only king.
An ordinary lion?
And you left my son to die?
I was injured.
There was no choice.
Please, Majesty,
you have to believe me.
There's no reason to fear me.
I would never harm
one of my own.
Thank you, Majesty.
I'll leave that pleasure
to them.
Majesty! No. Kiros!
Kiros!
No one
can ever know you ran.
That you ran from your mother.
It never happened, Taka.
Do you understand?
But I didn't know. I was
just... I was just scared.
It doesn't matter.
We must protect the bloodline.
Protect it with a lie?
Father, that's deceitful.
Deceit is a tool
of a great king.
Taka...
it's what kings must do.
But I'm not a king.
I'm just your son.
Obasi!
Chigaru.
Chigaru, I'm here.
What did you see?
They're coming
this way, Obasi.
Two lions
for every one of ours.
Each one bigger than the next,
but none as mighty as Kiros,
their terrifying king.
Outsiders.
The stories were all true.
I must protect
the bloodline, Eshe.
The future of this pride.
Taka, you are that future.
Future? Dad, what do you mean?
I'm sending you away.
Far from here.
You will leave
and start a new life,
a new beginning.
I need you to go with him,
Mufasa,
to pledge your loyalty.
They'll arrive
with the sunrise.
Where will we go, Eshe?
Without you, I have no home.
Mufasa, you and Taka together.
That...
-That is home.
-Eshe...
Mufasa, look out there.
Beyond the light...
You know what I see?
I see the place your mother
told you about,
a place beyond
the river's end.
Across the deepest canyon
on the other side
of the mountains,
a place beyond
the horizon itself.
A pride land so green,
so perfect
that to see it is to see
Milele.
Yes. Forever.
My parents spoke
of Milel often.
My mother told me
it was where we were going.
And don't you see, Mufasa?
You must keep going.
You must continue your journey
toward the light.
Please, Eshe.
I can't lose you.
You have my love
always, Mufasa.
But your family is still out
there, waiting for you.
I can feel their presence.
And I know you can, too.
Go.
Go, Mufasa.
Find your way home.
Mother, please forgive me.
I beg you.
There's no need, my love.
Taka, your moment of courage
will come.
Now both of you go.
Go and find your place
in the Circle of Life.
They left their family
never to see them again?
This story is killing me.
It's toying with my emotions.
And here
is the worst part.
-What's that?
-I'm out of crickets.
Oh, maybe that's for the best.
I need a bathroom break
before the second act.
Everyone wait for me.
I am back.
Pumbaa, did you wash
your hooves?
Mm-hmm.
-Pumbaa?
-I did. I did.
-I'm just gonna walk
-on them again right after.
-Pumbaa?
Rafiki,
did the Outsiders come?
Yes.
And as the hunters led Kiros
into the Valley of Kings,
Obasi and Eshe
stood their ground.
Which one of you is king?
You have no reason
to challenge me.
Does this look
like a challenge, King?
There are rules among lions.
Not anymore.
While you ruled this pride,
I've built my army.
Yours is the last pride
in the Valley of Kings,
which means
everything the light touches
belongs to me.
There will be one ruler.
One Lion King.
♪ You say you're the king ♪
♪ But you lie around
in the shade♪
♪ Out of shape, unafraid♪
♪ The moon cuts a path
through the sky♪
♪ By night or by day♪
♪ It doesn't obey♪
♪ And neither do I♪
♪ You took my son♪
♪ I hope you can run♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to be
the last thing you see♪
♪ Before you go bye-bye♪
♪ There you go, bye-bye♪
♪ Climb every tree
Cross land and sea♪
♪ I'll make you go bye-bye♪
♪ Everything
in my clutches, ha! ♪
♪ Bye-bye♪
♪ Everything
the light touches♪
♪ The Circle of Life
is a lie♪
♪ A pretty way to say♪
♪ There are predators
and prey♪
♪ That circle of vultures
up high ♪
♪ They keep stealing glances♪
♪ They don't like
your chances♪
♪ And neither do I♪
♪ I run my pride♪
♪ You run and hide♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to be
the last thing you see♪
♪ Before you go bye-bye♪
♪ There you go, bye-bye♪
♪ Climb every tree
Cross land and sea♪
♪ Until you go bye-bye♪
♪ Will you go bye-bye?♪
♪ Bye-bye,
for vengeance is mine ♪
♪ If I'm the last of my line♪
♪ I must be strong♪
♪ Gotta go bye-bye♪
♪ I'll make you go bye-bye♪
♪ Bye-bye♪
We have to move.
They'll be tracking us.
-Taka!
-What if you're wrong?
What if they're okay?
They live in you now.
Follow me, brother.
We have to move...
together.
Run, Mufasa.
Run!
Hunters.
-What's the plan?
-Uh...
Run! Very fast!
This way!
Back to the trees.
We're trapped.
We have to swim.
No, we have to fight.
If we fight, we die.
But if we swim, we drown.
Okay, I didn't
want to do this,
-but I command you to swim!
-You what?
You pledged your loyalty.
I command you to swim.
Taka, this is not the time
for jokes.
Which one of you
killed my son?
I did.
This lion with me is nothing
but a stray. Let him go.
Kiros, the other is no stray.
He holds the blood
of the pride.
The last blood
of the king? Hmm.
Blood for blood.
They're coming!
What do we do?
We find the advantage?
What advantage?
We're on a rock
in the middle of the water!
Taka, this is it.
We go for the king.
Mufasa, I'm ready.
Just one last thing.
-What?
-Chin up!
Taka!
This was a bad idea.
Mufasa!
-Mufasa...
-Yeah!
-We're alive.
-Ah!
I did it. I saved us.
You were saying?
Okay. Okay.
No... No more water.
Tell me you can track them
down river.
We can track them anywhere.
They can run,
but they can't hide.
So just to be clear,
we're not in this story?
It feels a little bit like
Kiros is stealing
my thunder here.
Yeah. You know,
I don't feel seen.
No. There's a lotta stories
with all of us.
Tell one of those!
Can I make
one small suggestion?
Less childhood trauma,
more meerkat.
Rafiki, I know
who Taka's gonna be.
Oh. Me too. It's so obvious.
But maybe, just so we're on
the same page, tell me?
-Is it Simba? Is it me?
-Pumbaa.
Oh, wait. Am I Obasi?
That makes no sense.
But seriously,
I have one question.
Am I Taka?
♪ I did
it again, I did it again ♪
Not that I'm counting,
but I saved your hide. Again!
As much as
it kills you to say it,
let's hear a little,
"Thank you, Taka."
You want me
to thank you
for pushing me
off a waterfall?
Yes, and you're welcome.
Look, it's not my fault
crocodiles are simply
attracted to you.
Don't...
Don't say that.
♪ I did
it again, I did it...
Mufasa.
Is it them?
Is it the Outsiders?
No.
She's right there.
"She"?
There's no place to run.
We have your scent.
My scent?
I've been stalking
you two all night.
That's not possible.
Then
why did I circle you
three times in this wood
while you two were
chasing each other's tails?
Uh... That's embarrassing.
Yeah, well, I, uh,
meant to do that, so...
Still think I'm afraid?
Why are you
following us?
I was hoping to find my pride.
What happened to them?
The Outsiders
happened.
A few of us got away,
but you're the only
other lions I've seen.
You two better keep moving.
Wait! Please.
Um... My name is Taka.
Son of Obasi.
I know what it's like
to lose everything.
Come with us. We can help you.
I don't need any help.
But you don't have anyone.
She does indeed have someone.
Thank you very much.
That's Zazu. Don't eat him.
You heard her. Do not eat me.
As a recent addition
to the King's Royal Guard,
I must kindly ask you both
to move on.
Thank you for stopping by.
Your king hired a bird
to protect you?
How high can you fly?
-Mmm.
-Look, I needed a scout.
Zazu was the last option.
Well, next to last.
Between Albert the Iguana
and I,
His Majesty decided
on the underling with wings.
And thus, I became
the lead scout
for the princess.
It's my third day,
going swimmingly,
if I may say so myself.
Sarabi, you can
say so as well.
How far do you think
you'll get with a bird?
How far do you two geniuses
think you'll get
stumbling around,
running into each other?
All the way to Milele.
-Milele is nothing but a myth.
-It's not a myth.
Circle of Life
and fairy tale herds.
-You're chasing something...
-Honestly.
-...that doesn't exist.
-As If.
I don't know that Milele
exists, but right now,
it's the only hope we have.
We don't need hope.
We need food.
Um...
Good job, brother.
Oh, real nice.
There's trouble in the trees.
My first real trouble,
and I am going to pass.
Not going.
I am staying right here,
thank you.
Come on, Sarabi. Looks like
there's dinner headed our way.
Sarabi, if I may.
He makes a valid point,
Your Highness.
But, on the other hand,
he's a starving lion,
he wants to eat me,
so I am slightly torn.
I think that went quite well,
all things considered.
And now, Kiara,
this is where I come in.
Rafiki.
Order! We will have order
in the Congress of Baboons.
Tonight, a cheetah
came into our trees
for the third night in a row.
Almost took one of our own.
It was Rafiki's fault.
He summoned the beast
with his dreams.
Rafiki
and his visions
must be banished
once and for all.
Rafiki tried to warn you.
His dreams
conjure our enemies.
He talks to the spirits,
summons the devil.
What are you talking about?
He's done it before.
His brother was chased
from these very trees,
never to be seen again.
Rafiki was just a child.
A child born with a leg that
does not work.
Yet somehow, he survived?
It was Rafiki who found water
in the dry season.
Who healed you, Inaki,
when you were sick.
He speaks to the insects,
converses with the moon.
Zala, you know
what will happen
if you send him
down from the trees.
He is amelaaniwa!
A curse to us all.
That's not true.
He doesn't
belong here.
All in favor of banishment,
cover one eye.
How can you
trust him?
Don't trust him,
and I don't trust his magic!
He doesn't
belong here.
He's not a baboon.
And he never will be.
He's not one of us.
And so, it is time.
No, wait.
Where will you go?
Where I should have gone
long ago.
To find all that was lost.
My family.
You can't survive on your own.
Nobody can.
And yet, here we are.
Oh, Rafiki.
The eye never forgets
what the heart has seen.
It's all right.
Hmm. Jamaa.
Hmm.
You can try to run, but I'm
afraid you won't get very far.
And why would I run from you?
Because we're lions.
As in... lions!
A flea
can trouble a lion
more than a lion
can trouble a flea.
I don't think you understand
what's about to happen.
There's no place
for you to go.
I am going forward.
I seriously doubt that.
It is easy to doubt everything
when you know nothing.
Can we get on
with this, please?
If you take my life,
you will never find Milele.
Wait, did you say Milele?
That is where I'm going.
Toward the light.
I have been there many times
in my dreams.
My brother waits for me there.
I've seen the tree.
Can picture it. The two of us,
together again.
And why would anyone trust
a baboon's dream?
Sometimes, a dream
is all you have.
The only truth
that lives in you.
Like the memory
of a great king.
How did you know?
Okay. Help us get to Milele,
and we will let you live.
-Do we have a deal?
-No.
What? Why?
Rafiki will let you live.
I've had enough of this!
Taka, do not eat him.
Wonderful.
Another misfit stray
we're not supposed to eat.
So, you expect us
to follow this baboon
to a place nobody
has ever seen?
-I'll be better off alone.
-Hhe ntombazane.
A single stick may smoke,
but it will never burn.
Okay, now that
there's five of us,
why don't we all go around
and say a fun fact
about ourselves?
I'll go first.
I once had
a crush on a flamingo.
I've never
said that out loud.
And they're walking away.
Yeah, places to go,
kingdoms to see.
We're busy. Let's hustle.
Wait, wait, wait. Now you're
the star of this thing?
Someone's a little tired
of bein' second banana, huh?
All of a sudden, there's
a lotta Rafiki in this story.
You even gave yourself
a long-lost brother.
-Yeah.
-What's next?
A funny catchphrase?
You gonna be fartin' next?
'Cause that's my thing.
You cannot tell the story
of Mufasa
without the story of Rafiki.
Oh, now he's even
talkin' about himself
in the third person.
Pretty soon, he'll have
his own fragrance.
And I'm the only one
with a fragrance around here.
It's called
"Pumbaa by Pumbaa,"
and from what I hear,
it's pretty gross.
Mom? Dad?
If you can hear me, come home.
Please.
Come home.
Mother?
Milele.
Mother!
-Rafiki.
-Ayi suka.
-What are you doing?
-I am fishing.
You're sitting on
a rock with your eyes closed.
My eyes are open.
It is my lids that are closed.
Why am I talking to a baboon?
I am not a baboon.
I am a mandrill.
No offense,
but a monkey is a monkey.
And a stray
is a stray.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means
we are very much the same.
Siyafana.
We are nothing alike.
Take a good look. I am a lion.
A lion
who fears water,
fears his own reflection.
Who can't sleep
because of what he sees
when he closes his eyes.
Huh?
You are afraid
of your dreams, Mufasa.
Afraid of what
you see in them.
I see my parents.
I feel them everywhere.
Of course
you do, Mufasa.
You will feel them forever.
My mother, I hear her voice.
She tells me that we are
on a journey to Milele,
but I feel so lost
without her.
Your journey
is not a dream, Mufasa.
Your mother is guiding you,
and where you are going,
a family awaits.
Ah... Ni heshima
kukutana nawe, binamu.
Nenda kwa amani.
Ah...
What are you doing?
We're starving.
'Twas not its time.
Instead, the fish has agreed
to let us share the water.
Iketle Rafiki.
Iketle mosimane.
I have a report.
It's morning.
End of report.
The earth divided
is now a choice.
Around or down?
The decision is yours.
Mmm.
Look out there,
beyond the light.
Across the deepest canyon.
"Across the deepest canyon."
We should go down.
Why? Because of some
fairy tale?
The rocks
will hide our tracks.
It's safer to go around.
I picked up their scents.
The only thing you picked up
is a hallucinating baboon.
I am a mandrill.
This is a waste of time.
Close your eyes.
What?
Tell me what you see.
What you feel.
There's nothing on the wind.
No, they're moving
-through the bush willow.
-They, who?
The females, out front.
Come on.
Clear your thoughts.
Concentrate.
I am concentrating.
He's right.
We have to go down.
Wow. Wow, wow, wow.
Ah! Uyabona mfana.
Now the many sticks
will make fire as one.
Come on. We have places to go.
And kingdoms to see.
And kingdoms to see!
Masihambeni.
♪ If you wanna go fast,
go alone ♪
♪ There's the road♪
♪ Off you go♪
♪ But if you wanna go far♪
♪ We go together♪
♪ So good, so far♪
♪ Your father left you
in my care ♪
♪ And now we're running
who knows where ♪
♪ Sometimes you need
a bird's-eye view ♪
♪ And I've got you
to see me through ♪
♪ By land, by air♪
♪ If you wanna go fast,
go alone ♪
♪ Day and night♪
-♪ There's the road ♪
-♪ I just might ♪
-♪ Off you go ♪
-♪ Yeah, right ♪
♪ If you wanna go far♪
♪ We go together♪
♪ So good, so far♪
♪ I will find
my family again♪
♪ I will walk with you
until then ♪
till the end ♪
♪ It's much easier
with a friend ♪
♪ I will find
my family again♪
♪ I will walk with you
until then ♪
till the end ♪
♪ Flying through ♪
♪ It's
much easier with a friend ♪
♪ Like the clouds and rain♪
♪ Like a meal
in a field of grain ♪
♪ Like the flecks of gold
in your mane ♪
♪ Sarabi, you and me,
we go together ♪
♪ Like clouds and rain ♪
♪ We will
find our family again ♪
♪ Like a meal
in a field of grain ♪
♪ We will
walk together till then ♪
♪ Like the flecks of gold
in your mane, Sarabi ♪
♪ We will
find our way to the end♪
♪ You and me, we go together ♪
♪ It's
much easier with a friend ♪
♪ My brother waits
for me to find him ♪
♪ We will
find our family again ♪
♪ My brother knows
I'm right behind him ♪
♪ We will
walk together till then ♪
♪ My brother tends to lose
his way ♪
♪ We will
find our way ♪
-♪ And go astray, say ♪
-♪ To the end ♪
♪ If you see my brother,
please remind him ♪
♪ It's
much easier with a friend♪
-♪ Sondela ♪
-♪ It's much easier ♪
-♪ With a friend ♪
-♪ Sondela mntanam! Sondela ♪
-♪ It's much easier♪
♪ Sondela mntanam! Sondela ♪
♪ We won't go alone ♪
♪ Not alone ♪
-♪ Here we go ♪
-♪ Down the road ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far ♪
-♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey♪
-♪ Sondela ♪
-♪ We go together♪
-♪ Sondela mntanam! ♪
-♪ So good, so far ♪
-♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
-♪ We go together ♪
-♪ Uyayiqonda mntanam! ♪
As we headed
across the Great Valley,
the hunters tracked
our every move.
Kiros. They are not alone.
They've collected a lioness.
And a monkey.
Mufasa.
You have to help me.
Help you how?
It's Sarabi, Mufasa.
She is the light
my mother spoke of.
-What?
-She's special.
The most amazing female
I've ever met in my life.
I don't know
what to say to her.
You've spent your life
with females.
Please, tell me what to say.
Just talk to her. Be yourself.
No, Mufasa.
You don't
understand.
Myself isn't good enough.
You...
just know things.
Fine. Fine.
Keep it simple.
Ask her a question.
Right. A question.
This... This is good.
Yeah, try to be confident.
Disinterested.
But I'm very interested.
-Tell her about the flowers.
-What flowers?
The valley she comes from.
There's flowers everywhere.
They're called duck flowers.
Long stems.
It's absolutely beautiful.
How do you know that?
When she passes,
I can smell them on her fur.
Okay.
Flowers. Disinterested.
-Flowers. And disinterested.
-And here's the most
-important thing, okay?
-Flowers.
-And disinterested.
-Listen...
-Flowers and disinterested.
-...when she speaks.
Males have trouble
with that one.
Flowers...
Sorry.
What did you say?
Really?
I heard you, brother.
I'm gonna make you proud.
It's very hot,
isn't it?
Yep.
I...
I love listening.
Okay.
-I'm listening right now.
-To what?
What you just said.
You're the one that's talking.
I am.
-You smell like a duck.
-What?
Flower.
Uh... A duck flower.
How do you know
about those flowers?
I, uh...
Well, I inhaled you
with my nose.
I can smell them.
That's amazing.
Our valley was
full of those flowers,
thousands of them
as far as the eye could see.
It was... It was the most
beautiful place, Taka.
Did he just say
she smells like a duck?
And you call me a baboon?
They shouldn't be here.
The migration patterns
are broken.
-I... I don't understand...
-Outsiders!
This is not a drill!
Just to be clear,
I never signed up for this.
It's okay. We're safe.
They're on the other side.
Nope!
They can just jump across!
We are trapped!
What do we do?
The elephants
will fight with us.
And why would they do that?
Because I'm going to ask them.
Got a better idea?
Yes,
Mr. Ask-Questions-First.
Get ready to run.
Uh...
Where is she going?
Hello? Listen to me, please.
We need your help.
Can you talk with me?
We need your help. Please.
They're coming!
Sarabi! Sarabi, wait!
Sarabi! Sarabi, wait. Wait!
Where is she going?
She's going for the hive!
Like I said, get ready to run!
Run!
Get to the trees!
Why am I running?
Uh, Your Highness,
hold on!
Zazu!
Sarabi!
Stand your ground!
Do not retreat!
I got you.
Oh, Sarabi, I got you.
That's right.
Run along, little kitty cats.
Thank you, my friend.
Ah!
Over here.
Ah...
Mmm...
Vuta Pumzi. Sarabi.
Alive. She's alive!
Why are you all looking at me?
You were thrown from the tree.
He saved your life.
-Who?
-Taka.
-Uh...
-Taka saved you.
Isn't that right, brother?
You saved me?
Uh... Well, I...
I had to do something.
Thank you.
We're lucky.
Those bees
almost killed us all.
Those bees saved our lives.
-Oh, Mufasa.
-Really?
Because, uh, it felt like
an elephant stampede.
We're alive, aren't we?
The elephants
would have fought with us.
We're lions.
Nobody will fight with us.
Not out here.
♪ Ngiya... ♪
♪ Milele... ♪
♪ Umfoweth'ungimele ♪
Where's he going?
Beyond the horizon itself.
♪ Umfoweth'ungimele... ♪
Mufasa, thank you.
Rafiki, who...
Who are the Outsiders?
Well, the Outsiders come
from many prides.
But, when they are born,
they are hated
because they are different
from their tribe.
Like you and your tribe?
Yes, just like me.
-But, Rafiki?
-Yes?
Why do they wanna
hurt everybody?
Sometimes, when the people
most like you don't love you,
it is a hurt that can cause
the greatest pain.
And this pain
can lead you
to hate everything.
I'm glad that didn't happen
to you, Rafiki.
Yes, my child. I'm glad too.
Um, hi. We're here, too.
Yeah, why are you leavin' us
outside this story
when I'm pretty sure
we are the ultimate outsiders.
-Come on!
-Yeah,
we've always
been misunderstood.
I contain multitudes.
There are many ways to Milele.
But this will be ours.
Go. Go, Mufasa.
Find your forever.
I got you.
Oh, Sarabi, I got you.
Mmm.
Iketle Rafiki.
Iketle mosimane.
Mmm...
Hey, Rafiki?
What are you doing?
I am confirming
my vision, Mufasa.
Can I ask you
something, Rafiki?
Hmm?
How many of your visions
have come true?
-So far, none.
-None?
But it's not what I see.
It's what I feel.
But how do you...
How do you know when
you should follow a feeling?
Milele exists.
I feel it in here.
The question is,
what do you feel, Mufasa,
in there?
The weather's shifted.
There's not enough fresh snow.
Hey, if the Outsiders
find our tracks,
they'll follow them to Milele.
Zazu, only you can
help us now.
Oh. Are you quite sure
about that?
No, I was actually thinking
that Rafiki looks pretty
handy, and with the stick...
Zazu, you can use your wings
to cover our tracks
as we head up the mountain
without leaving a trace.
Hey, you can do this.
Oh, hmm. Yeah.
Yes, sir. You're right.
I've got this.
Okay. It's just me against
a frozen mountain.
You know, one hornbill charged
with saving the future...
Whoa! Mummy!
Oh, man alive,
that's cold.
Now what's happening?
We can't keep stopping.
Somehow, they have
covered their tracks.
In the snow?
It's not possible.
Majesty, they could be
anywhere on this mountain...
Then find them!
Now.
♪ Zazu, Zazu, Zazu♪
♪ Zazu, Zazu!♪
I have a report.
The Outsiders
are completely lost.
Well played, Mufasa.
Great job, Zazu.
And as per usual.
I knew
you could do it.
We did it. We did it.
No, you did it.
Great thinking, Mufasa.
Oh, we're all
rubbing off on each other.
Perfectly normal thing to do.
Who wants to rub against Zazu?
No one. I'm leaving now.
I'll scout ahead.
Ah.
I got you, Rafiki.
-Hey.
-I got you.
Ho monate, Mufasa.
Yeah, I got you.
Mufasa...
"I got you."
Hidden in the shadows,
downwind, light of foot.
Interesting hunting style,
Mufasa.
We have to eat something
before we take on
that descent.
Unfortunately, there's
nothing to hunt up here.
See under that rock?
There's a civet
about to leave his den.
Of course
you can smell
a civet hidden in the snow.
You, the lion
who can do anything.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means I see you, Mufasa.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Now, that part, I believe.
Because, smart as you are,
you have a way of seeing
everything but yourself.
What is this?
What is this, Sarabi?
There is a civet in the snow
right where you said
it would be.
And you smelled the Outsiders
on the wind,
which means you're the one who
smelled the flowers on my fur.
It was a lucky guess.
You can smell the exact flower
from my valley.
No,
that's not possible.
You saved me.
Held me, covered me in the
stampede, comforted me.
No, it was Taka.
"I got you.
I got you, Sarabi."
-I'm here to protect him.
-That was you.
I was lost in the water,
and he found me.
My brother saved me.
Ah, I sensed it
from the beginning.
His blood is the blood
of the king.
Mufasa.
-That is his destiny.
-No!
His destiny was to save you.
Now tell me it's you.
♪ Ever since you appeared♪
♪ I've been running from
something deep inside ♪
♪ And it's worse
than I feared♪
♪ 'Cause I look in your eyes
and I can't hide♪
-♪ I push you away ♪
-♪ Don't push me away ♪
♪ But the feelings come back
just twice as strong♪
-♪ I don't know what to say ♪
-♪ You know just what to say ♪
♪ But I know that I'm right
where I belong♪
♪ The way you know
just where to be ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ The way you move,
the way you see ♪
♪ You see me ♪
♪ The way you feel
when you're with me ♪
♪ Beside me ♪
♪ Don't hide from me anymore♪
♪ Tell me it's you,
I know it's you ♪
♪ What do I say?
Where do I go?♪
♪ How do I know
you feel the same? ♪
♪ Tell me it's you,
I know it's you ♪
♪ Quiet and low,
letting it go ♪
♪ Letting you know
it's in me ♪
♪ Ev'rywhere that I roam♪
♪ I remind myself
not to overstay ♪
♪ Ev'ry time I find home♪
♪ Something happens
to take that home away ♪
♪ But you've seen
what I've seen ♪
-♪ I see you ♪
-♪ As you lead with ♪
♪ A strength that shines
right through♪
♪ You move like a queen,
a true queen ♪
♪ Don't let anything take me
away from you♪
♪ Tell me it's you,
I know it's you ♪
♪ Say it again,
say it again♪
♪ Tell me I'll always
be with you ♪
-♪ Tell me it's you ♪
-♪ I know it's you ♪
♪ Say it again,
say it again♪
♪ Tell me you're
always with me ♪
♪ The way you know
just where to be ♪
♪ Now I know ♪
♪ The way you move,
the way you see ♪
♪ I see you♪
♪ The love I feel
when you're with me ♪
♪ Beside me,
beside me♪
♪ Say it again,
say it again, say it again ♪
♪ Tell me the world
won't interfere ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again♪
♪ Tell me the words
I wanna hear ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again♪
♪ Open your eyes
and here we go ♪
♪ I know it's you♪
♪ You know I love her,
my brother ♪
♪ There's nothing we keep
from each other♪
♪ I saved your life♪
♪ This is how you repay me?♪
♪ What do I do?
What does it mean?♪
♪ How do I ever unsee
what I've seen?♪
♪ He was my kin
She was my queen♪
♪ Now it's broken forever
and...♪
♪ "Tell her it's you!
She knows it's you!"♪
♪ What did you say to her?
What did you do?♪
♪ I'm next in line
She should be mine, ha!♪
♪ Are the ancestors
laughing, I... ♪
♪ What would they say?
Father is gone♪
♪ Not before giving me
strength to go on♪
♪ He never trusted you!♪
♪ Did he know
you'd betray me so?♪
♪ When you were drowning
I pulled you out♪
♪ I gave you life
which you lived in my debt!♪
♪ Now I'm the one drowning
Tumbling down♪
♪ Trying to escape
what I cannot forget ♪
♪ I have a brother no longer♪
♪ It's over and done♪
♪ Now all I have
is this shame ♪
♪ And this rage
that I can't...♪
♪ Out...♪
♪ ...run♪
Deceit is a tool
of a great king.
There wasn't much
to eat on this mountain
until now.
Tell me, how did you cover
your tracks in the snow?
A bird helped us.
Lions getting help
from a bird?
Just as I will help you.
You will help us?
You think we need help
from a wounded coward?
I may hold the blood
of a king,
but it was Mufasa
who killed your son.
It was Mufasa
who trapped you up here,
outsmarted you at every turn.
Now I will lead you to him
and to Milele.
Milele!
Milele is nothing but a dream,
a vision sold to cubs.
Ah. Well,
tell that to the monkey.
He leads them to it.
Look at you.
A pack of starving wolves
clinging to the side
of a mountain.
No tracks to follow.
Only one chance at revenge.
Me!
Revenge...
What about your father?
Because of Mufasa,
I have no father.
He did this.
Yes.
You lost a father,
and I, a son.
Taka, will you join us?
Together, we can both
have our revenge.
It will be my pleasure...
King.
Taka!
Taka, where have you been?
Hunting.
I couldn't find anything,
but I was never
as good as you.
Or my mother.
There's something I need
to tell you.
No.
There's something
I need to tell you.
I need to thank you.
You kept your word
to Eshe and Obasi.
-Taka...
-You saved me, Mufasa.
And I...
will never forget
what you've done, my brother.
Oh, guys!
I have found a way down
just beyond those near peaks.
Was it something I said?
Hey, Rafiki?
Yes.
We are nearing
destiny, Mufasa.
And so, the earth must shake.
Okay, now I am
100 million percent sure
who Taka is.
Just be honest. Is it me?
In case you missed it,
we're not featured in this.
I think the civet has more
screen time.
Hey, maybe they'll put us
in the play.
No, no, please don't
mention the play again.
I went to see it.
I'm nothing
but a giant sock puppet.
You went to see it?
You didn't bring me?
Rafiki, Mufasa and Sarabi
are in love?
Love?
That sounds gross
and not something like
I constantly
think about and really want.
What is Taka gonna do to them?
Little one,
Taka's heart was broken.
And now his trap was set.
Mufasa. Do you see?
I don't believe it.
The other side
of the light.
Home.
Milele.
I can't believe it.
We found it. We found Milele.
Yes.
You found it, brother.
You always do.
Rafiki.
This is the tree
from your visions.
I have seen this tree
many times,
and, in each vision,
there was always a brother
standing right here.
But there's
no one here, Rafiki,
and you came here
to find your twin.
He was taken from me long ago.
What I saw in my dreams
was a brother.
Standing right here.
A friend, family.
What I saw was you.
The unseeable.
I saw Mufasa.
Me?
Yes, you.
My brother.
Mufasa.
How do you know who I am?
We know the Outsiders
are hunting you,
and we fear
you'll bring danger.
No. No. We covered our tracks.
I promise you
Milele is a safe place,
and I would never do anything
to jeopardize that.
Do not run.
You have nothing to fear.
We are not here for you.
We have come for Mufasa.
Oh, no, no.
How did they get here?
Do not let him divide us.
It's no use, Mufasa.
The Circle...
The Circle is broken.
No!
Mufasa, what are you doing?
I'm going to fight,
and I'm going to show them
that they can fight, too.
Rafiki, when you hear
my signal,
help me call them together.
Yes, my brother.
There are
other lions here.
Find them.
With pleasure, Your Majesty.
Mufasa, you're not alone.
It's my turn to go
ask questions first.
This is where the hunt ends,
Mufasa.
Thanks to your brother.
He left a trail of scars
for us to follow.
He made a deal
to save himself.
-Gave us this kingdom.
-Tell me he's lying.
Asked us to kill the stray.
Taka, please!
I'm the son of a king.
But Sarabi chose you.
Just like Mother.
Just like my own father.
I saved you
and you betrayed me!
What have you done?
I'm your brother,
fight with me!
You stole my destiny.
Now this is yours.
He's one of us now.
My son's name...
was Shaju.
Shaju!
All of this
should have been his.
And now I will rule it
without mercy.
This one is mine.
Please. We can't wage
this battle alone.
There's nothing we can do.
They've chased us
from our pride lands before.
-They're too strong.
-Fight with us.
Fight for your young.
For your future.
What future?
They've taken all we have.
And they will always
take more.
I am Mufasa,
a stray with no pride,
and yet I stand before you.
Head unbowed.
I know you're afraid,
but trust me.
Nothing will change
if we remain isolated
to our own tribes
without concern
for the fate of others.
But why should
we stand with you?
This is your fight.
Today, they are here
for us lions,
but I assure you,
as you let them walk among you
in search of us now,
they are plotting to come
for you tomorrow.
One lion's hope cannot change
the fate of Milele.
There is no lion as large
as an elephant,
as strong as an oxen,
fast as a cheetah
or tall as a giraffe,
who can soar and scout
as wide and far
as the cranes
and hawks in the sky.
So, can't you see...
Every being has a place
in the Circle of Life.
My breath is your breath.
Your fight is my fight.
I will not bend to evil,
and neither should you.
Nants ingonyama bagithi!
Mufasa is right.
Milele is home.
We must stand with Mufasa!
Nants
ingonyama bagithi!
Together we shall stand strong
for Milele!
Nants
ingonyama bagithi!
Nants ingonyama bagithi!
Here comes the lion!
From this moment on,
everything the light touches
belongs to me.
You'll have to take it.
Bye-bye.
You've messed
with the wrong hornbill!
Lunch is served.
Stand down! I am highly
trained and occasionally a...
This is so embarrassing.
I do have wings, you know.
Taka!
Taka, please. Please!
Mufasa.
You dare
to challenge me?
You took my son.
My future.
Taka... Taka, your
moment of courage will come.
Blood for blood.
Please. Don't kill him.
I didn't kill him.
You did.
They're coming.
The last lions.
Time for their extinction,
and we'll start
with the youngest.
The earth will shake.
Attack!
Mufasa.
Close your eyes
and tell me what you hear.
What you feel.
Mufasa!
He defeated the Outsiders.
The king of Milele!
Is that him?
Our king?
Your Highness.
The King of Milele.
-My king.
-Your Highness.
-Your Majesty.
-My king.
Defeated Kiros!
-King?
No, no, I'm not king.
Raise your heads.
No. I'm just... No, no!
No more kings.
We are all one. Please.
Please. Raise your heads.
But, Mufasa,
you have
brought them together.
You helped them see
in themselves
what they considered
unseeable.
Nothing is more kingly.
No, Rafiki.
I'm not king.
I'm not royal blood.
Don't you see, my brother?
It is not what you were,
it is what you have become.
The King of Milele.
My brother,
something beautiful
awaits you.
Is this real?
But it can't be.
It can't be.
Oh, Mufasa.
But how can it be?
I had a son named Mufasa.
Taken from me
by a great flood.
Mother?
I never stopped hoping.
Believing.
My son.
I've dreamt of this moment.
And now it's come true.
Oh, Mufasa.
But Father?
Where's Father?
He lives in you now.
He lives in you.
I always dreamed
we'd be together again.
And I knew it would be
in Milele.
My son.
Mufasa.
Mufasa, please forgive me.
You must banish him, Sire.
As long as I am king,
my brother will have
a place here.
Brother, I am so...
But I won't ever
say your name again.
I can't.
I won't.
Then call me Scar.
So I will never forget
what I have done.
Scar.
Your Majesty.
Welcome home.
So, Mufasa,
I see your family
has been awaiting you
in Milele after all.
Yes, Rafiki.
Yes, they were.
It is your time, Mufasa.
Rafiki, I wish
I could see him.
I wish I could meet
my grandfather.
As Mufasa once told
your father,
look into the heavens, Kiara.
The great kings of the past
will always be there
waiting for you.
Mmm...
I don't want him
to go, Rafiki.
I don't want it to end.
Don't you see, Kiara?
Mufasa lives in you.
He lives in you.
Dad!
-Rafiki.
-It was unbelievable.
-It was perfect.
-You could not improve on it.
That said, I do have notes.
Some suggestions. Take 'em
or leave 'em. But take 'em.
-Dad!
-Kiara!
Kiara.
Dad.
Where's Mom?
Well, love,
there's something
you need to know.
What? Did something
happen to Mom?
Baby, I'm right here,
and I'm fine.
Where were you?
Kiara,
this is your new brother.
Brother?
I have a brother?
Hi there. I'm Kiara.
I will take care of you.
Forever.
Little one,
let me tell you a story.
A story of a great king.