Made by Nara + the help of AI
Subsource: translator_nara.nim
DO NOT ERASE THE CREDIT!
Respect who made it.
https://trakteer.id/nara.nim/tip
Look at the stars, whenever you feel
alone, the great kings of the past will
always be
up there to guide you, and so am I.
My friends, the time of my family's
growth is upon us.
This home we share is the fulfillment of
my father's vision.
How wonderful is it that Nala and I get
to continue his dream and make even
greater the
in the circle of life.
Nala, my love, I'm on my way.
Simba, I'm here, I'm here.
Security detail has arrived!
One gentle reminder, we are not food.
No, no, no, no, no.
We are just two guys walking to work
through a pride of hungry lions.
Which is perfectly normal.
I'm not terrified.
Security detail reporting for duty, Your
Grace.
Your Highness.
Ruler of all four-legged creatures.
And that one three-legged zebra.
Oh, right, Ron.
That was tragic.
It was an Aiden Ron.
Yeah.
Ron has three legs.
That's still one more than me.
Well, are those arms really?
I don't know.
I think they're paws.
I consider all those legs.
Guys, this is serious.
I need you to stay with Kiara until I
get back.
Are you saying that your security detail
has been called on to do babysitting?
Pumbaa, we should really discuss this
because I don't really love Chew.
Guys, I promised her everything would be
okay.
Well, that's one way to parent.
You're gonna have to grow up sometime.
What else did you tell her?
That she could be whatever she wants to
be?
That life is fair?
I need you two to try and act like
adults, okay?
Don't scare Kiara.
And most of all, no stories.
No stories?
Wait a second.
I know where your head goes.
I grew up with you two, promise me.
Okay, you know what, you know what, you
know what?
Fine, no stories.
Speak for yourself, Pumbaa.
No.
Shh, we'll tell a story anyway.
Okay, we'll tell them that we're not
gonna tell a story
and that we're gonna tell a story.
Are you guys serious?
I'm clearly within earshot.
Dad.
Hey, little one.
Dad, the storm's coming and I'm scared.
I want to go with you and Mom.
Oh, don't be scared, my love.
Timon and Pumbaa will watch you while
I'm gone.
Be brave now, Kiara.
Be brave.
Okay, we've prepared a story!
Scar looked at us!
He knew it was the end of the line.
I could smell the fear.
That was actually me, but yes.
(Roar)
So you two defeated Scar, and then you
ate him?
Honestly, one of the best meals I ever
had.
My dad told me he defeated Scar.
Well, OK, but your dad, as we all know,
is a pathological liar.
He's always lying.
Get it?
Ooh!
Ah!
I'm scared.
I want Mom and Dad.
Oh, look, look, look, look, look.
Don't be scared, Kiara.
How about we sing you a song?
And a what?
No, it is way too early for the song.
It worked on Simba.
He thought he had murdered his own
father.
He was singing and dancing around in
seconds.
I can't just turn it on like that.
I have to be in the moment.
He sang that song for six years
straight.
Well, who didn't?
What?
Aah!
No!
It's Ron, the three-legged zebra!
Run for your lives!
He heard what we've been saying about
him!
We're sorry, Ron!
They were jokes!
They were just jokes!
It's Rafiki!
Rafiki!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Little one, there's no reason to cry.
My parents, they're gone.
Hey, look out there, m'doggo.
You see those baobab trees blowing in
the wind?
The roots of those trees are very
strong, like your family.
And just as they did for you, your
parents have gone to the ceremony of
birth in grounds.
And when they've returned, the circle of
life will bring a blessing to you,
Kiara, that you will never forget.
Man, he's good.
He's such a visual storyteller, yet it
makes sense that he lives alone.
I just want the storm to pass, and then
I promise to be brave!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I'll tell you a secret.
When your father, Simba, was your age,
he was afraid of the thunder and would
hide behind the king.
When did he stop hiding?
One day, during a big storm, your
grandfather, Mufasa, took your father to
the very top of Pride Rock,
told him to stand with him and howl into
the wind,
and Simba slowly stepped out with the
king,
and together, they roared into the
night.
But I'm not brave like my dad.
And I could never be like Mufasa.
Is that so?
Then maybe it's time I tell you a story.
A story of a cub, not much bigger than
you,
A lion born without a drop of nobility
in his blood, a lion who would change
our lives forever.
A story!
So glad I brought some crickets.
But go easy, we're in a cave.
This story begins far beyond the
mountains and the shadows, on the other
side of the light.
In this place, everything was dying of
thirst, as twenty full moons have passed
without a single drop of water.
But when the skies finally opened,
destiny would reign.
Mufasa!
Come see!
Mom!
What is that light way out there?
Oh, that's very special.
Beyond the horizon, beyond the last
cloud in the sky,
that's a place we call Milele.
Maléle?
It means forever.
Imagine a kingdom full of life,
water and food,
grass and sky,
as far as the eye can see.
Will we ever go there?
Oh, yes, Mufasa.
That's exactly where we're headed.
But we can also be there right now.
We can close our eyes,
let our dreams take us.
♪ Beyond the horizon, beyond the last  ♪
♪  cloud in the sky, there's a place I ♪
♪ know... ♪
♪ Imagine a kingdom, the water flows, the  ♪
♪  grass is hard, it's not a dream. ♪
♪ One day we'll grow, call it a dream. ♪
♪ Milele, come with me. ♪
♪ Milele.. ♪
♪ Milele ♪
♪ And it lives in me, it lives in me ♪
♪ You feel... ♪
♪ Life is circle, life is not small ♪
♪ We know that there's enough for all ♪
♪ There is always more.. ♪
♪ ..can you feel it? ♪
♪ We'll wander, no longer be carried by  ♪
♪  the thunders of the night ♪
♪ And you'll see it, and as you grow  ♪
♪  and there's more ♪
♪ Can you find your way? ♪
♪ We live it ♪
♪ It's always there ♪
♪ We call this Milele ♪
♪ It's always been... o..Milele ♪
♪ And it lives in you and it lives in me ♪
♪ Every... Milele ♪
What is this?
Rain!
Finally, we have rain!
Dad, race you to the light!
You're too fast!
I've never beaten you!
Nobody has ever beaten you!
I know!
Mufasa!
The fastest cub in the world!
Thank you.
Mufasa?
That's enough.
Come back now.
Mufasa, stay there!
I'm coming, son.
Father!
Mufasa!
Mufasa
I'll catch you on the turn, find my
voice, find my voice!
Mufasa, the cliff is too high for you to
cross it again.
Come on, Mufasa.
You can do this.
Find your mother's voice.
Listen to your father, Mufasa!
Listen to us!
Kapila, he's there!
Mom!
He's there!
Mother!
Mufasa!
Find your footing, one step at a time.
I can't!
You can do this, I'm right here.
Mom?
Dad?
Can you hear me?
Is anyone out there?
Mom?
Please.
I'm scared
The floodwaters joined a distant river,
carried Mufasa far from his mother and father
beyond..
All that he knew.
Hello!
I'm Taka, son of a Barsi.
What's your name?
Mufasa
I'm not allowed to talk to outsiders,
but I have a secret and I really want to
tell you.
What's the secret?
I'll get in trouble.
Please, just tell me.
Uh, I don't know.
Just tell me!
Okay.
You're about to be eaten!
I hate secrets!
Swim!
But I can't!
You have to swim!
I don't know how!
All right, chin up!
Then walk underwater, really fast!
I can't!
Come on, you bastard!
Faster!
Help me, Taka!
Help me!
I told you to wait for me!
It's not my fault mum.
I came down for a drink and saw him
floating by.
I'd like you to meet Mufasa.
Oh, you're lucky those crocs were young
and afraid to fight.
Let's go.
We can't just leave him here.
Rules are rules, Taka.
Obasi will never accept a stray.
I'm not a stray.
I'm just...
lost.
See?
He's just lost.
There was a flood.
My parents, they tried to save me.
Do you know which way is home?
Home, to be lost,
is to learn the way.
Call me, Ashe.
I'm tired, Ashe.
Come on, it's this way.
Come on, Mufasa
Is this..
Milele
No, my love
I was trying to nap, Aeshae, the
all-important nap of kings, only to be
awoken by the disgusting
hideous, revolting stench of a stray.
Will we come upon an outsider, tell me,
what do we do?
Obasi, I know.
Eat it!
But I found him, Dad.
I saved his life.
Taka, we do not associate with
outsiders.
The only true bond is blood.
I've heard stories of lions twice our
size.
These outsiders will devour everything
in their path.
Does he look like he's going to devour
you?
Oh, that smell is disgusting.
I'm not even sure I could eat this
quepete.
I'm not a quepete.
I'm a Mufasa.
Do you even know what Mufasa means?
No.
It means king, and that's me.
You better start running, little Mufasa,
for your life.
If I run, you'll never catch me.
I'm the fastest cub that ever lived.
My father taught me so.
Ooh, Taka, you have a challenge.
They will race to the dead tree and
back.
And when the prince defeats him, I will
finish him in one bite.
What if Mufasa wins?
If he wins, he lives, Obasi.
He stays with me.
You have my word.
Let the race begin!
Oh, clumsy little stray.
Run, Mufasa!
You did not have to do that.
Taka is the future king.
He has to win his first challenge.
No, Obasi.
To be a true king, he must earn it.
Don't take that away from him.
Better hurry.
I have one more secret, Mufasa.
I always wanted a brother!
Caesar!
Obasi!
You will keep him with the females,
Tucker.
How could you lose to a stray?
Well done, Taka.
Well done.
I thought you said you were fast.
I had to let you win.
Well, I did just go days with no sleep
or...
Anyway, come on, you fusser.
Let's get in some trouble.
♪ When I am king, no other animal will  ♪
♪  break my stride, break my stride. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ - And my brother  ♪
♪  - my brother  ♪
♪  - when I'm king, you'll always take my side. ♪
♪ Yeah, right  ♪
♪  That's right ♪
♪ When I am talking ♪
♪ No other animal will break our pride ♪
♪ Break our pride ♪
♪ And my brother ♪
♪ My brother ♪
♪ Our prey may run away but they can't  ♪
♪  hide ♪
♪ What's your hide? ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say you could be a  ♪
♪  beastly? ♪
♪ Okay, she didn't say ♪
♪ Hide away, hide away ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Hey, did your father say you could be  ♪
♪  out this far? ♪
♪ Okay, run away, run away, run away,  ♪
♪  let's go! ♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say you could be out  ♪
♪  this way? ♪
♪ I'm a cyber-chop, yes you are, yes you  ♪
♪  are, let's go! ♪
♪ Hey, did your father say you could be  ♪
♪  out this far? ♪
♪ Make a wish on the brightest star and  ♪
♪  I'll say ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother, I always  ♪
♪  wanted a brother ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother, just like  ♪
♪  you. ♪
♪ And I always wanted a brother, ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother, ♪
♪ I always wanted a brother, just like  ♪
♪  you. ♪
♪ See that tree? ♪
♪ Those birds are watching the world  ♪
♪  unfold. ♪
♪ The world unfold. ♪
♪ Oh, brother. ♪
♪ My brother. ♪
♪ When I'm king, they will do as I told. ♪
♪ You may look down on them, but they are  ♪
♪  free. ♪
♪ You can't catch me! ♪
♪ Then where they go cannot be controlled ♪
♪ No one looks down on me ♪
♪ They look down on us, brother ♪
♪ Some things you chase, but you cannot  ♪
♪  hold ♪
♪ Okay, it's getting old ♪
♪ Let's go, let's go! ♪
♪ Hey, did your mama say that you could  ♪
♪  learn this way? ♪
♪ I've got to find a way, find a way, find  ♪
♪  a way ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ I heard his father say he doesn't want  ♪
♪  this strain ♪
♪ I dare you to say that again to my face ♪
♪ What did you say about my brother? ♪
♪ He is not a stray, that's my brother ♪
♪ You stay away from my brother cause I  ♪
♪  say so ♪
♪ If you put your paws on my brother ♪
♪ You'll be the jaws of his brother ♪
♪ Those are the laws for my brother ♪
♪ Where'd he go? ♪
♪ I've always wanted a brother ♪
♪ I still remember my mother ♪
♪ One season after another ♪
♪ Season after season after ♪
♪ Season after another ♪
♪ I'd do one thing for my brother ♪
♪ I'd do anything for my brother ♪
♪ And I'll be king with my brother ♪
♪ In my sight! ♪
♪ I've always wanted a brother ♪
♪ Now we rely on each other ♪
♪ One season after another ♪
♪ Hey, move faster! ♪
♪ Hey, sucker! ♪
♪ I'll race you to the other side! ♪
ELEPHANT STAMPEDE!
Chigaru jerk like 20 feet
Oh, that's a new record!
Obasi, they did it again!
Your sons are nothing but trouble!
That one is not my son!
They're heathens!
The both of them!
This stray is forbidden to be near the
Shade Tree!
Mufasa and I were just playing.
You two will never be brothers!
Go back to the females and stay away
from my son
Oh.. your mother
She adopts every lizard speaks to
passing grasshoppers
- I want to go with him
- you want to be with the females.. you belong with the male
he gets to hunt
..with mother
One day..
He will betray you
- That is what strays do
- Mufasa would never betray me
- hey hey
This will all be yours my son.
You will be king so pay attention
Study every move I make
Sleeping again, that is what males do we
protect the pride as we nap that's
Well, that's power
Power
Why are we stopping?
close your eyes and tell me what you
hear, what you feel.
There's a herd of antelope heading
across the dry lake bed, about half a
day from here.
And how do you know they're not
gazelles?
Their steps are too heavy, moving way
too slow.
What else?
Come on, you can do it.
When the wind hits their horns, it moves
up instead of across, so definitely
antelope horns.
Very good.
What is it, Mufasa?
What's wrong?
Sometimes I get a scent.
It's barely a trace on the wind.
And it smells like home.
Then it's gone.
Mufasa, your parents are still out
there.
We can keep looking.
I lost them, Eshe.
You're wasting your time training me
like this.
But these skills you have, no other male
has them.
Obasi will never accept me.
I'll never be his blood, his family.
But you are my family.
And if Obasi could see how gifted you
are...
Well, maybe I like being a stray.
You know, no rules, no responsibility.
I'm the lucky one, Eshe.
What do you mean, Mufasa?
I never have to be like Taka.
I never have to be king.
Did he say no rules and no
responsibilities?
An outcast afraid of water never takes a
bath.
Which means he smells like me!
Which is not good!
Well, either way, I think that means
that he's one of us!
This is it?
It's our time!
This is our moment!
And a one, and a two, and a one, two...
Hakuna Mufasa, what a wonderful name.
Hakuna Mufasa, he ain't no passing
craze.
It means no prob--!
What?!
Don't go there.
All right, all right, Rafiki's right.
We'll get letters from legal.
Those vultures will take everything we
have.
Which technically is nothing.
Look at us, we're naked animals.
No wonder I'm always freezing.
They want this!
Come on, Pumbaa, let's bring it home!
Hakuna Mufasa!
Quiet!
Kiara's a music snob.
Rafiki, keep going.
Later that day, Eshe was teaching Mufasa
how to hunt in pairs.
But, as Taka was secretly watching,
something terrible was hunting them.
Mufasa, run!
Eshe!
Keep moving, Mufasa!
They go for the neck!
It's okay, Mufasa..
it's okay..
That was very brave of you Mufasa..
Thank you.
Eshe?
What has happened?
A-are you...hurt?
They were huge.
White as ghosts.
Like nothing I've seen before.
Oh.. Obasi.
Had Mufasa not been there, I...
Taka...
I owe you a great debt, Mufasa.
We need to prepare.
They're downwind, less than a day away.
No.
You couldn't possibly know this.
Send a scout and you'll see.
They'll be coming for us.
Father, please, let me explain.
Not now.
Taka, come.
Where is my son?
There was a young lion, Majesty.
He fought Shaju.
And yet, you came back.
You survived.
I was badly hurt.
I promise, Majesty, this is the truth.
The truth?
Yes, the truth.
The truth is standing behind you.
There were others, Majesty.
But only one left blood on his mane.
Which means he left Shaju to die.
Saved himself.
These young lions will see their king.
His blood is common, ordinary.
And was he their king?
No, Kiros.
You are the only king.
An ordinary lion, and you left my son to
die?
I was injured.
There was no choice.
Please, Majesty, you have to believe me.
There's no reason to fear me.
I would never harm one of my own.
Thank you, Majesty.
I'll leave that pleasure to them.
Majesty!
No!
no!
No one can ever know you ran, but you
ran for your mother.
It never happened, Taka.
Do you understand?
But I didn't know.
I was just...
I was just scared.
It doesn't matter.
We must protect the bloodline.
Protect them with a lie?
Father, that's deceitful.
Deceit is a tool of a great king.
Taka, it's what kings must do.
But I'm not a king.
I'm just your son.
Obasi
Chigaru.
Chigaru!
I'm here!
What did you see?
They're coming this way, Obasi!
Two lions for every one of ours!
Each one bigger than the next!
But none as mighty as Kiros!
Their terrifying king!
Outsiders.
The stories were all true.
I must protect the bloodline, Eshe.
The future of this pride.
Taka, you are that future.
Futu--re...
Dad-- what do you mean?
I'm sending you away.
Far from here.
You will leave and start a new life, a
new beginning.
I need you to go with him, Mufasa, to
pledge your loyalty.
They'll arrive with the sunrise.
Where will we go, Eshe?
Without you, I have no home.
Mufasa, you and Taka together, that...
that is home.
Eshe.
Mufasa, look out there, beyond the
light.
You know what I see?
I see the place your mother told you
about.
A place beyond the river's end, across
the deepest canyon on the other side of
the mountains.
A place beyond the horizon itself.
A bright land so green, so...
perfect.
That to see it, is to see...
Milele.
Yes.
Forever.
My parents spoke of Milele often.
My mother told me it was where we were
going.
And don't you see, Mufasa?
You must keep going.
You must continue your journey toward
the light.
Please, Eshe.
I can't lose you.
You have my love always, Mufasa.
But your family is still out there,
waiting for you.
I can feel their presence.
And I know you can too.
Go.
Go, Mufasa.
Find your way home.
Mother, please forgive me.
I beg you.
There's no need, my love.
Taka, your moment of courage will come.
Now both of you go, go and find your
place in the circle of life.
They left their family never to see them
again.
This story is killing me.
It's toying with my emotion.
And here is the worst part.
What's that?
I'm out of crickets.
Oh, maybe that's for the best.
I need a bathroom break before the
second act.
Everyone wait for me.
Ah!
I am back.
Thumba, did you wash your hooves?
Mm-hmm.
Thumba?
I did, I did.
Pumba?
I'm just going to walk on them again
right after.
Pumba.
Ugh.
Rafiki, did the outsiders come?
Yes.
And as the hunters led Kiros into the
Valley of Kings,
Obasi and Eshe stood their ground.
Which one of you is king?
You have no reason to challenge me.
Does this look like a challenge, King?
There are rules among lions.
Not anymore.
While you rule this pride, I've built my
army.
Yours is the last pride in the Valley of
Kings.
Which means everything the light touches
belongs to me.
There will be one ruler.
One Lion King.
♪ You say you're the king, but you lie  ♪
♪  around in the shade, out of shape, unafraid. ♪
♪ The moon cuts the path through the sky  ♪
♪  by night or by day, it doesn't obey, and neither ♪
♪ do I. ♪
♪ You took my son. ♪
♪ I hope you can run. ♪
♪ Cause, I'm gonna be the last thing you see ♪
♪ before you go ♪
♪ bye, bye ♪
♪ There you go. ♪
♪ Bye-bye. ♪
♪ Climb every tree ♪
♪ Across land and sea ♪
♪ I'll make you go, bye-bye ♪
♪ I make you go, bye-bye ♪
♪ Everything in my clutches, ♪
♪ Ha ♪
♪ Bye-bye. ♪
♪ Everything the light ♪
♪ touches ♪
♪ This circle of life is a lie. ♪
♪ A pretty way to say there are predators  ♪
♪  in prey. ♪
♪ That circle of vultures up high. ♪
♪ They keep stealing glances. ♪
♪ They don't like your chances. ♪
♪ And neither do I. ♪
♪ I own my pride. ♪
♪ You run and hide ♪
♪ And I'm gonna be the last thing you see ♪
♪ Before you go, bye-bye ♪
♪ There you go, bye-bye ♪
♪ Climb every tree across land and sea ♪
♪ Until you go, bye-bye ♪
♪ Will you go? Bye-bye ♪
♪ Bye-bye for vengeance is mine ♪
♪ And I'm the last of my line ♪
♪ I must be strong ♪
♪ Bye-bye ♪
♪ I'll make you go ♪
We have to move
They'll be tracking us
Taka!
What if you're wrong?
What if they're okay?
They live in you now.
Follow me, brother.
We have to move.
Together.
Run, Mufasa!
Run!
Hunters!
What's the plan?
Uh, run very fast!
This way!
Back to the trees!
We're trapped!
We have to swim!
No!
We have to fight!
If we fight, we die!
But if we swim, we drown!
Okay!
I didn't want to do this, but...
I command you to swim!
You...
What?
You've lent your loyalty!
I command you to swim!
Taka!
This is not the time for jokes!
Which one of you killed my son?
I did.
This lion with me is nothing but a
stray.
Let him go.
Kyros...
The other is no stray.
He holds the blood of the pride.
The last blood of the king.
Blood for blood.
They're coming!
What do we do?
Find the advantage?
What advantage?
We're on a rock in the middle of the
water!
Doc, this is it!
We go for the king!
Mufasa!
I'm ready!
Just one last thing!
with what!
Shut up!
Taka!
This was a bad idea!
Mufasa!
We're alive!
I did it!
I saved us!
You were saying?
Okay!
No!
No more water!
Tell me you can track them downriver.
We can track them anywhere.
They can run, but they can't hide.
So just to be clear, we're not in this
story?
It feels a little bit like Heroes is
stealing my thunder here.
Yeah, you know, I don't feel seen.
No, there's a lot of stories with all of
us.
Tell one of those!
Can I make one small suggestion?
Less childhood drama, more meerkat?
Rafiki, I don't think Taka scaring me
Me too. It's so obvious, but maybe just so we're
on the same page, dummy, is it, Simba?
Is it me?
Am I Obasi?
That makes no sense.
But seriously, I have one question.
Am I Taka?
I did it again!
Not that I'm counting, but I saved your hide.
Again!
As much as it kills you to say it,
let's hear it a little
"Thank you".
What are you talking about?!!
You want me to thank you for pushing me
off a waterfall?
Yes, and you're welcome.
Look, it's not my fault crocodiles are
simply attracted to you.
Don't say that.
Ha ha ha
I did it again.
Mufasa, is it him?
Is it the outsiders?
No, she's right there.
She?
There's no place to run.
We have your scent.
My scent?
I've been stalking you two all night.
That's not possible.
Then why did I circle you three times in
this wood while you two were chasing
each other's tails?
Ah!
That's a mess.
Yeah, well, I, uh, meant to do that,
so...
Still think I'm afraid?
Why are you following us?
I was hoping to find my pride.
What happened to it?
The outsiders happened.
A few of us got away, but you're the
only other lions I've seen.
You two better keep moving.
Wait, please.
Um, my name is Taka, son of Obasi.
I know what it's like to lose
everything.
Come with us.
We can help you.
I don't need any help.
But you don't have anyone.
She does indeed have someone.
Thank you very much.
That's Zazu.
Don't eat him.
You heard her.
Do not eat me.
As a recent addition to the King's Royal
Guard, I must kindly ask you both to
move on.
Thank you for stopping by.
Your king hired a bird to protect you.
How high can you fly?
Look, I needed a scout.
Zazu was the last option.
Well, next to last.
Between Albert the iguana and I,
His Majesty decided on the underling
with wings,
and thus, I became the lead scout for
the princess.
It's my third day going swimmingly,
if I may say so myself.
Sarabi, you can say so as well.
How far do you think you'll get with a
bird?
How far do you two geniuses think you'll
get
stumbling around running into each
other?
All the way to Milele
Milele is nothing but a myth
It's not a myth
Circle of life and fairytale herds
you're chasing something that doesn't exist
I don't know that Milele exists but
right now it's the
only hope we have
we don't need hope
We need food.
Oh, good job, brother.
Real nice.
There's trouble in the trees.
My first tree of trouble, and I am going
to cast, not going.
I am staying right here.
Thank you.
Come on, Sarabi
Looks like there's dinner headed our
way.
Sarabi, if I may.
He makes a valid point, Your Highness.
But, on the other hand, he's a starving
lion who wants to eat me, so I am
slightly torn.
I think that went quite well, all things
considered.
And now, Kiara, this is where I come in.
Rafiki
We will have order in the Congress of
baboon. Tonight a cheetah came into our
..trees for..
-..the third night in a row
- Almost took one of our own
- It was figured for he summoned
-..the beast with his dreams
-Rafiki and his visions must be banished once and for all
Rafiki tried to warn you.
His dreams conjure our enemies.
He talks to the spirits, summons the devil.
What are you talking about?
He's done it before.
His brother was chased
from these very trees, never to be seen
again.
Rafiki was just a child.
A child, born with a leg that does not
work, yet somehow he survived?
It was Rafiki who found water in the dry
season, who healed you, Inaki, when you
were sick.
He speaks to the insects, converses with
the moon.
Zala, you know what will happen if you
send him down from the trees.
He is Amalaniwa, a curse to us all.
That's not true.
He doesn't belong here.
All in favor of banishment, cover one
eye.
And so, it is time.
No, wait.
Where will you go?
Where I should have gone long ago, to
find all that was lost.
My family.
You can't survive on your own.
Nobody can.
And yet, here we are.
Oh, Rafiki.
The eye never forgets what the heart has
seen.
Hmm.
Jamaa.
Hmph.
You can try to run, but I'm afraid you
won't get very far.
And why would I run from you?
Because we're lions.
As in, lion!
A flea can trouble a lion more than a
lion can trouble a flea.
I don't think you understand what's
about to happen.
There's no place for you to go.
I am going forward.
I seriously doubt that.
It is easy to doubt everything when you
know nothing.
Can we get on with this, please?
If you take my life, you will never find
Milele.
Wait.
Did you say Milele?
That is where I am going, toward the
light.
I have been there many times.
In my dreams, my brother waits for me there.
I have seen the tree, can picture it..
-..The two of us together again
-And why would anyone trust a baboon's dream
Sometimes the dream is all you have.
The only truth that lives in you
Like the memory of a great king
how did you know..
okay help us get to Milele.
And we will..
-..let you live do we have a deal
-no
-what?!
- why?!
-Rafiki will let you live
- Had enough of this!
-Taka, do not eat.
Wonderful, another misfit stray
we're not supposed to eat.
So you expect us to follow this baboon
to a place nobody has ever seen.
I'll be better off alone.
Hey, Tombazan, a single stick may smoke,
but it will never burn.
Okay, now that there's five of us,
why don't we all go around
and say a fun fact about ourselves?
I'll go first.
I once had a crush on a flamingo.
I've never said that out loud.
And they're walking away.
Yep, places to go, kingdoms to see.
We're busy, let's hustle.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now you're the star of this thing?
Someone's a little tired of being second
banana, huh?
All of a sudden there's a lot of Rafiki
in the story.
You even gave yourself a long-lost
brother.
What's next, a funny catchphrase?
You gonna be farting next?
That's my thing.
You cannot tell the story of Mufasa
without the story of Rafiki.
Oh, now he's even talking about himself
in the third person.
Pretty soon he'll have his own
fragrance.
And I'm the only one with a fragrance
around here.
It's called Pumba by Pumba, and from
what I hear, it's pretty gross.
Mom?
Dad?
If you can hear me, come home.
Please, come home.
Mother.
Milele.
Mother!
Rafiki
Hi, Suga.
What are you doing?
I am fishing.
You're sitting on a
rock with your eyes closed.
My eyes are open.
It is my lids that are closed.
Why am I talking to a baboon?
I am not a baboon, I am a mandrill.
No offense, but a monkey is a monkey.
And a stray is a stray.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means we are very much the same.
Siafana.
We are nothing alike.
Take a good look.
I am a lion.
A lion who fears water, fears his own
reflection.
Who can't sleep because of what he sees
when he closes his eyes.
Huh?
You are afraid of your dreams, Mufasa.
Afraid of what you see in them.
I see my parents.
I feel them everywhere.
Of course you do, Mufasa.
You will feel them forever.
My mother.
I hear her voice.
She tells me that we are on a journey to
Milele, but I feel so lost without her.
Your journey is not a dream, Mufasa.
Your mother is guiding you.
And where you are going, a family
awaits.
What are you doing?
We're starving.
It was not its time.
Instead, the fish has agreed to let us
share the water.
I have a report!
It's morning.
End of report.
The Earth Divided is now a choice,
around or down.
The decision is yours.
Look out there, beyond the light, across
the deepest canyon.
Across the deepest canyon?
We should go down.
Why?
Because of some fairy tale?
The rocks will hide our tracks.
It's safer to go around.
I picked up their scent.
The only thing you picked up is a
hallucinating baboon.
I'm a mandrill.
This is a waste of time.
close your eyes.
What?
Tell me what you see, what you feel.
There's nothing on the wind.
No, they're moving through the
bushwallow.
They who?
The females, out front.
Come on.
Clear thoughts.
Concentrate.
I am concentrating.
He's right, we have to go down.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, you're born on
fire.
Now the many sticks will make fire as
one.
Come on, we have places to go.
And kingdoms to save.
What's up, baby?
♪ You want to go fast, go alone. ♪
♪ There's the road. ♪
♪ Off you go. ♪
♪ But, if you wanna go far, we go together ♪
♪ So good, so far, we go together ♪
♪ Your father left you in my care ♪
♪ And now we're running who knows where ♪
♪ Sometimes you need a bird's-eye view ♪
♪ And I've got you to see me through  ♪
♪  by land, by air ♪
♪ If you wanna go fast, go alone ♪
♪ Day and night  ♪
♪  There's the road ♪
♪ I just might ♪
♪ Off you go ♪
♪ Yeah, alright ♪
♪ If you wanna go far ♪
♪ We go together ♪
♪ So good, so far, we go together ♪
♪ I will find my family again, I will walk  ♪
♪  with you until then, I will walk with ♪
♪ you till ♪
♪ the end, it's much easier with a friend. ♪
♪ It's much easier with a friend ♪
♪ I will find my family again ♪
♪ I will walk with you until then ♪
♪ I will walk with you  'til the end ♪
♪ It's much easier with a friend ♪
♪ Like clouds and rain ♪
♪ Like a meal in a field of grain ♪
♪ One fleck's of gold in your mane, Sarabi  ♪
♪  You and me, we go together, ♪
♪ Like clouds and rain, Like a meal in a  ♪
♪  field of grain. ♪
♪ One fleck's of gold in your mane, Sarabi  ♪
♪  You and me, we go together, ♪
♪ My brother waits for me to find him  (yoo-hoo) ♪
♪ My brother knows I'm right behind him ♪
♪ My brother tends to lose his way ♪
♪ And go astray, say, if you see..(my brother, please remind him) ♪
♪ it's much easier with a friend ♪
♪ Here we go (here we go) ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna go far  ♪
♪  we go together, so good, so far  ♪
♪  we go together. ♪
As we headed across the great valley,
the hunters tracked our every move.
Kiros, they are not alone.
They've connected a lioness.
And a monkey.
Mufasa!
Mufasa, you have to help me.
Help you how?
It's Sarabi, Mufasa.
She is the light my mother spoke of.
What?
She's special.
The most amazing female I've ever met in
my life.
I don't know what to say to her.
You've spent your life with females.
Please, tell me what to say.
Just talk to her.
Be yourself.
Oh, Mufasa, you don't understand.
Myself isn't good enough.
You just know things.
Fine, fine.
Keep it simple.
Ask her a question.
Right, a question.
This is good.
Yeah, try to be...
confident.
Disinterested.
But I'm very interested.
Tell her about the flowers.
What flowers?
The valley she comes from.
There's flowers everywhere.
They're called duck flowers.
Long stems.
It's absolutely beautiful.
How do you know that?
When she passes, I can smell them on her
fur.
Okay.
Flowers.
Disinterested.
And here's the most important thing,
okay?
Listen when she speaks.
Male has trouble with that one.
Sorry.
What did you say?
Really.
I heard you, brother.
I'm gonna make you proud.
It's very hot, isn't it?
Yep.
Oh
I
Love listening.
Okay.
I'm listening right now to what what you
just said.
- You're the one that's talking
-I am
-You smell like a duck
-what
-flower. A duckflower
-how do you know about those flowers?
Well, I inhaled you with my nose I can
smell them
Amazing.
Our valley was full of those flowers,
thousands of them, as far as the eye
could see.
It was...
it was the most beautiful place, Taka.
Did he just say she smells like a duck?
And you called me a baboon.
We shouldn't be here
-the migration patterns are broken.
I-I-don't.. understand
This is not a drill
Just to be clear
I never signed up for this.
It's okay.
It's safe.
They're on the other side
No!
They can just jump across.
We're trapped.
What do we do?
-The elephants will fight with us
-and why would they do that
-because I'm going to ask them
Got a better idea?
Yes,
Mr. Ask-Questions-First, get ready to run.
Where is she going?
Hello?
Listen to me, please.
We need your help.
Can you talk to me?
We need your help, please.
They're coming!
Sarabi!
Sarabi, wait!
Wait, where is she going?
She's going for the hive!
Like I said, get ready to run!
Run!
Get to the trees!
Why am I running?
Your Highness!
Hold on!
Zazu!
Sarabi!
Back your throat!
Do not retreat!
I got you.
Sarabi, I got you.
That's right.
Run along, little kitty-cats.
Thank you, my friend.
Over here.
(speaking foreign language)
Alive, she's alive.
Why are you all looking at me?
You were thrown from the tree.
He saved your life.
Who?
Taka.
Taka saved you.
Isn't that right, brother?
You saved me?
Well, I...
I had to do something.
Thank you.
We're lucky.
Those bees almost killed us all.
Those bees saved our lives.
huh... Mufasa...
Uh, really?
Because, uh, it felt like an elephant
stampede.
We're alive, aren't we?
The elephants would have fought with us.
We're lions.
Nobody will fight with us.
Not out here.
Where is he going?
Beyond the horizon itself.
Mufasa..
Thank you.
Rafiki, who...
who are the Outsiders?
Well, the Outsiders come from many
tribes, but when they are born, they are
hated because
they are different from their tribe.
Like you and your tribe?
Yes, just like me.
But Rafiki, why do they want to hurt
everybody?
Sometimes when the people most like you
don't love you,
it is the hurt that can cause the
greatest pain.
And this pain can lead you to hate
everything.
I'm glad that didn't happen to you,
Rafiki.
Yes, my child, I'm glad too.
Um, hi, we're here too.
Yeah, why are you leaving us outside
this story
And I'm pretty sure we are the ultimate
outsiders!
Yeah, we've always been misunderstood.
I contain multitudes.
There are many ways to Milele.
But this, were ours.
Go.
Go, Mufasa.
Find your forever.
I got you, Sarabi.
I got you.
Hey, Rafiki.
What are you doing?
I am confirming my vision, Mufasa.
Can I ask you something, Rafiki?
Hmm?
How many of your visions have come true?
So far, none.
None?
But it's not what I see.
It's what I feel.
But how do you...
how do you know when you should follow a
feeling?
Milele exists.
I feel it in here.
The question is, what do you feel,
Mufasa?
In there.
The whether shifted. There's not enough for a smell.
Hey, if the outsiders find our tracks,
they'll follow them to Milele.
Zazu, only you can help us.
Um, are you quite sure about that?
No, I was actually thinking that Rafiki
looks pretty handy, and with the stick...
Zazu, you can use your wings to cover
our tracks as we head up the mountain
without leaving a trace.
Hey, you can do this.
Oh, hmm, yeah.
Yes, sir, you're right.
I've got this.
Okay, it's just me, get to the frozen
mountain, and a one-horned bill
charged with saving the future.
Whoa!
Mummy!
Ah!
Oh, I'm out of life, that's cold!
What's happening?
We can't keep stopping somehow they have
come out their tracks in the snow
It's not possible
It could be anywhere on this mountain
Then find them! Now.
Zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu, zazu.
I have a report the outsiders are
completely lost
-well played, Mufasa
-Great jobs, zazu
-As per usual
-I knew you could do it
-We did it
-No, you did it
-Great thinking Mufasa
-Now we're all rubbing off on each other probably normal thing
to do who wants to rub against us? no one.
I'm leaving now. Scout ahead
I got you, Rafiki..
I got you.
Yeah, I got you.
Mufasa, I got you.
Hidden in the shadows, downwind, right
afoot.
Interesting hunting style, Mufasa.
We have to eat something before we take
on that descent.
Unfortunately, there's nothing to hunt
up here.
See under that rock?
There's a civet about to leave his den.
Of course you can smell a civet hidden
in the snow.
You, the lion who can do anything.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means, I see you, Mufasa.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Now, that part I believe, because, smart
as you are,
you have a way of seeing everything but
yourself.
What is this?
What is this, Sarabi?
There's a civet in the snow, right where
you said it would be.
And you smelled the outsiders on the
wind,
which means you're the one who smelled
the flowers on my fur.
It was a lucky guess.
You can smell the exact flower from my
belly.
No!
That's not possible.
You saved me, held me, covered me in the
stampede, comforted me.
No, it was Taka.
I got you.
I got you, Sarabi
I'm here to protect him.
That was you.
I was lost in the water and he found me.
My brother saved me.
I sensed it from the beginning.
His blood is the blood of the king.
Mufasa!
That is his destiny.
No, his destiny was to save you.
Now tell me it's you.
♪ Ever since you appeared, I've been ♪
♪ running through something deep inside. ♪
♪ And it's worse than I feared, cause I ♪
♪ look in your eyes and I can't hide. ♪
♪ I push you away, ♪
♪ -don't push me away.. ♪
♪ -but the feelings come back just twice as strong. ♪
♪ -I don't know what to say.. ♪
♪ -You know just what to say ♪
♪ -but I know that I'm right where I belong. ♪
♪ -The way you know just where to be ♪
♪ -I don't know ♪
♪ The way you move, the way you see, ♪
♪ the way you feel when you're on me, ♪
♪ beside me, don't hide from me anymore. ♪
♪ Tell me it's you, I know it's you. ♪
♪ What do I say, where do I go, how do I ♪
♪ know you feel the same? ♪
♪ Tell me it's you, I know it's you. ♪
♪ Crying in love, letting it go, letting ♪
♪ you know it's in me ♪
♪ Every prayer that I wrote ♪
♪ I remind myself not to overstate ♪
♪ Every time I find hope ♪
♪ Something happens to take that hope away ♪
♪ Don't you see what I've seen? ♪
♪ I see you ♪
♪ As you lead with a strength that shines ♪
♪ right through ♪
♪ You move like a queen, a true queen ♪
♪ Don't let anything take me away from you ♪
♪ -Tell me it's you, I know it's you  ♪
♪ -Say it again, say it again, ♪
♪ -Tell me I'll always be with you  ♪
♪ -Tell me it's you, I know it's you ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again, tell me ♪
♪ you're always with me ♪
♪ The way you know just where to be ♪
♪ Now I know ♪
♪ The way you move, the way you see ♪
♪ I see you ♪
♪ The love I feel when you're with me ♪
♪ Beside me, beside me ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again, say it again ♪
♪ Tell me the world won't interfere ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again, tell me the ♪
♪ words I want to hear ♪
♪ Say it again, say it again, open your ♪
♪ eyes and here we go ♪
♪ I know it's you ♪
♪ You know I love her, my brother  ♪
♪ There's nothing we keep from each other ♪
♪ I saved your life. ♪
♪ This is how you repay me. ♪
♪ What do I do? ♪
♪ What does he mean? ♪
♪ How do I ever wanna see what I've seen? ♪
♪ He was my kin. ♪
♪ She was my queen. ♪
♪ Now it's broken forever and... ♪
♪ Tell her it's you ♪
♪ She knows it's you. ♪
♪ What did you say to her? ♪
♪ What did you do? ♪
♪ I'm next in line. ♪
♪ She should be mine. ♪
♪ Ha! ♪
♪ Are the ancestors laughing at me? ♪
♪ What would they say? ♪
♪ Father is gone, not before giving me ♪
♪ strength to go on. ♪
♪ He never trusted you, did he know ♪
♪ you'd betray me so? ♪
♪ For you are drowning, I've been drowned. ♪
♪ I can't do life with you, lived in my ♪
♪ death. ♪
♪ Now I'm the one drowning, tumbling down, ♪
♪ trying to escape what I cannot forget. ♪
♪ I have a brother, no longer, it's over ♪
♪ and done. ♪
♪ Now all I have is this shame and this ♪
♪ rage that I can't... ♪
♪ Out--! ♪
This is a tool of a great king.
There wasn't much to eat on this
mountain, until now.
Tell me, how did you cut me a traction
of snow?
A bird helped us.
Lion, get in help for me, pet.
Just as I will help you.
You will help us?
You think we need help from a wounded
coward?
I may hold the blood of a king, but it
was Mufasa who killed your son.
It was Mufasa who trapped you up here,
outspotted you at every turn.
Now I will lead you to him, and to
Milele.
Milele?
Milele is nothing but a dream, a vision
sold to cops.
Ah.
Well, tell that to the monkey.
He leads them to it.
Look at you.
A pack of starving wolves, clinging to
the side of a mountain.
No tracks to follow.
Only one chance at revenge.
Me?
Revenge.
What about your father?
Because of Mufasa.
I have no father.
He did this?
Yes.
You lost a father, and I, a son.
Taka, will you join us?
Together, we can both have our revenge.
It will be my pleasure, King.
Taka?
Taka, where've you been?
Hunting.
I couldn't find anything but I was never as good as you
..or my mother. there's something I need to tell you.
There's something I need to
tell you I need to thank you. You kept
your word to Eshe and Obasi
You saved me, Mufasa, and I will never
forget what you've done, my brother.
Oh, guys, I have found a way down, just
beyond those near peaks.
Is it something I said?
Hey Rafiki.
Yes, we are nearing destiny Mufasa, and
so the earth must shake.
Okay, now I am a hundred million percent
sure who Taka is.
Just be honest, is it me?
In case you missed it, we're not
featured in this.
I think the sit-it has more screen
time.
Hey, maybe they'll put us in the play.
No, no, please don't mention the play
again.
I-I-I went to see it on nothing but a
giant sock puppet.
You went to see it?
You didn't bring me?
Rafiki, Mufasa and Sarabi are in love?
Ew, love?
That sounds gross and not something like
I constantly think about and really want.
What is Taka gonna do to them?
Little one, Taka's heart was broken and
now his trap was set.
Mufasa, do you see?
I don't believe it.
The other side of the light.
(sighs)
Milele..
I can't believe it we found it
We found Milele
Yes
You found it brother
You always do
Rafiki
This is the tree
From your vision
I've seen this tree many times, and in
each vision there was always a brother, standing
But there's no one here, Rafiki.
You came here to find your twin.
He was taken from me long ago.
What I saw in my dreams was a brother,
standing right here.
A friend?
Family.
What I saw was you.
The unseeable.
I saw Mufasa.
Me?
Yes, you.
My brother.
Mufasa
How do you know who I am?
We know the outsiders are hunting you,
and we fear you'll bring danger.
No, no, we covered our tracks.
I promise you, Milele is a safe place,
and I would never do anything to
jeopardize that.
Do not run!
You have nothing to fear.
We are not here to move.
We have come...
for Mufasa!
How did they get here?
Do not let him divide us!
Esmeralda knows Mufasa.
The Circle...
The Circle is broken.
No!
Mufasa, what are you doing?
I'm going to fight, and I'm going to
show them that they can fight too.
Rafiki, when you hear my signal, help me
call them together.
Yes, my brother.
There are other lions here.
Find them.
With pleasure, Your Majesty.
Mufasa, you're not alone.
It's my turn to go ask questions first.
This is where the hunt ends, Mufasa.
Thanks to your brother, he left a trail
of scars for us to follow.
He made a deal to save himself, and gave
us this kingdom.
Tell me he's lying.
He asked us to kill the Stray.
Taka, please!
I am the son of a king, but Sarabi chose
you, just like mother, just like my own father.
I saved you, and you betrayed me.
What have you done?
I'm your brother!
Fight with me!
You stole my destiny.
Now this is yours.
He's one of us now.
My son's name...
Shaju.
Shaju!
All of this should have been his.
And now, I will rule it without mercy.
Oh
This one is mine.
Please, we can't waste this battle
alone.
There's nothing we can do.
They chased us from our pride lands
before.
They're too strong.
Fight with us.
Fight for your young.
For your future!
What future?
They've taken all we have!
And they will always take more.
I am Mufasa, a stray with no pride, and
yet I stand before you, head unbound.
I know you're afraid, but trust me,
nothing will change if we remain
isolated to our own
tribes without concern for the fate of
others.
But why should we stand with you?
This is your fight.
Today they are here for us lions, but I
assure you, as you let them walk among
you in search
of us now.
They are plotting to come for you
tomorrow.
One lion's hope cannot change the
fate of Milele.
There is no lion as large as an
elephant, as strong as an oxen, fast
as a cheetah, or tall as a giraffe, who
can soar and scout as wide and far as
the cranes
and hawks in the sky.
So, can't you see?
Every being has a place in the circle of
life.
My breath is your breath.
Your fight is my fight.
I will not bend to evil, and neither
should you
Mufasa is right, Milele is home.
We must stand with Mufasa!
Together we shall stand strong!
For Milele!
It's the Lion!
From this moment on, everything the
Light touches belongs to me.
You'll have to take it.
Bye-bye.
You messed with the wrong hornbill!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
The launch is soon.
Stand down!
I am highly trained and occasionally
effective!
This is so embarrassing!
I do have wings, you know!
Taka.
Taka, please, please!
You did challenge me.
You took my son, my future.
Taka.. Taka, your moment of courage
will come.
Blood!
Please, don't kill him.
I didn't kill him.
You did.
They're coming!
The last lions.
Time for their extinction.
And we'll start with the youngest.
The earth will shake.
Attack!
Mufasa..
close your eyes, and tell me what you
hear.
what you feel.
The king of Milele!
The king!
Mufasa!
Rise, your majesty.
My king.
No, no, I'm not...
King, raise your heads.
I'm just...
No, no more kings.
We are all one.
Please, please, raise your heads.
But Mufasa, you have brought them
together.
You held them see in themselves what
they considered unseeable.
Nothing is more kingly.
No, Rafiki.
I'm not king.
I'm not royal blood.
Don't you see, my brother?
It is not what you were.
It is what you have become.
The King of Milele.
My brother, something beautiful awaits
you.
But it can't be, it can't be.
Mufasa!
But how can it be?
I had a son named Mufasa, taken from me
by a great flood.
Father?
I never stopped hoping, believing, my
son.
Ah.
I've dreamt of this moment.
And now it's come true.
Oh, Mufasa.
But Father?
Where's Father?
He lives in you now...he
lives...in
you...I
always dreamed we'd be together
again...and
I knew it would be...
in Milelle.
My son.
Mufasa.
Mufasa, please forgive me.
You must banish him, sire.
As long as I'm king, my brother will
have a place here.
Brother, I'm so sorry.
But I won't ever say your name again.
I can't.
I won't.
Then call me Scar, so I will never
forget what I have done.
Scar.
Your Majesty.
Welcome home..
So, Mufasa, I see your family has been
awaiting you in Milele after all.
Yes, Rafiki.
Yes, they were.
It is your time, Mufasa.
Rafiki, I wish I could see him.
I wish I could meet my grandfather.
As Mufasa once told your father, look
into the heavens, Kiara.
The great king of the past will always be there
waiting for you..
I don't want him to go, Rafiki, I
don't want it to end.
Don't you see Kiara?
Mufasa lives in you.
He lives in you.
Dad!
Rafiki, it was unbelievable.
It was perfect.
You could not improve on it.
That said, I do have notes.
Some suggestions.
Take them or leave them, but take them.
Dad!
Kiara!
Kiara.
Dad, where's Mom?
Well, love, there's something you need
to know.
What?
Did something happen to Mom?
Baby, I'm right here, and I'm fine.
Where were you?
Kiara, this is your new brother.
Brother?
I have a brother?
Hi there.
I'm Kiara.
I will take care of you.
Forever.
Little one, let me tell you a story.
A story of a great king.