Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
You're here, Arjun? Freshen up.
The food is ready.
Who are you?
I am hungry, mother.
I haven't eaten in many days.
Poor guy! Please eat.
What is your name, son?
Krishna.
Go on, have it.
Come and have your food.
I've finished all the
work and come, mom.
Sit down first.
Here.
Hey...
Who is this brother, mom?
You have already called him brother.
Consider him as one.
Brother.
Mom, take this.
Have you made this for me?
- Hmm.
You are such a good kid!
What about me, mom?
You mean the world to me.
Sir...
Yes?
- You know the festival is near.
Yes.
- I need a loan.
Yes, I am aware.
Do you want a loan?
When else will you ask it,
if not on a festival?
Here! Where are you going?
Put your thumbprint here.
How else will I take
it back from you?
Press hard.
Harder. Hey!
Oh, my God.
Oh, you broke the table! Huh!
Ah, Goddess Lakshmi!
Uncle, bring Satto's son quickly.
Brother, focus on the job.
Sir!
- Yes?
We have fixed the table. Okay.
- Okay, keep it here. Come on, fast!
Hey, careful!
Sir...
What?
- Please pay the wages.
I will pass it for interest
on your mom's loan. Get going.
He is asking me for money!
Arjun...
Brother, this is Rukmini.
She's a great girl.
Who is he?
- Krishna. My elder brother.
Hey, Arjun! Your mom suddenly...
Run for home quickly!
What happened to mom?
Mom…
Mom! Open your eyes, mom!
Mom...
Mom! Get up, mom!
Mom!
Your mom had mortgaged
this hut and taken a loan, dear.
Now I will have to sell it
to recover my dues.
No one can stop a dying person
or a lender who is out
to recover his dues.
We will repay all your dues,
but please don't take
our house away from us, sir.
And how will you repay me, my dear?
Stop this drama. Lift the bier.
Hey!
I will kill anybody who touches her.
Who was she to you?
She is my mother,
and he is my younger brother.
Greetings.
What is the problem?
What can I tell you?
Times have changed.
The person who lent them money
and helped their mother…
Now he wants to kill him!
Tell me, what should I do now?
Spare the children.
I will pay their dues.
Didn't you hear?
This house was yours
and will always be yours.
Mom!
What is your name?
- Krishna.
Greetings, sir. - Take care.
- Sure, sir.
Enough.
Hey, come, kids!
Yeah.
Sit here.
Hey, what are you doing? Get up!
Don't sit on the floor.
Come here. Sit here.
Sit with us.
Listen...
- Yes?
Serve them food.
- Sure.
Do you eat 'dosa'?
- Hmm.
Huh?
Krishna...
Krishna, Rukmini is coming.
Bare your heart to her today.
Or just say the dialogue
that heroes say in the movies.
Otherwise, I will lose my face.
Hey, Arjun!
What are you guys doing here?
My brother wants
to tell you something.
Would you like to hear it?
Why are you quiet?
Go on. Tell me.
Uh... actually I...
A lot...
Huh?
Master… Master!
Hey! Come on, man!
Come on! Hey!
Hey, listen.
Where is Gopalrao's house?
It's the last house
on the right-hand side.
Hmm.
Uh, greetings, sir.
Is Bhaskar home?
Bhaskar!
Yeah, Dad!
How presumptuous you are!
The boys in my village are scared
to even look at my sister.
And you dared to give her a rose.
Now, I will give you a rose,
and you'll follow me.
Or else…
Why would a father die for his son?
Take him along.
Come, come on!
Hey! Who the heck are you guys?
Dump him in!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Where are you taking
my brother-in-law?
Hey, enough of your hooliganism!
Father, they are
taking your son away.
You didn't say anything to them
and playing the clarinet here!
Can't you see anything?
Let's lodge a complaint
with the police.
Son-in-law.
He will come home himself.
The snacks are ready. Please, come.
Are your snacks more important
than the son of this house?
Forget him now.
I've made snacks for you.
Oh, God. Keep quiet.
Are you guys crazy, or what?
Serve them. No, wait!
Who made these? You or my wife?
I made it. Shall I now?
- Thank God!
How can I eat it when it's so hot?
Your son has been kidnapped,
and you are busy eating fritters.
Who will save him?
- The one who saves everyone.
We are Bhaskar's parents.
But he is the master for all of us.
He's our God. Our master.
Will that old man save him?
Will he fight them?
Did you see the size of the goons?
Just like God protects his devotees,
our protector
protects the villagers.
Who is he?
Arjun, I forgot the matchbox.
Go on. Where did they take him?
They went this way.
Could you give me the matchbox?
- I don't have it, sir.
Okay, we'll handle them first.
And then I'll have a puff.
- Okay.
You can go, Arjun.
That's more like it.
Take him to task.
'This is Akashvani. This is a
warning for an incoming storm.'
Hey, Krishna!
Er… this is my personal issue.
Don't interfere.
Sir, what do you think?
Arjun would have reached?
Where exactly?
To inform your families
about your death.
Huh? This is not your area!
You can't enter just anywhere!
If my master orders me,
I'll cross the country and border.
I'll go to the world down under
and fight Yamraj, too.
Hey…
Aunty!
- What is it?
Go to the field with 4-5 sardines
and half a kilo of turmeric.
Why?
- To treat your son.
How did he get hurt?
One... two... three!
Like this.
Krishna…
Stop.
“Goodness gracious”
“My goodness gracious”
Hey, ma'am!
What is it?
Where is your husband?
He must be somewhere. He's still the
same even after becoming a father.
He won't be able
to become a father again.
Why? What for?
Hey!
Sister... what are you up to?
I am making butter for my husband.
Butter is necessary
to mend a broken back.
Eh?
Poor thing!
Come on, beat him up, Krishna!
Hey, uncle! Why are you sitting
with a long face?
What do I do? No business, kid.
Be prepared. The patients
must be on the way.
Hmm?
Yeah!
Hey!
I'm sparing you
because Master asked me to.
If you trouble my people again,
then I'll skin you alive
like a sugarcane.
Don't mess with me!
Hey, Krishna, come forward.
Master, you carry on.
- Come on, don't be shy.
Krishna is Master's favourite.
Master dotes on Krishna.
Dad prioritises that servant
over his own sons.
Krishna...
- Yes...
They are evil.
Take care of Bhaskar
until the festival is over.
Okay, master!
- Fine!
Arjun!
- I'll take care of him.
Sir, the rooster is ready
for the fight.
Sir?
The edge is sharp.
Fix it on our rooster.
Okay, sir.
'If you trouble my people again,'
'then I'll skin you alive
like a sugarcane.'
'Don't mess with me!'
How did Bhaskar meet my daughter?
I heard they met
on the bus for the first time.
After that, they continued meeting.
Both of them are in the same class,
Mr Veerabhadra.
Tell me something.
Why did you give her a flower?
It's an old custom, brother.
If you give flowers at a festival,
the relationship lasts forever.
You, Romeo. If not for master, you
wouldn't be alive to fall in love.
I know. But my heart has
stopped listening to my mind.
It does as it wants.
And my body moves as per its wishes.
If I don't meet her,
I can't stay happy.
And as soon as I meet her,
my heart starts racing.
I have no control when
my heart takes over.
For her, let alone the village,
I am ready to cross the seven seas.
Hey...
What did you do now?
He's telling me his love story.
He is a true lover.
- Hey!
Don't create any new problems now.
Give a break to your love story
for a while. Understood?
Your father-in-law is looking
for a chance to kill you.
What does Krishna know
about how powerful love can be?
He doesn't have a heart,
but a stone.
You have only seen his action,
not his love.
He is a real lover.
Lover? No way.
He can only woo a girl
by threatening her, not by love.
There are always
two sides to a coin.
He has three to four sides. Come on.
I'll tell you
his childhood love story.
The girl whom Krishna
used to love in childhood,
was sent to the city for studies
by her strict father.
Rukmini, you will not study with
these dull-heads in the village,
but you'll study
with the educated kids in the city.
Grandma will always be with you.
Study with interest.
And don't become friends with
any poor, uneducated child. Okay?
That girl came back
to the village after 20 years.
And Krishna got the news.
But Krishna could never
find her in the house.
Finally, they met on my wedding day.
Greetings.
- Greetings. Greetings.
Master! Please come. How are you?
Master has arrived.
Madam, please come. Be seated.
Greetings! Please sit.
- Greetings.
Master, there is Arjun.
Hey!
How did the lights go off?
This is Rukmini…
This isn't needed.
- Hey! Why not?
Hey, Rukmini!
When did you come back from town?
Please sit.
- How is everyone?
Rukmini, you have no idea.
Our village has changed a lot.
Is that so?
- Yes.
You might not even know we have
a permanent school building now.
And that too a big one.
New bridges have also
been built over all the canals.
You don't know about that too?
- Mmm-mmm!
Be blessed!
Take his blessings, too.
Mangla, come here.
Bless us, Krishna.
- God bless you.
Don't overdo it.
Only one of you should
call me brother.
This is such a torture!
Such an idiot!
Hey, stop it. Stop it!
I said stop it!
Don't dance! Stop it!
Are you making this noise
to make me deaf?
It's been a long time since we've
been happy, so we're dancing.
Is that so?
So celebrate within your limits!
You were already an orphan,
and you have chosen
an orphan bride too.
A poor, cheap guy like you
is celebrating as if you are
from a reputed family.
You sing on the mic,
you useless fellow!
There were two orphans here earlier.
Now you're three.
What is so big a change?
This is not a home, man!
This is an orphanage. Hey...
Hey!
If high-profile people are like you,
it's good that we are orphans.
Huh!
You're useless! You have no value!
The villagers hate you so much that
no one will come to your funeral.
You will rot like an orphan.
Don't point fingers
at my family again.
Don't mess with me!
What have you done, Krishna?
After all,
he is your future father-in-law.
So? But why did he call us orphans?
You are like my son,
and I'm like your father.
And she's the light of our house.
Don't be sad now.
Otherwise, I will also cry.
There will be only happiness
in the house today.
When will you stop feeling shy?
- Once you leave.
Give it quickly.
We'll play alone now.
All of you leave now.
Go back to your home.
Don't be too scared.
- Come on, let's go.
Take care. I'll meet you tomorrow.
What about you?
Are you the mother-in-law? Go now.
I'm leaving.
I won't open the door
till tomorrow afternoon.
Krishna.
- Hmm?
Do you really love the
accountant's daughter, Rukmini?
Yes. What is it now?
Nothing much. The love you have for
her is clearly visible in your eyes.
But she didn't even look
at you in the wedding.
Moreover, you threatened her father.
I don't know how you will
proceed with this relationship.
Hey... Go and sleep now.
Keep the radio here.
- Okay, Krishna.
The truth is always bitter.
- Idiot...
I better run before he hears me.
'But she didn't even look
at you at the wedding.'
"Here he comes"
"Your king"
"He'll shoo your sleep away.
He'll keep you awake all night"
Who the heck is this?
I will be right back.
Don't go to sleep.
Yes, coming...
What is it, Krishna?
- Hey...
Rukmini didn't recognise me, man.
Has she forgotten about me?
How would I know, Krishna?
Let's go and ask her tomorrow.
"Your king is back"
"He'll shoo your sleep away.
He'll keep you awake all night"
Krishna, what is it now?
Hey, ever since I saw Rukmini,
I have lost control of my heart.
I want to get married to her
as soon as possible.
I'm also not able to control myself.
I'm also in a great hurry
just like you.
My heart is fluttering
like a butterfly.
My heart too.
What can I tell you now, Krishna?
Krishna, let us
discuss this tomorrow.
Hmm.
"I am back"
Krishna...
Arjun, ever since I saw Rukmini,
I just don't know what to do.
I know what to do,
but you're not letting me.
You don't have to do anything…
- Krishna.
I'm a little busy.
Stop disturbing me now.
We will sort this out
in the morning, okay?
You got it, right?
"Your king is back"
"He'll shoo your sleep away.
He'll keep you awake all night"
The whole program ended
before it even started.
Krishna!
Tell me something, sir.
Why do you sprinkle salt
and basil water on the money?
That's a good question.
The borrower won't be able
to return the money
when you sprinkle salt water.
And when we sprinkle basil water,
this sinful money gets purified.
This is called balancing it.
Got it?
Let's go, driver. You can also go.
Let's go, Krishna.
Wait and watch, Krishna. She'll
hug you as soon as she sees you.
Arjun, give me your glasses.
- Here you go.
The newly married groom
is here early in the morning!
It must be something important.
Do I need a reason to come
and meet my friend?
Look who has come with me?
Krishna, my elder brother.
Krishna?
Didn't I tell you?
She's so happy to see you.
Oh… Krishna?
- Hmm.
How dare you grab my dad's collar!
How dare you touch him!
What kind of shameless guy are you?
You insulted my father first.
And now you've come to his house.
- I...
Don't show your face to me.
Get out of here!
Should we go, brother?
A man who single-handedly
fights 100 men,
was trembling in front of that girl.
Love has ruined him.
Hey, don't be shy.
We've also been
through these challenges.
Look at him.
We got Arjun married too.
Now, only Das and you are left.
I am looking
for a nice match for Das too.
He is about to return from Dubai.
Now, let's come to you.
Tell me who the girl is.
I will go talk to them.
Master, reference works everywhere,
but not in love.
When she believes in me
and insists me to meet you,
then I'll take you
to talk to her family.
If she doesn't want to look at you,
how will she fall in love with you?
She's not a fish
that you can catch easily.
Shut up, you idiot!
Will she get a diamond
like my brother?
And she won't fall for someone
who can't buy her a real diamond.
Arjun, fighting silly goons
and getting a city-bred deer
are different things.
She's from the city.
He won't be able to do it.
Hey…
- Hmm.
If I don't take her on my bicycle
by tomorrow evening,
I won't call myself Krishna anymore.
Some goons are dragging your father
and hitting him near the river.
Huh? What!
Let's go!
Hey, boy!
Huh? What is it, girl?
I need to go
to the river right away.
Can you please take me?
You told me not to show you my face.
Go and find someone else.
Darn it! I should have gone walking.
Hey, girl!
By the time you wander to the river,
the accountant's
bones will be broken.
If someone drops you there
on a bicycle, you'll reach on time.
Which way are you going?
I have to go far away, but I'll
take a shortcut near the river.
Why don't you take me along then?
Huh?
My bicycle has no carrier.
Will you sit in the front?
Hmm...
Hmm.
Huh?
Did she really not find anyone else?
Hey, Babulal! You were saying
something about diamonds, right?
Not everyone is as lucky
as you, brother.
You sit here waiting
for your fate to turn.
I believe in hard work.
Bring our sister-in-law
home sometime.
Whom is he calling sister-in-law?
Think about your dad. Let's go.
How did you manage to woo her?
Hey, stop! Stop!
Stop!
- Oh!
Be careful, all right?
- Okay!
Hey!
- Huh?
You said I won't be able
to do it, right?
What is he talking about?
He said I can't handle the deer
that has come into our village.
I accept defeat, brother.
What no one can do,
only you can do it.
You have found out just now.
But others have known
about it for a long time.
Tell me, will I get the deer or not?
Yes! Of course, you will.
Ah! See?
She said yes. Now its confirmed.
- What do you mean?
Will you only ask questions?
Don't you want to save your Dad?
Shall we go?
- Yes!
Bring another one.
- He looks fine.
Why did the boy lie to me?
Oh! So, did you send him to me?
I set this up to show you how
much the village has progressed.
'Hey... Stop!'
The cycle ride
on the canal bridge... was it good?
Hey, girl, listen!
What are these?
- Toe rings!
So give them to your wife, not me.
Look here.
- Hmm?
I'll store them safe in my heart
and give them after the wedding.
Why did you bring me here
at midnight?
Rukmini wants to meet you, Krishna.
Please go. I'll wait here.
Why did you ask me to meet
in private?
Um…
I want to tell you something.
Keep it to yourself.
Try me.
I want to know you
before marrying you.
How can I marry you
without knowing you?
That's why… I asked my maid
for advice…
'Do one thing, madam.'
'You heard about Rangeela Talkies?
There is a show at 5:00 p.m.'
'Go there with him.
You will know everything.'
Will you take me?
Do you know what kind
of movies they show there?
Hmm.
Don't be shameless like your father.
Why are you involving
my Dad into this?
Tell me
whether you'll take me or not.
I am highly respected
in the village.
If someone sees us,
my reputation will be ruined.
Disgusting! I won't take you.
What's the matter, Krishna?
Why do you look flustered?
What did she ask for?
If you hear her demands,
your whole buzz will disappear.
Let it be! She demanded something
for the first time.
We'll give it. We'll
fulfil her wish.
Fine.
I'll take you for a movie
tomorrow evening.
Hmm.
Amazing!
Where are you going all dressed up
Did you forget we're going
to the movies? Let's go.
We are not going for
a devotional gathering.
It's a vibrant movie.
If you enter the theater like this,
they'll make a movie about you.
Hmm! Then what shall I wear?
Wear this.
Hey, Krishna.
Who is that sitting with you?
If I reveal it,
all **** will break loose.
Hurry up!
We may miss the main scenes.
- Hold on.
There's a right time
to enter the theatre. - What time?
When all the lights are turned off.
I will count to three.
- Hmm.
Swifty barge in, find a seat
and quickly sit down.
Hurry up.
One.
Two… Hey, hey...
Did you run away? Hey, wait!
Stop, stop, stop!
Hey, what's wrong?
How will we enter without a ticket?
Huh?
- Two tickets please.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Let's go! Let's go!
When will they play the main scene?
What brings so many men here?
They don't get food at home.
Do they get food here?
- Hmm.
'What I said is final!
- I will marry her only.'
'No matter what!'
Has the main scene come yet?
- Not yet!
They will first sell the popcorn and
'samosa' and then show the scene.
Even the interval feels delayed.
These theatre guys are looting us.
You were getting
scared for no reason.
This is just like a normal film.
Because
this is not the original film.
It will be fun when they play
the new reel, after the interval.
Bend down. Bend down. Bend down.
All the youth seem to be here...
Hey! Aren't you Chamanrao's son?
Are you not ashamed
to watch such films?
Hey! Learn from my son.
He is a gem.
He doesn't go anywhere
apart from the college.
Huh?
Sir, isn't this your gem?
Shameless fellow! You're here!
Sit down!
Get your money's worth
out of the ticket.
When the scene plays,
closing your eyes.
He defamed me!
Disgusting!
- Huh?
The nation's youth
has wandered off the path.
We should blame their teachers
for making them go astray.
You're right.
Hmm?
Master! You are here too,
leaving the school...
I was tired
from checking the homework.
So I thought I'd take a break
and get some fresh air.
This is not like getting fresh air,
this is...
This is called fulfiling one's lust.
Enough. Let's go.
Wait.
The real scene just started.
I said enough.
Is that so?
Bah, let's go!
Hey! Why are you leaving
without watching the main scene?
Close your eyes! Quickly close them.
Come on. Look ahead!
I...
...want to watch rest of the movie?
That was over.
What do I do with this?
- Get such clothes for me.
What kind of girl are you?
You look simple.
But you don't act simple.
Your actions are quite devious.
Why do you say that?
What's wrong with these clothes?
There are hardly any clothes.
That's the biggest problem.
I thought you will surely understand
my feelings.
But no.
You're just like everyone else.
You want to crush my aspirations.
You wanted watch a film earlier.
Now you want to wear filmy clothes.
Your intentions don't seem right.
What happened, brother?
Today, you're flustered again!
What did she ask for this time?
She doesn't think before speaking.
You have no idea
what she is asking for.
Both of them don't listen to me.
Whatever it is.
She has asked for it,
considering you to be close to her.
Go ahead and do it.
We'll fulfil her wish.
"This..."
Did you prepare it?
I don't believe it.
Tell me the truth.
Why would I feed you something
that was made by someone else?
I made it specially for you.
After my mom's cooking,
it's your food that I am
enjoying most, Rukmini.
The size is perfect.
Shall I show it to you?
Would you listen if I say no.
Come on, show it!
How do I look?
Super.
It's very good.
That's true.
What do you feel like looking at me?
It's the same feeling as
when you look at delicious food.
What does it feel like? Tell me.
Let it be. The one who had
to understand has understood
What do you mean?
Hmm. Anyway…
For sure, my husband would
feel the same as you do.
'Despite all the bickering,
brother was sure'
'that Rukmini
had feelings for him.'
One night, Rukmini
finally accepted that.
I had called you today.
Why didn't you come?
Why should I?
Because I chose my groom.
What do you desire?
You come up with strange demands
every other day.
If I refuse, you say 'Who else could
fulfil them, if not you?'
After I fulfil them,
you say,
'It was for my would-be husband.'
If you don't value me... Go away!
Do people speak the truth
after drinking this?
No, it brings out all cuss words.
Hey!
You feel what I did,
was for my would be husband?
You said it.
You look smart, but you aren't.
I have liked you
since I was this small.
I didn't leave the big city
to see the new bridge or
the new school over here.
I came here for you.
Will you marry me, Krishna?
Everything was fine. Then
why couldn't they unite?
Yes, tell us.
Sister-in-law's dad fixed her
wedding with someone else.
Oh!
There is a star in the fourth
house. There are no flaws.
Sir! All the values of the
bride and the groom match.
God has made this pair himself.
- Yes.
Yes.
Das, the boss' third son who had
returned from Dubai got in the way.
Das will like her.
- A lot!
Hmm.
She is lovely, right?
- She is beautiful.
Come.
Master.
I told you that when she
would believe in my love
I would make her meet you, right?
Hey, Rukmini. What is this?
This man saved your house and
trusted you more than his children.
You are so ungrateful.
You are selfishly playing
with the honour of his family.
You are so shameless.
He helped orphans like you, but
you want to rob their happiness?
Hey. Let go of his hand.
Sir? Why are you quiet?
Tell him that she is going
to be your daughter-in-law.
Look. Nothing has changed.
If she is in love with Krishna,
then he is just like my son.
Just think that she will become
the daughter-in-law of this family.
Listen to me, Munshi.
Master, you have a big heart.
You can treat any beggar
on the street as your own.
But I make him my
son-in-law and pamper him.
Never!
Come home with me.
You'll get what you deserve.
Dad.
- Come fast.
Come on now.
- Dad. - Quiet!
Hey.
After your mother died, I gave
you the love of both parents.
Everyone in the village
told me to get married again.
But I didn't do it because I
didn't want to share my love.
Forget about having empathy, my
daughter doesn't even care about me.
I thought you wouldn't express
your feelings because I am a man.
So, I sent you to your grandmother.
With a heavy heart,
do you know why I am collecting
so much money with my hardwork?
It's because if I become rich,
you'll be able to
marry into a rich family.
And if I become super rich,
I can get you a billionaire.
But you choose to rot in his hut.
We don't even know
where he has come from.
Do you think you would leave
the house and would just watch?
You…
No.
Rukmini.
Wait, Rukmini.
If you step out of the
house, you will see me dead.
Even if you get some happiness with
Krishna by making your father sad,
you will remain sad forever.
This is a father's curse.
Stop, Rukmini.
Rukmini...
Dad.
Whatever happened,
it was bad, Rukmini.
But we can't stop living, right?
Krishna will bring you such joy
that you'll forget all your sorrows.
Everyone wants to live.
But my dad took his
own life because of me.
He said,
Even if I get some
happiness with Krishna,
I will remain sad
because I hurt my father.
Don't blame yourself, Rukmini.
Listen to me.
What do we do now?
It has been eight years,
but he is still waiting for her.
You were right.
This is called true love.
This is the bad
thing about true love.
It takes a gruesome test.
Whether it be hard work or cheating,
we will make them pass this test.
Come on.
Krishna is acting so smart
with all the master's power.
Krishna does not
have master's power.
Rather, the master is acting
smart with all the Krishna's power.
When I will clip off their wings,
both of them will die at my feet.
We don't even
have to lift a finger.
Master and Krishna are
going to welcome their deaths.
Do you know what happened
during the last year's festival?
Master's son Das is
returning from Dubai today.
Hey, smile!
It's a great smell.
Do you want it?
Give me one.
Okay, keep it.
Thank you.
Do you know Ramesh?
Yes, he is the coconut dealer.
I know him.
He is my friend.
- Right.
I have got these sunglasses
for him from Dubai.
Nice, aren't they?
They are awesome.
How are you, Das?
Come on. You look good.
You came to meet your childhood
friend directly from Dubai.
Sit down.
Hey…
- Yes, sir.
You guys leave.
- Okay, sir!
Leave!
I got a gift for you.
Did you get it for me?
They are amazing.
Thanks, man.
You didn't call or
write for all these years.
Did you meet someone in Dubai?
Your beard is turning grey.
Will you get married
when you get old?
Look at me.
I am a father of four kids.
I married Geeta from our school.
The same Geeta that you were after.
You have such a bad luck.
You fell for Geeta,
but I married her.
Your wedding was fixed with Rukmini,
but Krishna got in the middle.
You choose the girl, but your
friends get married to them.
You do the hard work
but we get the benefits.
I think there's a
fault in your destiny.
You should do something about it.
I ruined his destiny.
What? Did you stop laughing?
Do it. Smile!
I killed someone in Dubai
the same way.
They jailed me for nine years.
That's why I couldn't write or call.
Do you want to smoke?
It doesn't suit you.
Geeta is mine now.
Spray this on your wife. Your
wife won't be able to resist you.
Well, do you know Krishna?
Yes, I do.
Hmm!
He is also my old friend.
What is it?
We have reached home.
I'm seeing you after years.
Come!
Bless me, dad!
- Bless you.
Bless you.
Did you have a comfortable journey?
Come.
I heard they didn't get married?
I mean Krishna
and Rukmini.
If it didn't happen in nine years,
will it happen now?
Why don't you ask her to marry me?
She's somebody else's,
she'll never be yours.
How?
Is his name written on her?
Name is a small thing.
They're breathing for each other.
Despite not being married,
she belongs to Krishna.
Mom!
- Say.
Have it. It's hot.
- Thank you.
Pass me the kitchen knife.
- Huh?
What will you do with it?
- Give it here, mom.
Oh!
Here!
Hey! What are you doing? Come here!
Come!
Move!
Are you crazy?
- Come to your senses.
Why did you come out with it?
Do you want to kill your dad?
Yes, I will. Is his son Krishna?
Am I not nobody?
Hey, he is our dad.
You call him dad?
Did he ever think about us?
Listen to me.
Listen.
Dad won't give up his principles.
But you can marry her, right?
She is not married yet.
Marry her.
With love or force her.
Hmm!
Huh?
Who the heck are you?
Recognise? I'm Das.
I want to be your slave from today.
If you don't leave right now,
I will kill you.
It's because of this.
It's because of this
that you spotted me.
Let's come to the point.
Let me do the work
for which I am here.
I wanted to see the show from here.
I love you.
Leave!
Hey!
Move!
You!
Don't mess with him.
He's master's youngest son, Das.
Whoever he is, I won't spare him.
Stop!
Hey!
Where are you going?
Hey, what happened?
Das, why are you running?
Hey!
Move!
No!
Arjun!
Move!
Hey!
Uncle Krishna!
Kill him.
"My goodness gracious"
Hey!
- Hey!
"My goodness gracious"
Hey!
- No.
Arjun! Stop it.
- I won't spare him.
I won't spare him.
- Move!
He is our master's son. Leave him.
Do you know what he did?
What did he do?
Nothing. Let's go.
Change, or I won't spare you.
- Let's go.
Hey!
Hey! Das.
- Stop!
Hey!
No, Krishna, stop it.
- What are you doing?
Stop it.
- Das, stay away from him.
I'm telling you to calm down.
Huh!
Whether my dad or
my brother stops me,
but I will kill you
by the next festival.
Or else I am not my dad's son.
Hey!
Despite attacking my brother,
you are standing here alive,
it's because you are Master's son.
Or else,
forget about next year's festival,
I would kill you right now.
The ruckus Das created last year,
he's starting it again.
Holi's bonfire gets extinguished
in a couple of hours,
but the fire of revenge
is still there in Das.
Had he not been Master's son,
Krishna would have killed him.
That's what.
- They are rich people.
Money has a lot of power.
They can do anything. - Yes.
What's wrong with him?
- Yes.
Mother-in-law, talk to him.
How is your Krishna doing?
I told you not to
come to the village.
Why did you come?
I have come to give him the most
dangerous gift in the world.
Huh!
Why is the little
one's face fallen?
Look at him, brother.
I have been asking him to buy
her clothes for the festival.
But he wouldn't respond.
I think I'll celebrate the festival
in old clothes.
What, man?
Simmi!
Let's go shopping. Come.
Don't go.
You'll make Simmi happy but this
cunning girl will scold me later.
Once it's done, I'll take her.
Hey!
Show this simple face to somebody
else, not to your brother.
Kid, after shopping,
we'll have ice cream.
Brother, I...
Hey! What are you doing?
- Arjun.
Come here.
No, Arjun.
Das has sent a gift
for you and Krishna.
An inauspicious
gift on a festival day?
Wipe off your tears.
Is he saying he will kill us?
Hey!
Why did you send
biers to Krishna's house?
Have you lost your mind?
You didn't say anything
when he beat up Das.
Did you forget what he did?
His actions deserved to get beaten.
You again took his sides.
You take the side of outsiders.
If someone touches
a sheep's kid, the sheep
will attack with her horns.
Krishna saves sheep
like you from Wolves.
That's why not wolves,
rather prisoners released
from jail will him.
They don't kill their prey easily,
they give a torturing death.
Even the god of
death is scared of them.
I have called these people
to kill those two.
Greetings, sir.
- Yes.
Arjun and Krishna.
Hold on, I will be back.
Hmm.
Krishna is protecting Arjun.
We can't touch him.
Touching Krishna
means inviting death.
Krishna is a living weapon.
It's impossible to kill him.
If you want to live, then forget it.
We are going.
There's only one huge predator.
My Krishna!
Damn!
Listen, Subbu.
- Yes, Krishna.
A festival is all
about eating a lot.
Drink a lot and have lots of fun.
Hey! Man!
- Won't you have fun?
Krishna! Das sent biers home.
- What?
If you say, I can...
Das has sent two biers.
Why are you worrying for no reason?
Let's open the bottle.
Drink it and feel intoxicated.
Cheers!
Arjun.
- Yes.
Can I ask a question?
- You can ask two.
How would Krishna and Rukmini know
about everything about each other?
There's a postman who passes
messages from here to there.
Who is it?
- It's me! Hey! Get up.
Are you crazy? Get down.
Why are you beating?
- Please remove it. It's no kidding.
Hey! Should I tell you separately?
- I am having fun.
Go and burn this. Come on. Now go.
Arjun, I have another question.
- Yes, ask.
How is Rukmini able
to live alone for eight years?
She keeps herself busy.
Otherwise, an empty house haunts
her. She worships every morning.
She cooks something
new in the afternoon.
And every night...
She comes and sits with me.
Mangala sent this for you.
Tell me the new
story of your brother.
Only yesterday, he beat 20 guys
to pulp.
When will he start
doing something decent?
He always keeps on fighting.
- Why should he do something decent?
He will do what he's good at.
How can you praise him
after drinking my drink?
If you want to praise him,
keep the glass down.
Were the injuries too bad?
Why are you nodding?
Answer what I am asking.
He can't speak without drinking.
No injuries to my brother.
The one who got
beaten got hospitalised.
I was asking about them.
Who is this boy?
He's Bhaskar.
One of my new friends.
He is in love with
the village leader's daughter.
Yesterday's fight
was about this guy.
Master has left him
with us for safety.
It means, if someone
comes to hit him,
your brother is going
to save him like a hero?
What do you mean by hero?
My brother is a born hero.
I saw your hero
the other day.
Has his hair gone a bit grey?
Did you notice it?
I told him to colour them.
But he doesn't listen.
Hey! He looks better this way.
Keep it.
When you love him so much,
why don't you marry him?
Grumpy old man.
Let's go. Every evening, there's a
gathering to learn about my brother.
If I praise him, she scolds me.
If I say nothing, she sulks.
What about Krishna?
Come, I'll show you.
Look there.
Our hero is standing in tension.
After hearing his steps,
the heroine will come out.
He will send a whiff of smoke
in her direction.
Watch the heroine's
hair wave in the open.
So much drama for just a glimpse?
A glimpse is not enough.
That's why she grooms pigeons.
- Grooms, pigeons?
She comes out to feed the pigeons.
They keep on seeing each other.
Krishna watches her
to his heart's content.
The grains will finish soon.
What will she do then?
After this, just like she gives me
two pegs, she will water the plants.
Now, she will unlock the gate
and re-lock.
That's all.
As I do my thing, drink and leave,
they continue their flirting.
They are so close
yet so far from each other.
They pretend to be happy.
But they go through hell within.
Come. Let's go.
Why did you come in?
- I felt like just looking at you.
I was out for so long.
Not enough?
How can it be enough?
My heart is here, and I am
on the other side of the wall.
Hmm!
Enough with your sweet talk.
Hey, listen!
Oh, wow! Is that the same curry?
Hey, Rukmini!
Wear some clothes just like
in the movies, just once.
Enough of you now!
Wait right there!
You!
Are you not going to change ever?
The tree
before your house has changed.
This village has changed.
Even my brother Arjun has changed
after becoming a father.
Give it a thought.
Maybe your dad would be born
as our kid.
If I smell like cigarettes, should
I have a cardamom and come?
Hmm?
You…
I am going to kill you!
Stop right there!
Sunita...
Sunita, look at me, please!
Oh, my! If this happens just
by looking at you,
what will happen if I touch you?
Should we get married today only?
Looking at brother, it doesn't seem
that he has a daughter.
He is so lucky
to have such a beautiful daughter.
Tell us, brother!
When are you sending your daughter
to our house as my daughter-in-law?
Since she was born, I never
thought of her as a daughter.
I always thought of her
as your daughter-in-law.
Dad...
Bhaskar and I...
If you even take his name, it won't
matter that you're my daughter.
I can't let you play with my dignity
for your happiness.
I will kill you
before it comes to that.
What's the point
in strangling her now?
Try this on Bhaskar, with whom
your daughter roams around
in the village.
Remember Krishna?
Master's illegitimate son,
he's the one supporting Bhaskar.
Hey! Krishna is more important
than your father!
Tomorrow is the chariot festival.
The chariot will start
from our village as per tradition.
Until those villagers give up their
insistence on supporting Bhaskar,
I will not let any
of their chariots pass from here.
They will have to face my wrath now.
Greetings, sir!
For the last 400 years,
the chariot has passed
from Mr Veerabhadra's village.
Twenty-five years ago
when it stopped,
entire village was
swept away by floods.
I request
that we do not repeat that mistake.
Yes, sir!
This is like two bulls fighting
and crushing a calf by the side.
As this Bhaskar is in love,
should the whole village
pay the price?
It's not his fault.
It's the person protecting him.
This village is like a family to me.
If injustice is done to them
or Master is humiliated,
then Krishna will
never tolerate this.
Krishna makes you all a promise.
If they try to block our chariots
from going through...
I swear by Master!
No one will be spared.
There will be a river of blood!
Why should we get into a fight?
Collector sir is here only.
Let's talk to him.
Let us settle this peacefully.
Hmm.
Hey!
- Hey!
Hey! Quiet!
Tell me, Mr Parshuram,
what is your opinion?
Collector sir,
who is he to give an opinion?
He is the one protecting that guy!
- Hey!
If you blabber about Master,
I will cut off your tongue.
It's in everyone's best interest
that the chariots are not stopped.
What if we don't allow them? Huh?
Hey! You…
- Krishna!
The villagers still
remember the devastation
when the procession
was stopped 25 years ago.
But the whole world will remember
the devastation I will cause now.
Don't mess with Krishna!
Collector sir, Bhaskar is
well-educated and a good boy.
He will give all the happiness
to their daughter.
Hey! If you find him so good,
make him your son-in-law!
Hey, I'll hack you down
if you say anything against Master.
Hey! I dare you to try and do that.
As if we won't do anything!
Come on!
Hey!
Hey, stop it!
Hey, Inspector!
This is our personal matter.
You have nothing to do here.
Get going.
What is this!
What the heck is this!
If you wanted to fight only,
why did you come to me?
Mr Veerabhadra, you tell me.
What are your conditions
for allowing the procession through?
Collector sir, there's a
tradition in both villages.
Whoever supports a culprit
is a bigger culprit than him.
He'll be forgiven only when he falls
at the feet of the president
in front of the whole village.
Touch my feet,
and no one will stop the chariot.
Collector sir,
I understand their intention.
I'm ready to even bow
for the village.
Master, I can never let this happen.
Every village knows
that you're Master's shadow.
You can come instead and do it.
Hey!
Come on! Come forward.
Come on!
Yay!
Brother!
Brother, the job is done.
He won't be able
to tolerate it at all.
So? Uncle, your daughter
has run away with that, Bhaskar.
If your daughter herself has left,
we can't blame them now.
What's wrong?
Did you get a shock, huh?
Now, even if you fall at our feet,
she won't come back.
What sort of president are you?
This could have been resolved
between us, but you involved God!
Mr Collector!
The chariot procession will
start tomorrow morning,
and that too through his village.
If anyone tries to stop it,
I'll crush him under the chariot.
Don't mess with me!
I almost forgot...
Happy Sankranti to you all.
Hey, shut up!
Let's have some fun now.
Rukmini!
Beautiful girls like you
should not roam alone like this
in dark streets at night.
I know how to teach a lesson
to guys like you.
Blow the horn now!
Should we stop going out
because of people like you?
Come on now!
Let me deal with Krishna first,
and then I will take care of you.
I don't want any hassles for now.
Come on!
She is so cute!
Huh?
Hey, Bhaskar, this shirt would
look better on me, right?
This is my wedding.
Yeah, right.
It looks very plain on you.
And you are also quite
plain looking.
Dad! I want a white frock.
Excuse me!
Please, take out that white frock.
This one, sir?
- No, not that. The next!
This one?
- Yeah, that one.
Pack this, too. He will pay.
There's only one show for today.
Come and watch Superstar
Chiranjeevi's super hit film.
Hey, Bhaskar!
Let's watch the movie.
No! I have to buy
clothes for Sunita.
We can shop later.
Let's go for the movie.
Here, sir!
Come on, move!
Arjun!
It's fun, isn't it?
Here comes our hero!
Hey, move!
Sister, can you get me two tickets?
Make your wife stand in a queue
and get them.
My wife is pregnant.
She is the one
who always stands in the queue.
Idiot! That's my daughter-in-law.
Oh, boy!
You're going to get a beating.
Get going.
Aunt, I will buy you samosas.
Can you get me two tickets?
Okay, dear.
Here are your tickets, dear.
Hey, Bhaskar, come on!
Great trick!
Come here. These are our seats.
He who puts his feet
on the seat is a donkey.
There's the movie.
Oh, yeah!
It's the last one. Let me smoke it,
and then I'll watch the movie.
'Whoever messes
with me gets messed up!'
'Remember the name! Ranjit Kumar.'
Come on.
Hey! Who is it?
Show yourself if you have the guts.
Hey!
Bhaskar, run!
I said run!
Call Krishna!
Hey!
Hey, stop! Stop!
Hey, stop!
Hey!
How was that?
Wow!
What did you say?
Huh?
No one can kill Arjun
while Krishna is alive?
But we are hacking Arjun here.
Where is your brother Krishna?
Krishna!
Hey, Krishna!
Do you remember that day
of your childhood, huh?
'Hey, Arjun, save him!'
'Das, get up!'
'Get up, Das!'
I cannot sin killing
the person who saved my life.
You are spared. Go!
You can go now.
I was kidding!
What happened?
Did you think
that I would spare your life?
You must have thought
I would spare your life.
When you kill someone after
giving him hope… the high it gives…
Huh?
Mangla?
Hey! No, no!
She is your wife!
Hmm… Okay.
I'll look after her if you want.
Mangla!
Hey, my queen!
Hey, Das!
Das, stop! Stop...
Arjun…
Hey, move! Move!
Arjun!
Arjun! - Krishna...
- Who did this?
Arjun! My brother...
Arjun, talk to me.
Hey, Arjun!
Hey, bring the car!
Arjun...
Hey, get the car, man!
Arjun! Arjun!
Arjun, you'll be all right.
Hey, be careful!
Careful!
Brother, go fast.
Krishna, my brother!
Simmi was insisting.
She wanted a frock.
Now, she will see her father
in a white shroud.
Rukmini has no one
except you, Krishna.
She did not marry you
to fulfil her father's last wish.
Tell her that my dying wish was
that she should marry you.
That might melt her heart.
Arjun...
Arjun!
What is that?
Has Arjun sent this through you?
Wow, a frock!
Hey! Wear this
before your dad comes.
Okay!
What is this, brother?
He still isn't home
even on the festival day.
Dad! I will open my eyes
when you come.
Hey, Beera! Surya!
They have killed our Arjun, man!
They have killed our Arjun!
See how brutally
Arjun has been killed.
Arjun!
What happened?
What happened to my Arjun?
Bhaskar, what happened to him?
Arjun, get up!
Open your eyes!
You can't leave me like this.
No... Get up, Arjun!
Tell him to open his eyes.
Bhaskar! Talk to him...
What happened, brother?
I want Arjun back!
I want my Arjun back!
Why couldn't you save Arjun?
Tell me!
How could someone kill him
when you were with him, brother?
Stop kidding.
Get up, Arjun! Get up now!
Uncle, what happened to dad?
Why isn't he getting up?
Dad!
Look at Simmi. Get up for Simmi.
Dad… what happened to you, dad?
Dad!
Dad, please get up.
Hey... our Arjun…
It was Arjun's dying wish, dad.
Before he died,
more than about his wife and kid,
he thought about me, dad.
How can someone be so selfless?
Krishna must be dying inside, dad.
If I don't take care of him,
then who will?
I am going, dad.
Please forgive me.
Not one man who was involved
in Arjun's killing should live.
But you... don't die.
Come back to me alive!
Why should we run away fearing him?
- Hey!
Despite knowing Krishna's wrath,
you all killed his brother.
The only reason you're still
alive is because you're my son.
But even I can't save you now.
You have killed the brother of the
man who has been protecting me
for so many years
despite having no relation with me.
Run away from here
before you all get consumed
in the fire of his revenge.
How can he kill us just like that?
- No one can defeat him!
He is Krishna!
He will kill you all!
Run away from here.
Run away!
Krishna, they're not allowing
our chariots through their village.
I was wondering why no one came
to file a case against
Arjun's murder.
Why register a case
when the killer is not alive?
Das died? When?
So, Krishna killed Das?
I want that no case should
be filed against Krishna.
You will have to pay a heavy price
to hush up the murder case.
Hey, enough... That's it!
So much money is not necessary
for a single murder.
Who said it would be just one?
If you were a real man,
you would've come alone to fight me.
But you have come
with the entire village.
Every year,
our villagers sacrifice goats.
You will be
that goat this year, Krishna.
Attack!
You may not have seen
that many firecrackers at festivals
as you will find
chopped heads there.
"Goodness gracious"
"My goodness gracious"
Krishna!
Hey... Hey!
Hey, stop!
Krishna!
Hey, Krishna!
Hey!
Krishna!
No!
Finished!
What sort of a lion are you
that you couldn't stop
your brother from being hunted?
And you couldn't escape
being hunted yourself.
'Not one man who was involved
in Arjun's killing should live.'
'I will wait for you.'
Come back to me alive!
"Abode of the destroyer"
"Lord Shiva comes for protection"
"This is his ferocious war"
"This is his protection from evil"
"Annihilating the monsters"
The Krishna
whom you raised like a son
is the one
who is killing your son now.
Master, you raised a snake
offering it milk.
He will kill everyone!
"He is in ferocious form"
"Against all the evil"
"This is the end of all demons"
"Protection for the humankind"
Arjun saved your life in childhood.
So how can I kill you?
You are spared. Go.
So?
You thought I would spare your life.
When you kill someone after
giving him hope… the high it gives…
Hey!
Don't mess with me!
I killed them.
You killed all my sons.
He killed my brother, master.
My sons were no scapegoats!
Hey! Master has killed Krishna.
Master has killed Krishna.
- Krishna!
Krishna!
- Hey! No...
If you come even one step closer,
I will kill you.
Come on, get back!
Get back!
Master, nothing...
Nothing will happen to you.
Get inside! Please.
Please go inside!
Don't you dare...
Krishna!
Hey, don't cry.
Nothing happened to me.
After ten years,
you have asked me for something.
Not to die.
Now I won't die even after being
stabbed 100 times like this.
Rukmini...
Will you marry me?
Hey, Arjun!
Dad!