Hey, Anji!
Fresh up and come.
Food is waiting.
Who are you?
I am hungry, mother.
I haven't eaten in two days.
Oh! Please, eat.
What is your name?
Kishtaiah.
Have it, have it.
Come. come.
Come and have your food.
Sit down first.
Here.
Who is this brother, mom?
You have already called him brother.
Consider him as one.
Brother...
Mom!
Have you made this?
-Yes!
You are such a darling!
What about me?
You are my darling.
Sir...
-Huh?
You know the chariot festival is approaching.
-Yes!
I need some loan.
Festivals are most important.
Unless festivals are here,
how would we make money?
Huh?
-Yes.
Here!
Hello! Put this and go.
Fine fellow you are!
Careful, careful.
Oh! It’s broken.
-Sorry, sir!
Wait, wait. Don’t touch it.
Ah, Goddess Lakshmi!
Hey!
Send word for Sattemma's son.
“O, o, o…”
Brother, focus on the job.
-Sir, Sir!
-Ah!
It’s done, sir.
-Is it over?
Ah!
-Keep it aside.
Careful. Careful.
Sir...
Hm?
-Money, sir.
I will pass it for interest on
your mom's loan. Get going.
He wants money!
Anji...
This is Varalu.
With a heart of gold.
Who is this?
Kishtaiah.
My elder brother.
Hey, Anji! Your mom has died!
Mom…
Mom! Get up, mom!
Mom...
Oho!
-Mom!
Your mom...
had mortgaged this hut
and took a loan.
Now she passed away
without settling it.
If you lift the bier quickly,
I will take over the house.
If you can give me some time…
-Huh?
I will somehow repay your loan.
And how would you?
Huh?
The kid talks out of ignorance.
Lift the bier.
Hey!
Touch her and I will hack the hand.
How are you concerned?
She is my mother.
And he is my younger brother.
Mom, please open your eyes.
Please, make way.
Please, come, sir.
What is the problem?
What can I tell you?
Times have changed.
I lent them money against the house…
and the warrior comes at me
with a kitchen knife!
That’s the situation.
Bring the documents to my house
and collect your money.
Don't you hear?
This house is always yours.
Mom!
Sir!
What is your name?
Kishtaiah, sir.
I'll take leave, sir.
Enough! Enough!
Hey, come!
Huh!
-Sit, brother.
-Yes!
Hey, what are you doing?
Get up!
Hey! Get up!
Come here.
It’s okay. Come.
Sit here.
Wife!
-Huh?
Serve them food.
-I am doing it, husband.
Will you eat dosa?
-Hmm.
Ah!
Brother!
Brother, Varalu is coming.
Bare your heart to her.
Tell her like ANR told Savitri in
'Preminchi Chudu’ film.
Otherwise, I will lose my face.
Hey, Anji!
What are you waiting here for?
My brother wants to tell you something.
Something you would like to hear.
Is it so, boy?
Come on. Tell me.
Er...actually you...
Me...
Huh?
Master…master!
Hey, hey!
Hey! Come on!
Come on, man!
Come on! Hey!
Mom!
Hey...
Where is Gopalarao's house?
Go further down and it's
the tiled house on the corner.
Hmm!
Uh, greetings, sir.
Is Bhasker home?
Bhaski!
Dad!
How presumptuous you are!
You step into our village last night…
for my niece...
and jump over the wall!
Follow me quietly
and only you will go with me.
Otherwise…
Why do you trouble yourself
so much? Take him along.
Huh?
Come, come, come.
Hey, hey, hey!
Who the heck are you?
Dump him in!
-Hey, you!
Why are you abducting my brother-in-law?
Hey, where are you taking him?
Hey, father-in-law! They are taking him…
They are taking him
and why are you nodding to the clarinet?
Is your brain frozen?
Let's lodge a complaint with the police.
Don't stress, son-in-law.
He will come home himself.
Son-in-law… Vada is getting cold.
Please, come.
Look at you cool as cucumber
when your son is being taken.
Come on fast.
They are getting cold.
Hey! Damn your vada getting cold!
What sort of family this is!
Throw them now. Wait.
-Hmm.
Who made vada?
You or your daughter?
It was me.
Saved me. Give them now.
Did you get it straight out of
boiling oil?
You’re not even worried about your son.
I wonder how they are handling him.
-Why do you worry so much, son-in-law?
We have our master to
protect all of us.
Who?
The aged president?
Did you see the goons?
They were like fierce tigers!
Every village has a god to protect it.
But our village has a hunk to protect it.
Who is he?
“God Himself…”
“In his own hand…”
“Writes a poem”
“Anji’s…and Kishtaiah’s…”
“Inseparable bonding”
“Their blooming, smiling friendship”
“Is a lesson of whistling to the soft breeze”
“With joy unending…”
Anji, I forgot the match box.
-“A journey that would go on until the end”
Bullebbai, where are they?
They went this way, sir.
Give me a match box.
-I don’t have it, sir.
Fine. Let’s light it over there.
Come.
-Okay, sir!
You can start, Anji.
Akashavani...Presenting now
'The Beating You Sought' programme.
Hey, Kittaiah!
Er…this is our personal issue.
Don't interfere.
Hmm.
Yes. By now, Anji must have
reached this guy's village.
Why did he go to my village?
To convey the news of your death.
Huh?
Don’t you understand?
On whose orders have you come here?
Gita for the Hindus, Quran for Muslims
and Bible for Christians.
For Kishtaiah...
it's master's word.
Hey…
Aunty!
-Oi!
Take a clean cloth and a fistful
of turmeric and go to the farm bund.
Why?
Your younger son’s head is broken.
What? When?
One...two...three!
Just now.
Hey!
Kishtaiah…
No!
“Goodness gracious”
“My goodness gracious”
Huh?
Hey, aunt!
Oi?
Are you not going to stop?
How?
Why would your uncle let me?
He is going to stop you from today.
Why? What for?
Hey!
Sister...
what are you up to?
I am making butter for
my husband, brother.
What would a spineless man
do with butter?
Eh?
So sad!
Come on, beat him up, Kishtaiah.
Hey, grandpa!
How come you are sitting idle?
No business, kid.
Wait for half an hour.
You will get as busy as a bee.
Hmm?
Huh!
Hey!
If I find your wheels on our roads again,
I will flay you all alive.
My goodness gracious!
“Meddle with us, try to mess with us…
You will be in for a shock”
"My goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious"
"Cross your line, get caught by us...
You will be in for a shock"
"My goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious"
"When we say one,
we mean the village"
"When we say village,
we mean each one"
"When we say one...
-we mean the village"
"When we say village...
-we mean each one"
"With us...with us...
pick a fight with us and"
“Goodness gracious!”
“My goodness gracious”
"Goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious"
“Goodness gracious!”
“My goodness gracious”
"This air...is highly valiant"
"This soil...is most resolute"
"This water...is full of love"
"Drinking this water,
treading this soil,"
"and breathing this air...
grew up this body"
"As long as it breathes,
it shall be loyal"
"As long as it lives,
it shall love its people"
"With us...with us...
pick a fight with us and"
"Goodness gracious!"
"My goodness gracious"
"Goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious"
"Goodness
-gracious"
"My goodness gracious"
"Goodness
-gracious"
"My goodness gracious"
Hey, hey!
Call Vijay.
Boss!
-I have heard about you. Let’s move it.
Just a little…
-Fine, go on.
Hold on!
-Ah!
Hey Kishtaiah, come!
Master, you carry on.
-Hey! Come on, man!
We must agree Kishtaiah is great.
Master dotes on Kishtaiah.
Dad prioritizes servants
over his own sons.
Kishtaiah!
-Ha!
Take care of Bhasker
until the festival is over.
Hmm?
Ok, master!
-Fine!
Anji!
-I’ll take care, brother.
By the way,
why did you jump the wall?
Festival time, brother
She wanted braid tassels to
match her skirt, brother.
I jumped over to give them to her.
If she asked you for something,
why would you jump over the president’s wall?
Why would you?
Brother!
This heart here…
Stays fine until it falls in love.
The moment it falls in love,
it loses all reasoning.
It makes you feel it’s okay to do anything
or give anything.
The smile on her face when I give it,
and the joy it gives me…wow, wow, wow!
Our legs go weak and we sway
like puppets.
Forget the president’s wall,
we get ready to jump over even the China wall.
Brother, he's trying to say something
and I'm unable to understand.
You raise the volume
and you say it clearly.
“Why should one go to Brindavan
and Nandavan for honeymoon?”
“Why should one go to Rameswaram
and Varanasi for a pilgrimage?”
“When your beloved husband is right before you,
why look for another God?”
Shall we finish the story tomorrow?
-Huh?
Then? Why do you simply stare?
She’s leaving. Meet her.
“Why should one go to Rameswaram
and Varanasi for a pilgrimage?”
“My love’s face shines like the moon
Spreading moonlight in the day”
“With the soft gaze of the beloved,
Ooty has come down here”
“Why should one go to Kodaikanal
and Kashmir for honeymoon?”
"With the soft gaze of the beloved,
Ooty has come down here”
“Why should one go to Kodaikanal
and Kashmir for honeymoon?”
“Why should one go to Brindavan
and Nandavan for honeymoon?”
Great, my boy!
Such girl deserves our very life.
“Why should one go to Rameswaram
and Varanasi for a pilgrimage?”
Hey!
What are you doing here?
I was listening to his love story, brother.
It was so beautiful.
-I see!
What are you planning to jump next?
Give a break to your love story
during the festival and sit at home.
Your father-in-law is already in a rage.
Hmm!
My love story has become
a comedy for Kishtaiah.
He'd know that pain if he
falls in love with someone.
Hey, hey, if you know Kishtaiah’s story,
you wouldn’t say this.
He is in love too.
Our Kishtaiah? No way.
He knows only slaying.
Not romance. I don’t believe this.
Hey, Kishtaiah you know is different.
I’ll tell you his love story, come.
Hmm?
Pick the card.
Here comes the king!
-Show!
You simply rocked it.
Collect the money.
-Hey, hand over the money.
Hey, I heard Varadarajulu’s daughter, Varalu,
has returned? -King made me win.
She went to Madras for studies
and returned after fifteen years.
Mahalaxmi dear, don’t be worried.
Go with grandma
and study well in the city.
And I will, of course,
come to see you every week.
Don’t get home sick.
Her clothes...her styling...
What a change in her!
She is pink in complexion they say.
She looks like a film heroine.
Why? How are we less?
You can't take it when someone
is beautiful, can you?
You will be damned!
Don't cast your evil eye!
Why is he getting so upset?
Namaste!
-Namaste!
Master!
Kishtaiah.
-Please come, Master…
Master has arrived.
Madam, please come.
Be seated.
Namaste!
Please sit.
Hey!
Switch on the lights!
This is Varalu….
Hey, Varalu! Have you just come?
-Yes.
Sit.
-How is everyone?
Varalu, did you notice?
Our village has changed a lot.
Really?
-Hmm.
They have even painted
the school we attended.
Do you at least know that?
They have replaced the old bridge
with a new one.
Did you at least notice that?
No!
Be blessed!
Take his blessings too.
Manga, come here.
Bless us, brother.
-Brother!
Hey, hey!
Only one of you should
call me brother.
Bah! This is such a torture!
Oho!
“Here is the charming girl”
“Watch her mischief, Anji”
“A lass from Nellore, Anji. She came
in my dreams and tugged at me"
“She threw a challenge
and invited for a game”
“Here and there and everywhere
including the banana plantation"
“She asked me to have
unlimited fun”
“Here is the charming girl”
“Watch her mischief, Anji”
Hey, stop it. Stop it!
I said stop it!
Hey, move! Move!
It’s so blaring on the ears...
They started bleeding!
We have a celebration in
our family after 25 years, sir.
So?
You expect the whole village
to dance?
You have no parents.
She has no parents either.
Huh?
There is nothing to say about
this guy.
This is an orphan wedding and you
want songs on high watt mike set.
You were two till now.
Now you are three.
What is so big a change?
This is not a home, man!
This is an orphanage.
Shut up!
Why are you running your mouth?
You can't understand
someone's tears.
You can’t tolerate their smiles.
Hey!
How are you even born human?
Give me four names from the village...
who would carry your bier.
Who is an orphan?
Say that again and...
My goodness gracious!
What is this, brother? Why did
you pick a fight with him?
After all he is your future
father-in-law.
So? How are we orphans?
I have you.
And you have me.
Now we have that precious soul.
Don't start crying now.
I would be blamed.
Especially when there is
so much involved tonight.
Why do you feel shy? Do it.
Why don't you?
Enough with the games.
All of you leave now.
-Hey, hey!
You remember, right?
Yes, I do.
Get going now.
What about you?
You want to supervise?
Get lost!
I won't open the door till morning.
Sir?
Hmm?
Isn’t it Varadarajulu’s daughter
Varalu, you are in love with?
What is it now?
It’s not that.
You have lots of stories to say
about your love.
But she didn't even look at you
in the wedding.
And then you manhandled the man who is
supposed to give you his daughter’s hand.
What you say and what I see
don’t sync at all.
Hey…
-Huh?
Get going.
Hmm!
Keep the radio here.
-Okay, sir!
I only questioned him on what he said.
-Idiot...
He must be offended.
“Some strange desires disturb my heart”
"Those naughty jasmines
eavesdrop hiding behind the leaves"
But she didn’t even look at you
at the wedding.
"Get up, get up, my dear"
"Won't you get up?
Do you want me to wake you up?"
Who is waking me up?
I will be right back.
Don’t go to sleep.
Yes, coming...
What is it, brother?
-Hey!
Varalu didn’t recognize me, man.
Probably, she forgot.
Is that so important now?
Why don’t we talk tomorrow?
Hmm.
"Up, get up, my dear"
"Please, wake up, my dear"
"Won't you get up?
Do you want me to wake you up?"
Brother, what is this?
Hey, ever since I saw Varalu,
I have lost control of my heart.
I want to start wedding
arrangements fast.
I would like to start too, brother.
Today is the first day.
I will be blamed.
I imagined so many things, man.
I imagined lots of things
too, brother.
About all that I should do.
Brother, let us discuss this tomorrow.
Hmm.
"Get up, get up, my dear"
"Please, get up, my dear"
“Won’t you wake up?
Do you want me to wake you up?”
Brother…
Anji! From the moment I saw Varalu,
I just don't know what to do.
I totally know what to do
but you won’t let me.
It’s not that…
-Brother!
All that I want to do inside,
you call me out and do exactly same.
We will sort this out in
the morning, okay? Here.
Go, go.
-Sleep.
"Get up, get up, my dear"
"Please, get up, my dear"
"Won't you get up?
Do you want me to wake you up?"
I wanted to stay awake the whole night.
And look at you sleeping!
Brother!
Sir, sir!
-Hmm.
What is the secret behind
salt and basil water?
Silly fellow!
When we give money with salt,
the loan never gets repaid.
But when we sprinkle basil water,
this sinful money gets purified.
That is the secret behind.
Get it?
Ah…huh!
Move it.
You can go.
Brother, come.
Come on, brother.
Why would she forget you just
because she studied in Madras?
Anji, give me those glasses.
Huh! Here!
Hmm!
How come the newly married groom
is knocking at our door early morning?
I mean…couldn’t greet you properly
at my wedding yesterday.
Have you recognized?
Kishtaiah... my elder brother.
Kishtaiah?
Didn’t I tell you?
She won’t forget us though
she went to Madras.
Ah…Kishtaiah?
Hmm.
Was it you who caught my dad
by his collar?
Huh?
-Was it you?
You catch my dad’s collar...
and how dare you come home now?
-No, no, no.
Don’t ever show your face to me!
He would face a hundred
people alone.
But he couldn’t face a girl.
That is what you call love, brother.
Hey, stop it!
The older ones already got married.
Anji too got married.
Now only Das and you are left.
We are also looking for
a nice match for Das.
Wedding will be soon after
he returns from Dubai.
Now, let’s come to you.
Tell me who the girl is.
I will go talk to them.
But she should come to me
understanding my love for her.
Not because someone has
told her.
If she does come for me,
I will bring her to you then.
You can go talk to her father
and get us married.
When will she look at you again?
And when will she feel your love?
Anyway, she is like the hilsa fish.
Very difficult to catch her.
Why would you say that?
Don’t tell me she won’t fall
for my brother?
He might fall after one more peg.
But she won’t fall for him.
It’s not the bulls in the village to
get scared of your brother and obey.
She is a city bred college girl.
Not so easy.
Hey…
-Hmm.
If I don’t take her on my
bicycle by this time tomorrow.
My goodness gracious...
Sister Varalu! Sister Varalu!
They are beating up your dad
near the farm bund on the outskirts.
Huh? My dad?
Let's go!
Hey, boy!
Huh? What is it, girl?
I need to go the farm bund on
the outskirts. Can you take me?
You told me not to show
my face to you.
Find someone else.
Damn!
They are thrashing my dad.
Hey, girl!
By the time you reach there
walking like a swan,
your dad would have
a second round.
If there is someone going that side
on a cycle, try hitching a hike.
Which way are you going?
I am going to the farm on
the outskirts on some work.
Why don’t you take me along then?
Huh?
There is no carriage at the back.
Is that okay?
Hmm...?
Hmm.
Huh?
What the heck!
He has managed to impress her.
Hey, Bullabbai! You spoke about
some hilsa fish and how rare it is.
Who knew you had such
a long fish pole?
The fish is not cooked yet.
I will tell you when it is done.
When is the wedding?
What wedding?
Oh, no! Your dad!
Come on.
Great fish pole!
Hey, stop! Stop!
Stop!
-Oh, no!
Hmm, hmm.
You must be careful, right?
-Okay!
Hey!
-Huh?
You said she is from the city
and won’t relent?
Who is he talking about?
He says a heifer has come from
the city. And it can’t be handled.
Why just the bulls?
Even heifers listen to you.
I have just found out.
You have found out just now.
They have known it for long.
Do you think I can manage
a heifer?
Ah! Of course, it will give in.
Ah! See?
She says it will surrender.
The girl says so.
What?
Keep asking me all kinds of questions
and your dad will be beaten up more.
Shall we go?
-Yes!
Be at it!
What’s happening?
He told me someone was
beating my dad?
So, did you do this purposely?
The school you had attended...
does it look good after being painted?
Hey, hey! Stop!
Cycle ride on the new bridge...
was it good?
Hey, girl!
What are these?
-Toe rings!
Go, give them to your wife.
Look here.
-Hmm?
I'll store them safe on my heart
and give them after the wedding.
“Clad in a sari in onion pink
and tucking the pleats high”
“Do you call yourself
a rich kid, beauty?”
“Cute looking sweet little lady
Come forward dainty beauty”
“Wearing a ridge gourd green blouse
And sporting a coin sized vermilion”
“Why do you say you won’t
step out, lady?”
“Cute looking sweet little lady
Come forward dainty beauty”
“Shall I carry you away?”
“Glances that are sweet
and delicious”
“Words harsh and pungent”
“With a waist of a jasmine
and dame with style abundant”
“As you walk ahead…
O o o o o …”
“And as I stand watching you…
O o o o o ….”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
“Rolling you up, making a bundle,
carrying on my head, along Godavari”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
“Filling you in a pot, lifting your weight
Without letting you go, until death”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
“Shall I carry you away?”
“As you amble along…
touched by your feet”
“Clay-made balls
Have turned into tinkling bells”
“When you smile…”
“The sweetness of your smile”
“Makes the tree branches
turn into honeycombs”
“You are so, so, so very cute”
“To put it in one, single word”
“If the moon had kids…”
“Hey, if the moon had kids, it’d
show you and feed them in joy”
“What could I do when you
are so pretty?”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
“You are the queen
of my heart’s fortress”
“On the palanquin of my
two legs…”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
“Until babies bloom from our love
and you carry them on your side,”
“I want to carry you away, girl!
I want to carry you away”
Why have you brought me
here now?
Varalu asked you to meet, brother.
Please, go. I'll wait there.
Why did you ask me to meet
in private?
Urm…
I want to tell you something.
Keep it to yourself.
Tell me. What is it?
When I get married,
I should know how to be
with my husband, right?
Hmm.
That’s why… I asked my maid
for advice…
Do this. There is a show at 5pm
in Bhaskar Talkies.
Watch it.
You will know everything.
Hmm…
I mean…actually…
Don’t tell me you want me to
take you to the movie?
Hmm.
Have you lost your mind?
Hey, I asked you something
for the first time.
Why can't you take me?
I have some reputation here.
If people come to know
we went to that kind of movie…
Damn! I can’t do this.
Hey, brother!
Why do you look so dazed?
What did she ask for?
If you hear what she asked, you will
be so shocked you will need a tablet.
Whatever. She has asked you
for something.
Do it. Do it.
Otherwise, we will be blamed.
Fine.
Get ready for tomorrow evening.
Hmm.
What's the matter?
You got ready so well?
We are going for the movies.
That’s why.
We are not going for
a devotional movie.
It's a spicy movie.
If you go to the movie like this,
my goodness gracious!
Hmm!
How should I get ready then?
Hey, Anji!
Why are you sitting in the front
like a girl covering your face?
So that you can question me.
Come fast.
They might play the bits already.
-Hold on.
You shouldn’t walk in for
these films just like that.
Then?
He switches off the lights
when it’s time.
I will count to three.
-Hmm.
We should get in even
before we know.
Hmm.
-Hmm.
Fast!
One.
Two…what the heck!
Hey, hey! Wait! Wait, wait.
Hey!
-Huh?
Who will buy the tickets? Huh?
-What?
Huh?
-Give two tickets.
Come fast!
Let’s go! Let’s go!
I wonder when they will play
the bits.
How come there are so many?
Hunger.
For so many?
Hmm.
Did they play the bits, brother?
-Hmm?
Brother, did they play any bits?
Not yet, brother.
No one is buying popcorn and samosa.
-Hey, hey!
So, they will play the bits
after the intermission.
I wonder when the intermission
will be.
What’s so special about it?
Everyone is watching like
a normal film.
What is there to watch?
After the interval,
you will see real acting here.
Bah, bah!
All the youth seem to be here...
Hey!
Aren’t you Chinnarao’s son?
Are you not ashamed
to watch these films?
Hey! Learn from my son.
He is a diamond.
-Huh?
He doesn’t step out of the house.
Huh?
Sir, isn’t this your diamond?
Bloody scoundrel!
You also had to land here! Sit down!
Waste of ticket.
When bits come, bend your head.
You are ruining my reputation.
Damn it!
-Huh?
Society is gone to dogs, brother.
We shouldn’t blame them.
We should blame their teachers.
I know.
Hmm?
Subbaiah sir! You are also here!
I was stressed from teaching.
That’s why...
Stress... my foot! Thirst!
They began the screening.
Enough. Let's go.
Wait.
It has just started.
I said enough.
I have understood.
Aha…
Bah, let's go!
Hey! Why are you leaving just
when the bits are being screened?
Bend your head,
lower your head.
Look at the screen, man.
Brother!
Did you watch ‘Premnagar’?
-I saw.
-Did you see 'Premambhishekam'?
-Yes!
How touching they are!
Those are pure love stories.
These two went to a spicy film
and they call theirs a love story.
'A hasty groom made a pass
at a guest.'
Listen to the complete story.
Varalu called Kishtaiah again.
Actually…that…
Which movie this time?
Um hmm, not that.
What is it?
I want to wear those clothes.
There is a doctor named Gandham
Nagaraju at the end of the village.
Until you see him,
don't walk among public.
Why do you say that?
Can't I wear those clothes?
She is hardly wearing anything.
What is left there for you to wear?
Anyway, I can't wear such clothes
once I am married.
That’s why I want to wear them
at least once.
A small wish, boy.
You wanted clips yesterday.
Today it's clothes.
Whatever you are up to!
What?
What did she ask you, brother?
She doesn't know what to ask.
You have no idea what
she is asking.
I have no clue what I should do.
Something. She has asked you.
Go ahead and do it.
Or we will be blamed.
"You and I..."
Is this murrel?
It’s so delicious!
Who made it?
Why would I bring you curry
made by someone else?
I cooked it with my own hands.
After my mom, it's your cooking
that I am enjoying most.
Enough with your butter.
Shall I come?
It wouldn't be nice if I said that.
But please come.
Is it good?
To look at…
I find it good.
It's not that, boy.
What do you feel looking at me?
How does it feel when piping hot rice
with fish curry is placed before you?
How does it feel?
You feel like eating it up.
What?
Hmm. Anyway…
Probably, my husband would
feel the same after I get married.
It's past eight.
Why didn't you come?
Why should I?
I wanted to tell you about
my wedding.
What do you have in mind?
You put all your strange wishes
before me.
If I ask you why, you would say
who else could fulfil them.
After I fulfil them,
you ask me
if your husband would like it.
Go to your husband then!
Does drinking this bring
the truth out?
For me it brings out all cuss words.
Hey!
Why do I ask you what I should
be asking my husband?
That's what beats me.
How would I make you understand?
I have liked you since I was
this small.
As soon as my dad asked, I came here
not to see the canal or the new bridge.
It was to see you.
Will you marry me, Kishtaiah?
“Further and further…
as distance keeps vanishing”
as souls keep getting close”
“A strange feeling
peeps into the heart”
“Erasing all silences”
“And greeting in words”
“Looking at you…
-Looking at me”
“Wanting to say this…
-Wanting to say…”
“I feel…
-What?”
“That past wouldn’t come back
That there is no tomorrow”
“That right now I am yours”
Everything seems fine.
What disturbed their love story then?
Exactly!
If all is well, they call it a wedding.
Why would they call it a love story?
Star Ashwini, fourth quarter,
No fault found...
Sir!
Both their horoscopes are
a perfect match.
This is a God chosen wedding.
-Okay!
Ah!
She is beautiful, isn't she?
-Yes!
Hmm.
-Cute, isn't she?
-The bride is beautiful, right?
Come!
Master!
You asked me to bring them
to you when someone likes me.
Here. I have brought her.
Hey, Mahalakshmi!
What is this?
He saved your house and raised
you for years and looked after you...
And how can you eye
his future daughter-in-law?
For being kind to orphans like you,
you have taught him a great lesson.
Hey! Hey! Remove it.
Remove it!
Sir? Why don’t you speak?
Tell him! That she is your
would-be daughter-in-law.
We wanted a wedding.
But they are in love.
He is also my family.
If she marries him,
he will take good care of her.
Hey! Varadarajulu…
Hello!
You would probably shelter anyone
and everyone out of compassion.
But I can’t make him my son-in-law
and invite him home.
Damn!
Great job you have done.
Come now!
-Come on!
-Dad!
-Come on now! Come!
Hey!
When your mother died,
I was only 24.
Everyone would come and
ask me, “Marry my daughter.”
I have such status and influence.
But I didn’t relent because a stepmom
could never be your real mom.
Being a girl, you cannot express
everything after certain age.
So, I sent you to your grandmother.
Why do you think I collect interest
at the cost of others’ grief?
Because I thought with lakhs,
I can get you a millionaire husband.
And with crores,
I can get you a billionaire.
But you choose to go to a hut.
We don’t even know where he
was born and to whom.
What? Do you think I will simply
watch if you try to leave with him?
Huh?
You…
Listen.
Listen, Mahalakshmi!
If you step out of the house,
consider me dead.
Whether you laugh with him,
cry with him or do whatever…
Remember it would all be
over my dead body.
Look, Mahalakshmi!
Dad!
Don’t be sad, Varalu.
Brother will look after you so well
you will forget your dad.
My dad said, if I step across the threshold,
I should consider him dead.
Whether I laugh or cry or do
anything with Kishtaiah,
it would be over my dad’s
dead body.
Don’t overthink, Varalu.
Listen to me.
For just one statement, he has been
Waiting for her for eight years?
He doesn't have to cross
an ocean.
He could just jump over the wall.
Shree Rama may be powerful
Enough to cross the ocean.
But Sita should allow him, right?
We must somehow unite them
before the festival, brother.
Let's go.
Brother-in-law!
I got a rooster ready for the fight.
Sir!
The knife is quite sharp.
Tie it to our fighter cock.
Okay, Sir!
If I find your wheels on our
roads again,
My goodness gracious!
Kishtaiah is arrogant
because of Master's support.
Master is not Kishtaiah’s strength.
Kishtaiah is Master’s strength
and support.
I will show what Veerabhadrudu
can do once he makes up his mind.
We don’t have to take the trouble.
Death awaits Krishnaiah at
Master’s house itself.
Do you know what happened
during the last year’s festival?
Hey, smile!
Nice fragrance from perfume…
Do you want it?
Get me one, sir.
This is for you.
Thanks, sir.
Do you know Rambabu?
Yes. Coconut merchant, right?
Yes.
He is my friend.
-Oh!
I have got this for him.
Nice, isn’t it?
Terrific.
Hey, Dasu!
Hey, Dasu! How are you?
Have you come directly to
see me from Dubai?
Sit down.
Hey…
-Sir!
- You guys leave.
- Okay, sir!
Leave!
I have got you something.
-Huh?
For me?
Terrific. Just like me.
Thanks, man.
It’s been years since your
last visit.
Have you met someone in Dubai?
Get married soon.
You are already greying.
I have two kids already.
I married our classmate, Geeta.
The same Geeta you were after.
Look at your fate, man!
Geeta fell for you,
but I married her.
Your wedding was fixed with Varalu,
but Kishtaiah got in the middle.
When you like someone,
marry her immediately.
Otherwise, someone else will
snatch her… like I did.
But your horoscope is such.
Your horoscope is such.
Look at his horoscope!
Okay. Laugh now…
Come on, laugh! Cheese…
I tried to kill someone in Dubai
for laughing like this...
And they jailed me for
nine years.
That’s why it took me so long
to come here.
You want a smoke?
It doesn't suit you.
Geeta too is mine.
Spray this on your wife. You can
celebrate through the night.
You know...Kishtaiah, right?
Huh! I do, sir.
Hmm.
He is also my friend.
What is it?
We have reached home.
After how long!
Come!
Bless me, dad!
He hasn't changed a bit, brother.
-Yes!
Hey, had a comfortable journey?
-Hmm.
I heard they didn’t get married?
I mean…Kishtaiah…
and Varalu.
If she didn’t marry him for
nine years,
it means she won’t marry
him, right?
Why don’t you ask her once?
If she would marry me.
That’s a wrong question
to ask someone’s wife.
But why?
They said they are not married.
Whether they are married or not…
though they live in different houses...
He is her husband.
She is his wife.
Mom!
-Huh?
Have this vada, it’s hot.
-I don’t want it.
Pass me the kitchen knife once.
-Huh?
Why do you want a kitchen knife?
-Give it here, mom.
Oho...
Here!
Hey, hey, stop him.
Hey, hey, Dasu!
What is the kitchen knife for?
Do you want to kill dad?
Bloody! Why does he teach me
morals about Kishtaiah?
Hey, it’s our dad!
That’s wrong.
You call him dad? Ptui!
Do you know the humiliation
I face because of him?
Hey, Dasu!
Dasu!
What's the point in getting
angry with dad?
Look!
It's the girl that you want, right?
She is not married yet.
Marry her.
Do whatever you want.
Hmm!
Huh?
Who the heck are you?
Me?
Huh? It’s Dasu!
Someone entitled to see
your beauty long ago!
If you don’t leave right now,
I will make mincemeat of you.
It’s because of this.
It’s because of this that you
spotted me.
Do one thing, Varalu.
Imagine I am not here and start
from the beginning.
Ah!
-Huh?
I will hide myself right here.
Okay?
Damn!
Hey!
Ugh!
You...
Hey, Anji! Stop!
It is Mr Dasu.
It’s master’s youngest son.
Who cares who he is?
This bloody rogue...
Stop!
-Don’t do it.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Hey Anji!
Come on!
Hey, Dasu!
-Hey!
What happened?
-What happened?
Hey!
Finish him!
Husband!
Hey, Dasu!
Hey…
Kishtaiah!
Go, man!
"My goodness gracious"
Hey!
-Hey!
"My goodness gracious"
Mom!
-Hey!
Hey, Hey! Anji! Anji!
Hey, stop it. Stop it.
I will see his end.
-Anji…
He is our master’s son.
Leave him.
Do you know what he did?
What did he do?
Nothing. Let's go.
Someday I will get hold of him.
-Fine. Let's go.
Stop…
-Hey...
Hey…
Hey!
Hey, Kishtaiah, stop it.
Stop, Kishtaiah. Stop. Kishtaiah, stop!
Hey, stop!
-Hey, stop Dasu.
I don’t know about these two.
But if I don’t kill you both
by next festival...
I am not my dad’s son.
Hey!
You kicked Anji on his chest.
And yet if you are alive,
it's because you are Master's son.
Or else, before this festival itself…
My goodness gracious!
As if last year's ruckus wasn't
enough, Das is back in the village.
The bonfire made every Pongal
dies down by evening.
But Dasu has been burning
for a year.
If he were not master’s son,
he would have died a year ago.
I know…
Who knows?
Big people have a lot of money.
They are capable of anything.
What's wrong with him?
Aunt!
There he goes.
-Why is he like that?
How is your Kishtaiah doing?
I told you not to come.
Why did you still come?
I have come to give him
a huge gift for his wedding.
Huh!
Why is the little one’s face fallen?
Look at him, brother.
I have been asking him to buy
her clothes for the festival.
But he wouldn’t respond.
I wonder if he would buy at least
for the chariot festival.
What, man?
Sinni!
Let’s go shopping. Come.
Don’t, brother.
If you take her and buy her
a frock,
both of them will have a ball
with me until the next festival.
Once these sweets are ready, I’ll
go buy the clothes myself, brother.
Tsk! Hey!
Decide which of you would
call me brother.
Come, dear.
Let us go, buy mango jelly.
You had it good.
Hey! Who is that?
What are you doing?
-Husband!
-Stop!
Stop!
What is this inauspicious incident
on a festival day?
Hey, why do you cry?
Which man in this village is macho
enough to put us on the bier?
Hey!
Why did you send biers
to Kishtaiah’s house?
Have you lost your mind?
Huh?
He beat up your youngest son
last festival. Don’t you remember?
You only talk about Kishtaiah
beating him.
Has he told you what he had
done yet?
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
I am not sure whether we are
your sons or they are.
A hen is much better than you.
If someone goes near her chicks,
it pokes them to death.
He is the rooster who
protects us.
I know our own roosters
won't work.
So, I am getting hunting dogs
from jail.
They don't hear your
rooster's name.
They only see its head.
Cut throat criminals who
slit throats and drink the blood.
Greetings, sir.
-Ah…!
Anji and Kishtaiah...
I will talk to my boys
and get back to you.
Hmm.
We have to go past Kishtaiah
to kill Anji.
That is tough enough.
To kill Kishtaiah is walking
to death.
Kishtaiah is a life size weapon
and who can stop him?
It’s very difficult.
You better drop this idea too.
We take leave.
Who do you think he is?
Kishtaiah!
Damn!
Hey, Subbaiah…
-Yes, Kishtaiah…
A festival is all about chicken curry-
-Hmm.
Vada and a bottle of drink.
Of course.
Where is your drink?
-Kishtaiah!
I finished it long ago.
He has sent biers home, Kishtaiah.
-Hmm.
Hey, what is this nuisance?
Kishtaiah, they sent home biers.
Then tell me...what shall we do?
Let's take a sip.
Then uncap the bottle.
Yay!
“When the girl gives you a nod
-and the love track takes off”
“When the monthly salary at rice mill
-gets a hike that’s unexpectedly high”
“When your favourite hero’s
film…”
“Runs house full”
“When India…
-Clinches the cup”
“And the wife...
-makes a compromise”
“When your neighbour runs
into loss..."
"and you get a chance to
wipe his tears”
“What should we do?
-Uncap the bottle”
“What should we do”
“Do take a sip
and a sip after sip”
“When you are bored, try beer
when you are pained, try brandy”
“When you are vexed, have whisky,
when mood is out, drink all the three”
“With your wife, down the toddy
With your brothers, have some gin”
“Whoever calls you bro,
Have a drink mixed in soda”
“Whoever is close to you
always have it raw”
“When someone older than
you comes”
“Butter up but drink in secret”
“The first peg makes you
feel intoxicated”
“With the second peg,
your body begins to float”
“When the third, fourth and
fifth pegs go down the throat”
“My goodness gracious”
“Strange things happen”
“The kitten in the backyard
begins to say bow-wow”
“The fish in the well is
found smoking cigar”
“The fan in your hand looks like
a piece of chicken”
“The grinding stone in the corner
becomes a plate of silver”
“Ninety rupee note slips
from your pocket"
"The checkered lungi on you,
becomes a shirt”
“Grandpa dead a year ago
appears and…”
“Hey, boy! Aren’t you eating?
Not drinking anything?”
“You have gone so thin!
What is happening?”
“He greets you thus”
“And warns you with love”
“The guy who invented liquor,
Wherever he is…”
“Hey, the guy who invented liquor
“To his eyes, nose, and ears
to his feet, mouth and arms”
“I bow in respect…
-Hey, we bow in respect”
“What should we do?
-Uncap the bottle”
“What should we do?”
“Do take a sip
and a sip after sip”
For me, for me, Kishtaiah!
Kishtaiah, for me.
Hey…
Brother…
-Hmm.
I have a doubt.
-What is it?
How would Kishtaiah and Varalu
know about each other every day?
Like Narada in the Puranas,
there is someone here.
Who is it?
-It’s me!
Oh, no! Oh, no! How nasty!
Get up! Get up. Take it off.
Remove it from here. Up!
Hey, don’t you understand?
-What is your problem?
Remove this crap and throw it
into fire. Make it fast!
Brother…I have another doubt.
-What?
How is Varalu able to live alone
for eight years?
What could she do?
Unable to stay alone at home,
she prays to God in the morning.
She cooks rice in the afternoon.
And at night…
She serves me drinks like this.
Hmm.
Here…
Manga has sent this for you.
What is he up to?
Your brother?
Only yesterday, he beat 20 guys
to pulp in the mango grove.
Does he feel he is still young?
Ask him to slow down.
Why should he?
Kishtaiah is ever green.
How can you praise him
sipping at my drink?
If you want to praise him,
keep the glass down.
Were the injuries too bad?
Why do you stare without
answering?
Attend to that, first.
No injuries for my brother.
They had very bad injuries.
Who did you think I was
asking about?
Who is this boy?
He's Bhaskar.
One of my boys.
He is in love with president’s
daughter from the other village.
Yesterday’s fight was about
this guy.
Master has left him with us
for safety.
What now?
If something happens to this boy,
your macho man is going to save him?
What do you think?
Who is man enough to
beat Kishtaiah?
By the way…
I noticed it the other day…
Has his hair gone a bit grey?
Your brother’s?
I have been telling him, Varalu,
to colour his hair.
Hey! He looks better this way.
Keep it.
When you love him so much,
why don’t you marry him?
This bloody old...
That’s it.
Every evening…she serves me drinks
and keeps asking about my brother.
If I praise him, she scolds me.
If I say nothing, she sulks.
What about brother?
Let's go. I'll tell you.
Look there.
Watch our hero make his entry.
At the same time, the heroine
also steps out. Watch.
He will send a whiff of smoke
in her direction.
Watch our heroine's hair wave
because of the smoke.
A whole day of wait for a moment
of looking at each other?
A moment is not enough.
That’s why she grooms pigeons.
-What are the pigeons for?
To make our guy look at
her longer,
she wakes up the sleeping
pigeons and feeds them.
Great lady!
They are just pigeons with tiny
stomachs. How much can they eat?
That’s why… she pours two pegs for
the plants just like she offers to me.
“Further and further…
as distance keeps vanishing”
She will unlock the gate and relock.
“Further and further…
as souls keep coming close”
“A strange feeling
peeps into the heart”
“Erasing all silences”
That’s all.
When it’s night, we go for a drink.
But their story doesn’t
move ahead.
They are just a call away.
-“And greeting in words”
But it’s been ten years
since the call was heard.
"Looking at you..."
-They pretend to be happy.
"looking at me..." -But they go through
hell within. Wanting to say this..."
"Wanting to say..."
Come. Let’s go.
“It makes me feel…”
“What?”
“That past wouldn’t come back
That there is no tomorrow”
“That right now I am yours”
“That past wouldn’t come back
That there is no tomorrow”
“That right now I am yours”
Why are you here?
I felt like seeing you.
You saw me when I was
locking the gate.
Not enough?
What?
My life is here and what would
I do on the other side of the wall?
Hmm!
Enough with your sweet talk.
Hey! Come here.
“That past wouldn’t come back
That there is no tomorrow”
“That right now I am yours”
What curry is this? Murrel?
Hey, Varalu!
Wear some short clothes
just once.
You deserve a good lesson.
You!
Hey. Come here.
Are you not going to change ever?
The tree before your house
has changed.
This village has changed.
Even Anji has a daughter
and his life has changed.
Give it a thought.
May be your dad would be
born as our kid.
Do you want me to have a couple
of cardamoms and come?
Hmm?
You…
I am going to kill you!
Stop there!
Kumari...
Kumari! Look here once.
Don't look at me like that.
Like a gaff fitted fighter cock...
I will get slashed.
Why are you going away?
But uncle's upbringing
is commendable.
Fish in the pond and daughter at home...
See, how systematically he raised both!
Hey, brother!
When are you sending your daughter
to my house as my daughter-in- law?
When she was born, I never
thought a daughter was born.
I thought your daughter-in-law
was born.
Dad...
Bhasker and I...
Another word from you and
I will throttle you to death.
As a dad who killed his own daughter
for falling in love with the enemy...
my reputation will be intact.
What’s the point in throttling
her neck now?
You don't know how to take care of
shrimplets that reached count stage
or girls who have come of age.
When she went out smiling
wearing flowers, I knew...
That she was going to make
a fool of you and me.
Hey! What is your confidence?
That Kishtaiah would come
to the rescue?
Tomorrow is the chariot festival.
They have to bring their chariot
to our village as per tradition.
As long as that village supports
your love,
so long I shall obstruct
those chariots..
If I don't, stop calling me
Jakkannakota Veerabhadrudu.
Greetings, Sir!
Every Kanuma, the tradition of
carrying chariots to Jaggannathota
has been in vogue for 400 years.
Twenty five years ago when it stopped,
entire village was swept away by floods.
Let us not mess with God, master.
Yes, sir!
This is like two bulls fighting
and crushing a calf by the side.
As this Bhaskar is in love with
Veerabhadrudu's daughter,
should the whole village pay
the price?
No point in blaming him.
Blame the person protecting him.
This village is like a mother to me.
If Injustice is done to the village
or Master is humiliated,
consider Kishtaiah dead that
very moment.
Kishtaiah makes you all a promise.
If they block our chariots from
going through Jaggannathota...
My goodness gracious!
It's not a river that our Lord Shiva
would cross. But, a river of blood!
Why should we get into
a fight, sir?
Collector sir has come to
Amalapuram.
Let us settle this before
the Collector.
Hmm.
Hey!
-Hey!
You tell me Mr Peddaiah.
What is the issue?
Collector sir,
how is he a gentleman?
He is protecting the guy
who had jumped over my wall.
Hey,
if you blabber as you like,
I will cut off your tongue.
Put an end to this and let
the chariots pass through.
Huh?
What if we don't allow them?
What would you do? Huh?
If you don’t allow them what I…
-Kishtaiah.
When the procession was stopped
25 years ago there were disastrous floods.
And it is still discussed in
our village.
This time, your village would
remember that Kishtaiah came.
Collector Sir,
Bhaskar is well educated and
a good boy.
That's why we are supporting him.
Hey! If you find him so good,
send him a girl from your family!
Hey,
I'll hack you down
if you cross your line.
You think we’re cowards?
-Hey, you think you can hack away?
And we will sit watching you do it?
Come on!
Hey!
-Come, let’s have it out.
Hey, stop it.
Hey SI,
this is an issue related to
our two villages.
You have nothing to do here.
Get going.
Stop! Stop!
If it was a fight you wanted,
why did you even come to me?
Mr Veerabhadrudu, you tell me.
To allow the procession through
your village, what are your conditions?
Collector sir,
there's tradition in
both our villages.
Whoever commits a mistake
in either of our villages,
the culprit's supporter...
...must fall at the feet of the other
Person and ask for his forgiveness.
You decide now...
Who should come forward
to touch whose feet...
Collector sir,
I understand their intention.
I’m ready to do anything for
the village.
Master, how can you touch
his feet?
He doesn't have to do that.
You stand in support of
your village.
You can come instead and do it.
Hey!
Come, come on!
Yay!
Brother, the job you assigned
is done.
Otherwise we will be blamed.
Move!
Uncle! Kumari has run away
with that Bhaskar.
If your daughter herself has left,
you can't find fault with them.
Hey, did you expect us to
touch your feet?
I'll make you wash the feet
of the boy from our village.
And what sort of president
are you?
This could be resolved between us
but you involve the village and God!
Mr Collector!
Our chariots will go to his village
in a procession this time.
If you pull these tricks again…
My goodness gracious!
I almost forgot...
Happy Sankranthi to you all.
What’s this?
-Hey, shut up!
“The girl in one chair…”
“The boy in another…”
“Supporting their love
have come forward”
“Friends and relatives,
siblings and cousins"
Babies and toddlers,
and youthful gangs”
“Young and old, men and women
all come together to celebrate…”
“Great, gala party”
“Great, great, gala party”
“A noisy, gala party”
“Hey, it’s a grand gala party”
“Some whistle so loud,
some make a big noise”
“They scream aloud
Some shout out”
“More than screams, shouts,
the mischief and all the hubbub”
“Sound high in the couple’s heart
the drums of love and beats of amor”
“Hear it…”
“When you hear the rhythm…”
“Great, gala party”
“Great, great, gala party”
“A noisy, gala party”
“Hey, it’s a grand gala party”
“Great, gala party”
“Great, great, gala party”
“A noisy, gala party”
Varalu!
When beautiful girls like you
roam alone at night this way,
boys like me turn into criminals.
Sound horn if you have
the guts now.
You rogue!
What do you think of Varalu?
Huh?
Come, idiot!
Let me first deal with Kishtaiah
and then I will take care of you.
Be patient till then.
Come on!
Huh?
Hey Bhaski, this shirt would
Look better on me.
This is my wedding.
Yeah, right.
It looks very plain on you.
And you are also quite
plain looking.
Dad, dad! I want a white frock.
Excuse me!
Please, take out that white frock.
This one, sir?
-No, not that. The next!
This one?
-Yes!
Fold it and put it in cover.
You pay up.
Watch it today itself.
Watch it today.
Chiranjeevi’s ‘Manchi Donga’!
New film.
Hey Bhaski!
Wait, wait.
We got to shop for Kumari.
We can shop tomorrow.
Come fast.
Here, sir!
Come on uncle, louder!
Anji!
Sister, can you get me two tickets?
Make your wife stand in queue
and get them.
My wife is five months
pregnant, sister.
The doctor advised her not to
stand in queue for long.
Idiot! That’s my sister.
Oh, your sister!
Sister, I will buy you a soda.
Can you get me two tickets?
Okay, brother.
Here are your tickets, brother.
Bhaski!
Great trick!
Uh, here.
These are our seats.
Whoever placed a seat
in front of legs is a donkey.
Look straight.
Oh, crap!
If we watch Chiranjeevi’s film
without bidi, I will be blamed.
Rogues! Who are you all?
Show yourselves if you have
the guts.
Hey!
Bhaski! Go away!
I said go away!
Inform Kishtaiah.
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Come on!
Hey!
Wow!
What did he say?
Huh?
It’s not possible to kill Anji
while Kishtaiah is alive?
But we are hacking Anji here...
and why doesn’t Kishtaiah come?
Kishtaiah!
O, Kishtaiah!
What does that laugh mean?
Huh?
Hey Anji, come!
Hey, Dasu!
Dasu!
You saved my life
and I can’t kill you with my hands.
You are saved. Go!
Go on.
Hey!
Did you have a hope for life
for a moment?
When you kill someone who was
hoping to live… the high it gives…
Huh?
Manga!
Hey! No, no!
It's wrong.
She is your wife!
Hmm…!
Okay.
So, you want me to look after
Manga too!
Manga!
O, Manga!
-Dasu!
Dasu! Hey!
O, Manga!
-Dasu! Hey!
Anji…
Hey, hey! Anji!
Kishtaiah!
-Anji, Anji! I’m here.
Anji!
-Brother Anji!
Anji, talk to me.
Anji!
Hey, start the vehicle.
Hey, get the vehicle.
Anji! Anji!
Hey, careful!
Careful!
“Two bosom friends greeting
with intimacy”
Brother, go fast.
“Pulling each other’s leg and
having fun”
Brother,
Chitti insisted on
a frock all of a sudden.
Probabaly, she knew I’d be gone.
Varalu has no one except
you, Kishtaiah.
Varalu has restrained herself because
her dad told her something while dying.
Now I want her to marry you
and tell her this is my dying wish.
That might melt her heart.
"Time has brought them together
with love"
Brother!
What?
Has he sent this through you?
Wow, a frock!
Hey! Wear this
before your dad comes.
Okay!
What is this, brother?
He wants to roam around
even on the festival day.
Dad... here I come!
Hey, Bairi! Suri!
Hey! They have killed Anji, man!
Hey, they have killed Anji!
Hey! See what they have done
to Anji!
Oh, no!
Husband, husband!
-They have killed him, man!
Please, get up!
-They have killed him!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
What happened?
Oh, no! Oh, no.
Oh, no!
What happened? Speak!
What happened, brother?
Tell me, brother.
What happened?
How could he die
when you are with him, brother?
From tomorrow, only one of us
will call you brother.
Get up. Get up, husband.
Uncle, what happened to dad?
Dad!
Chitti is calling you.
Please, get up.
Dad!
-Please, get up.
Dad… what happened to you dad?
Hey!
Our Anji…
It’s our Anji!
This shirt would look better
on you, brother.
Take it.
Please, get up once, brother.
Brother Anji!
Pease, get up once.
Anji died because of me, dad.
Even before he died…
...more than about his wife and kids,
he spoke about me.
How do we deserve such people?
“God Himself…”
“In his own hand…”
Kishtaiah is all alone, dad.
-"Writes a beautiful poem"
Who else does he have, dad,
other than me?
I am going, dad.
Please, forgive me.
Not one man who had a hand
in Anji’s death should live.
But you... don’t die.
Tut! Why should we run away
fearing him?
Hey!
Everyone knows about Rama’s wrath
against Ravana who had abducted Sita!
But had Ravana killed Hanuman for Sita,
I can visualise this Rama’s wrath.
Just once...
For saving his honour just once,
he watched this house for years.
Before his loyalty turns into vengeance
and swallows you, run for your life!
But dad…
Hey, who do you think he is?
He is Kishtaiah!
He will kill you!
Run away…
Run away!
Kishtaiah, they're not allowing
our chariots through their village.
I believe someone has killed Anji?
I wonder why no one has come
to file a case.
How could they when the killer
is not alive?
You mean Das?
Why would he...
So, Kishtaiah is going to kill
Das too?
But there should be no case
against Kishtaiah.
He is committing a murder. And if
you don't want me to file a case...
Hey, girl… girl!
So much money is not necessary
for a single murder.
Did I say one?
You told me not to involve our villages
over something we can resolve between us.
Why did you come with
the villagers then?
Every Kanuma festival…
we sacrifice goats.
But this time…
we'll sacrifice you.
Attack!
After the procession this evening,
go, count the severed heads.
"Goodness gracious"
"My goodness gracious"
Kishtaiah!
Bhaskar!
Hey!
Hey, stop!
-Leave me, dad.
Leave me.
Kishtaiah!
O, Kishtaiah!
Hey!
Kishtaiah!
He said Anji could not be killed
as long as Kishtaiah was alive.
But I could kill him.
Now, I have killed Kishtaiah too.
None of Anji’s killers
should be alive.
But you... don't die.
“Abode of the destroyer”
"Abode of the destroyer"
"Lord Shiva comes for protection"
"This is his ferocious war"
"This is his protection from evil"
"Annihilating the monsters"
You keep chanting 'My Kishtaiah'.
But he is killing your sons there.
Master, you raised a snake
offering it milk.
He's killing everyone.
"He is in ferocious form"
"Against all the evil"
"This is the end of all demons"
"Protection for the humankind"
Your life was saved by Anji.
How can I kill you?
Live. Get lost.
Hey!
Did you hope for life for
a moment?
When you kill someone with
a hope to live, the high you get…
Hey!
My goodness gracious!
Master!
My sons are dead.
He killed my younger brother,
master.
So, are my sons
and that dog equal to you?
Hey! Master has killed Kishtaiah.
Hey, hey!
-Kishtaiah!
Hey, hey! Stop!
One step towards master
and I will kill you.
Get lost from here.
Go away.
Master, no problem.
You please go in.
Get inside! Please.
Go, master!
I'll kill you.
Kishtaiah!
Hey, don't cry.
Nothing happened to me.
After ten years,
you have asked me for something.
Not to die.
I wouldn’t die even after
ten more stabs from them.
Varalu!
Marry me.
Hey, Anji!
Daddy!
“Meddle with us, try to mess with us…
You will be in for a shock”
“My goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious”
“Cross your line, get caught by us…
You will be in for a shock”
“My goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious”
“When we say one, we mean the village
When we say village, we mean each one”
“When we say one…
-we mean the village”
“When we say village…
-we mean each one”
“With us…with us…
pick a fight with us and”
“Goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious”
“Goodness...
-gracious”
“Goodness gracious
-My goodness gracious”