1
00:02:40,823 --> 00:02:42,324
Get back, you lot.

2
00:03:00,509 --> 00:03:02,010
Get to the guillotine.

3
00:04:07,534 --> 00:04:09,453
The scourge of France!

4
00:04:38,916 --> 00:04:42,501
Terror is nothing more than justice.

5
00:04:42,502 --> 00:04:45,673
Prompt, severe, inflexible.

6
00:04:46,799 --> 00:04:51,512
It is therefore an emanation of virtue.

7
00:04:53,514 --> 00:04:56,684
Now, she was guilty of
three chargesagainst you:

8
00:04:57,851 --> 00:05:00,145
depletion of the national treasury,

9
00:05:01,397 --> 00:05:05,901
conspiracy against the internaland
external security of state,

10
00:05:06,985 --> 00:05:12,366
and high treason for actingin
the interests of the enemy.

11
00:05:15,786 --> 00:05:17,830
Mercy for the villains?

12
00:05:20,374 --> 00:05:21,375
No.

13
00:05:22,334 --> 00:05:25,003
Mercy for the innocent.

14
00:05:25,004 --> 00:05:27,798
Mercy for the unfortunate.

15
00:05:28,298 --> 00:05:30,592
Mercy for humanity.

16
00:05:34,763 --> 00:05:38,684
An inescapable outcomeof
democracy's connection

17
00:05:39,393 --> 00:05:42,979
in relation to the nation'simmediate
demands at this moment...

18
00:05:42,980 --> 00:05:45,566
The British navy have
takenthe port of Toulon.

19
00:05:46,066 --> 00:05:48,401
Half the French fleet is trapped there.

20
00:05:48,402 --> 00:05:51,780
If we lose those ships, the
Republic will fall.

21
00:05:52,865 --> 00:05:56,285
Lucky for us, there are only2,000
English troops in Toulon.

22
00:05:57,161 --> 00:06:03,584
But we are short of artillery and led
bya general who was a court painter.

23
00:06:04,501 --> 00:06:07,171
It is not necessaryto
recapture Toulon itself.

24
00:06:08,172 --> 00:06:11,383
The town is not a
town. The town is a port.

25
00:06:12,676 --> 00:06:14,969
If the harbor's untenableto
the English fleet,

26
00:06:14,970 --> 00:06:16,263
the town must surrender.

27
00:06:16,972 --> 00:06:20,558
My brother, Captain
Bonaparte, as artillery officer,

28
00:06:20,559 --> 00:06:24,772
has organized heated
shotsagainst English ships.

29
00:06:25,356 --> 00:06:28,233
He has proven his
commitmentto the Republic.

30
00:06:29,610 --> 00:06:31,612
And how do you propose to take the harbor?

31
00:06:32,404 --> 00:06:34,907
Capture the fortthat
dominates the harbor,

32
00:06:35,616 --> 00:06:36,950
and you have the city.

33
00:06:42,164 --> 00:06:46,085
We must make an example, or
other cities will fall.

34
00:06:47,753 --> 00:06:49,420
And I, for one,

35
00:06:49,421 --> 00:06:53,592
will never let the royalistsor
the English take my region.

36
00:07:06,605 --> 00:07:07,606
Morning, sir.

37
00:07:09,149 --> 00:07:10,150
General Carteaux?

38
00:07:11,568 --> 00:07:12,569
He's over there.

39
00:07:18,826 --> 00:07:22,663
Lucien, my dear brother, I
am in Toulon already.

40
00:07:23,956 --> 00:07:29,753
The troops are in a poor state, and
yourconscripts untrained and undisciplined.

41
00:07:30,504 --> 00:07:34,174
Without equipment and
resources, I see only failure.

42
00:07:48,814 --> 00:07:53,402
We are collecting scrap iron to recastsmall
mortars more suitable for my plan.

43
00:07:54,278 --> 00:07:55,738
If we do not succeed,

44
00:07:56,447 --> 00:08:01,242
those in power will only see us asCorsican
ruffians unfit for higher office,

45
00:08:01,243 --> 00:08:03,829
and our mother's
ambitionswill be quashed.

46
00:08:16,425 --> 00:08:19,510
That's it, madam. Fine eye you have.

47
00:08:19,511 --> 00:08:22,765
There you go.- I'll
still be here next week.

48
00:08:26,518 --> 00:08:30,397
The British control the big gunsthat
point out at their fleet offshore.

49
00:08:31,190 --> 00:08:35,736
Take those guns, and we can
fireonto them and end this blockade.

50
00:08:49,124 --> 00:08:53,087
Surprise is my advantage, but
I will win by fire.

51
00:08:53,754 --> 00:08:55,756
I cannot wait for your arrival.

52
00:08:56,422 --> 00:08:58,175
Your brother, Napoleon.

53
00:08:59,510 --> 00:09:02,720
Oi, shit rag! Yes, you!

54
00:09:06,724 --> 00:09:10,187
Move along now. Go on. Move!

55
00:09:12,648 --> 00:09:15,025
Move them fucking goats!

56
00:09:16,110 --> 00:09:19,613
Last chance! Fucking move them goats!

57
00:09:22,866 --> 00:09:24,910
You better fucking move them now!

58
00:09:26,370 --> 00:09:27,371
Do you understand?

59
00:09:43,637 --> 00:09:46,848
He sat himself down by the fire, my boys

60
00:09:46,849 --> 00:09:49,892
To join in our jovial crew

61
00:09:49,893 --> 00:09:53,062
Get in position.- Quick!

62
00:09:53,063 --> 00:09:57,316
By the chimney corner was his own place

63
00:09:57,317 --> 00:10:00,903
Where he could sit and dye his old face

64
00:10:00,904 --> 00:10:03,197
When Jones's ale was new, my boys

65
00:10:03,198 --> 00:10:04,699
Quick, quick!

66
00:10:04,700 --> 00:10:08,411
When Jones's ale was new

67
00:10:08,412 --> 00:10:14,917
Pints of beer and bottles of sherryTo
help them over the hill so merry

68
00:10:14,918 --> 00:10:19,214
When Jones's ale was new

69
00:11:10,724 --> 00:11:11,725
Fire!

70
00:11:14,853 --> 00:11:16,522
We're under attack!

71
00:11:19,817 --> 00:11:22,945
We're under attack! Grab your weapons!

72
00:11:25,155 --> 00:11:27,366
Get those ladders up quick, men!

73
00:11:40,254 --> 00:11:42,881
Fire! Hit your target!

74
00:11:45,342 --> 00:11:47,136
Get the mortars up there!

75
00:11:55,894 --> 00:11:58,355
Ready, boy?

76
00:12:01,859 --> 00:12:03,193
Oh, God!

77
00:12:12,661 --> 00:12:13,912
You all right?- I'm fine.

78
00:13:01,293 --> 00:13:02,878
Get the mortars!

79
00:13:12,513 --> 00:13:14,348
Protect the cannons!

80
00:13:17,810 --> 00:13:18,811
Into position!

81
00:13:24,441 --> 00:13:27,277
Vive la France!- Vive la France!

82
00:13:47,131 --> 00:13:48,506
Ready the cannons!

83
00:13:48,507 --> 00:13:50,092
Sir! Yes, sir.

84
00:13:51,051 --> 00:13:52,052
Mortars!

85
00:13:52,636 --> 00:13:55,681
Elevation 160.

86
00:13:59,101 --> 00:14:01,186
Fire!- Firing!

87
00:14:04,356 --> 00:14:06,566
Junot, heated shots!

88
00:14:06,567 --> 00:14:08,485
Fire!

89
00:14:22,166 --> 00:14:24,042
Junot, fire!

90
00:14:24,043 --> 00:14:25,544
Fire!

91
00:14:40,559 --> 00:14:42,770
Reload!- Reload.

92
00:14:46,940 --> 00:14:50,778
Fire!

93
00:15:06,585 --> 00:15:09,004
Shoulder, hold!

94
00:15:09,755 --> 00:15:14,802
Captain Napoleon Bonaparte, I award
you the rank of brigadier general.

95
00:15:18,806 --> 00:15:20,015
Long live the Republic!

96
00:15:20,599 --> 00:15:26,146
Long live the Republic! Long
live the Republic!

97
00:15:30,734 --> 00:15:34,822
I promised you brilliant
successes, and I've kept my word.

98
00:15:42,830 --> 00:15:45,165
Order, hold!

99
00:16:14,111 --> 00:16:15,320
For Mother.

100
00:16:21,285 --> 00:16:24,370
The current leadership of
France haspassed from enthusiasm

101
00:16:24,371 --> 00:16:25,789
to reckless ambition.

102
00:16:27,499 --> 00:16:31,420
And the public perceptionof the
guillotine is lawless passion,

103
00:16:32,087 --> 00:16:33,797
led by Robespierre.

104
00:16:34,590 --> 00:16:36,383
He is unfit to rule.

105
00:16:43,932 --> 00:16:44,933
Bonaparte.

106
00:16:47,311 --> 00:16:48,312
France!

107
00:16:48,812 --> 00:16:52,523
It has become increasingly
clear, Citizen Robespierre,

108
00:16:52,524 --> 00:16:57,279
that your motivations are to usethis
blade to your ultimate power!

109
00:16:58,822 --> 00:17:00,240
Let me speak!

110
00:17:01,867 --> 00:17:05,703
There is no man in this roomwho
has objected to my methods.

111
00:17:05,704 --> 00:17:10,209
If you say I am
guilty, you are all guilty!

112
00:17:11,794 --> 00:17:14,170
You are not a defender of freedom.

113
00:17:14,171 --> 00:17:20,760
You have deemed yourself judge, jury
and executioner, have you not?

114
00:17:20,761 --> 00:17:23,930
You're worse than
Caesar! Worse than Caesar!

115
00:17:23,931 --> 00:17:27,225
You are, all of you, the traitors!

116
00:17:27,226 --> 00:17:28,811
Arrest him!

117
00:17:45,076 --> 00:17:46,370
Get him.

118
00:18:11,979 --> 00:18:13,188
You missed.

119
00:18:16,316 --> 00:18:17,860
The guillotine, my friend.

120
00:20:48,886 --> 00:20:50,554
A seven, madame.

121
00:20:54,224 --> 00:20:55,351
Deal again.

122
00:21:06,236 --> 00:21:07,237
Deal again.

123
00:21:14,703 --> 00:21:15,788
Your bet.

124
00:21:26,757 --> 00:21:27,758
Seven again.

125
00:21:30,427 --> 00:21:32,262
No. No win.

126
00:21:35,307 --> 00:21:37,309
I'll be out first. That's mine.

127
00:21:47,319 --> 00:21:48,696
Why are you staring at me?

128
00:21:50,030 --> 00:21:51,031
Am I?

129
00:21:52,408 --> 00:21:53,492
No, I was not.- Yes.

130
00:21:54,493 --> 00:21:55,494
You weren't?

131
00:21:56,578 --> 00:21:57,579
I was.

132
00:21:59,039 --> 00:22:01,625
I was staring at your face.

133
00:22:03,085 --> 00:22:05,004
What is this costume you have on?

134
00:22:05,629 --> 00:22:07,089
This is my uniform.

135
00:22:08,841 --> 00:22:10,926
I led the French victory at Toulon.

136
00:22:18,058 --> 00:22:19,476
Do not tell me your name.

137
00:22:38,287 --> 00:22:39,288
General?

138
00:22:39,830 --> 00:22:43,166
There is a very young
man who wishesto see you.

139
00:22:43,167 --> 00:22:45,961
His name is Eugène Beauharnais.

140
00:22:55,179 --> 00:22:56,180
Citizen.

141
00:23:04,730 --> 00:23:06,065
General Bonaparte.

142
00:23:06,648 --> 00:23:07,648
Yes?

143
00:23:07,649 --> 00:23:11,904
My name is Eugène Beauharnais, son
of Joséphine Beauharnais.

144
00:23:12,654 --> 00:23:13,655
What do you want?

145
00:23:14,782 --> 00:23:16,200
My father's saber.

146
00:23:16,825 --> 00:23:21,246
It was taken from him beforehe
was arrested and executed.

147
00:23:22,247 --> 00:23:23,498
Yes?

148
00:23:23,499 --> 00:23:27,835
It would mean a great deal to me andto
my mother if it were returned to us.

149
00:23:27,836 --> 00:23:29,796
It's all we have of him.

150
00:23:29,797 --> 00:23:31,340
The sword is a weapon.

151
00:23:32,883 --> 00:23:35,969
I cannot allow citizensto have
weapons in their possession.

152
00:23:36,553 --> 00:23:40,140
The sword is a keepsakefor me
to remember my dear late father.

153
00:23:40,641 --> 00:23:42,726
Perhaps, but it is a weapon nevertheless.

154
00:23:46,355 --> 00:23:48,107
Young man, why are you here?

155
00:23:48,982 --> 00:23:52,861
My mother said that you were the only
manof authority to retrieve the sword.

156
00:24:05,332 --> 00:24:08,002
All of these arefrom officers
who were sentenced to die.

157
00:24:10,879 --> 00:24:13,007
Did no one thinkto attach
names to any of them?

158
00:24:15,134 --> 00:24:18,053
No, there are no names.

159
00:24:42,703 --> 00:24:43,829
General Bonaparte?

160
00:24:54,256 --> 00:24:55,341
Thank you.

161
00:25:02,139 --> 00:25:04,099
Is there reason to introduce myself?

162
00:25:06,060 --> 00:25:07,061
No, General.

163
00:25:07,895 --> 00:25:08,979
Good.

164
00:25:11,023 --> 00:25:13,525
My compliments tothe
chef of this fine family.

165
00:25:34,588 --> 00:25:36,256
Would you like to sit closer?

166
00:25:53,273 --> 00:25:54,983
Do I look like I'm in love?

167
00:25:56,485 --> 00:25:59,154
Do you find him without appeal?

168
00:26:04,284 --> 00:26:05,535
No.

169
00:26:05,536 --> 00:26:07,287
Then perhaps that is enough.

170
00:26:12,668 --> 00:26:14,753
Do not underestimate your grace.

171
00:27:05,637 --> 00:27:07,806
When you look at me, do
you see an aristocrat?

172
00:27:12,019 --> 00:27:13,020
No.

173
00:27:16,857 --> 00:27:18,901
My husband had more than one lover.

174
00:27:21,195 --> 00:27:24,073
And when his head was cut
off, all his mistresses watched.

175
00:27:30,996 --> 00:27:34,541
When I was in prison, I was told theonly
way to survive was to get pregnant.

176
00:27:36,293 --> 00:27:38,629
So, General...

177
00:27:45,094 --> 00:27:47,680
do I need warn you of my indiscretions?

178
00:27:49,640 --> 00:27:50,641
No, madame.

179
00:27:52,226 --> 00:27:54,311
Does where I have been concern you?

180
00:27:59,608 --> 00:28:00,609
No, madame.

181
00:28:18,168 --> 00:28:20,254
If you look down, you'll see a surprise.

182
00:28:21,630 --> 00:28:24,049
And once you see it, you
will always want it.

183
00:28:40,649 --> 00:28:43,861
People of France, don't be
fooled. There are more of us!

184
00:28:44,361 --> 00:28:46,530
We can occupy this Convention!

185
00:28:47,239 --> 00:28:52,411
Long live the king! Long live the king!

186
00:29:04,256 --> 00:29:06,466
No doubt you've seenthe
chaos in the streets.

187
00:29:06,467 --> 00:29:07,551
Yes.

188
00:29:08,469 --> 00:29:10,178
There is a belief amongst the Committee

189
00:29:10,179 --> 00:29:13,140
that there is an attackon the
Council coming by this mob.

190
00:29:14,475 --> 00:29:18,812
I have less than 4,000 troopsand
very little in the way of weapons.

191
00:29:19,855 --> 00:29:23,816
There are 40 cannons in Sablons. I
could have them here in three hours.

192
00:29:23,817 --> 00:29:25,819
This mob is 20,000 strong.

193
00:29:26,862 --> 00:29:27,863
Yes.

194
00:29:31,909 --> 00:29:35,995
As my second-in-command, what
would you intend to do

195
00:29:35,996 --> 00:29:38,791
if this assignment of
defensewas transferred to you?

196
00:29:45,547 --> 00:29:48,758
I accept, on the conditionthat
I command this as I see fit.

197
00:29:48,759 --> 00:29:50,427
Without interruption.

198
00:29:51,970 --> 00:29:53,889
I will not lead as second-in-command.

199
00:30:02,731 --> 00:30:03,857
Come on!

200
00:30:25,921 --> 00:30:27,047
Fire!

201
00:30:46,483 --> 00:30:51,530
According tothe law of
20th September, 1792,

202
00:30:52,322 --> 00:30:55,324
Marie-Josèphe-Rose Tascher,

203
00:30:55,325 --> 00:31:00,456
born 23rd June, 1767, in Martinique,

204
00:31:01,081 --> 00:31:05,293
accepts as her husband Napoleon Bonaparte,

205
00:31:05,294 --> 00:31:11,675
born February, 1768, in Ajaccio, Corsica.

206
00:31:13,469 --> 00:31:14,761
Do you consent?

207
00:31:14,762 --> 00:31:15,846
Yes.- I do.

208
00:31:16,347 --> 00:31:17,765
Do you consent?

209
00:31:20,559 --> 00:31:21,977
Yes. I do.

210
00:31:22,770 --> 00:31:25,647
I declare you united in marriage.

211
00:31:47,044 --> 00:31:48,920
To the savior of the Republic!

212
00:31:48,921 --> 00:31:50,672
And to Madam Bonaparte.

213
00:31:50,673 --> 00:31:52,257
To Madam Bonaparte.

214
00:32:10,442 --> 00:32:12,486
This guy right next to me?

215
00:32:24,957 --> 00:32:26,208
He wants my saber.

216
00:32:42,599 --> 00:32:44,935
Let that good work make us a son.

217
00:33:00,743 --> 00:33:02,077
Dear Joséphine,

218
00:33:03,037 --> 00:33:07,248
I follow in the footstepsof
Alexander the Great and Caesar,

219
00:33:07,249 --> 00:33:09,668
as I have been sent to liberate Egypt.

220
00:33:10,711 --> 00:33:12,962
I have 40,000 men,

221
00:33:12,963 --> 00:33:17,051
and the sights are wondrous, and
the weather is stifling hot.

222
00:33:18,719 --> 00:33:22,139
I have already conquered Italy, who
surrendered without conflict.

223
00:33:24,391 --> 00:33:27,435
The Directory has approvedmy
plan for attacking England

224
00:33:27,436 --> 00:33:29,021
through their eastern empire.

225
00:33:29,980 --> 00:33:33,859
But my achievements seem
slight, as they keep us apart.

226
00:34:01,011 --> 00:34:02,221
Dear wife,

227
00:34:03,180 --> 00:34:05,849
This love I have for
youis a kind of death.

228
00:34:06,767 --> 00:34:09,143
There is no survival for me except in you.

229
00:34:09,144 --> 00:34:10,645
Hello again.

230
00:34:10,646 --> 00:34:11,980
What are you doing?

231
00:34:12,564 --> 00:34:13,648
No letters from you.

232
00:34:13,649 --> 00:34:14,774
Good morning, Lucille.

233
00:34:14,775 --> 00:34:17,236
If you loved me, you'd
write me twice a day.

234
00:34:18,112 --> 00:34:20,530
Tell me there are no snakes in your bed,

235
00:34:20,531 --> 00:34:23,909
in your legs, inside what is mine.

236
00:34:25,160 --> 00:34:26,661
You must write me and tell me

237
00:34:26,662 --> 00:34:30,249
that you realize that I love
youbeyond the limits of imagination,

238
00:34:31,041 --> 00:34:33,252
that only you can please me.

239
00:36:54,268 --> 00:36:59,023
Are there limits to what I can tell you?

240
00:37:01,066 --> 00:37:02,109
There shouldn't be.

241
00:37:04,153 --> 00:37:07,156
Should I tell you somethingat the
risk of giving you personal pain?

242
00:37:09,241 --> 00:37:10,242
Yes.

243
00:37:17,374 --> 00:37:21,962
Your wife has takena lover
named Hippolyte Charles.

244
00:37:42,524 --> 00:37:44,777
You expect me to believe this?- Yes.

245
00:37:46,904 --> 00:37:48,697
That my wife would do this to me?

246
00:37:50,366 --> 00:37:51,367
Yes.

247
00:38:01,752 --> 00:38:04,129
No dessert for you. You may leave.

248
00:38:07,841 --> 00:38:09,093
I would never lie to you.

249
00:38:25,693 --> 00:38:26,694
How do you know this?

250
00:38:32,741 --> 00:38:36,537
Lucille is my lover. She writes to me.

251
00:38:38,080 --> 00:38:40,124
Joséphine's lady-in-waiting is your lover?

252
00:38:51,510 --> 00:38:55,264
Prepare two frigates and twosmaller
vessels in the greatest secrecy.

253
00:38:56,724 --> 00:38:58,058
I'm returning home.

254
00:38:58,684 --> 00:38:59,685
Napoleon,

255
00:39:00,436 --> 00:39:02,438
this will be seen as desertion.

256
00:39:05,149 --> 00:39:08,736
General Kléber will be informed ofhis
succession in command after I've left.

257
00:39:17,870 --> 00:39:20,164
Napoleon the victorious!

258
00:40:10,714 --> 00:40:11,964
Where's my wife?

259
00:40:11,965 --> 00:40:13,801
She has left to greet you in Lyon.

260
00:40:14,551 --> 00:40:16,470
Do not lie to me. Where is my wife?

261
00:40:17,012 --> 00:40:18,763
She left earlier today, General.

262
00:40:18,764 --> 00:40:20,723
Lyon?- Yes, sir.

263
00:40:20,724 --> 00:40:23,936
The entire world knows of
my arrival, but not my wife?

264
00:41:14,361 --> 00:41:16,280
What kind of creature are you?

265
00:41:19,408 --> 00:41:23,912
How could you care so
littlefor me and my feelings?

266
00:41:25,289 --> 00:41:27,875
You are a selfish little pig.

267
00:41:30,336 --> 00:41:32,338
Do you think so lowly of me?

268
00:41:33,672 --> 00:41:35,548
No. I don't.

269
00:41:35,549 --> 00:41:36,633
Then why?

270
00:41:39,386 --> 00:41:42,431
Because you're what? Say it.

271
00:41:46,685 --> 00:41:47,686
I'm sorry.

272
00:41:48,604 --> 00:41:49,855
That's not enough.

273
00:41:51,690 --> 00:41:54,609
What do you want me to
say?- I want you to say

274
00:41:54,610 --> 00:41:57,988
that I am the most
important thingin the world!

275
00:41:59,156 --> 00:42:00,323
You are.

276
00:42:00,324 --> 00:42:02,867
Say it!- You're...

277
00:42:02,868 --> 00:42:07,622
You're the most important thingin
my life, in the world. You a...

278
00:42:07,623 --> 00:42:11,042
And without me, you are
nothing.- I'm nothing.

279
00:42:11,043 --> 00:42:12,795
And you will do anything!

280
00:42:13,879 --> 00:42:15,214
I'll do anything.

281
00:42:18,759 --> 00:42:20,386
I'm not built like other men.

282
00:42:23,764 --> 00:42:26,100
And I'm not subject to petty insecurity.

283
00:42:31,772 --> 00:42:33,065
You're a beast.

284
00:42:37,820 --> 00:42:39,196
I feel sorry for you.

285
00:42:43,534 --> 00:42:44,827
You want to be great?

286
00:42:52,668 --> 00:42:55,087
You are nothing without me.

287
00:42:56,630 --> 00:42:57,631
Say it.

288
00:43:06,015 --> 00:43:07,099
Say it.

289
00:43:13,272 --> 00:43:18,694
You are just a brutethat
is nothing without me.

290
00:43:20,070 --> 00:43:24,032
I am just a brutethat
is nothing without you.

291
00:43:24,033 --> 00:43:24,992
Yes.

292
00:43:24,993 --> 00:43:31,749
You are nothing without me or your mother.

293
00:43:35,419 --> 00:43:36,503
My mother...

294
00:43:51,435 --> 00:43:52,603
Did you have affairs?

295
00:43:55,314 --> 00:43:56,315
Of course I did.

296
00:44:03,655 --> 00:44:05,115
And did you love them?

297
00:44:06,742 --> 00:44:08,786
No. No, I did not.

298
00:44:15,084 --> 00:44:16,210
Were they pretty?

299
00:44:18,420 --> 00:44:20,255
Yes, some of them.

300
00:44:23,258 --> 00:44:24,760
They served their purpose.

301
00:44:27,012 --> 00:44:28,013
More than I do?

302
00:44:28,972 --> 00:44:32,810
They cried less. That made
them more attractive.

303
00:44:36,230 --> 00:44:37,231
Don't...

304
00:44:38,565 --> 00:44:41,110
Don't leave me. Please, don't leave me.

305
00:44:44,905 --> 00:44:46,407
Just don't leave me.

306
00:44:48,158 --> 00:44:51,245
You don't have to forgive me. Just
promise me you won't leave again.

307
00:44:57,001 --> 00:45:00,713
What is it that made you
desertyour troops in Egypt?

308
00:45:04,216 --> 00:45:05,217
Citizens...

309
00:45:07,511 --> 00:45:08,762
what country are we in?

310
00:45:12,558 --> 00:45:15,561
Because she doesn't
resemblethe France that I left.

311
00:45:19,064 --> 00:45:22,151
Who should be responsiblefor
her governance while I'm away?

312
00:45:23,777 --> 00:45:25,904
Because it is not you, Citizen Gohier.

313
00:45:26,739 --> 00:45:27,739
It is not you.

314
00:45:27,740 --> 00:45:31,535
It certainly is not you. Although
you're very good at scowling.

315
00:45:34,371 --> 00:45:36,581
It is not you, Barras.

316
00:45:36,582 --> 00:45:37,708
Or you, Talleyrand.

317
00:45:39,126 --> 00:45:40,127
Or you, Sieyès.

318
00:45:41,670 --> 00:45:42,671
So, who?

319
00:45:44,173 --> 00:45:46,800
Who should be responsible? Fouché,
do you have any ideas?

320
00:45:48,177 --> 00:45:49,178
No?

321
00:45:51,388 --> 00:45:54,183
I have returned to
Franceto find her bankrupt.

322
00:45:55,601 --> 00:45:57,936
Printing money that is spent within hours,

323
00:45:59,855 --> 00:46:02,149
the Austro-Russian overrun of Italy,

324
00:46:03,233 --> 00:46:05,486
the Anglo-Russian occupation of Holland,

325
00:46:06,236 --> 00:46:12,117
and what appears to bethe imminent
invasion of France herself.

326
00:46:15,079 --> 00:46:18,582
And yet, you accuse me of desertion.

327
00:46:20,000 --> 00:46:23,379
Added to which the
discoverythat my wife is a slut.

328
00:46:36,558 --> 00:46:41,730
The only thing that every French citizencan
agree on is that you are our Caesar.

329
00:46:45,317 --> 00:46:46,318
What do you want?

330
00:46:50,406 --> 00:46:51,407
Well...

331
00:46:53,867 --> 00:46:57,329
the people would accept my
ruleif I have your support.

332
00:46:59,707 --> 00:47:04,336
Like you, though, I believe
that the Directory is corrupt.

333
00:47:05,963 --> 00:47:10,884
But together, we can save this
countryfrom a restoration of the monarchy,

334
00:47:11,844 --> 00:47:14,096
and we can preservethe
ideals of the Revolution.

335
00:47:16,807 --> 00:47:20,561
And I think thata seizure
of power is possible

336
00:47:21,895 --> 00:47:23,730
with your help, at the right time.

337
00:47:23,731 --> 00:47:27,026
And I think this is the right time.

338
00:47:27,776 --> 00:47:30,446
So, you expect me to be your sword?

339
00:47:37,077 --> 00:47:41,915
I expect that a coup
d'état, well-timed, well-executed...

340
00:47:44,501 --> 00:47:47,463
could transfer powerinto
the hands of three consuls:

341
00:47:48,380 --> 00:47:49,673
myself, Ducos...

342
00:47:52,259 --> 00:47:53,302
and you.

343
00:47:55,971 --> 00:47:57,806
I'm inviting you to the winning side.

344
00:48:02,102 --> 00:48:04,645
It's a simple letter of
resignationwe would like you to...

345
00:48:04,646 --> 00:48:06,856
I am not signing anything.

346
00:48:06,857 --> 00:48:10,234
You can piss before I sign anything away!

347
00:48:10,235 --> 00:48:11,320
Gentlemen.

348
00:48:20,287 --> 00:48:21,705
Who's doing this?

349
00:48:23,040 --> 00:48:24,208
Good morning, Paul.

350
00:48:27,378 --> 00:48:29,505
I'm going to make this
very simplefor you.

351
00:48:30,506 --> 00:48:33,884
I have documents announcingyour
resignation from the Council.

352
00:48:34,510 --> 00:48:37,554
You must retirebefore you
have your breakfast, please.

353
00:48:38,806 --> 00:48:43,143
Tell them I return with joyto
the ranks of simple citizen.

354
00:48:45,104 --> 00:48:46,105
I shall.

355
00:48:51,360 --> 00:48:53,362
There are some gentlemen here to see you.

356
00:48:54,196 --> 00:48:58,117
Citizen Moulins, we havea letter
of resignation for you to sign.

357
00:48:58,992 --> 00:49:01,744
No. I am eating my breakfast.- No.

358
00:49:01,745 --> 00:49:04,497
I am enjoying a succulent breakfast.

359
00:49:04,498 --> 00:49:08,918
This is outrageous! I shall finishmy
breakfast before you touch me!

360
00:49:08,919 --> 00:49:11,839
No!- Enjoy your breakfast.

361
00:49:33,444 --> 00:49:34,737
Director!

362
00:49:35,571 --> 00:49:37,947
I believe the time has
cometo demand an explanation.

363
00:49:37,948 --> 00:49:39,033
Hear, hear!

364
00:49:40,409 --> 00:49:44,871
This emergency sessionis to
draw a list of nominations

365
00:49:44,872 --> 00:49:49,460
for a new Directoryto
deal with the threat...

366
00:49:50,169 --> 00:49:52,128
The threat of the royalists.

367
00:49:52,129 --> 00:49:54,339
We are being asked to pass a resolution

368
00:49:54,340 --> 00:49:57,259
forming a provisional
governmentto three councils:

369
00:49:58,385 --> 00:50:01,889
General Bonaparte and Citizen
Sieyèsand Roger Ducos.

370
00:50:03,474 --> 00:50:05,601
Where are the five
membersof the Directory?

371
00:50:07,811 --> 00:50:09,730
Have they magically disappeared?

372
00:50:10,356 --> 00:50:14,860
And we are here, surrounded by
troops, Isolated far from Paris.

373
00:50:15,527 --> 00:50:16,527
Order!

374
00:50:16,528 --> 00:50:19,448
This is becoming increasingly clear:

375
00:50:20,366 --> 00:50:23,243
that your brother, Napoleon Bonaparte,

376
00:50:24,453 --> 00:50:28,332
with his show of military
might, Is acting as an outlaw.

377
00:50:30,250 --> 00:50:31,584
I vow to solve this matter.

378
00:50:31,585 --> 00:50:35,421
And that this isa ridiculous
and poorly executed takeover.

379
00:50:35,422 --> 00:50:37,466
A power-hungry upstart.

380
00:50:37,966 --> 00:50:40,176
Enough!

381
00:50:40,177 --> 00:50:44,180
If there is any questionof what
is happening here, I will answer!

382
00:50:44,181 --> 00:50:45,556
How dare you!

383
00:50:45,557 --> 00:50:49,477
This is... You have
violated the constitution!

384
00:50:49,478 --> 00:50:51,605
You have...- Hold him!

385
00:50:52,189 --> 00:50:53,190
Get him!

386
00:51:00,948 --> 00:51:03,158
Arrest him!- Stop him!

387
00:51:04,868 --> 00:51:06,161
Oh, fuck!

388
00:51:11,667 --> 00:51:13,043
Kill him!

389
00:51:21,218 --> 00:51:22,219
Let me through!

390
00:51:25,014 --> 00:51:26,264
Right.

391
00:51:26,265 --> 00:51:30,436
We are being terrorizedby
deputies armed with daggers!

392
00:51:30,978 --> 00:51:34,439
And these madmen have outlawed themselves

393
00:51:34,440 --> 00:51:37,150
by their attempton the
liberty of this country!

394
00:51:37,151 --> 00:51:39,737
They're trying to kill me!-
They're trying to kill him.

395
00:51:40,237 --> 00:51:41,905
Open these doors!

396
00:51:46,535 --> 00:51:48,202
Let us out of here!

397
00:51:48,203 --> 00:51:53,125
I will kill my brother if he betraysthe
freedom of the French people!

398
00:51:54,585 --> 00:51:56,085
Get in there now!

399
00:51:56,086 --> 00:51:57,171
Fuck.

400
00:52:02,259 --> 00:52:04,386
Move. Get back. Back.

401
00:52:05,679 --> 00:52:07,056
Move it!

402
00:52:08,932 --> 00:52:12,061
Back. Move back.- Move back.
Out of the way.

403
00:52:12,728 --> 00:52:14,813
Move. Backwards.

404
00:52:21,278 --> 00:52:22,613
Good luck, brother.

405
00:52:33,332 --> 00:52:34,333
Stand aside.

406
00:52:47,262 --> 00:52:48,514
Shall we vote?

407
00:52:52,017 --> 00:52:53,018
Where are we going?

408
00:52:55,813 --> 00:52:57,731
All our harsh words are behind us.

409
00:53:00,567 --> 00:53:03,112
I need you to be my most tender friend.

410
00:53:06,949 --> 00:53:10,119
Over this door is our destiny.

411
00:54:26,862 --> 00:54:28,864
Present arms!

412
00:54:41,418 --> 00:54:43,504
First Consul.- My lord.

413
00:54:44,505 --> 00:54:45,506
Milady.

414
00:54:49,426 --> 00:54:51,302
Citizen Bonaparte.-
Citizen Bonaparte.

415
00:54:51,303 --> 00:54:52,929
First Consul.- Citizen Bonaparte.

416
00:54:52,930 --> 00:54:54,223
First Consul.

417
00:54:57,768 --> 00:54:59,061
Come, little one.

418
00:54:59,770 --> 00:55:02,690
You get into the bed of your master's.

419
00:55:16,120 --> 00:55:18,913
Hello, madame!

420
00:55:18,914 --> 00:55:20,582
Hello, good evening.

421
00:55:26,130 --> 00:55:27,755
Mother, the Duke of Avignon.

422
00:55:27,756 --> 00:55:29,008
It's good to meet you.

423
00:55:40,185 --> 00:55:41,520
Could this be Joséphine?

424
00:55:42,730 --> 00:55:45,357
Mother, Joséphine. Joséphine,
Mother.- Good to see you.

425
00:55:47,067 --> 00:55:48,152
It's Charles.

426
00:55:49,111 --> 00:55:50,112
This way.

427
00:55:59,747 --> 00:56:03,333
"Your Majesty, Englandand France
are wasting their prosperity."

428
00:56:03,334 --> 00:56:04,335
Let me try again.

429
00:56:06,837 --> 00:56:09,464
Your Royal Majesty, England and France

430
00:56:09,465 --> 00:56:12,343
are wasting their
prosperity...- Your Majesty.

431
00:56:12,968 --> 00:56:14,136
What did I say?

432
00:56:16,847 --> 00:56:18,432
"Your Royal Majesty."

433
00:56:19,683 --> 00:56:20,768
"Your Royal Ma"...

434
00:56:21,894 --> 00:56:25,689
Your Majesty, Englandand France
are wasting their prosperity.

435
00:56:28,067 --> 00:56:30,485
I am not ashamed to take the initiative.

436
00:56:30,486 --> 00:56:33,321
I have, I think, sufficiently
proven to the whole world

437
00:56:33,322 --> 00:56:36,241
that I do not fear the chances of war.

438
00:56:37,576 --> 00:56:41,872
But peace is my heartfelt
wishfor England and France.

439
00:56:43,290 --> 00:56:44,291
Read it back to me.

440
00:56:45,209 --> 00:56:48,711
I have notified all foreign powersof
your accession to the Consul,

441
00:56:48,712 --> 00:56:52,298
I have addressed lettersto
all diplomatic agents abroad,

442
00:56:52,299 --> 00:56:56,302
and I understand that you have
madefriendly overtures of peace to England.

443
00:56:56,303 --> 00:56:57,680
Caulaincourt.

444
00:56:58,722 --> 00:57:01,516
What I need from you
isa better understanding

445
00:57:01,517 --> 00:57:03,394
of the Russian Tsar Alexander.

446
00:57:04,103 --> 00:57:06,939
Would you consider the tsar
an allyto England or France?

447
00:57:08,732 --> 00:57:12,735
Well, I would think that his tradewith
England is more beneficial to him

448
00:57:12,736 --> 00:57:14,238
than his trade with France.

449
00:57:14,822 --> 00:57:18,950
And do you have a sense ofBritish
influence in the Russian courts?

450
00:57:18,951 --> 00:57:21,537
I do not, but I imagine
it is quite robust.

451
00:57:22,830 --> 00:57:23,914
Robust?

452
00:57:29,003 --> 00:57:31,839
What kind of man is he? Describe him.

453
00:57:33,424 --> 00:57:34,758
Well, he's young.

454
00:57:37,052 --> 00:57:38,052
He's vain.

455
00:57:39,638 --> 00:57:41,639
He's popular, and he wishes to remain so.

456
00:57:41,640 --> 00:57:42,808
He's popular?

457
00:57:45,602 --> 00:57:46,602
Really?

458
00:57:46,603 --> 00:57:50,315
His greatest fear is to be
killedin his bed, like his father.

459
00:57:52,651 --> 00:57:56,947
This makes him dangerously fickleto
whoever last has his attention.

460
00:57:58,073 --> 00:58:01,160
So he needs an allythat
he can also call a friend.

461
00:58:08,125 --> 00:58:09,335
No more bets.

462
00:58:13,005 --> 00:58:14,381
What a surprise.

463
00:58:15,049 --> 00:58:16,425
How nice to see you out.

464
00:58:17,509 --> 00:58:18,761
Excuse me, gentlemen.

465
00:58:19,261 --> 00:58:21,764
Good evening. I'm just
trying to lose some money.

466
00:58:23,182 --> 00:58:25,433
Well, after this hand, why
don't you come and join me?

467
00:58:25,434 --> 00:58:27,226
I'm at my usual table.

468
00:58:27,227 --> 00:58:28,479
That's a lovely idea.

469
00:58:30,522 --> 00:58:31,523
Good evening.

470
00:58:34,109 --> 00:58:35,110
Did you hear?

471
00:58:36,945 --> 00:58:41,867
Your Majesty received a letter of
peacefrom the First Consul today.

472
00:58:43,744 --> 00:58:47,330
Monsieur Talleyrand, if I may be honest?

473
00:58:47,331 --> 00:58:48,414
Of course.

474
00:58:48,415 --> 00:58:53,252
Austria's coalition with England isin
such a strong position against France,

475
00:58:53,253 --> 00:58:57,215
that these peace overtures are clearly

476
00:58:57,216 --> 00:59:00,052
only for your handlingof
French public opinion.

477
00:59:01,512 --> 00:59:02,680
Oh, my friend.

478
00:59:04,723 --> 00:59:06,392
You know me so well.

479
00:59:07,559 --> 00:59:11,020
Yes, it is true. It is public
opinion Napoleon is after.

480
00:59:11,021 --> 00:59:14,065
But my warning to youis
that he's as hungry for it

481
00:59:14,066 --> 00:59:16,234
as any man in the history of the world.

482
00:59:16,235 --> 00:59:18,111
So my suggestion, with respect,

483
00:59:18,112 --> 00:59:21,949
would be to takethis little
offering of peace from him...

484
00:59:24,993 --> 00:59:30,708
or suffer the consequencesfrom
a man bent on peace at any cost.

485
00:59:33,252 --> 00:59:35,963
The English ambassador, Lord
Whitworth, has arrived, Consul.

486
00:59:44,847 --> 00:59:48,058
Do not look at me as ifyou don't
know what I'm about to say.

487
00:59:49,768 --> 00:59:52,479
Are you aware of my letter
of peaceto your king?

488
00:59:53,272 --> 00:59:54,314
I am not.

489
00:59:55,774 --> 00:59:57,067
Shall I repeat it?

490
00:59:58,360 --> 00:59:59,778
No, you may not.

491
01:00:00,904 --> 01:00:03,281
Take this as a warning to your king.

492
01:00:03,282 --> 01:00:06,034
I will keep you guessing and scared.

493
01:00:06,035 --> 01:00:08,244
You will watch your borders and your back,

494
01:00:08,245 --> 01:00:11,247
and your manners are bound, sooner
or later, to be French.

495
01:00:11,248 --> 01:00:13,708
I will offer no more letters of peace,

496
01:00:13,709 --> 01:00:18,212
and I will take the lack of a
swift replyas an act of disrespect!

497
01:00:18,213 --> 01:00:21,425
You think you're so
greatbecause you have boats!

498
01:00:25,262 --> 01:00:28,098
'Tis a shame such a great
manshould have no manners.

499
01:00:41,487 --> 01:00:42,488
Yes?

500
01:00:45,074 --> 01:00:46,075
Are you pleased?

501
01:00:48,744 --> 01:00:51,246
Are you about to tell mesomething
that will make me angry?

502
01:00:52,206 --> 01:00:53,581
Let's hope not.

503
01:00:53,582 --> 01:00:58,295
The European families thinknothing
more of you than a Corsican thug.

504
01:00:59,046 --> 01:01:00,046
Therefore,

505
01:01:00,839 --> 01:01:04,510
I'm going to suggest somethingthat's
been a long time arriving.

506
01:01:05,552 --> 01:01:10,224
I suggest that you abandonyour
role as First Consul of France

507
01:01:11,183 --> 01:01:15,604
in exchange for the
title "Victorious Consul."

508
01:01:17,648 --> 01:01:20,067
By another name, "king."

509
01:01:23,028 --> 01:01:24,029
What?

510
01:01:25,614 --> 01:01:26,615
"King."

511
01:01:29,201 --> 01:01:30,202
Yes, king.

512
01:01:32,788 --> 01:01:33,789
King?

513
01:01:53,809 --> 01:01:55,686
My hair has been set.

514
01:01:56,770 --> 01:01:58,564
The way you like it.

515
01:02:02,401 --> 01:02:05,154
Oh, you filthy man. My
hair has been set now.

516
01:02:09,450 --> 01:02:11,701
I have the most beautiful wife.

517
01:02:11,702 --> 01:02:13,704
I... All right, come on then.

518
01:02:16,749 --> 01:02:17,750
Hat off.

519
01:02:24,965 --> 01:02:26,759
Give me your hand.

520
01:02:27,843 --> 01:02:29,678
You feel that?- What?

521
01:02:31,305 --> 01:02:32,430
Can you feel that?

522
01:02:32,431 --> 01:02:34,391
That's yours.

523
01:02:34,975 --> 01:02:36,100
It's yours.

524
01:02:36,101 --> 01:02:37,186
Thank you.

525
01:03:00,918 --> 01:03:01,919
Stop.

526
01:03:02,711 --> 01:03:04,088
Why aren't you pregnant?

527
01:03:08,384 --> 01:03:11,679
Is that a question, or
is that an accusation?

528
01:03:15,891 --> 01:03:17,101
It was a question.

529
01:03:19,478 --> 01:03:20,688
Now it's an accusation.

530
01:03:24,400 --> 01:03:27,403
Well, I've seen Dr. Corvisart, and
he has no answer.

531
01:03:31,782 --> 01:03:34,451
Only that I dowhat Madame
de Rémusat has done.

532
01:03:36,829 --> 01:03:37,830
Which is?

533
01:03:39,373 --> 01:03:40,374
Which is...

534
01:03:42,960 --> 01:03:45,670
along with hopeful
thinkingand a bit of red wine,

535
01:03:45,671 --> 01:03:48,590
he suggested I take the
watersat Aix-la-Chapelle.

536
01:03:52,052 --> 01:03:53,262
And why haven't you?

537
01:03:54,638 --> 01:03:57,515
As wife of the First Consul, I
haven't found the time.

538
01:03:57,516 --> 01:04:00,519
I spend many hours cleaning up after you.

539
01:04:05,065 --> 01:04:06,525
Find the time.

540
01:04:08,986 --> 01:04:11,697
I don't need to explainto you
the importance of this, do I?

541
01:04:12,656 --> 01:04:13,949
What, you want an heir?

542
01:04:14,742 --> 01:04:16,493
I want one now.

543
01:04:34,178 --> 01:04:35,596
Oh, my God.

544
01:05:24,311 --> 01:05:27,022
May God affirm you on his throne,

545
01:05:28,357 --> 01:05:33,320
and Christ give you to rule
with himin his eternal kingdom.

546
01:05:59,388 --> 01:06:02,683
I found the crown of France in the gutter.

547
01:06:04,685 --> 01:06:09,023
I picked it up with the tip
of my swordand cleaned it...

548
01:06:11,108 --> 01:06:13,235
and place it atop my own head.

549
01:06:39,845 --> 01:06:45,141
The most glorious, the
most august Napoleon,

550
01:06:45,142 --> 01:06:47,769
emperor of the French,

551
01:06:47,770 --> 01:06:51,190
is crowned and enthroned!

552
01:06:52,024 --> 01:06:56,320
Long live the emperor!

553
01:06:56,904 --> 01:06:58,822
Long live the emperor!

554
01:07:38,862 --> 01:07:40,655
I do not support this idea.

555
01:07:40,656 --> 01:07:43,408
You suggest divorce after years of debate.

556
01:07:43,409 --> 01:07:45,285
You can see that it has me divided.

557
01:07:49,498 --> 01:07:51,249
I am not ambitious.

558
01:07:51,250 --> 01:07:53,168
I've never declared war with anyone.

559
01:07:56,922 --> 01:07:57,923
No.

560
01:08:00,175 --> 01:08:04,512
You are the greatest leaderin
the history of the world

561
01:08:04,513 --> 01:08:06,557
and the world's only chance at peace.

562
01:08:11,603 --> 01:08:15,524
The security of the empire and peacein
the world depends upon an heir.

563
01:08:23,198 --> 01:08:24,533
It was an option.

564
01:08:26,452 --> 01:08:27,953
And I said it at the time.

565
01:08:35,210 --> 01:08:36,837
Are you enjoying yourself?

566
01:08:38,797 --> 01:08:42,258
I'm going to war to defend our people,

567
01:08:42,259 --> 01:08:44,803
and my wife cannot provide me an heir.

568
01:08:48,515 --> 01:08:51,185
If you do not bear me a child tonight,

569
01:08:52,978 --> 01:08:54,520
there will be a divorce.

570
01:08:56,899 --> 01:09:00,277
Hasn't been enough lovemakingin
this home to bear a child.

571
01:09:01,362 --> 01:09:02,696
Yes, there has.

572
01:09:04,656 --> 01:09:07,533
There have been years of it. Years.

573
01:09:09,286 --> 01:09:10,703
And with more than just me.

574
01:09:12,206 --> 01:09:15,583
And still you are empty.

575
01:09:15,584 --> 01:09:17,169
And you're fat.

576
01:09:18,962 --> 01:09:22,216
I enjoy my meals. I do.

577
01:09:23,132 --> 01:09:24,884
Destiny has brought me here.

578
01:09:24,885 --> 01:09:27,429
Destiny has brought me this lamb chop.

579
01:09:52,871 --> 01:09:53,872
Joséphine.

580
01:09:58,419 --> 01:09:59,420
Come then.

581
01:10:00,921 --> 01:10:01,922
Come.

582
01:10:08,636 --> 01:10:12,515
I love your talents and your taste.

583
01:10:14,768 --> 01:10:17,438
And while I'm away, I
will miss your grace.

584
01:10:18,188 --> 01:10:19,481
And your dignity.

585
01:10:20,774 --> 01:10:22,568
And I will come back to you.

586
01:10:56,602 --> 01:10:58,062
To today's victory.

587
01:10:59,396 --> 01:11:01,398
Look, I'm always here for you, Francis.

588
01:11:02,399 --> 01:11:05,694
But I must admit, I'm overwhelmedwith
the excitement of the battlefield.

589
01:11:06,737 --> 01:11:08,529
I should not deceive you, Alexander.

590
01:11:08,530 --> 01:11:11,742
This battle against him will
be brutaland terrifying.

591
01:11:37,518 --> 01:11:38,394
Come on!

592
01:11:38,395 --> 01:11:40,354
Get in defensive position!

593
01:11:50,823 --> 01:11:52,616
My good wife, Joséphine.

594
01:11:53,409 --> 01:11:57,121
My God, it's cold
here. I miss your warmth.

595
01:11:58,539 --> 01:12:02,167
On this day, we celebratethe first
anniversary of our coronation.

596
01:12:04,003 --> 01:12:06,672
My previous allyhas now
joined with my enemy.

597
01:12:07,798 --> 01:12:11,635
The Russian Tsar Alexanderjoined
forces with the prince of Austria.

598
01:12:12,720 --> 01:12:15,346
I have heard thathe's been
studying the art of war

599
01:12:15,347 --> 01:12:17,181
and trying to emulate my battle tactics.

600
01:12:17,182 --> 01:12:18,182
More fires.

601
01:12:18,183 --> 01:12:19,685
He tries to copy me,

602
01:12:20,352 --> 01:12:23,105
but he is a little boywho
will make a terrible mistake.

603
01:12:24,273 --> 01:12:28,235
I am certain I will bring the laurels
ofanother glorious victory to my army today.

604
01:12:29,278 --> 01:12:31,447
Yours, Napoleon.

605
01:12:46,920 --> 01:12:49,756
Hey, tie it from the back. Peg
that corner to the ground.

606
01:12:49,757 --> 01:12:50,841
That's it.

607
01:12:57,931 --> 01:12:59,141
Fuck.

608
01:13:55,906 --> 01:13:57,199
Your Majesty.

609
01:13:58,158 --> 01:13:59,660
We are discovered.

610
01:14:01,245 --> 01:14:02,246
Good.

611
01:14:03,664 --> 01:14:04,832
Tell the men to rest.

612
01:14:35,279 --> 01:14:40,284
I-N-F-S.

613
01:14:42,119 --> 01:14:43,370
Infantry sighted.

614
01:14:57,509 --> 01:15:01,013
I-M-T.

615
01:15:03,557 --> 01:15:04,767
Imminent!

616
01:15:07,478 --> 01:15:09,520
Stand to!

617
01:15:09,521 --> 01:15:12,273
Stand to!- Stand to!

618
01:15:12,274 --> 01:15:14,025
Stand to!- Stand to.

619
01:15:14,026 --> 01:15:17,320
Wake up, men. Get ready!- Stand to!

620
01:15:17,321 --> 01:15:19,073
Come on, get up!

621
01:15:46,558 --> 01:15:47,768
Wait.

622
01:15:48,310 --> 01:15:49,310
Ready!

623
01:15:49,311 --> 01:15:52,981
Wait! Let them thinkthey
have the higher ground.

624
01:16:39,028 --> 01:16:40,237
Fire!

625
01:16:43,532 --> 01:16:44,783
Fire away!

626
01:16:52,499 --> 01:16:53,709
Fire at will!

627
01:17:00,215 --> 01:17:01,299
Send in the infantry.

628
01:17:01,300 --> 01:17:03,760
Take their position on the
higher ground. At the double.

629
01:17:03,761 --> 01:17:06,638
Take the ground!

630
01:17:38,587 --> 01:17:41,298
Cavalry from the
west. Pierce their flanks.

631
01:17:55,312 --> 01:17:58,398
Retreat! Withdraw!

632
01:17:58,399 --> 01:17:59,983
Withdraw!

633
01:18:11,662 --> 01:18:13,122
It's a trap!

634
01:18:17,668 --> 01:18:19,336
Retreat!

635
01:18:57,624 --> 01:19:00,753
Uncover the cannons.- Cannons!

636
01:19:05,049 --> 01:19:07,301
Fire!- Fire!

637
01:19:11,180 --> 01:19:12,306
Reloading!

638
01:19:30,491 --> 01:19:32,201
Keep to the one side.

639
01:19:43,879 --> 01:19:45,589
Off the ice!

640
01:20:35,764 --> 01:20:38,475
Renounce, sir. We're pinned in.

641
01:20:41,061 --> 01:20:43,564
Off the ice! Withdraw!

642
01:20:50,446 --> 01:20:51,655
Cut off their retreat.

643
01:21:42,915 --> 01:21:45,709
Francis. So nice to finally meet you.

644
01:21:46,293 --> 01:21:47,878
Please come in where it's warm.

645
01:21:48,712 --> 01:21:51,130
Thank you.- You must forgive me.

646
01:21:51,131 --> 01:21:53,717
This has been my only
palacefor the last two months.

647
01:21:54,927 --> 01:21:58,930
Seems very agreeable. You
make excellent use of it.

648
01:21:58,931 --> 01:22:00,974
Well, we do what we
canon the battlefield.

649
01:22:01,767 --> 01:22:03,310
Yes, we do, don't we?

650
01:22:04,144 --> 01:22:06,313
It's nice to finally meet another emperor.

651
01:22:07,606 --> 01:22:09,857
Where, may I ask, is Alexander?

652
01:22:09,858 --> 01:22:12,318
Are we waiting for his
arrivalbefore we get started?

653
01:22:12,319 --> 01:22:16,114
I do not believe he will be joining us.

654
01:22:16,115 --> 01:22:18,701
He's beside himself with rage.

655
01:22:21,161 --> 01:22:25,374
I realize I must compliment youfor
making me commit an enormous error.

656
01:22:26,458 --> 01:22:28,210
An error?- Yes.

657
01:22:29,336 --> 01:22:30,754
What error have you made?

658
01:22:32,756 --> 01:22:35,884
To be speaking with you hereand
accepting this invitation for peace,

659
01:22:36,760 --> 01:22:38,470
I have not followed up my victory.

660
01:22:39,930 --> 01:22:43,183
I could have taken the whole
Russianand Austrian army prisoners.

661
01:22:46,103 --> 01:22:47,104
Yes.

662
01:22:47,813 --> 01:22:49,815
But after all, there will be less tears.

663
01:22:51,358 --> 01:22:55,696
And I know you will rememberthis
gesture of kindness. Yes?

664
01:22:57,114 --> 01:22:58,115
Thank you.

665
01:23:02,786 --> 01:23:03,787
Toast?

666
01:23:12,921 --> 01:23:19,386
To friendship, a glorious peaceand
the best interest of Europe.

667
01:23:26,769 --> 01:23:27,769
Burgundy.

668
01:23:50,793 --> 01:23:53,003
Hold on. Hey, whoa!

669
01:23:53,796 --> 01:23:55,422
Whoa, we don't say woof. Okay.

670
01:23:57,883 --> 01:24:00,968
That's my boy. Attaboy.

671
01:24:00,969 --> 01:24:02,596
Come here. Sit.

672
01:24:18,278 --> 01:24:21,365
It is time to put this
mystery to rest, Emperor.

673
01:24:21,907 --> 01:24:24,702
I want to know if it's you or Joséphine.

674
01:24:25,285 --> 01:24:32,084
And to that end, we will conducta
very practical experiment.

675
01:24:34,920 --> 01:24:38,090
At the end of the hallway... Take this...

676
01:24:38,966 --> 01:24:42,928
Waiting for you,
undressed, ready to receive,

677
01:24:43,887 --> 01:24:48,350
is 18-year-oldEléonore
Denuelle de La Plaigne.

678
01:24:51,520 --> 01:24:53,689
She's brunette with brown eyes.

679
01:24:54,273 --> 01:24:56,441
And the object of this, well,

680
01:24:56,442 --> 01:25:01,780
hardly unpleasant task is to
seeif you can father a child.

681
01:25:03,157 --> 01:25:06,993
And then we will have an
answerto this nagging question

682
01:25:06,994 --> 01:25:12,124
of who is keeping who from an
heirto the throne of France.

683
01:25:17,629 --> 01:25:18,756
Shall we go?

684
01:25:19,381 --> 01:25:20,716
May I have another, please?

685
01:26:20,567 --> 01:26:22,193
The girl is pregnant.

686
01:26:22,194 --> 01:26:23,737
You made her pregnant.

687
01:26:37,793 --> 01:26:39,169
I know I didn't see her.

688
01:26:46,385 --> 01:26:48,554
When are you going to insist we divorce?

689
01:26:50,556 --> 01:26:52,057
Isn't that wonderful?

690
01:26:53,892 --> 01:26:57,937
From the only woman that I've ever
lovedand given all that I've conquered.

691
01:26:57,938 --> 01:27:03,986
I'm just too tired to waitfor you
to tell me what I know is coming.

692
01:27:06,405 --> 01:27:07,656
If you insist.

693
01:27:11,368 --> 01:27:13,120
I'll make it easy for you.

694
01:27:19,418 --> 01:27:22,087
I know you will have a bastard child.

695
01:27:27,301 --> 01:27:31,096
If I succeed in making the birth of
a boythat I shall call my own son,

696
01:27:32,014 --> 01:27:35,976
I want you as a witnessto pretend
the confinement of the empress.

697
01:27:38,562 --> 01:27:39,396
Your Highness,

698
01:27:39,397 --> 01:27:42,941
you are asking me to lie about the
statusof the mother of your heir.

699
01:27:44,651 --> 01:27:46,653
That is another way of putting it, yes.

700
01:27:48,906 --> 01:27:54,661
Emperor, it is my honorand
my duty, of course,

701
01:27:54,662 --> 01:27:56,663
to do as you require of me.

702
01:27:56,664 --> 01:28:00,626
But if asked, I cannot containthat
which I know to be the truth.

703
01:28:01,669 --> 01:28:03,670
And painful though it is,

704
01:28:03,671 --> 01:28:08,258
the truth is that the empress isno
longer capable of bearing you a child.

705
01:28:19,603 --> 01:28:21,814
My good Joséphine.

706
01:28:26,652 --> 01:28:28,278
You know how I've loved you.

707
01:28:31,240 --> 01:28:34,618
It is you, to you alone,

708
01:28:35,828 --> 01:28:39,415
that I owe the few momentsof
happiness I have known in this world.

709
01:28:43,377 --> 01:28:47,131
My destiny is more powerful than my will.

710
01:28:49,216 --> 01:28:55,222
And my affections must yieldto
the interests of my people.

711
01:29:16,869 --> 01:29:20,122
The imperial decreefor the
dissolution of the marriage

712
01:29:21,290 --> 01:29:25,002
between the Emperor Napoleonand
the Empress Joséphine.

713
01:29:33,635 --> 01:29:38,932
"My people desire that this
throne, where providence has placed me,

714
01:29:39,475 --> 01:29:41,143
would be given to my children.

715
01:29:42,895 --> 01:29:47,065
However, I have lost hopeof
having children from my marriage

716
01:29:47,066 --> 01:29:49,818
to my beloved wife, Empress Joséphine.

717
01:29:50,819 --> 01:29:54,906
I have then been led to listenonly
to the good of the state

718
01:29:54,907 --> 01:29:58,410
and to want the dissolutionof
years of my life."

719
01:30:05,459 --> 01:30:10,172
You have embellished my life for 15 years.

720
01:30:12,424 --> 01:30:17,846
The memories of whichwill remain
forever etched in my heart.

721
01:30:34,196 --> 01:30:37,991
"Our marriage has become an
obstaclefor the prosperity of France.

722
01:30:40,703 --> 01:30:45,206
She has been deprivedof
one day being governed

723
01:30:45,207 --> 01:30:49,127
by the descendantsof the man
brought to us by providence

724
01:30:49,128 --> 01:30:51,672
to mend the evils of a terrible revolution

725
01:30:52,297 --> 01:30:55,676
and restore faith, the
throneand the social order."

726
01:31:01,640 --> 01:31:03,017
Sorry.

727
01:31:04,893 --> 01:31:07,478
Emperor. Wait.- Go. No, listen.
All right?

728
01:31:07,479 --> 01:31:10,315
This is for your country. That's
what this is, all right?

729
01:31:10,816 --> 01:31:11,900
Now say it.

730
01:31:13,360 --> 01:31:14,570
Say it.

731
01:31:21,285 --> 01:31:24,330
"Our marriage has become an
obstaclefor the prosperity of France.

732
01:31:26,332 --> 01:31:28,876
Agreeing to the
dissolutionof our marriage,

733
01:31:29,501 --> 01:31:31,962
as I must, does not change my feelings.

734
01:31:38,177 --> 01:31:44,516
The emperor will have in
mealways his truest friend."

735
01:32:18,634 --> 01:32:19,718
Emperor,

736
01:32:20,552 --> 01:32:23,722
you have just pronounced the
wordwhich separates us forever.

737
01:32:25,557 --> 01:32:28,143
Your mistaken ambition has ever been

738
01:32:28,811 --> 01:32:33,023
and will continue to be the
guideof all your actions.

739
01:32:33,899 --> 01:32:35,109
Nevertheless,

740
01:32:35,901 --> 01:32:39,363
you can never doubt the sincerityof
my wishes for your happiness.

741
01:32:40,614 --> 01:32:44,201
May it at least afford mesome
consolation for my sufferings.

742
01:32:45,327 --> 01:32:47,871
Yours, Joséphine.- Thank you.

743
01:32:48,539 --> 01:32:50,873
Good morning, madame.- Thank you.
What's your name?

744
01:32:50,874 --> 01:32:53,127
Fleur.- Fleur. Pleasure.

745
01:33:55,689 --> 01:33:56,690
I miss you.

746
01:34:02,154 --> 01:34:04,156
Marital life is very agreeable now.

747
01:34:08,952 --> 01:34:11,538
You've shown such great courage so far.

748
01:34:13,874 --> 01:34:15,376
You must maintain it.

749
01:34:16,794 --> 01:34:19,713
Do not permit yourselfto
fall into melancholy.

750
01:34:25,260 --> 01:34:26,970
You look best when you're happy.

751
01:34:31,809 --> 01:34:33,394
Please take care of your health.

752
01:34:34,395 --> 01:34:35,771
It is precious to me.

753
01:34:37,106 --> 01:34:38,440
Will you write me tomorrow?

754
01:34:42,820 --> 01:34:43,946
And the next day?

755
01:34:44,655 --> 01:34:45,656
Yes.

756
01:34:46,740 --> 01:34:47,866
And the day after that?

757
01:34:51,704 --> 01:34:53,539
And the day after that?- Yeah.

758
01:34:56,959 --> 01:34:57,960
Good.

759
01:35:08,220 --> 01:35:12,057
Once, an English ambassadorchallenged
my reasons for war.

760
01:35:12,725 --> 01:35:16,185
He said,"You French, you
fight only for money,

761
01:35:16,186 --> 01:35:18,439
while we English, we fight for honor."

762
01:35:19,606 --> 01:35:23,277
I replied,"Everyone fights
for what they lack."

763
01:35:26,655 --> 01:35:29,657
This is not your story. This
never happened to you, did it?

764
01:35:29,658 --> 01:35:30,700
Of course it did.

765
01:35:30,701 --> 01:35:32,160
Of course it did.- What do you mean?

766
01:35:32,161 --> 01:35:34,288
We had the same sayingwith
my people and the Turks.

767
01:35:34,788 --> 01:35:35,622
Do you?

768
01:35:35,623 --> 01:35:37,790
The English lack honor. We
can agree on that.

769
01:35:37,791 --> 01:35:39,126
Listen, there is...

770
01:35:41,462 --> 01:35:46,383
There's nothing I think we can agreemore
with than our hatred for Britain.

771
01:35:49,720 --> 01:35:54,223
I just have to say that it actually...

772
01:35:54,224 --> 01:35:57,811
It would be my absolute pleasureand
honor if I could call you my brother.

773
01:36:01,607 --> 01:36:03,609
There is a way for you to call me brother.

774
01:36:06,153 --> 01:36:08,947
Last night, at dinner, I was...

775
01:36:11,283 --> 01:36:13,619
charmed by your sister.

776
01:36:15,162 --> 01:36:16,163
Is she spoken for?

777
01:36:17,456 --> 01:36:21,877
Sadly, yes. She's to be marriedto
the Duke of Oldenburg, I'm afraid.

778
01:36:22,586 --> 01:36:25,547
And what of her younger sister? Anna?

779
01:36:26,298 --> 01:36:27,966
Is there a formal offer for Anna?

780
01:36:35,849 --> 01:36:38,560
Well, you see, Anna, she's 15 years old.

781
01:36:39,770 --> 01:36:40,938
That is a detail.

782
01:36:44,358 --> 01:36:48,946
Our friendship is built onour
mutual distrust of England.

783
01:36:49,655 --> 01:36:54,033
When we hold to the Continental
Blockade, we choke them from the trade,

784
01:36:54,034 --> 01:36:56,411
and we fight for our most sacred rights.

785
01:36:56,412 --> 01:36:58,664
That is what is important between us.

786
01:36:59,331 --> 01:37:00,332
I just had a thought.

787
01:37:01,000 --> 01:37:02,291
No.- No, say it.

788
01:37:02,292 --> 01:37:04,003
Should I tell you?- Please.

789
01:37:05,254 --> 01:37:08,007
Imagine an army. 50,000 men.

790
01:37:08,507 --> 01:37:11,759
Russians, Frenchmen, perhaps
even Austrians,

791
01:37:11,760 --> 01:37:14,554
marching by way of
Constantinopleinto Asia

792
01:37:14,555 --> 01:37:16,305
would have only to reach the Euphrates

793
01:37:16,306 --> 01:37:18,725
to make England trembleand
bring her down on her knees

794
01:37:18,726 --> 01:37:20,310
before the continent.

795
01:37:23,856 --> 01:37:25,024
It is incredible.

796
01:37:26,233 --> 01:37:27,234
Toast.

797
01:37:34,074 --> 01:37:35,576
To you.- To us.

798
01:37:36,785 --> 01:37:41,706
His Majesty, the Emperor Napoleon, wishes
to make a formal offer to Austria

799
01:37:41,707 --> 01:37:44,001
and to His Majesty, King Francis,

800
01:37:45,210 --> 01:37:48,505
for the handof the
archduchess, Marie-Louise.

801
01:37:50,174 --> 01:37:51,300
His eldest daughter.

802
01:37:52,634 --> 01:37:53,844
No.

803
01:37:55,137 --> 01:37:57,680
This union would bring
togetherAustria and France

804
01:37:57,681 --> 01:37:59,892
in an unbreakable matrimonial bond.

805
01:38:01,685 --> 01:38:03,687
Is this a joke?

806
01:38:06,065 --> 01:38:12,821
I may find it humorous... but
His Majesty does not.

807
01:38:30,714 --> 01:38:32,382
Did you have a pleasant journey?

808
01:38:32,383 --> 01:38:34,009
It was wonderful. Thank you.

809
01:38:40,182 --> 01:38:41,600
You're quite petite.

810
01:38:42,643 --> 01:38:43,852
I'm not accustomed to that.

811
01:38:47,731 --> 01:38:49,024
How do I look to you?

812
01:38:50,651 --> 01:38:52,403
Do I resemble my portrait?

813
01:38:52,986 --> 01:38:57,324
Oh, yes. And even more
handsome and strong.

814
01:38:58,617 --> 01:39:02,121
And you are even more
handsome, more beautiful.

815
01:39:04,289 --> 01:39:06,166
I hope you're pleased with your choice.

816
01:39:07,835 --> 01:39:11,005
I hope so too. Would you
like to see the bedroom?

817
01:39:11,922 --> 01:39:13,382
Yes, thank you.

818
01:39:25,853 --> 01:39:27,980
Your Majesty, your son.

819
01:39:47,458 --> 01:39:48,459
Hello.

820
01:39:52,796 --> 01:39:53,797
Fire!

821
01:40:02,348 --> 01:40:03,557
My little king.

822
01:40:16,904 --> 01:40:18,030
Hold.

823
01:41:16,380 --> 01:41:18,132
Oh, sweet child.

824
01:41:28,684 --> 01:41:34,356
One day, you will understandwhat
I have sacrificed for you.

825
01:41:44,366 --> 01:41:47,244
My dear Joséphine, I'm sad today.

826
01:41:47,786 --> 01:41:51,623
Tsar Alexander has turned against
meand forced me to invade Russia.

827
01:41:52,583 --> 01:41:57,421
He's decided to open his ports to
Englandwhile taxing the French.

828
01:41:58,756 --> 01:42:02,551
I must wipe away my melancholyand
begin the march to Moscow.

829
01:42:03,594 --> 01:42:06,471
I've convinced the heads of
Europeof this resolution,

830
01:42:06,472 --> 01:42:11,059
and so I command the combined
forcesof France, Austria, Italy,

831
01:42:11,060 --> 01:42:12,853
Germany and Poland.

832
01:42:13,437 --> 01:42:16,105
I see nothing but success in my future.

833
01:42:16,106 --> 01:42:19,068
Keep your lines. Steady.

834
01:42:21,403 --> 01:42:23,071
To the front.

835
01:42:23,072 --> 01:42:25,074
Keep your step.

836
01:42:31,664 --> 01:42:32,581
Take cover!

837
01:42:32,581 --> 01:42:33,581
Get down!

838
01:42:39,963 --> 01:42:41,757
Get down!

839
01:42:55,020 --> 01:42:57,064
After them!

840
01:43:38,272 --> 01:43:41,942
Get back! Drop back.
Retreat.- Fall back!

841
01:44:49,343 --> 01:44:51,261
My dear Joséphine.

842
01:44:52,846 --> 01:44:56,100
I'm writing to you because I have
just wona great battle today.

843
01:44:57,726 --> 01:45:00,020
Tomorrow we will resume our advance.

844
01:45:00,729 --> 01:45:03,106
Moscow is now only 200 miles away.

845
01:45:03,107 --> 01:45:06,652
And I think of you all
the while. All yours.

846
01:45:07,361 --> 01:45:09,196
Nearly there.

847
01:45:16,620 --> 01:45:17,621
Thank you, sir.

848
01:45:24,712 --> 01:45:27,631
Thank you, Admiral.- You
were the brave of Austerlitz.

849
01:46:32,654 --> 01:46:34,198
Where are you?

850
01:46:47,294 --> 01:46:49,588
300,000 souls lived in this city.

851
01:46:51,465 --> 01:46:52,841
And they've all just left?

852
01:47:12,027 --> 01:47:14,947
Little boy.

853
01:47:20,160 --> 01:47:21,704
Where are you?

854
01:47:26,166 --> 01:47:27,793
Don't be frightened.

855
01:47:28,627 --> 01:47:30,838
I'm just gonna give you a little spanking.

856
01:48:01,702 --> 01:48:03,203
It's not very sporting, is it?

857
01:48:05,080 --> 01:48:06,957
For his honor and Russia's, not mine.

858
01:48:12,379 --> 01:48:14,340
There's dignity to be had in defeat.

859
01:48:58,008 --> 01:48:59,009
Who did this?

860
01:49:00,427 --> 01:49:01,428
They did.

861
01:49:02,930 --> 01:49:06,141
No, they did not. Be sensible.

862
01:49:09,061 --> 01:49:10,437
Who set these fires?

863
01:49:12,272 --> 01:49:15,693
Your Majesty, they did.

864
01:49:21,323 --> 01:49:24,284
He'd rather burn his own
citythan negotiate with me.

865
01:49:25,077 --> 01:49:27,121
I didn't think he had the courage.

866
01:49:32,584 --> 01:49:38,132
Well, we'll go to Saint
Petersburgand have him burn that too.

867
01:49:40,009 --> 01:49:43,554
We have let too much time slip away.

868
01:49:45,264 --> 01:49:48,642
We would be marchinginto
the Russian winter

869
01:49:49,601 --> 01:49:53,647
with horses that are not
raisedfor this weather.

870
01:49:55,190 --> 01:49:58,444
If we go back to Poland, we can
wait out the winter months.

871
01:50:13,959 --> 01:50:17,463
Napoleon, your letters are
a soothing balmto my heart.

872
01:50:18,380 --> 01:50:19,673
I fear for you.

873
01:50:20,424 --> 01:50:24,136
Remember that I alone know
your health, your fears.

874
01:50:24,928 --> 01:50:28,474
I thank you as tenderlyas
I will always love you.

875
01:50:29,016 --> 01:50:30,059
Joséphine.

876
01:50:31,727 --> 01:50:33,312
My friend, Joséphine.

877
01:50:34,480 --> 01:50:35,647
"Friend."

878
01:50:36,732 --> 01:50:38,901
It is strange to write that word to you.

879
01:50:40,152 --> 01:50:42,154
You have always been so much more.

880
01:50:50,245 --> 01:50:55,042
Despite careful organization, there
have been breakdowns in supply.

881
01:50:56,627 --> 01:51:01,423
We're suffering
sickness, desertion and famine.

882
01:51:03,467 --> 01:51:04,593
We are winning.

883
01:51:16,814 --> 01:51:20,150
Us or Cossacks?- Us.

884
01:51:23,362 --> 01:51:27,991
Joséphine. Fortune has abandoned me.

885
01:51:29,201 --> 01:51:31,870
I know that it is what fate has for me.

886
01:51:32,579 --> 01:51:34,748
Your words rattle in my head.

887
01:51:36,417 --> 01:51:38,419
I am nothing without you.

888
01:51:42,756 --> 01:51:49,387
Of the 600,000 men you sent to
Russia, only 40,000 have returned.

889
01:51:49,388 --> 01:51:55,102
Therefore, you have been
exiledin no uncertain terms.

890
01:51:56,895 --> 01:52:01,859
The allied coalition of Austria,
Prussia, Russia and England,

891
01:52:03,652 --> 01:52:05,946
and with the agreementof
the French Council,

892
01:52:07,156 --> 01:52:10,909
grant you sovereigntyof
the island of Elba.

893
01:52:12,661 --> 01:52:15,748
A revenue of two million
francsfrom the French funds,

894
01:52:16,749 --> 01:52:20,169
pensions for the Bonaparte
familyand the Empress Marie-Louise.

895
01:52:21,337 --> 01:52:26,550
It also provides for Empress
Joséphineto retain all of her properties

896
01:52:28,052 --> 01:52:31,889
and an allotted annual
incomeof one million francs.

897
01:53:01,001 --> 01:53:02,586
I love France too much.

898
01:53:07,841 --> 01:53:10,094
All I've desired was its glory.

899
01:53:12,888 --> 01:53:14,848
I would never bring her misfortune.

900
01:53:17,351 --> 01:53:18,936
They want me to abdicate.

901
01:53:20,646 --> 01:53:22,189
Fine, I'll abdicate.

902
01:54:29,006 --> 01:54:30,007
Your Highness.

903
01:54:31,759 --> 01:54:32,760
Empress.

904
01:54:47,816 --> 01:54:48,817
Here.

905
01:54:53,697 --> 01:54:55,449
Joséphine, Joséphine.

906
01:54:57,576 --> 01:54:58,577
I am charmed.

907
01:55:00,663 --> 01:55:01,664
But...

908
01:55:06,210 --> 01:55:10,464
you do not have to lock yourself
awayjust because he's not here.

909
01:55:12,216 --> 01:55:14,593
I know what it is liketo
be underestimated.

910
01:55:16,220 --> 01:55:22,226
But your eyes, your charm and your spirit,

911
01:55:23,435 --> 01:55:24,645
it is in there.

912
01:55:25,479 --> 01:55:29,024
It is yours, and you can use it.

913
01:56:13,068 --> 01:56:14,403
Dear Joséphine,

914
01:56:15,154 --> 01:56:18,240
You are mine. You will always be.

915
01:56:19,783 --> 01:56:21,785
I cannot stand it any longer.

916
01:56:22,411 --> 01:56:24,663
It has been 300 days on this rock,

917
01:56:25,331 --> 01:56:28,709
and I'm ready to come
homeand reclaim what's mine:

918
01:56:29,335 --> 01:56:31,128
you and France.

919
01:56:49,313 --> 01:56:51,064
I'm taking your ship.

920
01:56:51,065 --> 01:56:54,026
If you do not provoke me, you
do not have to fear me.

921
01:57:13,087 --> 01:57:14,296
Napoleon,

922
01:57:15,255 --> 01:57:19,468
I'm a flower that opens its
petalsand smiles to the sunshine,

923
01:57:20,594 --> 01:57:24,097
unconscious that the storm
is nearwhich will lay me low

924
01:57:24,098 --> 01:57:26,350
and scatter leaves to the heavens.

925
01:57:27,351 --> 01:57:29,353
Come quickly, my friend.

926
01:57:59,008 --> 01:58:01,343
If you would open your mouth, please.

927
01:58:06,598 --> 01:58:07,599
Thank you.

928
01:58:12,521 --> 01:58:13,731
Thank you.

929
01:58:14,523 --> 01:58:17,860
Well, your chest is
congested. Your throat is aflame.

930
01:58:19,028 --> 01:58:20,863
My suggestion is to stay in bed.

931
01:58:23,365 --> 01:58:24,658
But Napoleon is coming.

932
01:58:25,200 --> 01:58:27,952
It would be unwiseto
receive any visitors.

933
01:58:27,953 --> 01:58:29,662
But Napoleon is coming.

934
01:58:29,663 --> 01:58:30,831
I understand.

935
01:58:50,392 --> 01:58:52,353
Just keep her comfortable.

936
01:59:20,255 --> 01:59:21,340
Your Majesty.

937
01:59:26,178 --> 01:59:27,470
You may speak.

938
01:59:27,471 --> 01:59:30,723
Bonaparte, Your Majesty. He has returned.

939
01:59:30,724 --> 01:59:32,850
A ship landed on a beachin
Antibes this morning,

940
01:59:32,851 --> 01:59:33,811
and they're on the march.

941
01:59:33,812 --> 01:59:36,939
Napoleon Bonaparte is
marchingtowards Paris.

942
01:59:40,317 --> 01:59:41,609
More.

943
01:59:41,610 --> 01:59:42,695
Your Majesty.

944
02:00:16,103 --> 02:00:17,103
Afternoon, Colonel.

945
02:00:18,022 --> 02:00:19,231
Your Majesty.

946
02:00:19,815 --> 02:00:20,898
General Marchand,

947
02:00:20,899 --> 02:00:23,569
in defense of the royal
governmentof King Louis XVIII,

948
02:00:24,361 --> 02:00:27,406
requests that you surrender
your weaponsand cease your march

949
02:00:28,115 --> 02:00:30,784
so that you may be arrestedand
returned to your island.

950
02:00:31,827 --> 02:00:35,706
Will you please inform the general thatl
shall like to come and speak with him?

951
02:00:37,416 --> 02:00:39,418
I have no fight with my own Fifth Army.

952
02:00:41,211 --> 02:00:42,212
Sir.

953
02:00:51,263 --> 02:00:52,723
He wishes to speak.

954
02:00:54,224 --> 02:00:55,225
Make ready!

955
02:00:58,979 --> 02:01:00,189
Present.

956
02:01:11,200 --> 02:01:16,163
Soldiers of the Fifth
Regiment, do you recognize me?

957
02:01:19,958 --> 02:01:22,086
Do you recognize me, soldiers?

958
02:01:24,004 --> 02:01:25,589
Yes, Emperor!

959
02:01:31,804 --> 02:01:33,013
I miss you.

960
02:01:35,766 --> 02:01:37,768
I'm melancholy for my home...

961
02:01:40,062 --> 02:01:42,231
and for our victories together.

962
02:01:45,442 --> 02:01:46,944
I want to come home.

963
02:01:48,404 --> 02:01:49,697
Will you join me?

964
02:01:51,448 --> 02:01:53,199
Long live the emperor!

965
02:01:53,200 --> 02:02:00,708
Long live the emperor!-
Long live the emperor!

966
02:02:40,706 --> 02:02:45,627
On May 26th, Dr. Corvisart was called

967
02:02:46,920 --> 02:02:52,092
and found her chest congestedand
her throat inflamed.

968
02:02:54,470 --> 02:02:56,972
Her illness was diphtheria.

969
02:03:00,059 --> 02:03:05,939
On May 29th, last sacrament
was given, and she died.

970
02:03:10,569 --> 02:03:12,446
And no one thought to notify me?

971
02:03:22,748 --> 02:03:23,749
Hortense.

972
02:03:26,669 --> 02:03:27,670
Do you blame...

973
02:03:29,505 --> 02:03:30,714
Do you blame me?

974
02:03:33,467 --> 02:03:34,550
I don't blame you.

975
02:03:34,551 --> 02:03:35,636
Of course not.

976
02:03:38,514 --> 02:03:41,892
I'm not to bear the
burdenof responsibility

977
02:03:43,477 --> 02:03:45,396
for the misfortunes of your mother.

978
02:03:46,522 --> 02:03:48,606
I want the letters that I wrote to her.

979
02:03:48,607 --> 02:03:52,736
I'm sorry, I don't have them. They
were stolen by her valet.

980
02:03:55,531 --> 02:03:56,740
Where did she keep them?

981
02:03:59,118 --> 02:04:01,620
In the cupboard in her
bedroom, next to her bed.

982
02:04:05,249 --> 02:04:06,667
What did he do with them?

983
02:04:09,086 --> 02:04:10,671
Her valet sold them.

984
02:04:18,053 --> 02:04:19,054
I'm sorry.

985
02:04:22,016 --> 02:04:23,017
I forgive you.

986
02:04:27,813 --> 02:04:30,940
Napoleon Bonaparte has destroyed

987
02:04:30,941 --> 02:04:34,903
the only titleupon which
his very existence depended.

988
02:04:36,321 --> 02:04:39,657
This congregation of allies shall form

989
02:04:39,658 --> 02:04:43,202
along the borders of
Franceand Belgium an army.

990
02:04:43,203 --> 02:04:45,956
70,000 troops from England,

991
02:04:47,291 --> 02:04:49,877
120,000 troops from Prussia.

992
02:04:51,962 --> 02:04:55,924
This vermin has routedthe
farmyards of Europe

993
02:04:56,800 --> 02:04:58,969
while the farmers snored.

994
02:04:59,553 --> 02:05:01,764
We should have struck this blow long ago.

995
02:05:02,848 --> 02:05:07,185
He has held the world
hostagewith his egotism,

996
02:05:07,186 --> 02:05:10,480
his insatiable hunger for power,

997
02:05:10,481 --> 02:05:13,984
and his lack of simple good manners.

998
02:05:14,943 --> 02:05:17,404
We will all sleep again without him.

999
02:05:18,572 --> 02:05:23,702
I believe I speak for all of us when
I saythat the only regret we all share

1000
02:05:24,411 --> 02:05:27,831
is that we allowed this
verminto live at all.

1001
02:05:28,999 --> 02:05:32,628
250,000 men with the traitor.

1002
02:05:33,837 --> 02:05:39,801
25,000 men, 125,000 men

1003
02:05:39,802 --> 02:05:42,554
and 100,000 men...

1004
02:05:46,058 --> 02:05:49,395
against our 125,000 men.

1005
02:05:51,855 --> 02:05:53,440
This is a fight on land.

1006
02:05:55,109 --> 02:05:58,112
This is what Britain does not
knowhow to do that I know.

1007
02:06:00,406 --> 02:06:04,493
Strike quicklyagainst
Wellington and Blücher.

1008
02:06:05,285 --> 02:06:06,870
Defeat them separately.

1009
02:06:07,913 --> 02:06:11,333
Disallow them from uniting forces here.

1010
02:06:24,388 --> 02:06:26,682
Morning.

1011
02:06:27,766 --> 02:06:29,226
The Prussians are advancing.

1012
02:06:30,310 --> 02:06:31,812
We should begin the offensive.

1013
02:06:32,521 --> 02:06:34,606
We must wait for the ground to dry.

1014
02:06:37,109 --> 02:06:40,404
Blücher will never make it in
time. I'll have Wellington by lunch.

1015
02:07:03,218 --> 02:07:06,013
I never get wet if I can help it.

1016
02:08:12,121 --> 02:08:13,497
What shall I tell the men?

1017
02:08:15,541 --> 02:08:17,251
Tell them to make the rain stop.

1018
02:08:20,254 --> 02:08:24,591
Coming through!- In formation!

1019
02:08:26,051 --> 02:08:28,721
Now's your time, lads. Now's your time.

1020
02:08:30,055 --> 02:08:31,682
Now, listen very carefully.

1021
02:08:33,142 --> 02:08:38,063
Patience is the order of the day
today. Patience shall win the day.

1022
02:08:38,814 --> 02:08:41,066
We must hold this ground.

1023
02:08:41,775 --> 02:08:43,568
Let them come to us.

1024
02:08:43,569 --> 02:08:45,487
Huzzah!

1025
02:08:50,826 --> 02:08:52,077
Go on, boys. Go on.

1026
02:08:56,040 --> 02:08:57,248
Good morning, General Blücher.

1027
02:08:57,249 --> 02:08:59,959
Good morning.- Estimated
time of arrival, sir?

1028
02:08:59,960 --> 02:09:02,378
Officer?- About five hours.

1029
02:09:02,379 --> 02:09:04,048
About five hours.

1030
02:09:20,606 --> 02:09:21,982
Come on, boys.

1031
02:09:34,828 --> 02:09:35,829
There he is.

1032
02:09:36,747 --> 02:09:42,419
He appears to be just sleeping.

1033
02:09:43,879 --> 02:09:49,301
One thing you cannot resist,
my friend, Is a frontal attack.

1034
02:09:52,221 --> 02:09:55,224
Let's see how this generalcan
attack our position.

1035
02:09:58,227 --> 02:10:03,064
Sir. I have the emperor in my
sights. Do I have permission to fire?

1036
02:10:03,065 --> 02:10:04,274
Certainly not.

1037
02:10:04,775 --> 02:10:07,068
Generals commanding armieshave
better things to do with their time

1038
02:10:07,069 --> 02:10:08,194
than to shoot at one another.

1039
02:10:08,195 --> 02:10:10,738
Hold your fire,
rifleman, on pain of death.

1040
02:10:10,739 --> 02:10:12,615
Go on, boys. Come.

1041
02:10:12,616 --> 02:10:14,493
A runner coming through!

1042
02:10:15,995 --> 02:10:17,663
Blücher, 11 to 12 miles, sir.

1043
02:10:18,497 --> 02:10:20,332
Attention, follow me.

1044
02:10:20,833 --> 02:10:23,376
Blücher at 11 to 12
miles, sir.- Jesus Christ.

1045
02:10:23,377 --> 02:10:25,546
I want a report
every hour.- Yes, sir.

1046
02:10:28,340 --> 02:10:32,011
Runner coming through. Make way.

1047
02:10:36,598 --> 02:10:39,518
Prussians on the roadside, 12 miles.

1048
02:10:45,774 --> 02:10:49,653
Prussian troops have been sightedon
the road, sire. Twelve miles.

1049
02:10:53,282 --> 02:10:54,491
Ready the cannons.

1050
02:10:58,120 --> 02:10:59,788
Ready the cannons!

1051
02:11:02,958 --> 02:11:05,002
Go on! Move!

1052
02:11:14,428 --> 02:11:17,013
Ready! Cannons are ready!

1053
02:11:17,014 --> 02:11:18,973
Cannons are ready!

1054
02:11:18,974 --> 02:11:20,768
The rain has stopped, sir.

1055
02:11:29,693 --> 02:11:31,403
Prepare to fire!

1056
02:11:41,038 --> 02:11:43,624
Fire!- Fire!

1057
02:11:49,630 --> 02:11:51,173
Take cover!

1058
02:11:53,967 --> 02:11:56,302
Straight into position. Steady.

1059
02:11:56,303 --> 02:12:00,474
Prepare for the advance. Get ready.

1060
02:12:01,809 --> 02:12:03,267
Prepare for the advance.

1061
02:12:03,268 --> 02:12:05,436
Readjust to 195!

1062
02:12:05,437 --> 02:12:07,563
Adjust 195!

1063
02:12:07,564 --> 02:12:10,317
Elevation 195.

1064
02:12:13,362 --> 02:12:14,488
Adjusted!

1065
02:12:16,448 --> 02:12:19,325
Prepare to fire! Fire!

1066
02:12:19,326 --> 02:12:20,953
Fire!

1067
02:12:26,041 --> 02:12:29,169
Keep your head down. Seventh, take over.

1068
02:12:38,053 --> 02:12:40,931
Out the way!- Hold fast, men!

1069
02:12:44,977 --> 02:12:48,480
Infantry, advance!

1070
02:12:49,314 --> 02:12:50,941
Left company!

1071
02:12:53,318 --> 02:12:54,861
And march!

1072
02:12:54,862 --> 02:12:57,031
Get in formation. Now!

1073
02:12:59,033 --> 02:13:00,159
Keep to the line!

1074
02:13:01,410 --> 02:13:02,411
Join!

1075
02:13:11,795 --> 02:13:15,883
Second wave, advance! Over the top, men!

1076
02:13:16,884 --> 02:13:18,301
Hold the line!

1077
02:13:18,302 --> 02:13:20,346
Cannons!

1078
02:13:21,055 --> 02:13:22,848
Fire!

1079
02:13:26,268 --> 02:13:27,811
Get ready.

1080
02:13:28,896 --> 02:13:30,147
Hold fast.

1081
02:13:30,939 --> 02:13:32,358
Fire!

1082
02:13:41,700 --> 02:13:43,827
You there, get on that cannon.

1083
02:13:53,962 --> 02:13:55,005
Fire!

1084
02:14:01,887 --> 02:14:03,681
Fill the gap!

1085
02:14:05,516 --> 02:14:06,934
Keep the line!

1086
02:14:14,441 --> 02:14:17,068
Skirmishers, keep advancing!

1087
02:14:17,069 --> 02:14:18,486
Get in formation.

1088
02:14:18,487 --> 02:14:20,322
Fire at will.

1089
02:14:25,619 --> 02:14:27,955
Keep them back, men. Fire.

1090
02:14:31,125 --> 02:14:34,294
Go on. Don't let them rally!

1091
02:14:40,050 --> 02:14:41,259
The strike position.

1092
02:14:41,260 --> 02:14:43,804
Get up, boys. Go on. Go on, boys.

1093
02:14:49,268 --> 02:14:52,187
Prussians, roadside, five miles.

1094
02:14:53,897 --> 02:14:55,524
Five miles, maybe less.

1095
02:14:57,526 --> 02:14:59,194
We have to act before Blücher arrives.

1096
02:14:59,862 --> 02:15:00,863
Out.

1097
02:15:03,699 --> 02:15:04,700
Out!

1098
02:15:16,962 --> 02:15:18,380
Cavalry!

1099
02:15:19,673 --> 02:15:21,467
Charge!

1100
02:15:28,474 --> 02:15:32,519
Prepare to receive cavalry.

1101
02:15:41,195 --> 02:15:45,573
We must hold our ground. Stand
fast to the last man.

1102
02:15:45,574 --> 02:15:47,910
We must not be beat!

1103
02:15:48,702 --> 02:15:50,953
Or what will they say in England?

1104
02:15:50,954 --> 02:15:54,208
Hold the line.- Keep it tight.

1105
02:15:58,545 --> 02:16:02,049
Steady, men. Stay in formation.

1106
02:16:05,469 --> 02:16:07,846
Long live the emperor!

1107
02:16:10,182 --> 02:16:12,101
Company, halt!

1108
02:16:12,768 --> 02:16:16,146
Form square!

1109
02:16:31,787 --> 02:16:34,373
Long live the emperor!

1110
02:16:37,459 --> 02:16:41,130
One section, fire. Two section, fire.

1111
02:16:57,521 --> 02:17:00,440
What do we do, sir? We
can't break through.

1112
02:17:00,441 --> 02:17:02,985
Keep them running. Get
in back with the square.

1113
02:17:05,696 --> 02:17:07,281
Show them your British steel.

1114
02:17:18,959 --> 02:17:20,919
Present arms!

1115
02:17:24,630 --> 02:17:25,966
Shoulder, hold!

1116
02:17:30,554 --> 02:17:32,306
They're here, the Prussians.

1117
02:17:35,683 --> 02:17:37,061
First over the rise, Emperor.

1118
02:18:03,086 --> 02:18:05,172
We need to find a way through!

1119
02:18:08,008 --> 02:18:10,010
Break the square!

1120
02:18:20,646 --> 02:18:21,939
Charge bayonets.

1121
02:18:22,815 --> 02:18:24,650
Charge bayonets!

1122
02:18:26,735 --> 02:18:31,281
Your Emperor is with you. You
are the brave of Austerlitz.

1123
02:18:32,156 --> 02:18:33,701
Never surrender.

1124
02:18:34,535 --> 02:18:37,037
For homeland and glory!

1125
02:18:43,919 --> 02:18:46,671
Shoulder to shoulder! Form lines!

1126
02:18:46,672 --> 02:18:48,424
Shoulder to shoulder.

1127
02:18:55,388 --> 02:18:56,682
Infantry, advance.

1128
02:18:57,182 --> 02:18:58,851
Battalion!

1129
02:19:00,602 --> 02:19:03,022
Advance!

1130
02:19:08,693 --> 02:19:10,070
Keep the line!

1131
02:19:12,363 --> 02:19:14,575
Footmen, fire!

1132
02:19:18,495 --> 02:19:20,581
Second line, fire.

1133
02:19:24,501 --> 02:19:25,878
Prepare to charge!

1134
02:19:28,297 --> 02:19:29,673
Charge!

1135
02:19:36,513 --> 02:19:38,223
Go on! Batter them!

1136
02:19:40,642 --> 02:19:42,811
Advance!

1137
02:19:55,074 --> 02:19:56,282
Cavalry advance, sir?

1138
02:19:57,534 --> 02:19:58,826
Cavalry advance.

1139
02:19:59,411 --> 02:20:01,829
Prepare for counterattack.

1140
02:20:01,830 --> 02:20:06,669
Men, enter. Full support.

1141
02:20:41,620 --> 02:20:45,416
No. He can't help himself.

1142
02:20:46,667 --> 02:20:48,377
Sir, Blücher.

1143
02:20:55,092 --> 02:20:56,093
Thank God.

1144
02:20:56,593 --> 02:21:01,557
Your Majesty!

1145
02:21:02,891 --> 02:21:05,768
Come see how masse de la France dines!

1146
02:21:05,769 --> 02:21:06,812
Yeah!

1147
02:21:34,631 --> 02:21:36,925
Yeah!

1148
02:22:11,377 --> 02:22:15,839
The battle is mine. There
will be an end to the war.

1149
02:22:23,472 --> 02:22:25,307
Senior officer, on deck!

1150
02:22:27,851 --> 02:22:29,728
Good day.

1151
02:22:32,981 --> 02:22:38,361
I am the first to admitwhen I
make a mistake. But I never do.

1152
02:22:38,362 --> 02:22:40,280
Because it is geometry.

1153
02:22:41,740 --> 02:22:44,118
I simply knowprecisely
where to place a cannon.

1154
02:22:45,661 --> 02:22:50,374
But tragically I cannot transferthis
knowledge to my marshals.

1155
02:22:51,458 --> 02:22:54,670
That might bewhat is
most difficult in life.

1156
02:22:56,630 --> 02:22:58,298
Accepting the failures of others.

1157
02:22:59,383 --> 02:23:00,634
You must not do that.

1158
02:23:03,095 --> 02:23:04,430
Encourage greatness.

1159
02:23:09,768 --> 02:23:10,894
Mind your head, sir.

1160
02:23:13,814 --> 02:23:15,566
Mind your head, sir.

1161
02:23:22,698 --> 02:23:25,783
What are they doing there?- Sir,
it's the midshipmen. They adore him.

1162
02:23:25,784 --> 02:23:26,951
Well, get 'em out.

1163
02:23:26,952 --> 02:23:28,954
Clear the room. Quickly.

1164
02:23:45,346 --> 02:23:47,388
Your grace...- Good morning, General.

1165
02:23:47,389 --> 02:23:48,766
These boys are delightful.

1166
02:23:50,684 --> 02:23:51,976
May I sit down?

1167
02:23:51,977 --> 02:23:53,062
Please.

1168
02:23:54,355 --> 02:23:55,647
And this breakfast.

1169
02:23:56,648 --> 02:24:01,028
Now I know why you havesuch
a successful navy. Thank you.

1170
02:24:06,909 --> 02:24:09,285
I've never visitedthe
English countryside.

1171
02:24:09,286 --> 02:24:11,246
I imagine I'll love the Cotswolds...

1172
02:24:14,708 --> 02:24:17,795
soft flowing hills, gentle light.

1173
02:24:19,755 --> 02:24:24,133
My dear sir, it is only by
a narrow margin of opinion

1174
02:24:24,134 --> 02:24:26,428
that you have been spared
the fateof being shot.

1175
02:24:28,180 --> 02:24:30,431
Politically, I'm afraid it's impossible

1176
02:24:30,432 --> 02:24:33,936
for the British governmentto
allow you to stay in England.

1177
02:24:36,021 --> 02:24:39,065
You are permitted three
officersand 12 servants

1178
02:24:39,066 --> 02:24:41,360
to accompany you into exile.

1179
02:24:42,194 --> 02:24:45,863
Exile will be contained to
the islandof Saint Helena

1180
02:24:45,864 --> 02:24:50,536
under the watchful eyeof Governor
Hudson Lowe and his family.

1181
02:24:52,871 --> 02:24:53,872
Saint...

1182
02:24:55,082 --> 02:24:58,502
Helena. It's a small island.

1183
02:24:59,461 --> 02:25:00,963
More of a rock, really.

1184
02:25:02,006 --> 02:25:04,758
A thousand milesfrom
the mainland of Africa.

1185
02:25:05,509 --> 02:25:10,014
I'm told it's very pretty,
tranquil. You'll have time to reflect.

1186
02:25:11,724 --> 02:25:13,891
Your correspondence will be monitored,

1187
02:25:13,892 --> 02:25:17,521
your presence verified twice
dailyby the orderly officer.

1188
02:25:27,781 --> 02:25:31,035
Fix that rigging line. Draw up the sails.

1189
02:25:32,619 --> 02:25:33,954
Go below deck!

1190
02:25:43,088 --> 02:25:47,426
What will you do now? I
hate to see you alone.

1191
02:25:48,802 --> 02:25:53,599
Will you come to me? Will I forgive you?

1192
02:25:55,267 --> 02:25:57,686
My sweet, stubborn Emperor.

1193
02:25:58,771 --> 02:26:01,357
I let you loose and let you come to ruin.

1194
02:26:02,691 --> 02:26:05,902
Next time, I will be Emperor,

1195
02:26:05,903 --> 02:26:07,905
and you will do as I say.

1196
02:26:15,162 --> 02:26:17,873
Well, you were right.

1197
02:26:19,291 --> 02:26:21,835
Every night I beg to see you in my dreams.

1198
02:26:22,753 --> 02:26:26,048
And when I do, you turn me away.

1199
02:26:58,497 --> 02:27:00,457
Girls, what's the capital of France?

1200
02:27:03,002 --> 02:27:04,003
Paris.

1201
02:27:04,712 --> 02:27:05,713
And Russia?

1202
02:27:06,422 --> 02:27:08,674
Petersburg. And Moscow before.

1203
02:27:10,634 --> 02:27:15,055
Moscow. And who burnt
Moscow to the ground?

1204
02:27:19,476 --> 02:27:20,477
I don't know, sir.

1205
02:27:21,937 --> 02:27:22,938
I did.

1206
02:27:23,731 --> 02:27:27,568
I believe, sir, the Russians
burnt itto get rid of the French.

1207
02:27:28,068 --> 02:27:29,069
Who told you that?

1208
02:27:29,862 --> 02:27:31,321
It's common knowledge, sir.

1209
02:27:35,409 --> 02:27:37,703
Go. Go play.

1210
02:27:39,288 --> 02:27:40,289
En garde.

1211
02:27:43,584 --> 02:27:46,170
Can I tell you what I
have waiting for you?

1212
02:27:48,339 --> 02:27:52,551
It is a secret. And I will
show you when you arrive.

1213
02:27:56,138 --> 02:28:01,477
Come to me, Napoleon. And
let's try this again.

