[drumroll]
[guillotine falls]
[crowd cheering]
[breathes shakily]
[crowd shouting]
[guillotine falls]
[cheering]
- [crowd shouting]
- [breathing shakily]
[guillotine falls]
- [fife and drum playing]
- [cheering]
[horse hooves trotting]
[crowd jeering, clamoring]
Get back, you lot.
Get to the guillotine.
[jeering, clamoring continue]
[breathing shakily]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[drumroll]
- [laughing, cheering]
- The scourge of France!
[cheering]
- Terror is nothing more than justice.
- [people clamoring]
Prompt, severe, inflexible.
It is therefore an
emanation of virtue.
[clamoring continues]
Now, she was guilty of
three charges against you:
depletion of the
national treasury,
conspiracy against the internal
and external security of state,
and high treason for acting
in the interests of the enemy.
Mercy for the villains?
No.
Mercy for the innocent.
- Mercy for the unfortunate.
- [people cheering]
Mercy for humanity.
[clamoring]
[revolutionary] An inescapable
outcome of democracy's connection
in relation to the nation's
immediate demands at this moment...
The British navy have
taken the port of Toulon.
Half the French
fleet is trapped there.
If we lose those ships,
the Republic will fall.
Lucky for us, there are only
2,000 English troops in Toulon.
But we are short of artillery and led
by a general who was a court painter.
It is not necessary to
recapture Toulon itself.
The town is not a
town. The town is a port.
If the harbor's untenable
to the English fleet,
the town must surrender.
My brother, Captain
Bonaparte, as artillery officer,
has organized heated
shots against English ships.
He has proven his
commitment to the Republic.
And how do you propose
to take the harbor?
Capture the fort that
dominates the harbor,
and you have the city.
We must make an example,
or other cities will fall.
And I, for one,
will never let the royalists
or the English take my region.
[chuckles]
[people cheering]
- [horse whinnies]
- [soldiers chattering]
[soldier] Morning, sir.
General Carteaux?
He's over there.
[Napoleon] Lucien, my dear
brother, I am in Toulon already.
The troops are in a poor state, and your
conscripts untrained and undisciplined.
Without equipment and
resources, I see only failure.
We are collecting scrap iron to recast
small mortars more suitable for my plan.
If we do not succeed,
those in power will only see us as
Corsican ruffians unfit for higher office,
and our mother's
ambitions will be quashed.
[peddler 1] That's it,
madam. Fine eye you have.
- [peddler 2] There you go.
- [peddler 3] I'll still be here next week.
[people chattering]
[Napoleon] The British
control the big guns
that point out at
their fleet offshore.
Take those guns, and we can fire
onto them and end this blockade.
[soldiers chattering]
[Napoleon] Surprise is my
advantage, but I will win by fire.
I cannot wait for your arrival.
Your brother, Napoleon.
[soldier] Oi, shit
rag! Yes, you!
Move along now. Go on. Move!
Move them fucking goats!
Last chance! Fucking
move them goats!
[soldier 2 shouting]
[soldier] You better
fucking move them now!
Do you understand?
[French soldiers
whispering, grunting]
- [British soldiers singing, distant]
- [French soldier 1 shushes]
[British soldiers] ♪ He sat
himself down By the fire, my boys ♪
♪ To join in our jovial crew ♪
- [French soldier 2] Get in position.
- [French soldier 3] Quick, quick!
♪ By the chimney corner
Was his own place ♪
♪ Where he could sit
And dye his old face ♪
♪ When Jones's ale
was new, my boys ♪
Quick, quick!
♪ When Jones's ale was new ♪
♪ Pints of beer and bottles of sherry
To help them over the hill so merry ♪
♪ When Jones's ale was new ♪
[breathing heavily]
[whispering indistinctly]
[whispering continues]
[British soldiers singing
"Drunken Sailor," muffled]
[Napoleon] Fire!
[British soldier 1]
We're under attack!
[shouting, clamoring]
[British soldier 2] We're under
attack! Grab your weapons!
[French officer 1] Get
those ladders up quick, men!
[breathes heavily, grunts]
[soldiers shouting]
[British officer]
Fire! Hit your target!
[French officer 2] Get
the mortars up there!
[straining]
[horse whinnies]
Ready, boy? Ready,
boy? Ready, boy?
[horse whinnies]
Oh, God! [grunts]
[panting]
[grunting]
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
[panting, wheezing]
[soldiers shouting]
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[French officer 2]
Get the mortars!
[soldiers clamoring, shouting]
[British officer 2]
Protect the cannons!
Into position!
[wheezing, panting]
- Vive la France!
- [French soldier 1] Vive la France!
[shouting, clamoring]
[screaming]
[Napoleon wheezing, panting]
Ready the cannons!
[French soldier
2] Sir! Yes, sir.
Mortars!
[French officer
3] Elevation 160.
- Fire!
- Firing!
[Napoleon] Junot, heated shots!
Fire!
Junot, fire!
[shouting, clamoring]
- [Junot] Reload!
- [French soldiers] Reload.
Fire!
[Junot] Fire!
[French soldiers cheering]
[French officer] Shoulder, hold!
Captain Napoleon Bonaparte, I
award you the rank of brigadier general.
Long live the Republic!
[soldiers] Long
live the Republic!
Long live the Republic!
I promised you brilliant
successes, and I've kept my word.
[French officer] Order, hold!
[panting]
For Mother.
You know your
father's under arrest?
He's a prisoner.
[operative] Hmm.
Do you know why?
'Cause he's a noble.
[operative] Hmm.
Are you a noble?
- Hortense, it's al-- it's all right.
- [operative] Hmm?
Hmm? Are you a noble?
Yes.
[operative] Yes? Hmm.
Mm-hmm. What do your
parents say about royalty?
[stammers]
Come now. Don't be shy.
What do they say when they
speak of Louis and Marie Antoinette?
My father is for the
revolution. So am I.
Don't lie to me
or I will hurt you.
- [Joséphine] Sir, she is five years old.
- [operative stammers]
She's not lying. My
husband fought on your side.
[clamoring]
[warder 1] Hands.
Show me your hands.
Mouth. Open your
mouth. Open your mouth!
- [gasps]
- Look at those teeth.
[warder 2] Come on. Keep up!
- Keep her jewelry.
- [warder 1] Hands.
That way.
Joséphine.
- Theresa?
- [chuckles]
[breathes heavily]
Hey, stop it.
- Move it.
- Hurry up. Come on.
Move.
[clamoring]
The tombereau
comes every morning.
We have a rule. No
tears. No goodbyes.
We just wave like
we're off to the café.
Follow me.
[prisoners grunting, moaning]
[scoffs]
A pregnant woman gets a stay
of execution until the baby's born.
And men never need a
reason to fuck, do they?
[sighs] Welcome home.
They say the blade of the
guillotine can get caught in your hair.
Got stuck in the king's neck.
His neck was fat.
You have the neck of a
swan. You won't feel a thing.
[breathes heavily]
I'm not going to die.
I'll do what it takes.
And if that means
getting pregnant, so be it.
You can die like a lady,
or you can live. Like me.
This is the mark
of a blade. Look.
[murmuring]
[cheering]
[singing hymn, "Veni
Creator Spiritus"]
- [drumroll]
- [guillotine falls]
[bird cawing]
The current leadership of France
has passed from enthusiasm
to reckless ambition.
And the public perception of
the guillotine is lawless passion,
led by Robespierre.
He is unfit to rule.
[snoring]
- [knocks]
- Bonaparte.
- [people clamoring]
- [politician] France!
It has become increasingly
clear, Citizen Robespierre,
that your motivations are to use
this blade to your ultimate power!
[people clamoring]
Let me speak!
There is no man in this room
who has objected to my methods.
If you say I am guilty,
you are all guilty!
[Barras] You are not
a defender of freedom.
You have deemed yourself judge,
jury and executioner, have you not?
You're worse than
Caesar! Worse than Caesar!
You are, all of
you, the traitors!
- Arrest him!
- [clamoring]
[grunts]
[panting]
[citizen] Get him.
- [clicks]
- [onlookers gasp]
[sighs]
[gunshot]
- Justice.
- He's still alive.
[people muttering]
[Robespierre breathing
heavily, groaning]
[choking]
[screams]
You missed.
[Robespierre wheezes]
The guillotine, my friend.
- [prisoners clamoring, cheering]
- [grunting]
Knock off his head! Kill him!
No. [grunting]
[cheering]
[whispering] Hortense?
Eugène?
Lucille?
- [Lucille] Madame?
- [gasps]
Children, come.
Come.
[breathing shakily]
[sniffles]
Look at that. Look at that.
[whispering] Leaves
nothing to the imagination.
[normal] But then, I don't
have much imagination.
You know who they are?
The new queens of Paris.
Yeah, let's go.
[singing]
[ball guests
chattering, laughing]
[singing continues]
[Barras chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
[singing continues]
- [screaming]
- [audience laughing]
[cheering, applauding]
[musicians singing]
[audience laughing]
[Barras chuckles]
[exclaiming]
[laughs]
[groans]
[growling]
[singing continues]
[chuckles]
[groans]
Ooh.
- [classical music playing]
- [people chattering, laughing]
[croupier] A seven, madame.
[Joséphine] Deal again.
Deal again.
[croupier] Your bet.
Seven again.
No. No win.
I'll be out first. That's mine.
Why are you staring at me?
- Am I?
- Mmm.
- No, I was not.
- Yes.
Oh, you weren't?
I was.
I was staring at-- at your face.
What is this costume
you have on?
- This is my uniform.
- [scoffs]
- I led the French victory at Toulon.
- [chuckles]
Do not tell me your name.
[chuckles]
[moans, groans]
[panting]
You ran up a debt
at cards tonight.
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
I'll pay it this time.
I've made your reputation
in the salons, Paul.
I should really ask for more.
More?
- [chuckles]
- This will keep you afloat for now.
But you should get to
know Bonaparte better.
Why?
Because.
[clears throat]
- General?
- [Napoleon] Mmm?
There is a very young
man who wishes to see you.
His name is, uh,
Eugène Beauharnais.
Mmm.
Ow.
[clears throat]
[Junot] Citizen.
General Bonaparte.
Yes?
My name is Eugène Beauharnais,
son of Joséphine Beauharnais.
What do you want?
My father's saber.
I-It was taken from him before
he was arrested and executed.
Yes?
I-It would mean a great deal to me
and to my mother if it were returned to us.
It's all we have of him.
The sword is a weapon.
I cannot allow citizens to have
weapons in their possession.
The sword is a keepsake for me
to remember my dear late father.
Perhaps, but it is a
weapon nevertheless.
Young man, why are you here?
My mother said that you were the only
man of authority to retrieve the sword.
All of these are from officers
who were sentenced to die.
Did no one think to attach
names to any of them?
No, there are no names.
[bell rings]
General Bonaparte?
Thank you.
Is there reason to
introduce myself?
No, General.
[Napoleon] Good.
My compliments to the
chef of this fine family.
[chuckling]
Would you like to sit closer?
[laughs]
[chuckling]
[Joséphine] Do I
look like I'm in love?
Do you find him without appeal?
No.
Then perhaps that is enough.
Do not underestimate your grace.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
[groans]
Sir.
[sighs]
When you look at me,
do you see an aristocrat?
No.
My husband had
more than one lover.
And when his head was cut
off, all his mistresses watched.
When I was in prison, I was told the
only way to survive was to get pregnant.
So, General...
do I need warn you
of my indiscretions?
No, madame.
Does where I have
been concern you?
No, madame.
If you look down,
you'll see a surprise.
And once you see it,
you will always want it.
[crowd clamoring]
People of France, don't be
fooled. There are more of us!
- [crowd cheers]
- We can occupy this Convention!
Long live the king!
[all chanting] Long live
the king! Long live the king!
[chanting continues]
No doubt you've seen
the chaos in the streets.
Yes.
There is a belief
amongst the Committee
that there is an attack on the
Council coming by this mob.
I have less than 4,000 troops and
very little in the way of weapons.
There are 40 cannons in Sablons. I
could have them here in three hours.
This mob is 20,000 strong.
Yes.
As my second-in-command,
what would you intend to do
if this assignment of defense
was transferred to you?
I accept, on the condition
that I command this as I see fit.
Without interruption.
I will not lead as
second-in-command.
[soldiers shouting, clamoring]
Come on!
[chanting, shouting]
Fire!
[screaming]
[whimpering]
♪ We shall win or
we shall perish ♪
♪ The French must live for her ♪
♪ And for her the
French must die... ♪
[chuckling]
To the savior of the Republic.
- To the savior of the Republic.
- Savior of the Republic.
I'm just a watchman
for our laws.
For our Republic.
For the universe.
Nothing more.
Liberty or death.
- Liberty or death.
According to the law of
20th September, 1792,
Marie-Josèphe-Rose Tascher,
born 23rd June,
1767, in Martinique,
accepts as her husband
Napoleon Bonaparte,
born February, 1768,
in Ajaccio, Corsica.
Do you consent?
- Yes.
- I do.
[court official] Do you consent?
Yes. I do.
I declare you
united in marriage.
- [kissing]
- [Joséphine chuckling]
[cheering]
As part of the Peace Treaty,
these masterpieces will be placed
under the care of your archbishops.
These works now belong
to the people of France.
[guests] To the
savior of the Republic!
[guest 1] And to
Madam Bonaparte.
[guests] To Madam Bonaparte.
[guests chattering]
This guy right next to
me? [continues indistinctly]
- [Joséphine] Mmm.
- [guest 2] He wants my saber.
[grunting]
Let that good work
make us a son.
[panting]
[sighs, inhales deeply]
Is this what will
happen from now on?
I marry you and you leave?
[sighs]
Every time you leave, I have
no assurance of your return.
My sweet Joséphine...
The only thing you can
depend on in this world...
[whispering] ...is that I
shall always return to you.
[breathes deeply]
[Napoleon] Dear Joséphine,
I follow in the footsteps of
Alexander the Great and Caesar,
as I have been sent
to liberate Egypt.
I have 40,000 men,
and the sights are wondrous,
and the weather is stifling hot.
I have already conquered Italy,
who surrendered without conflict.
[Egyptian officer shouting]
[Napoleon] The Directory has
approved my plan for attacking England
through their eastern empire.
But my achievements seem
slight, as they keep us apart.
[Egyptian soldiers chanting]
[shouting]
[grunts]
[horse whinnies]
Bad luck?
Oh.
You may bring those
two out, if you wish.
Thank you, madam. Been a
great pleasure playing with you.
Perhaps something, if your
fortune might change later on?
- I'll take it. Thank you. Hmm.
- Sir.
[Napoleon] My dear Joséphine,
Away from you there is no joy.
You have robbed me of more than
my soul. You are the one part of my life.
You like it?
I like it a lot.
[Napoleon] I know not if you want money,
for you never speak to me of business.
If you do, will you
ask my brother for it?
He has 200 louis of mine.
Ladies, do you like it?
[murmuring, chuckling]
I love it.
I'll take that now.
[grunts, kisses]
[Napoleon] Dear wife,
This love I have for
you is a kind of death.
There is no survival
for me except in you.
Hello again.
[Napoleon] What are you doing?
No letters from you.
Good morning, Lucille.
[Napoleon] If you loved me,
you'd write me twice a day.
Tell me there are no
snakes in your bed,
in your legs,
inside what is mine.
You must write me and tell me
that you realize that I love you
beyond the limits of imagination,
that only you can please me.
[indistinct shouting]
[soldier chuckles]
- [chattering]
- [piano playing]
Thank you.
[speaks indistinctly]
- [chuckles] Absolutely. I like it.
- That's very ni-- [mumbles]
You know they have white,
silky things. Amazing. [chuckles]
Are there limits to
what I can tell you?
There shouldn't be.
Should I tell you something at
the risk of giving you personal pain?
Yes. [chuckles]
Your wife has taken a lover
named Hippolyte Charles.
[laughing]
- You expect me to believe this? [laughs]
- Yes. [chuckles]
That my wife would
do this to me? Mmm.
Yes.
No dessert for
you. You may leave.
I would never lie to you.
How do you know this?
Lucille is my lover.
She writes to me.
Joséphine's
lady-in-waiting is your lover?
Prepare two frigates and two
smaller vessels in the greatest secrecy.
I'm returning home.
- Napoleon...
- Hmm?
...this will be
seen as desertion.
General Kléber will be informed of his
succession to command after I've left.
Order arms!
[cheering]
[citizen] Napoleon
the victorious!
[sighs]
[citizens cheering]
[carriage driver]
Hyah, hyah, hyah!
Where's my wife?
She has left to
greet you in Lyon.
- [dog yelps]
- Do not lie to me. Where is my wife?
She left earlier today, General.
- Lyon?
- Yes, sir.
The entire world knows of
my arrival, but not my wife?
[dog whining]
[clears throat]
Forgive me for earlier.
Yes, sir.
Sit with me.
My wife has humiliated me,
and I need comfort, Lucille.
Yes, I'm sure that
you do, General.
[sighs] What do you suggest
would give me comfort?
I can draw you a
hot bath, General.
I can prepare you
something sweet...
and console you.
[thunder rumbling]
[groans, gasps]
[whimpers]
[crying, breathing shakily]
[bell rings]
- [dogs barking]
- [thunder rumbling]
[Napoleon] What kind
of creature are you?
How could you care so little
- for me and my feelings?
- [groans]
You are a selfish little pig.
[mutters]
Do you think so lowly of me?
No. I don't.
Then why?
Because you're what? Say it.
I'm sorry.
That's not enough.
[sighs]
- What do you-- What do you want me to say?
- I want you to say
that I am the most
important thing in the world!
You are.
- Say it!
- You're-- You're-- You're-- You're--
You're the most important thing
in my life, in the world. You a--
- And without me, you are nothing.
- I'm nothing.
And you will do anything!
I'll do anything.
I'm not built like other men.
And I'm not subject
to petty insecurity.
You're a beast.
I feel sorry for you.
You want to be great?
Hmm?
You are nothing without me.
Say it.
You are just a brute
that is nothing without me.
I am just a brute that
is nothing without you.
Yes.
You are nothing without
me or your mother.
[Napoleon breathing heavily]
My mother...
[sighs]
[Joséphine sighs]
Did you have affairs?
Of course I did.
And did you love them?
No. No, I did not.
Were they pretty?
Yes, some of them.
They served their purpose.
More than I do?
They cried less. That
made them more attractive.
Don't--
Don't leave me.
Please, don't leave me.
[whispering] Just
don't leave me.
You don't have to forgive me. Just
promise me you won't leave again.
What is it that made you
desert your troops in Egypt?
Shh!
Citizens...
what country are we in?
Because she doesn't
resemble the France that I left.
Who should be responsible for
her governance while I'm away?
Because it is not
you, Citizen Gohier.
It is not you.
It certainly is not you. Although
you're very good at scowling.
It is not you, Barras.
Or you, Talleyrand.
Or you, Sieyès.
So, who?
Who should be responsible?
Fouché, do you have any ideas?
- No?
- [sighs]
I have returned to France
to find her bankrupt.
Printing money that
is spent within hours,
the Austro-Russian
overrun of Italy,
the Anglo-Russian
occupation of Holland,
and what appears to be the
imminent invasion of France herself.
And yet, you accuse
me of desertion.
Added to which the
discovery that my wife is a slut.
The only thing that every French citizen
can agree on is that you are our Caesar.
What do you want?
[chuckles]
Well...
the people would accept
my rule if I have your support.
Like you, though, I believe
that the Directory is corrupt.
But together, we can save this country
from a restoration of the monarchy,
and we can preserve the
ideals of the Revolution.
And I think that a seizure
of power is possible
with your help,
at the right time.
And I think this
is the right time.
So, you expect me
to be your sword?
[chuckles]
I expect that a coup d'état,
well-timed, well-executed...
could transfer power into
the hands of three consuls:
myself, Ducos...
and you.
[scoffs]
I'm inviting you to
the winning side.
[chuckling]
Hmm?
Myself and Ducos
will resign first,
followed by Barras,
Gohier, and Moulin.
And this will create an
opening to transfer power.
[Lucien] Yeah, I like Barras,
but he is corrupt and isolated.
I think, given the proper threat, he
will quickly make the right decision.
As for the others, uh,
Gohier and Moulin, is it?
I-I don't know.
There are ways to dissuade
them from resistance.
Yes, but this may not become a...
[stammers] ...military or a violent matter.
It will be a police matter.
[Sieyès] Yes.
Lucien... [smacks lips]
As Governor of
the Council of 500,
you will persuade both Councils,
at an emergency session,
that a Jacobin coup is at hand,
and that the only safe
place is out of Paris,
away from the Parisian
mob, at Saint-Cloud,
where we'll then save
them from this threat.
[Lucien] Can I be honest?
There's only one problem
with Sieyès and Ducos's plan.
- And that's Sieyès and Ducos.
- Mmm.
[Lucien] They don't know
you're-- You've got all the power.
You're taking all the risks.
You're doing all the work.
I don't know why you're
bringing them along with you.
Well, I'll need
ladies-in-waiting.
[Lucien] Ladies-in-waiting,
huh? Doing what?
Well, tending to things.
- Tending?
- [chuckling] Yes.
You think those
fucking idiots could tend?
They couldn't tend-- I wouldn't
let them tend to my balls.
- [chuckles] Precisely.
- Yeah.
I'll need that.
[Lucien] Tongue bath? I
wouldn't let them wipe my arse.
[both chuckling]
From this moment on,
all friends that you've had,
anyone from the society of the Directory,
cannot be trusted. That life is over.
Well, what's the outcome
of this if you don't succeed?
[chuckles]
By this time tomorrow,
you will be sleeping with
the First Consul of France
and I will stick it to you.
[sniffs, groans]
It's a simple letter of
resignation we would like you to--
I am not signing anything.
You can piss before
I sign anything away!
Gentlemen.
[panting]
[grunting]
[shouts] Who's doing this?
Good morning, Paul.
Hmm.
I'm going to make
this very simple for you.
I have documents announcing
your resignation from the Council.
You must retire before you
have your breakfast, please.
Tell them I return with joy
to the ranks of simple citizen.
I shall.
[knocking]
There are some
gentlemen here to see you.
Citizen Moulin, we have a letter
of resignation for you to sign.
- No, no, no. I am eating my breakfast.
- [spouse] No.
I am enjoying a
succulent breakfast.
This is outrageous! I shall finish
my breakfast before you touch me!
- [cries] No!
- Enjoy your breakfast.
[wailing]
[Council member 1] Director!
I believe the time has come
to demand an explanation.
- [Council member 2] Hear, hear!
- [clamoring]
Uh, thi-this emergency session
is to draw a list of nominations
for a-- a new Directory
to deal with the threat--
- [members clamoring]
- the threat of the royalists.
We are being asked
to pass a resolution
forming a provisional
government to three councils:
General Bonaparte and
Citizen Sieyès and Roger Ducos.
Where are the five
members of the Directory?
[members clamoring]
[Council member 1] Have
they magically disappeared?
- [Council member 3 chuckles]
- And we are here, surrounded by troops,
isolated far from Paris.
- [clamoring]
- Order! Order!
[Council member 1] This is
becoming increasingly clear:
that your brother,
Napoleon Bonaparte,
with his show of military
might, is acting as an outlaw.
- [members clamoring]
- [Lucien] A vote will solve this matter.
[Council member 1] And that this is a
ridiculous and poorly executed takeover.
A power-hungry upstart.
- [members shouting]
- [Napoleon] Enough! Enough!
If there is any question of what
is happening here, I will answer!
How dare you!
This is-- You have
violated the constitution!
- You have--
- [Council member 4] Hold him!
- [Council member 5] Get him!
- [struggling]
[all clamoring]
- Arrest him!
- Stop him!
[panting]
Oh, fuck!
[Council members shouting]
[yelps]
[Council member 6] Kill him!
[grunts, panting]
[guards straining]
- [mutters]
- Let me through!
Right. [pants]
We are being terrorized by
deputies armed with daggers!
And these madmen
have outlawed themselves
by their attempt on the
liberty of this country!
- They're trying to kill me!
- They're trying to kill him.
- [Council member 7] Open these doors!
- [grunts]
[Lucien grunts]
[Council member
3] Let us out of here!
I will kill my brother if he betrays
the freedom of the French people!
Get in there now!
- [Lucien] Fuck.
- [guards shouting]
[guard 1] Move,
move. Get back. Back.
[guard 2] Move it. Move it!
- [guard 3] Back. Move back.
- [guard 4] Move back. Out of the way.
[guard 5] Move, move. Backwards.
[Council members gasping]
Good luck, brother.
[Napoleon panting]
Stand aside.
Shall we vote?
Where are we going?
[people cheering]
All our harsh
words are behind us.
I need you to be my
most tender friend.
Over this door is our destiny.
[cheering continues]
[French officer] Present arms!
- [aristocrat] First Consul.
- My lord.
Milady.
[inhales sharply]
First Consul.
- Citizen Bonaparte.
- First Consul.
First Consul.
Come, little one.
You get into the
bed of your master's.
[chuckling]
The decision of dress is
not just a matter of taste.
It is policy that guards against
the return of a fatal regime.
And so our uniforms
must be rich.
For staff, each a red coat.
For winter made in velvet, and
summer some other material.
Both embroidered in gold.
[aristocrats chattering]
Hello, madame!
Hello, good evening.
Mother, the Duke of Avignon.
It's good to meet you.
Ah. Could this be Joséphine?
- Mother, Joséphine. Joséphine, Mother.
- [Letizia] Good to see you.
Oh, it's Charles.
This way.
- Good evening. How are you?
- [chuckles] I'm very well.
[Napoleon] Mother.
Hello... [speaks indistinctly]
It's a pleasure to--
Her voice.
- I hope you're having a wonderful night.
- Thank you very much. [chuckles]
- Hello, sir. Hello, mademoiselle...
- Hello.
So happy to see you.
[scribe] "Your Majesty, England and
France are wasting their prosperity."
Let me try again.
- Your Royal Majesty, England and France...
- [clears throat]
- ...are wasting their prosperity...
- Your-- Your Majesty.
What did I say?
[stammers] "Your--
Your-- Your Royal Majesty."
"Your Royal Ma"--
[inhales deeply]
Your Majesty, England and
France are wasting their prosperity.
I am not ashamed
to take the initiative.
I have, I think, sufficiently
proven to the whole world
that I do not fear
the chances of war.
But peace is my heartfelt
wish for England and France.
Read it back to me.
I have notified all foreign powers
of your accession to the Consul,
I have addressed letters to
all diplomatic agents abroad,
and I understand that you have made
friendly overtures of peace to England.
Ca-Caulaincourt.
What I need from you
is a better understanding
of the Russian Tsar Alexander.
Would you consider the tsar
an ally to England or France?
Well, I would think that his trade
with England is more beneficial to him
than his trade with France.
And do you have a sense of British
influence in the Russian courts?
[Caulaincourt] I do not, but
I imagine it is quite robust.
Robust?
What kind of man
is he? Describe him.
Well, he's young. [sighs]
- He's vain.
- [scoffs]
He's popular, and he
wishes to remain so.
He's popular?
Really?
His greatest fear is to be
killed in his bed, like his father.
[laughs]
This makes him dangerously fickle
to whoever last has his attention.
So he needs an ally that
he can also call a friend.
No more bets.
What a surprise.
How nice to see you out.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Good evening. I'm just
trying to lose some money.
Ah. Well, after this hand, why
don't you come and join me?
I'm at my usual table.
That's a lovely idea.
Good evening.
Mmm. Did you hear?
Your Majesty received a letter of
peace from the First Consul today.
Monsieur Talleyrand,
if I may be honest?
Of course.
Austria's coalition with England is in
such a strong position against France,
that these peace
overtures are clearly
only for your handling
of French public opinion.
[chuckles] Oh, my friend.
- You know me so well.
- [diplomat chuckles]
Yes, it is true. It is public
opinion Napoleon is after.
But my warning to you
is that he's as hungry for it
as any man in the
history of the world.
So my suggestion, with respect,
would be to take this little
offering of peace from him...
or suffer the consequences from
a man bent on peace at any cost.
The English ambassador, Lord
Whitworth, has arrived, Consul.
Do not look at me as if you
don't know what I'm about to say.
Are you aware of my
letter of peace to your king?
I am not.
Shall I repeat it?
[inhales deeply] No,
you may not. [sighs]
Take this as a
warning to your king.
I will keep you
guessing and scared.
You will watch your
borders and your back,
and your manners are bound,
sooner or later, to be French.
I will offer no more
letters of peace,
and I will take the lack of a
swift reply as an act of disrespect!
You think you're so great
because you have boats!
'Tis a shame such a great
man should have no manners.
Stronger blue around Minorca.
Uh, t-take care. No, no, no, no.
First Consul, don't walk
there. The paint's still wet.
If-- If you want to walk,
w-w-walk on Italy. Italy is dry.
[Davout] The Austrians have consolidated
their forces here, First Consul.
To secure control of the
peninsula's northern half.
South of Alessandria.
In Marengo.
Their cavalry
reinforced, morale high.
The-- Their military is very,
very well provisioned for battle.
We will be light.
We will be swift.
We will cross the
great crest of the Alps.
And we will restore what
France lost while I was away.
[soldiers shouting]
Yes?
Are you pleased?
Are you about to tell me
something that will make me angry?
Let's hope not.
The European families think nothing
more of you than a Corsican thug.
- Therefore...
- [chuckles]
...I'm going to suggest something
that's been a long time arriving.
I suggest that you abandon
your role as First Consul of France
in exchange for the
title "Victorious Consul."
By another name, "king."
[chuckles]
What?
[scoffs] "King."
Uh, yes, king.
King?
- [chuckles]
- Mmm.
[murmuring]
My hair has been set.
- [murmuring continues]
- The way you like it.
- [whines]
- [scoffs] Oh, you filthy man.
My hair has been set now.
[murmuring continues]
I have the most beautiful wife.
- [whines]
- I-- All right, come on then.
Hat off.
Mmm.
[grunts]
Give me your hand.
- You feel that?
- [sighs] What?
Can you feel that?
- That's yours. That's yours.
- [breathing heavily]
It's yours.
Thank you.
[grunts, breathing heavily]
[Joséphine pants, grunts]
[grunts]
[panting]
This conspiracy of
royals against me is clear.
All exiled Bourbons whose
single aim is to overthrow my rule
and reinstate their
filthy perfume-Monarchy.
The Prince de Conde
is smuggling out plotters,
and his grandson, Louis,
the Duke d'Enghien,
is on the frontier
solely for that purpose.
I want this man seized, and I
want him brought swiftly to justice.
Where is he?
He's in Baden.
First Consul, I know this man.
He is not a conspirator against you.
He is a brave and
excellent officer,
- much loved by the soldiery.
- He's a filthy Bourbon weasel
who-- who-- who will be punished
for his part in this plot against me.
- [breathing heavily]
- If you proceed to Baden,
you will be operating outside of
France and so far outside the law
that it will be impossible
for anyone to ignore.
I see.
[inhales sharpy] Well, I've
always profited from your judgment.
And now it's time to profit from
watching you close your mouth.
Seize the Duke.
[sighs deeply]
You're letting your hatred make
your decision. [breathes shakily]
In a year's time, you will regard this
execution as an act of great policy,
and you will kiss my
mouth with those words.
Go to bed.
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
You are Frenchmen.
At least you will do me the
service not to miss your aim.
May I command the execution?
You are charged with
bearing arms against France.
Proceed to ready. Aim.
You may command the execution.
Aim for the heart.
Fire.
[body thuds]
[chuckles] Oh.
[Napoleon] Mmm.
Oh. [chuckles] Stop.
Why aren't you pregnant?
Is that a question, or
is that an accusation?
- [Napoleon] Mmm.
- [sighs]
It was a question.
[grunts, chuckles]
Now it's an accusation.
Well, I've seen Dr. Corvisart,
and he has no answer.
Only that I do what Madame
de Rémusat has done.
[Napoleon] Which is?
[sighs] Which is...
along with hopeful thinking
and a bit of red wine,
he suggested I take the
waters at Aix-la-Chapelle.
And why haven't you?
As wife of the First Consul,
I haven't found the time.
I spend many hours
cleaning up after you.
Find the time.
[inhales sharply] I don't need to explain
to you the importance of this, do I?
What, you want an heir?
I want one now.
[smacking lips]
- [chuckling]
- [Napoleon growling]
- [growling continues]
- [laughing]
Oh, my God. [gasps, chuckles]
- [growls]
- [chuckles]
[choir singing in Latin]
[song ends]
May God affirm
you on his throne,
and Christ give you to rule
with him in his eternal kingdom.
[attendees gasping]
I found the crown of
France in the gutter.
I picked it up with the tip of
my sword and cleaned it...
and place it atop my own head.
[attendees murmuring]
The most glorious, the
most august Napoleon,
emperor of the French,
is crowned and enthroned!
Long live the emperor!
[all] Long live the emperor!
[choir singing in Latin]
[drumroll]
[soldier] Fire!
[shouts] Fire!
[cannon fire]
Captain Charles.
Captain Charles...
I must confess something
to you in the greatest secrecy.
It is indiscreet.
And I hope you will not blush.
Do you have children?
Yes, Majesty. I have three sons.
If you please, may I ask
you something personal?
Of course, Majesty.
Tell me, when you made your wife
pregnant, did you spend much time?
Um, I don't remember, Majesty.
Mmm. If you were to guess.
We sometimes take 30 minutes.
And do you think this is what
your secret is, then, to having a son?
I cannot say for
certain, Majesty.
I love my wife.
So do I.
And I wanna see her happy.
So tell me...
do you think it important
for a man to pleasure his lady
in anticipation of entering her?
Um, I don't know what
you mean, Majesty.
Don't be shy, Captain.
Tell me.
If I want to have a son,
do you think I should spend time with
my mouth down between my wife's legs?
[swallows]
Um, I would assume,
Your Highness,
that the more pleasure
your wife gets...
[inhales shakily] ...the
more likely she is to conceive.
Captain Charles, I should like
to thank you for your honesty
in talking about such
uncomfortable matters.
I sought out your advice.
You're a man of notable
cocksmanship and stature.
And you have a pretty face
and a hairdresser's elegance.
Thank you.
You're dismissed.
[sighs shakily]
[Napoleon] I do not
support this idea.
You suggest divorce
after years of debate.
You can see that
it has me divided.
[Talleyrand] Mmm.
[sighs]
I am not ambitious.
I've never declared
war with anyone.
No.
You are the greatest leader
in the history of the world
and the world's only
chance at peace.
[sighs]
The security of the empire and peace
in the world depends upon an heir.
[sighs]
[dinner guests chattering]
[Joséphine] It was
an option. [chuckles]
And I said it at the time.
[Napoleon] Are you
enjoying yourself?
I'm going to war to
defend our people,
and my wife cannot
provide me an heir.
If you do not bear
me a child tonight,
there will be a divorce.
Hasn't been enough lovemaking
in this home to bear a child.
Yes, there has.
- [Joséphine sighs]
- There have been years of it. Years.
And with more than just me.
- [inhales deeply] Oh.
- And still you are empty.
And you're fat.
I enjoy my meals. I do.
Destiny has brought me here.
Destiny has brought
me this lamb chop.
[yelps]
Joséphine.
[sniffles]
- Come then.
- [sniffles]
Come.
[sighs]
I love your talents
and your taste.
And while I'm away,
I will miss your grace.
- [sighs]
- And your dignity.
And I will come back to you.
[sighs]
[horse whinnying]
[Austrian soldiers chattering]
[Austrian soldier shouts]
To today's victory. Hmm?
Look, I'm always
here for you, Francis.
But I must admit, I'm overwhelmed
with the excitement of the battlefield.
I should not deceive
you, Alexander.
This battle against him
will be brutal and terrifying.
[sighs]
[French soldiers shouting]
[grunting]
- [soldiers grunting]
- [officer] Come on!
Get in defensive position!
[Napoleon] My
good wife, Joséphine.
My God, it's cold here.
I miss your warmth.
On this day, we celebrate the
first anniversary of our coronation.
My previous ally has
now joined with my enemy.
The Russian Tsar Alexander joined
forces with the prince of Austria.
I have heard that he's
been studying the art of war
and trying to emulate
my battle tactics.
More fires.
He tries to copy me,
but he is a little boy who
will make a terrible mistake.
I am certain I will bring the laurels of
another glorious victory to my army today.
Yours, Napoleon.
- [shouts]
- [French soldiers cheering]
Hey, tie it from the back.
Peg that corner to the ground.
That's it.
[grunts, sighing]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Harder. Like a horse.
More.
[grunts]
[flute playing]
[French soldier shivering]
Fuck. [inhales shakily]
[Russian soldier
speaking Russian]
- [horse blusters]
- [speaking Russian]
[breathing heavily]
- Your Majesty.
- Mmm?
We are discovered.
Good.
Tell the men to rest.
[sighs]
[Russian soldier
speaking Russian]
I-N-F-S.
Infantry sighted.
I-M-T.
Imminent!
[clamoring]
Stand to!
- [officer 1] Stand to!
- [officer 2] Stand to!
- Stand to!
- Stand to.
- [officer 3] Wake up, men. Get ready!
- [soldiers] Stand to!
[officer 4] Come on, get up!
[panting]
[cavalry approaching]
[breathing shakily]
[Austrian soldier shouting]
Wait, wait.
[officer 5] Ready!
Wait! Let them think they
have the higher ground.
[cavalry approaching]
[Austrian soldier 1 shouting]
[Austrian soldier 2 shouting]
[all shouting]
[French soldier 1] Fire!
Fire away!
[French soldier 2] Fire at will!
[all shouting]
Send in the infantry.
Take their position on the
higher ground. At the double.
- [French soldier 3] Take the ground!
- [all shouting]
[gunfire]
Cavalry from the
west. Pierce their flanks.
Retreat! Withdraw!
[Austrian soldier 3] Withdraw!
[Austrian soldier
4] It's a trap!
Retreat!
[horses whinnying]
[grunts]
[panting]
[shouts]
- [Napoleon] Uncover the cannons.
- [French officer] Cannons!
- [Napoleon] Fire!
- [French soldiers] Fire!
[French soldier 4] Reloading!
[screams]
[screaming]
[French soldier 5]
Keep to the one side.
[Austrian general
1] Off the ice!
[screaming]
[grunting, screams]
[grunting, groaning]
Renounce, sir. We're pinned in.
Off the ice! Withdraw!
Cut off their retreat.
Hyah, hyah, hyah!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Francis. So nice
to finally meet you.
Please come in where it's warm.
- Thank you.
- You must forgive me.
This has been my only
palace for the last two months.
Seems very agreeable.
You make excellent use of it.
Well, we do what we
can on the battlefield.
- Yes, we do, don't we?
- Mm-hmm.
It's nice to finally
meet another emperor.
Uh, where, may I
ask, is Alexander?
Are we waiting for his
arrival before we get started?
I do not believe
he will be joining us.
- He's beside himself with rage.
- [sighs]
I realize I must compliment you for
making me commit an enormous error.
- An error?
- [Napoleon] Yes.
What error have you made?
To be speaking with you here and
accepting this invitation for peace,
I have not followed
up my victory.
I could have taken the whole
Russian and Austrian army prisoners.
Yes.
But after all, there
will be less tears.
And I know you will remember
this gesture of kindness. Yes?
Thank you. [sighs]
Toast?
To friendship, a glorious peace
and the best interest of Europe.
Mmm. Burgundy.
- [classical music playing]
- [chattering, laughing]
- [dog whines]
- [whines] Hold on.
- [barks]
- Hey, whoa, whoa!
- [chuckling]
- Whoa, we don't say woof.
Okay. [babbles]
That's my boy. Attaboy.
Come here. Come here.
Sit, sit, sit. [babbling]
- [dog barks]
- [barks]
It is time to put this
mystery to rest, Emperor.
I want to know if
it's you or Joséphine.
And to that end, we will conduct
a very practical experiment.
At the end of the
hallway-- Take this--
Waiting for you,
undressed, ready to receive,
is 18-year-old Eléonore
Denuelle de La Plaigne.
She's brunette with brown eyes.
And the object of this, well,
hardly unpleasant task is to
see if you can father a child.
- And then we will have an answer...
- Mmm.
...to this nagging question
of who is keeping who from
an heir to the throne of France.
[sighs]
Shall we go?
May I have another, please?
[chattering, laughing]
The girl is pregnant.
You made her
pregnant. [chuckles]
[Napoleon] Mm-hmm.
[chattering, laughing]
Uh, I know I didn't see her.
[speaking indistinctly]
When are you going
to insist we divorce?
Oh, isn't that wonderful?
From the only woman that I've ever
loved and given all that I've conquered.
I'm just too tired to wait for you
to tell me what I know is coming.
If you insist.
[sighs] I'll make
it easy for you.
[sighs] I know you will
have a bastard child.
If I succeed in making the birth of
a boy that I shall call my own son,
I want you as a witness to pretend
the confinement of the empress.
[stammers] Your Highness,
you are asking me to lie about
the status of the mother of your heir.
That is another
way of putting it, yes.
[scoffs]
Emperor... [sighs] ...it is my
honor and my duty, of course,
to do as you require of me.
But if asked, I cannot contain
that which I know to be the truth.
And painful though it is,
the truth is that the empress is no
longer capable of bearing you a child.
My good Joséphine. [sighs]
Hmm?
You know how I've loved you.
It is you, to you alone,
that I owe the few moments of
happiness I have known in this world.
Hmm.
My destiny is more
powerful than my will.
And my affections must yield
to the interests of my people.
[chuckling]
[Eugène] "Three
million francs per year.
Malmaison and its revenues.
The Élysée Palace in Paris.
The rank of empress.
The title of "Majesty"
and the right to use
the imperial coat of arms
and to have your carriage
drawn by eight horses."
[chuckles]
"Your present debts
of two million francs
to be paid as an advance
against all future revenues."
[inhales heavily]
The imperial decree for the
dissolution of the marriage
between the Emperor Napoleon
and the Empress Joséphine.
[sniffles]
"My people desire that this throne,
where providence has placed me,
would be given to my children.
However, I have lost hope of
having children from my marriage
to my beloved wife,
Empress Joséphine.
I have then been led to listen
only to the good of the state
and to want the dissolution
of years of my life."
[Josephine chuckles]
[grunts]
You have embellished
my life for 15 years.
The memories of which will
remain forever etched in my heart.
[sniffles]
"Our marriage has become an obstacle
for the prosperity of France." [chuckles]
"She has been deprived
of one day being governed
by the descendants of the
man brought to us by providence
to mend the evils of
a terrible revolution
and restore faith, the
throne and the social order."
Sorry.
[stammers, coughs]
- Emperor. Wait.
- Go. No, listen, listen. All right?
This is for your country.
That's what this is, all right?
- [whimpers]
- Now say it.
Say it.
"Our marriage has become an
obstacle for the prosperity of France.
Agreeing to the
dissolution of our marriage,
as I must, does not
change my feelings.
The emperor will have in me
a-always his-- his truest friend."
[Napoleon breathes shakily]
[sniffling]
[Joséphine] Emperor,
you have just pronounced the
word which separates us forever.
Your mistaken
ambition has ever been
and will continue to be
the guide of all your actions.
Nevertheless,
you can never doubt the sincerity
of my wishes for your happiness.
May it at least afford me some
consolation for my sufferings.
- Yours, Joséphine.
- Thank you.
- Good morning, madame.
- Thank you. What's your name?
- Fleur.
- Fleur. Pleasure.
[chuckling]
I miss you.
Marital life is very
agreeable now.
You've shown such
great courage so far.
[sighs]
You must maintain it.
Do not permit yourself
to fall into melancholy.
You look best when you're happy.
Please take care of your health.
It is precious to me.
Will you write me tomorrow?
Mm-hmm.
And the next day?
Yes.
And the day after that?
Mm-hmm.
- And the day after that?
- Yeah.
Good.
[kisses]
[door closes]
Once, an English ambassador
challenged my reasons for war.
He said, "You French,
you fight only for money,
while we English,
we fight for honor."
I replied, "Everyone
fights for what they lack."
[chuckles, stammers]
This is not-- This is not your story.
This never happened to you, did it?
Of course it did.
- Of course it did.
- What do you mean?
We had the same saying
with my people and the Turks.
- [chuckles]
- Do you?
The English lack honor.
We can agree on that.
- [Alexander] Listen, there is-- [sighs]
- [mosquito buzzes]
There's nothing I think we can agree
more with than our hatred for Britain.
I just have to say
that it actually--
It would be my absolute pleasure
and honor if I could call you my brother.
There is a way for
you to call me brother.
Last night, at
dinner, I was... [sighs]
...charmed by your sister.
[chuckles]
Is she spoken for?
Ah. Sadly, yes.
She's to be married to the
Duke of Oldenburg, I'm afraid.
Uh, and what of her
younger sister? Anna?
[stammers] Is there a
formal offer for Anna?
- [mosquito buzzes]
- [blows]
[chuckles]
Uh, well, you see,
An-Anna, she's 15 years old.
That is a detail.
[mosquitoes buzzing]
Our friendship is built on
our mutual distrust of England.
When we hold to the Continental
Blockade, we choke them from the trade,
and we fight for our
most sacred rights.
That is what is
important between us.
I just had a thought.
- No.
- No, say it.
- Should I tell you?
- Please.
Imagine an army. 50,000 men.
Russians, Frenchmen,
perhaps even Austrians,
marching by way of
Constantinople into Asia
would have only to
reach the Euphrates
to make England tremble and
bring her down on her knees
- before the continent.
- [chuckles]
It is incredible.
Toast.
[sighs]
- To you.
- To us.
His Majesty, the Emperor Napoleon,
wishes to make a formal offer to Austria
and to His Majesty,
King Francis,
for the hand of the
archduchess, Marie-Louise.
His eldest daughter.
No.
Uh, this union would bring
together Austria and France
in an unbreakable
matrimonial bond.
[in German] Is this a joke?
[in German] I may find it
humorous... but His Majesty does not.
[in English] Did you
have a pleasant journey?
It was wonderful. Thank you.
You're quite petite.
I'm not accustomed to that.
[Marie-Louise chuckles]
How do I look to you?
Do I resemble my portrait?
Oh, yes. And even more
handsome and strong.
And you are even more
handsome, more be-beautiful.
[chuckles] I hope you're
pleased with your choice.
I hope so too. Would you
like to see the bedroom?
[chuckles] Yes, thank you.
Your Majesty, your son.
[breathing shakily]
[doors close]
[soldier shouts, distant]
- Hello.
- [baby fusses]
[soldiers shouting, distant]
- [soldier] Fire!
- [distant gunfire]
- [baby crying]
- Oh. [shushing]
[crying stops]
[shouting continues, distant]
My little king.
[carriage driver]
Hyah, hyah, hyah!
[horse hooves approaching]
[carriage driver] Hold.
[baby fusses]
[baby coos]
[baby grunts]
[coos]
[cooing]
Oh, sweet child.
[baby grunts]
One day, you will understand
what I have sacrificed for you.
[baby cooing]
[sighs]
[in Russian] What's
good for Napoleon
is not good for Russia.
And if it is not
good for Russia,
it cannot be good
for His Majesty.
It is the timber trade with
Britain that makes Russia great.
Your father made
a serious error.
He put himself above Russia.
I do not want to
see Your Majesty
become unpopular
with the Russian people.
[inhales heavily]
I am not my father.
Do not make that regrettable
mistake of thinking that I am... again.
Russia will re-align itself with the
English. I am not afraid of Napoleon.
[Napoleon, in English] My
dear Joséphine, I'm sad today.
Tsar Alexander has turned against
me and forced me to invade Russia.
He's decided to open
his ports to England
while taxing the French.
I must wipe away my melancholy
and begin the march to Moscow.
I've convinced the heads
of Europe of this resolution,
and so I command the combined
forces of France, Austria, Italy,
Germany and Poland.
I see nothing but
success in my future.
[French soldier 1]
Keep your lines. Steady.
[French soldier 2] To the front.
[French soldier
3] Keep your step.
[speaking Russian]
- [shouting, grunting]
- [French soldier 1] Take cover!
[French soldier 2] Get down!
[French general]
Get down! Get down!
[Russian soldiers
speaking Russian]
[French general]
Hyah, hyah! Hyah!
After them! After them!
[grunts]
[Russian soldier grunts]
[grunting]
Whoa, whoa.
- [horse nickering]
- Whoa.
[horse whinnies]
- Get back! Drop back. Retreat.
- [grunts] Fall back!
[soldiers shouting]
[Napoleon] My dear Joséphine.
I'm writing to you because I
have just won a great battle today.
Tomorrow we will
resume our advance.
Moscow is now
only 200 miles away.
And I think of you all
the while. All yours.
[flies buzzing]
[gasps, coughs]
[groans]
[French soldier] Spread out.
Search the buildings.
[grunting, muttering]
Search everywhere.
[French soldier] Nearly
there. Nearly there.
- [French soldier 2] Thank you, sir.
- [speaks indistinctly]
[soldier coughing]
- Thank you, Admiral.
- You were the brave of Austerlitz.
[dogs barking]
[Napoleon shouting]
Where are you?
300,000 souls
lived in this city.
And they've all just left?
Little boy.
Pspspsps.
Where are you?
Don't be frightened.
I'm just gonna give
you a little spanking.
It's not very sporting, is it?
For his honor and
Russia's, not mine.
There's dignity to
be had in defeat.
[snoring]
[fire crackling]
[gasps, breathing heavily]
Who did this?
They did.
No, they did not. Be sensible.
- Who set these fires?
- [sighs]
Your Majesty, they did.
[sighs]
He'd rather burn his own
city than negotiate with me.
I didn't think he
had the courage.
Well, we'll go to Saint Petersburg
and have him burn that too.
We have let too
much time slip away.
We would be marching
into the Russian winter
with horses that are not
raised for this weather.
If we go back to Poland, we
can wait out the winter months.
Hmm?
[shouts]
[Joséphine] Napoleon, your letters
are a soothing balm to my heart.
I fear for you.
Remember that I alone
know your health...
- [spits]
- ...your fears.
I thank you as tenderly
as I will always love you.
Joséphine.
[sighs]
The horseman's disease,
Your Majesty. Piles.
Make it better.
[doctor] As you
wish, Your Majesty.
[sighing]
[Napoleon] My friend, Joséphine.
"Friend."
It is strange to write
that word to you.
You have always
been so much more.
[soldiers coughing]
[fife playing]
[Napoleon] Despite careful organization,
there have been breakdowns in supply.
We're suffering sickness,
desertion and famine.
We are winning.
[soldiers coughing]
- [Napoleon] Us or Cossacks?
- [French general] Us.
[Napoleon sighs] Joséphine.
Fortune has abandoned me.
I know that it is
what fate has for me.
Your words rattle in my head.
I am nothing without you.
I have no confidence.
I'm scared and I'm alone.
My men do not look
at me like you do.
I know I will return home to the
judgment of these European kings.
And they will not judge me
as they judge themselves.
They will punish me
by a standard they would
never apply to each other.
I wish you could put me on
your knee and take care of me.
[Berthier] Get the horses
covered and under shelter.
[Caulaincourt] This way,
Your Majesty. Over here.
[soldiers shouting]
[grunting]
Into the barn, quickly!
Everyone, in!
- Let us in!
- We're gonna freeze out here. Let us in!
- Block the doors!
- You have to find somewhere else.
Open up the doors!
We're gonna freeze to death.
Open the doors!
[soldiers shouting, grunting]
Out of my way!
We're gonna die out here!
[sniffs]
[grunting]
Majesty?
[exhales sharply, sniffs]
Yeah?
It's time for you to
leave this misery behind
and return to Paris.
I've found a way.
There's a sleigh
behind this building.
With two horses, we can
make Warsaw in a week.
Paris soon after.
It's our only way to get
you back alive, Majesty.
[breathes heavily] Please.
[French soldiers snoring]
- [screaming] Fire! Fire! Fire!
- Fire! Fire!
- [clamoring]
- It's spreading!
[French soldier 1] Hey,
wake up! Wake up! Get up!
- Fire!
[clamoring]
[screaming]
[panting]
- Put it out!
- Fire! Fire!
[clamoring continues]
This is a triumphant return.
I am the victor.
Alexander abandoned his city.
And though he lacks honor
and failed to sign a peace treaty,
my presence back home
will be proof to my people
they have no one
to fear in the world.
They fear you, Majesty.
They fear no one but you.
Do you think I'm this terrible--
terrible pers-- person
with a bad temper?
- No.
- Of course you don't.
You're not an idiot.
Or maybe you are.
I hope you get
eaten by Cossacks.
Stop!
[sleigh driver] Whoa, whoa.
[breathing heavily]
[wolf howling]
Where are we?
Borodino, Majesty.
- [howling continues]
- [horse neighs]
[Napoleon] I hear the
muskrats are agitated in Paris
at the idea of the
emperor's return.
The coward, Tsar Alexander,
now knows what I'm capable of.
Who else can move half a
million men everywhere in Europe?
Now a farmer boy knows that he
can become a marshal of the empire.
A minister. A cardinal.
[breathing heavily]
When I move, the
world moves forward.
[whimpering]
[Talleyrand] Of the 600,000
men you sent to Russia,
only 40,000 have returned.
Therefore, you have been
exiled in no uncertain terms.
The allied coalition of Austria,
Prussia, Russia and England,
and with the agreement
of the French Council,
grant you sovereignty
of the island of Elba.
A revenue of two million
francs from the French funds,
pensions for the Bonaparte family
and the Empress Marie-Louise.
It also provides for Empress
Joséphine to retain all of her properties
and an allotted annual
income of one million francs.
[sighs]
[sniffling]
I love France too much.
All I've desired was its glory.
I would never
bring her misfortune.
They want me to
abdicate. [sighs]
Fine, I'll abdicate.
[townsfolk
chattering in Italian]
Good.
[chuckles]
Wine.
[bell tolling]
[grunting]
Your Highness.
Empress.
[Joséphine] Here.
[Alexander] Joséphine,
Joséphine. Hmm?
[chuckles] I am charmed.
But... [sighs]
...you do not have to lock yourself
away just because he's not here.
I know what it is like
to be underestimated.
But your eyes, your
charm and your spirit,
it is in there.
It is yours, and you can use it.
[classical music playing]
[Napoleon] Boy, what day is it?
Tuesday.
The 11th?
Yes.
[inhales sharply] Boy, do you
know who Tsar Alexander is?
[stammers] No.
But you knew who I was?
[stammers] Yes.
There we are.
Ugh.
You know, it brings
me no great joy
to sit with my son and
have him gloomy and sullen.
[sighs]
You were not meant to
die on this island, my son.
My wife is entertaining
the Russian Emperor...
in my home.
[sighs]
[Napoleon] Dear Joséphine,
You are mine.
You will always be.
- I cannot stand it any longer.
- [crew member shouting]
It has been 300
days on this rock,
and I'm ready to come
home and reclaim what's mine:
you and France.
[crew members shouting]
[Napoleon] I'm taking your ship.
If you do not provoke me,
you do not have to fear me.
[Joséphine] Napoleon,
I'm a flower that opens its
petals and smiles to the sunshine,
unconscious that the storm
is near which will lay me low
- and scatter leaves to the heavens.
- [groans]
Come quickly, my friend.
[kisses]
- [wheezing]
- If you would open your mouth, please.
[groaning]
Thank you.
Well, your chest is congested.
Your throat is aflame.
My suggestion is to stay in bed.
[wheezing] But
Napoleon is coming.
It would be unwise
to receive any visitors.
But Napoleon is coming.
I understand.
[wheezing]
[Dr. Corvisart] Just
keep her comfortable.
Whoa, whoa!
Your Majesty.
You may speak.
Bonaparte, Your
Majesty. He has returned.
A ship landed on a beach
in Antibes this morning,
and they're on the march.
Napoleon Bonaparte is
marching towards Paris.
[breathing heavily]
More.
Your Majesty.
Afternoon, Colonel.
[colonel] Your Majesty.
General Marchand,
in defense of the royal
government of King Louis XVIII,
requests that you surrender your
weapons and cease your march
so that you may be arrested
and returned to your island.
Will you please inform the general that
I shall like to come and speak with him?
I have no fight with
my own Fifth Army.
Sir.
He wishes to speak.
Make ready!
Present.
Soldiers of the Fifth Regiment,
do you recognize me?
Do you recognize me, soldiers?
[French soldier] Yes, Emperor!
[laughing]
[Napoleon] I miss you.
I'm melancholy for my home...
and for our victories together.
I want to come home.
Will you join me?
Long live the emperor!
- Long live the emperor!
- [pledging continues]
- [cheering]
[crying]
[grunting]
Your Majesty.
[whimpering]
Thank you.
On May 26th,
Dr. Corvisart was called
and found her chest congested
and her throat inflamed.
Her illness was diphtheria.
On May 29th, last sacrament
was given, and she died.
And no one thought to notify me?
[sighs]
Hortense.
Do you blame--
[breathes shakily]
Do you blame me?
- [sniffles]
- I don't blame you.
Of course not.
I'm not to bear the burden of
responsibility... [breathes shakily]
...for the misfortunes
of your mother.
I want the letters that
I wrote to her. [sniffles]
I'm sorry, I don't have them.
They were stolen by her valet.
[blows]
Where did she keep them?
In the cupboard in her
bedroom, next to her bed.
What did he do with them?
Her valet sold them.
- [cries]
- [Hortense] I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
[congress member] Napoleon
Bonaparte has destroyed
the only title upon which
his very existence depended.
This congregation of allies
shall form along the borders
of France and Belgium an army.
70,000 troops from England,
120,000 troops from Prussia.
This vermin has routed
the farmyards of Europe
while the farmers snored.
We should have struck
this blow long ago.
He has held the world
hostage with his egotism,
his insatiable hunger for power,
and his lack of
simple good manners.
We will all sleep
again without him.
I believe I speak for all of us when I
say that the only regret we all share
is that we allowed
this vermin to live at all.
250,000 men with the traitor.
25,000 men, 125,000 men
and 100,000 men...
against our 125,000 men.
This is a fight on land.
This is what Britain does not
know how to do that I know.
Strike quickly against
Wellington and Blücher.
Defeat them separately.
Disallow them from
uniting forces here.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
[sniffs]
Morning.
- Morning.
- [grunts]
The Prussians are advancing.
We should begin the offensive.
[Napoleon] We must
wait for the ground to dry.
Blücher will never make it in
time. I'll have Wellington by lunch.
[thunder rumbling]
[sighs, grunts]
[clears throat]
I never get wet if I can
help it. [clears throat]
[thunder rumbling]
What shall I tell the men?
Tell them to make the rain stop.
- [British soldier 1] Coming through!
- [British soldier 2] In formation!
[Wellesley] Now's your
time, lads. Now's your time.
Now, listen very carefully.
Patience is the order of the day
today. Patience shall win the day.
We must hold this ground.
Let them come to us.
[soldiers] Huzzah!
Go on, boys. Go on.
Whoa.
Good morning, General Blücher.
- Good morning.
- Estimated time of arrival, sir?
- Officer?
- About five hours.
About five hours.
Come on, boys. Come on, boys.
[grunts]
[soldier shouting, distant]
Oh, there he is.
He appears to be...
[chuckles] ...just sleeping.
One thing you cannot resist,
my friend, is a frontal attack.
Let's see how this general
can attack our position.
Sir. I have the emperor in my
sights. Do I have permission to fire?
Certainly not.
Generals commanding armies
have better things to do with their time
than to shoot at one another.
Hold your fire, rifleman,
on pain of death.
Go on, boys. Come, come.
[British soldier] A
runner coming through!
Blücher, 11 to 12 miles, sir.
[British general 1]
Attention, follow me.
- Blücher at 11 to 12 miles, sir.
- Jesus Christ.
- I want a report every hour.
- Yes, sir.
[French soldier] Runner
coming through. Make way.
Oh. Oh.
[panting] Prussians on
the roadside, 12 miles.
Prussian troops have been sighted
on the road, sire. Twelve miles.
Ready the cannons.
Ready the cannons!
[French soldiers clamoring]
[French general] Go on! Move!
[French soldiers shouting]
[French soldier 1] Ready!
Cannons are ready!
[French soldier 2]
[French general] The
rain has stopped, sir.
Prepare to fire!
[breathes heavily]
- Fire!
- [French soldiers] Fire!
[British general 2] Take cover!
Straight into position. Steady.
Prepare for the
advance. Get ready.
Prepare for the advance.
Readjust to 195!
Adjust 195!
[French soldier] Elevation 195.
Adjusted!
Prepare to fire! Fire!
[French soldiers] Fire!
[British soldiers
shouting, screaming]
[British general 2] Keep your
head down. Seventh, take over.
[screaming]
- [British soldier] Out the way!
- [British general 3] Hold fast, men!
Infantry, advance!
- [march playing]
- [French general 1] Left company!
[speaks indistinctly] And march!
[French general 2]
Get in formation. Now!
Keep them away!
Join!
[drums playing]
[French general] Second wave,
advance! Over the top, men!
Hold the line!
Cannons!
- Fire!
- [French soldiers shouting]
[British general 1] Get ready.
[British general 3] Hold fast.
[British general 2] Fire!
[British general 3] You
there, get on that cannon.
[French soldiers clamoring]
[British soldier] Fire!
[screaming]
[French general 2] Fill the gap!
[French general
1] Keep the line!
[soldiers shouting]
Skirmishers, keep
advancing! [yelps]
[French general
2] Get in formation.
Fire at will.
[British general 2] Keep
them back, men. Fire.
[drums playing]
Go on, go on.
Don't let them rally!
[clamoring]
[British general 2 speaks
indistinctly] ...the strike position.
[French runner] Get up,
boys. Go on. Go on, boys.
Whoa, whoa.
Prussians, roadside, five miles.
[French general] Five
miles, maybe less.
We have to act
before Blücher arrives.
Out.
Out!
- [British general 2 shouting]
- [French general] Cavalry!
Charge!
[French army shouting]
Prepare to receive cavalry.
[British general] Prepare
to receive cavalry.
[soldiers shouting]
[Wellesley] We must hold our
ground. Stand fast to the last man.
We must not be beat!
Or what will they
say in England?
- [British general] Hold the line.
- [British soldier] Keep it tight.
[soldiers shouting]
[British general] Steady,
men. Stay in formation.
[French soldier]
Long live the emperor!
[British general] Company, halt!
[British general 2] Form
square! Form square!
[shouting, clamoring]
[French general]
Long live the emperor!
[British general] One
section, fire. Two section, fire.
[soldiers shouting, grunting]
[screams]
[grunts]
[French general] What do we
do, sir? We can't break through.
[British general] Keep them
running. Get them back in the square.
Show them your British steel.
[breathing heavily]
[French colonel] Present arms!
[huffs]
Shoulder, hold!
- They're here, the Prussians.
- [grunts]
- First over the rise, Emperor.
[panting]
[soldiers shouting]
[French soldier 1] We
need to find a way through!
[French soldier 2] Break
the square. Break the square!
[screams]
[clamoring]
[Napoleon] Charge bayonets.
[French colonel]
Charge bayonets!
Your Emperor is with you.
You are the brave of Austerlitz.
Never surrender.
For homeland and glory!
[British general] Shoulder
to shoulder! Form lines!
[British general 2]
Shoulder to shoulder.
[soldiers shouting]
[exclaims]
Infantry, advance.
- Battalion and infantry! Advance!
- [sighs]
[French general] Keep the line!
[British general] Footmen, fire!
Second line, fire.
Prepare to charge!
Charge!
[soldiers shouting]
[British general]
Go on! Batter them!
[British general 2]
Advance! Advance!
Cavalry advance, sir?
Cavalry advance.
[British general] Prepare for
counter. Prepare for counter.
Full support.
[shouting]
[screams]
[screaming]
[soldiers screaming, grunting]
[grunting]
No. He can't help himself.
[British general] Sir, Blücher.
Thank God.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Come see how a
marshal of France dies!
Yeah! Hyah!
[pants]
[gunshot fires]
Yeah! Yeah!
[soldiers struggling]
[shouting, screaming]
The battle is mine. There
will be an end to the war.
[whistle blowing]
[British general]
Senior officer, on deck!
Good day, good day, good day.
I am the first to admit when I
make a mistake. But I never do.
Because it is geometry.
I simply know precisely
where to place a cannon.
But tragically I cannot transfer this
knowledge to my marshals. [sighs]
That might be what
is most difficult in life.
Accepting the
failures of others.
You must not do that.
Encourage greatness.
- Mind your head, sir.
- [Wellesley grunts]
[British general]
Mind your head, sir.
- What are they doing there?
- Sir, it's the midshipmen. They adore him.
Well, get 'em out.
Clear the room. Uh, quickly.
- Your grace--
- Good morning, General.
These boys are delightful.
May I sit down?
Please.
[clears throat, sniffs]
And this breakfast.
Now I know why you have such
a successful navy. Thank you.
- [grunts]
- [Wellesley clears throat]
I've never visited the
English countryside.
I imagine I'll love
the Cotswolds...
- soft rolling hills, gentle light.
- [sighs]
Uh, my dear sir, it is only
by a narrow margin of opinion
that you have been spared
the fate of being shot.
[scoffs]
[chuckles] Politically,
I'm afraid it's impossible
for the British government to
allow you to stay in England.
You are permitted three
officers and 12 servants
to accompany you into exile.
Exile will be contained to
the island of Saint Helena
under the watchful eye of Governor
Hudson Lowe and his family.
[grunts]
Saint...
Helena. It's a small island.
[chuckles] More
of a rock, really.
A thousand miles from
the mainland of Africa.
I'm told it's very pretty, tranquil.
You'll have time to reflect.
Your correspondence
will be monitored,
your presence verified twice
daily by the orderly officer.
I see.
If I were to land
on British soil,
I would be allowed, by your
law, to stand here for a trial.
- [scoffs]
- You are denying me that.
[clears throat]
[exhales deeply, laughing]
One must also not forget
that I am only a man.
You forgot it, sir.
You thought you were a god.
I never said s-such a thing.
[crew member] Fix that
rigging line. Draw up the sails.
Go below deck!
[crew shouting]
[Joséphine] What will you do
now? I hate to see you alone.
Will you come to
me? Will I forgive you?
My sweet, stubborn Emperor.
I let you loose and
let you come to ruin.
Next time, I will be Emperor,
and you will do as I say.
[Napoleon] Well, you were right.
Every night I beg to
see you in my dreams.
And when I do, you turn me away.
- [soldiers chattering]
- [children laughing]
[Napoleon] Precision!
Precision.
[groans] Slow down.
First, you salute each other.
And drop down like this.
En garde.
Left foot back.
Yes.
Then you'll do two attacks.
Prime and seconde.
Okay?
Hold this.
Very good.
[children laughing]
[child] This way's more fun.
Girls, what's the
capital of France?
Paris.
And Russia?
Petersburg. And Moscow before.
Moscow. And who burnt
Moscow to the ground?
I don't know, sir.
I did.
I believe, sir, the Russians
burnt it to get rid of the French.
Who told you that?
It's common knowledge, sir.
[children chuckle]
Go. Go play.
[child] En garde.
[Joséphine] Can I tell you
what I have waiting for you?
[children laughing]
It is a secret. And I will
show you when you arrive.
Come to me, Napoleon.
And let's try this again.