h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
According to our intelligence,
Gilberto Rodríguez was
a stabilizing influence on the cartel.
His arrest may lead
to an increased violence
against civilians and police.
No doubt...
...the cartel leaders are now in hiding,
and their security apparatus
is operating in a state of high alert.
So, the only thing
we can be certain of
is that any further operation
against the cartel
will be both very difficult
and extremely dangerous.
We appreciate the volatility
of the situation, General.
Well, in that case,
I will turn things over to the man
who's responsible for this situation.
Maybe he can walk us
through his path to victory.
So Agent Peña, what comes next?
The floor is yours.
Don Gilberto...
- Leave it there.
- Okay.
Enjoy your meal.
- Hello?
- 'Hi, brother, it's me.
- 'How are you doing?'
- Better if I knew how this happened.
'Gilberto, someone betrayed us.
Where the fuck were those pigs we pay?'
It was an American operation.
It was the DEA.
Our friends knew nothing about it.
Unless our friends
have been lying to us all along.
Maybe they need a reminder
what all that money was for.
Relax, Miguel.
My situation will be rectified soon.
'The truth is that things
are getting more complicated.'
And our friends in the North Valley
need reassurance.
You need to set a meeting
with Henao.
'Compliment him.'
- On what?
- Doesn't matter. Offer him something.
'He likes tequila.
Have a bottle ready.'
Tell him...
this is just a small setback.
'In the meantime,
business goes on as usual.'
Increase your personal security.
'The Americans
will come after you next.
'Your freedom is our best leverage,
brother.'
Gilberto, this is getting dangerous.
What if there's a leak?
There may be.
Find out.
'I need to go, brother. I love you.'
I love you too, brother.
- 'What do you got for me?'
- Dog shit. Minus the dog and the shit.
Well, we knew it wasn't gonna be easy.
You gotta get creative.
All due respect, we're being told
we can't leave the base without an escort,
and now,
in a truly shocking turn of events,
we're being told there isn't enough
manpower to assign us one.
'We're fucking grounded.'
Look, I'll see what I can do
with the lockdown. I gotta go.
I'm meeting with the new
Minister of Defence.
And Feistl... you asked for this.
'Don't forget that, cos I know I won't.'
'Colombia had recently
elected a new president,
'a man named Ernesto Samper.
'Escobar's hitters had tried
to assassinate him in an earlier election.
'So he was no friend of the narcos.
'And while he knew his country
was tired of violence,
'he and his new staff, including
Defence Minister Fernando Botero,
'were already in a tough spot.
'Politically, the surrender deal was ugly,
but they were willing to live with it.
'Gilberto's arrest made that
harder than planned,
'and they weren't shy about saying it.'
I wanted to offer
my congratulations
on the arrest of Gilberto Rodríguez.
Thank you, sir.
Colonel Martínez deserves the credit.
Unfortunately,
he isn't here to receive it.
He should be.
I imagine he knew there might be
consequences for his actions.
A surrender deal was on the table,
which would've brought all four leaders
of the Cali cartel to justice.
And now, that's been complicated,
and we are faced with the unknown.
Understood.
Though I'm not sure murderers negotiating
their own punishment qualifies as justice.
The deal preceded my tenure.
But between the two of us,
I share your reservations.
But no one wants a return
to the days of Pablo Escobar
and the bloodshed of Los Pepes.
No, of course not.
I won't ask if the rumours
about your involvement
with the vigilantes are true,
but I do have a question.
If it turns out that
we are indeed on the same side,
can I trust you?
You can trust that my only agenda
is to take down the Cali cartel.
Let me know if I can do anything.
Sir, my team in Cali
are operating under...
...severe restrictions.
They need their independence.
I'll make a call.
Thank you, sir.
Peña...
Justice can be hard to find.
And a man as powerful
as Gilberto Rodríguez
won't stay in custody for long.
If you want to keep him behind bars,
you need someone to testify.
Yes, sir. I'm on it.
I'm working on a high-level target.
I suggest you work fast,
because without it,
nothing else will matter.
We went through the machine, sir.
We've got nothing.
So what am I supposed to do with that?
What does this mean?
If somebody sold us out,
we'd know about it.
Like you knew about the raid?
Look, gentlemen...
I want to know why my brother
is sitting in a fucking cell.
And if any one of us is involved in this,
I want to know by the end of the day.
Of course. Consider it done, sir.
Miguel's paranoid.
Maybe they used one of their spy planes
and spotted Gilberto from space.
You're not taking this seriously.
Miguel doesn't think they got lucky.
He thinks there's a leak.
And the system would tell us
about the leak.
This is about the surrender, right?
You're worried your retirement plans
are ruined now.
Listen to me. People love drama, brother.
You know that.
This isn't drama. He wants names.
And there's no reason to think
they couldn't be ours, Carlo.
We designed the system.
Mr. Cordova.
So? Anything good?
Just a bunch of shit-talking.
Gossip. Typical.
And what about internally?
Anyone suspicious you've flagged?
No, not really. Truth is, I have no idea
who would rat these guys out.
I want to hear everything you've flagged,
all the same. Quickly.
Yes, sir. I'll get that right away.
'These guys were supposed
to have all this under control.
'But it's clear they don't.'
'I thought those guys
were supposed to surrender.
'Does this mean it's not happening?'
'Somebody tipped off
the Americans, stabbed us in the back.'
'Where was his fucking security
team? What do they pay them for?'
'They better do something quick,
'or else it's going to be
every man for himself.'
You have many powerful allies,
Don Gilberto.
Your situation pains them deeply.
We're confident this will soon be
behind us. The surrender will proceed.
But we need to wait.
It's a matter of time.
Wait for what?
For the government to do something
they already agreed to? Fuck.
What did Medina say?
Currently, we don't have
an official position from Santiago Medina.
Why not?
Because we're waiting on his office
to confirm a meeting.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You didn't talk to him yet?
You're waiting on his office
to confirm a meeting?
I don't wait on him!
He waits on me!
You go to his office and fix this mess!
And remind him who the fuck
Gilberto Rodríguez is!
For fuck's sake!
Open this damn thing!
Nicolás, your father needs to understand
his arrest changes things.
It's political now.
Dad?
Sometimes you have to put on
a little show.
Helps bring the best out of people.
- I need to talk to Medina.
- I don't want you anywhere near this.
Dad, the circle is too big.
Medina won't meet anyone he can't trust.
He won't trust the lawyers.
But he will trust you?
Yes, I'm your son.
That's right.
And you'll obey my wishes.
'It's cold here all the time.
'I wake up
and the bed is freezing, empty.'
'I know,bonita.
I'll be home soon.'
'I just wish
I could be there with you.'
'I told you, Chris, it wouldn't look right.
it's not a good time.'
- Any word on the location?
- Nothing yet.
'I don't know, Franklin.
Maybe now is the perfect fucking time.
'You really think
they're gonna stop with Gilberto?
'And how long before the DEA
comes looking for you? For us?'
'Listen, I need you
to be strong, okay, babe?
'Nobody knows about us.
Nobody's looking for me, I promise.
- 'I'll call you later. I love you.'
- 'No, wait, Franklin...'
She's panicking.
Where are you going?
To give things a push.
We're running out of time.
Okay, can we talk
about this wiretap, though?
I mean, the legality of it?
Stoddard...
I want you to think about where
you see your career in five years.
Does having that conversation help
or hurt your chances of getting there?
You want something to drink?
I never refuse.
That's a great shirt, no?
That pocket... on the left.
Where the heart is.
Hey, this situation with Gilberto,
what a disgrace, huh?
After all your family's done
for this city. For this country.
Just the gringos meddling
where they shouldn't.
But our friends in Bogotá
are working to...
...rectify the situation.
Business proceeds as usual, right?
And how does this clerical error
affect the timeline of the surrender?
As I said...
...this was just a mistake.
Nothing more.
Glad to hear that.
I see a lot of new faces.
Did you notice that?
The woman, the Salazar girl?
The fear.
Miguel was scared.
These guys are in big trouble.
Little early for number three, no?
The fuck else am I supposed to do
around here?
You didn't have to come.
Who else was gonna watch your back?
You gonna tell me
what went down in Juárez?
I told you...
...we talked.
The Mexican made you an offer.
Didn't he?
Yes.
A pretty good one, too.
He says we're getting out
at the wrong time.
Maybe he's right.
Gilberto's in jail.
Maybe this is fate.
How'd you come up with this place?
Buddy in the Defence Department.
The place was leased out
to debrief a witness against Noriega.
That was like three years ago.
Danny, you never cease to amaze me.
Not bad, right?
Well, the fucking A/C's still running.
Yeah, your tax dollars at work.
So? What's our first move?
Circle back. See if we can pick up
a trail on that accountant.
World's deadliest fanny pack,
back in action.
Better fucking believe it.
No, the bill, please.
Compliments of the gentleman.
- Thank you, but I don't...
- Oh, uh...
Did I come over too fast?
It's tricky business
starting a conversation.
Not a lot of margin for error.
- You're an American.
- Yeah. Javi. From Texas.
- You?
- I'm from Boston originally.
Strangers in a strange land.
Well, I hope you don't mind. I was...
I saw you sitting over here and you...
...reminded me of someone,
someone from home.
Ah! Sentimental.
Just a lonely patriot.
Anyway, I thought we could talk.
- Okay.
- No, I mean it. Just...
Just talk.
- I heard people still do that sometimes.
- Oh, yeah.
You know,
I think I saw it in a movie once.
Look, you seem like a nice guy,
but I get the feeling
that just talking isn't your forte.
- And... I'm married, so...
- Happily?
Wow. Look at you now.
What? I mean, come on.
Your husband lets you brave the dangers
of happy hour by yourself?
He's traveling for work.
Oh, can I guess? He's...
...an astronaut.
- Brain surgeon.
- Yeah, uh-huh, a little bit of both.
- Uh-huh.
- Banking.
Oh, fuck.
I thought I couldn't like him any less.
I mean...
Okay, well, this has been fun.
So, what exotic destination
could pull him away from...
...from all this?
Say hi to Texas for me.
Christina...
I didn't tell you my name.
You didn't have to.
Okay... You got me.
How do you know my name?
Same way I know that your husband...
isn't in banking.
My name's Javier Peña.
I work for the DEA.
You want to sit back down,
have a conversation?
I'm not interested.
Enjoy your drink, Eliot Ness.
Fuck.
The bill.
And they don't appear
on the next flights either?
No.
Jorge... Motherfucking gringos
never got on a plane back to Bogotá.
- Our friend with the badge lied to us.
- Or he made a mistake.
There are no mistakes.
Hey. Here he comes.
There he is, the fucking bastard.
I would have gladly met you
in the usual place.
That's what you're worried about?
How about earning the money we pay you
to keep our bosses out of jail?
- You couldn't give a fuck about that.
- The fuck you want from me?
Logistics, planning, the dummy raid.
All that shit came out of Bogotá.
By the time we knew
what they were up to...
Martínez had already been
in Gilberto's house for 30 minutes,
you useless piece of shit.
You know what else is odd?
It looks like the DEA never left Cali.
And you were the one who confirmed.
You, only you, confirmed those two
fucking gringos took the plane to Bogotá.
Do you know where you are?
You want to hang me out to dry with
your boss? Do you know where you are?
I asked the Americans how they found
Gilberto's house. Know what they told me?
They followed someone there.
I know it wasn't me.
Fucking Calderón.
What he said made sense.
The DEA followed someone
to Gilberto's house.
It must be Pallomari. The DEA knows
who he is and where he works.
They must've come back
and tailed him to Gilberto.
Didn't you say you drove Pallomari
to Gilberto's that night?
It could just as easily have been me
driving him.
Yeah, but it wasn't, was it?
You think Miguel will let this slide?
Not a fucking chance.
Jorge, if this thing comes back on me,
it comes back on you,
and then we're both fucked.
The only thing we need is a name,
and we have it.
We have to get on the same page here.
Calderón told us those fuckers from
the DEA got on a plane to Bogotá, right?
He burned us. He's the one
responsible for what happened.
He's a dirty cop...
...who takes money from a drug cartel.
But you and me, we are brothers.
Let me cut to the chase.
My father still wants to retire.
I didn't realise you were taking such
an active role in your father's affairs.
No other choice when friends
don't return our lawyer's calls.
Of course.
Well, then,
tell your father there is still a path
to what he wants most.
No one here is happy
with the current predicament.
The DEA blindsided all of us, and it's
been difficult to carry out our old deal.
"Old deal"?
Nicolás...
Politics is about appearances.
For us, it's extremely difficult
to accept the surrender terms
of a man who's already in prison.
That just looks bad.
But different terms, new terms...
What do you say?
So what did you find out?
The DEA team that Calderón
was escorting never left Cali.
He reported that they had.
- What do you think, Jorge?
- It was a mistake.
Born of incompetence.
The DEA got lucky...
and Calderón took the bait.
Well, we're not paying for incompetence.
Besides, that doesn't explain
how they found my brother.
How did they get that information?
Was that also Calderón?
It's unlikely.
It's possible the DEA used
some high-end aerial surveillance.
From here on out,
keep an eye on Calderón.
Limit what we tell him.
No more lapses in security.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Thank you, Jorge.
It's either him or us.
What if they kill him?
They wouldn't kill a cop.
But they can question him.
And then what? What?
By the time they get to it,
this shit will all be over.
Hello?
'Good afternoon. Someone is here
for you, Mrs. Jurado. Mr. Eliot Ness.'
Thanks for seeing me.
Didn't want you waving a badge
around our lobby.
Are you gonna arrest me?
You want to sit?
If what I wanted counted for anything,
you wouldn't be
in my living room right now.
May not see it this way yet,
but I... I am here to help you.
Oh, I'm sure my well-being
is your top priority.
It's why you were buying me
martinis at the bar.
Gilberto Rodríguez is in jail.
It won't be long before he has company.
There's a very small window
for people like you and your husband
to still be of any use to us.
You're running out of time.
So if Franklin really does care about you,
then he'll do what's right.
I mean, I don't know if the two of you
are thinking about starting a family...
Okay, look, for the record, you don't know
a fucking thing about my husband or me.
Okay. You're right.
But I do know that
there is no future for you
in any version of how this plays out
if he doesn't help us.
I didn't plan on living like this.
It was...
It was a mistake...
not stopping it sooner.
You ever done anything like that?
I have.
Okay.
So... what, that's it?
That's it.
Think it over.
But don't take too long.
Don't you even
want to know what he said?
How dare you disregard my wishes.
Nobody was going to get into a room
with Medina, and I did...
I don't want you involved.
I won't even discuss it.
The old deal is dead.
But we can make a new one,
with certain adjustments.
Motherfuckers.
Adjustments how?
There has to be some jail time.
For you, Uncle Miguel,
Pacho and Chepe.
- Three years.
- Three years? No chance.
You surrender your illegal assets,
do the three years,
and the legitimate assets, the cash,
the business, will all be retained.
That's not the deal.
And you won't speak of this again.
Dad, stop being so stubborn!
You don't get to surrender.
You are in jail.
You are a narcotrafficker.
No politician is going to stand up
and say, "Let him go,"
no matter how much money
you've put in his pocket.
But son, it's three years...
It's not the old deal,
but it's a good one.
The best we're going to get.
But there's one loose end.
Medina is worried about his exposure.
More specifically,
the accountant... Pallomari.
He knows too much.
'Hola, bonita.'
Baby, I thought
you said that you were gonna call.
'I know. I had a late meeting.'
Sorry, babe. I'm sorry.
Can you leave it there?
Danki masha danki.
Right?
'Thank you.
Sorry. Room service.'
How many of those little cakes
have you eaten so far?
I can see our island from my room.
'I miss you,bonita.'
Franklin... what are we gonna do?
Christina, you can't just walk away
from these people.
I know you keep saying that,
but maybe...
maybe we have more options
than we think.
What do you mean,
"more options"?
'You know things. You know things
about the organisation...'
'You want me to be a rat?
Have you been talking to someone?'
'No, I just... Franklin, we need to talk.
We really need to talk about the future.'
'We can't do this
on the phone. I'll call you later.'
Rewind.
Okay.
'I had a late meeting.
Sorry, babe. I'm sorry.
'Can you leave it there?
Danki masha danki. Right?
'Thank you.
Sorry. Room service.'
I think I might know where he is.
They probably set up shop
somewhere else after the raid.
'Salcedo.'
The Americans are back
on the accountant's office,
hoping he shows.
Knowing that idiot, he might.
If that's all they've got,
then they don't have much.
'Stay on them.
Find out where they sleep at night.'
All right.
Hey, boss. You doing okay?
- 'You sound tired.'
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Keep me posted.
- How was the science test?
- Good.
Daddy!
My princess. Hello, my princesses.
How are you all?
Hello. What are you doing here?
Hi, my love.
Was it your turn or mine
to pick up the girls?
Yours. I was in the neighbourhood.
Just wanted to see how my girls are doing.
- Daddy, today we have piano lessons.
- I know, my love.
My little virtuosos.
And you? Everything okay?
I'm fine.
I just felt like I needed to see my girls.
That's why I came.
Excuse me.
Looks like I have to go.
Would you excuse me? Okay?
- Girls... I love you.
- Bye.
Bye, be good.
Salcedo.
- 'Where are you?'
- What can I do for you, David?
'My dad called a meeting.
Top personnel.'
What do you mean, a meeting?
We just had one.
'Well, we're having another one.
'2611 Avenida 14. Out by Jamundí.
See you there.'
'It's Carlo Cordova.
Leave a message.'
Carlo, I just talked to David.
Are you on your way to the meeting?
Call me.
Stoddard. Get this.
According to the language guy at SLS,
Dasha masha danki
means: "Thank you very much"
in Papiamento.
Okay.
Curaçao.
Curaçao... I guess there's
a lot of banks there.
Yeah, there's a lot
of fucking banks there. Here it is.
Baoase Luxury Resort.
Has an island villa you can rent.
Okay. What do we do then?
Call the Dutch Caribbean police
in Willemstad.
Ask them if they can confirm
anyone staying under
one of Franklin Jurado's aliases.
- We got him, didn't we?
- Not yet.
But he's there.
- Call them.
- Yeah.
'It's Carlo Cordova.
Leave a message.'
I'm sitting there,
enjoying my dick getting sucked,
when all of the sudden she stops.
I open my eyes
and I ask her, "What's up?"
She's all quiet,
looking at me like this.
Not a word.
I'm like, "What the fuck?"
I turn to see Toque.
Fuck, he has a gun pointed at him.
Like this.
And the other girl,
the one with the gun, says to me:
"Give me the money,
or she bites your dick off."
- So what did you do?
- I gave her the fucking money!
I even tipped her, Pacho.
You don't mess around with that!
- You want some ice?
- Sure.
I'm having a great time.
I'm heading to Juárez tomorrow.
Got some business with my partners.
What am I going to tell them, Pacho?
I want to give them an answer.
Some good news.
My turn to tell you a story, Amado.
About the time my father found me
in my room with a boy.
Hey, I never judged you for that stuff.
My father told me I wasn't a man,
that I'd never be one.
- It was the last time he spoke to me.
- What a fucking bastard.
For a long time,
I thought he was right.
Even after I started working
for Gilberto and Miguel.
Up until the day some motherfucker
told them I was a faggot.
And that it was a mistake
to let me be part of the business.
You know what they did?
They made me a partner.
Gilberto, Miguel and Chepe,
they are my family.
I can't just leave them
when they need me the most.
What can I say?
I admire your loyalty.
You're one of a kind.
There you go.
You better get inside.
Don't want to be late.
Has your dad arrived?
No, not yet.
Let's go.
♪ I'm overwhelmed
As my mind roams the realm
♪ My eye's the visions
Memory is the film
♪ Others act sub-tile
But they fragile above cloud
♪ They act wild
And couldn't budge a crowd
♪ No matter how loud they get
Though they growl and spit
♪ Clutch they fists
And throw up signs like a Crip
♪ And throw all types of fit
♪ I leave them split like ass cheeks
And ragged pussy lips
♪ And, yo, camouflage chameleon
Ninjas scaling your building
♪ No time to grab the gun
They already got your wife and children
♪ A hit was sent from the President
To raid your residence
♪ Because you had secret evidence
And documents... ♪
Let me go, asshole!
Let me go, motherfucker!
You don't have the balls!
Let me go!
Ah!
Up!
You motherfucker.
What the fuck did you tell them,
motherfucker?
Gilberto getting caught wasn't on me.
You feel so safe, motherfucker.
When it's your turn...
He was a tiger.
Let's go.
What the fuck is this?
Tell him what you did.
Tell him.
Tell him where we caught you.
While you were visiting
your wife and children,
this fucking rat was
on his way to the airport.
With his wife, bags packed.
About to leave you holding the blame.
Your friend, Jorge.
You had your bitch follow me?
- What did you say?
- Me? And my children?
You should be thankful,
motherfucker.
It's why you're standing there...
instead of sitting next to him.
You're making a big mistake, David.
I don't give a fuck what you think.
He's a loyal man.
He always has been.
- He's a piece of shit, Jorge.
- He's a good man and loyal.
- Then why was he running?
- What are you doing?
- This is a good man...
- He's a fucking snitch!
Jorge!
Look at me.
Sophia's inside.
She's inside that room.
Don't let them touch her.
Don't let them put a hand on Sophia.
She has nothing to do with this, brother.
These fucking bastards are crazy...
David, no!
Your friend was right, Jorge.
Go check on Sophia.
My brother is in prison
because we were weak.
Because mistakes were made.
Because we allowed people
to be dishonest with us.
These are the consequences.
Mistakes will not be tolerated.
Jorge, when he tried to run,
he proved he was willing
to turn against us, all of us.
Men with nothing to hide don't run, right?
Now... I trust you can take over
Cordova's responsibilities.
As our new head of security, Jorge.
What do you think?
I'm glad I can count on you.
My little girl, you're going to eat
a little bit of salad, okay?
Vera is going to teach you.
Look how much she ate.
Just a bit, sweetie.
Please, just eat a little bit.
- Hi. I thought you'd be home later.
- Daddy's here!
Give me a minute.
- Peña.
- 'It's me, Christina Jurado.'
I'm glad you called. Are you okay?
Please don't lie to me.
If I do this, if I get my husband to...
You can protect us?
We can go home?
'You have my word.'
I talked to him.
- You did? That's good.
- 'He's gonna... cooperate.'
He said that?
Oh, no, not yet, but he will.
I just... I need a little time.
That's fine.
You take all the time you need.
'Attention passengers:
Now boarding flight 1935 to Curaçao.'
Is that the landline?
- 'Hello?'
- The cartel knows where you are.
'Who is this?'
'I think we can help each other out.'
http://hiqve.com/