_
[Steve] Okay. Here we go again.
- [overlapping gunfire]
- [chatter in Spanish]
Let me break it down for you,
four thousand soldiers...
a 250-man team of
Colombia's elite forces...
tens of thousands of rounds fired...
[explosion booming]
- ...seven dogs...
- [dogs barking]
...and four fuckin' helicopters.
Pablo Escobar was surrounded in
the middle of fuckin' nowhere.
There was no way he was getting
out of this one... right?
_
- [overlapping gunfire in distance]
- [helicopters whirring above]
_
- _
- [rustling in bushes]
- [twig snaps]
_
[man over loudspeaker] _
[twig snaps]
_
[Pablo] _
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
- Re-sync by GoldenBeard -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[Steve] Yep.
Life ain't fair, man.
Pablo Escobar? He was headed home.
As for me and Connie,
well, we were in some deep shit,
and I hadn't even heard the news.
[Steve] This is what
I do. This is my job.
No, don't you dare say this is your job.
I know what your fucking job is.
And it doesn't entail being
kidnapped by a Colombian drug cartel.
Listen, I'm sorry, I am. I know
it must've been tough for you.
Listen, but Connie, I
was never in any danger.
I'm here now, back with you.
Hmm?
All I want... is for us to be safe.
I want to get the hell out of
this place and I want to go home.
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
- Murphy.
- Escobar's out.
- What?
- He's fucking out.
He took Sandoval hostage during the
siege and when the army
went in... he escaped.
Walked right out.
Pick me up in ten
minutes. I'll meet you downstairs.
[Connie scoffs]
Escobar's escaped.
[Steve] And you know what?
I was happy about it.
The fox was out of the
cage and the hunt was on.
[chuckles]
Yeah, it was the biggest law
enforcement blunder of all time.
Fortunately, it wasn't our blunder.
_
[grunts, low murmurs]
[vehicles approaching]
_
[Hermilda] _
[whispers] _ [kissing]
_
[slow Latin music plays on radio]
[Tata moans]
Pablo Escobar has escaped from prison.
[speaking Spanish]
[speaking French]
[speaking Norwegian]
He is out of that prison again after
a bizarre showdown between...
[Steve] By morning, word
was out on the streets
and all eyes were on Medellín.
This wasn't just a manhunt...
this was an invasion.
Gaviria was willing to go door
to door to catch Escobar.
And we wanted to be a part of it.
After all, we represented
America down here.
We thought of ourselves as the
guys who could get shit done.
- [Steve] Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- [Javier] Jesus Christ.
[Steve] Agent Murphy, Agent Peña. DEA.
_
- Name Pinzón mean anything to you?
- No, don't know him.
[Steve] You see this?
Well, it looks like we're
not invited to the dance.
_
Yeah, you mean when
nothing's left inside.
_
_ Huh?
[Steve] Now keep in mind...
the Medellín cartel wasn't
just one big gang.
It was made up of a
bunch of smaller gangs.
A collective, so to speak.
And as far as Pablo was
concerned, he was still their leader.
In his mind, every trafficker in
Medellín had to pay tribute to him.
Only a guy who'd
killed thousands of people
could think Judy Moncada would
forget what he'd done
to her husband Kiko
and his business
partner Fernando Galeano,
the guys who were running his
business while he was inside.
Fuckin' psycho. He thought that
they were stealing from him...
and naturally, they got
the short end of the stick.
[Kiko] _
_
[Steve] Why he thought
Judy'd be okay with that...
Well, she wasn't.
And alongside her brother Jaime, and
head of security Diego Murillo,
a.k.a. Don Berna, they'd broken
away from the Medellín cartel.
And now that Pablo was
out, they wanted payback.
And as for the other gangs,
they were all up for grabs.
[man grunts, groans]
Take the Prisco brothers, for instance.
The oldest of whom, Ricardo,
was a respected member of
the medical community.
[muffled groans, yelling]
[man screams]
[Steve] He didn't know who to side with.
Neither did the Gallón gang,
who became famous a year later
when they murdered Colombian
soccer player Andrés Escobar
for accidentally scoring a goal against
his own country in the 1994 World Cup.
But this wasn't a soccer game.
This was the blow business.
And whose side they
chose would come down
to two things, who
offered the better deal
and who had the better
chance of winning the war.
_
- _
- [Judy chuckles]
_
[Jaime] _
[Berna] _
_
[scoffs]
[Berna] _
[phone ringing]
_
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [music plays nearby]
_ [kissing]
- [slaps car]
- _
_
Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm?
_
Mmm.
- _
- [Maritza sighs]
_
_ Hmm?
[murmuring indistinctly]
_
- [Limón] _
- [La Quica] _
[Limón] _
_
[Rosa] _
[Rosa mutters indistinctly]
[Steve] Looking for a place for
your next corporate retreat?
Or maybe a quiet
getaway for the whole family?
How about 360 degrees of unobstructed
views of the Antioquian countryside?
Sixty thousand square
feet of creative living space.
Perfect for entertaining.
Look no further than La Catedral.
One man's prison...
is anyone else's palace.
Yep... it was a beautiful place.
And when the Colombian
cops were done with it,
they were gracious enough to let
us pick through the leftovers.
This and Mein Kampf.
Two classics of 20th century literature.
Yeah, what do you think the rent's
like? I'm thinking about moving in.
[Javier chuckles]
Hey, Javi, you think the, uh... the
Hague would want a couple of these?
How are you not wearing rubber
gloves touching that shit, man?
We should take this stuff to our office.
It's better than any of the shit we got.
Fuckin' Pinzón's guys
have taken everything
that's useful. There's nothing.
Look, I think I found
something that might help.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
[laughing]
Wait.
_
[chuckles]
[La Quica] _
_
[Limón] _
[Pablo] _
_
- [man shouts orders in Spanish]
- [men grunting]
[Steve] After La Catedral, the
next stop was Carlos Holguín...
the old police training academy that
had been repurposed as ground zero
in the search for Escobar.
The new honcho was Colonel Pinzón,
the guy who was famous for
his love of Uncle Sam.
As a courtesy to your government,
I'm allowing you to
participate in this manhunt.
But... I set the limits and
all decisions rest with me.
If this condition is unacceptable,
take it up with the president.
Of course, Colonel.
I hope we didn't get
off on the wrong foot.
Not at all. Every operation needs
a well-defined hierarchy.
[phone rings nearby]
I hope this will be an adequate
space for you to do your work.
What, you're talking about this? This...
This is more than adequate.
- Gracias, Colonel.
- [Pinzón] Welcome.
Oh, wow, this is from 1962.
[Steve] Like most tricks Pablo employed,
the audacity and simplicity of
the taxi was pretty damn good.
I mean, who in the hell would think that
the seventh richest man in the world
would be riding around in the
trunk of a piece of shit taxi?
_
As smart as it was,
Pablo wasn't the kind
of guy who left anything to chance.
Despite his absence, he still had
a loyal following in Medellín.
[siren wails]
And a network of
spotters... kids mainly.
And they were everywhere in the comunas.
The spotters could
identify which streets to take
and which ones to avoid.
_
[trunk slams shut]
- [murmuring in Spanish]
- [knocking at door]
[knocking continues]
_
- [sighs] _
- _
_
[softly] _
Mmm.
_
[softly] _
[man] _
_
[woman] _
[line ringing]
[screeching]
- [Steve sighs]
- Seriously? Directly in front of me?
I don't spend enough
time looking at your face?
That's better.
_
Nothing?
[sighs] You picked up the
"American" part, right?
Murphy!
_
- You think it's legit?
- Let's find out.
How credible is your source?
[Javier] It was an
unsolicited phone call.
She asked to speak to an American.
We would just need a couple
of cars and a few men.
[Pinzón] Well, my men are either
busy here or outside in the street.
And I'm not relocating men
to chase down bullshit tips.
If this turns out not to be
bullshit, La Quica could give us Pablo.
[Pinzón] So go. Go ahead.
Since when do you need an
excuse to go to a whorehouse?
_
One vehicle, three men.
Gracias.
[door opens, closes]
_
- [overlapping gunshots]
- [women screaming]
_
[phone rings]
[gunshot]
[sighs]
_
- _
- [glass shatters]
[screaming] _
- [sobbing]
- _
_
[sobs] _
[gasps, exhales]
_
[sniffles] _
Alleys run along the
house here... and here.
We'll keep the other
car waiting around back.
_
[phone beeping]
- Murphy.
- Hey, it's me.
Hey, honey. Um...
[softly] I'm just in the middle of
something. Let me call you right back.
We're at the airport.
You're where?
I can't do this.
I'm taking Olivia and
we're going back to Miami.
[softly] No, no, no.
Listen to me, please.
Please, you can't just do
it like this. You can't.
My sister's offered to help us out for a
while, so we'll be there if you need us.
Connie.
It's not right, Steve, to keep Olivia
here with everything that's going on.
Not when I can take her someplace safe.
You're safe in Bogotá. You're right
beside the goddamn fuckin' embassy.
Look, I have to go.
Connie, please. We can talk about this.
Do not get on that airplane. Wait, okay?
I'll be right there. I'm on my way.
- I'm sorry.
- [baby whimpering]
[whispers] Hey, hey,
hey. I'm here. Okay?
- She's at the airport.
- Go.
I'm sorry. I gotta go. Guys, sorry.
[Javier] All right.
[indistinct chatter in Spanish]
_
_ [grunts]
[La Quica] _
_
[indistinct chatter over PA]
Flight to Miami.
Gate 39, but... Sir, you can't go. Sir!
I'm DEA. I need to get on this flight.
I'm sorry, sir... Sir, I'm sorry,
but the plane has already left.
Sir, please. You can't be here.
Sir!
_
Just fuckin' drive.
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [rap music plays inside]
- [woman chuckles]
- [music continues loudly]
[laughs]
[woman speaks Spanish over PA]
- [urinating]
- [man sniffs nearby]
- [flushing]
- [whispers] Enjoy.
- Get you feeling pretty good?
- Huh?
Oh, fuck. Thanks, man. Shit.
[laughs] Phew!
You wouldn't imagine what
a kilo of that stuff cost.
Come on.
- How about you, golden boy?
- What are you talking about, man?
Time it's processed, shipped,
distributed to your buddies
on... the Upper East Side? Yeah.
Hey, man, we don't need any
problems here. We cool?
Six.
Lives.
That's how much it cost.
What do you think about that?
That was six people. Six
people were murdered
every time you and
your buddy over there...
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah?
[grunting]
[Steve grunts]
Whoo!
- [rap music continues]
- [woman grunts]
[chatter continues]
_
[Javier] _
- _
- [women shout]
_ [grunts]
_
[women gasping]
[woman screams]
[Limón shouts] _
[clattering above]
_
[panting]
Fuck.
_
[voice straining] _
[dialing]
_
[up-tempo Latin guitar music plays]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
- Re-sync by GoldenBeard -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --