The guy is innocent.
He didn't do any of it.
Easy, honey, easy, okay? Be careful.
The glove.
Screw the fucking glove, brother.
-That Fuhrman's a son of a bitch.
-He's an asshole.
-And he's been fucking the sister.
-Which one?
The sister! I don't even know her name.
Geraldo is fucking her, too.
Okay, guys, listen up.
Understood?
Good morning, gentlemen.
Good morning.
As many of you know,
since Córdova's resignation,
I am the head of security.
It's festival time.
That means the city will be crowded.
The festival is not an excuse
to party on the job.
One more thing. David and his team will
now be handling security for his father.
Let's make them feel welcome.
And help them any way you can.
That's all, boys. Get going!
Look at you. You're sliding
into your new job like a glove.
You're a natural.
Look, David, if we're going
to work together, we need to cooperate.
If you have questions or you want to talk
about your father's security...
I'm here.
Thank you.
I do have a question, Jorge.
How come none of your men
carry fucking guns?
Because we use our walkies
if we have a problem.
For what? To say goodbye
when you're getting clipped?
Do me a favour, Jorge.
You do your thing, I'll do mine.
All right?
Boss, you didn't mention the DEA agents
that are in Cali.
That's something David
might be interested in.
Listen, the last thing we need right now
is David and his crew
killing a federal agent, no?
Well, that's true.
For now, we'll monitor the DEA ourselves.
Besides... I doubt they have much.
I don't want to leave New York, Chepe.
-Why, Chepe?
-My love...
I know you don't want to leave New York.
I know.
I don't either.
But if they connect this lab to us...
we're going to have every cop in the city
after us.
Hey, look.
Here it comes.
Spokesmen for the DEA say that
the cocaine tab that exploded in Queens
was operated by a Dominican gang.
Exactly! Thank you, lady.
Fucking Dominicans!
But Manuel de Dios, editor of La Prensa,
has discovered another side to the story.
This lab,
along with a number of others in the area,
was recently seized
by Colombian gangsters,
led by a man going by the name
Victor Crespo.
Motherfucker.
-In the next few days,
we will be publishing
an investigative series
about this criminal enterprise,
including pictures.
This operation is much larger
than it seems.
"No speak Spanish" my ass.
So that means we have to leave,
right, Chepe?
No, my love.
This man, he knows who you are, Chepe.
Don't worry. We're not going anywhere.
Is that so?
So do me a favour and fix this.
Did you hear me?
Motherfucker.
So a new surrender deal.
Three years in jail. All of you.
Turn in the illicit businesses,
and we can keep all of the legal assets,
as in the old plan. It's a good deal.
He would've told you himself,
but he thought it was best for me
to explain in person.
Besides, I helped negotiate the deal.
I understand.
Thank you for coming, Nicolàs.
Give me an update, Uncle Miguel.
An update?
On our efforts to maximize business
before surrender.
So I can inform my father.
Tell your dad everything's
still on track here.
Pacho's settled new terms with Amado
Carrillo Fuentes and is coming back soon.
And this accident in New York?
Chepe encountered an obstacle,
but you know Chepe.
I'm not worried.
Are we done?
One last thing.
Our friends in Bogotà
are concerned about their exposure.
Too many people know about the deal.
They worry about Mr. Pallomari.
My father would like you to handle it.
"Handle it"?
Do you know what you're talking about?
Do you have any idea?
Pallomari's our chief accountant in Cali,
and not easily replaced.
He's too valuable to just kill.
Tell your father I'll take care of it.
He doesn't have to worry about Pallomari.
Thank you, Uncle Miguel.
Take care.
So now the little prince
is giving you orders?
His father's orders.
Have Salcedo put Pallomari
in one of the safe houses.
Keep an eye on him.
You decide if you're coming tonight?
Our Salsa Festival party, Dad.
It's important.
You know how I feel about parties.
That's Gilberto's thing, not mine.
Which is exactly why you should go.
Dad, you're the new boss here.
Please, show them.
Or at least have a good time
before we have to roll over and play dead.
Cheers, gentlemen!
How would you like to be my date tonight?
Where would we go?
Let's go dancing
Do you like dancing?
As you discussed with Don Miguel,
he'd like you to keep working from here.
Yes, I know what needs to be done.
Come in.
Guillermo, what's this?
You've got to be kidding, right?
-You're playing me for a fool.
-What's this?
This is unacceptable.
I need to speak to Miguel.
Talk to whoever you want. This is
the biggest apartment we have right now.
Three bedrooms. Two bathrooms.
A/C. Kids seem to like it.
-Kids, do you like it?
-Yes!
Really, Patricia.
Are you going to smoke inside?
What's the problem? This is a dump.
-The boys are here.
-Oh, now you're concerned about the boys?
Do not leave this apartment,
for your own safety.
Everything you've done for these people,
and this is how they repay you?
I'm telling you, they're done.
Gilberto's looking
for some new way to surrender.
And you heard about this thing in New York
with Chepe, right?
And Miguel's in charge of everything here.
Better said, the Cali cartel is dead.
And you intend to...?
To do whatever I have to do
for the North Valley cartel.
Which is why I'm talking to you.
It's funny how things change, isn't it?
So, Amado... what do you say?
I say you're no fucking fun,
that's what I say.
But we both see the future the same way.
Look, starting next week...
I'll only be shipping product
for my new North Valley friends. Good?
And what about the other thing
we discussed?
Look, I need you to make room here.
And I want you to take care of the guests,
get them everything they need.
I also want a bottle
at each of these tables.
But I want the good stuff.
None of that shit you serve here.
Understood?
I was told you needed me.
I need to talk about something.
Leave your bitch down here.
Come on.
You don't tell anyone about this, okay?
I was thinking about what you said...
if I ever need your advice, and...
I could use your help.
With your father's security.
He's coming to the party tonight.
He's coming here?
Unless there's another fucking party
I don't know about? Yeah, here.
What do you want me to tell you, David?
Public places are always bad.
I know.
Too many people.
When does he plan on arriving?
I was thinking around 11.
Well, what fucking time is best, then?
Well, I think ten is better.
It's less crowded.
Maybe I can take him up to the balcony.
You'll take care of it?
I knew I could count on you.
I just need this night to be perfect.
Everything has to go well.
You can relax. I think we can manage that.
Boss, did you tell him
it isn't a good idea?
Of course, you think he listened?
He's an imbecile.
Pull over here.
Pinchadito said there's
a bad phone tap or something.
Stay here. I'll be two minutes.
Hey. What's going on?
Nothing, boss.
-Is he bothering you?
-No, sir.
-I'm just buying fritters for my brother.
-Great, let's go.
-You want some?
-Sure.
-Let's see here.
-Zuelma prays every morning.
Very good. And here?
-The worm...
-Gotero...
-Dad!
-Hi, kids!
I need to speak to you.
Okay. Girls...
please, go to your room
and finish your homework.
Something came up.
-What is it?
-I know how hard this has been for you.
I just want you to know
that I've almost got it figured out.
-All right.
-I'll tell you more tonight,
but for now, I want you
to get everything ready to leave.
Where are we going? How...
Do you trust me?
My love...
Paola... do you trust me?
Yes?
Everything will be all right. I promise.
Done. I'm finished.
I love that length on you.
Thank you, I like it, too.
And... a little extra for you.
And I have a little extra for you, too.
-I'll see you later.
-See you later.
You were the one who approached my wife?
You enjoy it?
Using her to get to me?
You can say whatever you want.
-You can't scare me.
-No...
I can just ruin your life.
You know the brothers.
Pretty well.
What do you think will happen to them
without Gilberto running things?
You're young, Franklin.
You have your whole life ahead of you.
You really want to spend it in a cell?
Talk to me.
I'll get you a deal. You and Christina...
can start over.
Have a new life.
In the United States.
I'm not going to say a single word...
until I see my wife.
Then you'll have your witness.
Stop. Stop here.
Turn around.
Manny.
Thanks for meeting.
Julia said you might have...
something on Crespo?
Well, yes.
It's something I hope you like.
How can I help you, Mr. Crespo?
Or should I say, Mr. Santacruz?
Well...
I was hoping I could help you.
Where are you from?
-Cuba.
-Cuba! Gorgeous.
When you were young,
did you ever think you would come
to this country and do something special?
Well, I did.
I imagined myself coming here
to the United States, to New York...
and building something important.
That was also my dream.
The dream of a young immigrant,
like yourself.
And that's why I want to help you,
to make whatever dream you have a reality.
Whatever it is.
Regardless how much it costs.
In dollars.
You think you and I are the same
because we came to this country
with dreams?
Well...
My family fled Cuba
because we believed in freedom.
You came to sell cocaine.
Yes, we are both immigrants,
but we have nothing in common,
Mr. Santacruz.
My story is going to print.
Okay. Thank you for hearing my proposal.
Can I ask you a question?
How long will it take
to get to the airport from here?
I have no idea.
An hour or so.
I'll miss a lot about New York.
But not the traffic.
-Good evening, sir.
-Good evening. How are you?
Good evening.
Hello. How are you?
Good evening. Welcome.
Good to see you, David. What's up?
Looks like the whole family showed up.
Why don't we have a drink upstairs?
You know what?
I don't want this many people up here.
Good evening! Welcome to the Cali Fair!
Let's give a warm welcome
to a friend of the festival,
and our patron, Mr. Miguel Rodriguez!
Come. Come here.
Come!
Come here!
Say a few words.
Thank you all for coming.
Please, enjoy the party.
Your brother's a character.
His passion for tequila
exceeds his tolerance.
Well... my shift started already.
Bring me a pack of cigarettes
when you come back.
You're giving me a tip.
We aren't here for you.
Where is Pacho?
Pacho!
I need to talk to you.
-Don't interrupt me.
-We have a problem. We have to leave, now.
-Relax. It's a fucking party.
-We need to leave now!
-I said calm down! I'll say when we go.
-What's going on here?
We have to leave, sir. Please.
Get down!
Go! Watch out!
Pacho!
Watch out!
Stay there!
-Keep going!
-Careful! Get out of the way!
-Get out of the way!
Keep moving.
When I run...
Shit!
Give me the gun.
Go ahead.
Are you all right?
Motherfucker!
Alvaro!
Shoot them!
Go!
Over there!
-Careful!
-Head down, sir.
Head down!
-Slow down.
-Move it!
Motherfucker!
-Go!
-Let's go! Move it!
This shit...
Little brother! I need you to shoot.
Your gun. Keep shooting at them!
Head down!
I'll drive, Enrique. I'll drive!
Over here!
Who drove the car?
You got here by car. Who was driving?
-Me.
-Give me the keys.
Fuck you.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Are we close?
Yes. It's just around the corner.
Thank you.
You saved me. Really.
Just tell your friends about me.
But only the ones with money.
Why isn't this imbecile moving?
When is this car gonna move?
-Fuck!
-Oh, my God.
God.
-Go! Fucking drive! Oh, my...
Dad! Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
-Are you okay?
-Let's go inside.
-It's those North Valley motherfuckers.
-We got one of the shooters.
-They shot Alvaro, too.
Pacho is okay.
They're on their way back.
Are you okay?
-Close the damn door.
-What a fucking night.
Dario, please take her upstairs.
I'm coming soon.
What happened there?
It looked like...
you knew something was coming.
Jorge! You know what? I know why.
Because you are always working.
You saved my life tonight, Jorge!
-Dad, it wasn't my fault, I...
-One moment.
From now on, I want you back in charge
of my personal security.
Only you, Jorge.
Of course, Don Miguel.
And if you allow me, we don't know
if this will be the only attack or not.
So I need to know where you are
at all times.
Tomorrow is another day.
-Gilberto, it's me.
-Thank God!
-How are you, brother?
-We're okay.
Look, Gilberto,
they tried to kill Pacho, too.
-Pacho! No, it can't be...
-No, he's okay. He survived.
-He's on his way home.
-Thank God.
These North Valley motherfuckers,
I'm going to kill them. Sons of bitches.
Listen to me, Miguel.
Now's not the time for...
Everybody's watching.
-It could ruin everything.
-Look, Gilberto. They tried to kill me.
They tried to kill my son.
They tried to kill Maria.
They tried to kill Pacho.
Yes, I understand, brother, but...
for now, we can't afford to start a war.
Especially being so close
to the surrender.
What fucking surrender, Gilberto?
Before we can surrender,
they'll take everything from us.
-Brother, listen to me.
-Okay, no war. I understand.
You'll see.
Everything is going to be okay, brother.
Okay, Gilberto. Bye.
Over 15 people were killed, with dozens
more injured and in critical condition,
in a deadly shootout tonight
at the kick-off party for the Cali Fair.
Police say it's too early to say
what caused the incident,
but several people
who were inside the club...
-I was worried.
-I'm okay.
-We're safe.
-What happened?
It was the North Valley. I'm okay.
Where are we going?
Why do we have to leave?
What's going on?
Come with me. Come.
Tell me what's going on right now!
What I'm about to tell you
has to stay here.
You can't tell anyone, understand?
I'm working for the Americans.
It can't be.
I contacted the DEA.
I'm giving them Miguel.
In exchange, they will help us
get out of the country.
It's our only option.
There's no other way.
You're crazy.
They're going to kill all of us.
-You're insane. What were you thinking?!
-Paola...
I want to welcome Pacho, Chepe.
I'm sorry it's under these circumstances.
North Valley attacked us.
Their intentions were clear.
They saw us as vulnerable
without Gilberto.
Weak, with me in charge.
They are trying to destroy us.
Take what's ours.
I...
All of us know there's only
one appropriate response to this.
One way to react against these people
who want to take everything from us,
what we've worked so hard to build.
War.
This is Gilberto's decision?
It's...
mine.