Stop!
OK!
—How are you?
—Very well. How are you?
Your ID, please.
Certainly.
Give me that.
How many times have I told you
not to throw the ball over there?
Are you trying
to scare your sister or what?
—She’s crying.
—Of course she’s crying.
Don’t you see she’s just a baby?
You yourself were a baby
not too long ago.
Yes, Dad.
—What’s wrong?
—Nothing.
What’s wrong, Juan Pablo?
I want her to die.
Never say that.
We are a family and we have
to look out for each other, always.
You hear me?
—Hello.
—Cousin, Poison just took out some cops.
—Yes, go on. How many?
—Two.
Yeah, but two what?
Sergeants or officers?
Officers. You know Poison.
—Officers are a million each.
—OK, so two million?
—Yes, I’m writing it down here.
—OK, talk to you later.
All right.
What were you talking about?
Just business.
I want to be a businessman like you.
Good morning, ladies.
Where are you headed?
You speak Spanish?
Yes.
I asked where you are headed.
—Popayán.
—Popayán?
Your papers, please.
Ms. Connie Murphy.
Alba Borraga.
Have a nice trip.
—Thank you.
—Be well.
WITH GAVIRIA
THERE WILL BE A FUTURE
Have you heard of this thing
called a computer?
Some guy was trying to sell me one.
I don’t know what it is.
It’s a new kind of technology
that’s coming out.
—It’s coming out now?
—Yeah, Dad.
Hey, honey.
You look very beautiful today.
Relax, baby. Relax.
We don’t bite.
—Do you need anything else?
—I want you.
—Nothing more, thank you.
—Yes, sir.
I want to fuck her.
We have more important things
to worry about right now, my son.
Understood?
Talk to me. What do you know?
Mr Gonzalo,
we have people all over the property.
It’s secure.
We’ve got a few men in town as well.
Now, what can you tell me about Medellín?
The same, boss.
Carrillo’s entire Search Bloc
is out looking for Pablo.
Thank you, Navegante.
—Here to serve, boss.
—Keep us safe.
Don Freddy.
Son … a question.
Are we sheep or are we wolves?
—We’re wolves.
—We’re wolves! Right.
I like it.
They’re in a house outside of Cartagena.
Right here.
Just know there are a lot of people
guarding him.
Navegante, you’ve been
working for Gacha for many years.
I’m sure in that time you’ve
earned way more than we are giving you.
So tell me,
why do you want to betray him?
That fucker’s crazy.
He’s gonna get us all killed.
I don’t believe him one bit.
What do you care why he’s doing it?
Because we have 23 agents with
outdated weapons waiting in Barranquilla.
And he has twice as many men
with brand new weapons.
And frankly …
I’m tired of sending young men
to face certain death.
So then we have to be smart.
We have to create a trap.
If we catch him alive,
he’ll give us Escobar.
And the Ochoas.
—The entire cartel.
—I don’t give a fuck, Javier.
I want him dead.
He doesn’t care about death.
He only fears rotting in jail.
—That’s the real victory.
—Right, I forgot you’re a gringo.
—What’s that supposed to mean?
—What are you risking?
These aren’t your men.
You have no family here to lose.
If this goes badly, there will be
more widows and orphans,
and I will have to carry that
on my shoulders.
Well …
I trust his information.
And I trust you.
But if this turns out bad …
it’ll be on your conscience.
Here’s your payment, sir.
It’ll be taken to the coast of Spain
on a cargo ship.
From there, our trucks
will take it to the Basque country.
It’s all set up.
5,000 kilos or I go back to Spain
on the first flight.
What’s that?
As far as I know, you and my cousin
have an agreement.
The agreement is for this amount.
What kind of bullshit is this?
5,000 kilos or no deal.
Then there is no deal.
Who the fuck
do you think you’re talking to?
Forgive my cousin, sir.
5,000 it is, then.
We shouldn’t go.
I want you in the US.
You’ll be safe there,
far from all of this.
—What if something happens--
—Nothing is going to happen to me.
Let’s go.
Please, protect him.
Don’t worry. Everything will be fine.
Come on, I’ll walk you.
Bye, Daddy, I love you!
—Hello, Suárez.
—Look who’s here.
The Golden Gringo.
I called your office.
I only speak to Peña.
I need …
I need to know who he is.
“I need to know who he is.”
Don’t make me laugh, faggot.
You work for me, asshole!
Right? Is that clear?
Is that clear‽
—I feel like he’s still too soft.
—He’ll be fine.
I don’t know, Pablo.
I feel like we need
to suspend the operation.
—It’s too delicate.
—You worry too much, Gustavo.
That’s the reason
your hair is falling out.
Very funny, motherfucker.
Keep laughing.
How’s our boy doing, Mom?
He’s learning,
with a little tough love.
—What’s up, Aunt?
—What’s new?
That’s so he can mix
with the sons of the oligarchs, right?
—Yes, sir.
—So he can get us some information.
What about these clowns?
Are they treating you right?
More or less.
What do you mean “more or less”?
We treat you good.
Are we going to eat, Gustavo?
—Some rice?
—Yes.
Thank you.
Jaime.
Welcome to the family.
Thank you, boss.
Can’t you do anything?
No.
While we’re at war,
we can’t do anything.
This is bullshit.
People are turning up dead every day
and my friends
think my brothers are responsible.
Let’s talk about something else, baby.
Yeah.
All right,
let’s talk about running away together.
Let’s get away while we can.
“Let’s get away.”
Listen to this.
Why would you run away
with a criminal like me?
And why not?
I wish it was that easy.
I can’t just leave like that.
I know.
You say that because of your wife.
I don’t give a shit about my wife.
I’m talking about your other wife, Pablo.
Who is the woman in that relationship?
You?
Hey, doll.
What are you doing?
I’m married, sir.
That’s no problem.
I can make you a widow pretty quick.
Don’t touch me! Don’t touch me.
Freddy, leave her alone.
Come here.
What’s up?
The Search Bloc is here,
not in Medellín.
But Navegante said they were over there.
Navegante … Navegante is a liar.
He wouldn’t betray you.
Freddy … think, think.
Everyone in the world has a price.
All right, let’s go!
They want war, we’ll give them war!
His name is Steve Murphy.
He’s DEA.
I hope you’ll pay for this information.
Suárez is talking to the DEA.
You know what you have to do.
He got away.
They killed the goddamn maid.
Colonel!
Colonel …
They called from the road block.
They have a car stopped
and they’re saying the driver’s a senator.
—Does he have his identification?
—Everything checks out.
So what’s the problem?
They found a machine gun in the trunk.
Let’s go.
Look at my credentials.
No, I don’t know this Gacha person
you’re referring to.
Why do you have a gun in the trunk?
Gentlemen, are you asking why a politician
in this country carries a weapon?
Please.
—It’s my bodyguard’s.
—Where’s your bodyguard?
You’re alone in the car, right?
Listen to me, officers …
if you don’t let me go immediately,
you’re going to regret it.
Thank you.
—Give us a moment.
—Go on.
I don’t believe him.
I don’t either.
He could have bought his credentials.
What if it turns out he is a senator?
We’ll pay for that.
I can’t run that risk.
It’s true.
You can’t.
The next one …
goes in your head!
—All right, all right!
—Talk, bitch!
I’ll talk, I’ll talk!
I love you, my sweetheart.
I love you.
You have a guest.
It’s Don Pablo.
Hey, Jaime.
—Don Pablo.
—This is your house?
—Your family?
—Yes, sir. Welcome.
Tell me about them.
This is my daughter Marcela.
Look at what a cute baby.
—How proud you must be.
—Of course I am.
Of course.
Very soon, they will have the money
to buy everything they want, Jaime.
Thanks a lot, boss.
—May I please have a glass of water?
—Of course.
Thank you.
—What about you?
—Good, sir.
—How have you been?
—Good, thank you.
Guys.
All right, Jaime.
This is for you to wear
during your mission.
Thank you, Ma’am. Very kind.
Seriously, Pablo?
Thank you very much.
Everything is so beautiful.
You have to be very careful,
and get by unnoticed.
For sure, sir.
I’m ready to do what you’re asking.
All right, then, son.
Sit down.
These guys are going to give you
very specific instructions.
Tomorrow morning, you’re boarding
the plane that is leaving for Cali.
We want you to record a conversation.
It’s very simple. Nothing to worry about.
All right.
—How are you feeling?
—I’m … I’m very happy.
Thank you very much for the opportunity,
Don Pablo. Seriously. And for the clothes.
Really, for me,
it’s an honour to work for you.
Thank you very much.
Don’t mention it.
OK.
Come here, give me a hug.
Thank you, Don Pablo.
Thank you.
—Ma’am, have a good night.
—Take care.
Thank you very much.
See you later, boys.
—Take care.
—Yes, sir.
My love, look!
—Look at this jacket. Beautiful, right?
—It’s beautiful. What did Pablo say?
You know what?
We’re going to get ahead.
You, me and the baby
are going to get ahead.
Thank you, my love.
—Look at this.
—Let’s go try it on.
I have some news about Gaviria.
They’re going to kill him
on the way to Cali.
Wait a moment.
Someone is at the door.
Pablo doesn’t like you talking to the DEA.
It was her fault, Dad.
Are you still thinking about that?
Let it go, son.
All she had to do was say yes
and I wouldn’t have had to shoot her!
Be a man!
Son of a bitch! They found us!
Come on, son!
—Sir, are you OK?
—I’m fine. I’m fine.
—He’s trying to get away!
—He won’t get away.
Get me a radio, quick!
Correal, bring a radio!
Correal! A radio!
Dad, let’s go! Hurry, Dad, hurry!
Hurry!
Stop!
Peña! Gacha is in a red Chevy pick-up!
What did I tell you?
We got out OK.
—I’m scared.
—Scared of what?
You’re a wolf, right?
Yes, I am a wolf.
It’s a helicopter! It’s a helicopter!
They’re going to kill us!
Nobody is going to kill us!
Don’t talk like that!
Take this. Take it!
—I have a Chevy in sight.
—Stop him!
Don’t let him get away!
Try and disable the vehicle!
No good. We’re going in again.
Stop him!
Do whatever you have to do!
—Don’t leave me alone, Dad.
—No, no. Never, son, never!
Breathe! Breathe!
Do you want this, asshole?
Do you want this?
We’re taking fire. We’ll circle around
and approach from another direction.
You don’t need to worry about anything,
my son. Nothing.
Don’t take any chances!
We can’t afford to lose him!
Copy.
Look. Look outside. Look outside!
What’s happening?
Peña, what’s happening?
We stopped him.
He’s not moving.
Freddy. Freddy?
Let’s go, Freddy.
Freddy?
Son!
You’re a wolf. You’re a wolf.
Asshole!
Asshole! Hey, asshole!
Freddy! Wake up, Freddy!
Hey, asshole!
What are you going to do?
Asshole!
What are you going to do‽
He’s out of bullets.
We can take him alive.
It’s your call.
Give him lead.
Affirmative. Maintain positions
and patrol the area again. Very good.
Are you OK?
According to recent polls,
we’re doing well.
We’re gaining more points
in six districts within Cali.
They’re important
because we could gain the lead.
—Don’t put too much faith in the polls.
—I know.
The last time,
we fell five points in one day.
Yes.
Stop him!
Sir, we can’t let you through!
Relax. Let him through.
You nervous?
A little bit, but I’m fine.
Wait here.
You know what you have to do?
Yes, sir.
Remember, you have to record
the entire conversation. Don’t forget.
—No, sir.
—Have a nice flight.
Aren’t you coming with me?
No, the boss just told me
to bring you here.
But don’t worry.
Tomorrow, I’ll come and meet you there.
—All right, then.
—All right. Don’t be nervous.
You’ll see how fun it is to fly.
All right?
Go on. The line is right there.
Good luck, then.
It’s up to you, Eduardo.
Whatever you decide, I’ll do.
Avianca announces the departure
of Flight 203 to Cali,
now boarding at Gate 6.
I’ll organize the exit.
You guys stay with him.
Put on your seatbelt, please.