Thank you for being here with us,
with the groom and the bride.
Come and dance with us, everyone.
Let's begin.
Congratulations.
- Don Chucho.
- Luis, how are you?
How are you, sir?
Hello, Paco.
Everyone in Laredo is at this thing.
Will you tell me something?
- What happened to you over there?
- Dad, I don't know. It got ugly.
But you want to go back?
Sir, here you are.
Thank you.
FOR BEING FRIENDS WITH
PABLO ESCOBAR - LOS PEPES
Many observers fear Colombia's
other large cartel, the Cali cartel,
will now simply step up
its own drug production.
Hello?
Yes. What's up?
Let's see.
- Palmira's police superintendent.
- Didn't we just take care of him?
- I'm talking about the new one, Arango.
- How much?
- Should I put $20,000?
- No.
Put 17.
- Seventeen?
- Yes.
Anderson! Move all that over to the left.
The tables are too close together.
Are you planning
on saying anything tonight?
- No.
- I'll speak for the both of us.
- Did you talk to the North Valley people?
- Yes.
And?
They said what they thought
I wanted to hear.
But tonight, after the announcement,
we'll know the truth.
You're more superstitious
than Aunt Luz.
- Hey, boss.
- Is everything ready?
It took all night, but it's ready, sir.
You can handle it, you're young.
We're meeting Córdova.
He wants to go over the game plan.
Big night tonight, right?
Lots of company.
Gentlemen,
let's start with the obvious.
Tonight is fucking important.
The Rodríguez brothers never
gather members of their organisation
in one place.
That simply never happens.
But tonight, they're going to do it.
So we have to be sharp.
- Eyes in the back of the head, understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Jorge.
- Stayfocused.
Stay on the radio. Communicate.
Tonight is his last operation.
He's leaving us
to become a fancy businessman.
Let's leave a good impression.
Maybe he'll hire us one day.
Let's go.
What do you think Gilberto
is going to announce tonight?
I think it's a move into the Asian market.
I have no idea.
After Friday, it's not my problem.
- Are you really leaving?
- I promised Paola.
I promise things to my wife
every day, brother.
Relax, you'll find someone else
to make you look good.
I hope so, buddy.
Because right now,
I'm surrounded by a bunch of assholes.
Who am I speaking with?
This is Andres, his brother.
And how can I help him?
Hey, brother. Have a seat.
Something to drink?
Relax. You're safe here.
Let's talk about tonight's party.
We need info on the people attending.
Cops, politicians.
- Cops and politicians?
- Yes.
Who work for the cartel.
These people are ruining your country.
Look, the thing is, these people
never get together in one place.
We need to know why now.
Our guess is Gilberto Rodríguez
is making some kind of important
announcement, understand?
Come in.
We were getting worried.
Everything OK?
Yes, but...
I thought someone was tailing me.
I had to make sure I was alone.
Take off your shirt. Sit.
Look, don't you think you should
fix things with Pacho, Claudito?
He's a boss.
We're in their territory, right?
Yes.
I'll fix it tonight.
María.
For our children,
and our children's children.
That sounded great, brother.
Let me do it from the top.
No one gives a shit about your speech.
We can hear it after...
Come here, you crazy motherfucker.
What's up?
Look at you. How's New York?
Cold. But if you ask nicely,
the girls make up for it.
I brought you something, baby-face.
It's been too long
since we were all together.
Tonight is our night,
because we've earned this.
- Gentlemen of Cali, cheers!
- Cheers!
I think there is business
to discuss first, Gilberto.
You're acting like someone
just pissed you off.
Brother, you're richer than the Pope.
Cheers, then! To the Pope!
Welcome, Chepe.
Look, Gilberto...
you know I have a personal issue
with that son of a bitch,
Claudio Salazar from North Valley.
And he's downstairs.
I would like to solve it.
OK, Pacho.
I understand your need for revenge,
but this isn't the time to get into it.
There's too much at stake.
Well... shall we enjoy
this expensive party or what?
No. Instead, let's listen
to Gilberto's speech again.
Chepe, you motherfucker.
Look, that's Menga's chief of police.
I pay him money every month.
I pay all these people.
Well done, big shot.
It's not your money.
But I'm the one who controls it.
- Who bought you these earrings?
- Guillermo, enough.
Sure, you're turning into Al Capone.
Watch it.
- How are you, sir?
- Pallomari.
- Enjoying the party?
- Yes.
Yes.
Nice to see you.
Don Gilberto, good evening.
- Welcome, Mr Mayor.
- Don Gilberto, how are you?
Good evening, Don Gilberto.
- Look, here it is.
- Motherfucker.
Hello.
- Good evening.
- Can I have aguardiente with ice?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Are you...
enjoying yourself?
Yes. Very much, thank you.
Miguel Rodríguez, nice to meet you.
María Salazar.
Thank you for having us.
Good evening.
Mister Rodríguez would like
for his associates
to join him in the equestrian ring
for an announcement.
Please, go right ahead.
Gentlemen, please follow the ushers
towards the stables. Thank you.
Stop there.
You must be using
some high-end equipment
if you're getting anything
in this shitty light.
Who are you?
I'm in charge of security
for the Rodríguez brothers.
See that man over there?
His name is Navegante.
Guess what he does?
Either you come with me,
or you go with him.
You understand?
Follow me.
Your name is Andrés Restrepo.
You live with your mother
in commune number 3.
You have a girlfriend in Libertadores.
Your brother is Lucho.
He's in federal custody
in the United States.
That's why you agreed to work
for the DEA.
Don't lie to me.
Andrés, you made a bad decision.
But I think you're smart enough
to realise that.
You have another decision to make,
and it's the only way to get out alive.
Leave Cali.
Don't say goodbye to your mother
or to your girlfriend.
I need you to disappear.
Associates, friends.
Our enemy is dead!
Our business is strong!
Together we have taken this business
to heights that our predecessors
couldn't have imagined.
But friends, there are circumstances
that we need to acknowledge.
Listen to me.
The law enforcement spotlight
will shine brightly on us
as it once did on Escobar.
And so, while we celebrate,
they will do everything they can
to take away everything we've built.
An American named Joseph Kennedy
made his fortune
selling bootlegged liquor,
but he turned that money
into legitimacy.
His children, great politicians.
And one of them was even
elected president.
Yes, gentlemen, we have been
negotiating with the authorities,
and soon we will reach an agreement.
Our organisation, within six months,
will be out of the cocaine business.
We will surrender our labs,
our safe houses,
and our trafficking routes.
But gentlemen, don't make the mistake
of thinking it won't be on our terms.
Any prison sentences will be minimal.
Our money will remain ours.
Our legitimate businesses
will continue to grow.
We have six months to make
as much money as possible!
And gentlemen,
as a token of our friendship,
we'll give each of you a juicy share
of the final profits from this year.
To the bright future
we'll all soon enjoy.
For our children
and our children's children!
- Cheers...
- Cheers!
- Cheers, gentlemen!
- What did you think?
- I think it's a great move.
- Congratulations!
- For the future!
Thank you, brother.
Thank you for coming.
- What would you like?
- Whiskey. Dry.
Six months...
I'm going to bleed New York dry.
Come up behind the Statue of Liberty
and fuck her right up her ass.
And then what?
We only have six months
of doing whatever the fuck we want?
I love you, brother.
I'll see you on the dance floor.
- Can you get in the car, please?
- Why do you want to leave so early?
Because it's time, OK?
- Why are you treating me like this?
- That's enough!
Get in the car.
How was everything tonight, Jorge?
Very good, sir.
Do you think we surprised them?
Yes.
I think you surprised many people.
I'm told we had an uninvited guest.
What happened there?
Don't be modest.
Córdova told me.
That's your talent.
Spotting the threat, knowing
when they're going to fuck us.
It's priceless.
I'm told you want to leave.
I'm grateful to you
and your family, but...
I'm starting my own security firm.
I only wanted to stay until...
Escobar stopped being a threat.
And we are very grateful. Honestly.
You have done great things for us
over the years.
For my family. For me.
I cannot accept your resignation, Jorge.
With all due respect,
I've already made arrangements...
Arrangements can change.
Look, we didn't get where we are
by allowing good people to leave.
We will need you more than ever
in the months ahead.
It's only six months.
Can I count on you, Jorge?
Yes?
Of course, boss.
Miguel.
The same.
Thanks.
Hello?
Hello? Who is this?
NATIONAL POLICE
Who am I speaking with?
- Juan.
- Here it is, sir.
Thank you.
Don Gilberto.
This just arrived.
Play them.
Subject's name: Dîaz.
Recorded at El Nacional Hotel.
Room 117.
Retirement works
for these motherfuckers. They're rich.
I just bought a brand new plane.
So that motherfucker Gilberto
can shove it up his ass.
Besides, who are they to make a deal
without consulting with us?
They don't get to surrender
on our behalf.
That son of a bitch Díaz.
I'll send Navegante.
Subject's name: Santos.
Recorded in zone 4.
They're going to have to give me more
than that fucking wrapping paper.
Fucking balls on the old goat
to tell me how to run my business.
That's not going to be so easy.
These men are weak.
I'll handle that one myself.
The man is an animal.
Subject name: Beltre.
I'm not going to wait for Rasguño
or Henao to snatch the good territories.
Let's organise so we can
put a move together now.
Fuck Joseph Kennedy,
whoever that asshole is.
Córdova...
El Pecas will handle that one.
You got it, sir.
Subject name: Salazar.
Marîa, I'll be back soon.
I'm going out with some friends.
What do you mean, Claudio?
You're going out now?
Please don't look at me like that.
It's one o'clock in the morning.
Exactly, María. It's one o'clock.
Keep your voice down
so you don't wake the guests.
Fuck off, Claudio.
Go with your whores!
Don't fuck with me, María,
because I'm tired
from clapping all night
for that motherfucker's bullshit.
Don't fuck with me.
Well... that's husband and wife business.
Leave him out.
No, brother.
Salazar shows no respect.
Better safe than sorry.
Honey. What time is it?
It's late.
Go back to sleep.
How was work?
Fine.
I spoke with Miguel.
And?
He asked me not to leave.
Just for a little while.
How long?
I'm asking you how long.
- Six months.
- Six months?
What did you tell him?
What could I tell him? It's six months.
We've talked about this
for a long time.
You're telling me we can't start our new
lives because we have to wait six months?
You know what? I don't think
you really want to leave this job.
- How can you say that?
- You think I'm an idiot?
You like working for them.
It's become your life, Jorge.
You are my life.
The girls are my life.
- What do you want me to do?
- Don't say another word.
- It's six months, not six years!
- Not another word.
- She owns a spa.
- Let's go. We should go!
What can I get you?
A bottle of aguardiente,
and play Dos Gardenias for me.
Gladly, Don Pacho.
Thank you.
Please, Claudio...
accept this as a token of respect.
To let bygones be bygones.
You know what, Pacho?
I think our differences are in the past.
I'll be right back to share it with you.
- Excuse me.
- Please.
- Claudito.
- And now... the bottle.
Go ahead.
Claudito!
- Pacho, motherfucker!
- Pacho, please.
Don't do this. Don't do this to me.
Please, Pacho.
Pacho, please! Pacho, wait!
Please, let's talk. Pacho!
Motherfucker.
He didn't do anything to you.
Pacho, you motherfucker!
Wait, Pacho! Pacho, son of a bitch!
Pacho!
Please, no!
Son of a bitch!
Pacho, son of a bitch!
No!
Son of a bitch, Pacho!
Motherfucker!
Claudio!