WE LOVE YOU!
Present arms!
I am responsible
for the death of those men, Eduardo.
And if Escobar is using their deaths
to send me a message, then I will respond.
I agree completely.
We have to go in full force.
Keep in mind... bringing him back
won't be a popular decision.
But since when do we care
about being popular?
Colonel Carrillo.
Yes, Mr. President.
Boss, they're all saying
they don't know anything.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
You gentlemen are under the impression
that you work for the Moncadas.
Allow me to clarify.
You have never worked for the Moncadas.
You work for me,
and you have always worked for me.
- Blackie.
- Yes, boss.
Who gave Judy Moncada
the cash to buy this house?
You, Don Pablo.
- Jairo.
- Yes, Don Pablo.
The money that puts food on the table
for these men, where does it come from?
- From your pocket.
- Everything you see here is mine.
Everything you have
is because I allow you to have it.
Everything you think you are protecting,
you are protecting for me.
Are we clear on this?
You're going to tell me the location
of every safe house, every lab,
every office,
every account of the Moncadas.
And look...
that doesn't make you gentlemen traitors.
Certainly not.
You simply didn't know
who you were really working for.
So let's begin...
with what's most important.
You're... going to tell me right now...
where that bitch Judy Moncada is hiding.
- Ms. Judy, welcome.
- Thank you.
Pardon me.
- Hey!
- Navegante!
- Watch yourself.
- Mrs. Moncada is our guest.
We treat our guests with respect.
Even the ones who invite themselves.
Listen, Pacho,
are you sure you have enough men?
One might get the impression
you're scared of someone.
Perhaps if you took security
more seriously...
just maybe your husband
would still be alive...
and you wouldn't be coming to us for help.
Listen to this guy.
Who told you I was coming here for help?
Where's your boss?
You mean my partner.
- Handling the business.
- Is that right?
So he's still trying to pretend
he isn't a drug trafficker?
Mrs. Moncada...
why don't you go look around?
I don't know, pet the horses.
Or rehearse whatever it is
you came to say.
Gilberto will be here shortly.
Thank you, Pacho.
Ma'am? Here's what you asked for.
Who's that?
He's one of the new guys.
Excuse me.
POLICE STATION ATTACKED IN MEDELLÍN
What a hideous painting.
What a lovely surprise.
- To what do we owe the pleasure?
- Business.
"And one by one, the nights
between our separated cities,
they are added to the night
that unites us."
It's the middle of the fucking day,
Gilberto.
Not a fan of Neruda?
The only thing that unites us in this life
is a desire to see Pablo dead.
Gentlemen.
So tell me, Mrs. Moncada,
why did you come all this way?
To help you kill the man
who murdered my husband and brother
by offering very important information
that only I possess.
- And what is this information?
- Targets.
The location of every one of his labs.
Going after Pablo's infrastructure
will cripple him, force him to surface.
When he does, we put a bullet in his head
and we take turns shitting on him.
What's valuable isn't knowing
what Pablo has,
but what he wants to acquire.
Because that's where he'll be next.
Pablo is picking apart your operation
piece by piece.
Knowing what remains
tells us where he's going.
You want me to tell you where my labs are?
Well... let's say...
that I share that information.
What happens to my labs?
Oh, Judy.
Your sense of vengeance is heartwarming.
Kiko would be so proud of your priorities.
You're right.
He would be very proud of me.
I built the business by his side, Pacho.
I'm from the Medellín cartel.
I know what I am.
I don't need bullshit art
hanging on my wall to prove any different.
Wait.
Hold on.
Confronting Pablo directly
won't help us maintain a low profile.
But...
what if the Search Bloc were to learn
the location of your labs?
What good is it if he's arrested?
He's already shown
he can fuck us from prison.
This won't end with Pablo in a cell.
You think the police will kill him?
There is one officer
that seems particularly determined.
And President Gaviria
has arranged for his return.
Assemble the Search Bloc outside.
I want 100 men and six trucks.
- Tell them we're moving out. Got it?
- On it, Colonel.
- What's up?
- They just left. Four motorcycles,
five pickups, and a truck.
It's a large convoy.
They're heading to Barrio Escobar.
It's going to get crowded.
The convoy has arrived.
We're in position.
A MAN, A NEIGHBORHOOD, A COUNTRY!
Look. Look up there.
There's something weird happening.
What do you see?
- They're clouds.
- No, not clouds.
Because clouds form shapes.
- What I see is a turtle.
- Boss!
- Excuse me. I need to talk to you.
- Keep looking.
Keep looking at the clouds.
Sir, sorry to interrupt,
but it's very important.
- What's going on?
- Carrillo is back.
And he's here in Medellín.
What else?
That son of a bitch filled
Barrio Escobar with police and...
he pissed on your mural, sir.
Those fucking cops
are going up 26th Street.
Copy that, brother. All good.
Trujillo, load up six unmarked cars,
four men per car.
Instruct them to leave in 20-minute
intervals to avoid attention. Clear?
- Yes, Colonel.
- Okay.
Freeze! Don't move!
Relax. Everything's good.
What is this?
Piraña down.
Son of a bitch.
Where are you going?
Get him!
Don't move!
- Good evening.
- Yes?
Would you allow me to search your house?
We're looking for--
Stop! Stop, boy!
Stop!
Get on the floor!
Show me your hands.
You think you're slick?
Why were you running?
No! What did I do wrong?
You tell me what you did.
Do you know who I am?
My name is Colonel Horacio Carrillo.
Last week...
30 police officers were murdered.
Those pigs probably deserved it.
Many of them were my friends.
A person perched on rooftops,
guiding murderers with radios...
are assassins themselves.
I hope after this encounter,
you'll reconsider
working with someone
who thinks he's above the law.
What? Am I supposed to
shit in my pants in fear?
No.
Do I make myself clear?
I want you to tell your friends,
that this is what happens
when you work for Pablo Escobar!
Take it.
Tell them this is for Pablo.
Remember what you saw.
And know what will happen to you
if I see you on a rooftop.
You can leave.
Leave!
So, what book shall we read
before bed tonight?
The Witch.
No, my love. No scary stories.
The Witch? What's that? I don't know it.
Dad reads it to us. Right, Dad?
- The bad witch and the good witch, right?
- Yes.
Not The Witch, Pablo.
I don't want any more scary stories
in this house.
Love, take your sister
and brush your teeth.
And go straight to bed.
Listen, where's my kiss?
Good night.
- Good night, my love.
- Straight to bed, Manuela, please.
I heard a scary story, Pablo.
The man who killed Gustavo
is back in Medellín.
Is that story true?
Yes.
Does that sound like the government
is trying to negotiate?
Good night.
Someone has to tell you
how things are, Pablo.
That man is here to kill you.
I'm scared, Pablo.
I promise you one thing:
if things get out of hand
and I can't control it...
we'll leave the country.
Okay?
- Have you seen this woman?
- No.
She works at the market.
Sweetheart?
- Are you sure?
- No.
Nobody's seen the bitch.
I'm pissed off, brother.
Let's go for some ice cream.
Something cold.
You were different this time, Javi.
I always know when my clients
are trying to forget something.
You know what I do to relax?
- I write.
- You write?
- What do you write?
- Letters.
For my family, but I never send them.
It's good to forget.
What do you want to forget?
Why don't you stop?
Why don't you?
Welcome, brother.
This way.
- What is your name?
- David.
- I'm Pablo. Pleasure to meet you.
- Pleasure to meet you, too.
Follow me.
They told me you like soccer.
- I play defense.
- Of course.
Those are the real men.
You're very brave, David.
I'm sorry for what you witnessed.
The people we're fighting
are very bad people.
Tell me about the man who did that.
He said this bullet is for you.
I need you to do one last favor for me.
It's very important.
You think you can do it?
Thank you, David.
Agent Peña. This is Don Berna.
I have a proposition
you might be interested in.
What a surprise.
What's up, Peña?
Are you expecting anyone else?
No. Are you?
No, it's not necessary.
Everywhere I go in this town,
I'm surrounded by friends.
Sit down. Sit so you can taste
the best coffee in Medellín.
Doña Luz! Bring my friend a coffee.
You have something
other than coffee for me?
Look, Agent... I'm not one of those
street-corner informants
that you slip a few gringo dollars
for a tip. No, sir.
Then why are we here?
Agent, you and I
are like the snake and the cat.
If the snake has the chance,
it will kill the cat.
And if the cat has the chance,
it will kill the snake.
But there are times
when they see a big rat,
and they both want to eat it.
Gato!
No! Calm down.
Okay, relax. Don't kill me--
Relax!
Detaining the prisoners.
We captured about 45 of them.
Approaching.
We're locking you up.
Move it!
Hello, Valeria.
- I didn't realize you'd be here.
- I wanted to be sure it went well.
- People need to hear the truth, right?
- Yes, it's important.
They forced this boy
to watch his friend get shot.
When the country hears this story,
they'll turn on that son of a bitch
who's murdering children
for the Americans.
Well... that's what I hope.
I'm glad you came.
It's good to see you again.
Are all eyes still on you?
Except yours.
Let's begin.
Yes.
- How old are you?
- Ten.
I understand you're quite a soccer player.
Thank you for being brave enough
to tell us your story, David.
Tell me, who were the men
who brought you to the building that day?
They were Search Bloc policemen.
Do you know why they brought you there?
He said they were going
to send a message to other kids.
Who is "he"? Do you remember his name?
Colonel Carrillo.
Relax, gentlemen, everything's fine.
- Where are you taking us?
- Bogotá.
You're going to jail
until this gets resolved.
But look...
if you help me, I can help you.
Give me Pablo, or Blackie or someone else,
then I'll help you.
I don't know where they are.
I don't know them.
- So you don't know anything?
- No, sir.
What about you, Gato?
All right.
If it's going to be like this...
Who else was there
besides Colonel Carrillo?
A bunch of men.
Some I heard speaking English.
Americans. Like in the movies.
Are you sure they were police?
Yes.
What now?
You think Pablo is going to reward you
for being brave?
Asshole, he doesn't even know you exist.
Do you know that?
It's your last chance, Gato.
Ask your mother, you son of bitch!
- Hello.
- Everything is good.
- It worked.
- Very well.
It worked.
- They took my lab.
- And a bunch of Escobar's men.
It's for a noble cause, Mrs. Moncada.
Boss, forgive me, but there's bad news.
Search Bloc took down the Moncadas'
biggest lab before we could take it apart.
Carrillo got Gato. We don't know where
they are or what they're doing to him.