Hey!
Hey, ladies.
Are you looking for something?
We're just taking a ride.
Can't we pass?
No, sweetheart. You have to go back.
Listen... Do you want to hang out
later back in town?
- What?
- I said...
No, no, no!
- Julio.
- Pacho, you motherfucker.
Motherfucking dog!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Let me go! Let go...
You.
Mrs. Salazar.
Do you know
what makes me happy, Pacho?
Makes me very happy?
That my sons didn't kill
your brother Alvaro.
Because he's going to live
the rest of his life as half a man.
Half man, half...
Help!
'The great event
of the surrender
'of Helmer Herrera to Colombian justice.
'And this incident marked
the end of the Cali cartel,
'who were responsible,
according to international sources,
'for more than 80%
of the cocaine trafficking in the world.
'Throughout my campaign
and presidency,
'I committed to dismantling
all narcotrafficking networks,
'and we're doing it.'
'The Colombian government
was quick to claim victory.
'The arrest of Miguel Rodríguez
'and the surrenders of Pacho Herrera
and Chepe Santacruz
'looked like big wins
in The War on Drugs.
'But they were bullshit.
'The only real victory
belonged to the godfathers of Cali,
'safely ensconced in a Bogotájail...'
Leave that there.
'...still billionaires,
'submitting to a justice that
they had bought and paid for.
'They didn't need to build
their own prison.
'The minimum security wing
of La Picota would do just fine.
'They wouldn't be there long.'
Gilberto. How've you been?
Good, brother.
Grateful that we're all together.
The investment we made in our friends
can bear fruit.
And then, all this will pass away
like some old joke
you can't quite remember.
For this, gentlemen,
I propose a toast.
Of course you would.
Fucking Chepe.
Gilberto, I'd like to say a few words.
You all know this wasn't what I wanted.
So it's very hard for me to admit
that I know this is for the best.
And thanks to you, we're on
the verge of... How do you call it?
"A great victory."
We believe in you.
To my brother, Gilberto.
Our leader.
Gentlemen of Cali... salud!
Cheers!
Don't worry about it.
Agent Peña.
Hello.
- Can we talk?
- Yeah. Give me a second.
Go with your mum.
I checked with the embassy. They're
finishing up paperwork this afternoon.
You're on a flight tomorrow. First thing.
Guillermo Pallomari...
- Any idea where we can find him?
- No. Why do you need him?
Gilberto and Miguel Rodríguez
gave six million dollars
to Samper's presidential campaign.
So unless we get Pallomari in the States
testifying on the cartel,
generating new indictments...
- What are you telling me?
- The godfathers won't stay locked up.
What'll happen to my family if these men
keep all their money and all their power?
Witness Protection Services will provide
security for as long as you need.
Pallomari's wife's having an affair.
- With who?
- Some guy at her office. Fredy Moya.
The phones in the cartel safe house,
they're tapped.
I overheard a conversation between them.
It didn't sound like business.
- And he can keep them in prison?
- We find Pallomari or the godfathers walk.
You're not gonna find him without me.
You're right.
Go ahead, sir.
Director.
Don Miguel.
Please, go ahead.
♪ To all the killers
and a hundred dollar billers... ♪
- Hello.
- 'It's me.
- Where are we on Pallomari?
- 'We put Navegante on it, Dad.'
I'll find him, don't worry about it.
And fucking Salcedo too, you'll see.
David, don't take your eye off Henao.
That motherfucker might see this
as an opportunity. Keep a low profile.
Sure, don't worry.
- How's María?
- 'I really don't know.'
'How come you don't know?
Make sure she's taken care of.'
It's very important
that you handle Pallomari.
That motherfucker could ruin everything.
Call me when it's done.
- Guillermo?
- I need your help, Gonzalo.
You know I can't get involved.
Nothing is going to happen to you.
When has anything ever happened to you?
I'm asking you for legal advice,
and quickly.
I've decided that the best way
to get out of this situation
is to turn myself in to the authorities.
Yes, normally that would be
the case. Yes.
But the problem is you already
have a warrant out for your arrest.
An arrest warrant?
The police won't protect you.
In fact, they'll probably kill you.
I'm the head accountant.
And every dollar in this organisation,
and every secret,
has been through this head.
It's all in here.
So tell whoever needs to know
that I'm willing to negotiate.
Guillermo, my advice to you
is to get your family and leave Cali.
My wife's very attached to her work.
- What? I don't understand.
- You know her, she's stubborn.
She built her business
from the ground up.
I can't leave without her.
Look, Guillermo... this is not
my legal advice, but as your friend.
Talk some sense into your wife.
Immediately.
Can you get me a gun?
We'll have to look out for ourselves
for the rest of our lives,
but if I help them, maybe one day
we can come back to Colombia.
Are you insane? They almost killed us.
They almost killed us, and now you're
telling me you want to go back? To Cali?
Do you really think
we can come back to Colombia?
The moment we come back to Colombia,
they'll kill our daughters.
Are you doing this to make up
for the last four years of your life?
I'm a good man.
I was a good man.
I'll leave with the girls tomorrow.
I'm not waiting for you.
Wait for me, okay? Thanks.
That way.
Keep looking for him.
No more fucking excuses.
Okay.
Yeah?
Have you heard from your father?
Yes.
David, I've been wondering about
the arrangement I had for my son and...
Arrangement?
I thought it was true love.
Your father knows I care about him.
That's beautiful. Seriously.
But here's the thing...
You don't mean anything to me.
You're not my mother.
You're not my fucking problem.
- David...
- What?
What the fuck do I owe you?
María...
Open your legs for someone else.
You're good at that.
Okay?
Once we step off this plane,
whatever goes down is on me.
We are way off the well-lit path.
Jorge...
Good afternoon, Mr. Salcedo.
Mr. Espinosa's still at lunch.
He should be back soon.
- We'll wait for him inside.
- Okay, sir.
Another drink?
I need to go. See you next week.
Excuse me.
How are the girls here?
The best of Cali.
Open it!
Get in.
Get in, motherfucker!
Okay...
ACCESS RESTRICTED
PASSWORD REQUIRED
- Good afternoon.
- I'm looking for Fredy Moya.
- Yes.
- The one wearing purple.
- Thanks.
Don't pull my chain.
I'm looking at the numbers.
Excuse me.
You work with Patricia Pallomari?
Javier Peña, DEA.
I'll call you back.
I'm afraid Patricia has
taken a temporary leave of absence.
That so?
- You have any idea where I can find her?
- I wouldn't know.
- She in trouble?
- No, but her husband is.
There's a warrant out for his arrest
and a pretty substantial reward.
Any information is helpful.
- 'Hello?'
- It's me.
Baby, I can't talk right now.
Call me back later.
'No. Wait, I can't call you back.
Wait.'
Yes.
Yes, I'd have to check
my records in the office.
I can't talk. Wait...
Patricia, the DEA was just here.
The DEA. Asking questions.
- 'What did you tell them?'
- 'To go fuck themselves.
- 'They want Guillermo, not you.'
- 'I can't talk now. We'll discuss it later.'
- That's her.
- 'Patricia, they talked about a reward.'
So, she used the line
in an apartment
in the north part of the city.
We need to take advantage.
I need to use the bathroom.
- Work again?
- Yes.
Excuse me.
Open the window this time.
This way.
I'd offer a drink,
but I don't pour liquor for Cali whores.
Have a seat.
Don Orlando,
I'm here to ask for your protection.
Why? You don't feel safe?
I did what I had to do
after my husband died.
Now I'm in your home...
ready to do what I have to do once again.
So what is it you're offering me?
In here.
How was the drive?
It was easy.
Nice place.
Let me start by thanking you
for the meeting.
We're both busy men.
I won't waste your time.
But I'm a businessman, like you.
The information you seek maybe,
maybe, maybe is in my possession.
If we come to an arrangement,
my information becomes yours.
You feel me?
On the phone, you told me
you know where Pallomari is. Correct?
Look, let me put it this way...
Patricia and I are in love.
We want to be together.
So Guillermo's a problem for me.
And from what I've heard,
he's a problem for you too. Am I right?
You are correct.
So maybe we can help each other.
If we come to an arrangement,
my information becomes yours.
Okay.
- Let me fix you a drink. Okay?
- Sure.
By the way, are you guys
running Windows 95 yet?
Think we're going to wait for next year.
Where the fuck is Pallomari,
you queer?
Did you hear me?
Here's the milk. Just a few minutes
and then you go to bed.
- Get in your room.
- Who is it? Who is it?
I don't know.
Get in your room. Quickly.
- Drop the gun! Put it down!
- Drop your weapon! Put it down!
- It's okay.
- They're the gringos.
- Calm down.
- Do you know them?
- They came to my office.
- Put the gun down.
- Close the door.
- We're here to help you.
Close the door.
- Okay.
Lower your gun.
You understand?
- I'd put the safety on.
- Sorry.
Do you want to sit?
Okay, DEA, are we speaking English
or Spanish or...? I don't give a shit.
The Colombians have a warrant
for your arrest.
- I know.
- And the cartel wants you dead.
I'm well aware of that.
The only way you survive this
is if we get you out to the United States.
Guillermo...
- The United States?
- We have your ledger.
You decode it for us
and you testify on what you know...
That's quite a bit.
...and we make sure that
you and your family are safe.
- Which place in the United States?
- I'm not sure. We have a program that...
Yeah, I know. The program.
But if I'm giving up my life...
...I want to know
what I'm getting for it.
For instance,
which kind of house will we have?
My family requires
a certain amount of square footage.
It wasn't very hard for us to find you
and it won't be hard for them.
Do you understand that?
This is your chance
to keep your family alive.
We will negotiate the details later.
This is the only option you have.
Do you understand that?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Why don't you pack your things,
as little as possible.
No, Guillermo.
We can't leave for at least a week.
- You heard them.
- The company. I can't just leave!
- I need at least a week...
- Okay!
Put the radio on the dash
and your hands on the wheel.
How are you, Jorge Salcedo?
Go help your kids pack
and let me talk to your wife.
Yeah.
I know about Fredy Moya.
It's none of my business.
- You're right. It's not your problem.
- You realise what happens if they find you?
And your kids?
I have to say goodbye to him.
We're in love. I can't leave like that.
Mrs. Pallomari, if you stay, you die.
Understood?
I'll be honest with you.
The truth is...
I was very disappointed
to hear you were the fucking rat.
But I still like you.
It's all good. I'm not going to kill you.
David Rodríguez...
...he wants to do it himself
personally, you know?
That's fine by me.
That way,
our friendship will remain intact.
- Let's go.
- Come on, damn it!
- The jacket...
- Okay, that's it. Let's go.
We're on our way down.
'Salcedo, we're in the lobby now.'
Are we clear?
'Salcedo?'
Tell them to come out.
Jorge, we clear or not?
Tell them to come out, Jorge Salcedo.
All clear.
Copy.
All right, stay close.
Let's finish this.
Put the gun down.
I don't want to kill you.
We both know that's a lie.
Get down! Get behind the car!
Over there!
What the fuck happened?
He has the keys.
- Let's move!
- Come on, get in the car!
Let's go!
- You drive.
- Patricia!
Don't look!
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
- Don't look at that!
- What the fuck is he doing here?
He saved your life!
Get in the fucking car!
Open! Open!
Be careful, be careful. Okay.
Move, move, move, move!
What happened? Huh?
They killed Navegante.
- And Pallomari?
- The motherfucker's gone.
You sure?
We're going to the airport.
We're going to catch those...
We're leaving, now!
Motherfuckers!
You, come with me.
We're going to the airport.
Take the guys. Now, now, now!
That's the North Valley, you fuckers.
Who do they think they're messing with?
You just got smoked, bitches.
Boss!
Let's go. Out.
- Could you open, please?
- Yes. There you go.
Thank you.
Patricia, get out this way.
Careful, my love.
Okay.
- What's this?
- You're wanted by the CNP.
We can't aid the escape of a fugitive,
so you've gotta fly yourself out.
Do you see that?
We have a private plane.
We have a plane just for us.
- If you could sign here, sir?
- Me? Okay. Yeah.
You have to pay for the plane.
Whatever you have on you.
I don't carry that kind of cash...
It's just a technicality.
So that it's not kidnapping.
Just a moment.
If it's just a technicality...
- Thanks. Okay.
- Okay.
Get on the plane. Go.
Everything's going to be fine.
Come on. Let's go.
Goodbye, Salcedo.
Ladies and gentlemen, my next witness
has direct, first-hand knowledge
of the criminal activities uncovered
by Operation Cornerstone.
Please state your name, sir.
Guillermo Pallomari.
And you were an accountant
for the Cali cartel?
No, I was the chief accountant.
The chief. El jefe.
'Guillermo Pallomari
had a lot to say.
'And he said it in federal courtrooms
from Miami to New York City.'
This is the ledger of Mr. Pallomaro
that only he himself can interpret.
I'm sorry, your Honour, my English is not
quite good, but his Spanish is awful.
Can you repeat my name?
"Pallomari." It's so simple.
'And people were interested
in what he had to say,
'especially about the cartel's influence
with the Colombian government.
'So that government
went on the defensive.'
'And we have total
agreement in that these testimonies
'that we have heard from Mr. Pallomari
are ridiculous and grotesquely false.
'Thank you very much.'
'But the damage was done.
'It would be most helpful if the Colombian
president, who's head of the government,
'was as dedicated
to fighting narcotics trafficking
'as many of the people
in his own government.'
'The U.S. House and Senate
began making noise about decertification,
'turning Colombia from an ally
in The War on Drugs into an enemy,
'threatening to choke off
the vital foreign aid
'that served the shadowy interests
of both nations.
'And that scared people.
'Enough to see justice finally done?
Well, governments don't work that way.'
You know how many times
I've gotten a call
from the Department of Justice and State
the same morning?
Count 'em on one finger.
Guess we have you to thank for that.
I'm headed over
to the National Palace right now,
to make clear to President Samper himself
that the godfathers stay in jail.
- At least for the foreseeable future.
- But that's as far as it goes?
We drew up a draft indictment outlining
President Samper's ties to the Cali cartel.
Alleged ties.
And I suggest you keep that draft
to yourself.
The DOJ's not going to topple
a government, Agent Peña.
You can't tell me
you're surprised by that.
Some part of me
was holding out hope, I guess.
Well, you should tell that part
to grow the fuck up.
No, I mean it, Agent Peña.
You should be happy.
You played the system
like a goddamn fiddle.
You won.
Yes, sir.
'Another deal.
'A compromise.
'A charade.
'A way for governments
who don't give a shit
'about the war
they're supposed to be fighting...
'to go on pretending they're winning it.
'But it can't be won.
'It'll never be won.
'At least not until people see it
for what it is.
'Not until they know the truth.'
You know what it means
if you go on the record, right?
There'll be a price to pay.
Press the button.
Let's start with your name
and occupation.
Javier Peña,
DEA attaché in Colombia.
'And so the truth got out.
'The news that the Cali cartel had
donated to the president's campaign
'in exchange for virtual immunity
'turned Colombia upside down.
'And when the highest-ranking DEA agent
in the country went on the record
'and said not only did
the United States know about it,
'but we allowed it to happen,
'they couldn't hide from it anymore.'
'In an exclusive interview,
'he accuses the country
of being a Narco-Democracy.
'He said the country
has fallen into the abyss.
'His words have not been well received
by the Colombian people.
'The public is demanding
an official response...'
You didn't really call the country that
we're guests in a "Narco-Democracy"?
- Are you saying it isn't?
- The State Department's livid.
Good.
They're responsible. We all are.
Samper is not going anywhere.
Well, at least people know the truth.
I want you gone, Peña.
So do the Colombians.
I understand, sir.
You know, any aspirations you had
for your career...
...just got dragged
behind the barn and shot.
I resigned from the DEA this morning.
'Recordings that link the president
with narcotrafficking have been leaked.'
'The reality is that
they need five million.
- 'Uh-huh.'
- 'We're missing three, see?'
- 'We have it.'
- 'Yes?'
'Yes, that's done.'
'This scandal threatens elected president
Ernesto Samper's career
'if the authorities confirm his campaign
was funded by narcotrafficking money.'
'President Samper,
the only solution is your resignation!'
'Colombians can be certain...
'...that if they prove
any money transfer of any kind,
'the deposit would've been made
behind my back.'
'The Colombians called
the scandal "Proceso 8000".
'And it set into motion
a series of events
'that finally brought the reign
of the Cali godfathers to an end.
'Chepe Santacruz never did make it
back to New York.
'Without the government's guarantee
that their sentences would be minimal,
'Chepe decided that prison wasn't
the best place for him to be.
'And so, he released himself...
'...and set out in search of new alliances,
'with partners who could help him
rebuild the empire.
'You won't believe who he chose.'
Don Chepe.
I was happy to get your call.
'Predictably,
it wasn't much of a partnership.
'It seems the Castaños expected
a larger contribution to their cause...
'...than Chepe was comfortable making.
'So the alliance died quickly.
'And Chepe Santacruz's wild ride
came to an end.
'Pacho Herrera didn't fare
much better staying in jail.
'Vendettas in the drug game
never end.'
'And Pacho's war on the Salazars
'made him some lifelong
North Valley enemies.
Motherfucker!
'And as for
the Rodríguez-Orejuela brothers,
'political pressure from the U.S.
and a disgraced Colombian president
'who needed to prove
he was tough on narcos
'brought back the only effective weapon
we have in The War on Drugs: extradition.
'All out of favours
and unlikely to find more,
'they will spend the rest of their lives
in a U.S. prison.
'The good guys didn't do much better.
'Back in Colombia, Jorge Salcedo
was publicly branded a rat.'
The danger that he put himself in
to insure the success of our operation...
'And in the States, despite testimony
that he was instrumental to our efforts
'to capture and prosecute
the Cali godfathers,
'he still had to plead guilty
to felony conspiracy charges.
'And from there, Jorge Salcedo...
'...the guy who had the most to do
with bringing down the Cali cartel
'disappeared into the Federal
Witness Protection Program
'somewhere in the U.S.
'A prison of its own.'
- You knew him, right? Agent Camarena?
- Of him.
My first assignment out of the academy
was a task force that
searched for him in Guadalajara.
It all started there. Before him,
we didn't even know we were in a war.
Another hot one down there
for you, huh?
You took down the big players
in Colombia.
Yeah, well... we'll make new ones.
Don't turn a victory into a defeat, Javier.
The Colombian super-cartels are gone.
And whoever comes next are gonna be
fighting amongst themselves for years.
They're still only going to be a shadow
of what Medellín and Cali were.
And now it's time to take the fight
to the real enemy in The War on Drugs.
Mexico.
"The real enemy"?
Let me put in some calls. I'll make
this bullshit resignation go away.
What else is a guy like you gonna do?
All right, fellas. Let's move.
Keep going.
You helping me with this or not?
- I thought I was getting a partner.
- Come on, Pop. Give me that.
Stubborn.
You can stand here
for an hour and count 20 of 'em going by.
So... do you have to fix
the fence every time a storm hits?
Someone has to do it.
That's how life works.
You thinking
of taking them up on it? Mexico?
It's different there.
- Son, let me tell you...
- Dad.
I've done enough.
I'm through.
Hand me that cutter.