Good morning, Sergeant.
Good morning, Paisa.
What have you got for us?
I’ve got plumbing valves,
a bunch of clean towels,
and extra uniforms for the guards.
Let him go. He’s been checked.
Continue. Continue, Paisa.
Thank you, Sergeant.
—Good day.
—Good day, Paisa.
—Thank you! Good day, Sergeant.
You’re here, my friend!
—How you doing, Velasco?
—Good, brother. How was the trip?
Fine, fine. What a long drive!
—Really?
—It’s really hot.
Did you encounter any problems?
Nothing. Perfect. Complete success.
I brought everything, including
the special items requested by Pablo.
—What’s going on, buddy?
—Blackie!
—I thought you forgot about us.
—Let me show you.
Oh, my God. All right, boys!
Get a ladder over here!
—Welcome to La Catedral.
—Hello.
Come on down, ladies.
We’ll take care of you.
Come on! Hurry up!
What? Is it heavy?
—That looks delicious, Paisa.
—All right, lobsters.
Excuse me, boss.
I’ve got a report.
Moncada and Galeano
are reporting that we got 10,000 kilos
through Mexico and the Caribbean.
Did they pay the war tax?
Yes, boss, but ever since
you settled things with the government,
a lot of other people
have been complaining.
My expenses in and out of the prison
must be covered by everyone.
Understood.
Moncada and Galeano said the Cali cartel
are preparing for a ceasefire.
As am I.
We’re going to negotiate a truce.
But first,
we’re going to kill a few of his men.
I’m sorry, boss, but the Cali cartel
is going to take that as an act of war,
don’t you think?
The purpose of war …
is peace.
What’s the deal, brother?
Look what you’ve done to my car.
—Where?
—Look at this traffic jam.
Look what you did to my car!
—How am I gonna drive this?
—It’s nothing.
Look at the fucking traffic jam
this is causing.
Yeah, man!
And you don’t even speak Spanish?
Get out of here.
—Don’t mess with me, asshole.
—Easy, man.
Son of a bitch. Are you gonna hit me?
What the hell have you come here for, fag?
I deserve respect, you son of a bitch.
So that’s it, then.
What, are you gonna hit me?
You and who else?
OK, take it easy.
It’s all right. It’s OK, now.
—Calm down, asshole.
—OK?
—Relax, man. OK.
OK, calm down.
Have some tolerance.
—Do you hear that?
—What?
People. Children. Laughter.
Even the vendors are back out.
And all because we gave Escobar
the keys to his own prison.
You did the right thing.
You think?
You should be happy.
Finally, people can return
to their normal lives.
Finally … we are at peace.
We spoke with Pablo,
and he is willing to negotiate.
Ten of my men
have just been killed.
Is that how you guys
begin negotiations?
Two things, Pacho.
First … Mr Galeano and I
had nothing to do with those deaths.
And the second thing …
this is war, Pacho.
There are deaths everywhere,
and we have casualties as well.
We are willing
to pay three million dollars
to settle the dispute
we had in Los Angeles.
Pablo won’t accept anything
under $12 million, Pacho.
Twelve million is nothing to you.
Do you want to know something?
It’s over.
What’s over?
The Medellín cartel.
No, you’re wrong, Pacho.
We export twice the amount you do.
You invited me here
to give me this line of bullshit?
Pablo put a war tax on the two of you
for $250,000 a month.
That’s how he treats
his friends and associates?
Don’t forget that, thanks to
Mr Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria,
extradition was abolished.
That serves you very well, doesn’t it?
He was the one
who got us into this mess.
Killing politicians and cops,
bombing street corners and airplanes.
He started this fucking war.
Are we going to negotiate or not?
We’re here, gentlemen!
—Gentlemen!
—What a bumpy ride, Paisa.
Where did you learn to drive?
We closed the deal at ten million dollars.
This takes care of the problem
we had in LA and ends the war.
Sounds like a good proposition.
Do you know what this means, boss?
We can maintain our infrastructure
and the government won’t be the wiser.
That way, we can … double our exports
in less than a month, Pablo.
How did he behave …
when he offered you the money?
What do you mean,
“how did he behave”?
What was his attitude?
Well … he was respectful, Pablo.
Respectful in what way?
—He wants peace, just like us.
—Yes, but …
how did he react
when you told him our solution?
In a positive manner.
He just offered you the money,
just like that?
Well … he started
at three million dollars. Right?
But we said no, and told him
you wouldn’t take less than 12.
So he offered ten,
and we felt that was a fair deal.
Offered you three million?
He was feeling us out.
He knew we wouldn’t accept that.
If he really respected me,
he would be grateful if I accepted 20.
That’s right, boss.
Ask for 20. In one shot.
Tell him I’m not happy
with less than 30.
The Cali cartel won’t accept that, Pablo.
Thirty million …
if Cali wants peace.
Very good.
I also need to raise the war tax.
From now on,
a million a month,
for both of you …
and all our other partners.
Good move beating him,
you son of a bitch.
We talked with Pablo
and reached an agreement.
We agreed to …
—one million dollars.
—What?
Right.
What about the house in Cartagena?
That’s not happening, right?
Do you want your house in Cartagena?
—Of course.
—OK … you will have it.
Don’t you see
things are improving?
No, I see things
are getting more complicated.
Instead of getting better …
things are getting worse.
Pablo doesn’t want peace with Cali.
Now, what about this war tax
he’s charging you?
$250,000 was a lot of money.
And now a million? Ridiculous.
What do you think I should do?
Call Pablo and tell him I won’t pay it?
—Obviously not.
—Then I don’t understand.
—What do you want me to do?
—It’s not right, Kiko, and you know it.
Look, I … adore Pablo.
I adore him.
But the thing is, I don’t know
what’s going on with him these days.
I don’t know.
Maybe he’s depressed.
We’re here in a Jacuzzi …
free.
Do you love me?
Stop fucking around.
You make me angry.
What happened?
Did it stop?
Good morning.
—What’s up?
—Are you “The Paisa”?
—Yes.
—Nice to meet you. Javier Peña.
Do me a favour
and get out of the truck.
—What’s going on?
—Don’t be afraid.
Up against the truck.
Let’s go.
Do me another favour.
Open it up.
Go on.
Look, gringos …
you don’t have the right to do this.
Of course we have the right.
You just press the button in the truck
and we will do the rest, OK?
If the boss finds out that I let you
put cameras in the truck, he’ll kill me.
Pablo’s your boss?
Yeah? Yeah.
I am your boss. Yes?
It’s OK, it’s OK!
I’ll do whatever you say.
Yeah?
Are you OK, friend?
Good day.
—This is a--
—Yes, it’s a roulette wheel.
He has a casino
right there at La Catedral.
—Where did you get these pictures?
—From the DEA.
Of course.
It’s not just these pictures.
They also have pictures of judges,
local government people,
other narcos, prostitutes …
Even soccer players come to visit Pablo.
—Who else has seen these?
—No one, as far as I know.
That’s why we have to act now.
Do you think the DEA is capable
of leaking the photos to the media?
The DEA is capable of anything.
That’s why we have to do something now.
At one time, Escobar …
used to own all of Colombia.
Now he’s just the owner
of his own prison.
If I had to choose
between prostitutes at La Catedral …
or bombings in the country …
I would be eternally grateful
to these women.
Happy birthday, Pablo!
—Watch your step.
—Careful with the little girl!
How are you? Welcome.
Hello, sweetheart.
They’re the ones I hired?
I don’t believe you.
They are really good, Blackie.
I like them.
Come on, Pablo, tell us …
what are you doing these days?
—How do you spend your time?
—Aside from missing his family?
Of course.
He’s writing a book.
—Mother.
—What?
Isn’t it true?
You are writing a book.
Please, Mom.
Well, then, you tell them.
—It’s a collection of magazine articles.
—Many articles.
—Clippings. It’s a book of cartoons.
—Oh, cartoons!
From newspapers and magazines
all over the world.
And you know what?
People write him every day.
—It’s because they love him.
—Of course, I can imagine.
You have to find ways
to keep your mind occupied around here.
Yes, my love. And you have Judy’s husband
and Galeano to help you with the business.
Yes, on that note,
Kiko is so grateful to you
for all the responsibilities
you have given him.
Thank you very much.
—We were in Cartagena--
—Where?
—We were in Cartagena last week.
—Oh, yeah?
Oh, yes, we spent
some beautiful days there relaxing.
It must feel good
to be able to relax like that.
—How nice.
—Wonderful, Tata. You can’t imagine.
But I’ll tell you,
Cartagena is really expensive.
Oh, it’s unaffordable.
Besides, this whole “war with Cali” thing,
it’s tough, you know,
with the tax we have to pay.
We understand it’s not easy,
but there’s not much we can do.
It’s OK.
Kiko complained about that?
He mentioned it.
He didn’t complain, Pablo,
he didn’t complain.
Everyone here is absolutely aware
of the huge sacrifice that you’re making,
for God’s sake.
So I think it’s normal, right?
It’s normal that
we’d give you our support.
Well, I think it’s normal …
I really do.
Juan Pablito, go play with your dad
for a little while, OK?
Honey, you should
play with the kids a little bit.
Leave the gift here.
I’ll look after it.
Apologize!
—Were you watching?
—Yes.
You apologize!
I’m sorry, boss.
I didn’t mean it.
—Relax.
—Are you all right, boss?
Relax. That’s how the game goes.
Go on, go on.
You guys continue.
Are you all right, sir?
Boss.
Excuse me, boss,
but I need to speak to you.
Everything OK?
—Boss, we have a problem.
—What problem?
You remember that Moncada and Galeano
had a large shipment
—that was seized in Boyacá?
—Yes.
—250 kilos.
—Exactly.
Can you imagine, a farmer found
three million dollars buried in a field?
Do you know where that was, boss?
In Rionegro.
There’s cash buried everywhere.
The guerrillas, the paramilitary,
the narcos …
—Everybody’s burying cash.
—Yes, I know.
But right on Moncada
and Galeano’s property?
Don’t you think that’s strange, boss?
I think it’s strange.
Look. All this cash …
was found … in a field.
That’s good luck, Pablo.
Or it could be bad luck.
For you both.
It was on your property,
in Rionegro.
But Pablo,
those lands are over 300 acres,
and most of us rent out to the farmers.
You told me that you had
a 250-kilo shipment seized.
That’s true.
The shipment equaled that amount of cash.
Who told you to open your mouth?
Not true?
Pablo, do you think
we’re stealing from you?
That we made up that whole story
about the seizure?
If you’d like,
check with the cops in Boyacá.
Right, because cops in Boyacá
are so honest, right?
Keep in mind that
we bought that property from Gustavo.
I even remember Gustavo saying
that you had cash stashed in every corner.
Gustavo …
would never forget where he buried cash.
Who’s putting this shit
in your head, Pablo? These assholes?
These fuckers would sell their own mother.
We are partners and friends.
Maybe that cash was lost
because I raised the tax?
Bullshit.
I paid the tax and never complained.
That’s a lie.
—Because you complained to your wife.
—I haven’t complained.
You have no idea
what I talk about with Judy.
I understand this
is difficult for you, Pablo--
What is difficult for me?
Well, managing all of this.
That’s why you hired us.
So we can manage it
and look after it.
You trust us, right?
I understand this makes you anxious--
—Do I look anxious?
—No, I didn’t mean that.
—You said with certainty that--
—No, no, what I meant to say was--
—I think you’re the one who’s anxious.
—We didn’t do shit, Pablo!
With that tone of yours …
you’re telling me you didn’t do shit?
Like I was some kind of idiot.
Is this my cash or not‽
No, Pablo.
Did you take it and bury it
in Rionegro or not‽
For sure,
these guys hid your cash, boss.
—It’s the truth, you pair of liars.
—Of course, he--
—Shut up, motherfucker!
—You’re petty thieves!
You shut up, motherfucker!
Don’t you disrespect me!
Pablo, look at me, man.
We’re family.
You’re my daughter’s godfather.
And also godfather to Galeano’s kids.
What’s going on?
We’re like brothers.
We’re partners and friends.
We’ve been in this
our whole lives, Pablo.
We made our first trip to Miami together.
We made so much cash together that
we don’t even know what we spent it on.
What’s the problem?
What’s happening?
The two of us love you very much.
And we’re very grateful.
All right.
Being stuck in here …
can make someone paranoid.
Well, man,
these things happen, right?
We’re here for whatever you need.
Trust us.
I’m going to make a trip to Miami.
I’ll bring you a few little things
to keep you entertained, OK?
Pablo, don’t do it! Pablo, no!
You’re a dog,
you son of a bitch!
What does it feel like
to take a shit on your own empire?
You want us to tell you
that we stole the money?
At the end of the day, you’ll believe
whatever you want, motherfucker.
Goodbye, Kiko.
Kill me if you’re such a man,
motherfucker.
Kill me with your own fucking hands!
Who are you talking to, asshole?
Motherfucker!
Wait a second!
Be careful, man.
Look what the dead guy gave me.
What the fuck!
You’re going to burn all the meat!
What is wrong with you? Can’t you see
I’m doing it to cover the smell?
—Yeah, but let’s not burn it all.
—What are we gonna do with all this meat?
—What are you going to do?
—What am I supposed to do?
What?
Boss, are you OK?
Do you need anything, boss?
We’re grilling some meat.
Do you want some?
No. I’m not hungry.
Navegante.
Boss.
—Do you want me to wax it?
—No, relax.
This one’s my favourite.
I enjoy it.
This is a beautiful car.
Anything new on Galeano and Moncada?
Looks like the rumours are true, boss.
It’s a shame.
I warned them.
As the twig is bent, so grows the tree.
Do you still have that DEA contact?
Javier Peña? Of course.
I want you to contact him
and confirm the rumours.
They’re just as interested
in screwing Escobar as we are.
I haven’t heard from him since yesterday.
I’ve called everyone. I’m so worried.
Pablo told me
that they left La Catedral.
Just relax, sweetie.
Your husband is fine.
No, thank you.
Maybe … they had to go
somewhere else urgently?
Or maybe they left
without saying anything.
The way our men usually do.
Yes, but it’s a little strange,
don’t you think?
Kiko was very clear that he had
a meeting with Pablo at La Catedral.
He said he would be home later.
We’re trying to have another baby.
I think I told you that.
No? We’re trying to have another baby,
and the time is right,
so we had a very important date to keep.
Are you sure that Pablo
told you that Kiko left La Catedral?
Are you telling me
that my husband is a liar?
I want my husband back.
If Pablo told Tata that they left …
it’s because they left.
Listen …
Pablo is your kids’ godfather.
He would never hurt them.
What do you think?
These photos are worth looking into.
And believe me, I’m going to.