Tata.
Tata. Where is everyone?
Pablo.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
Go back to bed.
Do you know why they brought you there?
He said they were going to send a message
to other kids.
Who is "he"? Do you remember his name?
Colonel Carrillo.
I know this is difficult...
but tell me what happened
when they brought you there.
They killed my friend.
- I'm very sorry...
- This is a farce.
- Escobar trained this kid very well.
- I'll speak with Carrillo.
Whether he did or didn't do it
is beside the point.
Colombia is tired of Escobar.
Besides, Valeria Velez?
My God, she has no credibility
in this country.
I need to know if Carrillo
killed that boy.
If we say that she's doing this
to discredit Carrillo, they'll believe us.
But if the press finds out
that you spoke to Carrillo about this...
They'll assume it's the truth.
Exactly.
What do you propose?
That we don't play Escobar's game.
And that we leave things as they are...
for the time being.
I think we're going to need
more than an interview.
- No. No violence.
- That's not what I mean. I suggest--
Now we need to have the people
on our side.
Yes, of course. It's just the president
has denied it ever happened,
and the American news
hasn't even picked up the story.
Of course.
If David were the son
of an important politician, but...
the men of always aren't interested
in the children of never.
- Of course.
- Right?
I'm writing a letter to the editors
of the most important newspapers
to tell them how that boy came to me,
scared for his life.
The world has to know what sort of monster
that son of a bitch Carrillo is.
Don Pablo, that's excellent.
Give me that pencil.
Burn everything.
Don't move! Felix, take this one.
Don't even think about it.
Up against the wall.
We don't know yet. We're working on it.
Are we having a good time?
That's a very pretty girl.
But you're paying for those lines,
asshole.
Clean this shit up!
Who taught you to live like this?
Not from our mother!
And wake up, asshole!
And you, Edgar!
Call Pablo and ask him
where he wants us to take his half.
All right. All right.
What are you doing calling
from that phone? Use the pay phone!
- Relax, brother.
- Edgar...
What?
- Have you been calling from this phone?
- No.
Son of a--
Move it, faggot!
Hey there.
Dad?
- Quickly, inside!
- Friend.
Calm down, friend.
Everything is all right.
I can't believe it. You son of a bitch.
It's carbon rock.
The cocaine is dissolved and mixed in.
Did you think I bought chemistry labs
because I enjoyed the class in school?
You're going to put chemists
out of business.
I'm more interested
in putting Pablo out of business.
Now's the time to move in on Miami.
It won't be hard for us
to take that business.
- But don't you think it's too early?
- Pablo's in hiding.
The Search Bloc is killing his men.
Soon they'll catch him,
and I want us to be in an advantageous
position when that happens.
Could you take care of that?
Yes, of course.
But don't make it too obvious.
I don't want Judy Moncada asking fucking
questions and negotiating for a piece.
Then you should call Pablo
and tell him we'd be happy
to turn Judy over to him.
We'll dump her in the same ditch
we'll be dumping him in.
Guys.
The Search Bloc took another Moncada lab.
The sons of bitches killed
three of the Prisco brothers.
Ricardo got away.
- When was this?
- Last night.
It's that son of a bitch, Don Berna.
He's telling the cops everything.
Let's hide out on the coast.
I'll convince Don Pablo.
Since when do we hide, brother?
Let's trust the boss.
Yes. Don Pablo always finds a solution.
- Hello?
- Get me Don Pablo.
- Who is this?
- Fernando Duque.
- Fernando.
- Get him now.
Yes, sir, right away. Limón, please.
Boss?
Your lawyer, Mr. Duque.
- How many were published?
- Don Pablo,
we sent all of them to the newspapers.
How many of my letters were published,
Fernando?
Yes. None.
They're very well written.
It's not about how well written they were,
Fernando. It was the fucking truth!
This is why we saw ourselves forced
to take up arms and defend ourselves...
Move it, you sons of bitches!
All right. Very good.
Guys.
Ms. Judy.
All right, now... I would like
to know the reason for this meeting.
- You don't see this every day.
- Look, Pacho, it's simple.
We need to get rid of Pablo Escobar.
We know you all joined forces against him.
And we want to know if it's possible
for my brother and I to join the cause.
Why? What do you want out of this?
- We want what's best for Colombia.
- That's it?
Pablo Escobar,
aside from being a terrorist,
is also allied with the guerrillas,
who he has helped on many occasions.
Putting an end to Pablo Escobar
is a patriotic act.
Imagine, Pacho, your financial resources
combined with all of the information
you have on Pablo Escobar's operation
- with our military experience--
- We'd make one hell of a death squad.
No, Mrs. Moncada. No.
A death squad? No. An army.
And when this army gets to Medellín,
Pablo Escobar's death
won't be a matter of months.
It'll be a matter of weeks.
What do you say, Pacho?
Can we count on the support
of you and your partners?
All of this sounds interesting.
With all due respect, gentlemen,
our organization already
has a strategy in place, and it's working.
It doesn't seem to me like it's working.
Because, to this day,
Pablo Escobar is still alive.
- That's right.
- At this rate, not for long.
Look, I'll share this conversation
with our partners.
But I think that, for now,
our answer is no.
Excuse me.
- Calm down. I'm not going to hurt you.
- How did you find me?
I'm not going to hurt you, I promise.
- And La Quica?
- He's not here.
He's back there, looking for you.
If he finds out that I'm here, he's going
to want to kill me too. Let's talk. Relax.
Because of you,
I'll never be able to go back to Medellín.
- Maritza!
- Because of you,
- my daughter and I have to live in hiding.
- Relax!
I really am sorry,
and I'm here because I want to help you.
Like you helped the girls
you used to drive around in your taxi?
- I had nothing to do with that.
- And why would I believe you?
Because you know me,
and I wouldn't do something like that.
You killed me, Jhon.
You killed me by putting me
in your fucking taxi.
You knew how badly I needed that money
and you took advantage of that.
I really am sorry, Maritza.
Believe me. I think I have an idea
to get us both out of this.
What is it?
We'll give them what they want.
We'll give them Escobar.
- What the fuck are you saying?
- Believe me, Maritza.
I'm the one who drives Escobar.
I know when his sicarios aren't with him.
- You can call the police.
- Maritza, what's going on here?
Mom, go back inside. Go inside.
Doña Liliana.
- I don't trust the police.
- Listen to me.
This is your chance
to get a visa from the Americans,
so you can leave with your daughter.
And you? What do you get out of this?
Working for Escobar isn't what it seems.
They're killing all of his men.
I'm afraid.
I need to get out.
We both need to get out, Maritza.
All right. My turn.
You both look beautiful.
All right, my love, go to your room
so I can talk with your dad, all right?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What?
Velasco told me.
There are 20 men out there, Tata.
Yes, Pablo... 20 strangers.
Let's see.
How do you hold it?
What? Are you sure you want to laugh
at your wife while she's holding a gun?
It's not a joke, Pablo.
Those 20 men out there
don't care what happens to us.
When the time comes,
it will just be you and me.
And I will be a part of this, Pablo.
All right.
But I think you need
more practice with that.
- Javi, it's Gabriela.
- What's up?
- It's been a while and I want to see you.
- Now?
I can't right now. I'm working.
Don't be like that.
All right. Give me...
20 minutes, all right?
Hello.
- I've got half an hour.
- Wait.
- Javi...
- Come here. What's wrong?
Hello.
She's a friend of a friend.
Maritza, meet Javier.
And...
why are you introducing me
to a friend of a friend?
She's in trouble.
Just hear her out.
Goddammit, Gabby.
You could have told me over the phone, no?
- I knew you wouldn't come.
- Well, I'm leaving.
- Bye!
- No. Wait. It's important.
Please.
Hear her out.
What's your name? Maritza?
What kind of trouble are you in?
Who are you in trouble with?
- La Quica.
- La Quica. You know La Quica?
- He wants to kill me.
- Well...
La Quica wants to kill a lot of people.
Why does he want to kill you?
Because I can tell you
where Pablo Escobar is.
And how are you going to do that?
I know exactly when and where
he'll be tomorrow.
If this is true, Colonel, she can tell us
when Limón and Escobar go somewhere.
Let's go.
Can you explain this?
A subpoena.
You're going to answer the questions
I have regarding La Catedral.
You mean your witch hunt.
Tell me, how did Pablo Escobar
get out of that prison
while being surrounded by 400 soldiers?
How many times do I have to tell you
that I don't know how Escobar escaped?
He must have paid someone off.
I would say that's
almost certainly the case.
This is about transparency, truth, law.
And I sense from your reluctance to speak
that the truth will not be kind to you
or our esteemed president.
Look, sir, what happened that night
was complicated and, yes,
I must confess that we lost control
of the situation, we made mistakes,
but we're talking about a national crisis.
So what? Does that mean
that we should just trust you?
Look, sir... I ask you to please trust me.
All you're doing by making
this investigation public
is destroying the life of a very good
human being. Our president.
Well, let's hope it doesn't come to that.
Hello?
Hello, Maritza. It's me.
I spoke with Peña.
Pay attention.
In one hour, I will take Pablo
to his accountant.
He lives in the south. I need you to give
the Americans the address. Understand?
Are we really going to turn in
Pablo Escobar?
Yes, Maritza.
We're going to do this together.
But I need you to trust me.
Give me the address.
Write it down.
9th street with 98-3. Got it?
Got it.
...my love. Do it again.
I'm sorry, boss.
You'll be late to your appointment.
Thank you, Limón. A kiss.
Come on. Ice cream. Ice cream.
One, two, and...
Everything all right, boss?
9th Street. 98-3.
Okay. Got it.
All right.
Now turn off the satellite phones.
We'll be out in 20 minutes.
So be on alert.
Yes, Colonel.
Attention! We're headed out!
We're on San Juan.
Everything's calm.
Murphy, you're buying the drinks tonight.
Of course, blondie.
It's burning!
Reverse!
It's an ambush!
Sabada!
Carrillo, respond!
Carrillo! Trujillo! Do you copy?
Son of a bitch!
Look at me.
You asked a child to give me this.
You can have it back.
And this... is for my cousin, Gustavo.
Coward.
Son of a bitch.
Don't worry. It's going to heal well.
They're saying that Pablo himself
killed Carrillo.
Next, he'll come after the two of you.
Or me, or you, Pacho.
No, we've got to come up
with another plan.
Another approach.
Another way to achieve our goals.
Pacho, we need to call the Castaños.
Soon we'll know what's in it for them.
Carrillo hasn't been buried yet...
and they're already asking for my head.
They want a scapegoat.
And we have to give them one.
That's why we're going to say that you
were poorly advised by your vice minister.
- We can find another way.
- Let me finish.
We're going to say that I acted alone
and without authorization
when I entered La Catedral.
And that it was I who insisted
that Carrillo return.
I don't accept your resignation.
Now, more than ever, the country
needs you, Eduardo. I need you.
We have to do it, César.
You know it. The attorney general,
the press, the opposition, the citizens,
everyone's looking for someone to blame.
All of them.
And it's not going to be you.
It's been my honor serving you
and the people of Colombia.
Good luck.
Limón told me you have a daughter.
How old?
- Two.
- And what's her name?
- Salome.
- What a beautiful name.
This is the second time
that I've felt indebted to you.
Now, Maritza...
our daughters will be safe.
Thank you.
Know that... you have a friend in me.
What did you do?
I took care of it.
You're safe now.
What now?
What the fuck do you want?
I want to help you.
Oh, yeah?
Come with me and I'll show you.
Make yourself at home.
Agent Peña.
Welcome to Montecasino.