Citizens of Colombia,
we present your new president,
Pablo Escobar!
PABLO ESCOBAR PRESIDENT
Thank you.
How are you, Mr. President?
Much appreciated.
Thank you.
Please come in, Mr. President.
- All yours.
- Thank you.
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you
- What's this?
Happy birthday, dear Pablo
Happy birthday to you
Bravo, Pablito!
I love you, son.
Don't eat the whole cake.
Don't forget to blow out the candles,
Dad.
Happy birthday, Daddy!
Pablo, we miss you so much.
We wish we could be there with you.
I know, my love.
Soon this will all be behind us.
I promise.
Good morning, boss.
I made some eggs.
- There's leftover cake.
- Yes, sir.
Thanks.
I got everything we need, boss.
You went to a different store, correct?
Yes, sir.
I go to a different one every time.
So, the shopkeeper's mom, she's a healer.
I paid her a visit.
I told you not to talk to anybody.
Yeah, boss, but...
only thing is, since I was a kid,
I've believed in these things.
Look...
I asked her for something to protect you.
The sword of St. Michael the archangel...
- the Virgin--
- ...and the Holy Child of Atocha.
You know my mother and I built a church?
Yes, sir.
In Barrio Pablo Escobar.
That's where I grew up, boss.
Happy birthday, sir.
Thank you, Limón.
Pardon me.
From south Medellín.
Casablanca neighborhood, to be exact.
If he does, we'll be listening.
This stays between us, understood?
We will set up a temporary base
in Casablanca.
We need to act as quickly as possible
as soon as Escobar appears, understood?
- Yes, Colonel.
- Good work.
Lieutenant Martinez?
How long since we heard anything
from Escobar? A month? A month and a half?
A month and a half, sir.
And that whole time you've been
in the van listening to static?
Yes. Waiting.
Stubbornness seems to run in my family.
It's in our blood.
Excuse me.
Six.
Can you imagine what would happen
if cocaine were legal?
It's your turn.
I think if coke was legal, boss,
you would be the boss of the world
and the cops couldn't touch you.
Yes, sir.
We're sure that the call came from
the Casablanca neighborhood in Medellín.
This is the best intel
we've received in months.
Don't underestimate him.
We've made that mistake in the past.
Gentlemen, I want to be loud and clear.
If your men are able to find Escobar...
I don't care about the consequences.
I want him dead.
Do you have a problem with that?
With all due respect, Mr. President,
if he resists, that's how it will go.
Otherwise, we're going to capture him.
Keep me informed.
Gentlemen.
Mrs. Escobar?
The attorney general called this morning.
He's decided to end
your protective custody.
So we have to leave by the weekend.
No. No, you can't do this to us.
They were waiting for your husband
to turn himself in, and he never did.
Ma'am?
May I give you some advice?
I think it's time for you to think
about you and your children's safety.
Forget about him.
The kids miss you.
Should I wake up Juan Pablo?
Probably not a good idea right now,
my love.
So... do you feel a year older or what?
More like four or five.
We've missed you very much, Pablo.
The days feel longer.
For me too.
I still don't understand
why you're in Medellín.
That place is too dangerous, my love.
That's exactly why.
No one would think I'd be here.
Pablo...
I think the time has come.
We don't have a choice.
Turning yourself in
isn't the end of the world, my love.
You can survive prison.
We both know that won't happen.
Stop!
- Listen to me, Pablo...
- They're talking.
- You will always be Pablo Escobar.
- Boss.
You will always be that man
that's admired and followed.
My man.
My love, there's a lot of journalists
who want to speak with you.
The people love you and follow you.
Tata, Limón wants me off.
It's Escobar. Let's go west!
Fix the position, Morales.
My love, look at Nelson Mandela.
They put the man in jail,
but the people still believed in him.
They gave him the Nobel Prize.
They say he may even become president.
President, Pablo.
Of the same country that imprisoned him.
I need to hang up.
We'll talk about this later.
Alvaro, stop. Stop for a second.
All right, Pablo.
But think about what I'm saying.
It's very important.
It's our only way out really.
Alvaro, let's go slowly.
Colonel! This is Lieutenant Martinez.
Think about turning yourself in, my love.
Think of your family.
I'll think about it.
All right?
I love you very much.
Where are you going?
To Medellín.
What? No, Hermilda. You can't leave.
My son needs me.
How so?
What you want...
for him to turn himself in
to those monsters...
I don't want them to kill him.
They're going to kill him either way,
and you know that.
They won't if he turns himself in.
- It's a trap! Tata, my God!
- Lower your voice.
No! No, ma'am.
I will not stay quiet
when I see you betraying my son.
I have never betrayed Pablo.
Let's make that very clear.
We're locked in this hotel
as if it were a jail.
We can't even leave the country.
And the only shot I have at
getting my children out of this alive...
is for Pablo to turn himself in.
My son...
needs his mother.
Hermilda.
Please be very careful. Please.
Tell the children...
I'll tell them.
We have intel that Escobar
is in this building.
Listen up. I want you to do
what you can to get him alive.
Escobar must be brought to justice
before the people of Colombia
and answer for the atrocious crimes
he has committed against this nation.
Now, if he resists...
if a single one of our men
is in harm's way...
I want you to take his life. Understood?
- Yes, Colonel!
- Let's go.
Everything all right, boss?
Tata wants me to surrender.
She said I can be like Nelson Mandela.
Nelson Mandela?
Who's that, boss?
Did you buy more rolling papers?
Sorry, no, boss.
I can't think with that
fucking smell of Chinese food in here.
He's not here.
Boss, come inside.
You can't risk being seen, sir.
This is my city, Limón.
These are my people.
Medellín will never betray me.
Colonel.
- We fucked up again, sir.
- He's not here.
Looks like your little machine is broken,
right, Lieutenant?
Go and fiddle with the little knob. Go on.
Excuse me, Colonel.
Listen up! Take down the staging area
and head back to Holguín.
The son of a bitch wasn't talking
from this building, but he was close.
- A ghost.
- What's that?
That's what you call a signal that's been
reflected and appears somewhere else.
That's what happened with Escobar's
signal. It bounced off the water.
I'm going to get the rolling papers
and clear my head.
Give me the keys!
- If you want, I'll go.
- Where are the sunglasses?
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, how are you?
Can I have a strawberry with cream,
please?
- My pleasure.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. How much do I owe you?
- Just two thousand pesos.
- There you go. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hello. Give me a juice, please.
- Hello, how are you? My pleasure.
Sir.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
- Kick it here!
- There you go.
You'd have to be really stupid
or have a lot of balls
to sit here as if nothing's happening.
They're offering seven million dollars
for you head,
and you're sitting here
like a fucking tourist.
You look just like Che Guevara.
What's beautiful is always beautiful.
You look like you ate Che Guevara.
What? You don't miss me or what?
Yesterday, I turned 44 years old.
Son of a bitch, you're old, Pablo.
Thank you, Gustavo.
Did you know that Julius Caesar
invaded Britain when he was 44?
He lost power many times,
but always got it back.
Never letting anything stop him.
Yeah, but that motherfucker
had a fucking army.
You remember when we used to talk about
going to the jungle if shit got too heavy?
Yeah, and joining the guerrillas.
Tata wants me to surrender.
Tata's a smart woman, Pablo.
She loves you very much.
Maybe it's a good idea.
You surrender, go to jail
and take the time to rest, think,
to restructure the business,
and escape whenever you want.
The legend grows.
- She said the same thing.
- Yeah.
We both know that things aren't
going to be as easy as before, cousin.
Let's cut the bullshit.
We are bandits, Pablo.
Right?
What do you think?
I think...
that everything started to fall apart
the day you left.
So you do miss me, you son of a bitch.
Every fucking day of my life, brother.
Boss? Don't do that again, sir.
- I was worried. It's dangerous.
- Look...
It worked perfectly.
You're a good man, Limón.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
- Are we going to eat the pasta or what?
- Yes, sir.
- Put salt on it, pussy.
- Yes, boss. Whatever you say.
I'm hungry.
Tata?
Pablo?
There's the love of my life.
- You sound different.
- I'm good, my love.
I feel good.
And ready to talk to those reporters.
Good, my love.
Does that mean you're turning yourself in?
No, Tata.
I'll never surrender.
We won't be under protection, Pablo.
You have to.
I'll never surrender, my love.
I know, Pablo.
But what's your plan?
All right.
I know what we're going to do.
We will talk to all of those
foreign journalists.
That's what we are going to do.
- ...foreign journalists...
- Alvaro, slow down!
...so the world will know
what these bastards are doing...
- It must be around here, Morales.
- You sure?
We will make the international press
put pressure on the Colombian government.
And listen, we will succeed, Tata.
We will succeed.
We will fight and we will succeed.
You have to believe me.
- We will succeed.
- Stop!
As soon as we do that, I'll go
to the jungle, join the guerrillas...
Son of a bitch, it's Escobar.
We have to get you and the kids
out of the country.
And listen...
I will not rest until that happens.
Alvaro, drive slowly. Park up ahead.
I only have one notebook.
Let me go get it.
The helicopters are triangulating
that area, correct?
Yes, Colonel, just in this area.
- Very well.
- Excuse me, Colonel.
Lieutenant Martinez is on channel four.
All right, excuse me. Thank you.
Go ahead, Lieutenant.
Colonel, I found him.
Who? Escobar?
Yes, Colonel.
He's in Los Olivos.
Son, are you sure?
We can't afford the luxury
of making another mistake.
I'm sure. I saw him.
What do you mean you saw him?
Yes, he looked out a window.
He's got a beard now, but it's him.
And did he see you?
No, I don't think so.
Listen up, Lieutenant.
There's still some men
in the staging area.
I need you to wait until they get to you.
Understood?
Copy that, Colonel.
One more thing. Be safe. Over and out.
- Fix the position.
- Right away.
Hello, Dad.
How's it going, son?
You wanted to ask me something or what?
Yes, sir.
What wish did you make for your birthday?
If I tell you, it won't come true. Right?
Tell me! Don't be like that!
Well, the only thing that I can tell you
is that it was a very good wish.
You know,
you deserve the best birthday
in the world.
Thank you, my love.
- Captain, can you hear me?
- Yes, Colonel?
How many men are left
in the provisional base?
- Counting me, about 12.
- Listen up.
- Lieutenant Martinez found Escobar.
- Shit! Let's go!
Everybody to Los Olivos!
Hello.
Hello, my little princess.
How's my little girl?
Good.
I've got your little rabbit here.
He's getting very fat.
Perez!
Attention! Two groups. Captain, Sergeant
in the back, and I'll take the front.
Get your mom on the phone, okay?
Pablo.
- Do you have the questions?
- Yes, my love, I've got them here.
The first one
is from a Spanish journalist.
"How do you feel after
all of these days on the run?"
Write this down.
"It's been very hard
being far from my family,
who I love more than anything
in the world."
- Sergeant, go around.
- "But I feel good.
I feel strong.
And I have the will to fight
all of these injustices.
The government has made a mockery
of our rights.
It's allowed our justice system
to become corrupted by murderers.
The people of Colombia deserve
much better than that.
The government
is holding my family hostage.
That's a crime against human rights
committed by a government
that calls itself democratic.
My little kids are innocent children
that have nothing to do
with their father's problems.
All we want from the government
is that they bring those killers,
Los Pepes, to justice.
But above else, that they allow my family
to leave the country immediately.
Without that--"
One moment.
What happened, Pablo?
Something strange is happening here.
I'll call you back.
Pablo.
Pablo. Pablo, don't hang up.
Pablo, what's going on?
What's wrong, Mom?
Go on. All right.
Go!
Let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Come on!
Come on! Move!
Move!
Go!
Keep going!
Nobody shoot!
Sergeant Sarmiento!
You just shot Pablo Escobar!
Is he alive?
Long live Colombia.
- Long live Colombia!
- Long live!
We killed Pablo Escobar!
- Long live! Long live!
- Long live Colombia!
Go ahead.
They killed Pablo Escobar!
My son!
I pray to God that other mothers
don't have to experience
the pain that I'm feeling.
And I know my son wasn't as bad
as they made him out to be.
I know that they blamed him
for anything bad that happened.
I want the good things he did
to be remembered,
because he didn't do the bad things
they say he did.
He built playing fields.
He built a neighborhood for the poor.
No one has paid attention to that.
As a son,
there will never be anyone better.
He was the noblest of men.
Not just as a son...
Sit down, ma'am. Sit.
Thank you.
Talk to me.
Before he died,
my husband told me to find you.
He told you that?
He told me that despite the fact
that you became enemies,
you were once associates and friends.
You were saying?
He told me that you were a decent man.
That you would understand the situation.
That you would forgive us.
And that you might help us
get out of the country.
How much do you have left, Mrs. Escobar?
In property? In cash?
I can find out.
That's good.
Because I want all of it.
All right, gentlemen.
Gentlemen!
In the history of every business,
there are decisive moments.
The first sale.
The first million. The first billion.
And when your rival no longer exists.
The important thing in these moments
isn't how one reacts,
but how well one has prepared for them.
Gentlemen, I have to tell you
that we are ready.
And we won't be needing kidnappings
and bombs to succeed.
We will do it covertly.
And when they turn around
to see what happened,
we'll no longer be there.
No, sir!
- Cheers!