[Man in Spanish] This is one of the
largest and most mysterious plane crashes
in Colombian history.
It may have been a bomb
that blew up a plane in Colombia today.
The boeing 727 of avianca airlines...
[Newswoman in French]
[Steve]
In his unsuccessful attempt
to assassinate presidential candidate
césar gaviria,
Pablo Escobar murdered
107 innocent people.
The "paisa Robin hood"...
Had become a terrorist.
[Reporter in Spanish]
[Man in English]
But American intelligence authorities
say the drug bosses in Colombia
have to be considered prime suspects.
[Baby crying]
[Carrillo in Spanish]
You know where Jaime is?
No, sir.
I don't know where he is.
He left home and hasn't returned.
- Have Pablo and his men come by here?
- [Girl] No.
- [Javier] Your name is Natalie?
- [Natalie] Yes, sir.
Natalie, your boyfriend, Jaime,
was he with Pablo's sicarios?
- No.
- Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
Well, then, why do you have
this picture of Pablo in your house?
Nothing wrong with that.
Everyone in the comuna has one.
You think those thugs
are going to protect you?
You don't understand...
That you represent a big problem for them.
We can help you.
We can protect you.
But you have to tell us the truth.
[Javier flicks lighter]
[In English] She's lying.
He's got this poor sucker to carry a bomb
without him even knowing it.
- Well, maybe he knew.
- — I don't care if he knew or not.
It's time we put a bullet in Escobar.
[Pablo in Spanish] I don't want
to leave, my love. I don't want to leave.
But I must, for all our safety.
Did you do something wrong?
Your dad did nothing wrong.
These are people who are jealous of us,
who are trying to take what we have.
[Whispers]
You have to be strong.
I want you to be strong.
You have to be strong
and never show weakness.
I promise I'll never be weak.
And watch out for your sister.
I love you very much.
I love you all very much.
- Mama.
- [Hermilda] Pablo?
- Do not spoil this boy.
- [Hermilda] But... what do you mean?
- Watch her.
- Just a few sweets and some pork rinds.
Be careful, son. Be careful.
- I love you.
- [Whispers] Me, too.
Take care.
[Softly] And what about you?
Come on.
I'm going to take you with me.
I'm going to take you with me...
[All chuckling]
[Sighs]
[Pablo whispers] Take care.
[Door opens]
You think he did it?
- [Door closes]
- Surely not.
Blow up that plane?
Of course he did it, hermilda.
But he had his reasons.
We've got everyone looking
for Jaime's wife throughout the comunas.
I want you to find her and kill her.
And kill any motherfucker that
can connect me with that fucking plane.
Yes, sir.
[Starts engine]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[Man in Spanish] ...The functions
of president of Colombia?
[Gaviria] I swear.
[Applause]
[Steve] The avianca bombing created
a tidal wave of support for césar gaviria.
He became the 28th president of Colombia
by a landslide.
[Indistinct chatter]
[In Spanish]
Well, Cesar, congratulations.
Not Cesar... I mean, Mr. President.
- [Chuckling]
- Salud.
- [Woman] Salud.
Excuse us.
- As a former president to a new one...
- Mm-hm?
What advice would you give?
Well... you'll be asked
to make many difficult decisions.
I would say one thing...
Do what your wife says.
- I always do.
- — [both chuckling]
Trust your instincts,
and be confident in your decisions.
But that's easier said than done.
You'll never be able to please everyone,
so find the solution
that rings true in your heart.
Thank you.
Another thing I did want to tell you,
about the Americans...
What about the Americans?
This will have to be off the record,
my dear.
I can't have my opinions
broadcast on your television show.
No, no, no. You have my word.
- The Americans...
- Yes?
Be careful.
[In English] We killed José Rodriguez
gacha with a minimal loss of life.
Bringing Escobar to justice
is my number one priority.
But we will do so
on our own terms and own resources.
[Noonan]
We wanna help you catch Escobar.
I have enormous gratitude to you,
especially with agent Murphy,
whose warnings kept me off that plane.
You, sir, yes. Unfortunately,
not the rest of the passengers.
The people in Colombia are horrified
about the bombing of avianca's plane.
But they're also against
American soldiers on our soil
and spy planes intercepting calls, 30...
America doesn't intercept
civilian phone calls. That's absurd.
Presidente, you need
additional resources to get this man.
Your government's research says...
660 tons of cocaine were consumed
in the United States last year.
Perhaps if your resources
were focused at home,
we'd all be better off.
[Clears throat]
[Steve] Gaviria made good
on his promise to go after Escobar.
[Men shouting]
Colonel carrillo's search bloc
was set loose with a vengeance.
Carrillo mounted dozens of raids.
[Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
But with an army of informants,
Escobar somehow always got away.
We sat on the sidelines,
hands tied by bureaucracy.
In response, Pablo took
his narco-terrorism to a whole new level
with a bombing campaign that would
shake the country to its foundations.
In doing his best to avoid war,
that's exactly what gaviria got.
And the toll on both sides
was devastating.
The thing about war is...
It's just bad for business.
And when you got a bull's-eye
on your back... your rivals get bold.
[Up—tempo Latin music playing]
- Pablo.
- [In Spanish] What's up, pacho?
[Steve] That's right.
Pablo and the medellin cartel
weren't the only game in town.
Thank you.
This is helmer "pacho" herrera, one
of the four leaders of the call cartel.
[Up—tempo Latin music plays]
While Pablo left a trail of bodies
and chaos in his wake,
Cali made problems disappear with an army
of lawyers and a mountain of legal briefs.
The medellin cartel was Miami:
Swimming pools, bikini girls...
Tacky as a two-tone Cadillac.
- ['80s dance music plays]
- The Cali cartel was New York:
Elegant, smooth, subtle.
Where they could fuel
the 24-hour nightlife with cocaine,
and still make sure everybody showed up
for work on wall street the next morning.
At first, medellin and Cali
worked side by side.
But in Colombia, when money's involved,
blood inevitably flows.
There had been violence
between medellin and Cali before.
But right now, a war on two fronts
was not something Pablo could afford.
[In Spanish] We have Miami...
And have left you alone in New York.
- Yes, for a price.
- Certainly.
Look, pacho, we agreed that we would
share the Los Angeles territory...
And that hasn't been happening.
It seems you are not
holding up our agreement.
- How's that?
- Exactly what I'm saying, pacho.
Look, Pablo...
You know that our partners
sometimes operate independently.
If Mr. Galeano
and Mr. Moncada are correct,
then you have my assurance
that it will be rectified.
Thanks a lot, pacho.
Disputes between us
cause needless bloodshed.
Then fix it. A war between our groups
is the last thing we need right now.
It would seem you already have a war.
Maybe bombing that plane
was a step too far.
Careful, pacho.
Careful.
The only difference between us
is our little misunderstanding
with the government.
And that will be resolved soon.
Besides, that's the business,
for all of us.
- Yes, it's true for all of us.
- Mm-hm.
The only war we are really fighting
is the war against extradition.
And the outcome of that
is something we're all interested in.
It's true, Gustavo.
Gustavo is right.
We have a common goal,
and that is to get rid of extradition.
The United States is big enough
for all of us to operate in.
Let's figure out Los Angeles
once you take care of your business here.
You know what bothers me?
Your arrogance.
Your attitude, your air of superiority.
Careful, pacho... that you don't
get yourself killed for that.
Thank you for coming.
- I'm gonna kill that homo bastard.
- [Moncada] Pablo, let me kill him.
Stop talking shit, moncada.
We'll kill that fag later.
Right now, we can't be out in the open.
If that son of a bitch
starts selling shit in Los Angeles,
I'm personally gonna put a gun up his ass
and pull the trigger. I swear.
That will make him fall in love with you.
[Laughing]
[Javier in English]
We got Escobar's most trusted soldiers:
Poison, la quica, sure shot, blackie.
Cocky, careless motherfuckers.
Now we're hearing about two new guys:
Fernando galeano and Kiko moncada,
basically picking up
where Carlos lehder left off.
[Steve]
Kill the body, the head will die.
Without Colombian permission
to put assets in the air, we can't help.
In terms of intercepts, yeah,
but what do you guys got on ground intel?
- You mean spies?
- [Steve] Yes.
[Sighs, chuckles]
We don't have any narco assets.
Our human intelligence
is limited to communists.
Besides, gaviria doesn't want you
chasing Escobar with CIA spies.
But you got satellites
in the sky, right?
Yes, but to use them in pursuit of narcos
would be a direct violation
- of the order of our host country.
- Man, you're CIA.
You break rules all the time.
These are aerial photographs of comunas
controlled by Escobar and his associates.
- We'll use them to track his men.
- These are aerials.
- We can't track individuals with these.
- Take a look.
The los priscos gang controls El poblado.
Here in Santa Cruz, we got the comuna
where they recruited the avianca bomber.
And both places more densely packed
than a Marrakesh bazaar.
So let's take a tip from the Colombians.
You notice anything special about these?
Search bloc follows vehicle traffic
in the comunas. You've got...
Japanese imports... four-by-fours.
Cars over 40 grand.
Narcos are the only ones
who can afford these cars.
Whenever aerials see these cars,
we know sicarios are inside.
- That's right.
- — we start tracking these rice rockets,
we might be able to get to Escobar.
[Up-tempo Latin music plays on radio]
[Sure shot in Spanish]
I think it's up this way.
I don't want to shoot her.
Kill that cute girl?
And the baby, too?
I don't know why the boss
wants us to kill that girl.
- What does she know about avianca anyway?
- Just shut up and follow orders!
[Marina] Does he think
putting a bomb on every corner
is gonna get the police
to quit chasing him?
Gustavo, we need to get away,
out of this country.
And go where?
We'll be treated like criminals
wherever we go.
They'll kill him, and you know it.
I just hope he doesn't
take you down with him.
[Scoffs] This isn't our war.
This isn't war. It's negotiation.
Don't you understand
what an opportunity this is?
He's willing to consider
terms of surrender...
- Under what conditions?
- [Overlapping dialogue]
My god, he just blew up a plane!
Eduardo, calm down.
Let the man speak.
[Exhales] We can end this violence
with dignity. It's good for both sides-...
Do you realize
how stupid you sound right now?
César, this is absurd.
- Eduardo, please...
- This is a farce.
Please.
Let me deal with this. Please.
Fine. Whatever you want.
[Softly]
We can at least begin a discussion, right?
Even though you never stated it,
surely you'd like
to see the bombings stop.
- Yes. Yes, I would.
- Exactly.
So if we begin a dialogue,
they will cease.
That affords us all some time,
including the search bloc.
Fernando...
You saw his money,
and it blinded you to his soul.
That son of a bitch has no soul.
If telling him we're negotiating
allows the bombs to stop
while we find him...
Then be my guest.
[Exhales]
Thank you. Really, thank you.
Look, man,
Pablo's turned into a Saint.
Of course.
- He sends people straight to heaven.
- [Laughs]
[Sighs]
She's not here.
She might have just left.
Let's search the comuna.
Look, poison, I'm telling you
Pablo is being paranoid.
Careful what you say, son.
One day,
he is going to ask me to kill you.
Would you do it?
If he asks me... of course.
There is no way around it.
Wouldn't you?
All right, all right,
let's just go find this girl.
We'll look around
and see where she's hiding.
- [Baby squeals]
- What's wrong?
Here you go.
It's ok, Natalie. Don't worry.
Before you know it, we'll get you
some food. Right? Isn't that right?
Thank you.
[Thunder rumbling]
What then, Fernando?
Has the Colombian government
offered a truce?
The government
hasn't been willing to offer anything
I would consider acceptable.
What did they offer?
They want you to admit...
[Clears throat]
That you're responsible for avianca.
And of course, I told them that...
That we can't even—-
is it that you're not negotiating a thing?
No, no, of course I'm negotiating...
Then why is carrillo
stopping every car in the comunas
and killing my boys
with the help of the gringos?!
Why are the Americans helping them if we
are supposed to be negotiating, Fernando?
Gaviria doesn't want the gringos to know
he's willing to negotiate with you.
Be very careful, Fernando.
Yes, Pablo.
You've got to stop the bombing, Pablo.
I don't know what you're thinking anymore.
I think we should...
Reorganize a bit...
And start sending our boys out to burn
some houses down and do some damage
to politicians and senators
all over the country.
And to the soldiers and cops in our way,
the judges who annoy us
and the reporters that watch us,
basically, we have to create a presence so
disruptive they'll want nothing but peace.
That's the only way
we're going to get there.
Is that it? Is that what you want?
A civil war?
- You've gone crazy, asshole.
- We have to fight, brother.
Let's put our hearts into this.
And if we all must die, so be it.
Well, yes...
The thing is,
I don't want to die yet, Pablo.
[Sighs]
Nor do I.
But the bombs make the public want peace.
And that will influence the politicians.
You're the one who says the politicians
don't give a shit about the public.
If you want to influence politicians,
you'll have to narrow your focus.
You know what I mean?
[Steve] Gustavo was right.
They needed a new strategy,
one that brought terror directly
to the people that mattered the most.
[Pablo] What about her?
No, she is way too much of a Princess.
Surely we would have problems with her.
My god, look at that face.
The media is going to love that fox,
right?
Sure they will,
but so will our boys.
Just think what
they're gonna do to her.
I say let's start with her...
- [Gunshot]
- [Woman shrieks]
And this fag.
- [Tires screech]
- [Shouts in Spanish]
Let's go!
And this cute couple.
- [Tires squealing]
- [Shouting in Spanish]
[Steve] When you kill someone, you lose
all your leverage the moment they're dead.
Now, you take someone's children
away from them,
you'd be amazed
what they'd do to get them back.
[In Spanish] Family members of
the most influential people in the country
have been kidnapped
on the very streets they call home.
What does Pablo Escobar want?
I'll see you tomorrow on the same channel
for a special report.
- [Up-tempo news soundtrack plays]
- [Bell rings]
Is everything all right?
All the victims are my friends.
[Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
Excuse me.
[Valeria]
The kidnapping of Francisco Santos,
the editor in chief of the most important
newspaper in the nation,
is the latest and most shocking
in a string of kidnappings
orchestrated by the medellin cartel.
Reporting to you, I'm Valeria velez.
- All right.
- First on the scene, right? As always.
[Chuckles] Maybe if you actually
had to work for a living,
you'd be hungry enough to get here first.
I found out from Santos' wife...
A half hour after
he didn't show up for dinner.
You?
Who tipped you off?
It's a pleasure to see you,
as always.
[Engine starting]
[Clock chiming]
[Duque] These are Pablo's conditions
for the release of the hostages.
You've read them,
you can see they're very reasonable.
"Very reasonable," he says.
You are definitely an imbecile, Fernando.
And I'm going to tell you something.
You will get what you deserve very soon,
I assure you.
I'm also one of those hostages.
I myself could be walking around calmly...
But like them, I am not free.
Escobar is asking us to surrender,
but that will never happen.
[Duque sighs]
If he releases the hostages
and turns himself in,
we will take this into account.
Gaviria isn't going to bend.
Then I'm going to break him.
[Hushed whispers]
You, get up from there.
[Hostages gasping]
The body of ofelia Hernandez was found
dumped next to the presidential palace.
One must admire president gaviria.
I'm sure it can't be easy for him
to stand by his decision
to not negotiate with Escobar.
- [Continues indistinctly]
- What's the plan?
A few more hostages and they will give in.
Their time is running out.
I'm talking about us.
What about us, Valeria?
I don't have time
for that pussy shit right now.
[Valeria] Colombia's sweetheart.
You know the only reason
this hag has any fame
is because her father was president.
I despise her.
And why do you care so much?
[Voice straining]
Your ratings are through the roof, right?
Hers are higher.
- [Gunshots]
- [Groans]
[Man] Open the door, quick!
Move!
- [Man] Let's go!
- [Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
Hurry up!
[Exhales]
Where am I?
Hello!
Tell me where I am.
Does my family know I'm alive?
[Man] How would I know?
Who are you?
You work for Escobar?
You can call me gorilla.
Gorilla.
Very well... gorilla.
Where's my crew?
Did you bring them here as well?
I'm here to guard you. That's it.
[Overlapping chatter in Spanish]
Ladies and gentlemen, excuse me.
We understand the frustration and pain
you must be feeling for your children,
but believe me,
we are doing everything we can
to make sure your children get home soon.
Our daughter was kidnapped
on her way to an interview.
They killed the bodyguard.
No one is safe.
As a former president, I understand
the terrible position you're in.
But we're here to find a solution.
I understand your frustration,
Dr. Turbay.
But if we give in now, any criminal
can hold our government hostage.
This isn't "any criminal."
This is the worst criminal in the world.
- And he is laughing at all of us.
- [Dr. Turbay] Mr. President,
you're proceeding as you must, but we must
act as the parents of our children.
Let's pray you find a solution.
[Steve] A good president
can stand up to external pressure.
It's the internal pressure
that can wear you down.
We knew the clock was ticking before
gaviria had to cave in to Escobar...
But hopefully not before
our unauthorized operation struck gold.
Catching a top sicario could be the break
we needed in leading us to Pablo.
Here.
We 'd continue to join
in an "observational capacity."
[In Spanish] Hands up!
[In English] Up!
[In Spanish] Why are you driving this car?
I don't know. Someone paid me 50,000 pesos
to drive it around the city.
[Steve] The sicarios had figured out
we were tracking their rides.
So they traded down to junkers
to avoid our eye in the sky.
But we weren't the only ones
that had Pablo in the gun sights.
[Pacho in Spanish]
Pablo came to see me.
[Jorge] Why?
[Pacho] He wants to settle
the dispute we have in the us.
The Los Angeles problems.
[Fabio] He has bigger issues
than that right now.
[Pacho]
He'll make a deal with the government.
He's managed to secure
some very effective bargaining chips.
Of course,
he'll look after you guys, right?
We haven't talked to Pablo in weeks.
He's in hiding.
Look at that.
What a beautiful animal, Jorge.
You like it?
Yes, of course.
I'm sure he'll look after you.
After all, you're partners.
Yes, of course. Partners.
[Softly] You could always have your sister
put in a good word with Gustavo.
What do you mean?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I thought you knew.
It could be gossip.
You know how people like to talk.
You should eat,
because you're going to be here a while.
You're going to get very hungry.
I don't feel well.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I can get you some medicine.
It's not that kind of illness.
I want to congratulate you.
I know you're a very good reporter.
Thank you.
Gorilla, how long have you been
working for Escobar?
Oh, it's been a while.
So you know what's going on out there,
don't you?
The truth is, I don't go out,
so I have no idea what's happening.
What the fuck are you doing, gorilla?
Why isn't she wearing the blindfold?
I didn't know you were coming.
Put it on, man!
We have to take her.
- Says who?
- Didn't I tell you to stay quiet?
Just put it on.
Pleasure to finally meet you,
Ms. Turbay.
Sit down, please.
[Chair sliding]
I suppose you want me to interview you?
No, even better.
I'm going to interview you.
So you can tell the world about
the humane treatment you've received here.
Don't you want your parents
to know you're well?
That you're alive?
I don't want to become
a piece of propaganda for you.
Who do you think you are?
So what's necessary, miss,
to have your cooperation?
Let one of the hostages go.
You and I know that
I'm the one you really want.
[Pablo] You see?
Two reasonable people
coming to an agreement.
Maybe we can convince president gaviria
to do the same. Right?
Mr. Escobar has shown
a willingness to negotiate.
This afternoon,
he let one of the hostages go.
President gaviria...
I ask you to at least
consider discussions with Mr. Escobar.
I don't understand.
I thought you said he wouldn't bend,
but now he's let one go.
Because he has your daughter.
And she's worth more to him
than the rest of them combined.
If you knew all I know, you'd understand
it's nothing more than a stunt.
Give him what he wants.
What he wants is an insult to us
and to this country.
I don't care. I want my child!
[Dr. Turbay] What I believe
my wife is trying to say is,
we'd like you to make a deal with Escobar.
If you refuse,
we'll have to take certain measures.
Financially, by robbing you of donors...
And politically,
by robbing you of whatever support
your legislative agenda needs.
Are you threatening me?
We all use the tools at our disposal.
You as a politician, me as a father.
I'm sorry.
Doctor...
You told me to follow my instincts...
And they tell me
not to give in to this criminal.
That was before they took my daughter.
[Sighs]
I came over as quickly as I could.
I was told you needed me urgently.
What's up?
Tell Fernando...
I'm willing to open negotiations.
We'll make a counter to Escobar's demands.
I thought you weren't going to negotiate.
[Gaviria sighs]
I have to stop this madness, Eduardo.
But god willing,
we can catch him first.
Tell the Americans
they can put their planes in the air.
[Steve] And there it was.
Negotiate with a terrorist while
trying to catch him at the same time.
[In English] Hammer, we have calls
originating in comuna 3,
manrique, from known
sicario satellite phones.
[Javier] Do you have a location?
[Sure shot in Spanish] What?
Yes, we're here in campo valdés.
Campo valdés.
That's in the central eastern area,
bordered by the comuna popular.
Roger that.
Campo valdés.
[Steve] Going into the comunas
without Colombian backup,
that's about the most dangerous
thing you can do.
[In Spanish] We're gonna
score a quick goal and then come back out.
All right, all right. All right.
That's how bad
we wanted to catch these guys.
- [Baby crying]
- [Natalie sobs] Don't kill me, please!
I swear I didn't hear anything!
I'm not going to say anything!
Please, don't kill me.
- I'm not...
- Hey! Hey!
- Please, don't kill me!
- What?
[Sobbing]
I'm begging you, please...
- [Gunshot]
- [Baby shrieks]
You could have at least waited till
I got her off me. Look at me now! Huh?
You got blood all over my new shoes.
I don't give a shit about your shoes.
Stop bitching.
I'm not.
What about her?
Put a bullet in her.
What? The baby's not a witness, man.
I don't give a shit.
- Pablo told us to kill everyone.
- — yeah, but it's a baby.
She won't say shit in court.
If she grows up and talks?
Really? Do you remember
what your mom told you when you were two?
Why is it so fucking difficult
for you to follow Pablo's orders? Huh?
[Cooing]
[Baby crying]
[People screaming]
[Grunts]
[Chickens clucking]
[Bullet ricochets]
[Yelling]
- [Shouts in Spanish]
- [Gunshot]
[Chatter in Spanish]
[Grunts]
[In Spanish, panting]
Drop the gun.
[Shouts] Now!
[Gun clatters]
You're under arrest,
you son of a bitch.
Let him go!
- Put the gun down.
- You put yours down.
I don't want to have to kill you.
[Clicks]
[Panting]
- [In English] Fuck.
- [Motorcycle idling]
[Engine revving]
[Baby cooing]
[Baby babbling]
Hey.
- Hey...
- [Steve sniffling]
[Gustavo sighs]
[In Spanish]
80 those fags want to sit and negotiate.
We have to spend some time in jail, right?
So what the fuck.
You won, Pablo. They gave in.
But that faggot president has yet
to accept our most important demand
before we turn ourselves in.
Which demand is that?
It's been a while
since we've been up here, right?
We used to come up here
with our girlfriends and smoke a joint.
What does that have to do with anything?
[Latin guitar music plays]
[Pablo] I know every centimeter
of these mountains.
From here,
we can see anything coming.
And we have enough space
to build whatever we want.
We're going to design it...
We're going to build it...
And we will be protected
from all our enemies.
- You want to build a jail?
- Not a jail, cousin.
A castle.