Hey, ladies.
Are you looking for something?
We're just taking a ride.
Can't we pass?
No, sweetheart.
You have to go back.
Listen... do you want to hang out later
back in town?
- What?
- I said...
- Julio.
- Pacho, you motherfucker.
Motherfucking dog!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
- Let me go!
- Let's go.
Let go...!
You.
Mrs Salazar.
Do you know what makes me happy,
Pacho?
Makes me very happy?
That my sons didn't kill
your brother Alvaro.
Because he's going to live
the rest of his life
as half a man.
Half man, half...
Help!
...the great event of the surrender
of Helmer Herrera,
to Colombian justice.
And this incident marked the end
of the Cali cartel
who were responsible,
according to international sources,
for more than 80%
of the cocaine trafficking in the world.
Throughout my campaign
and presidency,
I committed to dismantling
all narcotrafficking networks,
and we're doing it.
Gilberto. How have you been?
Good, brother.
Grateful that we're all together.
The investment we made in our friends
can bear fruit.
And then all this will pass away like
some old joke you can't quite remember.
For this, gentlemen,
I propose a toast.
Of course you would.
Fucking Chepe.
Gilberto, I'd like to say a few words.
You all know
this wasn't what I wanted.
So it's very hard for me to admit
that I know this is for the best.
Thanks to you, we're on the verge of...
What do you call it?
"A great victory."
We believe in you.
To my brother, Gilberto.
Our leader.
Gentlemen of Cali... cheers!
Hello.
Go ahead, sir.
Director.
Don Miguel...
Please, go ahead.
- Hello.
- It's me.
- Where are we on Pallomari?
- We put Navegante on it, Dad.
I'll find him, don't worry about it.
And fucking Salcedo too, you'll see.
David, don't take your eyes off Henao.
That motherfucker might see this
as an opportunity. Keep a low profile.
Sure, don't worry.
- How's María?
- I really don't know.
How come you don't know?
Make sure she's taken care of.
It's very important
that you handle Pallomari.
That motherfucker
could ruin everything.
Call me when it's done.
- Guillermo?
- I need your help, Gonzalo.
You know I can't get involved.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
When has anything ever happened to you?
I'm asking you for legal advice,
and quickly.
I've decided that the best way
to get out of this situation
is to turn myself in
to the authorities.
Yes, normally that would be the case.
But the problem is, you already have
a warrant out for your arrest.
An arrest warrant?
The police won't protect you.
In fact, they'll probably kill you.
I'm the head accountant.
And every dollar in this organisation,
and every secret,
has been through this head.
It's all in here.
So tell whoever needs to know
that I'm willing to negotiate.
Guillermo, my advice to you
is to get your family and leave Cali.
My wife's very attached to her work.
- What? I don't understand.
- You know her, she's stubborn.
She built her business
from the ground up.
I can't leave without her.
Look, Guillermo... this is not
my legal advice, but as your friend.
Talk some sense into your wife.
Immediately.
Can you get me a gun?
We'll have to look out for ourselves
the rest of our lives, but if I help them,
maybe one day we can come
back to Colombia.
Are you insane? They almost killed us.
They almost killed us, and now you're
telling me you want to go back to Cali?
Do you really think
we can come back to Colombia?
The moment we come back to Colombia,
they'll kill our daughters.
Are you doing this to make up
for the last four years of your life?
I'm a good man.
I was a good man.
I'll leave with the girls tomorrow.
I'm not waiting for you.
Wait for me, OK? Thanks.
That way.
Keep looking for him.
No more fucking excuses.
OK.
Yeah?
Have you heard from your father?
Yes.
David, I've been wondering about
the arrangement I had for my son and...
Arrangement?
I thought it was true love.
Your father knows I care about him.
That's beautiful. Seriously.
But here's the thing...
You don't mean anything to me.
You're not my mother.
You're not my fucking problem.
- David...
- What?
What the fuck do I owe you?
Open your legs for someone else.
You're good at that.
OK?
Good afternoon, Mr Salcedo.
Mr Espinosa's still at lunch.
He should be back soon.
- We'll wait for him inside.
- OK, sir.
Another drink?
I need to go.
See you next week.
Excuse me.
How are the girls here?
The best of Cali.
Open it!
Get in.
Get in, motherfucker!
ACCESS RESTRICTED
PASSWORD REQUIRED
- Good afternoon.
- I'm looking for Fredy Moya.
- Yes.
- The one wearing purple.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
You work with Patricia Pallomari?
Javier Peña, DEA.
I'll call you back.
- Hello.
- It's me.
Baby, I can't talk right now.
Call me back later.
No. Wait, I can't call you back. Wait.
Yes.
Yes, I'd have to check my records
in the office.
I can't talk.
- Wait.
- Patricia, the DEA was just here.
The DEA. Asking questions.
- What did you tell them?
- To go fuck themselves.
They want Guillermo, not you.
I can't talk now. We'll discuss it later.
Patricia, they talked about a reward.
We need to take advantage.
I need to use the bathroom.
Work again?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Open the window this time.
This way.
I'd offer a drink,
but I don't pour liquor for Cali whores.
Have a seat.
Don Orlando,
I'm here to ask for your protection.
Why?
You don't feel safe?
I did what I had to
after my husband died.
Now I'm in your home...
ready to do what I have to again.
So what is it you're offering me?
In here.
- How was the drive?
- It was easy.
Nice place.
Let me start by thanking you
for the meeting.
We're both busy men.
I won't waste your time.
But I'm a business man, like you.
The information you seek
may be in my possession.
If we come to an arrangement,
my information becomes yours.
You feel me?
On the phone, you told me
you know where Pallomari is.
Correct?
Look, let me put it this way...
Patricia and I are in love.
We want to be together.
So Guillermo's a problem for me.
From what I've heard,
he's a problem for you, too.
Am I right?
You are correct.
So maybe we can help each other.
If we come to an arrangement,
my information becomes yours.
- Let me fix you a drink. OK?
- Sure.
By the way...
are you guys running Windows 95 yet?
Think we're going to wait for next year.
Where the fuck is Pallomari, you faggot?
Did you hear me?
Here's the milk.
Just a few minutes and then you go to bed.
- Get in your room.
- Who is it?
I don't know.
Get in your room. Quickly.
- It's OK.
- They're the gringos.
- Calm down.
- Do you know them?
- They came to my office.
- Put the gun down.
Close the door.
No, Guillermo.
We can't leave for at least a week.
- You heard them.
- The company. I can't just leave.
- We must go.
- I need at least a week.
Put the radio on the dash...
and your hands on the wheel.
How are you, Jorge Salcedo?
I know about Fredy Moya.
It's none of my business.
- You're right. It's not your problem.
- You realise what happens if they find you?
And your kids?
I have to say goodbye to him.
We're in love.
I can't leave like that.
Mrs Pallomari, if you stay, you die.
Understood?
I'll be honest with you.
The truth is...
I was very disappointed to hear
you were the fucking rat.
But I still like you.
It's all good.
I'm not going to kill you.
David Rodríguez...
he wants to do it himself personally,
you know?
That's fine by me.
That way,
our friendship will remain intact.
- Let's go.
- Come on, dammit!
- The jacket...
- OK, that's it. Let's go.
Tell them to come out.
Tell them to come out, Jorge Salcedo.
Let's finish this.
Put the gun down.
I don't want to kill you.
We both know that's a lie.
The children!
Don't look, don't look!
Don't look!
What the fuck is he doing here?
- What the hell?
- Open!
Be careful!
We're in.
What happened?
They killed Navegante.
And Pallomari?
The motherfucker's gone.
You sure?
We're going to the airport.
We're going to catch those...
We're leaving, now!
Motherfuckers!
You, come with me.
We're going to the airport.
Take the guys. Now, now, now!
That's the North Valley, fuckers.
Who do they think they're messing with?
You just got smoked, bitches.
Boss!
Let's go. Out.
Patricia, get out this way.
Careful, my love.
Do you see that?
We have a private plane.
We have a plane just for us.
Get on the plane. Go.
Everything is going to be fine.
Come on. Let's go.
Goodbye, Salcedo.
And we have total agreement
in that these testimonies
that we have heard from Mr Pallomari
are ridiculous and grotesquely false.
Thank you very much.
You know what it means
if you go on the record, right?
There'll be a price to pay.
Press the button.
Let's start with your name and occupation.
Javier Peña,
DEA attaché in Colombia.
An exclusive interview
with this news channel.
He accuses the country
of being a Narco-Democracy.
He said the country has fallen
into the abyss.
His words have not been well received
by the Colombian people.
The public is demanding
an official response from...
Recordings that link the president
with narcotrafficking have been leaked.
The reality is that
they need five million.
- Uh-huh.
- We're missing three, see?
- We have it.
- Yes?
Yes, that's done.
This scandal threatens elected president
Ernesto Samper's career
if the authorities confirm his campaign
was funded by narcotrafficking money.
President Samper,
the only solution is your resignation!
Colombians can be certain...
that if they prove any money transfer
of any kind,
the deposit would've been made
behind my back.
Don Chepe.
I was happy to get your call.
All right, fellas.
Let's move. Keep going.
Keep going.
Stubborn.
So...
do you have to fix the fence
every time a storm hits?
Someone has to do it.
That's how life works.