Come. It's gonna be fine.
Nothing is going to happen to you.
Please...
No.
Take that with you.
- Careful.
- Yes, sir.
Were you shot?
No.
Get him out.
- You're scaring him.
- Out!
What happened last night...
someone pays.
We took care of Calderón,
but those fucking gringos
still knock on my door!
Where the fuck were the guards?
Where the fuck were our men?
How the fuck did they know where
you were, Dad? How the fuck...?
We have a rat.
An informant.
They found my ledger.
Hey, what about Enrique?
He was manning the checkpoint
when the cops came in.
Let's get inside.
Going once, going twice...
Girls, please.
No. You can't go out that way.
Please, no, sweetie.
Honey, let's go inside. Inside.
- Hello?
- Salcedo.
No one's seen you since the raid.
Where the fuck are you?
David.
I'm having some trouble
with my wife lately...
but I'm monitoring my radio.
- Have you talked to Enrique?
- Why?
We've been trying to reach him.
My father wants to talk to him.
Your dad wants to talk to Enrique?
Do you have any problem with that?
I'll find him.
Good. Bring him in.
And Salcedo, you come, too.
I stand by the operation,
Minister, as does General Serrano.
Who was in Bogotá at
the time of the raid,
while you and your men
were there for five hours,
drilling holes, breaking furniture.
We were one minute away from
getting Miguel Rodríguez.
But you did not.
I need you to hand over all intel,
including informants,
over to a special prosecutor.
And I'm afraid the DEA can no
longer be part of this operation.
- You're taking us off?
- Yes, I am.
Minister, we recovered
something from the house.
It's a ledger.
Cartel accounts, transactions,
going back years.
- What is this? I don't see names.
- It's coded.
It's bribes, money
laundering... cocaine sales.
- Cali's whole operation.
- That's right.
And do you have someone who can read it?
There are two possibilities.
There's the cartel accountant,
Guillermo Pallomari.
Yeah, but he's underground. Maybe worse.
And there's the money launderer
we extradited from Curaçao,
Franklin Jurado.
Jurado's the most important
witness to this case
and he's in U.S. custody.
We're not handing him over
to a special prosecutor.
So you're welcome to keep
the ledger, Minister...
but we have the only
guy who can read it.
Then, Agent Peña, I suppose
you have to see this out.
- Ambassador.
- Minister.
You make my job a lot fucking
harder, you know that?
Now you told me the only way Jurado
talks is if you find his wife.
Do you have any idea where she is?
I know someone who might.
After the fall of Escobar,
Medellín went from being the most
dangerous city in Colombia...
to one of its safest.
This wasn't a result of the
end of cocaine trafficking.
That was alive and well.
It was due to the new
godfather of Medellín.
His name is Diego Murillo,
but you know him as Don Berna.
Did you find her?
Sure you don't want something?
- The picada here is the shit.
- You have what I asked for or not?
Pretty girl.
Long way from home.
Gotta be fucking kidding me.
I'm imagining the headline...
"American woman held hostage
in Colombian jungle." Fuck.
- Thanks for the info.
- Wait.
I'm going to help you
rescue the Barbie doll.
To do this job, we need to work
with some old friends of ours.
They can help us.
They know the terrain like
the back of their hand.
How to get in and out.
What's it going to cost?
Cheap.
You just have to make
me a promise, Peña.
When my name pops up on
the DEA to-do list...
you pick up the phone and call me.
So I can be cautious and protect myself.
I see now.
A get-out-of-jail-free card.
Exactly.
To us, Peña.
Enrique!
Boss.
Open the door. Quick.
- Boss...
- What are you doing? Get in.
- What happened?
- David has been calling.
What for? He never called before.
- I wanted to talk to you first.
- Last night was a big fuck up.
You're in danger.
Pack a few things and let's go.
Jorge, I swear. I radioed in.
It doesn't matter, Enrique.
The DEA passed right in front of you.
I should just run, bro.
Like Córdova?
What? It doesn't matter!
Stay, run. It's the same fucking thing!
No matter what I do,
I'm a fucking dead man.
Nobody is going to die, you hear me?
Nobody is going to die.
But right now, let's just get
you to tomorrow, Enrique.
Keep paging him until he hits us back.
Nothing else we can do.
Fuck.
We should've arrested him.
You know, brought him in for
assault or something to save him.
Fuck. I hope we didn't
hang him out to dry.
I thought you didn't like him.
Yeah, doesn't mean I want him dead.
Why the fuck do I have to hide here?
I didn't do anything.
I know you didn't do anything.
This is David being an idiot.
But... trust me. Have some
patience. I'll handle it.
Jorge...
last week, when you told
me to not say anything...
- about the DEA and their safe house...
- Hey.
That has nothing to do with anything.
Why are you bringing this up?
Stay focused.
Sit down.
It's very important you do what I say.
Don't leave this room.
And don't call anyone.
Not your mother, your brother or
your girlfriend. No one. Understood?
Hey, look at me.
We'll get you through this.
I promise.
Thank you, Jorge.
Seriously.
- Jorge.
- Fercho, how's it going?
Don Miguel.
Where the fuck is Enrique, Jorge?
I left him messages at his
house, at the tap room,
but trust me, I'll find him.
Regardless of where he is,
you know him as well as me.
He's a man we can trust.
The thing is, Jorge,
I don't know Enrique.
Because I didn't hire him, you did.
No, Córdova hired him.
But that doesn't matter.
I don't like to make judgments
before I know all the facts,
and we don't know them, David.
I find that funny, you know?
Because lately,
you're missing too many facts.
More specifically,
about the fucking DEA, Jorge.
Huh?
When the DEA burst into the building,
I was six feet away from your dad.
Don Miguel,
I've been investigating and it
looks like Enrique did radio in.
I think the DEA is using a signal
to interfere with our radios.
Dad...
Dad, please.
It could be.
But you know what, Jorge?
That doesn't explain how the DEA
knew where I was. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Someone sang and I want to
know who the fuck it was.
Find Enrique. Let's have
him speak for himself.
We fucking fix this once and for all.
- Hi, fellas.
- Sir.
Welcome.
Hello.
War makes for strange alliances,
putting you into business
with people that,
under other circumstances,
you wouldn't even shake hands with.
Great machine.
You people know how to build
a fucking assault chopper.
The same is true of your enemies.
They will unite when they need to.
FARC, or Revolutionary
Armed Forces of Colombia,
were a guerrilla army
about 17,000 strong...
engaged in the longest civil
war in modern history.
And in the early days of that war,
how did they finance their struggle?
Kidnapping.
Wealthy Colombians would pay a ransom
to have their loved
ones returned unharmed.
So when the Cali cartel wanted
to keep someone on ice,
safely hidden somewhere in
the middle of the jungle,
they hired the pros.
For a hefty fee, of course.
Nice look, Berna.
You're coming on the raid?
Thanks, but no.
I'm coming to make sure all
goes well with our friends.
Look at me.
Do you think an important man like me...
is going to risk his life for
some gringo piece of ass?
You don't know how to take a joke.
I'll go in.
Sure.
But they go with you.
What about you, brother?
Are you trying to fuck us all or what?
Calm down, Gilberto.
Franklin Jurado's in U.S. custody.
You don't want to surrender,
and you let them get the goddamn ledger!
Since you were a kid, I had to tell
you what to do and what not to...
You know what, Gilberto?
Since you were a kid, you had a big
mouth. Why don't you just shut up?
He's fucking lost his mind.
All these acts of violence
in the North Valley
are straining our friends' patience.
Any surrender deal's
hanging by a thread.
Uncle Miguel has to see that.
I told him, no violence.
Is this all my fault?
Haven't I always done
what was best for him?
Franklin Jurado.
I need to reach out to Chepe. Or Pacho.
But how the fuck...?
There's no one else I
can trust with this.
Let's see...
Dad.
Nicolás...
I need you to get involved
in the Jurado situation.
Hello.
Any news?
He has a girlfriend on
the other side of town.
Look, David, if Enrique was a rat,
he wouldn't be around anymore.
Ah... Thanks.
I think I'll wait here.
You know he's a mama's boy.
That fucker will be back.
So now what?
Now you go to Toro Negro.
Navegante's waiting for you.
He'll give you an
assignment from my father.
Why didn't he call me?
I'm going to explain something to you.
Until this is figured out,
you only talk to me. Understood?
Yes, sir.
Better get moving.
Navegante hates to wait.
Coming up to coordinates
Kirk 5-7, maneuver incoming.
Private militias not only
weren't illegal in Colombia,
they were encouraged.
A government program called
CONVIVIR was started in 1994.
And it authorized
private security forces
to take up arms against
the communist guerrillas.
A free pass for crimes against
humanity, sponsored by Uncle Sam.
Gentlemen. So good to see you again.
Third generation night vision goggles.
The same ones the Americans used
in Operation Desert Shield.
Peña, can we keep them afterwards
as a contribution to the cause?
The Castaños ran the largest
private militia in Colombia.
Their AUC, or Autodefensas
Unidas de Colombia,
numbered in the tens of thousands.
Their victims...
in the hundreds of thousands.
Theirs was a perpetual war.
And if you're hunting communist
guerrillas in the jungle,
they were your only call.
This one has AFCS.
And the 701 engine. Hmm.
- Not like last time.
- Last time?
The CIA.
They had us out here hunting
commies on Christmas day.
- That's real dedication.
- It is God's work.
Merry Christmas.
My dad trusts him, but...
did you see him?
That son of a bitch
looks nervous, right?
Never stopped adjusting
the mirror, staring.
I kind of love how much
this motherfucker hates me.
Our man in Bogotá confirmed
there must be an informant.
Huh?
Salcedo has to be the one the
gringos are calling "Natalia."
I'm going to love killing
that motherfucker.
You know who else I am going
to kill? His arrogant wife.
I'm going to leave those
poor girls orphans.
Poor things.
You can adopt them.
You son of a bitch...
Answer.
This is Paola, leave a message.
Hello, love, it's me.
Paola, listen,
I need you to call me back.
It's very important.
3 NEW MESSAGES
DELETE?
CONFIRM
0 NEW MESSAGES
Take me to where you
stashed him, Jorge Salcedo.
Stashed who?
Pallomari.
Are we taking him someplace?
Uh-uh.
I see.
What do you mean,
you're going to a meeting?
I have a business to run, Guillermo.
A meeting with who?
With Fredy. We're meeting a new client.
Fredy? Patricia, the police
almost caught Miguel yesterday.
For fuck's sake.
What's the problem?
You didn't tell them
where he was, did you?
- No.
- No. What are you worried about?
Miguel likes you.
That's what you always tell me.
Yes, but always within limits.
You're worrying too much, Guillermo.
They need you. You're the brains
behind the organization...
None of that matters, Patricia,
none, if they decide not
to leave loose ends.
You're giving me a headache.
Listen to me.
My love, we have to get out
of here before it's too late.
It's just a couple hours.
Call me if there's a problem.
What is it, Jorge Salcedo?
What do we do if we find Pallomari's
family in the apartment?
Hope that we don't.
We'll need to be quick.
I have someplace to be.
The love of my life is in
town and we have a date.
That's great.
When was the last time you saw her?
Eight years.
Eight long years.
Why so long since last time you saw her?
You know, she was abroad.
- In Japan.
- Japan?
Working?
She fucked a police captain.
Then tried to turn me in.
All these years, I've been
hanging around her parents' house
waiting for her to come back.
People say things happen for a reason.
All I know is... she came back.
She came back.
Beautiful day. Right?
How many tents, give or take?
I think around 20.
The FARC arrange themselves in
staggered positions, two circles.
Then they always go for lookouts
in high places along the trails.
Sun sets in three hours.
As soon as they hear the chopper,
they're going to hide.
Generators, flashlights,
fires... everything.
Those rats have a lot
of practice hiding.
Once the lights go, they'll use
guidelines strung into the jungle.
They grab hold, follow ropes to safety.
Once we find one of those ropes...
It's a fucking slaughter.
Berna.
Look, I don't want a bloodbath.
Listen to me, Peña.
You want the girl...
there will be a body count.
This is a war zone.
But if you want, we can
still call this thing off.
I need to get her back.
Just to be clear...
something goes wrong...
you still keep your promise.
Hey, you talk to Pallomari,
try to keep him calm.
- Then I come in.
- Okay.
Pallomari.
Pallomari!
He's not here, of course.
No luggage.
Must've freaked out when
Miguel almost got caught.
You know, Pallomari, he's the smart one.
Guess that's why he's the accountant.
And not a thug.
Hey, Salcedo.
You'll need to find him.
Miguel gave this priority.
Do you understand?
I'll take care of it.
Let me know when you have him.
I need tonight for the
business I told you about.
Oh.
Sure.
Good luck then.
- Hey, it's me.
- Salcedo! Busy today.
Listen...
any chatter from Pallomari?
None I've heard. But we got him.
- Who?
- Enrique.
He called his brother, the idiot.
David's on his way to get him.
That's great news.
Miguel must be pleased.
- David?
- We have him.
Yes?
He showed up at the house?
Meet us at 11th & 614th.
You ever hear anything from Judy?
Not since you sold her out.
Who would've thought it, Javier?
Both of us, bosses.
They give you a nice place in Bogotá?
It's good.
You should see my house.
I can take a shit in a different
bathroom every day of the week.
My wife loves it.
Your wife?
I'm a family man.
Bet you still live out of a suitcase.
Guess catching guys like me...
makes it all worth it. Right?
Don't forget the suitcase.
Keep going!
Come on. Let's go! Assume position!
Be advised, team: five minutes to LZ.
Let's see how our new toys work.
Get ready.
God bless America.
Ah... Our guest of honor's arrived.
What's going on here?
Jorge, you're going to have
to explain some things.
Alpha in position.
Tell him what you told us.
Huh?
Salcedo knew about the DEA.
You're going to talk to me
like a man, motherfucker.
Salcedo works with the DEA!
He knew the DEA was in Cali.
He knew where they were at
and he told me to watch them.
And he told me not to tell you.
Charlie in position.
Bravo in position.
Everyone's in position.
Rotor, force them to the north.
Copy that. We're going to push them out.
We're circling back.
Arriving in 30 seconds.
Is that true, Jorge?
Tell me.
Are you working with the DEA?
Sir... it's true I've been
successful tracking the DEA.
But saying that I knew where their
safe house is, that's absurd.
That's absurd.
Rotor ETA five seconds. We have visual.
FARC is on the move. They're going dark.
Peña, they have your girlfriend
in the southeast part of camp.
Let's move.
They're about to kill me
because of you, motherfucker!
That fucking son of a bitch is lying!
If you're looking for an
infiltrator, it's him, not me.
Shut up! Know what they're gonna do
to my family if you say that shit?
You son of a bitch!
Let go of me!
I'll kill you, motherfucker!
- Let it go, motherfucker!
- Sir, that bastard is lying!
What do you want me to say if
that's the truth, motherfucker?!
Cut the bullshit!
All right, men, let's get
these fireworks started.
And don't be pussies.
This is easy. Get ready.
This shit is on!
I'm tired of this, Dad.
Sir, no.
David, please. What is this?
- Sir, I have no idea...
- Dad...
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
Is that you, motherfucker? Huh?
- No.
- What the fuck is that?
- What the fuck is this?
- I don't know, sir.
I've never seen that!
Sir, I swear I've never
seen that before.
Let's give those fucking
guerrillas a rain of bullets!
They're in the river! Give them lead!
Sir... it's a SkyPager.
It's American high-end tech.
- Don Miguel, please.
- Shut up.
- What the fuck does it say?
- Let's see.
These are messages in
English. He's your rat!
Motherfucker, you're
going to have my family
killed dragging me into this!
It's not yours?
It's not yours, Enrique?
Sir, I swear I've never
seen that before.
I swear on my mom I've never
seen that before, Don Miguel.
Can they track us with this shit?
I think so, sir.
Motherfucker!
- No.
- Don't move.
- Please! Don Miguel, no!
No! Let me go!
Tell the truth, motherfucker!
Salcedo, you motherfucker!
Ah! Don Miguel!
Look, Jorge.
Your friend.
- Christina.
- Don't. Don't.
Stay where you are.
Put the gun down!
Don't move.
- Stay still.
- Please.
One more step and...
The rat is dead.
What's wrong?
Start.
- Feistl.
- I have her.
Get Franklin ready.
Yes, I know my signature.
- Hi!
- Hi, Dad!
Where's Mom?
Jorge?
She doesn't want to see you.
Paola!
Have some respect.
This is my mom's house.
What's going on?
What is it?
Breathe.
What happened?
What's going on? Come here.
In less than an hour,
we're on that plane.
Your husband knows.
He'll be waiting for you.
It's all behind you now, Christina.
And you think I should
thank you for that?
No.
No, I don't.
No, you think you're a
hero because you, what,
executed a bunch of
farmers to get me out
so that my husband
would testify for you?
I did what I had to do and I'm
sorry for what happened to you.
No.
No, you're not.
And you know it.
You're a piece of shit.
- Salcedo?
- I know where Miguel is.
This needs to happen right now.
Yeah, of course.
Your code name for me? Natalia?
- What about it?
- They know. You have a leak.
The cartel knows about it.
It won't be long before
they know about me.
This needs to happen now or I'm dead.
Call for you. Number four.
Hello?
Brother.
That phone doesn't work.
Try number five.
You're Colombian.
Right?
I'm from Cali.
Hello?
Yeah?
Hey... it's been taken care of.
Yeah, we're about to get on the
plane. We'll be in Miami...
When?
Let me call you back.