Mrs. Moncada.
Please, call me Judy.
Let me tell you...
before this son of a bitch
killed my husband and my brother,
all these people were my friends.
What do you think of that?
Well, it looks to me
like you made some new friends. No?
We might say that we share a common goal.
- The same as yours, Agent Peña.
- Is that right?
Yes.
Wait, Javier.
I'd like you to listen
to what we have to say.
You want to catch Escobar,
just like we do.
But let's not lie to ourselves.
You haven't been able to get close to him.
The only play you had to get to him
was using Carrillo.
And we know how that ended, right?
So, you're taking a break
from burning down villages?
What we do is fill in
for an absent government.
We're going to kill everyone
close to Escobar one by one.
Until he's alone. With nothing.
What we want, Mr. Peña,
is to make Escobar understand
he is not untouchable.
We want him to be afraid.
There's just one small problem.
Just one?
To catch him, we need the satellite
technology and surveillance
that your government has, Agent Peña.
And I'm just going to...
hand that over to you?
We have been partners for a while now,
Agent Peña.
All the information that he gave to you,
I gave to him.
We are simply making...
a small adjustment.
Thanks for the drink.
Too much stupidity for my liking.
The Castaños can be useful.
I was talking about you.
Yes, Javier.
I'm a narco.
And I believe in honor and loyalty,
like you.
Pablo doesn't.
Berna. Go get the car.
Are you going to give me a cigarette
or what?
Well...
we really want you to realize, Agent Peña,
the potential of what we're offering you.
Because, well...
with all the information in the world,
you still have to be a policeman, right?
I know what it feels like
when Pablo kills someone close to you.
What's that?
Information that would be
very valuable to you.
That was very easy for us to find.
Take it.
She's staying with a friend.
That little girl, Maritza.
The woman that betrayed you
and got Carrillo killed.
You'll find her there.
I told you we have an enemy in common.
If you change your mind, give us a ring.
LEADER OF THE SEARCH BLOC KILLED
COLONEL HORACIO CARRILLO
- Look, Dad.
- Let's see.
- Nine point seven.
- Why?
I would've given you a ten,
but here, next to me,
is an Argentinian judge who's very picky.
Very picky.
Why don't you jump in here with me?
If I dive in there,
I'd splash all the water out of the pool.
Sir, Fernando Duque is here.
And you... And what are you doing,
my little love?
That's it. Little kicks, little kicks.
Like a little pair of scissors.
That's right, like a little puppy.
That's it, beautiful.
Hey, ladies.
My kids are in the pool.
Does someone know how to swim?
- Yeah, boss, they call me "Flipper."
- Flipper?
You talk so much shit, Blackie. You'd sink
like a rock tied to a heavier rock.
Eat shit, Velasco.
- Velasco, I'm putting my trust in you.
- Yes, sir.
Not in Flipper.
Flipper.
"They call me Flipper."
- What's the score?
- Two to zero.
The National team is winning.
We're killing them!
That's it!
Careful with that little dance.
You're starting to put ideas in my head.
Love, who is picking up Carlos?
La Quica. He's on his way.
That smells good.
Pablo, the kids love this place.
- It's nice, isn't it?
- Yes.
On your feet. Now!
I didn't know. I didn't know, I swear.
Limón lied to me.
No, please. When they find me,
they're going to kill me.
- No!
- Stay still!
Please.
Do you think I wanted this?
They used me
and they're throwing my life away.
You're all the same.
You don't listen. Nobody listens!
And all those people dying for no reason.
What's up, Peña?
What should we do with her?
Is that your father?
Over there with the president?
That's cool.
To all those present,
it is my honor to present
the President of the Republic...
His Excellency,
Don César Gaviria Trujillo.
Congratulations, Class of 1992.
Recent events...
contrast heavily with today's ceremony.
Each one of you has decided to sacrifice
your personal interests...
and dedicate your lives
to the service of the nation.
There is no higher honor...
than to serve your homeland.
- Colonel, how are you doing?
- Very well.
I enjoyed your speech very much,
Mr. President.
I'm glad. It was also for you.
Look, Colonel, in the last 24 hours,
I've been discussing with my advisors
who should be at the head
of the Search Bloc.
They mentioned many names.
But I would like it to be you,
Colonel Martinez.
That's an honor, Mr. President,
but at this point in my career,
- I'm sure you can find a better candidate.
- Colombia wants to end this nightmare.
And I know you're the man to do it.
The nation deserves someone
better than me.
Your son was one of the best
in the academy. He's an excellent cadet.
He worked very hard.
I'm very proud of him.
We asked the best in the class
to join the Search Bloc.
And your son happily accepted.
I ask that you at least
consider my request.
For Colombia.
Come on, come on. Let's see.
Go ahead.
- I can't believe it. Look at you.
- Slowly.
I don't want any more visits
to the doctor.
- Manuela, you're so beautiful. Look at me.
- Look how tan he is.
- He looks like a movie star, right?
- Yes, boss.
- He looks like Tom Cruise.
- Well...
Look at her, Pablo.
I can't believe you brought me all the way
from Miami to see my sister like this.
No. I'm just so happy to see you.
Oh, my God. Carlos!
Welcome, sweetie.
I'm so happy to have you home.
Tonight, I am going to make
the best meal this family has ever had.
Well, then...
ready to go for a little walk?
It's incredible how much the children
have grown, Pablo.
Manuelita is a princess. She is beautiful.
She's the one who controls everything
around here. I just pay the bills.
I heard about Carrillo.
If that son of a bitch was still alive,
many more policemen would have died.
I did the police a favor. Believe me.
Do you think the police agree with you?
No one wants war, Carlos.
Especially when they know they would lose.
But all that's in the past.
And I'm ready to get back to business.
I'm all in.
- Tell me about Miami.
- What can I tell you, Pablo?
The demand keeps increasing
and the merchandise keeps on coming.
Business hasn't been affected
by what happened at La Catedral,
nor by what you did.
Well, business can always
get better, right?
Let's bring the Lion over here.
I want to speak to him face to face,
like the old days.
- Okay.
- Make some new arrangements.
Some better ones.
Quica.
Give Velasco a call.
Tell him to find the Lion.
Carlos and I want to speak to him
about business.
It's time to get back
to making money, brother.
- Like the good old days, Pablo.
- Exactly.
What's up, Maritza?
What happened?
The police are looking for me.
They want to put a bullet in my head.
I'm sorry, Maritza. I thought
something good would come from all this.
Something good?
Let me come work with you.
No, Maritza, you're crazy.
I have to get this.
Give me one second.
What's up?
Where the fuck are you, Limón? Think you
can make me wait around for you, bitch?
I'm close by, man.
I mean, there's a lot of goddamn traffic,
but I'm on my way.
I don't give a fuck if there's traffic.
I need you here now!
You have to take this shit with you,
so get your ass over here. Right now.
Yes, I know, I know.
Forgive me. I'm on my way.
Maritza, I have to go.
I can't help you right now.
We already gave you money.
I'll call you later.
And we'll figure it out,
but I can't right now.
- Search Bloc.
- It's Peña.
I'm here with Trujillo at the corner
of 38th and 24th streets. We need back up.
I'm sorry, but there's no authorization
to dispatch patrols.
We're watching one of Escobar's guys.
He just entered the building.
Return to base with the location.
We can ask for authorization from Bogotá.
Sure.
And you'll show up next Tuesday,
son of a bitch.
What time were you supposed to be here,
asshole?
You knew you had to make the delivery
before I pick up Lion tomorrow.
No, brother, don't get mad.
It's just that--
Limón!
You're going to take this goddamn bag
and get out of here now! I'm watching you.
- Calm down.
- Calm down?!
This is the last time you pull shit
like this, Limón. The last time!
- This is the last time you make me wait.
- Come on, man--
I told you. Get out of here.
Shit. What do we do?
We stick with Velasco.
The other one doesn't matter.
How many guys do you think are inside,
Peña?
Too many for just us two, no?
Yeah. We'd be screwed.
Son of a bitch.
We should call for backup, right?
Who are you calling?
- What's going on, Peña?
- I'll handle this.
This is Trujillo. You can trust him.
You are finally seeing the light, Javier.
Let's just see if this works.
You two coming?
Okay, then. You two, in the front with me.
Berna, with his men, around back.
Understood?
Just stay clear of the windows.
- Let's go, then.
- Let's move.
- They're everywhere.
- Let's go down.
Hey!
Where were you going,
you filthy son of a bitch?
Here it is, Mrs. Escobar.
- What's that?
- It's a delivery.
- But who told you to buy this?
- It was me.
It's some clothes.
Hermilda, for God's sake...
you can't send him out with so much money.
- Oh, Tata!
- They are going to know where we are.
You worry too much.
It's going to affect the children. Do you
want Juan Pablo and Manuela to worry?
You're right.
When Pablo was a little boy...
he came home from school one day,
very angry.
A little girl made fun of his shoes.
They were ragged.
And we didn't have any money
to buy him new ones.
But that night, I went into town
and I stole a pair from a store.
The next day, Pablo went back to school.
Being poor is not an excuse
to look like you are.
You've always just taken
what you wanted, right?
And Pablo as well.
It worked.
We're even.
I need you to help me get a visa
and get my family out of Medellín.
Somewhere Pablo can't find us.
It doesn't work like that.
I'm sorry.
So, then...?
How am I supposed to be okay?
Is this how things are going to work
from now on, Peña?
Don't worry about it, okay?
It won't happen again.
No. I'm not worried.
Leave us.
Life's funny, Velasco.
This could easily
have ended up in reverse.
Me lying there,
you and your men ready to torture me.
Look how everything's changed.
We are both loyal soldiers.
Serving our generals.
But you know what?
When it's time to give up your boss...
we give up our boss.
Ma'am, nothing about Pablo, but...
he gave up this.
- Three of his accountants.
- And their addresses.
He also told me Pablo
still has a large army and a lot of money.
Yes, but that could be complete bullshit,
no? To scare us off.
Or it could be true. To scare us off.
There lies the key.
If we leave him without money,
we leave him without an army.
Something else.
Velasco was going to the airport tomorrow
because the Lion will be arriving
in the afternoon from Miami.
Excuse me, sir. It's Judy Moncada.
Mrs. Moncada.
How can I help you?
How was your trip? You must be beat.
Where's Velasco?
There he is.
Welcome.
- Gilberto Rodríguez Orejuela.
- Lion.
This is my brother, Miguel.
And this gentleman is our associate,
Pacho Herrera.
I'm very pleased to meet you, gentlemen.
It's a pleasure.
Lion... May I call you that?
- Yes, sir.
- Have a drink. Relax.
They say, over there,
that you like whiskey.
Listen, gentlemen,
if I did something to offend you, or--
What? Would we offer you a drink
if we were offended?
Have a seat.
Tell me something, Lion.
Do you like working for a thug?
One...
two, three!
Very good.
Good job.
Look after your sister.
What happened?
Hey, boss...
Lion just called, sir.
He said Velasco never showed up
at the airport, sir.
Lion got scared shitless and left.
He took a plane back to Miami.
Fucking Lion.
Is he a little bitch or what, brother?
- And where is Velasco?
- Boss, I have no idea.
Find him for me.
Right away, boss.
- I can't believe you're cooking, Tata.
- But you know I always helped my mother.
I helped while you ate.
You know, I'm very happy
that Pablo brought me here.
But I'm worried about you.
No. There's no reason to worry.
For God's sake, Tata.
Every cop in the country
is looking for Pablo.
Every drug trafficker
who's not from Medellín wants him dead.
And you're telling me there's no reason
to worry? Don't kid yourself.
Today is a good day, Carlos.
My family is all together. You're here.
Pablo is a strong man.
He's always had to be.
There's no reason to change anything now.
I hope you're hungry.
Come inside, I'm packing.
Are you going to let me go to Medellín
or what?
Is that why you accepted the job?
You never should have volunteered.
But you can't be reassigned now,
because it would end your career, right?
Sure, only now I'm gonna be
"the boss's son."
It appears to me you don't understand
what's happening.
I accepted because I wanted
to help my country.
Come here. I want to show you something.
I received this urn with my name.
Look. On behalf of Pablo Escobar.
It's an obituary.
Look, son, you're going to do
exactly as I tell you.
I'm going to make sure you survive this.
Understand?
From now on, the Search Bloc is going
to operate in a more systematic fashion.
Since we unfortunately cannot rely on
the information given to us
by the people of Medellín,
we are going to implement
a quadrant search.
We will position ourselves
in the neighborhoods
where we believe Escobar
and his allies might be,
proceed to search them...
and if we don't find
what we're looking for,
we'll process anything of value
and continue on to the next one.
- Understood?
- Yes, Colonel!
What did you find out from Velasco?
Not a fucking thing.
That son of a bitch turned out to be
a lot tougher than I thought.
Is that what I think it is?
Rules of the game:
We only go after armed people. Sicarios.
There won't be any information
about businesses or labs or shipments.
This isn't about helping Judy.
This is about killing Pablo.
Well, then...
here's to killing Pablo.
For Colombia!
Follow me. Follow me and cover me!
Boss?
Sorry to bother you, but something bad
is happening in the city, boss.
Five of our men, dead.
Who was it?
I don't know, boss. If I knew,
I'd kill the son of a bitch that did it.
Boss, I'm so sorry,
but La Quica's on the phone.
- And Velasco?
- It looks like a battlefield, boss.
No one's seen Velasco
and no one knows where he is. Boss...
you know that if someone
grabbed Velasco...
Yes.
Start packing.
Your turn, let's do it again.
My little rock made of paper...
how much do you want to eat?
Show your grandmother
how you washed your hands.
Looks good.
Pardon me.
Should we start?
Dig in, dig in.
- A little meat.
- So good.
A spoon?
There's no spoon, love. How about a fork?
The Castaños are very efficient.
But not very discreet.
No one can know
we had anything to do with this.
Excuse me.