[men shouting in Spanish]
[Steve]
Pablo Escobar said, "Sometimes I'm God.
If I say a man dies,
he dies the same day."
[screaming sobs]
In his career, this asshole
killed thousands of police officers
at a rate of over 400 a year.
With numbers like that staring you
in the face, you have to ask...
what possesses a man to put on a uniform
that all but guarantees
his days are numbered?
[shouting in Spanish]
Most of them were just kids,
raised to reach a fork in the road
and choose the right path.
Fight for the good guys.
They were young, they were full of hope...
and they thought they were invincible.
WE LOVE YOU!
And those that were left behind
would feel their loss the most.
Everybody's got a breaking point,
when shit sickens them so much
that they just have to act.
For Pinzén,
that breaking point meant resignation.
[man speaks Spanish]
Present arms!
[Steve] But there were those who couldn't
resign, who couldn 't just walk away.
- [man shouts orders in Spanish]
- Presidents have breaking points, too.
And Gaviria had finally found his.
[in Spanish] I am responsible
for the death of those men, Eduardo.
And if Escobar is using their deaths
to send me a message, then I will respond.
I agree completely.
We have to go in full force.
Keep in mind... bringing him back
won't be a popular decision.
But since when do we care
about being popular, huh?
[phone ringing]
Colonel Carrillo.
Yes, Mr. President.
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[slow Latin song plays]
[in Spanish] Boss, they're all saying
they don't know anything.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
You gentlemen are under the impression
that you work for the Moncadas.
Allow me to clarify.
You have never worked for the Moncadas.
You work for me,
and you have always worked for me.
- Blackie.
- Yes, boss.
Who gave Judy Moncada
the cash to buy this house?
You, Don Pablo.
- Jairo.
- Yes, Don Pablo.
The money that puts food on the table
for these men, where does it come from?
- From your pocket.
- Everything you see here is mine.
Everything you have
is because I allow you to have it.
Everything you think you are protecting,
you are protecting for me.
Are we clear on this?
You're going to tell me the location
of every safe house, every lab,
every office,
every account of the Moncadas.
And look...
that doesn't make you gentlemen traitors.
Certainly not.
You simply didn't know
who you were really working for.
S0 let's begin...
with what's most important.
You're... going to tell me right now...
where that bitch Judy Moncada is hiding.
[horse whinnies nearby]
- [in Spanish] Ms. Judy, welcome.
- Thank you.
Pardon me.
- Hey!
- Navegante!
- Watch yourself.
- Mrs. Moncada is our guest.
We treat our guests with respect.
Even the ones who invite themselves.
Listen, Pacho,
are you sure you have enough men?
One might get the impression
you're scared of someone.
Perhaps if you took security
more seriously...
just maybe your husband
would still be alive...
and you wouldn't be coming to us for help.
Listen to this guy.
Who told you I was coming here for help?
Where's your boss?
You mean my partner.
- Handling the business.
- Ls that right?
Oh, so he's still trying to pretend
he isn't a drug trafficker?
Mrs. Moncada,
why don't you go look around?
I don't know, pet the horses.
Or rehearse whatever it is
you came to say.
Gilberto will be here shortly.
Thank you, Pacho.
- [Juan Pablo] We're safe!
- [man] Pass me the ball.
- [Juan Pablo] Here you go.
- Here it is.
Ma'am? Here's what you asked for.
[chatter continues outside]
Who's that?
[Gato]
He's one 0f the new guys.
[children laughing]
Excuse me.
POLICE STATION ATTACKED IN MEDELLIN
What a hideous painting.
[helicopter approaching]
[indistinct]
What a lovely surprise.
- To what do we owe the pleasure?
- Business.
"And one by one, the nights
between our separated cities,
they are added to the night
that unites us."
It's the middle of the fucking day,
Gilberto.
Not a fan of Neruda?
The only thing that unites us in this life
is a desire to see Pablo dead.
[Steve]
This is Gilberto Rodriguez Orejuela.
And if you've never heard of him,
it's because that's exactly
the way he wants it.
Ask him what he does for a living
and he'll tell you that he's a banker,
and that would be true.
In fact, he and his brother Miguel
controlled their own bank.
Or he might tell you that
he and his brother owned and operated
one of Colombia 's largest chains
of drug stores.
The brothers could also tell you they ran
their own soccer team. Which they did.
America de Cali,
one of the best teams on the continent
and a fierce rival
of Pablo 's At/ético Nacional.
But what they'd never tell you
is that these businesses were a front
and that the Rodriguez brothers
were the second biggest
cocaine traffickers in the world:
the leaders of the Cali cartel.
Like Pablo and the Medellin cartel,
they started out as run-of-the-mill
criminals: bank robbers.
And with all that money they scored
from their heists,
they quickly graduated to smuggling weed.
And when they realized
that ten pounds of blow
was worth as much as a ton of marijuana,
they jumped headfirst
into the cocaine business.
These guys were no piece of shit
street dealers.
They planned meticulously,
maximizing profit, minimizing risk.
And as the business grew,
a young ambitious Colombian kid,
a guy you might know named Pacho Herrera,
was such a good earner,
that the brothers eventually
promoted him to partner.
But they had a competitor,
and not just any competitor.
One that wasn't interested in abdicating
the throne as the king of coke.
- Don Pablo.
- But Gilberto was smart.
He didn't care that Escobar
wore the crown.
[in Spanish]
Gentlemen.
So they went to him with a proposal:
Miami, the cocaine capital of the world,
would remain Pablo 's territory,
and in return, the Rodriguez brothers
would make do with a little territory
in the northeast called New York City.
- [up-tempo dance music plays]
- The extra 1,089 miles may have made it
a little harder to get to,
but it turns out the folks in New York
were just as head over heels for cocaine
as the folks down south.
And while there were
1.8 million people in Miami,
there were seven mi//ion in New York City.
As much as the Cali guys loved money
and the finer things in life,
they hated the wrong kind of attention.
For the "Gentlemen of Cali," it was about
appearing like legitimate businessmen.
And business was good. But that didn't
mean that it couldn't get better.
[in Spanish] So tell me, Mrs. Moncada,
why did you come all this way?
To help you kill the man
who murdered my husband and brother
by offering very important information
that only I possess.
- And what is this information?
- Targets.
The location of every one of his labs.
Going after Pablo's infrastructure
will cripple him, force him to surface.
When he does, we put a bullet in his head
and we take turns shitting on him.
What's valuable isn't knowing
what Pablo has,
but what he wants to acquire.
Because that's where he'll be next.
Pablo is picking apart your operation
piece by piece.
Knowing what remains
tells us where he's going.
You want me to tell you where my labs are?
Well... let's say...
that I share that information. Hmm?
What happens to my labs?
Oh, Judy.
Your sense of vengeance is heartwarming.
Kiko would be so proud of your priorities.
Mmm. You're right.
He would be very proud of me.
I built the business by his side, Pacho.
I'm from the Medellin cartel.
I know what I am.
I don't need bullshit art
hanging on my wall t0 prove any different.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Confronting Pablo directly
won't help us maintain a low profile.
But...
what if the Search Bloc were to learn
the location of your labs?
What good is it if he's arrested?
He's already shown
he can fuck us from prison.
This won't end with Pablo in a cell.
You think the police will kill him?
There is one officer
that seems particularly determined.
And President Gaviria
has arranged for his return.
[Steve] This was one thing that
the Cali guys and the DEA could agree on.
As controversial
as Colonel Carrillo 's methods were,
he was the only guy
that Escobar was afraid of.
And returning command
of Search Bloc to him
was exactly what we needed.
The president has offered us every
available resource to defeat Escobar.
All we have to do now
is manage it properly.
So I'm still gonna rely on
intelligence from you.
But we're gonna do things
a little bit differently.
No more large-scale operations. Search
Bloc goes back to small-scale tactics.
- Amen.
- Stealth operations, surprise raids,
that sort of thing. We change the game.
But there's one thing
that we need to do first. Trujillo.
[in Spanish] Assemble the Search Bloc
outside. I want 100 men and six trucks.
- Tell them we're moving out. Got it'?
- On it, Colonel.
[in English] A hundred men?
That's not exactly small-scale tactics.
First thing is,
we let Pablo know that we're back.
[sirens chirping]
[Steve] Now you can bet that
the second a convoy of a hundred men
and six marked police trucks
leave that base,
that Escobar's army of spotters
would be burning up the phone lines
- just to tell Escobar all about it.
- [phone rings]
- [in Spanish] What's up?
- Theyjust left. Four motorcycles,
five pickups, and a truck.
It's a large convoy.
[Steve] And you'd be right.
But that was the point.
You see, these spotters
made it impossible for us to operate
in the secrecy we required.
So we needed to blind them.
And the first step to blinding someone
is getting them to open their eyes.
[in Spanish] They're heading to Barrio
Escobar. It's going to get crowded.
[in English]
Probably this rooftop here.
[Steve] Once those signals went up,
we could pick them up,
get a fix and get a location of each one.
[in Spanish]
The convoy has arrived.
[men chattering in Spanish]
[man]
We're in position.
A MAN, A NEIGHBORHOOD, A COUNTRY!
[Steve] And I guess you could say
that the second part of Carrillo's plan
was to show Pablo
that the sheriff was back in town.
And he did that the best way he could.
[in Spanish]
Look. Look up there.
There's something weird happening.
What do you see?
- [Juan Pablo] They're clouds.
- [Pablo] No, not clouds.
Because clouds form shapes.
- What I see is a turtle.
- [Velasco] Boss!
- Excuse me. I need to talk to you.
- [Pabl0] Keep looking.
Keep looking at the clouds.
Sir, sorry to interrupt,
but it's very important.
- [sighs] What's going on?
- Carrillo is back.
And he's here in Medellin.
Hmm.
What else?
That son of a bitch
filled Barrio Escobar with police and...
he pissed on your mural, sir.
Hmm.
[man 1] Those fucking cops
are going up 26th Street.
[man 2]
Copy that, brother. All good.
- [in English] We got 'em.
- Keeps going like that
until you reached Barrio Pablo Escobar.
We captured six radio transmissions.
But we haven't pinpointed
the exact location.
- No, sir.
- So our best bet
is to corner each of these buildings.
This time, we hit the ground.
[in Spanish] Trujillo, load up
six unmarked cars, four men per car.
Instruct them to leave in 20-minute
intervals to avoid attention. Clear?
- Yes, Colonel.
- Okay.
[in English]
Pefia, you're with me.
Murphy, Jacoby, you stay here to guide us.
- Careful out there.
- [Javier sighs]
[up-tempo Latin song plays]
[laughing]
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [engines start]
- [in Spanish] Freeze! Don't move!
- [weapons cocking]
Relax. Everything's good.
[man]
What is this?
[man on radio]
Pirafia down.
[in English]
Oh, we got one. Spotter One is down.
[in Spanish]
Son of a bitch.
Where are you going? Where are you going?!
[mutters in Spanish]
[man shouts]
Get him! Get him! Get him!
- Don't move!
- [man whistles]
Don't move!
- Good evening.
- Yes?
Would you allow me to search your house?
We're looking for...
Stop! Stop, boy! Stop!
- [woman chatters in Spanish]
- Get on the floor!
Show me your hands.
You think you're slick?
Why were you running?
- No! What did I do wrong?
- You tell me what you did.
Do you know who I am?
My name is Colonel Horacio Carrillo.
Last week,
30 police officers were murdered.
- Those pigs probably deserved it.
- [murmurs in English] Shut up, kid.
Many of them were my friends.
People perched on rooftops,
guiding murderers with radios...
are assassins themselves.
I hope after this encounter,
you'll reconsider
working with someone
who thinks he's above the law.
[Carrillo cocks pistol]
What? Am I supposed to
shit my pants in fear?
N0.
[Carrillo]
Do I make myself clear?
I want you to tell your friends,
that this is what happens
when you work for Pablo Escobar!
Take it.
Tell them this is for Pablo.
Remember what you saw.
And know what will happen to you
if I see you on a rooftop.
You can leave.
Leave!
S0, what book shall we read
before bed tonight?
The Witch.
No, my love. N0 scary stories.
The Witch? What's that? I don't know it.
Dad reads it to us. Right, Dad?
- The bad witch and the good witch, right?
- [Juan Pablo] Yes.
Not The Witch, Pablo.
I don't want any more scary stories
in this house.
Love, take your sister
and brush your teeth.
And go straight to bed.
[Pablo]
Listen, where's my kiss?
Good night.
- Good night, my love.
- Straight to bed, Manuela, please.
[dishes clattering]
- I heard a scary story, Pablo.
- [Hermilda] Tata.
The man who killed Gustavo
is back in Medellin.
Is that story true?
Yes.
Does that sound like the government
is trying to negotiate? Huh?
Good night.
Tata.
Someone has to tell you
how things are, Pablo.
That man is here to kill you.
I'm scared, Pablo.
I promise you one thing:
if things get out of hand
and I can't control it...
we'll leave the country.
Okay?
[in English]
Javi, where are the fucking spotters?
Carrillo went a different way.
He, uh... he cut them loose.
Oh, we're letting people go now?
Yeah, Murphy, we're letting people go.
And what does that mean?
- Don't worry about it, man.
- Hey, fucking talk to me.
- Let go of my fucking arm.
- What the fuck happened?
Carrillo put a gun to the kid's head
and he pulled the trigger.
To make a fucking point.
We good now?
[engine starts]
Yeah, we're good.
[up-tempo Latin music playing]
- [in Spanish] Have you seen this woman?
- No.
She works at the market.
Sweetheart?
[negative grunt]
- Are you sure?
- No.
[La Quica sighs]
Nobody's seen the bitch.
I'm pissed off, brother.
[sighs]
Let's go for some ice cream.
Something cold.
[starts engine]
[raps on door]
[in English] I'd like to talk to you
about what happened tonight.
- What do you think happened?
- I know I got left behind on purpose.
For your own best interest.
You don't know a goddamn thing
about my best interest.
You know, Murphy, what happens out there
isn't pretty for everyone.
- But it is for Pefia?
- You're not Pefia.
- 'Cause I'm a damn gringo.
- Because I trust him.
Why dOrft you try me?
This fight against Escobar,
you want to win it.
These guys aren't fighting
by the same rules, so why should we?
- You know what that means?
- Oh, I do.
So whether this is about protecting me
or protecting you, stop icing me out.
[door opens]
[woman speaks Spanish]
You were different this time.
I always know when my clients
are trying to forget something.
You know what I do to relax?
- I write.
- You write?
- What do you write?
- Letters.
For my family, but I never send them.
It's good to forget.
What do you want to forget?
Why don't you stop?
Why dOrft you?
[men murmur in Spanish]
[Velasco]
Welcome, brother.
This way.
- What is your name?
- David.
- L'm Pablo. Pleasure to meet you.
- Pleasure to meet you, too.
Follow me.
They told me you like soccer.
- I play defense.
- Of course.
Those are the real men.
You're very brave, David.
I'm sorry for what you witnessed.
The people we're fighting
are very bad people.
Tell me about the man who did that.
He said this bullet is for you.
I need you to do one last favor for me.
It's very important.
You think you can do it?
Thank you, David.
[phone ringing]
Pefia.
[in Spanish]
Agent Pefia. This is Don Berna.
I have a proposition
you might be interested in.
What a surprise.
What's up, Pefia?
Are you expecting anyone else?
No. Are you?
No, it's not necessary.
Everywhere I go in this town,
I'm surrounded by friends.
Sit down. Sit so you can taste
the best coffee in Medellin.
Dofia Luz! Bring my friend a coffee.
You have something
other than coffee for me?
Look, Agent, I'm not one of those
street-corner informants
that you slip a few gringo dollars
for a tip. No, sir.
Then why are we here?
Agent, you and I
are like the snake and the cat.
If the snake has the chance,
it will kill the cat.
And if the cat has the chance,
it will kill the snake.
But there are times
when they see a big rat,
and they both want to eat it.
[in English]
This is Moncada's biggest lab.
It'll have to be inventoried
before it's dismantled and moved.
How you know that?
- One of my Cl's.
- Hell of a tip.
It's a hell of a Cl.
Look, you want Escobar's men,
there they are.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
[rap music playing inside]
[men shouting in Spanish]
- [automatic gunfire]
- [shouting continues]
[in English] Get up! Move! Move!
[murmurs indistinctly]
Get up!
Gato!
[in Spanish] No, no, no! Calm down.
Okay, relax. Don't kill me... [grunts]
Relax, relax, relax!
[men chattering in Spanish]
[man]
Detaining the prisoners.
[in English]
Your Cl hooked us a pretty big fish.
Yeah, he's a winner.
[in Spanish]
We captured about 45 of them.
- I wonder if he'll give us Escobar.
- I don't know.
- We'll see what Carrillo gets out of him.
- Yeah. We'll see.
Carrillo told me that he talked to you.
He thinks he can trust you.
Yeah, he can.
- That's not what I mean.
- Ahh.
[in English]
Let's go.
I'm a big boy. I can handle it.
Yeah.
[in Spanish]
Approaching.
We're locking you up.
Move it!
- [in English] You get anything out of him?
- Something.
Not everything. Are you coming?
I'm in, yeah.
- [in Spanish] Hello, Valeria.
- Pablo.
- I didn't realize you'd be here.
- I wanted to be sure it went well.
- People need to hear the truth, right?
- Yes, it's important.
They forced this boy
to watch his friend get shot.
When the country hears this story,
they'll turn on that son of a bitch
who's murdering children
for the Americans.
Well... that's what I hope.
I'm glad you came.
It's good to see you again.
Are all eyes still on you?
Except yours.
[Pablo sighs]
Let's begin.
Yes.
- [Valeria] How old are you?
- [David] Ten.
I understand you're quite a soccer player.
[chuckles]
Thank you for being brave enough
to tell us your story, David.
Tell me, who were the men
who brought you to the building that day'?
They were Search Bloc policemen.
[Valeria]
Do you know why they brought you there?
[David] He said they were going
to send a message to other kids.
[Valeria]
Who is "he"? Do you remember his name?
[David]
Colonel Carrillo.
Relax, gentlemen, everything's fine.
- Where are you taking us?
- Bogoté.
You're going to jail
until this gets resolved.
But look...
if you help me, I can help you.
Give me Pablo, or Blackie or someone else,
then I'll help you.
I don't know where they are.
I don't know them.
- So you don't know anything?
- No, sir.
What about you, Gato?
All right.
If it's going to be like this...
[man screams]
[Valeria] Who else was there
besides Colonel Carrillo?
[David]
A bunch of men.
Some I heard speaking English.
Americans. Like in the movies.
Are you sure they were police?
Yes.
What now?
You think Pablo is going to reward you
for being brave?
Asshole, he doesn't even know you exist.
Do you know that?
It's your last chance, Gato.
Ask your mother, you son of bitch!
[faint screaming]
[sighs]
[line ringing]
[rings]
- Hello.
- Everything is good.
- It worked.
- Very well.
It worked.
- They took my lab.
- And a bunch of Escobar's men.
It's for a noble cause, Mrs. Moncada.
Boss, forgive me, but there's bad news.
Search Bloc took down the Moncadas'
biggest lab before we could take it apart.
Carrillo got Gato. We don't know where
they are or what they're doing to him.
[dialing]
[phone rings]
Hello?
- Steve?
- Hey, baby.
What time is it?
Uh...
It's late.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm... good.
I just need to hear your voice.
I wanted to call, Steve. I...
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
What's happened?
Tell me.
I'm good, baby. I'm... Don't worry.
[clears throat]
[baby crying]
[crying continues over phone]
You have to go.
Let's talk tomorrow. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Good night.
[heavy breathing]
[9 Fu nts]
[up-tempo Latin music playing]