[Crowd cheering]
[Galén speaking Spanish]
Beloved countrymen,
the new liberalism party
is the only force in Colombia
that is not afraid of narcotraffickers.
[Gaviria recites speech] "There are
three ways the narcotraffickers...
- Try to weaken extradition."
- [Galan] ...Try to weaken extradition.
- [Gaviria] "Bribery..."
- Bribery...
[Gaviria]
"Intimidation through violence..."
Intimidation through violence...
- [Gaviria] "...And extortion."
- [Galan] ...And extortion!
[Cheers and applause]
- "A dark and terrible scourge."
- [Galan] A dark and terrible scourge.
- What are you doing?
- [Galan continues speech nearby]
Just making sure he gets it right.
- [Man] You wrote it, you should know.
- [Gaviria sighs]
- Mm.
- Look, I brought you this.
What's this?
Clean socks.
Your wife dropped them off before we left.
How's galan doing?
- All right.
- [Galan continues indistinctly]
I wish he didn't focus so much
on extradition of narcos.
- [Audience applauding]
- — there are other things to mention.
Galan's got some balls.
[Chuckles]
Brave men have a way of dying quickly.
Well, then, you don't have to worry...
Do you?
[Chuckles]
Aah...
Pass me the socks.
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[Indistinct chatter on TV]
[Speaking English] First thing
is that we get you out of Bogota.
- Ok.
- There's an orphanage in cumaral.
It's out of the guerrilla zone
and away from the narcos.
And then what?
We get you a passport.
From another country, we can depose you
about Escobar and the siege.
You may have run away from your country,
but I'm not running away from mine.
This is about keeping you alive.
[Speaking Spanish]
Do you sleep with all your informants?
I'm not your responsibility.
If Pablo Escobar finds you...
He'll kill you in a heartbeat.
Not if I kill him first.
- [Elevator dings]
- Yeah, she's a live hand grenade.
She's the only witness we got that
can tie Escobar to the palace massacre.
Hard to bring her in when
she gets turned over to the Colombians
and she gets disappeared.
Are you ready for that?
So what's our options,
since we have none?
Well, we keep her in hiding
until things cool down,
and get her immunity
in exchange for her testimony—-
are you gonna get us immunity?
[Softly] We are going to jail
if we get caught with this woman.
Well, the next time your wife decides
to bring home a human hand grenade,
how about she hands it to you?
Are you fucking her?
Sleep with a communist?
That would be downright UN-American.
[Noonan]
Any intel to support the DEA theory
that Escobar is behind
the palace of justice siege?
No, ma'am.
Agent pena claims to have an informant
that can testify to that effect,
but he hasn't brought him forward.
[Man] In my book,
there's only two of them that know that.
And one of them is Elisa Alvaro,
girlfriend of Alejandro ayala.
The other one is Ernesto sobrino,
a radical priest who gave shelter
to m—19 fugitives in los altos comuna.
Is one of these people your informant?
Ambassador, this is...
Unofficial wiretap information.
We, uh, intercepted
a discussion between narcos.
[Noonan] What? Which narcos?
- Sounded like Pablo Escobar.
- [Javier] We're almost certain.
It was, uh... [clears throat]
It was hard to tell.
The... connection was bad.
They were calling from Panama.
- Panama?
- They know galan's gonna win
and they know
that he'll support extradition,
and they're not gonna sit around
and await being sent back to the us.
Ambassador, word is Manuel noriega
is providing safe harbor for the narcos,
and possibly shipping points
for their cocaine.
[Noonan] They're moving
their drug operations to Panama?
That's horseshit, pena.
Excuse me, ambassador.
On one hand, you're saying Escobar's
in bed with left-wing communists.
Now you're saying
he's in bed with Manuel noriega.
You can't have it both ways, son.
Ambassador, Manuel noriega has helped us
fight communism all over Latin America
for the last two decades.
I take great offense at any attempt
by the DEA to smear his good name.
[Steve chuckles]
I couldn't help but laugh.
Right wing, left wing...
For Manuel noriega,
it was all about the money.
When bush was head of the CIA,
noriega pretended to be a commie hater
so the us would ignore the fact that he
was heavily involved as a drug trafficker.
When noriega realized he could
make even more money shipping his drugs
by siding with communists,
he switched teams.
So, we invaded Panama,
and arrested "old pineapple face."
But, that was later.
For now, the trusted friend and ally
was a right-wing CIA asset
who was taking money from bush...
And right from the narcos.
[Rock music playing]
Pablo had knocked off half the Colombian
supreme court to fight extradition.
And now, he was offering
to pay off Colombia's national debt
in exchange for a truce.
Guess he missed home.
[Music continues, muted]
[Gacha speaking Spanish] Look at this
shit. We are spending millions of dollars,
and can't even get a decent meal anywhere.
Listen, the problem isn't the food,
the problem is noriega.
First chance he gets,
he'll sell us to the Americans.
You guys stay calm.
Once we reach an agreement with the
government, we'll be back in our homeland.
[Jorge] Pay the Colombian
national debt for amnesty?
I'd rather go live in Spain.
I say we go back and fight.
No, sir, none of that.
War is bad for business.
We will negotiate with them
as Pablo agreed.
[Clanging]
[Grunts] Look, Gustavo,
none of this would've happened
if he hadn't started
killing politicians and judges.
[Gustavo]
Tell me what we are supposed to do, then.
Do you want to sit here
and cry over spilled milk?
You know something, Pablo?
Sometimes, I think you kill these men
because they won't let you in their club.
You better watch your mouth, asshole.
[Clearing throat]
The Colombian government
has refused our amnesty offer.
Get used to the food, gentlemen.
It's not safe to go back home.
They've rejected our amnesty deal.
We may have to stay.
I hate this place.
We can go some place else.
- I hear Switzerland is very beautiful.
- — [soft chuckle]
In Switzerland,
we are nobody, Pablo.
What good is having all the money
in the world if you can't go home?
If we go back...
I'm going to have to fight.
Do whatever is necessary,
my love.
[Steve] 80, there it was.
The decision that would
change Colombia forever.
- [Excited shouting, whistling]
- — [band plays up-tempo tune]
[Speaking Spanish]
You're way ahead in the polls.
In my opinion,
the outcome is decided.
My question is... why do you
keep getting involved with the narcos?
I want a country at peace.
And if I don't do it, who will?
You're backing them into a corner.
I'm wearing a vest.
I'm afraid that a bulletproof vest...
Isn't enough to ensure
that you have a future.
Don't worry, my friend.
There will be a future.
[Crowd chanting]
[Crowd applauding, cheering]
[Steve] Luis Carlos galén
took the stage in soacha on August 18th,
against the advice
of his campaign manager, césar gaviria.
[Overlapping chatter]
[Automatic gunfire]
[Steve] The bullets entered just below
his vest and he was dead within minutes.
For a brief shining moment,
there was hope...
Extinguished by the pull
of an assassin's trigger.
To mourn galan's death, every hut in the
countryside lit a candle in remembrance...
And in the cities, thousands took
to the streets in a march of the silent,
a mute protest
against the violence of the narcos.
With galén's murder... came the end
of hope for a peaceful future.
[Fabio sniffs]
[Speaking Spanish]
Let's speak clearly, brother.
Galan's dead.
You had him killed, didn't you?
You didn't tell us shit,
and you killed him, you son of a bitch.
- I want to go home, fabio.
- Home?
Why are we going home?
So they can capture us?
All this shit you talk about partnership,
and then you do this on your own? Huh?
Galan was the only threat.
There is no one left to challenge us.
And you know why, fabio.
Because no one
has the balls that we have.
- [Sniffs]
- Going home.
- [Steve] Pablo was right.
- [Sniffing]
Who would have the balls
to fill galan's shoes?
[Bell tolling]
[Man speaking Spanish]
That unique honesty.
As the people now rise
and call forjustice,
I pray to god
that this sacrifice will serve at last...
As motivation for society
to react and bond...
To support the government...
And institutions...
While also demanding
a more effective leadership,
one undeterred by the hitmen,
the hijackings,
or any other manifestations of violence.
My father, Luis Carlos galan,
will be remembered
for awakening the Colombian people
to the danger of the narcos.
The assassin's bullets...
Will not stop what my father began.
As he fell,
another rises in his place.
I want to tell Dr. César gaviria...
In the name of the people of Colombia,
and my family...
That we entrust my father's ideals to him,
and that he can count on our support...
To become the president
Colombia wants and needs.
Dr. César gaviria, save Colombia!
[Crowd cheering]
[Crowd chanting]
Gaviria! Gaviria! Gaviria!
[Cheenng]
[Steve] Dr. César gaviria...
The new hope of Colombia.
If he took galan's position on
extradition, the narcos would declare war.
If he didn't,
the country would become a narco state.
[Phone ringing]
[Wife speaking Spanish] Phone!
Let it go to the answering machine.
- The machine's full.
- [Machine clicks, beeps]
I wish it would stop ringing.
It's your friends.
They're calling to offer support.
Or opinions about what I should do.
Why can't you run
without backing extradition?
- I wrote those speeches.
- Yes...
But do you even believe in them?
I don't know what I believe.
I don't want the narcos having free reign.
But I don't want the United States
involved in our affairs.
So say nothing.
That's the best way to stay alive.
[Airplane soaring]
[Up-tempo Latin music playing on radio]
[Pablo] Gentlemen.
Fernando, cheer up. Have a drink.
We're going home!
- How are you? Hm?
- Fine, my love.
What about you?
Give me one.
Margarita, right?
Let's see.
- Son of a bitch, that's good.
- Right?
Thank you.
Listen, I've got a question for you.
[Softly] Why are we going back?
We're walking into a world of shit.
Relax, brother.
Spain's too far away
to protect our interests.
We have a better chance
of influencing Pablo at home.
We need to be close by.
Relax. [Chuckles]
Don't you get it?
[Sniffs] He's only comfortable at war.
He's taking us to the slaughter.
[Gacha chatters indistinctly in Spanish]
How's business?
Fucking noriega is charging us a fortune,
but we got 175 tons to Miami.
Gacha's Mexican routes
are opening up Los Angeles.
But do you know what matters most
for our business, Pablo?
That the situation at home stays calm.
Know what I mean?
Sure.
[Softly] You should have
consulted with me about galan.
You would have tried to talk me out of it.
I would have tried.
The amount of money we are losing
is because of that bullshit.
Are you listening?
Look at those peaks, Gustavo.
I'll die...
Before I ever leave Colombia again.
[Phone ringing]
[In Spanish]
What's happening, carrillo?
[In English]
Thank you for coming.
I understand the narcos
are back from Panama.
[In Spanish]
So you practice your English with me?
[In English] Because these men
aren't cleared, and if we speak Spanish,
it could get back to Pablo.
So I started this to monitor
Pablo's sicarios' communications.
Sat phones, landlines, you name it.
I've got dozens of wiretaps,
but I've only managed to seize
about ten kilos in the last month.
Probably because I've listened
to my own men tipping the narcos off.
So I've had to start surveilling them.
I listen to them
tell their girlfriends they're afraid...
Cry to their mothers
when one of our men gets shot down.
But every once in a while...
I hear them trade secrets with Pablo.
Do your bosses know you're doing this?
I trust them even less.
Most of my men are from here,
where they can get to your mother,
your aunt, your cousin.
How do I fight... when my soldiers
are already working for Escobar?
Well, do they have to be from medellin?
[Speaking Spanish] Yes.
I definitely like the red one best.
- Really?
I prefer the gray.
Red is the color of the party,
and it makes you more...
Sociable and close to the people.
- That's important.
- Mm.
[Sighs]
I wonder what Luis Carlos
would have chosen?
You know, we should
also hire an image consultant.
We have to make you more appealing
to the youth, give you a more modern look.
Now you are going to give me image advice?
I'm just thinking about the polls.
Anyway...
Galan had professionals at his side,
but which could he trust?
And you know perfectly well
that you can trust me, right?
Mm-hm.
Well, what are you going to choose,
red or gray?
[Sighs]
Luis Carlos said something to me
before he died.
"There will be a future."
Now let's see what kind of future it is.
[Duque]
We worked together in the ministry.
The idea that
he's a presidential candidate
shows you our sad state of affairs.
I need to know which side he is on.
He speaks with
the foreign press next week.
They'll certainly ask his position.
Don't worry, Pablo.
He'll be easy to influence.
- No, I disagree.
- Why?
I did an interview with him once,
when he was an economic advisor.
I found him sitting in the parking lot
in his beat-up Renault,
eating a bag of apples...
And reading economic reform textbooks.
He was testifying to the cabinet
and wanted to be ready.
He's a bookworm, not a leader.
- No... no...
- No, no, no, you're missing my point.
- No.
- He's not an oligarch.
He's from modest circumstances.
Like you,
he's worked for everything he has.
You have to be careful
with people like that.
[Voice straining]
I want you to deliver a message.
[Jorge] We've made a lot of money.
What we have to decide is do we stick
with Pablo... or chart our own course?
[Horses whinnying]
We should talk to our friends down south.
No, no. It's not time. No. Mm?
- Whatever you say. — [chuckles]
Have you seen Marina?
She told me she was
going to buy a new brush.
You know your sister.
- Her shopping expeditions take weeks.
- [Both laughing]
[Up-tempo Latin song plays]
You have no idea how much
I wanted to go down on you in Panama.
- Yeah? — yeah.
I could tell that you really wanted to.
- Come here, baby.
- You are very patient.
Yes, of course.
All your people were there,
your brothers...
[Moaning]
[Gustavo exhales]
[Sighing]
My brothers are driving me crazy.
[Grunting]
- You know what?
- What?
- They can go fuck themselves.
- [Laughs]
If they want to,
they can go live in Spain...
- [Both grunting]
- — ...But you're staying here with me.
Let's not hide anymore.
- Not anymore.
- [Moaning]
All right.
- What do we do about my wife?
- — [both grunting]
Ask Pablo to do us a favor.
Just like he took care of galan,
he can take care of your wife.
[Grunts]
Are very evil for such a young girl.
[Grunting]
You've moved up, Fernando.
From government minister
to Pablo Escobar's errand boy.
I guess the pay is much better.
I'm not doing this for the money.
What country sends its own citizens
to an iron tomb in the United States?
I understand your dilemma.
Speak out in favor, you're seen as a us
puppet and you might not win the election.
Speak out against,
you anger the us...
And are criticized by our media
as a shill of the narcos.
César, I was thinking I would love
to dedicate a program for your campaign.
It would be an honor for me,
and would benefit us both.
What a great idea.
You guys are really shameless,
aren't you?
- How do you sleep at night?
- — césar, it doesn't have to be this way.
If Luis had been as smart as you,
perhaps we could have avoided
this horrible tragedy.
We could have had peace.
Easy.
Get out.
Read Pablo's letter.
Maybe you will have a future.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Knocking]
[Speaking English] They just picked up
that commie priest, father sobrino.
He's gonna talk. And when he does,
I hope you DEA boys understand
what's important in this hemisphere.
Well, how about you, uh...
Clue us in?
Drug dealers, I mean, bad as they are,
they want your money.
Communists want everything.
I don't know about you, pena, but I...
I like to own shit.
Right.
Good talk, Lou.
- Very, uh... enlightening.
- — yeah.
This... priest?
If it comes out that he was your informant
and you protected him...
I'm gonna make sure
you're tried for treason.
[Steve] Pena had to figure out
how to get fake papers for Elisa.
So he did what he does best.
Let me guess: It's a very
sad and complicated situation
involving you and a beautiful local.
You got your nails done.
It's... it's your color, Colleen.
- What do you want, Javier?
- — It's simple.
I just need your signature...
Right there.
You want me to create an embassy ID?
- Who is this woman?
- What I want you to do
is sidestep a little bullshit bureaucracy
and help someone stay alive.
You really think I'd be asking you
if it wasn't important?
She's my informant.
And she could be the key to bringing down
the whole medellin cartel,
so come on, Colleen,
whose side are you on?
[Speaking Spanish]
Cousin, what happened?
Where were you?
- In the office.
- In the office?
Is that where you were?
That's weird...
Because I called
and they said you hadn't been in all day.
I don't know which office you called,
but I was there.
They're seizing everything, Pablo.
All the accounts...
We knew there would
be a reaction with galan, right?
Relax, Gustavo.
Relax, because everything
will calm down later.
[Fuse hissing]
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna kill us both?
- You afraid to die?
- No. Are you?
- Put it out.
- Where were you?
Put it out, Pablo.
Put it out, Pablo!
Are you with me or what?
And when have I not been with you?
From the beginning,
it has been you and me.
I cannot do this without you.
Are you doubting my loyalty, Pablo?
But I'm having serious doubts
about the ochoas.
[Slams dynamite onto table]
[Door opens]
- [Exhahng]
- [Door closes]
[Steve] Gaviria read Pablo's letter.
The terms were simple.
He promised peace
if the narcos were left alone...
And if not...
He promised all-out war.
[Sighs]
Carrillo with his wiretaps
knew a storm was on the horizon.
Pablo became his duty
and his obsession.
He came to recognize Pablo's voice,
his sleep patterns,
what he liked to eat,
his tastes in art,
his love of silk sheets,
and his favorite music.
[Up—tempo Latin music playing]
[Steve] He would die
for the love of his wife
when you'd hear him over the airwaves.
But did she know
how easily he ordered his men to kill?
[Speaking Spanish]
[Steve] He came to understand
that Pablo spoke in code.
[Pablo in Spanish]
Time to thin the herd.
[Steve] "Cattle" were judges
or politicians who supported extradition.
But did we score a goal?
- The reporter, right.
- [Boy protesting in Spanish]
Let's make sure
we score a goal on him as well.
[Steve]
A "goal" was a targeted assassination.
Come on, come on.
If you spoke out against him,
you were dead.
- The list grew by the week.
- [Pablo] Ooh!
[Steve]
Guillermo cano, editor of El espectador,
and his reporter, Luis camacho.
Jaime Rodriguez, the former head
of the anti-drug squad before carrillo.
The drumbeat went on and on.
For carrillo,
the war had already started.
But he just couldn't trust his army.
[Speaking Spanish] You are aware
that I can end your military career?
- I don't give a fuck.
- Excuse me?
Horacio... don't give up.
You've always been the leader
of the persecution of Pablo Escobar.
Is this how you show your appreciation
for all we've done?
This operation
could be a failure before it starts.
I'm not here for fun.
What's gonna happen
is the defense minister
will give you credit for the evidence
that we found at hacienda napoles.
So... then if you resign,
I will look really bad.
Is that what you're doing?
Is that what you want?
Horacio...
You remember when were cadets,
we never thought they would call us
to lead the country's most important unit.
Horacio, as your friend...
I'm asking you to think about it.
Rodrigo, I don't even know who Pablo pays.
It could be any of us three.
- Horacio, please.
- I've put my family at risk.
If there is going to be a war,
I need the right tools.
All right.
Perfect.
Then tell me what you need. Hm?
Incorruptible men.
[Steve]
And that's how the search bloc came to be.
[Shoufing]
[Shouting in Spanish]
[Steve] But carrillo
wasn't the only one recruiting soldiers.
[Speaking Spanish] Hey, punk.
Are you all right?
- Sure.
- Come here.
[Steve] La quica and poison
had kids deliver packages.
And if they didn't look inside,
it meant they could be trusted
to deliver anything from cocaine to...
Well, anything else.
[Cheenng]
[Chatter in Spanish]
[Murmurs in Spanish]
[Pablo] How are you, son?
- How are you?
- Good.
- [Thunder rumbling]
- — [indistinct chatter in English on TV]
[Speaking Spanish]
I have to kill that son of a bitch.
Carrillo's a cop.
You can always buy a cop with money.
- I've tried, believe me.
- Then offer more.
Or I can loan you navegante.
He will do whatever I ask.
[Voice strains] That's true.
It's silver or lead.
That's the choice for that bastard.
Speaking of lead,
I'm getting a shipment of weapons in.
Uzis, grenades...
If I could find a nuclear weapon...
But now I'm negotiating a fucking missile.
- A missile? No fucking way.
- Yes.
- Boss.
- Eh?
[President bush] This is crack cocaine,
seized a few days ago
by drug enforcement agents,
in a park just across the street
from the white house.
And our message
to the drug cartels is this:
The rules have changed.
- [Bush continues indistinctly]
- — he's bullshitting, right?
He's smoking that shit.
I guarantee it.
[Sighs]
[Gacha] Motherfucker.
Mrs. Ouiroga told me
the neighbors on the block took a vote.
They want us to move.
But we have guards stationed
outside the house 24 hours a day.
That's what scares them.
Come here.
It won't always be like this,
my love.
[Knocking at door]
[Cocks gun]
- Rodrigo.
- Hello, horacio.
- Everything ok?
- — may I speak with you?
Yes, sure. Come in, come in.
[Rod rigo]
Let's talk about the incorruptibles.
I'm listening.
[Sighs]
I've been instructed to tell you that
if you cease and desist your operations,
you will receive
a one-time payment of six million.
Horacio... that's us dollars,
not pesos.
Instructed by whom?
I think you can guess.
Say the name.
You know who.
Say the name, Rodrigo.
[Sighs]
Escobar.
Don't look at me like that, horacio.
I've always cared for you.
I'm making this suggestion to save
you and your family from terrible grief.
[Sighs] This man has tentacles.
I'm surprised
he hasn't killed you already.
Get out.
Horacio, please...
Horacio...
[Sighs]
Take care.
[Door opens, closes]
[Javier in English]
I was driving to the church.
Was with my buddy, John.
He was my best man.
- We were late. [Sighs]
- — [thunder rumbling]
It was fucking blazing outside,
110 degrees.
Whole bridal party was there
sweating their balls off, I'm sure.
- And all of a sudden, I stopped the car.
- — [soft chuckle]
Please don't tell me
you left her at the altar.
I don't know if she actually
made it to the altar.
[Laughing]
Well, you saved her
a lifetime of hell.
Yeah, she forgave me. Eventually.
- Married a stockbroker from Dallas.
- Hm.
Randy... I think.
Trust me, she's better off.
[Sighs]
What if father sobrino talks?
He's gonna talk.
[Steve sighs]
[Javier speaking Spanish]
It's about time, navegante.
[Sighs]
[Speaking broken English]
Sorry I'm late. I couldn't came before.
[Javier] What do you got?
Gacha's going tonight to cartagena.
I can help you get him.
You said you had information.
You didn't say gacha.
I guess is your lucky day.
- What's the informant's motivation?
- Could be money.
The reward for gacha is one million us.
I'd say that's pretty good motivation.
He spends his life on the run
if we don't catch him.
- Something else going on with this guy.
- — It's worth taking a risk.
Pena, you go to cartagena.
Solely in an observational capacity.
We want this man captured alive,
if possible.
Murphy stays here in Bogota'.
Gaviria's press conference is tonight,
and I wanna be sure whatever
he plans to say, he gets to say it.
Yes, ma'am. [Clearing throat]
That's a beautiful dress,
ambassador noonan.
[Door opening]
- [Lou] Come on, father. Ah, yeah. Talk!
- [Sobrino grunting]
[Muffled groaning]
- [Lou] Huh?
- [Struggling grunts]
- [Sputtering]
- [Lou] Huh?
[Panting] More? You want more?
No! No more, please! No more!
[Sobbing] No more!
Ah, he's all yours.
He's ready to talk.
Father...
How did Elisa Alvaro get away?
[Gasping]
[Speaking Spanish]
- [Sobrino sobbing]
- She left with the American woman.
- [Sighs]
- Murphy's wife.
I just don't understand.
How'd you get involved with communists?
Have you actually met a communist?
Yeah, I have, actually...
And she lied to me.
Well, I'm not a communist, Connie.
I'm fighting against poverty,
corruption, injustice and greed.
But I guess Americans
don't have the same problem.
Don't we?
It's not the same.
Look, I just wish
you'd been straight with me.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps I should go.
You can't just go.
Look, if they find you, they'll kill you.
I fell in love with a man...
With a good man.
And I was hoping
to do something good.
But instead, I fell into something...
Else, something more violent.
Yeah, that makes two of us.
[Steve murmurs indistinctly]
I'll see you when I get home.
Here, Elisa's ID.
- What am I supposed to do with that?
- Take her to cumaral.
My contact there agreed to hide her.
[Scoffs] While you go to cartagena?
[Mutters] I can't believe this shit.
- Who made this?
- Brother, what do you suggest we do?
Jump out of a window?
Look, she's...
- She's important.
- To who?
To us.
[Sighs]
I take care of Elisa...
You better fucking get gacha.
[Wife chuckles]
[Speaking Spanish]
Finally, a romantic date.
It's been a long time
since we've been alone.
Mm. Just you, me...
And our bodyguard.
[Chuckles]
Like the old days when we were young
and your father watched us.
- Mm. My father adored you.
- [Softly] Yeah, right.
- [Chuckles]
- [Motorcycle idles outside]
- [Automatic gunfire]
- — [patrons screaming]
[Grunts]
[Groans]
- Garcia...
- — [chaotic chatter in Spanish]
[Panting]
[Phone ringing]
Hello? Yes.
But he's all right?
All right.
[Exhaling]
[Soft clattering]
Ana?
[Clattering continues]
Ana!
- A little bird... came into the house.
- [Chirping]
I'm helping it out.
What?
There was an assassination attempt...
On colonel carrillo.
Did someone die?
[Sighs] One of his men.
- [Thunder rumbling]
- It must be terrible,
the position you're in.
I want you to know
I think you are very brave.
I'm not brave. Not like galan.
That fear keeps you alive.
That's what none of them understand.
I will support any decision you make.
[Steve] It's been said that
nothing gives the fearful more courage...
Than another's fear.
[Audience murmuring]
Luis Carlos galan
had made a decision that cost his life.
[Approaching footsteps]
And now, it was gaviria's turn.
[Feedback]
[Speaking English]
Welcome, American press.
Tonight, I have the great pleasure
of introducing candidate césar gaviria.
- [Clears throat]
- — [camera shutters clicking]
[Speaking English] It has long been
our government's policy...
To deal with every man equally...
In the eyes of the law.
- [Hushed whispers]
- [Sighs]
[Soft chuckle]
Colombians say...
God made our land so beautiful...
It was unfair to the rest of the world.
Soto even the score...
God populated the land...
With a race of evil men.
[Gaviria on TV] The primary impediment
to a free and uninhibited future
is the violence and terror
that currently grips our beloved country.
A violence initiated by these evil men...
Will be brought to justice...
In the name of decency...
And in the memory of Luis Carlos galan.
We will extradite.
This decision...
Will not come from fear.
It has come from a clarity of judgement...
Free from the cloud of terror
that surrounds us
and obscures our view.
I can say only one thing to Colombians
in these times of peril:
There will be a future.
- Thank you.
- [Applause]
[Applause continues on TV]
[Chatter in Spanish]
[Men cheering]
[Pablo] Hello?
[Speaking Spanish]
You think you're hot shit?
You should change your satellite phone.
Who is this?
Your mother's in rionegro
with that tub of lard you call your son.
And your wife was at carrera 11 today,
shopping for clothes.
You bastard son of a bitch,
you think that...
What, you think because you're a cop
I'm afraid of you or something?
You know where my family is, fag,
well, [know where yours is, too.
- Don't forget that.
- Gonorrhea bastard son of a bitch.
Why don't you take money
like everyone else?
I could have had you living like a king.
But now, guess what?
Time to kill your dad, your mom,
your kids, your entire family,
and you should be smart enough to realize
I have each and every one of them
under watch, you fucking bastard.
Not everyone's for sale, Pablo.
You just keep hiding,
and I will find you.
Don't know when...
But I will find you.
And when I find you...
- I'm going to kill you.
- I'm going to kill you
and your entire family,
you son of a bitch!
[Line disconnects]
[Exhales]
It's war, then.
[Slow Latin guitar music plays]