_
Thank you for being here with
us, with the groom and the bride.
Come and dance with us,
everyone. Let's begin.
As they say, here we have the
most beautiful women in Laredo.
- Congratulations, Danny.
- Thank you for coming.
Congratulations.
The last time I saw Danny, he was
riding a big wheel down the sidewalk.
It means a lot to your
tía that you're here.
- Don Chucho.
- Luis, how are you?
How are you, sir?
- Javi.
- Hey, Luis.
We heard about what you did in
Colombia. We sure are proud of you.
- Thanks, Luis. Have a good night.
- You, too.
Hola, Paco.
Everyone in Laredo is at this thing.
Hey!
- Be right back, Pops.
- Mm-hmm.
- Here you go, sweetheart. You got that?
- Yummy!
Hey, Lorraine.
Javi. Heard you were back.
I mean, the whole
town's talking about it.
I had some time off.
Decided to spend it here?
Actually, I'm...
trying to quit.
Doing the Nicorette thing.
Look at you. A whole new man.
Listen, Lorraine...
I just wanted to say I've
thought about things...
and I'm real sorry about all of it.
You waited ten years
to tell me you're sorry?
I know what I did.
I was, um...
It was wrong.
I forgave you a long time ago, Javi.
The truth is, I'm grateful.
I ended up where I'm supposed to be.
Maybe we both did.
If you hadn't come into my
life and disappeared from it,
none of that would have ever happened.
Can you imagine if we
were actually married?
- Here you go, baby.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Jav.
- Randy.
- How are you?
- Good.
Yeah, I just... I just wanted to say hi.
Yeah.
You hungry?
Oh, you are getting so big.
I know you didn't like it
tonight, all the attention, but...
folks want to pay their respects.
You're a hero to them.
I'm not a hero.
Will you tell me something?
What happened to you over there?
- Dad, I don't know. It got ugly.
- But you want to go back?
When you were a kid, a little guy,
all you wanted to do
was get out of here,
out into the world.
But you didn't like what you found.
A lot of people don't.
But don't try to change it.
More likely, it'll change you.
It was right here, wasn't it?
The last time we had this conversation.
You didn't listen to me then, either.
Nope.
So, Cali.
Cali.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Sir, here you are.
Thank you.
I'm not a hero.
There were some in the hunt for Escobar.
A lot, actually.
But it's tough to see
them through all the blood.
To kill a monster, sometimes you have
to get in bed with other monsters.
If that surprises you,
pick up a history book.
It's what we do.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend,
until he becomes my enemy again.
When that happens, God help them.
The day Pablo went down, the Cali
cartel became Public Enemy Number One.
And the fact that they helped us
bring him down didn't mean shit.
Many observers fear Colombia's
other large cartel, the Cali cartel,
will now simply step up
its own drug production.
And that's exactly what happened.
While the world was focused on Escobar,
Cali's operations had
grown exponentially,
differing from their rival
in every possible way.
Where Pablo sought the love and
protection of the masses of Medellín,
these guys rubbed shoulders
with Colombia's elite
and called themselves
"the Gentlemen of Cali."
And whereas Escobar craved the spotlight,
these guys stayed in the shadows,
perfecting the game,
building complex smuggling and
distribution networks through Mexico,
Europe, and the Far East, without
leaving so much as a fingerprint.
Even the people working for them didn't
know it was Cali coke they were moving.
It was fucking Cocaine, Incorporated.
And they ran it like
a Fortune 500 company.
So, without further ado,
meet the management
team of the Cali cartel:
Pacho Herrera, head of
distribution and security.
Hello.
He led a team of young psychopaths
who would do anything he asked.
Yes. What's up?
Chepe Santacruz-Londoño.
Let's see.
Grew up with the Rodríguez brothers.
He was in charge of U.S. operations
and responsible for Cali's
crown jewel: New York City.
He actually lived there, under
an assumed name, of course.
Cartel's number two was operations
chief: Miguel Rodríguez.
Palmira's police superintendent.
Didn't we just take care of him?
- I'm talking about the new one, Arango.
- How much?
- Should I put $20,000?
- No.
Put 17.
- Seventeen?
- Yes.
Miguel watched over
all the money coming in,
and what bribes they were paying out.
And last but not least, cartel CEO, the
man with the plan: Gilberto Rodríguez.
They called him the Chess Player,
because he was always one move ahead.
They were the pinnacle of trafficking
evolution. Apex drug dealers.
And being number two
allowed them to quietly grow
into the biggest cocaine
cartel in history.
Except now, that was over.
Now that the guy that occupied
our attention was gone,
they were number one
with a fucking bullet.
And there was no chess move
that would get them out of it.
But I was looking forward
to seeing them try.
Anderson! Move all
that over to the left.
The tables are too close together.
Are you planning on
saying anything tonight?
No.
I'll speak for the both of us.
- Did you talk to the North Valley people?
- Yes.
And?
They said what they
thought I wanted to hear.
But tonight, after the
announcement, we'll know the truth.
You're more superstitious than Aunt Luz.
Hey, boss.
Is everything ready?
Yes, sir.
It took all night,
but... it's ready, sir.
You can handle it, you're young.
We're meeting Córdova.
He wants to go over the game plan.
Big night tonight, right?
Lots of company.
Gentlemen. Let's start with the obvious.
Tonight is fucking important.
The Rodríguez brothers never...
gather members of their
organization in one place.
That simply never happens. But
tonight, they're going to do it.
So we have to be sharp.
- Eyes in the back of the head, understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Jorge.
- Stay focused.
Stay on the radio. Communicate.
Tonight is his last operation.
He's leaving us to become
a fancy businessman.
Let's leave a good impression.
Maybe he'll hire us one day.
Let's go.
What do you think Gilberto
is going to announce tonight?
I think it's a move
into the Asian market.
I have no idea.
After Friday, it's not my problem.
Are you really leaving?
I promised Paola.
I promise things to my
wife every day, brother.
Relax, you'll find someone
else to make you look good.
I hope so, buddy.
Because right now, I'm
surrounded by a bunch of assholes.
Congratulations on the promotion, sir.
Tell me what you do again.
I'm the deputy country attaché.
I'll also be your driver.
I drive myself.
You know, you're kind of a big
deal around here. Since Escobar.
- Katie.
- Good morning.
Sir, can I ask?
What was Escobar like?
Never met him.
Just because we'd been focused
on Escobar the past few years
didn't mean we were completely
ignoring the Cali godfathers.
I want updates from Duffy and Lopez
on where we're at with Cornerstone.
- ASAP.
- Yes, sir.
Those are our intelligence
summaries on the Cali cartel.
I don't want summaries.
Where's everything else?
We had agents on them the whole time.
Good agents.
And recently, we had gotten lucky.
You got some kind of medical condition?
Oh. No, I got one.
The latest break in
the case against Cali
came from a joint Customs-DEA
operation called Cornerstone.
And it put a lot of mid-level Cali
guys behind bars in the States.
And while they weren't eager to help us,
you could always count on some
poor relative in Colombia...
who would do whatever it takes to
get their brother or son back home.
Who am I speaking with?
And if that sounds harsh,
that's because it is.
This is Andres, his brother.
The DEA doesn't fuck around.
And how can I help him?
Here we go.
Hey, brother. Have a seat.
Something to drink?
You're fine, brother.
Nobody out here knows us.
Cali cops don't even know we're here.
Relax. You're safe here.
Lay it on him.
Let's talk about tonight's party.
We need info on the people attending.
Cops, politicians.
- Cops and politicians?
- Yes.
Who work for the cartel. These
people are ruining your country.
And the why. Tell him.
Look, the thing is, these
people never get together in one place.
We need to know why now.
Our guess is Gilberto Rodríguez
is making some kind of
important announcement.
Understand?
If no...
bye-bye, hermano.
- How are things in Texas, Agent Peña?
- Hot.
How's the family? You know, you
had a few more weeks off coming.
Could've spent more time at home.
Yeah, well, I guess they
couldn't wait to get rid of me.
Sir, this operation in Miami,
Cornerstone, shook some leads loose.
Could be a break on Cali.
- Anyone testifying?
- No, but it put an asset in play.
Could shed some light
on their next move.
Things won't be like
Escobar, Agent Peña.
It can't be. Things
have changed down here.
New President coming in.
Gaviria put up with things
that this guy might not.
Just take it a little slowly.
Get your feet under you,
get used to the new job.
Sir, the CIA station chief...
he and I have history.
I'm hoping it won't be
an issue moving forward.
I know you and Stechner
have your differences.
- It won't be a problem.
- I'm not sure I share your confidence.
Stechner signed off on your appointment.
In fact, he wanted you back.
The CIA and the DEA need to
work together on this one.
We have the same goal.
Come in.
Hola, brother.
We were starting to
worry. Everything cool?
We were getting
worried. Everything okay?
Yes, but... I thought
someone was tailing me.
- He thinks he may have been followed.
- No, yeah, I figured.
I had to make sure I was alone.
Let's get you suited up.
Run through the plan again.
Take off your shirt. Sit.
Okay.
Ready.
We're good to go.
Look, don't you think you
should fix things with Pacho, Claudito?
He's a boss.
We're in their territory, right?
Yes. Yes.
I'll fix it tonight.
María.
For our children, and
our children's children.
That sounded great, brother.
Let me do it from the top.
No one gives a shit about your
speech. We can hear it after...
- Pacho!
- Chepe!
Come here, you crazy motherfucker.
What's up?
Look at you. How's New York?
Cold. But if you ask nicely,
the girls make up for it.
I brought you something, baby-face.
Lovely. Thanks.
It's been too long since
we were all together.
Tonight is our night,
because we've earned this.
- Gentlemen of Cali, cheers!
- Cheers!
I think there is business
to discuss first, Gilberto.
You're acting like someone
just pissed you off.
Brother, you're richer than the Pope.
But I work harder than him.
Cheers, then!
To the Pope!
Cheers.
Welcome, Chepe.
Look, Gilberto...
you know I have a personal issue
with that son of a bitch,
Claudio Salazar from North Valley.
And he's downstairs.
I would like to solve it.
Okay, Pacho.
I understand your need for revenge,
but this isn't the time to get into it.
There's too much at stake.
Well... shall we enjoy this
expensive party or what?
No. Instead, let's listen
to Gilberto's speech again.
Chepe, you motherfucker.
Look, that's Menga's chief of police.
I pay him money every month.
I pay all these people.
Well done, big shot.
It's not your money.
But I'm the one who controls it.
- Who bought you these earrings?
- Guillermo. Enough.
Sure. You're turning into Al Capone.
Shit. Get out of here.
- How are you, sir?
- Pallomari.
- Enjoying the party?
- Yes.
Yes.
Nice to see you.
Don Gilberto, good evening.
- Welcome, Mr. Mayor.
- Don Gilberto, how are you?
Good evening, Don Gilberto.
- Look, here it is.
- Motherfucker.
Hello.
- Good evening.
- Can I have aguardiente with ice?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Are you...
enjoying yourself?
Yes. Very much, thank you.
Miguel Rodríguez, nice to meet you.
María Salazar.
Thank you for having us.
Good evening.
Mr. Rodríguez would
like for his associates
to join him in the equestrian
ring for an announcement.
Please, go right ahead.
Gentlemen, please follow the
ushers towards the stables.
Thank you.
Stop there.
You must be using
some high-end equipment
if you're getting anything
in this shitty light.
Who are you?
I'm in charge of security
for the Rodríguez brothers.
See that man over there?
His name is Navegante.
Guess what he does?
Either you come with
me, or you go with him.
You understand?
Follow me.
Your name is Andrés Restrepo.
You live with your mother
in commune number 3.
You have a girlfriend in Libertadores.
Your brother is Lucho.
He's in federal custody
in the United States.
That's why you agreed
to work for the DEA.
Don't lie to me.
Andrés, you made a bad decision.
But I think you're smart
enough to realize that.
You have another decision to make,
and it's the only way to get out alive.
Leave Cali.
Don't say goodbye to your
mother or to your girlfriend.
I need you to disappear.
Associates.
Friends.
Our enemy is dead!
Our business is strong!
Together we have taken this business
to heights that our predecessors
couldn't have imagined.
But friends... there's circumstances
that we need to acknowledge.
Stoddard!
Listen to me.
The law enforcement spotlight will shine
brightly on us, as it
once did on Escobar.
And so, while we celebrate,
they will do everything they can
to take away everything we've built.
An American named Joseph Kennedy
made his fortune selling
bootlegged liquor,
but he turned that
money into legitimacy.
His children, great politicians.
And one of them was
even elected president.
Yes, gentlemen, we have been
negotiating with the authorities,
and soon we will reach an agreement.
Our organization, within six months,
will be out of the cocaine business.
We will surrender our labs,
our safe houses,
and our trafficking routes.
But gentlemen, don't make the mistake
of thinking it won't be on our terms.
Any prison sentences will be minimal.
Our money will remain ours.
Our legitimate businesses
will continue to grow.
We have six months to make
as much money as possible!
And gentlemen, as a
token of our friendship,
we'll give each of you a juicy share
of the final profits from this year.
To the bright future
we'll all soon enjoy.
For our children... and
our children's children!
- Cheers...
- Cheers!
- Cheers, gentlemen!
- What did you think?
- I think it's a great move.
- Congratulations!
- For the future!
Thank you, brother.
Thank you for coming.
What would you like?
Whiskey. Dry.
Hey, sir!
We were wondering if we
could get you a drink.
I'm good. Thanks.
Okay.
Six months.
I'm going to bleed New York dry.
Come up behind the Statue of Liberty
and fuck her right up her ass.
And then what?
We only have six months of
doing whatever the fuck we want?
Hello.
I love you, brother.
I'll see you on the dance floor.
- Can you get in the car, please?
- Why do you want to leave so early?
Because it's time, okay?
- Why are you treating me like this?
- Enough!
Get in the car.
How was everything tonight, Jorge?
Very good, sir.
Do you think we surprised them?
Yes. I think you surprised many people.
I'm told we had an uninvited
guest. What happened there?
Don't be modest.
Córdova told me.
It's your talent.
Spotting the threat, knowing
when they're going to fuck us.
It's priceless.
I'm told you want to leave.
I'm grateful to you
and your family, but...
I'm starting my own security firm.
I only wanted to stay until...
Escobar stopped being a threat.
And we are very grateful. Honestly.
You have done great things
for us over the years.
For my family. For me.
I cannot accept your resignation, Jorge.
With all due respect, I've
already made arrangements...
Arrangements can change.
Look, we didn't get where we are
by allowing good people to leave.
We will need you more than
ever in the months ahead.
It's only six months.
Can I count on you, Jorge?
Yes?
Of course, boss.
Miguel.
Pretty girl.
Displays some shaky
judgment in men, though.
Welcome back, Agent Peña.
Mazel tov on the promotion.
That extra, what, 9K a year
is really gonna come in handy.
The same.
So?
You signed off on me
coming back to Bogotá.
Did indeed.
Because you know how things work.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
To the folks back in
D.C., Escobar was a win.
Thanks.
But down here... we know
what it cost, don't we?
Medellín was a failure.
Thousands of Colombians dead,
and coke still flooding
American streets by the ton.
Oh, come on. You don't care about
American streets or dead Colombians.
What was accomplished, Agent Peña?
We do Cali differently.
No swallowing the spider
to catch the fly this time.
America's got plans for Colombia.
Another bloodbath complicates them.
So...
what's the play?
Surrender.
Cali cartel throws in the towel.
Hands over the keys to the biggest
criminal enterprise in history.
As far as I'm concerned, the
DEA can even take the credit.
And these fucking guys walk?
Negotiations are on the two-yard line,
but it has backing from Washington.
So, what the fuck do you need me for?
Well, you're the dashing DEA
agent that took down Escobar.
Always helps to have a hero on board.
Don't worry. Cali will serve some time.
Technically speaking.
And that's enough for you?
If there were any justice in this
world, Javier, you'd be in jail.
I know your guys are running
an operation on Cali tonight.
Please.
I can tell you this:
it'll come up double zeros.
These guys don't make mistakes.
You try to go after the Cali bosses,
all you'll get are more bodies.
I don't know, man.
I met him at an embassy
thing about a year ago.
Yeah?
Couldn't drink it or fuck
it, dude wasn't interested.
I hear you. I mean, he's not a bad guy.
He was in my class at the Academy.
Kid's been gone eight hours.
He better have something good.
Fucking retard.
Something's up.
Maybe he got made. Or just spooked.
Either way, we stay here tonight.
- Head out when it's light.
- Yeah.
Does Andrés have this number?
We don't know the phone
number. How could he?
Answer it.
Hello?
Hello? Who is this?
Hang up! And get away
from the fucking window!
They're fucking watching us.
Turns out that break from
Cornerstone wasn't much of a break.
Cali spent a billion
dollars a year on payoffs.
That's "billion," with a B. Which
bought eyes and ears everywhere.
Anyone visiting Cali was
ID'd and background checked
before they put their bags down.
Walk into a police
station, they know about it.
Get into a taxi, they know.
Make a phone call, forget it.
They basically owned the
fucking phone company.
Operators were told to pay
close attention to calls
that came from places of interest,
like, say, the U.S. Embassy in Bogotá.
Get a call from them...
you got flagged.
Who am I speaking with?
And from that point on...
Bye-bye, hermano.
Understand?
They were on you.
It was like the Soviet
Union with nice weather.
- Fuck!
- Even called it the Cali KGB.
- Juan.
- Here it is, sir.
Thank you.
Don Gilberto.
This just arrived.
Put them on.
Subject's name: Díaz.
Recorded at El Nacional Hotel. Room 117.
Retirement works for these
motherfuckers. They're rich.
I just bought a brand new plane.
So that motherfucker Gilberto
can shove it up his ass.
Besides, who are they to make a
deal without consulting with us?
They don't get to
surrender on our behalf.
That son of a bitch, Díaz.
I'm going to send Navegante.
Subject's name: Santos.
Recorded in zone 4.
They're going to have to give me
more than that fucking wrapping paper.
Fucking balls on the old goat to
tell me how to run my business.
That's not going to be so
easy. These men are weak.
I'll handle that one myself.
The man is an animal.
Subject name: Beltre.
I'm not going to wait for Rasguño or
Henao to snatch the good territories.
Let's organize so we can
put a move together now.
Fuck Joseph Kennedy,
whoever that asshole is.
Córdova...
El Pecas will handle that one.
You got it, sir.
Subject name: Salazar.
María, I'll be back soon. I'm
going out with some friends.
What do you mean, Claudio?
You're going out now?
Please don't look at me like that.
It's one o'clock in the morning.
Exactly, María. It's one o'clock.
Keep your voice down so
you don't wake the guests.
Fuck off, Claudio! Go with your whores!
Don't fuck with me, María, I'm tired
from clapping all night for
that motherfucker's bullshit.
Don't fuck with me.
Well... that's husband
and wife business.
Leave him out.
No, brother.
Salazar shows no respect.
Better safe than sorry.
Honey. What time is it?
It's late.
Go back to sleep.
How was work?
Fine.
I spoke with Miguel.
And?
He asked me not to leave.
Just for a little while.
How long?
I'm asking you how long.
- Six months.
- Six months?
What did you tell him?
What could I tell him? It's six months.
We've talked about this for a long time.
You're telling me we can't start our new
lives because we have
to wait six months?
You know what? I don't think you
really want to leave this job.
- How can you say that?
- You think I'm an idiot?
You like working for them.
It's become your life, Jorge.
You are my life. The girls are my life.
- What do you want me to do?
- Don't say another word.
- It's six months, not six years.
- Not another word.
She owns a spa.
Let's go. We should go!
What can I get you?
A bottle of aguardiente, and
play "Dos Gardenias" for me.
Gladly, Don Pacho.
Thank you.
Please, Claudio...
accept this as a token of respect.
To let bygones be bygones.
You know what, Pacho?
I think our differences are in the past.
I'll be right back to share it with you.
Excuse me.
Please.
- Claudito.
- And now... the bottle.
Go ahead.
Claudito!
- Pacho, motherfucker!
- Pacho, please.
Don't do this. Don't do this to me.
Please, Pacho.
Pacho.
Pacho, please! Pacho, wait!
Please, let's talk. Pacho!
Motherfucker. He didn't
do anything to you.
Pacho, you motherfucker!
Wait, Pacho! Pacho, son of a bitch!
Pacho!
Please, no!
Son of a bitch!
Pacho, son of a bitch!
No! No, no, no!
Son of a bitch, Pacho!
Motherfucker!
Claudio!
When Pablo Escobar killed you, he
wanted everyone to know about it.
But the Gentlemen of Cali...
they did that differently, too.
They wrapped your body with chicken
wire and dumped you in the Cauca River.
When you bloated and your body expanded,
the wire cut you into little pieces...
for fish food.
Not very "gentlemanly,"
but it did the trick.
And that's all they wanted.
You and whatever your beef
with them was... vanished.
Forever.
No body, no crime.
No murder statistics...
no problem.
I suppose that's for the best.
It makes it easier
to look the other way.
To let them fucking slide.
To pretend that these guys weren't just
as evil as the guy
that came before them.
And to a country that had
seen enough of the drug war...
maybe that worked for Colombia.
It certainly worked
for the Cali godfathers.
Because God forbid anyone
thinks they're the bad guys.