PUSSY
Leave it there.
Enjoy your meal.
Hi, brother, it's me.
How are you doing?
Better if I knew how this happened.
Gilberto, someone betrayed us.
Where the fuck were those pigs we pay?
It was an American operation.
It was the DEA.
Our friends knew nothing about it.
Unless our friends have
been lying to us all along.
Maybe they need a reminder
what all that money was for.
Relax, Miguel.
My situation will be rectified soon.
The truth is that things
are getting more complicated.
And our friends in the North Valley
need reassurance.
You need to set a meeting with Henao.
Compliment him.
- On what?
- Doesn't matter. Offer him something.
He likes tequila. Have a bottle ready.
Tell him... this is just a small setback.
In the meantime,
business goes on as usual.
Increase your personal security.
The Americans will come after you next.
Your freedom is our best leverage,
brother.
Gilberto, this is getting dangerous.
What if there's a leak?
There may be.
Find out.
I need to go, brother. I love you.
I love you too, brother.
Justice can be hard to find.
And a man as powerful
as Gilberto Rodríguez
won't stay in custody for long.
If you want to keep him behind bars,
you need someone to testify.
Yes, sir. I'm on it.
I'm working on a high-level target.
I suggest you work fast,
because without it,
nothing else will matter.
We went through the machine, sir.
We've got nothing.
So what am I supposed to do with that?
What does this mean?
If somebody sold us out,
we'd know about it.
Like you knew about the raid?
Look, gentlemen...
I want to know why my brother
is sitting in a fucking cell.
And if any one of us is involved in this,
I want to know by the end of the day.
Of course. Consider it done, sir.
Miguel's paranoid.
Maybe they used one of their spy planes
and spotted Gilberto from space.
You're not taking this seriously.
Miguel doesn't think they got lucky.
He thinks there's a leak.
And the system would tell us
about the leak.
This is about the surrender, right?
You're worried your retirement plans
are ruined now.
Listen to me. People love drama,
brother. You know that.
This isn't drama. He wants names.
And there's no reason to think
they couldn't be ours, Carlo.
We designed the system.
Mr Cordova.
So? Anything good?
Just a bunch of shit-talking.
Gossip. Typical.
And what about internally?
Anyone suspicious you've flagged?
No, not really.
Truth is, I have no idea
who would rat these guys out.
I want to hear everything you've flagged
all the same. Quickly.
Yes, sir. I'll get that right away.
These guys were supposed to have
all this under control.
But it's clear they don't.
I thought those guys
were supposed to surrender.
Does this mean it's not happening?
Somebody tipped off the Americans,
stabbed us in the back.
Where was his fucking security team?
What do they pay them for?
They better do something quick,
or else it's going to be
every man for himself.
You have many powerful allies,
Don Gilberto.
Your situation pains them deeply.
We're confident this will soon be
behind us. The surrender will proceed.
But we need to wait.
It's a matter of time.
Wait for what?
For the government to do something
they already agreed to? Fuck.
What did Medina say?
Currently, we don't have an official
position from Santiago Medina.
Why not?
Because we're waiting on his office
to confirm a meeting.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You haven't talked to him yet?
You're waiting on his office
to confirm a meeting?
I don't wait on him!
He waits on me!
You go to his office and fix this mess!
And remind him who the fuck
Gilberto Rodríguez is!
For fuck's sake!
Open this damn thing!
Nicolás, your father needs to understand
his arrest changes things.
It's political now.
Dad?
Sometimes you have to put on
a little show.
Helps bring the best out of people.
- I need to talk to Medina.
- I don't want you anywhere near this.
Dad, the circle is too big.
Medina won't meet anyone he can't trust.
He won't trust the lawyers.
But he will trust you?
Yes, I'm your son.
That's right.
And you'll obey my wishes.
You want something to drink?
I never refuse.
That's a great shirt, no?
That pocket...
on the left.
Where the heart is.
Hey, this situation with Gilberto,
what a disgrace, huh?
After all your family's done
for this city. For this country.
Just the gringos meddling
where they shouldn't.
But our friends in Bogotá
are working to...
rectify the situation.
Business proceeds as usual, right?
And how does this clerical error
affect the timeline of the surrender?
As I said...
this was just a mistake,
nothing more.
Glad to hear that.
I see a lot of new faces.
Did you notice that?
The woman, the Salazar girl?
The fear.
Miguel was scared.
These guys are in big trouble.
Little early for number three, no?
The fuck else am I supposed to do
around here?
You didn't have to come.
Who else was gonna watch your back?
You gonna tell me
what went down in Juárez?
I told you...
we talked.
The Mexican made you an offer.
Didn't he?
Yes.
A pretty good one, too.
He says we're getting out
at the wrong time.
Maybe he's right.
Gilberto's in jail.
Maybe this is fate.
No. The bill, please.
Compliments of the gentleman.
Thank you, but I don't...
The bill.
And they don't appear
on the next flights either?
Motherfucking gringos never got
on a plane back to Bogotá.
- Our friend with the badge lied to us.
- Or he made a mistake.
There are no mistakes.
Hey. Here he comes.
There he is, the fucking bastard.
I would have gladly met you
in the usual place.
That's what you're worried about?
How about earning the money
we pay you to keep our bosses out of jail?
- You couldn't give a fuck about that.
- The fuck you want from me?
Logistics, planning, the dummy raid.
All that shit came out of Bogotá.
By the time we knew
what they were up to...
Martínez had already been
in Gilberto's house for 30 minutes,
you useless piece of shit.
You know what else is odd?
It looks like the DEA never left Cali,
and you were the one who confirmed.
You. Only you confirmed those two
fucking gringos took the plane to Bogotá.
Do you know where you are?
You want to hang me out to dry with
your boss? Do you know where you are?
I asked the Americans how they found
Gilberto's house. Know what they told me?
They followed someone there.
I know it wasn't me.
Fucking Calderón.
What he said made sense.
The DEA followed someone
to Gilberto's house.
It must be Pallomari. The DEA knows
who he is and where he works.
They must've come back
and tailed him to Gilberto.
Didn't you say you drove Pallomari
to Gilberto's that night?
It could just as easily
have been me driving him.
Yeah, but it wasn't, was it?
You think Miguel will let this slide?
Not a fucking chance.
Jorge, if this thing comes back on me,
it comes back on you,
and then we're both fucked.
The only thing we need is a name,
and we have it.
We have to get on the same page here.
Calderón told us those fuckers from
the DEA got on a plane to Bogotá, right?
He burned us. He's the one
responsible for what happened.
He's a dirty cop...
who takes money from a drug cartel.
But you and me, we're brothers.
Let me cut to the chase.
My father still wants to retire.
I didn't realise you were taking such
an active role in your father's affairs.
No other choice when friends
don't return our lawyer's calls.
Of course.
Well, then, tell your father
there is still a path
to what he wants most.
No one here is happy
with the current predicament.
The DEA blindsided all of us,
and it's been difficult
to carry out our old deal.
"Old deal"?
Politics is about appearances.
For us, it's extremely difficult
to accept the surrender terms of a man
who's already in prison.
That just looks bad.
But different terms, new terms...
What do you say?
So what did you find out?
The DEA team Calderón was escorting
never left Cali.
He reported that they had.
What do you think, Jorge?
It was a mistake.
Born of incompetence.
The DEA got lucky
and Calderón took the bait.
Well, we're not paying for incompetence.
Besides, that doesn't explain
how they found my brother.
How did they get that information?
Was that also Calderón?
It's unlikely.
It's possible the DEA used
some high-end aerial surveillance.
From here on out,
keep an eye on Calderón.
Limit what we tell him.
No more lapses in security.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Jorge.
It's either him or us.
What if they kill him?
They wouldn't kill a cop.
But they can question him.
And then what? What?
By the time they get to it,
this shit will all be over.
Good afternoon. Someone is here
for you, Mrs Jurado. A Mr Eliot Ness.
Don't you even want to know
what he said?
How dare you disregard my wishes!
Nobody was going to get into a room
with Medina, and I did...
I don't want you involved.
I won't even discuss it.
The old deal is dead.
But we can make a new one,
with certain adjustments.
Motherfuckers.
Adjustments how?
There has to be some jail time.
For you, Uncle Miguel,
Pacho and Chepe.
- Three years.
- Three years? No chance.
You surrender your illegal assets,
do the three years,
and the legitimate assets, the cash,
the business, will all be retained.
That's not the deal.
And you won't speak of this again.
Dad, stop being so stubborn!
You don't get to surrender.
You are in jail.
You are a narcotrafficker.
No politician is going to stand up
and say, "Let him go,"
no matter how much money
you've put in his pocket.
But, son, it's three years...
It's not the old deal,
but it's a good one.
The best we're going to get.
But there's one loose end.
Medina is worried about his exposure.
More specifically,
the accountant... Pallomari.
He knows too much.
The Americans are back
on the accountant's office,
hoping he shows.
Knowing that idiot, he might.
If that's all they've got,
then they don't have much.
Stay on them.
Find out where they sleep at night.
All right.
Hey, boss. You doing OK?
You sound tired.
Yeah. I'm fine.
Keep me posted.
- How was the science test?
- Good.
Daddy! Daddy!
My princess. Hello, my princesses.
How are you all?
Hello. What are you doing here?
Hi, my love.
Was it your turn or mine
to pick up the girls?
Yours. I was in the neighbourhood.
Just wanted to see how my girls are doing.
- Daddy, today we have piano lessons.
- I know, my love.
My little virtuosos.
- And you? Everything OK?
- I'm fine.
I just felt like I needed to see my girls.
That's why I came.
Excuse me.
Looks like I have to go.
Would you excuse me?
- Girls... I love you.
- Bye.
Bye, be good.
- Where are you?
- What can I do for you, David?
My dad called a meeting.
Top personnel.
What do you mean, a meeting?
We just had one.
Well, we're having another one.
2611 Avenida 14. Out by Jamundí.
See you there.
It's Carlo Cordova.
Leave a message.
Carlo, I just talked to David.
Are you on your way to the meeting?
Call me.
It's Carlo Cordova.
Leave a message.
I'm sitting there,
enjoying my dick getting sucked,
when all of the sudden she stops.
I open my eyes
and I ask her, "What's up?"
She's all quiet, looking at me like this.
Not a word.
I'm like, "What the fuck?"
I turn to see Toque.
Fuck, he has a gun pointed at him.
Like this.
And the other girl,
the one with the gun, says to me,
"Give me the money,
or she bites your dick off."
- So what did you do?
- I gave her the fucking money!
I even tipped her, Pacho.
You don't mess around with that.
- You want some ice?
- Sure.
I'm having a great time.
I'm heading to Juárez tomorrow.
Got some business with my partners.
What am I going to tell them, Pacho?
I want to give them an answer.
Some good news.
My turn to tell you a story, Amado.
About the time my father found me
in my room with a boy.
Hey, I never judged you for that stuff.
My father told me I wasn't a man,
that I'd never be one.
- It was the last time he spoke to me.
- What a fucking bastard.
For a long time, I thought he was right.
Even after I started working
for Gilberto and Miguel.
Up until the day some motherfucker
told them I was a faggot.
And that it was a mistake
to let me be part of the business.
You know what they did?
They made me a partner.
Gilberto, Miguel and Chepe,
they are my family.
I can't just leave them
when they need me the most.
What can I say?
I admire your loyalty.
You're one of a kind.
There you go.
You better get inside.
Don't want to be late.
Has your dad arrived?
No, not yet.
Let's go.
Let me go, asshole!
Let me go, motherfucker!
You don't have the balls!
Let me go!
Up!
You motherfucker.
What the fuck did you tell them,
motherfucker?
Gilberto getting caught
wasn't down to me.
You feel so safe, motherfucker.
When it's your turn...
He was a tiger.
Let's go.
What the fuck is this?
Tell him what you did.
Tell him.
Tell him where we caught you.
While you were visiting
your wife and children,
this fucking rat was
on his way to the airport.
With his wife, bags packed.
About to leave you holding the blame.
Your friend, Jorge.
You had your bitch follow me?
- What did you say?
- Me and my children?
You should be thankful,
motherfucker.
It's why you're standing there
instead of sitting next to him.
You're making a big mistake, David.
I don't give a fuck what you think.
He's a loyal man.
He always has been.
- He's a piece of shit, Jorge.
- He's a good man and loyal.
- A good man? Then why was he running?
- What are you doing?
- This is a good man...
- He's a fucking snitch!
Look at me.
Sophia is inside.
She's inside that room.
Don't let them touch her.
Don't let them put a hand on Sophia.
She has nothing to do with this, brother.
These fucking bastards are crazy...
David, no!
Your friend was right, Jorge.
Go check on Sophia.
My brother is in prison
because we were weak.
Because mistakes were made.
Because we allowed people
to be dishonest with us.
These are the consequences.
Mistakes will not be tolerated.
Jorge, when he tried to run,
he proved he was willing
to turn against us, all of us.
Men with nothing to hide don't run, right?
Now, I trust you can take over
Cordova's responsibilities.
As our new head of security, Jorge.
What do you think?
I'm glad I can count on you.
My little girl, you're going to eat
a little bit of salad, OK?
Vera is going to teach you.
Look how much she ate.
Just a bit, sweetie.
Please, just eat a little bit.
- Hi. I thought you'd be home later.
- Daddy's here!
Give me a minute.
Attention passengers:
Now boarding flight 1935 to Curaçao.