- Agent Peña?
- What's this?
It's from upstairs.
Oh, I get a card.
Oh, CIA.
"Congratulations,
Central Intelligence Agency."
This is, uh... this is blowing up
a little bit more than we expected, no?
Well, hopefully,
the son of a bitch rots in jail.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
We gotta transfer him first.
- I forbade you to leak this.
-  How do you know it was us?
- Escobar has a lot of enemies.
- 'Course it was you.
Whoever did this, it doesn't really
matter now. What's done is done.
Ambassador, like you said, this is
a Colombian matter. What do we care?
I'm filing a report with the
Board of Personal Conduct in Washington.
- Ambassador--
- Good, report to Washington.
'Cause if something isn't done,
every American down here
associated with the government
is gonna look like a fool, including you.
I wasn't finished. Until further notice,
you're both suspended.
Go home.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Ahh!
Hm.
Success.
Sure, it cost me a suspension,
but who cares?
I just call it a week's paternity leave.
I was ready to crack a beer
and watch Escobar's endgame on TV.
See, because of me and Peña,
the Colombian government
was sending in the army.
Not the cops,
but the fucking army.
There was no way that Escobar
was getting out of this one.
But, then again, in Colombia...
nothing goes down
the way you think it will.
The car was
outside the garage, still idling,
the keys still in the ignition.
- I've called his phone 20 times.
- Did you call embassy security?
- No, I wanted to talk to you first.
- Good. Don't.
What? Why not?
Nothing. I just... I don't wanna
ring any alarms before I check things out.
- What are you guys up to?
- Connie...
Just try to relax, OK?
I'm sure everything's fine.
I'm gonna take care of this.
I'll find out where he is, all right?
Look, I'll make you a drink.
What are you doing back here?
- I forgot my socks.
-  I want you out in five minutes.
Son of a bitch. These Colombians
are knee-deep in a shit storm.
We gotta talk.
Back here.
What? You get a hooker pregnant?
I think Agent Murphy got snatched.
I checked all area hospitals,
police stations.
We were pursuing leads
on the Cali cartel.
It could be related to that,
or it could be Escobar.
Did you report it
to the Regional Security Office?
If I tell the ROS,
it becomes a five-alarm fire,
and whoever has him
might panic.
If it is Escobar,
he's dead already.
Well, can you check your sources?
See what comes up?
Jesus Christ.
Let me see what I can do.
Checked my sources with the Colombian
military. Nobody knows jack shit.
So no indication Escobar had anything
to do with Murphy's disappearance?
It's time to sound the alarm.
Just hold off for a couple of hours, OK?
We call out the troops,
he ends up dead like Diana Turbay.
Thanks.
Mm.
Where have you been?
You don't even answer your phone?
Sorry, I've, uh...
I've been working on it.
What the fuck does that mean?
Doing what?
I'm sorry.
Just trying to hold it together.
God, I just wanna go home.
I want my husband back.
- Do you think he's alive, Javi?
- Yeah.
No.
You're just not sure he's dead.
Now what?
I'm sorry, Ambassador.
We have a situation.
Damn right we do.
Hey, partner.
Remember how I told you
that no one in their right mind
would ever kill a DEA agent?
Well, to be honest,
after they snatched me,
I'd forgotten that, myself.
But then, I calmed down and realized
that if they wanted to kill me,
they would've blown my brains out
right in front of my house.
This... was something different.
I figured this was Escobar
knowing that they were coming to get him,
and grabbing
a get-out-of-jail-free card: me.
Sit.
Man, you fucked up. You think
that they're gonna make a trade for me?
No. No!
They're gonna storm that bullshit fuckin'
prison and blow his fuckin' head off!
I'm sorry
you were taken against your will,
but I knew you wouldn't meet willingly,
given your last meeting with Navegante.
Mr. Herrera, I'm glad to see
your Cali cartel is doing so well,
but you've made a huge mistake.
I don't see it that way.
I know you like whiskey, but I'm taking
the liberty of making you a cocktail.
I just learned how to do a really
interesting passion fruit daiquiri.
That's wonderful,
but I don't want your fuckin' daiquiri.
You're free to leave anytime.
We are a long way from Bogotá.
Fine. I'm leaving.
I'll show myself out.
I thought you might
like to see some pictures I have.
Several weeks ago, a wire tap caught you
calling Colonel Horacio Carrillo
to ID a location
where Pablo's sicarios were gathering.
Two hours later, they were dead.
Along with an innocent woman.
OK.
Poison will be at La Dispensaria
at around midnight with his crew.
Who's your contact at the embassy?
Did you know she had two kids?
What do you think our newspapers
will think of that?
Our government doesn't take too kindly
to American-backed death squads.
I could blackmail you
with these pictures.
You'd lose your career at the DEA,
go to jail...
maybe here in Colombia.
But don't worry.
I won't ask you or Javier Peña
to cross any line
you haven't already crossed.
So you think the DEA and Cali cartel
would be a good match.
There are many,
in every segment of Colombia,
who have been persecuted
by Pablo Escobar.
The families of Moncada and Galeano,
the families of judges and police...
people with resources
who need to be unified.
They want vengeance.
- And you'll help them get it?
- With your help.
I can't make any commitments right now.
But I can tell you this:
When Pablo goes down,
and he will go down...
you'll hear a knock at your door,
and it'll be me.
You haven't tried my daiquiri.
That Herrera's a pretty good host.
Makes a mean cocktail, gives you
door-to-door service right to the embassy.
- What did Herrera say?
- What'd he say?
What'd he say?
You fuckin' gave him that information.
He's got pictures on me,
he's got tape on me, Javi.
Answer me.
- What?
- Did you give that shit to Herrera?
- Do you think I would do that to you?
- Are you playing with Cali, Javi?
That your version of "all in"?
I got one goal: get Escobar.
That's not an answer.
Who gave him the fucking photos?
Hey.
See you around, Jav.
I'm gonna go call my wife.
- All clear!
It's OK... it's OK.
It's OK.
Steve...
I just wanna go home.
This is home.
Less than an hour
after Escobar escaped La Catedral,
word had spread all over Colombia
that war was coming again.
But this time would be different.
This time,
there would be no surrender...
no negotiations...
no deals.
This time...
we were gonna kill him.
Escobar said, "Better a grave
in Colombia than a cell in the US."
Well, guess what, motherfucker?
That works for me.
doubled subs eliminated by sixsnobs