Sir?
The telephone recordings you requested.
From La Picota.
Excuse me.
He killed the DEA rat.
He's beating the shit
out of the North Valley.
What do you want me to say?
-Miguel's surprised us, brother.
-Look, Pacho,
I'm proud too of how my brother's
handled things while I'm gone.
But we all have limitations.
I led our organization for 20 years,
always taking care of all of you.
I know. But the thing is, I don't think
I'm ready to surrender, Gilberto.
Besides, I still have to find the Salazars
and resolve the situation.
There will be time for that, Pacho.
It is important to keep
a cool head right now.
Until we finish the negotiations,
it's necessary
that we are all on the same page.
A fucking fridge?
A message from Miguel Rodriguez Orejuela.
Son of a bitch! What's that smell?
The surveillance team we sent to Cali.
Call me
General, Miguel Rodriguez
is on the 7th floor.
His son, David,
doubled security after the raid,
and, well, there's no way
to get inside that building
without attracting attention.
We have to get Miguel to move.
-And we capture him while they're moving.
-Exactly.
How?
Leave that to me.
I'll stay here in Bogota.
You coordinate the operation in Cali.
But it has to be today.
There's no time.
Today.
Agent Peña, after our last operation,
my superior came to see me.
He was very diplomatic, but he made sure
to remind me of all I've achieved.
And that it could all be taken away.
What worries me is that the only people
who could do more damage to the country
than the cartel,
are the sons of bitches they've bought.
And I don't want to risk bringing Miguel
Rodriguez to jail through the front door
so they can let him out the back,
you understand?
General...
you put him in jail
and I'll make sure he stays there.
All right.
Let's do it.
Let's hope the bastard
enjoys his last day of freedom.
All right, gentlemen,
Miguel is here in his apartment.
Protected by a small army.
Once I get the signal, I'll organize
a convoy and come down this way.
Carrera 15, until we get here.
There we will turn and go down 25th street
until Santa Rita.
How many cars?
Four SUVs. I'll be in the first
and Miguel will be in the third.
I think that gives him an opportunity
to escape.
I've got something
far more aggressive in mind.
I don't want to give that son of a bitch
the opportunity to end up anywhere
other than the back of my truck.
You flush him out of the apartment,
and I'll take him down.
Sir, please believe me!
I swear it on my family, sir.
No! No, sir! Please wait!
I already told you the truth, sir!
Play it again. From the beginning.
But what for?
All you're going to hear is a man yelling
because he's being tortured, nothing more.
I told you, maybe he said something
that will help us nail the motherfucker.
But didn't we already catch the mole?
I'm going to tell you something.
I hate that motherfucker Salcedo
with all of my heart.
But what's your problem with him?
He may be clean.
The problem I have with him is that
he's a fucking lying son of a bitch.
And I know it.
Now start it from the fucking beginning.
You hear?
Put all the clothes you want to take
on the bed.
Put any jewellery and valuables
under the clothes.
Anyone comes in,
it will look like you just did the wash.
When it's time,
put everything in the suitcases, okay?
Good. One more thing.
Come with me, please.
Paola, don't freak out.
-Wait, Jorge, wait.
-It's only a precaution, Paola.
Wow.
My love.
Take it, Paola.
Like this. Hold on tight.
Here's the safety. Now it's ready...
and now it's not.
That's the only thing you need to do.
If anyone you don't know
comes through that door, use it.
-Okay?
-Yes.
My love, you can do this.
You can do this.
I'll leave it here.
I can do this.
It's my only choice.
As soon as the DEA gets here,
you go with them. You can't wait for me.
What about you?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Don't worry. Everything will be okay.
What I'm about to tell you
is a little delicate.
But it concerns all of our futures.
I've been concerned about my brother,
Gilberto.
The thing is, he's been speaking to some
of our partners without telling me.
Undermining me.
Making it very difficult
to run this business.
So...
I decided to have
my brother's phone tapped.
What the fuck are you saying, Miguel?
We don't tap each other's phones.
I know.
But in this case, it was necessary.
I heard you two talking to him
about the surrender.
And you heard something
I wasn't supposed to say or what?
What is this shit, Miguel?
Now we can't talk to Gilberto?
Of course you can.
You're not going to make
a fucking speech now.
No, I'm not going to make a speech,
but I will tell you one important thing.
The surrender was Gilberto's dream.
It was never ours.
Besides, we all know
how good Gilberto is at promising things
when he wants something from us.
What did he promise you?
New York.
But did he tell you when? How?
You have shit.
Chepe...
here you have a passport,
a new social security number,
and the addresses to two labs
in New York...
so you can rebuild what's ours.
And what did he promise you?
The Salazars?
Here's the location
where the Salazars are hiding.
So you can avenge your brother.
Henao gave it to me.
So the North Valley war is over or what?
That's right. In our favour.
Of course, first I had to send
that motherfucker a little gift.
Look, Miguel...
I think you need to tell us the truth.
No fucking lies.
What the fuck have you done
with the real Miguel Rodriguez Orejuela?
Surrender's for pussies.
Listen up... Mr. Wiretap.
Never ever touch my phone.
Understood?
Don Miguel.
Sir.
-What?
-Excuse me.
I just heard DEA agents are back in Cali.
Any update on the accountant?
Well, we're still looking, but no luck.
Motherfucker.
This has to be the place
Enrique told us about.
Look there.
See if you can find anything
about Salcedo.
Motherfuckers.
I know this isn't the ideal situation
for you and your team,
but I appreciate your cooperation
with the transition.
Of course.
I'll put you in touch with the police
investigative team I've assigned.
I'll give you the phone number.
And they'll stop by for the files
this afternoon.
Thank you.
One more thing, Minister.
It almost slipped my mind.
What's that?
I received some information regarding
Miguel Rodriguez's hideout.
It seems he's in a building in Cali.
It's called Hacienda Buenos Aires.
Well done, Agent. Well done.
I'll get this information to my men
right away.
No, that won't be necessary.
I've already got my men there
preparing for the raid today.
Excuse me?
Jorge?
Don Miguel wants to see you right away.
Coming.
Sir.
Just got off the phone
with our friend in Bogotà.
Seems those DEA agents
are here for a reason.
He says they're planning a raid.
We can take you to Santa Rita.
-Do it.
-Of course, sir.
We got some news.
Get the cars ready.
Good morning.
Hello.
You seem happy.
Defence Minister Fernando Botero...
is working with the Cali cartel.
-What makes you so sure?
-Played a little "telephone."
Something I said to him that only I know
was repeated in Cali.
Normally, I'd say you're crazy, but...
I'm going to show you something.
-Those Curacao bank files you gave me.
-Yes.
I had a bank source help me
dig through them.
And?
What's interesting is who's listed
alongside Franklin Jurado's name
on this account.
Santiago Medina. Who's he?
He's an art collector.
But rumour is he does some money laundering
for upper class Colombians.
Cleans their cash through fancy charities,
dummy corporations,
campaign contributions.
Guess who Santiago Medina worked with
on the last presidential campaign?
Fernando Botero.
There's nothing.
Have you thought about the possibility
that Salcedo is telling the truth?
Just because you don't like him doesn't
mean everything he says is bullshit.
That's got nothing to do with it.
There's plenty of people I don't like
but still trust. Like you.
Dario. You see that camera?
Maybe it caught something.
Come on.
I found this one from last week.
Play it.
Fast forward.
Faster.
Hit play.
And stop... stop it there.
See? These motherfuckers
must be the DEA, right?
Keep going.
His transport arrived.
We're in position.
I'll let you know when they come out.
Despite how difficult this week has been,
we're making it out of the storm.
It would seem so, sir.
I've been thinking about the promise
I made to you.
Six months...
until you open your security business.
That's right, sir.
It's even possible
that I'll invest in your business.
What do you think about that?
It would be an honour to have your support.
Can I help you with your bag?
No, this is almost ready.
Take those. I'll see you downstairs.
Of course, sir.
Keep going.
Stop it there.
No, that's Enrique. Keep going.
Open it.
Salcedo is downstairs.
We're waiting for Miguel.
Copy that.
Stop. Go back.
Go back.
More.
There.
-Isn't that Enrique again?
-Can you get this shit to stop shaking?
Man...
Man, you were right.
You were right, man.
I'm going to kill that motherfucker.
Take this.
Careful with this.
Fuck, he's not answering.
Here.
Thank you.
-Hello.
-Dad.
It's him.
It's that bastard, Salcedo.
David, again with this bullshit?
When will you stop?
Listen to me.
I found the DEA hideout. The one Enrique
told us Salcedo knew about.
And on the same street, there's a hotel
with a camera pointed towards the street.
We checked the video with Dario,
and we saw the DEA, Enrique,
and that motherfucker Salcedo, Dad.
Are you sure about that?
One hundred percent. I checked the plates.
Dad, think about it.
He's trying to take you out of a safe
place so they can catch you in the open.
It's a trap, Dad.
Dad...
I'll call you back.
Jorge. Don Miguel asked me to tell you
that he needs your help with something
before we leave.
Jorge?
Yes.
NO SERVICE
-Tell Serrano we're going in.
-Let's go.
General!
We have to go in now! Out!
You need me, Don Miguel?
Take a seat.
All right, but we should be going.
I think we're going to be
a little safer here.
You fucking son of a bitch!
What is this? What's going on, Don Miguel?
Don Miguel!
Look how diligent! Very--
Girls, whatever happens,
you don't leave the room, all right?
-All right.
-Don't come out for any reason.
Cover his mouth.
Don Miguel!
Please!
Go to your room.
Let's go through the back.
I believed you over my own son.
You took my money.
I let you protect my family.
You listened to our private conversations,
you son of a bitch.
I gave you all my trust.
And what did it mean to you? Shit.
Nothing.
You're an animal.
You're a little wharf rat.
Not even that.
A rat has more dignity than you.
Do you know what I've just done,
motherfucker?
I told David to go to your house...
and kill your wife and daughters,
you motherfucker!
Mrs. Salcedo.
Ma'am, please open up.
Girls, stop folding, please.
Back here. Go back here.
Back! Here.
I want to talk, Mrs. Salcedo. Open up.
Keep shooting.
I know you're in there, Mrs. Salcedo.
Don Miguel! The DEA is in the building.
Get Maria and the boy into a car.
Sir, you should come as well.
Get the fuck out of here!
Give me that shit. Get out. Motherfucker!
Fucking rat, die!
Go!
Don Miguel, we have to leave right now!
Don Miguel! Don Miguel, no!
-Don Miguel, we have to go!
-Kill him!
Go out the other door.
Hurry up, damn it!
Miguel Rodriguez...
you're under arrest.
-General.
-Agent Peña.
I've got Miguel Rodriguez, handcuffed,
at my side.
And Salcedo?
Get in.
-Hello, my love. Are you all right?
-Yes, and you? The girls?
Yes. Yes, the girls are all right.
They're scared, but all right.
We did it, Paola.
Yes. Yes, we did it.
I'll be with you soon, my love.
Got a minute?
-We were wrong.
-Wrong?
Yes. I checked
the Samper campaign financials
and I found that in July of last year,
they had serious losses.
They needed money
for travel, ads, etcetera.
And they got $6 million.
Just happens to be the amount
Botero took from the cartel.
So...
-he wasn't laundering the money.
-No.
That money stayed in the campaign.
It was a contribution.
We've been talking, Mr. Rodriguez.
There's a lot of interest on our part.
If there's interest on your end...
Yes. Of course.
POLICE
We would need to know what we would
be getting for our contribution.
Of course.
As you know, our goal is to reward
our supporters once we take office.
The terms we discussed
are certainly reasonable.
Then you have our support.
-How would we organize the payments?
-We should get together and discuss it.
I know it's difficult.
But you get used to being here.
You bastard.
Look, brother...
let's put the past behind us.
I know this isn't
what you wanted to hear...
but, regardless, we are winning.
I don't know what the fuck we're winning,
Gilberto.
By catching you, brother,
they did us a favour.
Now Pacho and Chepe
have to turn themselves in.
That's the only way
we'll be able to negotiate the terms.
Well, you better be right,
because I'm not staying in this shithole.
I heard about Miguel.
I'm going to surrender.
And Chepe too.
But before that,
I have one last thing I have to finish.
Gentlemen.
Mr. Santacruz,
we have to ask you to come with us.
You're under arrest.
There's room at the bar.
Make yourself comfortable.
Please, Mr. Santacruz.
You have to come with us.
Who do you think called the police?
Here's how this is gonna go.
When I'm done...
when I'm fucking ready...
then you can give me a ride to jail.
Take a seat.
Eat this. Come on.
Order whatever you want.
Come on.