Let’s get down!
This is going to sell better
than the original.
The time has come
to take Pablo’s money.
—Search.
—What’s happening?
Look at that.
Your prize dog didn’t even stop.
There’s no coke in that boat.
Come here.
It’s blended
right into the fibreglass hull.
Give me the money … the cash!
Looks like you got taken
with this dog, brother.
—Hold this a moment.
—Oh, Marquessa, my dear …
It’s OK, it’s OK.
—Are you fucking crazy?
—What?
It’s my dog.
Son of a bitch.
What happened?
You want to know what happened?
Go look.
Pablo?
—Pablo, we have a motherfucking problem.
—Bastard murderer.
—He killed the dog.
—I don’t give a shit.
If we don’t resolve this problem,
we’re gonna all get murdered.
—Come on, man.
—Son of a bitch.
Let’s see …
This is the problem?
People are watching us, Pablo.
They’re asking themselves
how two small businessmen
suddenly came up with so much cash.
Gustavo, brother …
just launder the money.
Make it look legitimate, that’s all.
Isn’t that what Al Capone did?
—Al Capone?
—Al Capone.
You’re a dumbass, Pablo.
—Al Capone is a terrible example.
—Why?
Because Al Capone
never had this much cash.
This is too much to launder.
Well then …
let’s buy a bigger washing machine.
You’re spending too much cash, Pablo.
You have Picassos, Dalís, farms,
houses, apartments, boats, planes, cars.
I told you we have to fly low.
If you keep spending like that,
you’re going to end up in Forbes Magazine.
And if that happens,
the government is going to have our asses.
Enough, Gustavo, enough.
What do you want me to say?
Bury it.
—How’s that?
—Bury the cash.
And cut the bullshit.
Go on, pussy.
Hey, Mom.
—I’m praying, Pablo.
—Just for a second.
Sit.
It isn’t very comfortable, Pablito.
I’ll buy you another sofa later.
Wouldn’t it be better
if you put all this money in a bank, son?
No.
All bankers are bandits.
Really, honey?
Forbes Magazine says …
… that the narcos have more money
than the richest capitalist pig
in this country.
Let me see?
If we kidnap someone in their family,
what are they going to do?
Call the police?
Commander.
It says here that Gacha, “The Mexican,”
is the ninth richest man in the world.
I say we kidnap his son.
He’s a psycho maniac, comrade.
Plus, he’s bought off half the military.
Well, the Ochoa brothers
are number 14 on the list.
Their sister Marta goes to the university.
How about her?
I like that more. The Ochoas are soft.
Wait a second!
What about Pablo Escobar?
He’s the richest of them all.
Escobar gives money to the poor.
You’re right.
Escobar is a man of the people.
He’s all right with me.
OK, then.
Let’s do the Ochoas.
Good afternoon.
Mr and Mrs Murphy.
Sir, this couple has no sanitary B-47 form
and no I-435 identifying papers, either.
Yes, sir.
They brought an American cat with them.
Sure, but without the I-435, I can’t
officially state that it is indeed a cat.
I also can’t guarantee
that it’s American.
Sir, I’m not trying
to make your life more difficult.
OK, sir.
—Hello, Pablo.
—Hello, Valeria.
—This is my wife, Tata.
—Hello.
Don’t worry. Everything will be perfect.
I’m just not used
to these type of things.
Just be yourself.
Ma’am, it would be best
if you weren’t here.
Look, Tata,
there are a lot of people here.
It might not be good for the baby.
Go to the house.
Welcome to Nuevos Tiempos.
I’m Valeria Velez and I’m here with the
man known as “the Robin Hood of the poor”
for his generosity
with the poor of Medellín.
Tell us about your program,
“Medellín Without Slums,” Mr Escobar.
I was born in Rionegro,
not too far from here.
And I asked myself how a government
that exists for the people
can be so out of touch
with what they need.
Hospitals, social and athletic programs,
plus the construction
of 400 houses in this community.
I hear you told your mother that one day
you would be president of Colombia.
Do you have any political aspirations,
Mr Escobar?
None at all.
My business takes up most of my time.
I will tell you one thing, Valeria.
For decades, our country has been led by
Lopez and other families that are wealthy
who made their fortune
off exploiting the poor.
They don’t know the dreams
of common people, but I do …
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Does your wife do it standing up?
Don’t ever disrespect Tata.
Do you hear me?
I’m sorry, Pablo. I’m sorry.
Forgive me.
It won’t happen again.
I promise.
How can I apologize?
Want to put it in my ass?
We get better every time we practice.
You’re amazing, Javi.
Don’t go overboard.
It’s the truth.
What can you offer me to drink?
Whiskey or tap water.
Water.
What you’re missing
in this apartment is a woman.
It’s fine the way it is.
I wasn’t offering.
Here.
If you were a client,
you would have paid me already.
—And you wouldn’t know my real name.
—Don’t take it the wrong way.
It’s cash from Uncle Sam
for the information you never gave me.
Take it.
And my visa?
Give me something I can use
and we’ll talk about it.
What are you doing this weekend?
—I’m going to Medellín.
—Work or play?
I have to take care of my child.
I can pay, too.
Those guys are richer
than Uncle Sam, Javi.
Come here.
—What?
—Give me a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
I guess I’ll have to find another girl.
Good luck with that.
We’re all going to Medellín.
Some of us are even going by plane.
Helena?
Whose party is it?
Just one thing.
Who told you about this?
Mother Teresa of Calcutta.
Pablo says they’re not going to pay a dime
to M-19 for Marta Ochoa. Gustavo, too.
—And Jorge?
—No. Jorge doesn’t agree.
—Then what?
—They’re all going to a meeting.
At Las Margaritas.
—Everyone?
—Yeah, they’ll all be there.
—Good day, Major.
—Good day.
Your intel was good. The traquetos
are gathering at Las Margaritas.
Fresh meat.
What I propose at this moment, gentlemen,
is that we form an organization.
Pool our resources to train soldiers,
trade knowledge and buy information.
And so the message is clear,
we’re going to name our group …
“Death to Kidnappers.”
What I propose …
I will manage all operational aspects.
All you need to do is cover my expenses.
What you gentlemen
will receive in return:
two things.
One … I promise to end the kidnapping.
Two … and at this moment,
the most important …
I promise to return
Marta Ochoa to her family.
Death to Kidnappers!
Come in! Enjoy!
Don’t forget La Quica!
Take care of him, too.
Sit down, my love.
—How are you?
—Good. And you?
I like your hat.
It looks good on you.
—Do you think so?
—Yes, it looks good.
Let’s see.
Very cute.
You’re tired.
Let me relax you a bit.
So what happened at that meeting
that made you so tired?
What did you hear?
Nothing. Just making conversation.
I want you to find the girl.
I can pick up a sicario.
You OK with that?
—I’m going with you.
—What about Fresh Meat?
That’s it, guys.
Guys.
Hey, what happened?
That little girl doesn’t move.
Like a dead cow.
What, did you kill her?
It’s my turn now.
Where’s the girl?
—Where’s the girl, asshole?
—I don’t know.
I don’t know.
Choke him.
Enough with the party.
I gotta rough this girl up.
Gacha wants to know
if she knows something.
Gacha’s paranoid.
Wait a second …
I don’t like them bruised.
Let me have a little more fun,
then I’ll let her go.
It’s all right, boys.
This one’s for all of you!
Slap her around!
—Should I tell him?
—No.
Remember what Carrillo said.
Sorry, I don’t speak English.
—How far is it?
—Come on, you piece of shit.
Helena?
I’m going to get you out of here, OK?
I promise.
All right. She’s coming out.
Copy, Major.
Let’s go, boys.
—Where’s Peña?
—Over there.
“Deliver Marta Ochoa safe and sound …
or your family is next.”
Signed, “Death to Kidnappers.”
Please! Please, let me go.
—Hurry up!
—Please, don’t!
—Tell him to get a little closer.
—A little closer.
A little closer!
You know what, boss?
Go a little higher.
A little bit higher and a little bit
closer so you can see the tree!
That’s it.
Now a little bit higher …
so you can see the little tree!
DEATH TO KIDNAPPERS
A little more.
That’s it! There you go.
—Much better.
—Yes, boss.
Didn’t I tell you
not to let anyone into the park?
—I’ll take care of it.
—Are you crazy or what?
Stupid asshole.
It’s a woman with a baby.
Take a picture
so we can send it to the newspapers.
Do it.
Good day, ma’am.
—Good day.
—I’m sorry, but the park is closed today.
What do you mean the park is closed?
May I escort you out?
Why is it closed?
I come by here every day.
It’s because there is a foul odour
and I don’t want the child to get sick.
I thought I smelled something.
—Right?
—Yes.
Oh, look,
what a beautiful little baby.
Right, just like his dad.
Thank you very much.
—You must be proud.
—Yes, of course.
My wife and I are having a baby very soon.
Oh, very good. Congratulations!
I don’t know if it’s a boy or a girl,
but as long as it’s healthy.
Yes, of course.
The most important thing is health.
Hey, Don Pablo.
What do you want us to do
with this guy?
Should I kill him or what?
From what I can see,
you’re not going to stop.
Here I am,
so you can finish what you started …
but with the sword of Bolívar.
It’s a very beautiful gift.
Thank you very much.
Stand up.
I guarantee no harm
will come to you or your family.
From now on,
we are going to work together.
Go in peace, brother.
Is that what I think it is?
You’ve gotta be kidding.
I want you to run
my day-to-day operations.
And you’ll do what?
Liberate Colombia.