Please, pay attention!
I need you to put your mobile phones,
beepers, and radios in the container.
Please. I'll take that.
- Thank you.
- OK.
For the next three hours,
we'll be running silent.
My colleagues and I will take the lead.
And the target?
I'll just say that it's everything
you've trained for.
Gentlemen, you heard!
I need you to be tight and right.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Let's go.
So, what are we doing here?
We're arresting
one of the godfathers of Cali.
Applauded by the multitude
present on 10th street,
president-elect Ernesto Samper Pizano
is welcomed by the people of Colombia...
It's too early.
I rise early. I'm up with the sun.
Up all right!
Hi!
How did it go, honey?
Very good! Look, what a beauty.
Look at that pass. Goal!
Dammit, what sort of defence is that?
Piece of shit!
I'm paying your fucking salaries!
Thank you.
I can help you expand your businesses...
I could help you make millions.
Two units: Calderón's and mine.
Breach one here. Breach two... here.
Feistl, Van Ness: pool.
You come in from the back.
- All right, let's do this already.
- OK.
If anyone kills the godfather,
I kill you.
We can't repeat what happened
with Escobar.
I want him alive.
Understood?
Go.
What do you think? What do we do?
I think there could be hideouts here.
- We have to check the house again.
- All right.
Gentlemen, we're going to search
every corner of this house, understood?
It's an elegant house in Palmira, boss.
I don't know whose it is,
but it's not one of ours.
Very good. Get out of there
and make sure no one sees you.
Sir.
I need you to do something important.
When you leave your house,
you'll find Navegante.
He knows where you have to go.
Of course, sir, but what should I do
with the operation I'm monitoring?
Cordova. Give it to Cordova.
- Be careful.
- Of course, sir.
He's one of my best men.
He'll take care of it.
You're a man of your word.
So close to heaven and so far from God.
Impressive.
I'm so glad you brought me
to see the eighth wonder of the world.
Don't be an asshole, Pacho.
El Paso, Texas
is what I wanted you to see.
Fucking NAFTA changed everything, Pacho.
It's been around for what?
Two years, more or less?
More than two million trucks
have crossed already.
Many of them ours.
Filled to the brim.
Do you know how many trucks
the Americans check?
Less than ten per cent.
It's insane.
They don't have the manpower.
Assholes opened the floodgates
and now they stand there
with a baby's bucket to try and stop it.
This is the right business.
I already know this, man.
No, man. What I'm saying is,
you're getting out of the right business
at the exact wrong time.
And you're going to regret it.
You want some?
Amado, are you suggesting
that I betray my partners?
No. No way. Why betray?
They want to get out.
I'm proposing that we start
something new, you and I.
Just imagine it:
You send it to me, I get it across.
In two years, we'll be flooding
this fucking shitty country.
Think about it, all right?
Think about it.
Just don't take too long,
because in six months,
I need to secure a new supply.
Hopefully, it will be with you.
Give it another once-over?
Thirty seconds.
Hey! You can't park there!
Damn truck.
These fucking trucks
are always breaking down.
What's up? You can't park here.
Let me just grab the cables
and I'll move it.
Move the fucking truck.
- That's the one Lady Di uses.
- Really?
Someone's ringing the doorbell!
- Careful.
- Sorry, wait just a moment.
Let me get the door.
Look.
Police! Back up. Quickly! Move it!
Quickly! Move it!
What's going on?
Sit down, ladies.
Sit down, ladies, I won't say it again.
You can't come in here. Get out.
He's fucking running!
Get up! Look at my face!
Let's go.
- Sit down, Miss.
- I already told you, Gilberto is not home.
Did he contact anyone?
- No one, Colonel.
- No? All good?
Mrs Rodríguez, I have a federal warrant
signed and executed by myself,
as representative
of the Colombian National Police.
The question is, will you cooperate?
Are you all right?
Yes.
It's good here.
The only thing left
is to demolish the house.
I'm sorry, I thought we had something.
Welcome to my world.
Well...
Look, when we get there,
I think it's better if I go in alone.
These people are angry.
What we're asking of them,
it's an insult on top of their grief.
You're different, Jorge Salcedo.
Different? How?
You're crippled. You don't carry a gun.
Most people don't carry guns.
Yeah... but you're not most people.
And that's why it's so weird.
Interesting.
That you never carry a gun.
I see. Why do you think that is?
I don't know.
Maybe you're scared.
Fear... of what you could do with it.
That you've been walking around a killer
and never knew it.
Pedrito, go in the house!
Good afternoon, Mrs Salazar.
Calm down, Mrs Salazar.
Calm down.
My name is Jorge Salcedo.
I'd like to speak with you, if I could.
Go right back to where you came from,
and tell that whore
if she wants my grandson,
she can come looking for him.
I just came to talk.
If you don't like what I have to say,
I'll go back to Cali
and deliver whatever message you want.
I'm unarmed. I'm here to talk.
Your boss murdered my son...
to take up with his whore wife.
And now you come to take my grandson
far from the only family he has left.
I know this is not what you want to hear.
But she is his mother.
And Miguel Rodríguez is protecting her.
Protecting?
Is that what they call it now?
And he will be protected as well.
And if you let me take him back, I promise
you can see him whenever you'd like.
You promise. How nice of you.
Who told you I would do that?
I have him here and I can see him
whenever I want and protect him.
That bitch made her choice.
Mrs Salazar... please accept my offer.
The next men who come... won't be asking.
There will be war.
Why don't you ask my sons?
See what they think.
What is this?
- Colonel Martínez.
- Captain.
You know what's happening here?
Yes, I think I know.
I'm giving you one chance
to do the right thing
and not fuck up this operation.
You think you're clever?
You're in Cali. Cali is my city.
This isn't Bogotá.
You're way out of line here, Hugo.
Perhaps.
He's here. We'll find him.
Watch him.
I'm unarmed.
I didn't come for a fight.
We're going to send your fucking head
back to Miguel in a fucking box.
- Walk, motherfucker.
- Let's go.
Bring out the car.
Pedro. Let's go. I'm taking you
to your mother. Take my hand.
- Very good.
- Shut your fucking mouth or I kill her.
All right, my lady.
Make like a statue or I'll shoot you.
I'm getting in first, you hear?
Real still.
You're taking the boy.
What else do you want?
Relax.
- Stop!
- Mama!
What else, motherfucker?
Fucking asshole!
Drop the weapon.
Don't shoot.
I'm a man of peace.
Let's go.
Hey! Stop!
Colonel! Calderón has taken off.
- Do you have a phone in there?
- Yes, in there.
They got Gilberto and they're moving
towards the aerial base.
The whole workforce is on this.
They're not going to leave the city.
Tell all the men to be alert.
Understood?
Move it, asshole.
They'll try to take us on the road.
Guns out!
Cleaning, cooking, working.
Hello.
- Don Miguel... something's happened.
- What happened?
I'm outside Gilberto's house.
They got him.
They got your brother.
We've got a visual.
Surround him in the market!
Look! There he goes! Faster!
Let's get him on the next turn!
Hold your fire!
Driver! Put your hands
where I can see them!
Driver!
Out further!
Further!
Get out.
Open the back.
- OK. Let me get the keys.
- Open it.
Open it.
Those American sons of bitches tricked us.
We've got the wrong fucking truck!
They're going to the air field.
We'll get them there.
I took care of security.
Let those sons of bitches
try to touch us again.
Send Salcedo's beeper another message.
Uncle! It's me, Nicolas!
Come in.
- Nicolas.
- Uncle.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
They got him.
Nicolas, why don't you go home
and wait there?
Once something happens, I'll call you.
No, sir, I have to help.
Come.
You know your dad
doesn't want you mixed up in this.
We have to have faith that your dad
won't be taken out of Cali.
And if he is?
Why did we waste all of that money
on my education? I'm a lawyer.
I'm taking the first flight to Bogotá.
I want to help him.
Let's hope that's not necessary.
Sir, please don't come any closer.
Your men are impeding the transport
and arrest of a fugitive under warrant.
You know it.
And that means prison.
What you do today...
what you do this moment...
defines you.
For the rest of your lives.
Are you police or not?
That's better.
Shit!
What's up? It's me.
- About fucking time.
- I was out of range.
They have arrested Gilberto.
- What?
- They got him, Jorge.
They got Gilberto.
You were monitoring the raid.
But they never mentioned
Gilberto's name.
Even so, we checked all the tapes.
It's impossible.
Brother...
They got him.
They took him away.
We got beat.
Get back here quick.
Take that.
Five seconds to take photos, no more.
Congratulations.
But you know this won't hold up.
You're fucking with things
that are much bigger than you are.
Smile, Gilberto.
You're about to be on TV.
Mr Rodríguez, do you have a response
to the charges against you?
Conspiring to export cocaine
and illegal enrichment?
Enough. Let's go.
Do you have anything to say
to the people of Cali?
Mr Rodríguez.
- My love!
- Mummy!
- Are you hungry? No?
- No.
How cute.
Looks a lot like his dad.
Come on.
Mum will read you a story in a bit.
Go. I'll be right there.
Thanks for showing up, Jorge.
Sir, we don't know
how much the DEA knows.
We need to assume
all your current homes are... unsafe.
I'll stay here for now.
We all need to talk.
What did you expect?
A warrant by definition
authorizes the police...
Wait, wait, wait...
Let's not lie to ourselves.
This operation was run
by the Drug Enforcement Administration
of the United States.
The takedown, Mr Attorney General,
was National Police.
The transport was by our police.
The booking was by our police.
So a war started by National Police?
Look, as Attorney General,
my main... concern is achieving
a peaceful settlement with the godfathers.
And the arrest
of Gilberto Rodríguez Orejuela
means we now have new leverage
to negotiate with.
The President of Colombia,
Ernesto Samper.
I hate to be late to a good debate.
You know us, might as well
try to smooth rough water with a hammer.
I've been apprised by Minister Botero
about our newly-incarcerated Cali godfather.
- With all due respect, Mr President?
- Go ahead, Miguel.
We've worked for months
to negotiate this surrender.
We recommend the immediate release
of Mr Rodríguez Orejuela.
Colombia is a nation of laws.
Not of concessions.
If I give a pass to the largest criminal
organisation in the world,
the trust of the people
will be lost forever.
Mr Rodríguez is entitled to the same
due process as any Colombian citizen.
Let's see where due process gets him.
For now...
his arrest stands.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
We talked about this.
I don't want the stink of this on you.
Relax, Dad.
I'm a lawyer. I'm the only one
in the family who can visit you.
Besides, I thought you could use
a friendly face.
What I could really use
is a tumbler of whiskey about this big.
How does it look?
The warrants are old.
- Invalid?
- Vulnerable.
I have a lunch tomorrow at 1:00pm
with the Colombian Board of Pharmacies.
8:00am at the latest, I'll be out.
Dad, you're here until our lawyers
get you in front of a judge.
And he'll hold you here in Bogotá
due to the conspiracy charge.
I don't get it.
This is a mistake, a blunder.
A gross overstep
by a rogue American agent!
That's what you want to believe.
But if that was the case,
you'd be out by now.
- Dad, this is real.
- No, money is real.
And what about all I've paid?
Sons of bitches
can't leave me confined here.
How the fuck did they surprise us
like that, gentlemen?
It was Calderón.
Dad, I say we tear him to pieces.
- And his fucking family and his children.
- David, please.
Obviously, there's responsibility
on all sides.
- Cordova...
- Sir, just as we realised...
By the time you realised,
Colonel Martínez had already been
in my brother's house for 30 minutes.
Don Miguel. The failure's mine.
When it comes to the DEA,
Cordova counts on me.
Wait. Cordova, you're my brother's
personal head of security.
Yes, sir.
Then you should've been there.
Your men should've been there.
Your guards were fooled
by a fucking chicken truck.
I want to know what the fuck
is happening here.
Because I'm starting to believe
that none of us are safe.
Not your families...
and not mine.
My family.
Thank you, Attorney General Valdivieso,
Defence Minister Botero.
Colonel, please.
Thanks.
What are you talking about?
I turned in my weapon and my badge.
Good luck.
Colonel...
I'm sorry.
Men like me would give our lives
to arrest a man like him.
You did everything right, Peña.
But now you're all alone.
We need to talk about your security.
Let me be in charge.
I'll protect you, Dad.
Now's not the time for a change.
We need to keep things on track
until your uncle is back.
What if he doesn't come back?
- They got Gilberto.
- I don't understand.
I thought Gilberto
had this all under control.
So did I.
And what now?
This could get messy.
Stay where you are.
Right now, we look out for ourselves.
Pacho... be smart.
For now, we wait.
You stay there a while longer.
We have to keep everything running.
The health of the business has never been
more important. Understand?
Yes. Of course.
You listening to me, motherfucker?