What’s up, Lizard?
We’re going out tonight.
At La Dispensaria.
I got a table ready.
Show up around midnight.
La Dispensaria?
All right.
Guess who that was?
Your partner.
He just gave me a great gift.
Poison.
Does he know
how I’m going to package it?
Yeah, sure.
He’s not a fool.
Gotta go.
Gonna stick me with the bill?
Cheap son of a bitch.
—What’s up, son?
—Hey, brother.
Let’s go inside and have a good time.
It’s on, boys!
We’re gonna stop on 14th
and go around the corner.
Riano, Trujillo,
you’re in the front with me.
Galvis and Silva, you take up the rear.
You got it, boys? We’re gonna
go at it with everything we got.
We’re gonna kill these fuckers,
all right?
How many fucking times do I have
to tell you not to waste the acid?
To be productive, you can’t waste money!
Come on!
Hands up!
Everybody on your knees!
What the fuck is going on here?
Get down!
Attention!
Position!
Take aim!
Load weapons!
Fire!
Start packing.
We have to leave the country.
Fucking Pinochet
is killing the whole world.
But you’re not a communist.
No, not a communist, something worse.
A trafficker.
—A trafficker?
—Yes, a drug trafficker.
WELCOME TO COLOMBIA
Hey, partner.
What are you doing here?
Pablo Escobar?
Where’s Felipo?
Felipo’s been arrested.
Bullshit. Felipo works for me.
He used to work for you. Now he’s going
to jail. What do you think about that?
—Do you know who you’re talking to?
—Shut the fuck up.
—I wasn’t talking to you.
—Relax, Gustavo, please.
Show some respect.
Now what’s the problem, Mr Jose Luis?
How do you know my name?
You’re Colonel Jose Luis Herrera.
And that’s Nacho Ibarra.
There’s Garcia, Lopez …
—Is that Pinilla?
—Yes, Pinilla.
That’s Pinilla.
Pinilla …
and with Phillipe is Esparanza.
I don’t give a rat’s ass.
Open the fucking trucks.
I don’t have all day.
Open them up.
Tell me something, Mr Escobar.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
You don’t even bother
to hide your contraband.
Because I pay for the privilege, Colonel.
Oh, yeah? You don’t say.
Where are your import papers?
You need papers for these TV sets.
Take them.
Sorry, Mr Escobar. We’re not
Medellín police making a shit salary.
—Look, brother, it’s not for you.
—Then who?
It’s for Carlitos.
Your son.
Wouldn’t he like a TV in his room?
Hey, Pinilla!
Your daughter just
got her driver’s license, right?
I’ve got some car stereo systems in there
that are really cool. Real nice.
That friend of yours, Lopez …
he’s got a wife that’s really beautiful.
Right? She’s a fox.
Your wife is gorgeous, brother.
What’s she doing with a guy like you?
I think she deserves some jewellery, no?
Why don’t I have my boys
drop off a few gifts?
Colonel, how is your mom doing?
—She just got out of the hospital, right?
—Yes, she’s feeling better.
Good. That makes us happy.
Gentlemen …
I’m going to tell you who I am.
I am Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria.
My eyes are everywhere.
That means you guys
can’t move a finger in all of Antioquia
without me knowing about it.
Do you understand? Not a finger.
One day, I’m going to be
president of the Republic of Colombia.
So look, I make deals for a living.
Now, you can stay calm
and accept my deal …
or accept the consequences.
Silver …
or lead.
You decide.
—Let ‘em go. Let ‘em go.
—All right, then.
We’re going to let them through.
The trucks. Let them through.
This is Pablo.
—Hi.
—Nice to meet you.
—What’s up?
—Mateo Moreno.
No, no, no.
“Cockroach” to my friends.
All right, yesterday we were talking,
and I think this business
can make us a lot of money.
Explain.
Well … I get the paste in Peru.
I will handle
the chemical part of production,
and all the other details
in producing this exquisite white powder.
What I need from you
is to help me get it into Colombia.
Now tell him how much it costs.
In Chile, this little thing
costs 10 bucks a gram.
—They sell it by grams?
—Yes, it’s very good. Look …
You do a little bit, and in 20 minutes,
you want to do some more.
Also …
it’s a digestive aid.
It makes you want to take a shit.
It’s very clean, this stuff.
Want some?
If this is really that good
and we can make some money,
we can find room on our trucks.
We can sell it in Bogotá, Barranquilla,
Cali, Cartagena …
We’re going to be rich.
—What did you say your name was?
—Cockroach.
Well look, Cuca …
you don’t have any vision, my friend.
If it costs $10 a gram here …
imagine how much
it will sell for in Miami.
I love that song.
One more.
These are my friends,
Pablo and Gustavo.
Would you like a little coffee?
Yes, a coffee.
My factory is small,
but highly productive.
Look. For crushing the leaves, I like to
use children because of their tiny feet.
Little magic leaves.
The kerosene
separates the drug from the leaf.
Over here, the sulphuric acid
distills and distills it.
Then you cut it,
and mix it with gasoline.
Then, basically, you pull the merchandise
out of the liquid.
Let it dry, dry, dry.
You use ammonia to get the paste.
And here it is. It’s pasty … but pure.
Here is the prize.
It’s like the kitchen in your house.
Like baking a cake.
Only a much better cake
than you’ve ever had.
Look, an old press, an antique.
Now we put it in the oven.
Here’s one. The other will follow.
All natural, organic and healthy.
Very good.
Well …
—we’ll take a kilo.
—A whole kilo. Perfect.
—No.
—You said a kilo.
We’ll take five.
How do we get five across the border?
That’s Gustavo’s department.
This one has got a good engine.
I was taking a look at it,
and the best place to hide the merchandise
would be under the rear wheel well.
It’s 22 and one half horsepower.
Is this easy to take off?
Don’t worry about that shit.
I’ll stick five kilos in there easy.
All right, all right.
I’ll take three cars, please.
—Sure, when do you need them?
—Now, brother.
All right, we’ll take the cars
and head back to the lab.
Why the fuck
are we going back to the lab?
Because there are four wheel wells per car
and that’s 20 kilos.
For three cars, that’s 60 kilos.
So it’s $9 profit per gram.
$9,000 per kilo.
$9,000 times 60…
the profit is $540,000.
Do you know how to drive, Cockroach?
OK, Pablo and I drive fast.
How are you feeling, Gustavo?
All this smells like shit to me.
What an ignorant bastard.
It’s like French cheese.
The stinkier, the better.
All right.
What about all these lights?
Is that to tip off the cops, or what?
Just worry about transporting the stuff
and selling it.
I’m the artist here, clear?
Clear.
You know the thing
that has me worried, Pablo?
Don’t you think the workers
will choke with all that smoke?
Let’s build them a chimney.
Gentlemen, the first three?
If this business makes so much money,
why are you sending me coach?
We just started up.
We have to be careful with money.
—Don’t be a dick.
—No, no, don’t give me that dumb shit.
How much can a first class ticket cost?
I don’t know.
Why don’t you buy it yourself?
Hey, Mom, how much
do you think we can fit in there?
—Around five kilos, honey.
—That much?
Trust me, Pablito.
I love it. Let’s do it.
—Pablo.
—Thank you, my love.
It’s Gustavo.
Five kilos, right?
—Meet my friend.
—Hello, how are you doing?
Hey Pablo, this is Lion.
It’s not like we’re rich, right?
Pablo Escobar Gaviria.
How are you?
—Lion.
—Pleased to meet you, Lion.
Here’s three.
We’re going to need two more,
right, Mom?
—That’s right.
—Pablito …
make sure it is not you
who wears it, OK?
Look, my love … it won’t fit me.
Try it on.
Come here.
That’s it.
Good, right?
One …
—two …
—Wow, it holds a lot!
… three.
—Two more.
—Got it. I’ll be right back.
He looks really handsome,
doesn’t he?
Listen, Lion,
that jacket fits you very nicely.
Yeah. Excuse me, ma’am, can you adjust
the jacket a little bit here in the back?
—Listen to this guy.
—He looks very handsome, son.
Like a fag model, isn’t that right?
—What’s up, my man?
—What’s up, son?
—Welcome.
—Thanks a lot. How are ya?
—Everything good?
—Everything’s good.
It’s so hot.
What the hell are you doing
with a jacket on?
You like my jacket, brother?
I got it in Colombia and look,
it has a little gift.
I was in jail for a while, remember?
I saw this shit there.
It’s pure poison.
What you got there
is the perfect product.
Pablo says the gringos
will fall in love with this shit.
It’s gonna fuck up their brains,
that’s for sure.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Go on. There are five kilos.
Where are you going?
I’m gonna get another jacket, brother.
We’ll meet at the same time tomorrow,
all right?
The briefcase doesn’t have a false bottom?
You guys are pilots,
so you can get this stuff by
without a problem.
Look, it’s $150,000 per kilo,
so whatever you want.
We’ll take four.
All right, much better.
Take these two and tell Jairo
to give you two more. All right?
—All right.
—Perfect. Thank you very much.
Come in, please.
Look, here are the packets.
You take a packet,
you dip it in the oil and swallow it.
Easy, right?
You swallow 50,
and I pay you $10,000.
All right?
But with you two,
we have a problem.
You girls are pregnant, right?
That’s good, because US Customs
won’t search pregnant women.
You two can easily swallow 70
instead of 50.
And I’ll pay you $15,000
to help you with the kids.
All right? All right. Perfect.
COLOMBIAN COFFEE
Do you trust this guy?
I don’t know.
He was in prison in the United States.
—So is he gay or what?
—Oh, for sure he’s gay.
But he’s got good routes.
Hello, Carlos.
Gustavo Gaviria,
nice to meet you.
—Nice to meet you.
—My cousin.
Pablo Escobar Gaviria.
Nice to meet you.
How was your flight?
Smooth.
Let’s get down to business.
The Lion tells us you’ve been transporting
a lot of marijuana in your plane.
—That’s true.
—About how much per flight?
—How far?
—Miami.
—Somewhere around 1000 kilos.
—1000 kilos?
Counting the gasoline.
Carlos …
Yes?
What if we take out the seats,
the carpet and all the other crap
and only leave space for the pilot?
We’ll leave the engine, right?
How much?
About … 300 more.
All right then, Mr Carlos.
Let’s take a walk.
We brought you a little present.
Brazilians.
Best asses in the world, believe me.
No, I’m not feeling well.
What the fuck is up with you guys?
You’re flying around in planes …
while I’m rotting here in this jungle?
Look, let us explain what we have to--
Wait.
From now on, in all of my labs …
I’ll build a large house with a pool
—and air-conditioning--
—And whores from Brazil.
—Just for you.
—One problem.
These are my labs.
Relax. No one’s arguing with you.
Come show me the production
and we’ll talk later.
How something like this
can make so much money!
Now I ask myself …
if I should get involved with this.
What do you think, Pablo?
I heard the “potato” business
is like the “egg” business.
I wouldn’t get involved.
Look, man,
I took a good look at the market.
Importing potatoes from Peru is easy.
Of course.
Same old contraband routes.
Be careful, guys. If we all start
buying potatoes at the same time,
the Peruvians will raise the price.
They also grow potatoes in Bolivia.
We can reduce the cost of
the refining process if we buy together.
Well, guys, the hard part
is getting the merchandise to Miami.
You need a lot of creativity for that.
How much would you charge us
to be “creative”?
You deliver the product to me, labeled.
I will take it to you in Miami
and deliver it to your contact there.
Better yet, Lehder will do it.
I’ll charge 35 percent
of the sales value,
but I’ll insure the safety of your load
up to 50 percent of the value.
The potato business is ours.
We don’t need--
Deal?
Deal.
Sounds good to me.
All right, I will create my own routes
and stop using your services
as soon as possible. OK?
We expect nothing less, Gonzalo.
Partners?
We know your policy toward partners.
Let’s just call us …
“friendly associates.”
To Miami.
Why won’t Pablo ever see me?
I spent all this time
waiting around for him.
Tell me something, Cockroach.
Did you ever think
you were going to have this much money?
Fuck the money.
I’m talking renegotiation.
If it wasn’t for me, you two
would still be smuggling cigarettes.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Never say this to Pablo.
He’s not as forgiving as I am.
Stop!
What do you have in the spare tires?
390 kilos, Pablo. We lost it.
Gustavo, what do you mean
“we lost it”?
Just what I said, we lost it.
It just disappeared?
Into thin air?
Don’t mess with me, Pablo.
We lost it.
It looks like the cops must have stopped
the guys when they were leaving Ipsalia.
Look …
we’ve paid every cop
from here to Ipsalia.
So how did we lose a load, brother?
It looks like Colonel Herrera
suddenly turned honest.
And how much is he asking?
Too much.
What are you going to do?
Come back, Pablo.
Don’t go and risk it for this asshole.
Come back.
Where are you going, Pablo?
Pablo?
What’s going on, brother?
Mr Escobar …
—we need to renegotiate.
—Eat shit.
Eat. Shit.
What if I shot you in the head?
Are you sure about this, Colonel?
He hasn’t stopped laughing
since we arrested him.
We’re DAS, Ibarra.
What’s that faggot gonna do?
There we are.
No, lower, lower.
No that low.
Ready.
Another one, another one.
I’m ready.
Remove the handcuffs.
You can go now, officer.
Sit down, Mr Pablo.
We counted more than 300 kilos
in those trucks.
That’s a street value
of over four million dollars, Mr Escobar.
And you only gave us $150,000.
Well, that’s what we agreed upon.
You know something?
I make deals for a living.
Now, you can either accept my deal
or accept the consequences. You decide.
Or we can renegotiate,
come to an agreement,
and everyone goes home happy.
Deal?
I’ll give you one million dollars.
Under one condition.
What is it?
Someone in my organization
gave you the street value of my cocaine.
Otherwise, how would you know?
Give me a name.
And you won’t have
to split the cash with him.
No, no, no! No, Pablo, no, no!
No, no!
Leave this piece of shit here.
Look at what happened, boss.
They killed Poison at La Dispensaria.
—Who did it?
—I think it was Carrillo.
And there was a gringo
DEA agent taking pictures.
—Raise the bounty.
—On Carrillo, sir?
I’ll pay half a million
for the head of a DEA agent.
Half a million?
Do it.
As you wish, sir.
Fucking gringos.