h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
(♪ Upbeat Latin ballad playing)
(♪ Pablo sings along in Spanish)
(♪ Song continues)
(Indistinct chatter in Spanish)
- (Chaotic yelling)
- (Cocks handgun)
(La Quica shouts indistinctly)
(In Spanish) Get down!
(Woman gasps)
(♪ Continues singing along)
(Man) One!
(Women scream)
(Gunshot)
(♪ Song continues)
- (La Quica) Rosa! Rosa!
- (Sobbing) Quica...
Tell me who talked to the police!
Who talked to them? Huh?
(Screams) It had to be that whore
in the market. Please, Quica!
(Rosa sobbing)
(Taking deep breaths)
(Gunshot)
(Joint hisses out)
(♪ Song ends)
(♪ Latin guitar theme song)
(Steve) 'lmagine this:
'President of Colombia goes on TV
and tells the whole world
'he'll never make a deal with you.
'Now a normal person thinks,
"I'm fucked."
'But Pablo Escobar,
he thinks that's just your opening offer.
'So the man finds a way to respond.'
(In Spanish)
Thanks for accepting the invitation.
Forgive me for the hood.
It's for security reasons.
- I hope you understand.
- I understand.
Can I offer you something?
Coffee, water?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
Let's begin, then.
(Clears throat)
- Do you regret going to jail a year ago?
- Absolutely not.
In fact, what I regret least
is having escaped.
The Special Forces came in
and opened fire.
I couldn't risk getting killed, right?
However...
I hope this interview
makes it clear to the president...
I'm willing to return to any prison
in the District of Antioquia.
(Pablo continues over radio)
'The most modest and humble.
'But I have to examine the conditions
they're going to put me in
'because it would be easy, for example,
for someone to rig a car bomb
'that would explode when I arrived.'
(Steve)
'And how did Gaviria take Pablo's offer?
'I think it's safe to say
that he didn't really care for it.
'But it wasn't just Gaviria
Pablo was talking to.
'In his mind, he was also negotiating
with the leader of the free world.'
(In Spanish) It turns out that my problem
turned into a political problem.
It seems I'm very important
to the re-election
of the president of the U.S.
(Steve) 'You see, the problem was,
'George Bush had his own plans
for Escobar.'
We will, for the first time,
make available the appropriate
resources of America's armed forces.
And for the drug kingpins,
the death penalty.
(Steve) 'And with a commander in chief
who used to be the head of the CIA,
'well, you can use your imagination
'as to what "appropriate resources"
might mean.
'He started by appointing
a new ambassador.
'Badass former Navy man,
Arthur Crosby...
'who specialised in Latin American
affairs and counterterrorism.
'Next, he dug into his old CIA Rolodex,
'where there was no shortage of guys
who knew how to fight dirty.
'And he sent us one of those, too.
'Lastly, and what Peña and I like to call
his own personal "fuck you" to us...
'he sent us something
he thought we must need: a boss.
'Now just how long that person
would be my boss remained to be seen.'
I'm ready to pay for my mistakes
by accepting the most humble jail cell
as long as my rights are respected
and they guarantee me that I won't be
transferred anywhere for any reason.
Do you acknowledge that
you have committed crimes in the past,
or that you ordered someone's death?
That answer
I could only give to a priest.
In a confessional.
(Indistinct chatter in Spanish)
Marietta.
- What's up?
- What happened?
They killed them.
I think there were six or seven girls.
Who would do something like that?
(lnterviewer) Are you, by nature,
violent and proud?
Those who know me
know I have a great sense of humour.
I consider myself a happy man.
I've always been happy,
always optimistic.
I've always had faith in life.
I always sing in the shower.
How do you think the story
of Pablo Escobar will end?
Well... one can never know.
But I always hope for the best.
I'd like to die on my own two feet.
In the year 3047.
(Crosby)
'My title might be "ambassador,"
'but that's some bullshit
politician's word.
'I know what it means
to be on the front lines.'
And everybody in this room wants
the same thing: to take down Escobar.
Now as a veteran of numerous conflicts,
I learned one immutable truth:
the only way to succeed is by
working together, communicating,
sharing intelligence and collaborating.
Understood?
Uh, this is Claudia Messina.
She is the new DEA country attaché.
She'll be taking over all DEA operations
in-country. Messina?
Thank you, Ambassador.
The DEA will be opening field offices
in Cali, Cartagena and Barranquilla.
As far as the Medellín team
is concerned,
they will be housed out of
CNP headquarters until further notice.
But only after some personnel changes
have been made.
Now as far as
long-term intelligence is concerned,
that's under the purview of the CIA,
the station chief, Bill Stechner.
- Bill, anything you'd like to add?
- I'm good.
(Low chuckle)
- Who's here from Centra Spike?
- I am, sir. Edward Jacoby.
Let's get Centra Spike
in the air immediately.
I wanna know every word
these assholes say.
All information flows through me
and I'll disseminate it.
Yes, sir.
When Escobar
sticks his fucking head out,
we're gonna nail that son of a bitch.
(Messina) What about him?
Other than the fact he wasn't here today.
Well, I suggested that he stay home.
You mentioned making some changes.
What exactly does that mean?
It means I'm making some changes.
Murphy's a good agent.
He's done a lot down here.
Yeah.
Looks like it.
Do you have any idea
the strings that were pulled
to get that guy not to press charges?
The guy would've had
a dog sniffing up his ass
before he got on the plane.
Maybe Steve did him a favour.
Was that a thank you?
Be straight with me
and I'll be straight with you.
I don't need a guy like that
making my life more difficult.
- And making the DEA look bad.
- Ma'am...
Messina. Or boss.
We've been down here a long time.
You've been down here all of what,
two hours?
It may not make the front page, but...
a lot of the intel we have
is because of Steve.
He's a good man.
He's going through some shit right now.
He was at the airport
to stop his wife from leaving the country
with their kid. He didn't make it.
Add that to watching Escobar
build a five-star prison
and walking out the back door.
We both deserve to see this through...
boss.
(Steve sniffs, clears throat)
Have you, uh... had anything to eat
in the last 24 hours?
This new boss... Messina...
What do you know about her?
Only what I've heard.
She's out of New York.
- Doesn't put up with any shit.
- (Steve sputters)
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Am I out?
I don't know.
Well, I ain't ready to go home yet, Javi.
I'll tell you that.
- Damn it! She's fucking...
- (Bottle top clatters)
- Take a shower. Sober up.
- (Sighs)
Talk to you.
(Pablo speaks Spanish)
Behind you. Watch out for that guy.
(Video game noises)
That's it.
Smash the telephone booth.
Get the pipe.
I already know, Dad.
You have to get it.
And what's that, a woman?
I'm about to fight a woman or what?
- Her name's Nora.
- Oh, yeah, what's her name?
Nora.
(Velasco) Boss, excuse the interruption.
How do you...?
What about the laboratories?
It's been difficult
to find the Moncada laboratories, boss.
And the ones that we find,
we can't get inside.
There are police checkpoints
everywhere.
We lost four men
trying to get through one.
Bastards.
And what about Judy Moncada?
We can't find her anywhere.
Or Don Berna.
Find her.
Yes, sir.
And you, boys?
- Everything is good, boss.
- All good, boss.
- How are you, Limón?
- Very good, sir.
- How are you feeling?
- Very good.
- Comfortable?
- Thanks. Very good.
Good.
I'm going to teach you something.
There is nothing lower than a rat.
And if we let the rats run free,
the streets will be filled with them.
- Understand me?
- Yes, boss.
Give me one second. One second.
Boss, excuse me. It's Fernando.
Tell me, Fernando.
'Your interview clearly worked,
Don Pablo.
'Palace wants to meet with me
right away.'
You heard that, brother? Hmm?
- We have to finish our little job.
- But we already finished it, right?
No, brother, there's still one left.
But you already killed all the whores.
I'm not talking about whores, brother.
Why her?
- She did everything we told her to.
- Someone talked to the police.
Yeah, it was those fucking whores.
- She is someone we can trust, man.
- (La Quica snorts)
You can trust her, but I can't.
Move it.
Quica.
I'm not telling you again, brother.
And we've got some shit to do.
- (Fernando) Good day.
- (Man) Good day.
I have a meeting with the president.
I'm Fernando Duque.
Your meeting is not
with the president, Mr Duque.
How's that?
- With the vice minister, then?
- No, sir.
The information I have here says
you are meeting the attorney general.
My apologies, Mr Duque.
(Steve)
'Now, Gaviria had made it clear
'that the government
was not to negotiate with Escobar.
'But Colombia Attorney General
Gustavo de Greiff
'didn't give a shit
what the president wanted.
'Unlike the US, where the attorney
general is appointed by the president,
'in Colombia, the Supreme Court
chooses the attorney general,
'whether the president likes it or not.
'And in the case of Gustavo de Greiff,
you bet your ass Gaviria didn't.'
(In Spanish) Mr Duque...
I believe everybody
has the right to a fair trial.
Pablo Escobar has the same rights
as any other Colombian.
If he has committed a crime,
he must be judged and indicted.
He can't be hunted and killed
like an animal.
Mr De Greiff,
everything you're telling me I find...
fascinating.
However, I don't...
I don't buckle under the pressure
of the Americans...
like Gaviria, Mr Duque.
(Fernando) Uh-huh.
Then that means that...
you would consider...
making a deal with Pablo.
I'm saying that Colombia...
has been at war far too long.
Of course.
The Americans are bringing in
new people.
Different faces but, ultimately,
with the same motivation.
They are using us
to advance their political agenda.
Perhaps.
But the reality is we have to accept help
wherever it comes from.
The thing about the gringos
is they are limited
to Carlos Holguín
and the embassy.
On the other hand, Pablo Escobar
is gaining ground and support.
Everyone is helping him in Medellín.
- A long manhunt plays into his hands.
- Let's talk about Medellín.
Colonel Pinzón basically
has Escobar surrounded.
Do you think we'll succeed?
(♪ Up-tempo Latin music plays on radio)
Listen, thanks for talking
to Messina, man.
I mean it. You saved my ass.
One more fuck-up, Murphy...
Oh, I know.
Is it gonna happen again?
I don't know.
(Steve) 'DEA politics weren't
the only thing we had to navigate.
'The Pinzón plan was in full effect.
'He was doubling down
on police presence.
'Medellín was under martial law
and the base of Carlos Holguín
'would look like Fort Apache.
'Me and Javi were officially guests
of the CNP.
'With all the comforts and amenities
'that a guest of the National
Colombian Police could expect.
'Which was zero.
'And we weren't alone.
'The DEA, CIA, Centra Spike
and the army, all under one roof.
'It was one-stop shopping
for all things Pablo Escobar.
'After Gaviria announced a new
$1 .4 million reward for Pablo's capture,
'Colonel Pinzón activated a new tip line.
'And apparently he thought Javi and I
were just the guys to oversee it.
'Forget about the fact
that my Spanish was for shit.
'He was side-lining us and there was
nothing we could do about it.
'Pablo would even have his men call in
just to fuck with us.'
(Phone rings)
(In Spanish)
What do you want to report?
(Loud fart over phone)
(Men laughing)
(Steve)
'I'm not sure what we expected.
'To many people, Escobar was a hero.
'It was like asking Chicago
to rat out Michael Jordan.
'And those that didn't worship Escobar,
they were simply too scared to call.
'But we had a system anyways.
'One tip in a particular location
didn't mean shit.
'A second call with the same information
still might not be worth acting on.
'But three calls on the same location
from three different sources?'
- Agent Peña?
- Yeah.
'That had to be checked out.
'Hey, I said it was a system.
'I didn't say it worked.'
Fuck me.
(Man shouts in Spanish) Faggots!
(Men laughing)
(Steve) 'Our inability to catch Escobar
was frustrating.
'But back in Bogotá,
it was becoming a real liability.'
(In Spanish)
Mr De Greiff.
They told me that you met
with Mr Fernando Duque.
That's right.
The president was very clear
when he said that no one was
to communicate with Escobar's people.
Unfortunately for the president,
I don't work for him.
I work for the people of Colombia.
And, just like the president,
I also work for the people of Colombia.
And we should be working
in a united front against Escobar.
- Not in a war...
- Are you afraid of what I might find
if I speak with him, Mr Sandoval?
- Excuse me?
- Tell me something.
Why did you need to be there
that night at La Catedral?
Why was the presence of
the vice minister of justice necessary
to transfer a prisoner?
(Sighs) Because we're not talking about
any prisoner.
We're talking about Pablo Escobar.
And I was only following the orders
of the president.
I don't think that's true.
Are you insinuating something, sir?
- Are you accusing me of something?
- No, I'm not accusing you of anything.
At least, not yet.
But I'm going to open up an
investigation about the allegations...
that, possibly,
you helped Pablo Escobar escape.
You know what, Attorney General?
Eat shit.
(Door closes)
- (Limón) What are we doing here?
- (La Quica) Running an errand.
- What errand?
- For Don Pablo, brother.
Hello, hello.
Hello, gentlemen,
can I help you?
Of course, brother, I'm here to pick up
a package, under the name Alvarez.
Yes, sir.
Right away, with pleasure.
Go ahead.
Brother... let's give up on the girl.
She's not coming back. Hmm?
Are you afraid or what, Limón? Huh?
Close your fucking mouth
and do what I say.
- (Man) Mr Alvarez.
- (Clears throat, coughs)
Quica!
(Man) Best one in the market.
You really know your shit.
Brother!
That's great, brother.
Good.
Boys, put it in the car.
We've got stuff to do.
I'm going to take out her eyes
and make her eat them, that rat bitch.
- What number?
- Room three. I already told you.
(Buzzing)
Bastard. You told me
she'd be here.
(Limón) I don't know, brother.
I think this is where she lives.
(Bangs door)
(Buzzing)
She's not there.
Tomorrow is better.
Or we'll come back later.
Fuck that, brother.
Quica!
Over there, brother.
(Objects clattering)
(La Quica)
I got something.
That bitch. I'm going to rip out her
tongue and shove it up her ass, brother.
I told you she wasn't here.
At this hour, she's already working.
- This is bullshit, brother.
- She's not here.
(La Quica)
We'll come back later, then.
(Retreating footsteps)
If the president
refuses to negotiate,
then we haven't won anything.
Right?
Pablo, we have found
a very good option.
Definitely.
If you let me negotiate with De Greiff,
create some dissension in his ranks...
Oh, Fernando.
That's not why I pay you, Fernando.
You pay me to strategise
and that's exactly what I'm doing.
Pablo, you have to understand...
The moment... The position
that Gaviria is in right now...
What happened at La Catedral
was a humiliating failure for him.
Right now, he's thinking
that capturing you is his only option.
And he's not thinking about
trying to find some way
to speak with us, but...
De Greiff, he is willing to speak.
And he has the autonomy
to make deals.
Fine, OK.
Let's try it.
You're not going to believe it,
but the attorney general
supports the legalisation of drugs.
- Don't bullshit me.
- It's true.
Trust me, Pablo, little by little,
with patience, with time...
What we don't have is time, Fernando.
Fernando, excuse us.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
- Blackie.
- Sir.
Thank you very much, Fernando.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
We can't live like this, Pablo.
Running from one place to another,
hiding,
hoping the government
wants to negotiate.
Gaviria is going to negotiate, Tata.
He's too intelligent and too weak not to.
How are you so calm, huh?
Pablo, if Gaviria doesn't want you in jail
then we know what he wants.
I think it's time for us
to leave Colombia.
I know we said we would never leave,
but things have changed.
No, nothing has changed.
My love, we have everything
we need.
Let's get the children
and go to some other place.
A place where we don't have to hide.
We're not going to
spend our lives in hiding.
I promise you that.
Get ready to get your balls snipped.
So... your wife left.
You're upset,
knocked a few back to numb the pain
and then decide to take it out
on some Wall Street scumbag.
Yeah, something like that.
Isolated incident?
Yeah.
Look, I know I've been in Colombia
for all of about 20 seconds.
Mmh.
Before that,
you and Peña had complete autonomy
to call your own shots.
It's gonna take you a minute
to get used to the new order.
You don't trust me yet? That's fine.
But if I'm gonna have your back,
I need to know I can trust you.
Otherwise, I have no problem
sending you back to your wife in Miami.
Am I making myself clear?
Loud and clear.
Excellent.
You're dismissed.
(Sighs)
(Sighing)
(In Spanish) Ortiz, don't let him
out of your sight. Over.
They saw La Quica buying a toilet.
(In English)
I got "La Quica" and "toilet."
(In Spanish)
Guess which one he bought.
The same one that Pablo had
at La Catedral. A Kohler.
(In English)
All right, now, that I got.
We can't take that to Pinzón.
He'll laugh us out of the office.
(In Spanish)
We need more.
- But what else, Peña?
- Where did they see him?
Going toward the hills
on San Isidro Avenue.
(In English) Maybe we can
get Centra Spike to do a flyover.
Be a lot better than the fucking tip line.
I'll be right back.
(Chatter in Spanish over radio)
- A toilet?
- It's a long story.
- Give me the CliffsNotes.
- Just do me a favour
and ask them to sweep over
that specific area.
We're looking for any chatter from
Escobar's sicarios. Anything at all.
You recognise a voice,
you come get me.
(Over radio) 'Duvall 1 -4-4-3-6,
'we've heard some chatter
at 1600 megahertz. Be advised.'
(Woman, in Spanish) 'Baby,
when are you coming? I'm all alone.'
(Velasco) 'I can't right now.
It's too dangerous.'
(Woman) 'But you said
you were coming.'
(Velasco) 'Let things calm down
a little bit. I'll show you a good time.'
That is definitely Velasco.
No ID on the girl.
What's the deal with the other call?
(Garbled radio chatter)
The quality's too poor
for voice recognition.
(Steve sighs) All right...
these were taken about two hours ago.
What's here is fincas, fincas.
Everything else is smaller houses
here and here, and the outskirts.
You can probably eliminate
the smaller ones, not Escobar's style.
Which of the fincas have road access
both east and west?
(Javier) This one here.
Rough terrain down the back
of the mountain, but drivable.
It's gotta be the one.
We'd have a chance
if we came at him from both sides.
(Messina) Good.
Great. What about Pinzón?
We're gonna need vehicles,
we're gonna need men.
Leave Pinzón to me.
(In Spanish)
Correct me if I'm wrong...
In the last raid,
your two men managed to capture
the president of the United States,
George Bush.
(Messina chuckles)
(In Spanish) That was based on
several calls from the tip line.
This is the voice of Velasco.
Ms Messina, apparently
you think my men work for you.
You are mistaken.
I don't work for you.
I decide how we are going
to work together. Is that clear?
And I know what happened
to the last man that worked with you,
Colonel Carrillo.
He was exiled to Spain.
What did he say?
He said no.
Oh, she's not gonna last.
She gives up pretty fuckin' easy.
(Steve)
'But Messina didn't give up easy.
'She called Crosby...
'Crosby called Gaviria...
'and in less than 15 minutes...'
I understand.
'Pinzón was getting' a kick in the ass.'
(In Spanish)
Colonel, General Silva is on the phone.
Excuse me, Colonel.
(Steve)
'I guess everybody works for somebody.'
General?
(Steve) 'Just because we could
make Pinzón dance
'didn't mean we could call the tune.
'We would've gone in stealth.
Surround the fucker, then grab him.
'Pinzón didn't do shit that way.
He liked kicking down the front door,
'waking up
the whole damn neighbourhood.'
(In Spanish) Move your asses!
The police are coming!
Get the cars and the money ready
right now. They're close, now!
Boss! (Knocks rapidly on door)
Boss, forgive me, it's urgent.
(Knocking continues)
Boss.
It's the police.
They're coming up the hill.
We have to leave right now, boss.
Pablo. Pablo!
Sons of bitches.
They're coming from
the other side too, sir.
- What happened?
- We have to leave.
The police are coming.
- Get the cars ready.
- Yes, boss.
- Wait out back.
Pablo!
Go get the kids.
We have to leave right now.
- (Pablo whispers) Come this way.
- (Indistinct whispers)
(Trucks approaching, stopping nearby)
(Pablo whispering)
Hurry. Through the tunnel.
(Indistinct whispers)
(Indistinct shouts in Spanish)
Surround the house! Let's go!
(Indistinct whispers)
(Soldiers chattering above)
(Silent mouthing)
(Glass clinking)
(Footsteps, chattering above)
(Indistinct whispers)
(Low, indistinct chatter)
(Man speaks Spanish)
They're gone, sir.
Colonel, nobody's in the house,
no signs of life, sir.
Shit.
At ease.
(Steve) 'Don't forget
that Pablo made a career
'of staying ahead of the cops.
'A lot of the fincas he used
had tunnels built just for this purpose.
'Even though he didn't like using them.
'I guess you could say that
he was paranoid, but then again,
'if people are actually after you,
that's not paranoid. That's just smart.'
Peña! Messina!
(Low chatter in Spanish)
(In English) He was here.
(In Spanish)
Go ahead, come in.
The bedrooms...
they're on the right.
Everything is OK, Tata.
No, Pablo.
This time everything is not OK.
Sweetheart, if Pablo
says everything's fine...
Was I talking to you?
I'm talking to my husband.
That was very close, Pablo.
And tomorrow, what?
Do you want the children
to watch those men kill you?
No one is going to die, Tata.
I'm dealing with it.
How, Pablo?
Tell me how.
Negotiating?
Yesterday, they nearly killed you
for negotiating.
If you are going to fix everything,
fix it for good.
Don't worry.
(Spoon clinking in cup)
(Steve) 'You know,
in all the years I chased Escobar,
'I could count on one hand
the times we almost had him.
'And each time, we forgot
the two most important things
'we already knew about him:
'Close doesn't count.
'And Pablo is never more dangerous
than when you almost have him.'
- (Soldiers speak indistinctly)
- (Chatter in Spanish over radio)
(Steve) 'With all the cops on the street,
it was easy to forget...
'this was still Escobar's town.
'He tolerated it all
in the interest of negotiations.
(Man whistles)
'Chasing a man and his family out of
their home in the middle of the night?
'That wasn't a negotiation.
'To Escobar...
'well, that was an act of war.'
(In Spanish) Ready.
Boss, everybody is ready.
What's the order?
Do it.
Yes, sir.
- Huh? What's up?
- Ready.
- All right.
- OK.
- (Man whistles)
- (Indistinct chatter in Spanish)
We're ready, sir.
(Whispers) Come.
(♪ Upbeat Latin ballad playing)
- (♪ Song continues)
- (Tyres screech)
(Men grunting)
(Shouts in Spanish) Step on it!
(Engine revving)
(♪ Song continues)
(Men shouting)
(Indistinct chatter in Spanish)
- (Men grunting)
- (People screaming)
- (Man cries out)
- (Groaning)
Do it, brother.
It's cold, you fucking fag!
Kill him! Do it, bitch! Kill him!
No!
(Indistinct chatter)
(♪ Song continues)
(Chaotic chatter)
(Indistinct shouts)
(Sirens wailing)
(Newswoman reports indistinctly)
(Overlapping chaotic chatter)
(♪ Song continues)
(Man screams)
Peña!
(♪ Song ends)
http://hiqve.com/