[Men shouting in spanish]
[Steve] Pablo Escobar
said, "sometimes I'm god.
If I say a man dies,
he dies the same day."
[Screaming sobs]
In his career, this asshole killed
thousands of police officers
at a rate of over 400 a year.
With numbers like that staring
you in the face, you have to ask...
What possesses a man to put on a uniform
that all but guarantees
his days are numbered?
[Shouting in spanish]
Most of them were just kids,
raised to reach a fork in the
road and choose the right path.
Fight for the good guys.
They were young, they
were full of hope...
And they thought they were invincible.
And those that were left
behind would feel their loss the most.
Everybody's got a breaking point,
when shit sickens them so
much that they just have to act.
For Pinzón, that breaking
point meant resignation.
[Steve] But there were
those who couldn't resign,
who couldn't just walk away.
- [Man shouts orders in spanish]
- Presidents have breaking points, too.
And Gaviria had finally found his.
[Phone ringing]
[latin guitar theme music plays]
[Slow Latin song plays]
[Horse whinnies nearby]
- [juan pablo] We're safe!
- [Man] Pass me the ball.
- [juan pablo] Here you go.
- Here it is.
[Chatter continues outside]
[gato]
[Children laughing]
[Helicopter approaching]
[Indistinct]
[Steve] This is Gilberto
Rodriguez Orejuela.
And if you've never heard of him,
it's because that's
exactly the way he wants it.
Ask him what he does for a living and
he'll tell you that he's a banker,
and that would be true.
In fact, he and his brother
Miguel controlled their own bank.
Or he might tell you that he and
his brother owned and operated
one of Colombia’s largest
chains of drug stores.
The brothers could also tell you they
ran their own soccer team.
Which they did.
América de Cali, one of the
best teams on the continent
and a fierce rival of
Pablo’s Atlético national.
But what they'd never tell you is
that these businesses were a front
and that the Rodriguez brothers
were the second biggest cocaine
traffickers in the world:
The leaders of the Cali cartel.
Like Pablo and the Medellín cartel,
they started out as
run-of-the-mill criminals: Bank robbers.
And with all that money they
scored from their heists,
they quickly graduated
to smuggling weed.
And when they realized
that ten pounds of blow
was worth as much as a ton of marijuana,
they jumped headfirst into
the cocaine business.
These guys were no piece
of shit street dealers.
They planned meticulously, maximizing
profit, minimizing risk.
As the business grew, a
young ambitious Colombian kid,
a guy you might know named Pacho
Herrera, was such a good earner
that the brothers
eventually promoted him to partner.
But they had a competitor,
and not just any competitor.
One that wasn't interested in
abdicating the throne
as the king of coke.
- Don Pablo.
- But Gilberto was smart.
He didn't care that
Escobar wore the crown.
So they went to him with a proposal,
Miami, the cocaine capital of the world,
would remain Pablo’s territory, and
in return, the Rodriguez brothers
would make do with a little territory
in the northeast called new york city.
- [Up-tempo dance music plays]
- The extra 1,089 miles may have made it
a little harder to get to, but
it turns out the folks in new york
were just as head over heels for
cocaine as the folks down south.
And while there were 1.8
million people in Miami,
there were seven
million in new york city.
As much as the Cali guys loved
money and the finer things in life,
they hated the wrong kind of attention.
For the "gentlemen of Cali," it was
about appearing like
legitimate businessmen.
And business was good. But that
didn't mean that it couldn't get better.
[Steve] This was one thing that the
Cali guys and the DEA could agree on.
As controversial as colonel
Carrillo's methods were,
he was the only guy that
Escobar was afraid of.
And returning
command of search bloc to him
was exactly what we needed.
The president has offered us every
available resource to defeat Escobar.
All we have to do now
is manage it properly.
So I'm still gonna rely
on intelligence from you.
But we're gonna do
things a little bit differently.
No more large-scale operations.
Search bloc goes back
to small-scale tactics.
- Amen.
- Stealth operations, surprise raids,
that sort of thing. We change the game.
But there's one thing that
we need to do first. Trujillo.
A hundred men? That's not
exactly small-scale tactics.
First thing is, we let
Pablo know that we're back.
[Sirens chirping]
[Steve] Now you can bet that the
second a convoy of a hundred men
and six marked police
trucks leave that base,
that Escobar's army of spotters would
be burning up the phone lines
- just to tell Escobar all about it.
- [Phone rings]
[Steve] And you'd be
right. But that was the point.
You see, these spotters made
it impossible for us to operate
in the secrecy we required.
So we needed to blind them.
And the first step to blinding someone
is getting them to open their eyes.
Probably this rooftop here.
[Steve] Once those signals
went up, we could pick them up,
get a fix and get a
location of each one.
[Men chattering in spanish]
[Man]
[Steve] And I guess you could say that
the second part of Carrillo's plan
was to show Pablo that the
sheriff was back in town.
And he did that the best way he could.
Hmm.
- We got 'em.
- Keeps going like that
until you reached barrio Pablo Escobar.
We captured six radio transmissions.
But we haven't
pinpointed the exact location.
- No, sir.
- So our best bet
is to corner each of these
buildings. This time, we hit the ground.
Peña, you're with me.
Murphy, Jacoby, you
stay here to guide us.
- Careful out there.
- [Javier sighs]
[Up-tempo Latin song plays]
[Laughing]
- [Indistinct chatter in spanish]
- [Engines start]
- [In spanish]
- [Weapons cocking]
[Man]
Oh, we got one. Spotter one is down.
[Mutters in spanish]
[Man shouts]
-
- [Man whistles]
- [Woman chatters in spanish]
-
- Shut up, kid.
[Carrillo cocks pistol]
[Carrillo]
[pablo]
[Dishes clattering]
-
- [Hermilda] Tata.
Javi, where are the fucking spotters?
Carrillo went a different
way. He, uh... he cut them loose.
Oh, we're letting people go now?
Yeah, Murphy, we're letting people go.
And what does that mean?
- Don't worry about it, man.
- Hey, fucking talk to me.
- Let go of my fucking arm.
- What the fuck happened?
Carrillo put a gun to the kid's
head and he pulled the trigger.
To make a fucking point.
We good now?
[Engine starts]
Yeah, we're good.
[Up-tempo Latin music playing]
[Grunts]
[La Quica sighs]
[Sighs]
[Starts engine]
[Knocks on door]
I'd like to talk to you about
what happened tonight.
- What do you think happened?
- I know I got left behind on purpose.
For your own best interest.
You don't know a goddamn
thing about my best interest.
You know, Murphy, what happens out
there isn't really for everyone.
- But it is for Peña?
- You're not Peña.
- 'Cause I'm a damn gringo.
- Because I trust him.
Why don't you try me?
This fight against
Escobar, you want to win it.
These guys aren't fighting by
the same rules, so why should we?
- You know what that means?
- Oh, I do.
So whether this is about protecting
me or protecting you, stop icing me out.
[Door opens]
[Men murmur in spanish]
[velasco]
[Phone ringing]
Peña.
This is Moncada's biggest lab.
It'll have to be inventoried before
it's dismantled and moved.
How you know that?
- One of my ci's.
- Hell of a tip.
It's a hell of a Ci.
Look, you want Escobar's
men, there they are.
- Let's do it.
- All right.
[Rap music playing inside]
[Men shouting in spanish]
- [Automatic gunfire]
- [Shouting continues]
Get up! Move! Move!
Get up!
[Men chattering in spanish]
[Man]
Your Ci hooked us a pretty big fish.
Yeah, he's a winner.
Wonder if he'll give us Escobar.
- Don't know, we'll see what Carrillo gets.
- Yeah. We'll see.
Carrillo told me that he talked
to you. He thinks he can trust you.
Yeah, he can.
- That's not what I mean.
- Ahh.
Let's go.
I'm a big boy. I can handle it.
Yeah.
- You get anything out of him?
- Something.
Not everything. Are you coming?
I'm in, yeah. Let's go.
-
- Pablo.
[pablo sighs]
[Chuckles]
[Man screams]
[valeria]
[Faint screaming]
[Sighs]
[Line ringing]
[Rings]
[Dialing]
[Phone rings]
Hello?
- Steve?
- Hey, baby.
What time is it?
Uh...
It's late.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm... good. I just
need to hear your voice.
I wanted to call, Steve. I...
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
What's happened?
Tell me.
I'm good, baby. I'm...
Don't worry. [Clears throat]
[Baby crying]
[Crying continues over phone]
You have to go.
Let's talk tomorrow. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Good night.
[Heavy breathing]
[Grunts]
[Up-tempo Latin music playing]