The Lord of the Skies!
How fucking elegant, motherfucker.
-Don't tease.
-God damn, fucker.
-Your little brother?
-Yes. Alvaro.
Come here, son.
-You also get a hug.
-Sir.
How are you doing?
320 million kinds of okay.
Doesn't it smell like
the fucking US. Treasury in here?
-This half is yours.
-Yes?
-Don't forget it.
-All right. We came at a good time, then.
A Tuesday like any other, Pacho.
You know how it is.
Motherfucker.
-Let's go to the house.
-Let's go.
-All right. Son, do you like margaritas?
-Of course I do.
Great, because I have a Margarita for you.
She'll suck you dry.
Let's go.
Take the money and destroy the plane.
-Gracias.
-Captain Calderón.
We're happy to be here.
And what brings you to Cali?
We've got some addresses
we want to investigate.
Cartel-related?
Not necessarily.
What a surprise.
DEA agents that don't trust us.
How did that work out
for the last two guys?
Friend, in Cali, there are more
corrupt cops than there are churches.
You don't trust me? I understand.
But if you want to get anything done
in Cali, you need the police's help.
If not me, someone else.
Not my rule.
-I understand.
-Good.
The addresses are linked
to cartel financial operations.
We want to put eyes on them.
See if any of the dots start connecting...
You've come a long way to connect dots.
We work with what we've got.
Unless you can tell me where I can find
Gilberto and Miguel Rodriguez.
If they didn't own half of the city,
I couldn't even be sure they exist.
The Rodriguez brothers are ghosts.
He served as director at Interamericas.
The Rodriguez brothers' bank.
They later gave him a more important job.
-Do you have an address for Jurado?
-I can get it for you.
So what happened
since the last time I saw you?
Are you going to take these men on,
or what?
-I'm going to do my job.
-And your bosses?
Do they know what you're doing?
The dining room is over here.
You have a room over here.
You have another one over here.
And here, you have the living room.
The dimmer is over here.
And you can adjust the light.
Well... you get the idea.
-No. I don't understand.
-What don't you understand?
Does this seem normal to you?
You indicated to Mr. Rodriguez
you were uncertain about returning
to the North Valley.
And that's why he bought me a palace.
With dimmers.
Please tell Don Miguel thank you,
but I need to think about
his generous offer.
We have that dinner tonight.
With your friends?
With the investors.
They're not going to like
the six month delay.
And I think it's best if we don't mention
the Rodriguez brothers by name.
I know you're embarrassed by what I do.
I know you did it for your family.
But if these people like everything
they hear tonight,
you'll have your own security firm
the second these six months are up.
-Ready!
-Good!
A choir!
All right, say goodbye to Dad.
We're leaving.
-Bye.
All right. Let's go, or we'll be late.
Will you make it on time?
If you're wearing the dress
with the flowers, yes.
Let's go, girls.
Today is a busy day for us, boys.
Bosses have meetings all day
at the National Hotel.
I need you to pre-sweep
each and every location on this schedule.
And I don't want a bunch of cars parked
like bullshit, blocking escape routes.
-He's looking at you, Montez.
-Of course I'm talking to you, you idiot.
Don Miguel's team on channel six.
Don Gilberto's, channel eight.
Jorge says that the DEA is visiting Cali.
Two agents from Bogotà. They're new.
They're working with the National Police.
But they don't have warrants.
They're tourists.
They need permission
to wipe their own asses.
Regardless, while they're in Cali,
we'll be watching them.
-That's your job, Enrique, my brother.
-Yes, sir.
That's all, gentlemen.
Communicate. Stay safe. Get to work.
I have to duck out early.
It's a work thing for Paola.
Of course.
Do you want to practice your English?
Starkman, the American lawyer,
arrives today.
Can you pick him up from the airport?
Aren't you worried about the tourists?
The second team's
never as good as the first.
If they were ever there at all.
Where are we headed next?
INTERNATIONAL ARRIVALS
I assume you would prefer U.S. currency?
Of course.
Currency aside, we aren't in the habit
of paying for things in advance.
What guarantee do we have
that you will provide what you promise?
Forgive my brother.
We are grateful for the support
you and your people have offered.
This afternoon, our associate,
Mr. Pallomari,
will prepare the contribution
and arrange delivery.
Very well.
The contribution should be divided
among seven men.
Their names are on the list.
All right, very well. Going forward,
I think it's best if Mr. Pallomari deals
with my colleague, Mr. Giraldo.
As you wish.
Have a great day, gentlemen.
Well, our surrender has been bought.
Now it must be paid for.
And they say we're the criminals.
Sons of bitches.
Small price to pay, brother,
for the rest of your life.
Gentlemen, I will prepare
these payments myself,
as soon as I'm back in the office.
And I'll make sure
that all of this is in order.
Mr. Starkman is next, the lawyer.
The Arellano Felix brothers
are still wasting time with heroin.
Hey! What? You're not going to say hello?
-Hello.
-Are you in a bad mood or what?
Amado... this is the life.
You guys helped me.
I moved the last 100 tons
in less than 50 days.
You tell me if we're a great team or not.
That's why we're here.
Can you handle a bigger package?
I'm the Lord of the Skies, brother.
What do you think?
I can move however much you give me.
I just have two questions: How much?
And for how much longer, Pacho?
Because I know about your deal.
I know you want to turn yourselves in.
There is a deal on the table, Amado.
But we have six months
to turn ourselves in. That's the truth.
Until then,
we will honour our commitment to you.
Right, and after?
What happens after that?
The business will adjust.
This I know. It will always adjust.
This will never end.
There will be other partners
and more drugs. But what about you?
What will happen to you?
You can't tell me you're going to retire,
as if this was any normal business.
You know this is a way of life.
It retires you when it's done with you.
Or are you going to start playing golf
like an old man?
We need to count on you maintaining
the same terms on this last shipment.
Done.
It'll be my gift to the Gentlemen of Cali.
All right? But...
you have to come with me to Juérez.
-I want to show you something.
-What is it?
The future, Pacho.
The fucking future, that's all.
-Here's your passport.
-Thank you.
All right, and you board through Gate 15.
-Have a great trip.
-Thank you.
Have a great day.
Next.
SEARCH WARRANT
This is the kind of bullshit I don't like.
Are you playing me or what?
I need a tactical team sent to 15th Street
and 4th Avenue, copy?
Copy that. Requesting a tactical team
at 15th Street and 4th Avenue.
You do realize, don't you,
after we surrender,
all of this shit will end.
No more sitting by the pool,
smoking your cigar,
telling everyone what to do.
Look, Miguel,
I'm tired of telling people what to do.
And no one has ever listened to you.
What's the difference?
But you know what?
Never, in human history, have two brothers
accomplished what we have.
We aren't the first people in history
to build an empire, Gilberto.
But we're the first to retire
leaving the empire intact.
If Mom were alive, she'd be proud.
Brothers are well, nephews are well,
sons are well.
Boss, we just heard a call
that a tactical team left Jamundi station
heading to 4th Avenue.
Enrique, where are you?
Watching our visitors from the DEA.
They've been checking addresses
all over town.
But right now, they're stopped,
just doing nothing.
Yes, but where are you?
At 15th Street and... 4th. On 4th Avenue.
Enrique, fuck!
There's a police convoy coming at you!
Get Pallomari out of there now!
Answer, you bastard, answer.
-Hello? What's up?
-Listen, it's Salcedo.
You're going to have unwelcome guests.
Leave now.
I don't have time for this.
I'm supervising an important project.
That's exactly why I need you to get out.
Just because you say so?
I know you're arranging an important
transaction for the bosses this afternoon.
Listen, this is none of your business.
I'll bet your desk is covered
with American dollars.
Look, Guillermo, please.
You've got papers. You've got names.
You've got things that shouldn't be seen.
-Jorge...
-Get out of there!
You do your job and I'll do mine.
This is my job! I'm telling you...
Son of a bitch!
Fuck your mother.
I need you to check the paper shredders
and the floppy disks
still in the computers.
Invoices. Bills of lading.
Anything on the computers.
Let's go.
Fucking shit!
-Gentlemen, how may I help you?
-Seventh floor. Mr. Pallomari's office.
All right. I'll let them know you're here
so you can head up.
People love surprises.
Gentlemen, you can't...
You. What the fuck
are you still doing here?
What the fuck am I doing? My job.
We told your associate the same thing.
Sorry, boss, I tried, but he won't listen.
-You go get the car.
-Please get out.
-I have to finish this. Fuck your mother.
-Take the back stairs.
-Yes, sir.
-Finish what?
My job, Jorge.
No. Please, we have to get rid
of all of that now.
We aren't arguing.
You aren't touching anything.
I've got a method and a system.
-A method and a system?
-Yes, sir.
Yes? What you've got is ten years of jail
time sitting on your desk, you idiot.
-Get out.
Attention! Colombian National Police!
Where are the files?
Get to work. Let's go!
This is an office.
We're working. How can I help you?
We need access to your files, invoices,
and all of your correspondence.
If that's the case,
I need to see a warrant.
Are you supposed to be in charge?
Well, yes, I'm in charge.
Good morning.
I have to see every invoice you have.
Hey!
This says documents only.
Fuck your mother.
You didn't get that?
Only papers. Documents only.
Keep an eye on the things
they're taking. Now!
Yes, sir.
Leave it. Let it be.
Chivo, check everything
and make an inventory, all right?
That's private.
Ignacio, please show the gentleman
last year's documents.
This way, please.
I must insist.
Do you have a bill of lading'?
Yes? Let me see.
More? Everything.
-Just these?
-And the copies below.
-These as well, no?
-Yes, sir.
-All right. '93. Yeah?
-Those are the most recent.
EVIDENCE
Grab that.
This 24-hour party thing...
is tiring after a couple of days.
Can you imagine if it was your life?
What's on your mind?
Dad, and the last thing he said to me.
What? "Get the fuck out"?
No.
He said... that in this world...
there was no place for a man like me.
I made a place for myself.
I proved him wrong.
And now, I have to give it all up.
What kind of man would I be
if I gave it all up?
I don't know, brother.
But what I do know is that you have
a couple billion dollars...
and the rest of your life
to figure it out.
What are they giving me?
What do you mean,
"What are they giving you?"
They took my son, didn't they?
They have to give us something.
Have they offered you something?
An apartment.
Accept it.
Afterwards, I'll sell it for cash.
We'll take their money now.
Later, we'll take vengeance.
-Do it, then get back up here.
—Can you wake Pedro up?
-I want to speak with him.
-Don't worry about Pedro. He's sleeping.
I heard we cut it close today.
I thought they didn't have a warrant.
That's what I was told
by our friend on the force.
A few more seconds
and we'd have had real trouble.
Those new DEA guys
are sharper than they look.
Well, luckily, we have you.
Did they get anything?
Some files.
So nothing. Good.
I'll take care of the rest today.
That thing you've got tonight with Paola,
enjoy yourself. Go on.
But anything we find
we'll be sure to share with you.
I was instructed
you should be back in Bogotà tonight.
You're going out on the last flight.
-And where are they now?
-I just put them on a plane to Bogota'.
-And the files?
-We've got them.
Are you sure?
Look, they tricked me
with that fucking warrant, all right?
And I couldn't warn you because we were
all together like a fucking family.
These Americans know what they're doing.
They aren't fucking idiots.
Well, the truth is, we're very interested
in your proposal, Jorge.
And in your potential for growth.
You've exceeded Paola's description,
which wasn't easy.
Of course, we were inconvenienced
by the six-month delay, which...
took us by surprise.
I take my commitments very seriously,
gentlemen.
And I couldn't leave without ensuring
my replacement met the standard
they've come to expect.
Go wait for him over there.
-Good evening. How are you?
-Good, thank you.
Well, I think that merits
another bottle of wine, no?
Yes.
Look at that son of a bitch.
Thinks his shit doesn't stink, or what?
Thank you.
So, a security expert married to a rising
star in one of Cali's top law firms.
Have you worked together before?
My compliments.
David Rodriguez.
How are you?
Don't let the elegant suit fool you.
This guy's a real son of a bitch.
Seriously.
In fact, he's one of our best men.
You see?
Enjoy it.
Ma'am.
You... Where do you know him from?
Is he a friend of yours?
You know Cali is a very small city.
Even more so
when one is in the security business.
One must deal with all sorts of people.
Is that the paperwork
I'm supposed to deliver?
These documents are very sensitive.
And I don't feel comfortable
transferring possession to anyone else.
All right. Let's go, then.
Open the door, Cordova.
Go fuck yourself, Pallomari.
In the front seat.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Open the door. Fuck your mother.
In the front.
I'm not your fucking employee.
Look, I haven't been able to reach
an agreement yet. He's very stubborn.
Listen to me, Pacho.
We have to seal the deal.
It's very important.
Amado has to go to Juérez tomorrow.
I'll go with him and close the deal.
All right. Keep me informed.
Good night.
Good night, Gilberto.
Compliments of Mr. Carrillo.
It's been a long time
since anyone asked me on a date.
Come in, please.
Take a seat.
Sir... your offer of this apartment
is very generous.
But?
But... I would like to know the terms.
The terms?
How often will you come here to visit me?
As often as you like.
Or never.
This is your home.
Is there a monthly stipend?
A stipend?
Mr. Rodriguez, I married Claudio Salazar
when I was 18 years old.
I knew nothing.
Now I need to get away from his family,
and I need my son back.
If you could help me with that...
I can.
Then I accept.
It's great to hear that.
Why don't you get some rest?
Eat something.
Tomorrow morning, I'll send for your son.
How does that sound?
Good.
Take a seat.
Sorry to interrupt.