One!
Rosa!
Tell me who talked to the police!
Who talked to them?
It had to be that whore in the market.
Please, Quica!
Thanks for accepting the invitation.
Forgive me for the hood.
It's for security reasons.
- I hope you understand.
- I understand.
Can I offer you something? Coffee, water?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
Let's begin, then.
- Do you regret going to jail a year ago?
- Absolutely not. In fact...
what I regret least is having escaped.
The Special Forces came in
and opened fire.
I couldn't risk putting my life
in their hands, right?
However...
I hope this interview
makes it clear to the president...
I am willing to return to any prison
in the District of Antioquia.
The most modest and the most humble.
But before that, I have to examine
the conditions they are going to put me in
because, look, it would be easy,
for example, for someone to rig a car bomb
that would explode when I arrived.
It turns out that my problem
turned into a political problem.
It appears that I am very important
to the re-election
of the president of the United States.
I will always be ready to pay for
my mistakes and accept a humble jail cell
when my rights are respected
and they guarantee me that I will not
be transferred anywhere for any reason.
Do you acknowledge that
you have committed crimes in the past,
or that you ordered someone's death?
That answer one could
only give to a priest.
In a confessional.
Marietta.
- What's up?
- What happened?
It looks like they killed them.
I think there were six or seven girls.
Who would do something so horrible?
Are you, by nature, violent and proud?
Those who know me
know I have a great sense of humor.
I would say that I'm a happy man.
I've always been happy.
I've always been optimistic.
I've always had faith in life.
I always sing in the shower.
How do you think the story
of Pablo Escobar will end?
Well... one can never know.
I can only hope for the best.
I would like to die on my own two feet.
In the year 3047.
Look behind you. Watch out for that guy.
That's it.
Smash the telephone booth.
Get the pipe.
I already know, Dad.
You have to get it.
And what's that, a woman?
I'm about to fight a woman or what?
- Her name's Nora.
- Oh, yeah, what's her name?
Nora.
Boss, excuse the interruption.
One moment, please.
How do you...?
What about the laboratories?
It's been difficult
to find the Moncada laboratories, boss.
And the ones that we find,
we can't get inside.
There are police checkpoints everywhere.
We lost four men
trying to get through one.
Sons of bitches.
And what about Judy Moncada?
We can't find her anywhere. Or Don Berna.
Find her.
Yes, sir.
And you, boys?
Everything is good, boss.
- How are you, Limón?
- Very good, sir.
- How are you feeling?
- Very good, boss.
- Comfortable?
- Thank you. Very good.
Good.
I'm going to teach you something.
There is nothing lower than a rat.
And if we let the rats run free,
the streets will be filled with them.
- Understand me?
- Yes, boss.
Give me one second. One second.
Boss, excuse me. It's Fernando.
- Tell me, Fernando.
- Your interview clearly worked, Don Pablo.
Palacio wants to meet with me right away.
You heard that, brother?
- We have to finish our little job.
- But we already finished it, right?
No, brother, there's still one left.
But you already killed all the whores.
I'm not talking about whores, brother.
Why her?
- She did everything we told her to.
- Someone talked to the police.
Yeah, it was those fucking whores.
She is someone I can trust, man.
You can trust her, but I can't.
Move it.
Quica.
I'm not going to tell you again, brother.
And we've got some shit we gotta do first.
Good day.
I have a meeting with the president.
I am Fernando Duque.
Your meeting is not
with the president, Mr. Duque.
How's that?
- With the vice minister, then?
- No, sir.
The information I have here says
your meeting is with the attorney general.
My apologies, Mr. Duque.
Mr. Duque...
I believe the whole world
has the right to a fair trial.
Pablo Escobar has the same rights
as any other Colombian.
If he has committed a crime,
he must be judged and indicted.
He can't be hunted and killed
like an animal.
Mr. De Greiff,
everything you're telling me I find...
fascinating.
However, I don't--
I don't buckle under the pressure
of the Americans...
like Gaviria, Mr. Duque.
Then that means that...
you would consider...
making a deal with Pablo.
I am saying that Colombia...
has been at war far too long.
Of course.
The Americans are bringing in new people.
Different faces but, ultimately,
with the same motivation.
They are using us
to advance their political agenda.
Perhaps.
But the reality is we have to accept help
wherever it comes from.
And right now,
the gringos are very limited,
confined to Carlos Holguín
and the embassy.
On the other hand, Pablo Escobar
is gaining ground, gathering more support.
Everyone is helping him in Medellín.
- A long manhunt plays into his hands.
- Let's talk about Medellín.
Colonel Pinzón basically
has Escobar surrounded.
Do you think we'll succeed?
Tip line. What do you want to report?
Agent Peña?
Pansies!
Attorney General De Greiff.
They told me that you met
with Mr. Fernando Duque.
That's right.
The president was very clear
when he said that no one
was to communicate with Escobar's people.
Unfortunately for the president,
I don't work for him.
I work for the people of Colombia.
And, just like the president,
I also work for the people of Colombia.
And we are all working together,
in a united front, against Escobar.
- This isn't a single war--
- Are you afraid of what I might find
if I speak with him, Mr. Sandoval?
- Excuse me?
- Tell me something.
Why did you need to be there
that night at La Catedral?
Why was the presence of
the vice minister of justice necessary
to transfer a prisoner?
Because we're not talking about
any prisoner, Attorney General.
We're talking about Pablo Escobar.
And I was only following the orders
of the president.
I don't think that's true.
Are you insinuating something,
Attorney General?
- Are you accusing me of something?
- No, I'm not accusing you of anything.
At least, not yet.
But I'm going to open up an investigation.
About the allegations...
that, possibly,
you helped Pablo Escobar escape.
You know what, Attorney General?
Eat shit.
- What the hell are we doing here?
- Running an errand, brother.
- What errand?
- For Don Pablo, brother.
Hello.
Hello, gentlemen,
can I help you with something?
Of course, brother, I'm here to pick up
a package, under the name Alvarez.
Yes, sir. Right away, with pleasure.
Go ahead.
Brother... let's give up on the girl.
She's not coming back.
Are you afraid or what, Limón?
Close your fucking mouth
and do what I say.
Mr. Alvarez!
Quica!
This is the best toilet they make.
You really know your shit.
Brother!
That's what I'm talking about, brother.
Good.
Boys, put it in the car.
We've got some business to take care of.
I am going to take out her eyes
and make her eat them, that rat bitch.
- What number?
- Room three. I already told you.
Son of a bitch. You told me
that she was going to be here.
I don't know, brother.
I think this is where she lives.
She's not there.
Anyway, tomorrow is better.
We'll come back later.
Fuck that, brother.
Quica!
Over there, brother.
I got something, brother.
That bitch. I'm going to rip out her
tongue and shove it up her ass, brother.
I told you she wasn't here.
At this hour, she's already working.
- This is bullshit, brother.
- She's not here.
We'll come back later, then.
If the president
doesn't agree with the deal,
then we haven't won anything. Right?
Pablo, we have found a very good option.
Definitely.
If you allow me to negotiate
with De Greiff
- and create some dissention in the ranks--
- Oh, Fernando.
That's not why I pay you, Fernando.
You pay me to strategize
and that's exactly what I am doing.
Pablo, you have to understand...
The moment-- The position
that Gaviria is in right now--
What happened at La Catedral
was a humiliating failure for him.
Right now, he's thinking
that capturing you is his only option.
And he's not thinking about
trying to find some way
to speak with us, but...
De Greiff, he is willing to speak.
And he has the autonomy to make deals.
Fine, okay.
Let's try it.
You're not going to believe it,
but the attorney general
supports the legalization of drugs.
- Don't bullshit me.
- It's true.
Trust me, Pablo, little by little,
with patience, with time--
What we don't have is time, Fernando.
Fernando, excuse us.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
- Blackie.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you very much, Fernando.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
We can't live like this, Pablo.
Running from one place to another, hiding,
hoping the government wants to negotiate.
Gaviria is going to negotiate, Tata.
He's too intelligent and too weak not to.
How are you so calm?
Pablo, if Gaviria doesn't want you in jail
then we know perfectly well what he wants.
I think it's time for us
to leave Colombia.
I know we agreed we would never leave,
but things have changed.
No, nothing has changed.
My love, we have everything we need.
Let's get the children
and go to some other place.
A place where we don't have to hide.
We're not going to
spend our lives in hiding.
I promise you that.
Ortiz, don't let him
out of your sight. Over.
They saw La Quica buying a toilet.
Not just any toilet.
The same one that Pablo had
at La Catedral. A Kohler.
We need more.
- But what else, Peña?
- Where did they see him?
Going toward the hills on San Isidro Road.
Baby, when are you coming?
You left me all alone.
I can't right now. It's too dangerous.
But you said you were coming.
Let things calm down a little bit.
I'll show you a good time.
Correct me if I'm wrong...
In the last raid,
your two men managed to capture
the president of the United States,
George Bush.
That was based on many different calls
from the tip line.
This is the voice of Velasco.
Ms. Messina, apparently
you think my men work for you.
You are mistaken. I don't work for you.
I decide how we are going
to work together. Is that clear?
And I already know what happened
to the last man that worked with you.
Colonel Carrillo.
He was exiled to Spain.
Colonel, General Silva is on the phone.
Excuse me, Colonel.
General?
Move your asses! The police are coming!
Get the cars and the money ready
right now. They're close, now!
Boss!
Boss, forgive me, it's urgent.
Boss.
It's the police.
They're coming up the hill.
We have to leave right now, boss.
Pablo. Pablo!
Sons of bitches.
They're coming from
the other side too, sir.
- What happened?
- We have to leave right now.
The police are coming.
- Get the cars ready.
- Yes, boss.
- Wait out back.
Pablo!
Go get the kids.
We have to leave right now.
Come this way. Hurry up!
Hurry. Over here, through the tunnel.
Surround the house! Let's go!
They're gone, sir.
Colonel, nobody's in the house,
no signs of life, sir.
Shit.
At ease.
Go ahead, come in.
The bedrooms...
they're on the right.
Everything is okay, Tata.
No, Pablo.
This time everything is not okay.
Sweetheart, if Pablo
says everything is okay,
- it's because everything is--
- Was I talking to you?
I'm talking to my husband.
That was very close, Pablo.
And tomorrow, what?
Do you want your children
to watch those men kill you?
No one is going to die, Tata.
I am dealing with it.
How, Pablo?
Tell me how.
Negotiating?
Yesterday, they nearly killed you
for negotiating.
If you are going to fix everything,
fix it for good.
Don't worry.
Ready.
Boss, everybody is ready.
What's the order?
Do it.
Yes, sir.
- What's up?
- Ready.
All right.
We're ready, sir.
Come.
Step on it!
Do it, brother.
It's cold, you fucking fag!
Kill him! Do it, bitch!
Kill him!