Beloved countrymen, the New Liberalism
party is the only force in Colombia
that is not afraid of narco-traffickers.
“There are three ways
the narco-traffickers …
—try to weaken extradition.”
—… try to weaken extradition.
—“Bribery …”
—Bribery …
—“… intimidation through violence …”
—… intimidation through violence …
—“… and extortion.”
—… and extortion!
—“A dark and terrible scourge.”
—A dark and terrible scourge.
What are you doing?
Just making sure he gets it right.
You wrote it, you should know.
Look, I brought you this.
What’s this?
Clean socks.
Your wife dropped them off before we left.
How’s Galán doing?
All right.
I wish he didn’t focus so much
on extradition of narcos.
There are other things to mention.
Galán’s got some balls.
Brave men have a way of dying.
Well, then …
you don’t have to worry … do you?
Pass me the socks.
Do you sleep with all your informants?
I’m not your responsibility.
If Pablo Escobar finds you …
he’ll kill you in a heartbeat.
Not if I kill him first.
Look at this shit.
We are spending millions of dollars …
and can’t even get a decent meal anywhere.
Listen … the problem isn’t the food,
the problem is Noriega.
First chance he gets,
he’ll sell us to the Americans.
You guys stay calm.
Once we reach an agreement
with the government,
we will be back in our homeland.
Pay the Colombian national debt
for amnesty?
I’d rather go live in Spain.
I say we go back and fight.
No, sir, none of that.
War is bad for business.
We will negotiate with them
as Pablo agreed.
Let’s see, Gustavo.
None of this would’ve happened
if he hadn’t started
killing politicians and judges.
Tell me what we are supposed to do, then.
Do you want to sit here
and cry over spilled milk?
You know something, Pablo?
Sometimes, I think you kill these men
because they won’t let you in their club.
You better watch your mouth, asshole.
The Colombian government
has refused our amnesty offer.
Get used to the food, gentlemen.
It’s not safe to go back home.
They’ve rejected our amnesty deal.
We may have to stay.
I hate this place.
We can go someplace else.
I hear Switzerland is very beautiful.
In Switzerland, we are nobody, Pablo.
What good is having all the money
in the world if you can’t go home?
If we go back …
I’m going to have to fight.
Do whatever is necessary, my love.
You’re way ahead in the polls.
In my opinion, the outcome is decided.
My question is … why do you keep
getting involved with the narcos?
I want a country at peace.
And if I don’t do it, who will?
You’re pushing them into a corner.
I’m wearing a vest.
I’m afraid that a bulletproof vest …
isn’t enough to ensure
that you have a future.
Don’t worry, my friend.
There will be a future.
Let’s speak clearly, brother.
Galán’s dead.
You had him killed, didn’t you?
You didn’t tell us shit,
and you killed him, you son of a bitch.
—I want to go home, Fabio.
—Home?
Why are we going home?
So they can capture us?
All this shit you like to talk about our
partnership, and then this on your own?
Galán was the only threat.
There is no one left to challenge us.
And you know why, Fabio.
Because no one has the balls that we have.
Going home.
That unique honesty.
The village stands up
and calls for justice.
I pray to God …
that this sacrifice will serve at last …
for society to react … and bond …
to support the government …
and institutions …
but also …
demanding a more effective work …
undeterred by the hitman and hijacking
or any other manifestation of violence.
My father, Luis Carlos Galán,
will be remembered
for awakening the Colombian people
to the danger of the narcos.
The assassin’s bullets …
will not stop what my father began.
As he fell, another rises in his place.
I want to tell Dr César Gaviria …
in the name of the people and my family …
that we entrust my father’s ideals to him,
and that he can count on our support …
to become the president
Colombia wants and needs.
Dr César Gaviria, save Colombia!
Phone!
Let it go to the answering machine.
The machine’s full.
I wish it would stop ringing.
It’s your friends.
They’re calling to offer support.
Or opinions about what I should do.
Why can’t you run
without backing extradition?
—I wrote those speeches.
—Yes …
but do you even believe them?
I don’t know what I believe.
I don’t want the narcos having free reign.
But I don’t want the United States
involved in our affairs.
So say nothing.
That’s the best way to stay alive.
Gentlemen.
Fernando, cheer up. Have a drink.
We’re going home!
—How are you?
—Fine, my love.
What about you?
Give me one.
Margarita, right?
Let’s see.
—Son of a bitch, that’s good.
—Right.
Thank you.
Listen, I’ve got a question for you.
Why are we going back?
We’re walking into a world of shit.
Relax, brother.
Spain’s too far away
to protect our interests.
We have a better chance
of influencing Pablo at home.
We need to be close by. Relax.
Don’t you get it?
He’s only comfortable at war.
He’s taking us to the slaughter.
How’s business?
Fucking Noriega is charging us a fortune,
but we got 175 tons to Miami.
Gacha’s Mexican routes
are opening up Los Angeles.
But do you know what matters most
for our business, Pablo?
That the situation at home stays calm.
OK.
You should have consulted me about Galán.
You would have tried to talk me out of it.
I would have tried.
The amount of money we are losing
is due to that bullshit.
Are you listening?
Look at those peaks, Gustavo.
I’ll die …
before I ever leave Colombia again.
What’s happening, Carrillo?
So you practice your English with me?
Yes.
I definitely like the red one best.
Truly?
I prefer the grey.
Red is the colour of the party,
and it makes you more …
sociable and close to the people.
And that’s important.
I wonder what Luis Carlos
would have chosen?
You know, we should
also hire an image consultant.
We have to make you more appealing
to the youth with a new look.
Now you are going to give me image advice?
I’m just thinking about the polls.
Anyway …
Galán had professionals at his side,
but which could he trust?
And you know well
that you can trust me, right?
Well, what are you going to choose,
red or grey?
Luis Carlos said something to me
before he died.
“There will be a future.”
Now let’s see what kind of future it is.
We worked together in the ministry.
The idea he’s a presidential candidate
shows you our sad state of affairs.
I need to know which side he is on.
He speaks with
the Foreign Press next week.
They’ll certainly ask his position.
Don’t worry, Pablo.
He’ll be easy to influence.
—No, I disagree.
—Why?
I did an interview with him once,
when he was an economic advisor.
I found him sitting in the parking lot
in his beat-up Renault,
eating a bag of apples …
and reading economic reform textbooks.
He was testifying to the cabinet
and wanted to be ready.
He’s a bookworm, not a leader.
—No-- No--
—No, you’re missing my point.
He’s not an oligarch.
He’s from modest circumstances.
Like you,
he’s worked for everything he has.
You have to be careful
of people like that.
I want you to deliver a message.
We’ve made a lot of money.
What we have to decide is do we stick
with Pablo … or chart our own course?
We should talk to our friends down south.
No, no. It’s not time. No.
Whatever you say.
Have you seen Marina?
She told me she was going
to buy a new brush.
You know your sister.
Her shopping expeditions take weeks.
You don’t have any idea how much
I wanted to go down on you in Panama.
It seems to be you really wanted to.
—Come here, baby.
—You are very patient.
Yes, of course.
All your people were there,
your brothers …
My brothers are driving me crazy.
—You know what?
—What?
They can go fuck themselves.
If they want to,
they can go live in Spain …
but you’re staying here with me.
Let’s not hide anymore.
Not anymore.
All right.
What do we do about my wife?
Ask Pablo to do us a favour.
Just like he took care of Galán,
he can take care of your wife.
You …
are very evil for such a young girl.
You’ve moved up, Fernando.
From government minister
to Pablo Escobar’s errand boy.
I guess the pay is much better.
I’m not doing this for the money.
What country sends its own citizens
to an iron tomb in the United States?
I understand your dilemma.
Speak out in favour … you’re seen as a US
puppet and you might not win the election.
Speak out against, you anger the US …
and are criticized by our media
as a shill of the narcos.
César, I was thinking I would love
to dedicate a program for your campaign.
It would be an honour for me,
and would benefit us both.
What a great idea.
You guys are really shameless, aren’t you?
How do you sleep at night?
César, it doesn’t have to be this way.
If Luis had been as smart as you,
perhaps we could have
avoided this horrible tragedy.
We could have had peace.
Easy.
Get out.
Read Pablo’s letter.
Maybe you will have a future.
Cousin, what happened?
Where were you?
—In the office.
—In the office?
Yes.
Is that where you were?
That’s weird …
because I called
and they said you hadn’t been in all day.
I don’t know which office you called,
but I was there.
They’re seizing everything, Pablo.
All the accounts--
We knew there would
be a reaction with Galán, right?
Relax, Gustavo.
Relax, because everything
will calm down later.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to kill us both?
—You afraid to die?
—No. And you?
—Put it out.
—Where were you?
Put it out, Pablo.
Put it out, Pablo!
Are you with me or what?
And when have I not been with you?
From the beginning,
it has been you and me.
I cannot do this without you.
You’re doubting my loyalty, Pablo?
No.
But I’m having serious doubts
with the Ochoas.
Time to thin the herd.
But did we score a goal?
The reporter, right.
Let’s make sure
we score a goal on him as well.
Come on, come on.
You are aware
that I can end your military career?
I don’t give a fuck.
Horacio … don’t give up.
You’ve always been the leader
of the persecution of Pablo Escobar.
Is this how you show your appreciation
for all we’ve done?
This operation
could be a failure before it starts.
I’m not here for fun.
What happens is the defence minister
gives you credit for the evidence
that we found at Hacienda Nápoles.
So … then if you resign,
I will look really bad.
Is that why you’re doing that?
Is that what you want?
Horacio … you remember when were cadets,
we never thought they would call us
to lead the country’s most important unit.
Horacio, as your friend …
I’m asking you to think about it.
Rodrigo, I don’t even know who Pablo pays.
It could be any of us three.
Horacio, please.
I’ve put my family at risk.
I need the right tools …
if there is going to be a war.
All right.
Perfect.
Then tell me what you need.
Incorruptible men.
Hey, punk. Are you all right?
—Sure.
—Come here.
How are you, son?
How are you?
I have to kill that son of a bitch.
Carrillo’s a cop.
You can always buy a cop with money.
I’ve tried, believe me.
Then offer more.
Or I can loan you Navegante.
He will do whatever I ask.
That’s true.
It’s silver or lead.
That’s the choice for that bastard.
Speaking of lead,
I’m getting a shipment of weapons in.
Uzis, grenades …
If I could find a nuclear weapon …
But now I’m negotiating a fucking missile.
—A missile? No fucking way.
—Yes.
Boss.
He’s bullshitting, right?
He’s smoking that shit …
I guarantee it.
Motherfucker.
Mrs Quiroga told me
the neighbours on the block took a vote.
They want us to move.
But we have guards stationed
outside the house 24 hours a day.
That’s what scares them.
Come here.
It won’t always be so, my love.
—Rodrigo.
—Hello, Horacio.
—Everything good?
—May I speak to you?
Yes, sure. Come in.
Let’s talk about the incorruptibles.
I’m listening.
I’ve been instructed to tell you that
if you cease and desist your operations,
you will receive
a one-time payment of six million.
Horacio … that’s US dollars, not pesos.
Instructed by whom?
I think you can guess.
Say the name.
You know who.
Say the name, Rodrigo.
Escobar.
Don’t look at me like that, Horacio.
I’ve always cared for you.
I’m making this suggestion to save
you and your family from terrible grief.
This man has tentacles.
I’m surprised
he hasn’t killed you already.
Get out.
Horacio, please--
Horacio …
Take care.
It was about time, Navegante.
Finally, a romantic date.
It’s been a long time
since we’ve been alone.
Just you, me …
and our bodyguard.
Like the old days when we were young
and your father watched us.
—My father adored you.
—Yeah, right.
Garcia …
THE EXTRADITABLES
Hello? Yes.
Yes.
But everything is fine?
All right.
Ana?
Ana!
A little bird … came into the house.
I’m helping it out.
What?
There was an assassination attempt …
on Colonel Carrillo.
Did someone die?
One of his men.
It must be terrible,
the position you’re in.
I want you to know …
I think you are very brave.
I’m not brave. Not like Galán.
That fear keeps you alive.
That’s what none of them understand.
I will support any decision you make.
Hello?
You think you’re hot shit?
You should change your satellite phone.
Who is this?
Your mother’s in Rionegro
with that tub of lard you call your son.
And your wife was at Carrera 11 today,
shopping for clothes.
You bastard son of a bitch,
you think that--
What, you think because you’re a cop
I’m afraid of you or something?
You know where my family is, fag,
well, I know where yours is, too.
Don’t forget that.
Gonorrhœa bastard son of a bitch.
Why don’t you take money
like everyone else?
I could have had you living like a king.
But now, guess what?
Time to kill your dad, your mom,
your kids, your entire family,
and you should be smart enough to realize
I have each and every one of them
under watch, you fucking bastard.
Not everyone’s for sale, Pablo.
You just keep hiding and I will find you.
Don’t know when …
but I will find you.
And when I find you …
—I’m going to kill you.
—I’m going to kill you, fag!
I’m going to kill
you and your entire family!
This, then, is war.