Amado Carrillo Fuentes!
The Lord of the Skies!
How fucking elegant, motherfucker.
- Don't tease.
- God damn, fucker.
- Your little brother?
- Yes. Alvaro.
Come here, son.
- You also get a hug.
- Sir.
How are you doing?
320 million kinds of okay.
Doesn't it smell like the
fucking U.S. Treasury in here?
- This half is yours.
- Yes?
- Don't forget it.
- All right. We came at a good time, then.
A Tuesday like any other,
Pacho. You know how it is.
Motherfucker.
- Let's go to the house.
- Let's go.
- All right. Son, do you like margaritas?
- Of course I do.
Great, because I have
a Margarita for you.
She'll suck you dry.
Welcome to Mexico, motherfucker.
Let's go.
Take the money and destroy the plane.
First off, Senator Martin
and I would like to thank you
for having us down, Ambassador.
But, you gotta know what's
going on in Washington.
Folks are wondering if
we're gonna win this thing.
And as senior members of
the Appropriations Committee,
those questions are directed at us.
Now, everyone's proud of the work
you guys did to bring down Escobar.
And it's particularly an
honor to meet you, Agent Peña.
But cocaine continues to flow
north, and the American people wonder
if the Colombians share our
enthusiasm to take this threat head-on.
Our colleague, Senator Helms, put
forward some tough language on them.
But we wanted to come down here
and get the real from you all.
See firsthand what's at stake.
See how and... if we can give
you all the support you need.
Let's extend the senators every
courtesy while they're here.
Their mission is a priority.
They ask... you answer.
Thank you.
Money makes the world go 'round.
Legal or illegal, good guys and
bad guys, we all chase money.
For the DEA, it's about budget
meetings and kissing the right ass
to keep the funding flowing.
But if you're a trafficker,
getting the money is easy.
It's holding onto it that's hard.
♪ C.R.E.A.M., get the money ♪
♪ Dollar, dollar bill, y'all ♪
♪ I grew up on the crime side... ♪
In the early days, cash
was flown back to Colombia
on the same planes that
carried coke into the States.
Then it was converted into pesos,
or, if you were Pablo Escobar,
stuck in a hole somewhere.
One trafficker died with so much cash
buried on his property, when it rained,
the river downstream became clogged
with bills that had washed free.
The biggest problem with illegal
money is the trail that it leaves.
Once upon a time, American banks would
take your money, no questions asked.
That changed when President
Nixon signed the Bank Secrecy Act,
requiring all U.S. banks
to report transactions
involving more than $10,000 in cash.
And from that law, money
laundering was born.
The first stage of money
laundering is called placement,
and Cali had it down to an art.
Bringing workers from
the comunas to the U.S.,
where their job was to buy money orders,
each just under ten grand,
so they wouldn't be reported.
No I.D. was required.
And the orders could even remain blank
until they were deposited or cashed.
Once they bought a bunch of money orders,
they packed them up and sent them south
to a land of sunshine and lax oversight.
Switzerland on the Caribbean: Panama.
Since they didn't regulate wire
transfers, Panama was the perfect place
for the second stage of
money laundering: layering.
And here's where the
master goes to work.
The behind the scenes MVP of any
drug cartel is the money launderer,
the guy that takes the dirty money
and scrubs it clean. Here's how:
The money orders were deposited
into local bank accounts,
and then bounced through shell
companies and limited partnerships,
creating an untraceable web of phony
purchase orders and transaction reports,
wiping clean the
money's criminal origins.
But no matter how well you hide
it, money always leaves a trail.
And the best way to hurt the
Cali cartel was to find it.
♪ Dollar, dollar bill, y'all ♪
Cali. Muy hermosa, right?
Fuck you, Chris.
The man asked me if I had a partner,
and your desk is across from mine.
You really fucked me, man.
You gonna ride a desk all the
way to Special Operations Unit?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I am.
Agents Feistl, Van Ness...?
- Feistl.
- Welcome to Cali.
- Gracias.
- Captain Calderón.
We're happy to be here.
And what brings you to Cali?
We've got some addresses
we want to investigate.
Cartel-related?
Not necessarily.
What a surprise. DEA
agents that don't trust us.
How did that work out
for the last two guys?
Friend, in Cali, there are more
corrupt cops than there are churches.
You don't trust me? I understand.
But if you want to get anything done
in Cali, you need the police's help.
If not me, someone else.
Not my rule.
- I understand.
- Good.
The addresses are linked to
cartel financial operations.
We want to put eyes on them. See if
any of the dots start connecting...
You've come a long way to connect dots.
We work with what we've got.
Unless you can tell me where I can
find Gilberto and Miguel Rodríguez.
If they didn't own half of the city,
I couldn't even be sure they exist.
The Rodríguez brothers are ghosts.
It was true.
While the terms of surrender
were being finalized,
the brothers had gone
underground to avoid capture.
They abandoned their swank estates,
secretly moving to new homes,
where they could continue
running their empire
without setting foot in one
of their legitimate businesses.
And all this while Chepe continued
to expand their New York operation.
But sometimes, even
the best get unlucky.
A computer glitch in Monaco
led authorities to notice
that one limited partnership had
multiple accounts at the same bank.
When they looked closer,
they found it had ties to hundreds
of bullshit accounts across Europe.
And they all led back to one bank...
right here in Bogotá.
Lucky for us, the president had
given the DEA our best weapon yet:
the Clinton list.
If we suspected a company
of working with traffickers,
their name went on the list.
And then they were banned from
doing business with U.S. companies
and U.S. companies were banned
from doing business with them.
You get fucked both ways.
And you want to know
what the best part is?
We don't even have to prove it.
We just... put you on the list.
And the OFAC takes care of the rest.
How can I help you, Agent Peña?
Armed with the threat
of the Clinton list,
we could get pretty much
any information we wanted,
and that's how we were able to give
Cali's number one money launderer a name:
Franklin Jurado.
Because it was illegal
for Colombian citizens
to have U.S. currency
in their possession,
a money launderer became
more than just a connection
to the financial institutions
that washed their cash.
For all intents and
purposes, he is their money.
Jurado was the perfect bridge between
the narcos and the world of high finance.
He spoke five languages and
traveled on multiple passports.
He married an American girl he met
while at business school in the States,
took her down south, and
got her in on his action.
That American passport was
solid gold in any Caribbean bank.
Jurado was smooth. But
now, we knew his name.
These are cash transfers.
The accounts are controlled
by a man named Franklin Jurado.
- You know him?
- Of him.
He served as director at Interamericas.
- The Rodríguez
brothers' bank. - Mm-hmm.
They later gave him
a more important job.
Do you have an address for Jurado?
I can get it for you.
So what happened since
the last time I saw you?
Are you going to take
these men on, or what?
- I'm going to do my job.
- And your bosses?
Do they know what you're doing?
No comment.
♪ Dance with me ♪
♪ In my world of fantasy ♪
♪ Won't you dance with me ♪
♪ Ritual fertility ♪
I was thinking...
maybe I could come with you.
Oh, come on, this could be our last
chance to travel like we used to.
- Remember that place in Milan?
- With the leaking roof?
On your birthday. And
that terrible risotto.
That balcony.
The brothers are pushing now, baby.
They are opening more accounts.
- It's dangerous.
- I don't care.
How high are you right now?
Hey, fuck you!
Give me your passport.
I can't stay in this
apartment anymore, Franklin.
I can't watch another movie
with subtitles by myself.
I don't want to listen to the cartel
wives talk about their husbands...
- With an English degree from Harvard...
- Please don't tell me I can teach.
Then what did you want me to say?
Fuck.
We'll do this another time.
The dining room is over here.
You have a room over here.
You have another one over here.
And here, you have the living room.
The dimmer is over here.
And you can adjust the light.
Well... you get the idea.
- No. I don't understand.
- What don't you understand?
Does this seem normal to you?
You indicated to Mr. Rodríguez
you were uncertain about
returning to the North Valley.
And that's why he bought
me a palace. With dimmers.
Please tell Don Miguel thank you,
but I need to think
about his generous offer.
We have that dinner tonight.
With your friends?
With the investors.
They're not going to
like the six-month delay.
And I think it's best if we don't
mention the Rodríguez brothers by name.
I know you're embarrassed by what I do.
I know you did it for your family.
But if these people like
everything they hear tonight,
you'll have your own security firm
the second these six months are up.
- Ready!
- Good!
A choir!
All right, say bye
to Dad. We're leaving.
- Bye.
All right. Let's go, or we'll be late.
Will you make it on time?
If you're wearing the
dress with the flowers, yes.
Let's go, girls.
Today is a busy day for us, boys.
Bosses have meetings all
day at the National Hotel.
I need you to pre-sweep each and
every location on this schedule.
And I don't want a bunch of cars parked
like bullshit, blocking escape routes.
- He's looking at you, Montez.
- Of course I'm talking to you, you idiot.
Don Miguel's team on channel six.
Don Gilberto's, channel eight.
Jorge says that the
DEA is visiting Cali.
Two agents from Bogotá. They're new.
They're working with the National Police.
But they don't have
warrants. They're tourists.
They need permission
to wipe their own asses.
Regardless, while they're in
Cali, we'll be watching them.
- That's your job, Enrique, my brother.
- Yes, sir.
That's all, gentlemen.
Communicate. Stay safe. Get to work.
I have to duck out early.
It's a work thing for Paola.
Of course.
Do you want to practice your English?
Starkman, the American
lawyer, arrives today.
Can you pick him up from the airport?
Aren't you worried about the tourists?
The second team's never
as good as the first.
Got a look at the directory. That
company moved out three months ago.
If they were ever there at all.
Quiet part of the city here.
Cartel keep Cali buttoned down?
Nobody talks.
All the multinationals used
to have offices here in Cali.
"Used to"?
Pulled out because of the city's
ties to the narcotics trade.
The Rodríguez brothers are
the only game in town now.
Fucking drug dealers
pretending to be stockbrokers.
Motherfuckers ruined this city.
Where are we headed next?
Please.
This way, Mr. Starkman.
How the hell are you supposed to
fly international if you can't smoke?
I guess you can always quit.
And let United Airlines
tell me how to live?
Remind me again... Kansas City?
- Leavenworth.
- What the fuck for?
My father was in the
army. There's a base there.
They sent him to train. I
was like... seven years old.
What? It's America.
That's for sure.
So am I meeting the
brothers at the hotel?
Yes.
Serious stones on these guys.
Retiring, like they run Lehman Brothers.
It's a good break for you, though.
You'll get immunity when
the surrender goes through.
I don't sell cocaine.
I don't shoot anyone.
You're a member of the Cali cartel.
You ever hear of conspiracy, amigo?
Relax. I got this. Look, they're
lucky to have us both, Jorge.
You can't put a price on freedom.
Though Lord knows I try.
I assume you would prefer U.S. currency?
Of course.
Currency aside,
we aren't in the habit of
paying for things in advance.
What guarantee do we have that
you will provide what you promise?
Forgive my brother.
We are grateful for the support
you and your people have offered.
This afternoon, our
associate, Mr. Pallomari,
will prepare the contribution
and arrange delivery.
Very well.
The contribution should
be divided among seven men.
Their names are on the list.
All right, very well. Going forward,
I think it's best if Mr. Pallomari
deals with my colleague, Mr. Giraldo.
As you wish.
Have a great day, gentlemen.
Well, our surrender has been
bought. Now it must be paid for.
And they say we're the criminals.
Sons of bitches.
Small price to pay, brother,
for the rest of your life.
Gentlemen, I will prepare these payments
myself, as soon as I'm back in the office.
And I'll make sure that
all of this is in order.
Mr. Starkman is next, the lawyer.
If you ever make it to Miami
and you need a lawyer...
hit me up.
I wasn't planning on it,
but thank you, Mr. Starkman.
Yeah, nobody ever plans on it.
Mr. Starkman.
- Welcome to Cali.
- Yeah.
The Rodríguez brothers
are pleased to welcome you.
No offense, but remind
me again what you do?
I'm the chief accountant
to the Rodríguez brothers.
What happened to the other guy?
The good-looking one? Pacho?
Mr. Herrera?
Yeah, I bet he's the guy who's got
all the pussy in town on speed dial.
Yeah. Please, sir.
- Feistl.
- How's it going?
Well, slow so far, but
Calderón seems like good police.
Yeah. Good.
That journalist come through?
I'm on the money man right now.
- See where he takes me.
- Gracias.
Eyes open, Feistl.
- Everything by the book.
- Will do.
- Keep me posted.
- Baby, wait.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
The Arellano Felix brothers
are still wasting time with heroin.
Hey! What? You're not
going to say hello?
- Hello.
- Are you in a bad mood or what?
Amado... this is the life.
You guys helped me.
I moved the last 100
tons in less than 50 days.
You tell me if we're
a great team or not.
That's why we're here.
Can you handle a bigger package?
I'm the Lord of the Skies,
brother. What do you think?
Amado Carrillo Fuentes.
Leader of the Juárez cartel.
He was one of the most
enterprising traffickers in Mexico
and one of the first to get into business
with his Colombian friends to the south.
While Escobar saw the Mexican
traffickers as a threat,
Cali saw them as a partner.
A partner that shared over 1,900
miles of virtually undefended border
with Cali's biggest
customer: the United States.
And right about the time
the Caribbean corridor closed
along came NAFTA, when the U.S.
- Mexico border was open for business.
And Amado took full advantage,
agreeing to ferry Cali
cocaine into the States.
They called it "the Mexican trampoline,"
bouncing cocaine into America,
and bouncing cash right back.
I can move however much you give me.
I just have two questions: How much?
And for how much longer, Pacho?
Because I know about your deal.
I know you want to turn yourselves in.
There is a deal on the table, Amado.
But we have six months to turn
ourselves in. That's the truth.
Until then, we will honor
our commitment to you.
Right, and after?
What happens after that?
The business will adjust.
This I know. It will always
adjust. This will never end.
There will be other partners and
more drugs. But what about you?
What will happen to you?
You can't tell me you're going to retire,
as if this was any normal business.
You know this is a way of life.
It retires you when it's done with you.
Or are you going to start
playing golf like an old man?
We need to count on you maintaining
the same terms on this last shipment.
Done.
It'll be my gift to
the Gentlemen of Cali.
All right? But... you have
to come with me to Juárez.
- I want to show you something.
- What is it?
The future, Pacho.
The fucking future, that's all.
- Here's your passport.
- Thank you.
All right, and you
board through Gate 15.
Okay.
- Have a great trip.
- Thank you.
Have a great day.
Next.
I'm going to Panama.
I need you to radio
ahead to the DEA office.
I'm afraid not. This plane
can't take off. New orders.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, sir. I'm not looking
for that kind of trouble.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is going on?
Orders are orders. You
heard the ambassador.
Our friends from the Senate here want
the down-low from a real-life hero.
Guess that's you.
You got somewhere better to be?
You wore the wrong shoes.
Fuck.
Is that the Río Negro?
What do we got here?
The captain likes this one.
You won't find their name on the lease,
but the Rodríguez brothers
own the top six floors.
Oh, fuck. For real?
I told you, there are
some honest cops in Cali.
Let me reach out to men I trust.
Quietly. Keep an eye on this
place. You go back to Bogotáand...
get a warrant.
Come on, guys, the place
isn't moving anywhere.
Get that paper and we'll
turn this place upside down.
Why wait?
Judge in Bogotásigned a
warrant for us before we left.
Which you never told me about.
This is the kind of bullshit I don't
like. Are you playing me or what?
Hey, man, it's like you said.
It's hard to know who to trust.
I wasn't even sure
we were gonna need it.
There's no address on this warrant.
You said this place is connected,
so let's put in some work.
Do you know the kind
of shit I could land in?
Huh?
I don't have a DEA
pension waiting for me.
Pensions aren't that
great, to be honest.
Fuck.
Let's do it.
I need a tactical team sent to
15th Street and 4th Avenue, copy?
Copy that. Requesting a tactical team
at 15th Street and 4th Avenue.
You do realize, don't you,
after we surrender, all
of this shit will end.
No more sitting by the
pool, smoking your cigar,
telling everyone what to do.
Look, Miguel, I'm tired of
telling people what to do.
And no one has ever listened to you.
What's the difference?
But you know what?
Never, in human history, have two
brothers accomplished what we have.
We aren't the first people in
history to build an empire, Gilberto.
But we're the first to retire
leaving the empire intact.
If Mom were alive, she'd be proud.
Brothers are well, nephews
are well, sons are well.
Boss, we just heard a call
that a tactical team left Jamundí
station heading to 4th Avenue.
Enrique, where are you?
Watching our visitors from the DEA.
They've been checking
addresses all over town.
But right now, they're
stopped, just doing nothing.
Yes, but where are you?
At 15th Street and...
4th. On 4th Avenue.
Enrique, fuck! There's a
police convoy coming at you!
Get Pallomari out of there now!
Answer, you bastard, answer.
- Hello? What's up?
- Listen, it's Salcedo.
You're going to have
unwelcome guests. Leave now.
I don't have time for this. I'm
supervising an important project.
That's exactly why I
need you to get out.
Just because you say so?
I know you're arranging an important
transaction for the bosses this afternoon.
Listen, this is none of your business.
I'll bet your desk is
covered with American dollars.
Look, Guillermo, please.
You've got papers. You've got names.
You've got things that shouldn't be seen.
- Jorge...
- Get out of there!
You do your job and I'll do mine.
This is my job! I'm telling
you... Son of a bitch!
Fuck your mother.
I need you to check the paper shredders
and the floppy disks
still in the computers.
Invoices. Bills of lading.
Anything on the computers.
- Warrant says paper only.
- Yeah? Warrants say a lot of things.
Let's go.
At least someone's willing to get wet.
Don't worry, you'll be back in
Intelligence Group soon enough.
It's not...
This is a waste of our time, Chris.
And more importantly, this
is a waste of a warrant.
You know what?
Andrew Jackson here says all we
find in this fucking high rise
- is a nice view of the city.
- All right.
Well, I got... whoever this
guy is and he says otherwise.
Fucking shit!
Gentlemen, how may I help you?
Seventh floor. Mr. Pallomari's office.
I'll let them know you're
here so you can head up.
Oh, oh, oh... People love surprises.
Gentlemen, you can't...
You. What the fuck are
you still doing here?
What the fuck am I doing? My job. We
told your associate the same thing.
Sorry, boss, I tried,
but he won't listen.
- You go get the car.
- Please get out.
- I have to finish. Fuck your mother.
- The back stairs.
- Yes, sir.
- Finish what?
My job, Jorge.
No. Please, we have to
get rid of all of that now.
We aren't arguing. You
aren't touching anything.
I've got a method and a system.
- Method and a system?
- Yes, sir.
Yes? What you've got is ten years of
jail time sitting on your desk, you idiot.
- Get out.
- No.
Attention! Colombian National Police!
Where are the files?
Get to work. Let's go!
This is an office.
We're working. How can I help you?
We need access to your files, invoices,
and all of your correspondence.
Ah...
If that's the case, I
need to see a warrant.
Are you supposed to be in charge?
Well, yes, I'm in charge.
Come on.
Good morning. I have to
see every invoice you have.
Hey!
This says documents
only. Fuck your mother.
Could you repeat that, sir? My
Spanish is... is a bit rough.
You didn't get that?
- Only papers.
- Documents only.
- All right.
- Claudia.
Keep an eye on the things
they're taking. Now!
Yes, sir.
Leave it. Let it be.
Chivo, check everything and
make an inventory, all right?
Hey, I like presents. What'd you get us?
That's private.
Ignacio, please show the
gentleman last year's documents.
This way, please.
Excuse me, sir.
I must insist.
Your phone's off the hook.
Do you have a bill of
lading? Yes? Let me see.
More? Everything.
- Just these?
- And copies below.
- These as well, no?
- Yes, sir.
- All right. '93. Yeah?
- Those are the most recent.
Grab that.
Looks like you owe me that 20.
Oh, yeah.
You were right.
This area saw the biggest spike in
trafficking after Escobar was killed.
Can't we just spray chemicals on
this place and be done with it?
Unfortunately, agricultural concerns
in the region won't allow it.
That's right. Chiquita
Bananas is down here.
I know those guys. Big contributors.
Okay. Here we are.
Jesus H. Christ.
Must've been one hell
of a firefight, huh?
No doubt, sir.
- Gentlemen, this is Captain Mills.
- Captain.
- Our advisor on this mission down here.
- How you doing, sir?
He liaised with a team of Colombian
commandos on this raid here.
These guys FARC or traffickers?
Both.
Probably started out doing security
for the traffickers, or extorting them.
FARC wants to overthrow the government.
Cocaine finances their struggles.
Top of the line.
There's an arms race going on down here.
And this shit...
is jet fuel.
You guys ready for lunch?
Lunch? Yeah. Sure. Why not?
Go. Go. Go.
This 24-hour party thing...
is tiring after a couple of days.
Can you imagine if it was your life?
What's on your mind?
Dad, and the last thing he said to me.
What? "Get the fuck out"?
No.
He said... that in this world...
there was no place for a man like me.
I made a place for myself.
I proved him wrong.
And now, I have to give it all up.
What kind of man would
I be if I gave it all up?
I don't know, brother.
But what I do know is that you
have a couple billion dollars...
and the rest of your
life to figure it out.
What are they giving me?
What do you mean, "What
are they giving you?"
They took my son, didn't they?
They have to give us something.
Have they offered you something?
An apartment.
Accept it.
Afterwards, I'll sell it for cash.
We'll take their money now.
Later, we'll take vengeance.
- Do it, then get back up here.
- Can you wake Pedro up?
- I want to speak with him.
- Don't worry about Pedro. He's sleeping.
I heard we cut it close today.
I thought they didn't have a warrant.
That's what I was told by
our friend on the force.
A few more seconds and
we'd have had real trouble.
Those new DEA guys are
sharper than they look.
Well, luckily, we have you.
Did they get anything?
Some files.
So nothing. Good.
I'll take care of the rest today.
That thing you've got tonight
with Paola, enjoy yourself. Go on.
We got names, addresses.
These files are legit.
How are you guys?
Captain.
We'll catalog and seal
the ones from today.
If you could help us with transport...
Okay... there must
be a misunderstanding.
The files stay here.
We need to sort through these.
As you can see, we know how
to process evidence, Feistl.
- That wasn't the deal. This was our intel.
- It was a CNP operation.
We let you join, support.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not.
But anything we find we'll
be sure to share with you.
I was instructed you should
be back in Bogotátonight.
You're going out on the last flight.
He burned us.
Who's that, Chris?
The last honest cop in Cali?
No, man. He clowned me,
too. I'm calling the boss.
Fuck!
Those things ain't
going 25 feet down here.
Thanks. Hey, you DOD?
So they say. But I still ID as a Marine.
I'm part of the military
assistance package.
- CIA?
- Oh, shit. Fuck, no.
Can I get a smoke?
Thanks.
Where you from?
The last place? Pendleton.
I was out there teaching Saudi
soldiers how to do jumping jacks.
That shit's a lot harder than it sounds.
- So is it really that bad down here?
- Yeah. It is.
You got paramilitary,
FARC, traffickers, us.
Some pretty hairy bullshit down here.
Right, but not hairy enough
for the truth to make its case.
Magazines on those bodies
are 7.62 millimeter.
They go in an AK-47, right?
Those guns, the fancy ones,
they chamber in a 5.56.
This whole thing is staged.
Those are run-of-the-mill
guerrillas. Peasants, not traffickers.
You know your guns.
I'm gonna head on down.
Not very original, Stechner.
Even for the CIA.
Yeah, well, sometimes you need to
make the truth a little more... plain.
Well, how's this for truth?
They go home and tell everyone the
war on drugs is a fucking stage show.
And all the money they
put in is pissed away.
Even the hero said it's fucked up.
What's that do to your plan?
I'm gonna level with you.
Sending a five-billion-dollar
aid package
to a country that's on the verge
of becoming a narco-democracy,
that's a bad look in the Senate.
All due respect, Senator, you're looking
at a petri dish for the next Castro,
and this one's fed by narco dollars.
And not just here. Venezuela, Honduras.
Rich dictators with
anti-American hard-ons.
We turn our back on this
place, it all goes to hell.
Colombia is perfectly situated to help
us in both Central and South America.
The right American footprint
here, Black Hawks, small arms,
night vision, advisors like Mills...
we help secure a stable Colombia,
and it becomes a beacon for the region.
Well, if you want the American people
to get behind sending billions
of dollars to Colombia...
we need a no-fucking-around
victory down here.
Look, gentlemen, the
Colombian government
is months away from dismantling one
of the biggest drug cartels in history.
And they will do it
without firing a shot.
No body count, no dirty hands.
I can't imagine the folks
back home won't like that.
Agent Peña.
What do you think?
Is it true? Is a big win coming?
Agent Stechner and I...
we have a long-standing difference
of opinion on just about everything.
But he and I can both agree...
a big win is coming.
Glad we're on the
same page, Agent Peña.
So the whole surrender plan
is about fucking fundraising!
The Colombians get a check and you
get to play army men in the jungle?
I'm thinking about the next
battle, the one that really counts.
Which means you're
willing to lose this one!
The drug war?
Oh, come on, man! We lost it!
You were there!
Ever stop and think that anyone that
takes this as personally as you do
is doing it wrong?
- Fuck you!
- Yeah.
See ya!
Where are they now?
I just put them on a plane to Bogotá.
- And the files?
- We've got them.
Are you sure?
Look, they tricked me with
that fucking warrant, all right?
And I couldn't warn you because we
were all together like a fucking family.
These Americans know what they're doing.
They aren't fucking idiots.
I ever tell you I did
a rotation in Chile?
No, Dan, you never told me you
did a rotation in fucking Chile.
The accountant.
- You clock his accent?
- No.
A little off. You know, he said
something: "Concha su madre. "
Okay, what's that? "Fuck
your mother" or something?
Exactly.
But then he said another word:"Cachai. "
It's a phrase that they
typically only use in Chile.
And if he's from Chile...
He can be extradited.
Panama DEA said no
warrant, no detention.
- Fuck.
- Plus, Jurado didn't stay in Panama.
They know where he went?
No.
So Jurado could be anywhere. Fuck!
Also, boss, Feistl and Van Ness
have been trying you. A lot.
All right, well, put them through
when you get them. I'm on my way back.
- And Stoddard?
- Yeah, boss?
Jurado has a wife in
Bogotá. She's American.
Put a tap on her phone.
- I don't think I can do that.
- Just do it.
Well, the truth is, we're very
interested in your proposal, Jorge.
And in your potential for growth.
You've exceeded Paola's description,
which wasn't easy.
Of course, we were inconvenienced
by the six-month delay, which...
took us by surprise.
I take my commitments
very seriously, gentlemen.
And I couldn't leave without ensuring
my replacement met the standard
they've come to expect.
Go wait for him over there.
- Good evening. How are you?
- Good, thank you.
Well, I think that merits
another bottle of wine, no?
Yes.
Look at that son of a bitch.
Thinks his shit doesn't stink, or what?
Thank you.
So, a security expert married to a rising
star in one of Cali's top law firms.
Have you worked together before?
My compliments.
David Rodríguez.
How are you?
Don't let the elegant suit fool you.
This guy's a real son of a bitch.
Seriously.
In fact, he's one of our best men.
You see?
Enjoy it.
Ma'am.
You... Where do you know him
from? Is he a friend of yours?
You know Cali is a very small city.
Even more so when one is
in the security business.
One must deal with all sorts of people.
Is that the paperwork
I'm supposed to deliver?
These documents are very sensitive.
And I don't feel comfortable
transferring possession to anyone else.
All right. Let's go, then.
Open the door, Córdova.
Go fuck yourself, Pallomari.
- Huh?
- In the front seat.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Open the door. Fuck your mother.
In the front. I'm not
your fucking employee.
Making friends everywhere he goes.
No shit.
Look at this fucking neighborhood.
This guy's doing more than filing W-9s.
Es el cabrón.
The fucking man.
I haven't been able
to reach an agreement.
He's very stubborn.
Listen to me, Pacho. We
have to seal the deal.
It's very important.
Amado has to go to Juárez tomorrow.
I'll go with him and close the deal.
All right. Keep me informed.
Good night.
Good night, Gilberto.
Compliments of Mr. Carrillo.
♪ Play a part ♪
♪ In a greater scheme ♪
♪ Try to live the dream ♪
♪ On a wider scene ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
♪ Right now ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ In sweet harmony ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
♪ Right now ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ In sweet harmony ♪
♪ Let's come together ♪
It's been a long time since
anyone asked me on a date.
Come in, please.
Take a seat.
Sir... your offer of this
apartment is very generous.
But?
But... I would like to know the terms.
The terms?
How often will you
come here to visit me?
As often as you like.
Or never.
This is your home.
Is there a monthly stipend?
A stipend?
Mr. Rodríguez, I married Claudio
Salazar when I was 18 years old.
I knew nothing.
Now I need to get away from his
family, and I need my son back.
If you could help me with that...
I can.
Then I accept.
It's great to hear that.
Why don't you get some rest?
Eat something.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll send for your son.
How does that sound?
Good.
Take a seat.
Fifty miles an hour, you could
jump into water and survive.
- You can't leave her on the bus.
- I guess you do. You leave her on the bus.
No.
- I would leave her.
- You would leave her?
Shh...
All right. Here we go.
Dan.
Is that who I think it is?
Gilberto fucking Rodríguez.
Fuck.
Oh, my fucking God. Okay.
- Peña.
- Boss, it's Feistl.
- Where the fuck have you been?
- Sir, I got eyes on Gilberto Rodríguez.
- You're looking at him right now?
- Yes.
Just say the word and
we can take him down.
What's the move, boss?
Sorry to interrupt.
You want to go after
Gilberto Rodríguez?