Murphy, join the party, huh?
What's wrong?
All you guys having a good time?
You gotta let it go, man.
There's good that came out of this.
Yeah, we used him,
then we got him killed.
No, we didn't kill him... Escobar did.
And now we get to go after
that motherfucker.
- Look on the bright side, huh?
Peña was right.
There was a silver lining.
One of the sicarios caught
after Lara Bonilla's assassination
confessed that Pablo had put out the hit.
An important politician had been murdered
and everyone knew who did it.
Finally, the Colombian government
had to react.
Pablo Escobar was indicted
for the murder of Rodrigo Lara Boniila.
WANTED: PABLO ESCOBAR GAVIRIA
$100,000 REWARD
Colombia agreed to the one thing
narcos feared most: extradition.
Now any Colombian
who smuggled drugs to America
could be prosecuted
and jailed in the US,
even if they never
stepped foot on our soil.
This made all the difference in the world.
- If you were a narco in Colombia,
jail time meant banging girls,
watching movies,
hanging with the fellas...
Grease the right hands and you'd
get a reduced sentence for good behavior.
It was a fucking joke.
Back home,
it was a whole different deal.
The seventh richest man in the world?
No one gives a shit.
You still get a 6x8 cell 23 hours a day,
just like every other loser,
a fucking nightmare.
Now Pablo had someone to fear: us.
Extradition doesn't mean anything
unless you can catch him.
- With our help, you will.
- Oh, that's right.
Gringos to the rescue.
It's one fucking man
against the United States of America.
One man with helicopters, airplanes,
vehicles, planned escape routes,
- and a network of informants.
- Our government will provide money,
- men, weapons--
- You make it sound so easy.
But Escobar has always
managed to stay one step ahead of us.
Help us catch him.
I'll never be assigned to this.
Jaramillo hates my guts.
Let me take care of that.
- You think extradition's a victory.
- It is.
Escobar will not go lightly.
He will make Colombia bleed.
Now more than ever
is the time for solidarity.
You make the mistakes,
and then you preach solidarity?
- Shut up, fag.
- What the fuck, Carlos?
Why are you always defending him?
Did he get your sister back
for you or not?
We rescued her because we did it together.
Right?
Gentlemen...
I suggest we form another organization
to fight against
the injustice of extradition.
Like John Lennon said,
- "Come together, brothers and sisters--"
- Stop that fag shit right now.
So Jorge...
what will we call it?
First, "Death to Kidnappers, "
then "the Extraditables."
Once again, the narcos were united
against a common enemy: jail in America.
But it was not quite like
"one for all, and all for one."
It was more like each man for himself.
Next!
Gacha, being Gacha, decided that
all he had to do to defeat extradition
- was kill anyone who tried to arrest him.
- Fire!
So he hired a bunch of
Israeli mercenaries and prepared for war.
Next!
Lehder, being Lehder, got high as a kite
and took to the airwaves.
The gringos
are the ones who use the drugs.
So why are we the ones
who need to be extradited?
I'm not sure how helpful that was.
I mean, all of our problems...
are because of those imperialist gringos!
No, stay there... stay there.
As for the Ochoa brothers,
they went with a fancy PR firm
and got ripped off because, well...
that's what PR agencies do.
"Better a grave in Colombia
than a grave in the United States."
No, I've got it, Fabio, I've got it.
Let's see...
"Better a grave in Colombia
than a cell in the United States."
- What do you think?
- I love it.
- Very good.
And for $50,000 more,
we'll make your logo.
Done.
By the way,
here's the logo $50,000 got you.
In the upcoming presidential election,
extradition became the defining issue
amongst the candidates.
Those the narcos could buy,
they bought.
The ones they could scare,
they scared.
But Luis Carlos Galán was neither.
And so, unable to buy him
and unable to scare him,
Escobar tried out
that fancy new stationery,
and he wrote Galán a letter.
"And to conclude, I want
to express my most energetic protest
over the improper interference
of North America
in a way that entails
the most flagrant violation
of the sovereignty of our Motherland."
He's got some balls.
Escobar is shameless.
The United States is inclined to support
your bid for the presidency, Mr. Galán.
But even if we indict these narcos
in the United States,
we still can't get them there
without Colombian approval.
We're curious
as to your view on extradition.
My campaign manager,
Dr. Gaviria,
doesn't want me
to stick my foot in my mouth.
America wants Pablo Escobar
to prove they're winning a battle,
when clearly,
they're losing a war.
I'll do what's best for Colombia.
If you speak in favor of extradition,
you will be their puppet,
and that will be your death sentence.
I don't care about the Americans, but I am
still going to support extradition.
Besides, if the gringos want to take away
all the goddamn killers of this country,
then let them take them.
Since he couldn't get to Galán,
Pablo reached out
to many of the country's judges.
He figured out that a sanctioned law
would do no harm
if no judge was willing to apply it.
"As you pass judgment
on one of our sons
and consider sending him
to his fate in the United States,
know we, the Extraditables,
will pass judgment on you
and bring a sentence far harsher."
The judges were so scared and intimidated
that special court procedures
had to be created.
For the first time
in the history of Colombia,
it was the good guys who
had to hide their faces behind the masks.
Defendants, please rise.
You've been tried and convicted
of cocaine trafficking.
You will immediately be turned over to the
DEA for extradition to the United States.
Despite his threats,
many brave men defied him.
And true to form,
when the pen failed...
Pablo was always ready with the sword.
In light of this terrorism,
you'd think that everyone in Colombia
would've made catching Escobar
the number one priority, right?
Well, guess again.
Communists. They're the real threat
to the security of this country.
All due respect, but Colombian cocaine has
killed more Americans than Soviet troops.
We got FARC, we got M-19,
we got EPL, we got ELN,
all supported by the Soviets and Cubans.
Sorry, Agent Peña, but our resources
gotta be directed at America's problems,
and you don't get to tell us
what those are.
Communists. Remember them?
With Reagan in the White House,
it was hard to forget.
In his words:
They are the focus of evil
in the modern world.
The Soviet evil empire
was Reagan's thing, always had been.
In Hollywood, he named some actors
as communist sympathizers.
In Washington,
he created the Reagan Doctrine,
which opposed Soviet-backed communists
all over the world.
Drug traffickers just didn't rate.
You want to turn on the tap
of the richest country in the world,
you'd better be chasing reds.
Ambassador, if the CIA
and the Mil Group provide assets,
the Colombians will get Escobar.
We're talking about a huge blow
to the cocaine trade
- and saving thousands of lives--
- Ambassador.
The CIA agrees with Mil Group.
Pablo Escobar is no longer a congressman.
He's just a wanted Colombian
drug trafficker, and as such,
he is not a direct threat to our country's
strategic interests in South America.
The CIA would prefer not to get involved
in local police problems.
Let the Colombians get him.
Noonan really thinks
allocating $100,000
- will be enough to go after Escobar.
- Yeah, it's a fucking joke.
That's about what he spends on shoes,
isn't it?
The CNP has zero chance
of capturing him with that bullshit.
So what do we do now?
Use what little we got
to try to even the odds.
It's true,
the hundred grand wasn't that much.
But delivered into the right hands,
it could make a difference.
There were a lot of good cops in Colombia,
honorable men.
But the head of counternarcotics,
General Jaramillo, wasn't one of 'em.
And as such,
he was exactly what we needed.
Thank you for seeing me, General.
You're welcome.
Listen, I have General Gomez
assigned to the operation against Pablo.
With all due respect, General Jaramillo...
I propose Horacio Carrillo.
But Carrillo only acts on his own orders.
He doesn't follow anyone.
Well, I don't want him to follow.
I want him to lead.
Go ahead.
Yes, General.
As you wish.
Understood.
What happened, honey?
Things with work.
When will Horacio arrive
to have dinner with us?
I'm making the chicken he likes,
but he's outwith the girlfriend.
Tell me what's wrong.
They want me to catch Pablo Escobar.
The Ochoas aren't happy at all.
They're saying that since
you've become a wanted man,
bribing the police
has gotten very costly.
They want to renegotiate
the price of our routes.
Hm.
When it came to me killing
to get their sister back, well, then...
I didn't hear them complaining, did I?
Yeah. The problem is that
it is one thing to kill communists
- and another to kill politicians.
- So what now?
What I would do is increase
the payments to the police, you know?
And most of all, to the top brass.
We're already giving too much money
to those bastards.
Mm.
Oh, shit. What's that?
Is it snowing or what?
- Egrets from the Himalayas.
It took two years
to train them to stay there.
They cost me a million dollars.
Bastards.
Stay in the fucking tree!
Seems like you lost that dough,
eh, cousin?
That's your problem, Pablo.
You think that everything
can be controlled,
but it turns out that nature
cannot be controlled.
OK, OK, OK, Gustavo... OK.
Your English is really good.
Thank you. I took a course
at the University of Antioquia.
How long you been at the comuna?
Just a few weeks.
Is your husband
gonna help us here, too?
I saw him when he dropped you off.
What does he do?
Oh, he's, uh... head of janitorial
services at the US Embassy.
- I fucked up.
- How?
Carrillo got the job
just like you wanted.
No, Jaramillo's sending a message.
He's telling me I got his price wrong.
He's setting Carrillo up for failure,
and when he does fail,
he'll fire him for incompetence,
and me and you,
we lose the only cop we can trust.
- Hey!
- Sorry I'm late, honey.
- Mm...
Javier, this is my friend, Elisa.
- Javier works with Steve.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you another... janitor at the embassy,
like Steve?
No, actually, I'm CIA.
But that's classified,
so don't tell anybody.
I'm here to hunt communists
and prevent a Marxist invasion from Cuba.
- The janitor thing, what, that was you?
- Mm.
No, it's just a cover.
- Thank you for being so honest.
- Mm-hm.
Just so you know,
I'm a communist guerrillera.
Perfect.
If we had known at the time
she was telling the truth...
we probably wouldn't have cared.
We cared about Pablo Escobar.
And catching him...
wasn't gonna be easy.
He had better resources
and better information.
And at the time,
he owned over 800 homes and fincas,
surrounded by dozens of sicarios
willing to die for him.
And cops...
he owned a lot of them, too.
But not all of them.
Jaramillo's intel says Pablo's gonna be
at his finca called El Bizcocho tomorrow.
The only way to surprise him
is an aerial assault.
Jaramillo didn't give us a helicopter.
Then we need to figure out
where he's hiding today.
Trapped a little bird.
And I'm gonna make sure that he sings.
Jesus.
Just remember that you wanted all in.
Hand me that coffee.
He already gave up
the name of three fincas,
but Pablo's not gonna be at any of them.
But you do know
where he is hiding, don't you?
Look, little brother,
I know it scares the shit out of you
that Pablo will kill you.
But I will also kill you.
And very slowly.
Pablo is going to kill me more slowly.
Well, then, you should pray we find him,
and quickly.
We knew that Escobar would
get a heads-up the second we moved out,
but there was a small part of me
that thought, in his arrogance,
he would stand and fight.
Or maybe we just wanted
to send him a message.
Boss!
Poison...
They were headed for El Bizcocho,
but they got off the main highway.
- They're already on their way here.
- How far are they?
Two hours, boss.
Round up the guys,
and tell them to get ready.
- We're leaving.
- All right.
We have to go.
Go where?
The police are coming.
- But Pablo, I've been cooking for hours.
- I'm sorry, my love,
- but we need to leave now.
- What about our things? Our clothes?
We'll buy new ones later,
won't we?
I'm sorry.
Do you hear me complaining?
As long as you're with us, Pablo,
I'm prepared to do whatever it takes.
- Bring all of the boxes here.
- Yes, sir.
- Cangrejo!
- Yes?
Go to Pablo's room
and see if anything is in there.
- Efrain!
- Yeah?
The two blue notebooks
are the only ones I'm taking.
Search the whole house to make sure
that not a single loose document remains.
Yes, sir!
What's wrong, Gustavo?
You fucked us, Pablo.
Not only you and me.
You fucked the whole family.
But of course, since you needed
to present yourself to Congress...
since you want to be president
of this motherfucking country,
the rest of us get screwed,
isn't that right?
But what the fuck...
a man only dies once, right?
Come here.
My brother.
I'm going to let you sit
next to the pilot. Come on, come on.
- There we go.
I like to think
that as Pablo looked down
on Hacienda Nápoles for the last time,
he got our message...
and I hope it really pissed him off.
You may have 800 houses, my friend,
but none of them is home.
We will keep you on the run
for the rest of your life,
or until we catch you...
or kill you.
From now on,
nowhere is safe.
The only people to detain
were the maids and the gardeners
while we searched the finca
from top to bottom.
The dirt-poor cops
were astounded by the luxury.
Hey, if you're risking your life
for $22 a week... you'd pig out, too.
There's an old saying in law enforcement:
"The bad guys
need to get lucky every time.
The good guys
just need to get lucky once."
And in the ashes of Pablo's hasty exit,
I got very lucky.
The address I found led us to a
nondescript building in downtown Medellín.
We raided it,
and guess who we found?
Blackbeard.
Pablo's number one accountant
and keeper of all secrets.
In custody,
he would describe a cocaine empire
that was bringing in $60 million a day.
Pablo was bigger than General Motors.
The mountain of evidence filled
an entire room in the Palace of Justice,
home of Colombia's supreme court,
the only place
thought safe enough to store it.
We had enough evidence
to put him away for 100 lifetimes.
Fuck.
- What's up?
- Jaramillo's running the show.
He's pissed we only gave him 100 grand.
He's not letting us
make any copies of anything.
Javi, there's some good stuff in here,
stuff we can use.
None of it can leave the room.
The narcos have been
paying some guy named Ellis McPickle
- to run coke all over the place.
- Ellis McPickle?
I'm assuming that it's an alias.
Take 'em.
- What?
- Just stuff 'em down your pants.
What are you talking about?
Do you want to catch Pablo or not?
- Why me?
- Because they'll suspect me.
- They won't suspect you.
- What if they search me?
They're not gonna
search a white boy, OK?
- You're a guest in their country.
- Guests don't steal.
Just do it.
Sometimes you gotta do bad things
to catch bad people.
- And sometimes, bad people...
- Señor.
...help you do good things.
These are
from the narcos' account in Miami.
A cashier's check
payable to "Ellis McPickle."
Yes.
I've heard that name mentioned
in some of the narco wiretap transcripts.
Obviously, it's an alias.
No Colombian would go by the name
"Ellis McPickle."
Because he's not Colombian.
He's an American pilot who transports
tons of cocaine for the cartel.
- A gringo?
- Mm-hm.
- What's his name?
- We don't know.
But we do know that Gustavo
frequently mentions "McPickle."
Suarez, do you ever worry
what will happen to you
if Pablo finds out
that you work for both sides?
- I'm on your side.
- Yeah?
Then prove it.
What else can you tell me about McPickle?
We have his photograph
in some of our files.
But maybe you should check with the CIA.
He started his career with them.
Wha-- What the fuck is this?
This is me giving you homework.
Former CIA pilot
flying coke for the narcos.
And I need you to find out who it is.
First off, I don't fucking work for you,
Murphy, you hear me?
- So don't come in here thinking that--
- Is that Barry Seal?
What's he up to these days?
Barry Seal.
Barry Seal, a good ol'
Southern boy who loved college football,
mind-altering chemicals,
and pussy...
which made him perfect CIA material.
But his expensive lifestyle
also made him perfect narco material.
Finding Barry was easy.
We just had to stake out
his favorite whorehouse.
It just so happened
to be Peña's favorite, too.
A friend of mine told me about this place.
I've never been here before.
No, I'm serious.
Look.
Oh, my God.
That's Freckles. I know her.
Until next time.
- Goddamn, is that Barry?
- Or should we say McPickle?
Come on, we got you a ride
waiting over here.
Hi, Vanessa.
It's fun to say, though,
ain't it? "McPickle"?
Have a seat, Barry.
You seem awful relaxed for someone
who's facing life in the clink.
- Well, you guys ain't got shit.
We got records from Escobar listing
shipments from Medellín to Louisiana
- to the tune of 500 tons?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Well, let's see
if that holds up in court, huh?
The funny thing is you can't make
a direct flight from Medellín to Louisiana
without making a refueling stop.
Yeah, according to the records,
you made stops in Cuba and Nicaragua.
The manifests don't lie.
An ex-CIA man making stops in communist
countries with or without cocaine,
that would be considered treason
by the US Justice Department, wouldn't it?
Well, damn...
you guys are good.
Communist sympathizer.
We're gonna wrap you up
in a big, red bow
and drop you right off
at Reagan's doorstep.
Using Cuba and Nicaragua
as refueling stops for coke shipments,
that's treason and trafficking.
What's that,
two life sentences for the price of one?
That's right.
Well... see,
I figured this day might come.
Why don't you uncuff me, boys.
I got something to show you.
Yeah? What's that?
It's what I call
a "get out of jail free" card.
Y'all gonna wanna see this.
Come on, uncuff me.
What Barry had was a picture of Escobar
loading cocaine on a tarmac
in Nicaragua. Why does that matter?
'Cause at the time, Nicaragua was
governed by the communist Sandinistas,
who were letting Escobar
use their country as a landing strip
for cocaine shipments to the US.
Colombian cocaine coming through
a communist country and into America?
I couldn't have made that up.
- Holy shit.
- It was too good.
- Gotta turn this over to the ambassador.
- Wait, wait, wait. No.
This leaks wide and Barry Seal
is a dead man. We gotta be careful.
Why are you trying to protect some scumbag
who's trafficked over 500 tons?
I have a code of ethics
when it comes to informants.
But not when it comes
to torturing suspects with hot coffee.
- You know, I wouldn't judge Carrillo.
- Why is that?
You had a partner killed.
He's had a dozen.
I always admired
Penã's commitment to informants,
but frankly,
Barry Seal wasn't an informant.
He was just another busted trafficker
who ratted on the guys
he worked with... a snitch.
If I could use
the narco-communist connection
to get the resources we needed,
then fuck him.
Strange bedfellows, indeed.
You have single-handedly
exposed a narco-communist connection.
Washington is gonna go crazy.
Thank you, Ambassador.
This has to be highly classified
for the safety of the informant.
Of course.
Thank you.
In Washington, "highly classified"
didn't carry much water.
Especially when a Marine colonel named
Oliver North got his hands on the picture.
I know every American parent
concerned about the drug problem
will be outraged to learn that
top Nicaraguan government officials
are deeply involved in drug trafficking.
This picture shows Federico Vaughan,
a top aide to one of the nine comandantes
who rule Nicaragua,
loading an aircraft with illegal narcotics
bound for the United States.
No, there seems to be no crime
to which the Sandinistas will not stoop.
Being a rat is a dangerous business,
and Escobar's reach was long.
Barry Seal refused federal protection...
...and met his end
in a parking lot in Baton Rouge.
Whoops.
Motherfucker!
I told you we had to be careful.
- You got Barry Seal killed.
- Peña, if he wanted a long life,
- he should've worked at Kodak.
- You're responsible for his death.
I didn't kill him, Escobar did.
Now we can go after that motherfucker.
Look on the bright side, man.
From then on, according to Reagan,
fighting the narcos
was the same as fighting the commies.
We got a tidal wave of money
and all the resources we needed.
The US Southern Command in Panama
sent us a care package:
planes, helicopters,
you fucking name it. Everything.
Our resources and intel helped the
Colombians raid labs all over the country
and burn 'em straight to the ground,
seizing over a billion dollars in coke.
We were kicking ass,
and the narcos were feeling it.
The price of cocaine in Miami
was skyrocketing.
Despite all this, we'd yet
to net one of the Medellín kingpins...
tilt we put a tracking device
on a Colombian-bound shipment of ether,
the essential ingredient
in cocaine processing.
Got it!
The barrel that we tracked
brought us to Tranquilandia,
Medellín 's biggest processing lab,
and we hit it hard.
The ensuing gun battle
cost dozens of men...
but in the end,
it got us our biggest victory to date,
the first of the Medellín kingpins:
Carlos Lehder.
In my tent is a bag with $50,000...
ten times this if you give me one hour.
There's no way out, Carlitos.
You're going to Disneyland.
Lehder was immediately
extradited to the States,
where a federal court
sentenced him to life... plus 135 years.
Extradition worked.
Carlos will die in an American jail.
And no one savored this victory
more than the Colombians.
For anti-narco candidate
Luis Carlos Galán,
it would provide him the momentum
he needed to propel him to the presidency.
Extradition would become his battle cry.
Gentlemen?
Thank you.
And for the narcos,
this was a declaration of war.
What happened to Carlos was terrible.
But I have already presented a motion
before the Supreme Court of Colombia
against the legality of extradition.
They are examining it this week
at the Palace of Justice.
Can we buy someone in that court?
Unfortunately, no.
It's the only institution in this country
that is incorruptible.
Let's pray that the ruling
comes out in our favor.
Brother... even after he's dead,
Carlos still has a sentence
of 135 years in prison.
He's totally fucked.
This is gringo bullshit.
That happened to him for speaking
about the revolution on the radio.
We're next, aren't we?
You're right.
Pablito?
Do you have an answer or what?
Well... in my opinion, a jail
in the United States is worse than death.
We can never forget
what happened to Carlos.
Carlos was one of us.
Fabio is right.
The Americans are fucking us.
But remember,
there's something they want more than us.
So, brothers...
it's time to give them what they want,
isn't it?
I didn't think our paths
would cross again.
What you want isn't going to be easy.
It's very risky.
It's going to require weapons and men.
There will be casualties.
I understand what you want.
How much are we talking about?
Two million US dollars.
It's very dangerous.
Fighting a revolution
comes with sacrifice...
and it goes without saying
that it will dangerous, right?
But for us, brother...
it is our duty to fight to the very end.
We have a historical obligation.
- We can't forget that.
I'm his girlfriend.
Meet Pablo Escobar.
Miss.
- OK.
- We have a deal.
All right, then.
We were just leaving.
Good night.
What the hell is this?
Why are you meeting with Escobar?
We made a deal...
obviously for money.
In exchange for what?
Unless you are willing to be part of it,
I cannot say.
It's a partnership,
necessary for the revolutionary fight.
I fight for the people...
not for drug traffickers.
Connie?
Elisa? What's going on?
- I need to talk to you.
- About what?
You told me your husband
works at the embassy.
Yeah.
I need you to speak with him
and warn him.
About what?
Pablo Escobar is planning something
with a communist group called the M-19.
I don't know what it is,
but I know it's gonna be bad.
Wait, Pablo Escobar?
How do you know anything about Escobar?
I-- I just know.
You need to warn him...
and you need to hide me.
OK. Come on.
Steve's already at work,
but Javi lives downstairs.
I just hope he's here.
I am.
- Well, what have we here?
- I'll explain later.
I'll be right back. Go.
- She told me that Escobar...
- Slow down.
...hired guerrillas called M-19. Thinks
they're gonna do something terrible.
- Slow down.
- Escobar is using members of M-19.
- Say that again?
- Pablo Escobar and M-19 guerrillas.
Escobar and M-19?
She didn't tell me any details,
just that it would be bad.
No... that doesn't make any sense.
She asked me to hide her,
so I took her to Javi's apartment.
OK. All right.
- Agent Murphy!
- All right.
Ambassador, I got information
with Escobar and M-19. I think they're--
-  ...supreme court building.
- Oh, my God.
"Oh, my God" is right.
Financed by Escobar, the M-19 guerrillas
stormed the Palace of Justice
and occupied the supreme court.
They took over 100 hostages
and made a bunch of demands
about the redistribution of wealth
and an end to injustice and tyranny...
but it was all bullshit.
The military attacked.
Dozens of lives
were lost in the carnage,
including half of
Colombia's supreme court justices.
Most of the M-19 were killed.
Some escaped... but not before
accomplishing their true goal:
setting fire to the room that contained
600,000 pages of evidence against Escobar.
The entire case against him
turned to ash.
In the United States,
the Mafia makes witnesses disappear
so they can't testify in court.
In Colombia, Pablo Escobar
made the whole court disappear.
The fires set by guerrillas
earlier in the day grew even stronger
as cannon shells exploded inside.
- Where is she?
- Well, come on in.
You, up! Who in the fuck is she
and why is the military after her?
Put the gun away.
Put it away.
She told me who she is.
Put the gun away.
- Can I say something?
- No, you may not.
Murphy... calm down.
I have no idea
why you'd get yourself involved in this.
Your wife brought her to me.
I appreciate you putting yourself
out there for my wife, I truly do,
but why are we risking
our whole careers over this woman?
Because she can prove
that Pablo was behind the palace siege.
If she can tie Escobar to the siege,
I say we bring her in.
Well, she's M-19.
Noonan would have to turn her over
to the Colombian military
and then she gets disappeared.
I'd like to avoid
another Barry Seal situation.
So we're gonna
harbor a communist fugitive?
Look, all she did was warn us.
She's not on anybody's radar.
She's not involved in anything.
The red X's you see in these pictures
indicate M-19 revolutionaries
terminated by
the Colombian Special Forces.
The remaining individuals you see
are fugitives.
Folks, this is more complicated
than what it seems.
This was Escobar, classic.
He's cut a deal with M-19.
Next you'll tell us
Escobar sank the Titanic.
Was it coincidence the extradition
evidence against him was destroyed?
He doesn't hold grudges,
not if it suits his purposes.
- How do you know he cut a deal?
- We have a confidential informant.
You willing to identify this informant,
Agent Peña?
- No, I am not.
- Needless to say...
Southern Command has rescinded
its offer of resources to the DEA
in light of this communist aggression.
We need to target the M-19 leadership:
Ivan "the Terrible" Torres
and Elisa Alvarez.
They're looking for us everywhere.
What did you expect?
That it would be any different?
You did a very good job.
You can't imagine how much
this is going to help our cause.
No, brother.
The truth is, you helped mine.
You, Ivan...
gave me the sword of Simón Bolívar.
The same one that freed this country.
Now it belongs to you.
With it, you will continue the fight...
to free this country.
I promise you,
I will continue the fight.
You earned it, brother.
As for me...
I'll be in Panama until this blows over.
We are also--
Make sure you grab the briefcase.
And the fucking sword.