h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
(Low rumbling, growing louder)
(Horses whinnying)
(Engines racing)
(In Spanish) Bastard.
- Let's make a bet. I'm for the boss.
- I'm betting on the boss, too.
This one is going to be easy.
They always let the boss win.
That's true, but if someone's going
to beat him, it's this guy.
(Gustavo over radio)
'Tell me something. Are you a pussy?'
(Gustavo cackles)
(♪ Up-tempo Latin music plays)
Son of a bitch.
- What's going on?
- You're a little slow, son.
Careful, son, careful!
Keep looking forward, son!
(Excited chatter in Spanish)
(Honking)
(Laughing) Oh, shit!
All right, boys,
start getting that money out.
(Overlapping chatter)
(Kissing)
...eighty. I'm missing 20.
(Pablo) Looks like
you won some money, eh?
Of course,
we're enjoying ourselves, boss.
Very good, son.
- Very good.
- (Softly) What? Did he get pissed?
Hey.
Do you know why you won?
That little trick.
The same one, right?
Don't be an idiot.
You know why you lost, Pablo?
- Why?
- Hmm?
Because you're a very smart guy,
but you're too stubborn.
You understand?
What I understand is I don't like to lose.
Especially because of tricks.
- Someone had to teach you how to lose.
- Yeah, why?
(Low chuckle)
- Very well, you son of a bitch.
- (Poison) Boss?
- A photo?
- Sure, but not with that pansy.
No, no, no, no. You go over there.
Over there, motherfucker.
Cousin, cousin, cousin, cousin.
It's because he doesn't know
how to lose, but that's fine.
- Where are we headed, guys?
- To the whores!
Look how they left this place.
We found both the guards.
Stuffed into a trunk, burned alive.
Did anybody see anything?
We're sending spotters out, but...
they either come back with nothing or...
- Or what?
- Or they don't come back.
That bitch Judy Moncada did this.
But she couldn't do this alone.
No fucking way.
The guys that came at me
had high-end weapons.
Big ones.
Gringo shit.
The Cali cartel.
I fucking know it.
Those sons of bitches
will regret it.
I will personally burn that fucking city
to the ground.
(Carlos) We don't know that Pablo.
Until we know who did it, we can't attack
the Cali cartel. It would be a mistake.
Get whoever we can out on the street.
Give them cash.
And if anyone needs more persuasion,
motivate them.
Put the word out. We're going to kill
all the bastards who did this.
I know I hit one of them.
Let's hope he's still breathing.
Because then...
we can find out who that son of a bitch
is working for.
(Vehicle doors slam shut)
(♪ Latin guitar theme music plays)
- (Festive music playing)
- (Children chatter indistinctly)
(Steve) 'Colombia is a Catholic country,
so Christmas is a big deal.
'But the people of Medellín
always take it to the next level.
'And despite the manhunt for Pablo
going on around them,
'this year was no different.
'Call it faith, optimism,
or stubbornness,
'the people of Medellín thought
they'd seen it all, but they hadn't.
'In fact, they hadn't seen anything yet.'
(Low murmurs)
PABLO MERRY CHRISTMAS
LOS PEPES
HAPPY HOLIDAYS
'Medellín was about to get a show
they would never forget.'
(In Spanish) Good day.
In a letter sent to the media, a group
that identifies itself as "Los Pepes",
an acronym for
"People Persecuted by Pablo Escobar."
(Woman in English) '...or
"People Persecuted by Pablo Escobar,"
'the vigilantes waging war on those
associated with the notorious drug lord.'
(In Spanish) Mr President, the media
is asking for a comment on Los Pepes.
It's only a matter of time
before it's made public.
Acknowledgement isn't the same
as condemning.
Sooner or later, you'll have to make
an official public statement.
They're doing God's work
as far as I'm concerned.
- That can't be our official position.
- It can be our official position...
(Overlapping arguments)
(Gaviria) Gentlemen!
Los Pepes is a vigilante death squad.
We'll take care of them
when the time comes.
But for now, let's focus
on our own efforts to catch Escobar.
I believe that's proven
a big enough job for all of us.
(Martinez) Communications picked up
conversations in the Manrique district
between Jairo, who is one of Escobar's
sicarios, and his mother, who is ill.
We know Jairo is her only child
and likely to visit her.
We'll continue to monitor the frequencies
for further information.
One more thing.
I don't have to tell you that there's
another group now operating in Medellín,
combating Escobar: Los Pepes.
Let me be very clear.
There must and will be a clear line
between them and us.
- Understood?
- (All) Yes, Colonel.
(Martinez) Dismissed, thank you.
(In English) So Los Pepes
is an interesting new wrinkle.
Well, are you surprised?
Escobar's got a lot of enemies.
I heard from Messina this morning.
There's a lot of eyes on them and us,
so she wants us to steer clear.
Are you working for Los Pepes, Murphy?
No, I'm not.
Then I guess we're good.
(♪ Latin music plays over radio)
(In Spanish) CNP's been busy
with wiretaps.
They picked up chatter
from Jairo's mum here... and here.
Search Bloc won't be able to move until
they get corroboration he's in the area.
Which could take days.
Even longer...
for them to find the house.
I think... Jairo is planning
a homecoming.
Maybe even today.
I'll see what I can find out
on the streets.
(Phone rings)
- Hello?
- (Berna) 'Listen up, Carlos.'
I have information that Jairo
is going to his mother's.
(Steve) 'For Los Pepes, it was easy.
'They had all the man-on-the-street
intelligence they needed.
'If they heard a guy, take Jairo
for example, was in a certain vicinity,
'they just asked around
and they find them.
'But for us, well,
we had to go door-to-door,
'asking for help from people
who don't tell cops shit.'
- (In Spanish) Police. Can you open up?
- What do you need?
Open up. Hurry. Hurry.
(Steve) 'Los Pepes, on the other hand,
had no problems.
'They were quite persuasive.'
(Murmuring in Spanish)
'Sure, once in a while,
we got lucky and picked somebody up.
'But it was rarely the guy
we were looking for.'
(Arguing in Spanish)
Shh! Don't make me kill you
in front of your mother.
Don't touch her!
Relax, mother, relax.
(Steve) 'It was slow-going.'
(Martinez in Spanish) If you don't
cooperate, we can't find your son.
But I don't know where he is.
I didn't notice anything.
Do you have enemies here
in the neighbourhood?
I don't know.
It was my fault that he was here.
He came to see his mother...
(In English) We're too late.
Says they already got him.
We finally get corroboration on Jairo,
Martinez orders the raid...
So?
Well, so, how does Los Pepes
get here first?
Maybe he got followed.
Or the dumb fuck shot his mouth off
and somebody else got lucky.
Mmm. That's it?
That's all you got to say on that?
Yeah.
If it worries you, look into it.
(Steve) '"Look into it"? Right.
'Nobody was looking into it.
Why would they?
'Pablo's crew was turning up dead
all over Medellín,
and Jairo became the latest victim.
'The terror that Pablo had spread
across the country
'was finally back on him tenfold.
Los Pepes' method was working.
'And you better believe
it was getting to Escobar.'
IN DEFENCE
OF THE COLOMBIAN PEOPLE
(Carlos in Spanish)
What did you ask Santa for?
- (Juan Pablo) A game.
- Which one?
- (Juan Pablo) The Joker game.
- You think he'll bring it to you?
(Juan Pablo) Dad?
Santa is going to bring me
the Joker game, right?
Dad? Dad?
Pablo, my love?
Of course, Santa will bring you
everything you want, like always.
Christmas without Christ.
Pablo.
I'm planning on going to the advent
service tomorrow with the kids.
What? No.
No one should leave this house.
I'm sure the kids would love
to see the lights, Pablo.
(Tata) The children are staying here
and so are you.
(Hermilda) Remember the first time
you saw the fireworks?
My love, can you tell your mother
she can't take the children to Medellín?
(Pablo) Mama, it's best for us
to stay here.
It's been a month
since I've gone to church.
I'm sure that God
can hear your prayers from here.
(Blackie) Don Pablo.
Boss, they killed three more
of our men.
They found Jairo dead
next to the river.
- (Low chatter)
- Look, it's the Baccarat Crystal.
- Thank you.
- Oh!
- That's also Baccarat Crystal.
- Feel the weight. Look...
(Woman taps on crystal)
You can feel it's Baccarat.
This is from the Lloredas, right?
How's it going, my love?
My love, look at what
the Lloredas brought.
- Look, there's two.
- The Lloredas always treat us well...
(Chatter continues)
NEW DEATH SQUAD IN MEDELLÍN
(Gilberto) 'As gratifying
as these displays may feel,'
I'm not comfortable with these signs.
They invite too much attention
and will lead to questions.
Our objective is to eliminate Escobar
as efficiently and discreetly as possible.
Without a doubt.
No more proclamations or manifestos
or letters to the media.
What about Miami?
We buy time.
Let him think he still has control.
Until the moment we take it from him.
(In Spanish) New intel
from the embassy.
Thank you.
(In English) Centra Spike
give us anything good for Christmas?
Well, Blackie's been getting calls
from Envigado.
The son of a bitch
has got a girlfriend.
Here, I'll give that to Martinez.
I'm sure it's gotta get vetted.
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
(Line ringing)
(Berna in Spanish)
'What do you have for me?'
I got something new.
- 'Blackie.'
- I like the way this is going, Javier.
He's got a girlfriend. She's pregnant,
keeps calling. They're vetting it now.
It'll take a while.
Blackie's going to show.
'It's done.'
(Steve) 'I didn't know how Los Pepes
was beating us to the punch.
'Not yet anyway.
What I did know was that if Search Bloc
'was gonna have any kind of impact
on the hunt for Pablo,
'we'd have to play the game
better and faster.'
All right, Blackie's had a girlfriend
in Envigado for a while.
According to Centra Spike,
the last known intercept
places her somewhere in this vicinity.
Yeah. And how's that relevant?
Intel says she's pregnant.
I know protocol is to vet intel,
wait for corroboration,
but I feel this one in my gut, sir.
Blackie's gonna show.
Los Pepes keeps getting
the jump on us,
sicarios are gonna keep
winding up dead.
This way, we get to Blackie first,
bring that son of a bitch in
and get something out of him.
Well, we could set up a perimeter.
No one walks in or out.
(Steve) Collapse that perimeter
house by house.
- (Martinez) Yeah.
- (Steve) Sounds good to me.
(Groans, in Spanish) Almighty Holy Child
of Atocha. Carmelita, help me please.
Don't fight with me anymore.
I'm going to tell you two things:
first, relax.
That's harmful for you and the baby.
Second, for the love of God,
take the money.
I'll find more later.
It's not for you or me, it's for the baby,
please understand.
Try to understand me.
I don't want your money.
I want you to be with me
and the baby, that's it.
Stop being stupid, girl.
We need that money.
- Listen to your dad.
- I don't know what's wrong with this girl.
(Blackie) She's stubborn.
(Chatter in Spanish)
- (In English) Hey!
- Hey.
What's going on?
Martinez gave the green light
to go after Blackie.
- It's a good thing, right?
- Yeah. Right.
Goddamn Christmas miracle.
(In Spanish) Post three is in position.
(Man over radio) 'Yes, sir,
we'll be there in five minutes.'
(Berna) 'Wait, Javier.'
(In English) We're moving in.
Let's go.
(Phone ringing)
(In Spanish) Talk to me.
We're just getting here.
Copy that, we're leaving now.
It was Berna.
The streets are full of Search Bloc.
All right, boys, the hunt is over for now.
Let's get out of here.
- What's going on?
- Nothing, sir.
We're conducting a police operation.
All good?
(Affirmative murmur)
Let him through.
Keep calm, guys.
Hide your weapons while we handle this.
Let him through.
Good evening, what can I do for you?
Good afternoon, gentleman.
I need to see some form of ID, please.
Of course, with pleasure.
How's this for an ID?
Get out of the car and put your hands
where I can see them.
Quickly.
Boy, come over here.
- Colonel. Situation at checkpoint 20.
- What's going on?
- Armed men attempting to pass through.
- Checkpoint 20?
That's correct, sir.
- All units move to position 20.
- Understood.
All units to position 20. Move!
- (In English) What's going on?
- Some shit's going down at checkpoint.
(In Spanish) My love,
you have to take the money.
Blackie! Blackie.
The cops are here.
Take care of the baby!
Take care, Carmelita!
We're both on the same team here.
What's the problem?
Stay where you are!
Hands where I can see them.
Relax, relax.
Want to see my ID?
- Take it out slowly.
- OK.
You point a gun at me, motherfucker?
Do me a favour.
Move those cars because we're
not playing cops and robbers here.
(Steve in English)
What the fuck is this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
(In Spanish) Relax! Relax!
Relax! Relax!
Disarm. Disarm!
- No, you disarm!
- Sir...
(Carlos) Lower your firearm!
(In English) Put the fucking gun down!
(In Spanish) Easy! Easy!
(Javier clapping)
OK, tough guys. Bravo!
Bravo!
Bravo, yes, we know it.
We all want Escobar.
But let us do the fucking job.
(Softly) What? You want to
kill each other at a checkpoint?
Lower your weapon.
Lower it.
(Whispers) Lower it.
OK. These dreamers
think they're helping.
- Are you OK? Yeah? Everything OK?
- Yes, sir.
OK. Let's go home alive.
- OK?
- OK.
- Let them pass.
Well then, thank you.
(In English) Trying to avoid
a bloodbath, brother.
(In Spanish) What happened?
Everything OK? Yes?
Yes, sir.
(Trujillo) Miss,
we need your cooperation.
Tell us where Blackie is.
Where do we find him?
I told you.
I haven't seen him.
Don't be afraid.
We don't want you.
We want your boyfriend, Blackie.
Sir, I told you,
I don't know where he's at.
That bastard has not come around
in a long time.
If you want, let's go to the station.
But I told you, I don't know where he is.
So please leave my house.
They were eight, maybe ten.
How did they take your firearm?
- I don't know, he just took it. Sorry.
- (Sighs)
Next time, might as well
put the gun to your own head.
It's easier.
(Sighs)
(In English) When were
you gonna tell me
about your new friend
Carlos Castaño?
He's not a friend, he's a...
he's a man with a shared interest.
Jesus Christ.
I hope you know what you're doing.
Don't worry.
It's not gonna blow back on you.
- No, it's not me I'm worried about.
- I can handle it.
These aren't the guys
you wanna be messing with.
They're gonna do what they're gonna do
with or without me, right?
At least this way...
I'm on the inside and I can control it.
- Make sure it doesn't go too far.
- So that doesn't go too far?
The good guys, they got guns
pointing at their fucking head
- and the bad guys get away with it?
- Who are the good guys, Steve?
That's us?
(In Spanish) Mr President,
these men, the Castaños,
I've seen their tactics firsthand
in the jungle against the FARC.
'Their method of war is murder.
I think this is only the beginning.
'And it will get even worse.'
'Colonel, I understand your concern.'
It's strange. They usually operate
against the guerrillas
but now they're operating
against the narcos.
Hugo, my cabinet is still evaluating
the best course of action
with regard to Los Pepes.
Sir, I'd like your permission
to engage them.
No. The greatest service we can do
for this nation is capture Escobar.
That's what we must focus on, Colonel.
'It's our priority.'
I understand. Thank you, sir.
(Steve) 'Los Pepes may have
seemed to be running the board,
'but Escobar still had a trick or two
up his sleeve.
'Remember I told you Ricardo Prisco
was a licensed doctor?
'Well, he was.
'And as such, he had privileges
at just about every hospital in Medellín.
'Including the one where the Los Pepes
gunman he shot was recovering.
'Unfortunately for that guy,
Dr Prisco paid him a visit.'
(In Spanish) Let's take a look
at this injury.
Oh... very good.
- (Muffled screams)
- Shh!
(Whimpering)
This is going to hurt.
Tell me who you work for.
(Pablo) The Castaños.
Mmm.
The Castaños.
What could have brought them
out of the jungle?
I say it was money.
More money
than Judy Moncada can find.
Pablo.
Now is not the time
to take on more problems, brother.
The Cali cartel thinks
they're immune to attack.
This can't go unanswered.
Go.
(Men murmur in Spanish)
Maria.
(Whispers) Carlos, you scared me.
Tata, you have to do it now.
Pablo's gone mad.
With everything he's planning,
there will be consequences.
You and the kids
need to separate from him.
No, Carlos.
Tata, my God, listen to me.
There's a fearlessness to Los Pepes
that I've never seen.
The public declarations,
the open displays.
They won't stop until he's dead.
I know that, Carlos.
I've known for a long time now.
You know what's the only thought
on my mind?
That this is the last time...
the last time
I'll look at my husband's face.
The last time
I'll feel his arms around me.
The last time I'll see him play
with our children.
I automatically push that idea
out of my mind.
And now? Hmm?
Now I know, Carlos,
that wherever I go...
I'll always be Pablo Escobar's wife.
My children will always
be Pablo Escobar's children.
Even if we lived in exile
with him.
But without him? (Scoffs softly)
No.
OK. OK.
Let's do something.
If we talk to him,
maybe he'll reconsider leaving with us.
I've had a good life.
Did you ever imagine
we'd have all this?
(Overlapping chatter slowly subsides)
When my niece was growing up,
she didn't think this day would come.
- (Low chuckles)
- She was so skinny.
- She wore glasses and had braces.
- Yes.
When she was 12,
she thought her life was over.
I told her to wait and be patient.
Someday her beauty on the outside
would match her beauty within.
You have never looked more beautiful
than you do tonight.
(Murmurs of agreement in crowd)
Cheers to the family.
To Marta and Diego! Cheers!
- (Crowd) Cheers!
- (Applause)
(♪ Up-tempo Latin music plays)
(Whispers indistinctly)
(Indistinct chatter)
(Music continues nearby)
(Explosion, people screaming)
(Diego) Wait!
Wait! Wait!
(Woman moans)
(Chaotic chatter)
(Woman sobbing)
Ma! Papa! Papa!
- I'm here, my love.
- Mum! (sobs)
(Sobbing continues)
That man...
has no decency.
To attack my family like this...
my daughter...
on the night of her wedding...
Only a madman would do that.
A crazed animal, dangerous.
I want him dead.
Not next year. Right now.
Kill all of them.
I don't just want you to kill his lawyers,
accountants and bankers...
I want you to kill his secretaries...
anyone who lifted a finger
to help that man.
I want to see them dead.
Anyone who has ever licked
a postage stamp
and put it on an envelope
in his name,
I want to see them dead!
And then I want you to find anyone who
ever shook his hand and kill them too!
That son of a bitch.
From this night, we'll show no mercy.
(Pablo) 'Gilberto?'
(La Quica) Gilberto, Miguel
and Pacho survived, boss.
That'll be all, Quica.
Thank you, boss.
(Carlos) Pablo?
I'm worried about Tata.
I think you should let her travel.
She'll be safer.
What you're doing
will have consequences.
That's why they're here. Right?
That's why they're here with me,
to be safe.
- Cali is going to want payback for...
- I know...
who my enemies are, Carlos.
And I can fight them all.
I know that.
But if Tata and the children
are out of the country,
you'd be free to wage this war
with no holds barred.
Let me ask you something.
- Why are you here?
- Pablo...
For Tata.
Right?
To make her happier.
To help her be more comfortable
with the life we're being forced to lead.
Have you done that?
Pablo, my sister is terrified.
And you can't see that...
Your sister is a lot tougher
than you think.
My wife... and my children...
stay with me.
(Sighs)
(In Spanish) Hello.
(In English) Did you see this?
Reports of a massive bombing
in Cali last night.
Gilberto Rodríguez's
daughter's wedding?
(Chuckles)
I know of only one person
in Colombia
with the balls big enough
to go after that guy.
Yeah, Pablo Escobar.
He had to have had
a damn good reason.
I'd like to shift some of our resources
from Medellín to Cali.
Now's a bad time
to deviate from Medellín.
Cali is trafficking
in the billions right now.
- If they get a free head start...
- You're not wrong.
But you're thinking
about this too logically.
The best thing for you right now
is to keep your head in the game.
Because right now,
the game is Pablo Escobar.
Right. Escobar.
I'll see you at the party tonight.
We could all use a few hours break
from this shit.
I'll see you there.
Manuel.
(In Spanish) Ma'am?
Take me to Mass.
- But the boss said we couldn't.
- Pablo worries too much.
Besides, you work for me.
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
on earth, as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
(♪ Festive Latin music plays)
(Man in English)
Welcome, Mr President.
Welcome, Ma'am.
Yeah, Bogotá is beautiful. It's a lot more
like an American city than I thought.
I didn't know it'd be so cold.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you.
(In Spanish) It's shameful for the country
to stand by while a group of mercenaries
distributes its version
of perverse justice.
It makes all of us look bad.
- Including the president.
- Especially the president.
If he continues to allow Los Pepes
to do the dirty work,
which is his responsibility...
Colombia will never forgive him.
(Church bells tolling)
(Murmurs indistinctly)
MERRY CHRISTMAS
(Engine starts)
(Overlapping chatter)
(In English) Mr President.
Lovely party, Ambassador.
It's nice we can pretend
we're all friends.
Believe it or not, the State Department
does the guest list, not me.
I can't wait to tell them
that he wants us to legalise drugs.
He thinks I should
publicly condemn Los Pepes.
They're criminals.
Their activities cannot be condoned.
Even if one does approve of the results.
(Sighs) Mr President,
I'm not one to bullshit.
Maybe that's hurt me in my career.
Yes, Los Pepes are an ugly business.
They're getting to Escobar.
That's all that matters at the present.
If I condemn them,
I have to police them.
With politics and war...
the trick is in the timing.
Watch how they evolve,
how their actions are received.
And, uh, up till then,
pretend they don't exist.
Well, we can if you can.
(♪ Singing "Silent Night" in Spanish)
What are you up to in here?
Have a drink.
Thanks.
Saved me a trip to the bar.
Call it inter-agency cooperation.
Hmm. That's a joke.
And it's funny.
Cheers.
So where are you from, Bill?
Originally, Oregon.
You were in Afghanistan, right?
Well, I could tell you that
but then I'd have to...
Funny.
I know Bill Haler.
He was our guy in Afghanistan.
Oh, yeah.
DEA Bill, we used to call him.
I liked him.
Stayed in his lane.
So, as I'm sure you know,
I recently asked for a resource redirect
into some emerging players
in the trafficking world.
- A group based in Cali. Ring a bell?
- (Sighs)
We're not gonna talk
about work, are we?
My request was denied, Bill.
We were just
getting to know each other.
So I spoke to DEA Bill.
- He's in Washington now.
- You don't say.
And he told me the roadblock
was caused by the agency.
Something about an ongoing operation.
He actually said,
"That sounds like CIA Bill."
Look, I don't care what you do
with the commies and the paramilitaries.
But as soon as your ongoing operations
involve narcos... you're in my backyard.
(Door opens, closes)
(In Spanish) Where were you?
- I went to church.
- I told you it wasn't safe.
And I told you that it would be fine.
And look, everything's fine.
How could you put
the children's lives at risk?
No one here is in danger.
I'm surprised at you, Pablo. This one
has always been nervous, but you?
Don't talk that way to my husband.
I can talk to him however I want.
I don't know why everyone is...
http://hiqve.com/
- (Gunshot)
- Take Tata and the kids!
- You, cover my mother!
- (Automatic gunfire)
- (Shouting in Spanish)
- (Screaming)
(Gunfire continues)
(Panting)
Juan Pablo! Juan Pablo!
Put your coat on, quick!
Put your coat on.
Come here, Manuela.
Let's go, Pablo!
This way! Run!
- Run! Run!
- (Automatic gunfire nearby)
- Run quickly! (Screams)
- (Glass shatters)
- Quickly!
- (Overlapping gunfire)
- Pablo!
- Get out! Get out! Get out!
Carlos, let's go!
Run, Limón, run!
Let's go! Outside!
- Come on, Tata, come on.
- Get him in the car. Get him inside!
- Quickly! Let's go!
- Quickly!
Give me the girl.
- Get in, Tata, get in.
- (Overlapping shouts)
Come on, brother. Go!
Cover that side!
Move!
(Gunfire continues nearby)
(Overlapping gunfire)
(Grunts)
(Man grunts)
- (Glass shattering)
- (Gunfire continues)
(Indistinct shouts in Spanish)
They're in the house!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Calm down.
- Don't let her move.
Carlos!
Come on, boss! Let's go.
- (Tata) Pablo!
- Carlos!
(Grunts)
- (Scream) No!
- (Groans)
- Come on! Come on!
- (Gunfire continues)
- Boss, come on!
- (Screaming)
Let's go, boss!
- Come on!
- (Screaming)
- Let's go!
- (Shrieks) Carlos!
(Sobbing)
No!
Los Pepes...
the Cali cartel, Judy Moncada,
the Castaños, the government,
the gringos.
Let the bastards come.
We'll be ready for a war,
a fucking bloodbath.
We will fight like we have never
fought before in our lives.
Yes, boss.
Go for food
and you go for firewood.
(Softly) Whoever did this
will never get near us ever again.
I promise you.
Daddy, how will Santa
know how to find us?
(Voice trembling)
(Softly) Santa...
Santa will always find
your good and kind heart.
Wherever you are in this world.
Boss? The wood is all wet.
There's no way to light it up.
Go to Envigado for wood and food.
- Right away, boss.
- Be careful not to be seen.
Got it.
This is all I could find, boss.
How do you open that shit?
I'll go look, boss.
(In Spanish) This just came in.
Shit's getting real, Peña.
(Sirens wailing in distance)
- (Tata sniffling)
- Mummy, I'm cold.
She's freezing.
Put this on.
You and the children...
need to leave Colombia.
When you're safe,
I'll be free to do what's best for us.
(Softly) It won't be long.
Soon we'll be together again.
Forever.
(Sniffling)
(♪ Slow Latin guitar song plays)
http://hiqve.com/