On the road from Galilee,
Christ came upon a beggar
who had thrice been denied alms.
Christ asked him if he'd taken before
that which wasn't his.
"Yes," the man said. He'd taken
what he felt hadn't been given.
Christ asked him...
Christ asked him
where had it left him...
Give him some.
Boss, I think I know whose car this is.
My name is Pacho Herrera.
I want Gerda Salazar
and her fucking sons delivered to me.
Until that happens,
nobody in the North Valley is safe.
Is that clear?
Make sure Orlando Henao
gets the message.
And now... pray.
Pray.
...that war is bad for business.
Unless it's won.
Buenaventura is in Henao's territory.
We have to get the port back so we can
maintain our delivery schedules.
You think that... it can be done?
Negotiating with the government
and the fucking surrender...
it all means one thing.
Our allies and enemies think
we're weak.
My brother Gilberto
is responsible for that.
- How's Alvaro?
- What do you want me to say, Miguel?
The doctors still don't know
if his cock will ever work again.
He's 22 years old.
I swear to you, Pacho,
the Salazars will pay for that shit.
MONASTERY OF EL CARMEN
Agent Peña, nice to meet you.
Your reputation precedes you.
ANTI-NARCOTIC POLICE
I will put in maximum effort,
with all my soul,
into fighting corruption.
Because when there is corruption,
there is no procedure,
there is no peace of mind.
This informant of yours,
is he close to Miguel Rodríguez?
He's provided us with Miguel's location.
That's why it's urgent we move now.
It may take a miracle
to get this close again.
Only God creates miracles.
It's for us to use the tools he's bestowed
to resolve these matters.
Any chance God's bestowed
the right men to pull off this operation?
God has many soldiers.
Mine are honest men who answer
to higher powers than you or I.
I'm not concerned about them.
But I'm worried about other issues.
Gilberto Rodríguez's arrest
has led to new stipulations.
From now on, any warrant I sign
has to be filed with the local
fiscale office in Cali.
Which the cartel will know about.
Possibly.
Truth is, your tactics won't be
allowed a second run.
Just have to find new ones, General.
Your men, General,
where are they now?
Awaiting their orders.
The target is Miguel Rodríguez.
Our operation will succeed
because you fulfil your duty
to your God and to your country,
understood?
Yes, sir!
The operation from a strategic
point of view is a nightmare.
There's a security perimeter.
As soon as the lead team hits the lobby,
the target knows we're inside.
Agent Feistl and I will be right
behind you, arriving by helicopter.
We'll land on the roof
and come in from above.
- We're going to box them in.
- Yes.
We have an inside man.
He'll be posted right here,
giving us our best way in.
- Which one do you want?
- This one!
Okay. Perfect.
Girls, please get ready.
Paola... you can't do this.
- I'm taking the girls to my parents'.
- Paola, you can't do this.
Especially with what's going on
with the cartel.
What are you saying?
Are you telling me I can't protect
my daughters? Is that what you're saying?
No. What I'm saying is that we need
to act normal, like everything is fine.
Everything isn't fine, Jorge.
Everything isn't fine.
They could be watching
you, me, the girls.
Miguel's become paranoid.
Do you understand?
I'll call you in a few days.
The girls will want to hear from you.
Paola. Please.
The Americans are going to try
to arrest Miguel.
I'm going to make sure they succeed.
Tomorrow, we will be on a plane.
You, me, the girls.
- We're leaving Colombia.
- Who told you I want to live in the U.S.?
Who told you our girls want to leave
the only home they've ever known?
So we need to disappear.
Is that your plan?
Explain to me again
because I don't get it!
What happens if the Americans fail?
Paola, please. Please... wait.
Don't leave.
We weren't poor, Jorge.
We always had choices.
This was your choice.
What about the warrant?
You still haven't filed the paperwork.
- And we can do nothing without it.
- We're bringing the fiscale with us.
Until we're on-site,
no one else knows the real target.
Arrest him quickly.
Because if word of this gets out,
they'll try to stop us
with everything they've got.
General...
One more thing.
I'd like to ask you
to remain in Bogotá.
Those are my men.
That's my signature on the warrant.
Which puts your name on the line, sir.
If anything goes wrong,
and we look like...
Like what? Like idiots?
It wouldn't be the first time,
as I understand it.
You don't trust me.
But you can't do this without me.
That's true,
but I know the system we're up against.
With your name on the warrant,
there's no doubt
the cartel's watching you.
As soon as you make the arrest,
I'll be the one to lead Miguel Rodríguez
into custody when the press arrive.
I'll stay here praying for your success,
because there's no doubt
that it's your reputation now on the line.
Hi, boss. What's going on?
Getting a little late for you, huh?
Just checking in. You run those taps
over in El Lido like I asked?
- Yes, sir. Perfect.
- All right. Well done.
Enrique, why don't you take off
and I'll keep an eye out here tonight?
Is this some kind of test?
Someone offers me a day off,
I say yes.
My wife's been hounding me.
I could use a night away
from all of her questions, Enrique.
I'm glad I'm not married yet.
Don't make that mistake.
Thank you, boss.
It's Miguel.
Don't worry, boss.
I'll hang out until you get back.
Good.
Miguel's just finishing his call.
Come on in.
We can discuss that later.
He's here now.
Yes, you've said.
My son.
You know how he is. A little...
complicated.
He's your son.
Good things are coming, Jorge.
You'll be part of it.
I'm glad, sir.
Is there anything else?
Take a seat.
You know that my brother...
he doesn't like this war thing.
He thinks it's a mistake,
being at war with the North Valley.
He said this brings too much tension,
with the violence and everything.
He's getting counsel from men
I don't trust at all.
Those phones that you...
What do you call them? Wiretaps?
Wiretap.
Do you think...
you could put one
on my brother's phone in prison?
You want me to tap
Gilberto's phone in prison?
For his own good.
Only if it became necessary.
So... for him.
Of course, sir. Anything you need.
Good.
- This stays here.
- Of course, sir.
Well, I should get back downstairs.
I'm posted outside tonight.
You? Nonsense.
You're too old for that!
I don't mind at all. It's part of my job.
No. No way.
Have one of the young guys do it.
You know, I'm eating late.
Fercho was about to make something.
You'll join us.
You'll join us, Jorge.
Fercho, we will be two! Come.
Do you like filets, Jorge?
Yes, very much.
Hey, I've been meaning to tell you...
the building guys,
they've been idling in front of the house.
Blocking our exit.
You see that?
Feels good when one's been taken care.
Yes. Keep your walkie charged.
And the exits clear, like you said.
- You want one?
- Yes, thanks.
Look, I have a bottle
of white wine that is...
Excuse me, boss, if it's not
too much trouble, I prefer red wine.
Okay. It's a shame, but... OK.
But I have a really nice bottle
of red wine. I'll bring it. I'll be back.
You're in for a treat tonight.
Miguel has me cooking
with these Japanese bread crumbs.
Sounds crazy,
but it's actually more tasty.
That's very interesting.
Hey, Fercho,
looks like the oil's ready.
Yes.
Boss!
We have cars heading towards the building.
I repeat, boss, three trucks with cops...
Gentlemen, by law, I can't let you in.
This is a residence...
A residence?
You hear that?
Enrique!
What the fuck's going on?
How come you didn't inform us
there's a helicopter?
- How the fuck did they find us?
- Sir, calm down.
We need to get you out of here now.
There's no time to discuss this.
- Miguel, what's happening?
- You need to hide.
Is there somewhere we can take you?
A caleta in the apartment?
Stop. Get to the lobby.
Get to the lobby and stop them.
It's better if he goes.
Every second counts.
- Get to the lobby! Stop them.
- María.
What the fuck is this?
- Are you Fernando Castillo?
- What's this about?
We're here to arrest Miguel Rodríguez.
Miguel isn't here.
- There's nothing.
- Look above.
Take that off!
Cabinets. There's nothing here.
Try the ones below.
Who's in charge here?
I asked you a question.
Sorry, sir. We're not authorised
to let anyone inside.
You see this fucking badge?
Your superiors failed to report
this operation with the local bureau.
I'd like to know
who'll be answering for that.
These are direct orders
from my superiors, sir.
Step out of my way.
Peinados, stay here.
- Let's go!
- Move!
Sergeant, you copy?
The local police are heading up.
Go to the back, please.
You can sit on the couch.
How long is this going to take?
What are you doing?
Hey, kid. Where is he?
Was Miguel Rodríguez here?
Don't speak to my son.
Can he please go to his room?
He's just a child.
- Is the room clear?
- Clear.
Okay, leave. Go ahead.
Flores.
- Who's in charge here?
- DEA.
I assume with Colombian support.
I don't see a ranking officer.
Guess that puts me in charge.
There's an exit over there
that leads to the street.
Do you have anyone posted there?
Of course.
If you'd properly notified my unit,
we could've blocked that exit
and prevented this escape.
There's no evidence he got out.
That's why you're looking
through the kitchen cabinets?
Wake up, man! We have to go.
Let go of her already.
Come on, man!
Don't say a word, brother.
We need to put them each
in separate rooms.
Fercho. Let's go.
To the right.
This is messed up, man.
- If your dad's still inside...
- Just drive the fucking car.
We know that agents of the DEA
burst into the building this morning,
just before dawn...
Hey, what did Salcedo say?
Salcedo! What did he say?
Sir, the thing is...
no one's heard from him.
Motherfucker!
Do me a favour.
Go to his house and check
what the fuck he's doing
that's more important than this.
Please.
Bye.
There's a surreal atmosphere
outside the San Jardîn building.
While curiosity is growing
about the operation
and this has grabbed
the attention of the city,
it isn't clear who the target
of the operation is.
Good morning, ma'am.
We need to get into your apartment.
Help me.
- Lift.
- Hold on.
Okay. One, two...
Sir, listen to this.
635.
486.
480.
- That's it. Try to control the wrist.
- Okay, let's go.
The motherfucker's practising
his backhand.
That's it. Try to control it.
- Hey! You bastard!
- Hey, fellas. Where are you going?
- We're in the middle...
- Who are you talking to, motherfucker?
We're in the middle of a lesson here.
Who are you talking to?
Why the fuck is there a raid going on
at my dad's house,
while you're here having tennis lessons?
David, I don't know what you're
talking about. I don't understand.
You're going to go and help
my fucking dad. Now! Understood?
Let's go. Go on. Quickly.
What were you saying?
It's fine.
Pussy.
- Can you set me up?
- Got the perfect shot.
You guys can't tear down that wall.
You don't have authorisation.
What are you going to do to stop us?
Stop what you're doing.
As Head of the Attorney General's
office in Cali,
I have to insist you put down
that hammer right now.
You're currently in violation
of Article 22 of the...
As the legal authority in this room,
I demand that you cease and desist
your search of the premises immediately.
Yes, and I'll need your documentation
from the embassy. Your passports.
I'm filing an official complaint
against each of you.
It has now been confirmed
that the search
of the San Jardîn building
has been abandoned.
Agents from the DEA
along with the Colombian special forces,
have been seen leaving the building.
We can now confirm that
the target of this investigation
was in fact cartel godfather
Miguel Rodrîguez.
With the search now over
and no arrest made,
questions about the actions of the DEA
and the credibility of their sources
will surely arise.
It's been a frenetic morning here,
as a great number of police officers
exited the building.
Official word from the National Police
is the search has been abandoned.
Now the question is, what evidence
did the DEA have to run this operation?
The U.S. Embassy
hasn't released a statement yet.
It's all good. He's in front of me.
I'm about to tell him.
Hey, I just talked to Manny.
They've left the apartment.
Okay, good. But my dad isn't safe
until he's here with us. Call Fercho.
- Right.
- Just make sure. You hear me?
Sounds good.
They almost had you today, brother.
- They didn't, Gilberto.
- Thank God.
It's a miracle you got away.
You need to revise
your security network.
Bring this to an end, brother.
You have to embrace
that this is the reality we've built.
It's what's best for all.
Accept it, before it's too late.
You, Gilberto.
The reality you built.
And where the fuck has it got you?
You're upset, brother. I get it.
Yeah, I'm pretty fucking pissed off.
Then listen to me. Embrace it.
Look, everything we have,
everything we've ever built,
is because of the decisions I've made.
Our best strategy is non-violence.
The best option we have is surrender.
I'm not going to surrender, Gilberto.
That was just a dream
you fell in love with.
It isn't mine.
Miguel?
It takes balls, I'll give him that.
Balls I wasn't sure he had.
You can appreciate
needing to show them off.
You again with those trucks?
I have orders to follow.
And I have new orders.
I don't like it,
this disagreement between them.
Doesn't feel right.
It isn't us.
Maybe.
But times are changing.
Let's go!
Follow me!
Everything is going to be OK, brother.
- Don't you worry.
- I'm not worried.
Makes you wish you were out there.
Yes, I know she doesn't want to talk
to me, that's why she's not fucking home!
But it's important I talk to her.
Understood?
Look, I don't know what's going on
between you guys, but she's upset.
Pass her the fucking phone now!
No, Jorge. Give her some space.
She'll call you when she's ready.