- [overlapping gunfire in distance]
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
[Gustavo] There's no respect.
I couldn't even grab the cigarettes.
I'm gonna shoot every fucking hostage
in the head. That's right.
Who's doing this?
Carrillo and Search Bloc,
I'm sure of it.
- In the middle of our negotiations?
- Either Gaviria is trying to catch me...
[automatic gunfire in distance]
[Gustavo panting]
...or Carrillo doesn't give a shit
about the negotiations.
You know what we have to do, Pablo.
We have to close the deal fast...
before they find us and kill us.
Not before we build our own jail.
And that fucking pussy president
will have to agree to that,
even if I have to stick a bomb up his ass.
It's so fucking cold.
Is there a jacket there for me?
- Check it out, fag.
- What's up?
It's a miniskirt with your name on it.
- "Gustavo Gaviria."
- Give me that.
[dialing satellite phone]
All right, let's call the boys.
And what about you?
Are you all right?
If Gaviria'd let us put US boots
on the ground,
we would've caught the son of a bitch
in five minutes.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Escobar is a lot smarter than he looks.
- Oh, shit.
- [man on radio] Hold on, hold on!
We picked up a signal in the woods
surrounding the target area.
[Pablo in Spanish]
OK, boys, we're in the clear.
Pick us up at El Mariano pass.
- [man] We got new Escobar coordinates.
- Smarter than he looks, huh?
Yeah, don't count your chickens just yet.
[chuckles]
[man] We have a tracking signal
on the phone presumed to be Escobar's,
five clicks from the finca.
Request Colombian units to be sent ASAP.
[in Spanish] Search Bloc,
we are registering the latitude
and longitude at a fixed point.
The subject appears
to have stopped moving.
[in Spanish]
You've gotta be shitting me.
[snorts]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
- [Connie chuckles]
- [door opens]
- [babbling]
- I know.
[baby crying]
[Steve] He got away.
Again.
- Shh.
- You hear what I said?
[Connie whispers] Come on.
Yeah, I'm a little preoccupied, Steve.
- I think she's got colic.
- [sighs]
What is that?
Well, it means she can't sleep,
which means neither can I.
Did you call the orphanages?
You think I could explain the situation
in English, let alone Spanish?
I still don't understand
why you brought her back here.
Well, let's take her to a hospital.
No, Steve, we can't just take her to
a hospital. It's not like a puppy shelter.
Look, I know you're busy, but we've gotta
figure out what we're gonna do with her.
There's a war going on, Connie.
You said it was only
gonna be for a couple of days.
It's already been a week.
What are we doing here?
- Is that my t-shirt?
- We're out of diapers.
Why don't you go get some more before
she shits through your whole closet?
[door opens]
[in Spanish] How nice to see
that you have made friends.
Careful, son.
This woman is very clever.
She can grab your gun
and shoot you in the head.
My apologies, boss.
[sighs]
How do you feel?
As well as one might expect.
I need you to record another tape for me.
No.
No, not until you free more hostages.
Maruja is very ill.
Ricardo has an ulcer.
I'm the only one you need to negotiate.
Then why does the Colombian government
keep trying to capture me?
Look...
I admire your bravery very much.
But Gaviria is a piece of shit, and,
with all due respect, so is your father.
And what did you expect?
To get into Congress
like it was nothing?
Without it mattering that you,
in fact, traffic drugs?
I expected respect.
You had respect
when you built homes for the poor.
But when you didn't get that respect
from a herd of egocentric bureaucrats,
you threw a tantrum.
I was going to do marvelous things
for this country.
If I have made myself into a monster,
like all of you say,
that is the fault of people
like your father...
and those politicians "of always."
Those oligarchs and those people
were never going to tolerate
that little paisa from Medellín
who had more money
and was more intelligent than all of them.
Yes.
You would have done marvelous things.
And that is the saddest part.
Mr. Escobar has promised
to free two more hostages.
But in exchange, he has asked that you
continue negotiations with transparency.
President Gaviria...
he knows what you are doing.
He knows.
If you insist on trying to capture him
with the help of the Americans...
they're going to kill us all.
You are risking my daughter's life!
No, Nydia, with all due respect,
we are not risking anyone's life.
Our priority is the life of your daughter
and the lives of the rest of the hostages.
But our priority
is also to capture Escobar.
You cannot have both things at once.
Negotiate with Escobar
while trying to capture him?
Do you know what he is demanding?
That we call a constitutional referendum
to abolish extradition.
That he only plead guilty
to having trafficked drugs one time.
And worst of all,
he wants to build his own jail
and have his own guards
to watch over him.
This is a deal with the devil.
You are the president of a country
that became a living hell some time ago.
With whom else did you expect
to be making a deal?
[Steve] Gaviria could easier
cut a hundred deals with the devil
before he could cut one with Pablo.
Bowing to Pablo's demands
was political suicide.
So, he did what politicians do best:
he stalled.
He kept our planes in the air
and prayed to God that we got a hit.
[in Spanish] Hello. It's Gorilla.
[in English] Ground units,
begin trilateration for signal origin.
[Steve] And when we did, it was
not the hit that we were hoping for.
[in Spanish]
Forgive me, Gorilla, I don't feel well.
Miss Diana...
why are you so unpleasant with the boss?
You are loyal like a sheep,
aren't you?
That man is your kidnapper... and mine,
and that of the whole nation.
Here, you go first.
- [automatic gunfire]
- [indistinct shouts in Spanish]
[men shouting]
Hide in here, quickly!
[Steve] Who would've thought a failed raid
would result in Escobar's biggest victory?
Pablo didn't even have
to pull the trigger. We did it for him.
[Carrillo in English]
Guys, we have a problem.
[Steve] For the battle-fatigued
citizens of Colombia,
Diana's death was the final straw.
This wasn't just an oligarch dying.
Her presence on the nation's TV screens
and in their homes transcended class.
The people were devastated.
For President Gaviria,
there was little room left to move.
[speaks indistinctly in Spanish]
[Nydia] Mr. President!
You killed my daughter.
Let her pass.
Wait...
If you had accepted his terms,
my daughter would still be alive!
Give him whatever he wants.
Don't let others go through the suffering
we've had to endure.
Mr. President... we need to leave.
God be with you, Nydia.
[sighs]
There's something
I want to make very clear.
You are not to blame for Diana's death.
OK? That has to be clear.
Escobar has the resources
for this to go on forever.
Yes, and so do we.
We are the state.
We are going to fight, do whatever we have
to do, and we are going to finish him.
We have options.
For instance, why don't we allow
the American military to come in?
I know-- We don't like it.
I personally don't like it.
But if it's a specific, clear mission--
- No.
- Something covert.
No!
It's time to end all of this.
Give Escobar what he wants.
[Eduardo] Let's go.
[Javier in English] If your Congress
abolishes extradition, we lose our teeth.
- We're a paper fucking tiger!
- Everything we have done is lost.
[Eduardo] We have no choice.
The people, the public... it's tired
of all these bombs and bloodshed!
Right, and business goes as usual,
- he just runs it from that jail.
- Exactly!
All things considered,
it's a victory to put Escobar in jail.
For public relations?
It's capitulation.
You want Escobar.
Why?
Because you want to parade him
in your DEA jackets?
You think this is a game, right?
This is Colombia,
and our people want peace!
This is not a fucking game!
[in Spanish] Well...
at this time, our friend, Fernando,
is going to tell us a little something.
[clears throat]
The Colombian government is going
to allow Pablo to turn himself in,
accepting only one simple charge:
drug trafficking.
And...
they are going to let him build a jail
which the police
cannot be within three kilometers of.
At last...
we have liberated ourselves from tyranny!
- Long live Colombia, motherfuckers.
- ¡Viva!
- Fernando...
- Mm?
- ...thank you very much.
- No problem, Pablo.
And do you know when Congress
is going to vote to abolish extradition?
Mm! Yes, it's--
It's a matter of... of weeks.
And at that time, you will be able
to turn yourself over to the authorities.
It pleases me very much to finish my work
with you with such a great victory.
No, brother. Now is when I am
going to need your services the most.
- How-- How's that?
- Fernando...
now it's time for us to find legal means
to reduce my sentence even more.
Right?
[chuckles]
[sighs]
And what does this mean for us, huh?
It means, my love...
that now I have a jail.
And for you,
visiting days will be...
- every day.
- [laughs]
- I'm serious, Pablo.
- So am I.
[sighs]
The problem, Pablo, is that...
now that you have admitted
to trafficking in narcotics,
my image as a journalist
cannot be associated with yours.
[Pablo] Hm.
So then...
now you think I am going to damage your
credibility as a journalist... is that it?
You understand what I'm saying.
Oh, yeah, sure. Of course I do.
I think that... it's time for me
to set you free, so that...
you can find a boyfriend who's honest...
so that you can get a little house,
have little kids,
- little dogs...
- Don't joke around, Pablo.
No, I'm not joking.
[softly] I just want you to know...
that you, Valeria...
are a bandit, just like me.
So don't come to me with bullshit.
Looks like you got away with it,
eh, asshole?
Shit, I'd thought you'd gone crazy.
Geniuses...
are always branded as crazy.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
- The Ochoas...
- The Ochoas what?
You can bet
they're going to be pissed off.
Because of the treaty?
Or because you're fucking their sister?
That was a stupid mistake, Gustavo.
Let's hope they don't
charge you for it later.
[Steve] The race was on.
Pablo needed to build his jail
as fast as possible.
As for his enemies, they needed
to get to him before that happened.
As soon as he walked inside,
Pablo would be safe.
And everyone on the outside wouldn't.
[in English] We got an official cease
and desist order for any further operation
when Pablo officially surrenders.
- Search Bloc is gonna be disbanded.
- [Javier] We heard the terms.
- No cops within two miles of the prison.
- This is a fucking sham.
It's a death warrant for my men.
I won't be able to protect them.
I won't let that happen.
There are cops that hate Escobar
just as much as I do.
More.
They're not gonna stop
just because they're told to.
You talking about vigilantes?
Call it what you like... but I'm still
gonna need those intel reports.
- We'll get you anything we find.
- Javi, you gotta cool it with that shit.
They know we've been helping.
One more and we're out.
I thought you said you were all in.
[in Spanish]
The soccer field will be over here.
Here, I want to have
a little doll house for Manuela,
and downstairs,
a bar with a Jacuzzi for the guys.
My family will live in a house
down the hill.
I'm going to install a telescope
so I can look at them whenever I want.
Yeah, right. More like
you can look at other girls' asses.
No. The family, the family.
To see my kids.
- What can we do to help you, Pablo?
- Well...
while we're in prison,
Gustavo and me,
I will count on you, Moncada, and you,
Galeano, to oversee operations.
Thank you, Pablo.
We're privileged to be given
that responsibility. You can count on us.
We've already spoken about the operational
plan and everything's clear, right?
Yes. We won't let you down, Pablo.
Did you tell them about the tax?
- No, I didn't.
- The tax?
What tax is this?
Who paid for the war we fought?
You.
- You, Don Pablo.
- That's right.
We have peace now.
You're going to directly
benefit from that.
It's only fair that you contribute
to the legal and security costs
that Gustavo and I will face behind bars.
And about how much will that be?
We agreed to what,
$200,000 a month, right?
Yes, 200 grand.
200 grand?
That's a lot of money, brother.
A lot of money.
But consider it done.
And again... thank you
very much for this responsibility,
- and for considering us.
- All right, then.
- Don Pablo. All right. Gustavo.
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
Do you think that was a smart move, Pablo?
Why should I let them
reap the fruits of our labor
without compensating us for it, Gustavo?
I agree with you.
But right now, we really
need those two fags to be loyal.
And what?
You don't think I inspire loyalty?
My loyalty?
Yes, you know you have it.
But I'm not sure about everyone else's.
You know, the thing is, Pablo...
you won.
There's no arguing that.
But you gave in.
And there are people
who will see that as weakness.
We've gotta keep our enemies close,
now more than ever.
- [waiter murmurs in Spanish]
- [Valeria] Thank you.
It's great to see you again, Valeria.
Likewise, Pacho.
I'm very happy to see you.
Although, I must say...
it was a little unexpected.
We are worried about you.
And... why are "we" worried?
Pablo's cutting a deal
with the government.
He's going to have
to admit to certain things.
Things that may damage
your reputation by association.
If I'm good at anything,
it's protecting my reputation.
Listen, this time it's different.
Look... you helped create
that "Robin Hood Paisa" bullshit.
And when it all goes to shit, you'll have
to take responsibility for that.
Maybe he tricked me, too.
Like the rest of the world.
You have enemies, see?
They're not gonna
let you get away with it.
Look, Valeria...
we have a lot of connections in New York,
a strong presence, you could say.
You should go there,
at least for a little while.
And leave Colombia.
There are a million Colombians there.
A new audience.
And they don't care if you shared your bed
with a monster or not.
- [sighs]
- Just for a while.
When this is all over, you'll be able to
come back here with your head held high,
I guarantee it.
And not only that, you'll have earned
a brand-new audience in the United States.
- Betrayal is not my style.
- What betrayal?
And what would you be betraying?
Your role as his mistress?
You remain loyal to a man who has never
thought you good enough to be his wife.
His wife? Me?
No, no, no,
you're very much mistaken, my dear.
The last thing I want
is to be married to him.
Besides...
do you think I'd want to be his wife?
Do you think I want to be locked up,
waiting all day at the Monaco building,
while he's out with...
with me?
No.
That's too boring.
- [Tata moans]
- [Pablo grunting]
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
- [Pablo grunts]
- [moaning]
No, it was terrible.
It was terrible.
Every day in a different house...
worried about you...
the kids...
[sighs]
The truth is...
it's very good to be home.
- You look happy.
- Of course.
[soft chuckle]
That time has passed.
It's the happiest face I've ever seen
on a man about to go to jail.
[explosion]
- [shouting outside]
- [alarm blaring]
The kids!
[screams] The kids, Pablo!
- The kids!
- No, Tata!
- I have to go to them!
- Stay here!
- [sobbing] My children!
I'll go get them. Stay here.
- [Tata sobs]
- [alarm continues]
- Juan Pablo!
- [Manuela crying]
Juan Pablo!
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
Come on.
Go to your mother.
- [sobbing]
- Come on, come on.
[sirens wailing outside]
[crashing]
[Steve] The explosion was
from a car bomb on the street below,
about 800 pounds' worth of dynamite.
It made little Manuela
forever deaf in one ear.
- [whispers in Spanish]
- [Steve] In this war,
the innocent always seemed
to be the ones who got hurt.
For Escobar, the Monaco bombing
told him two things:
First, it showed him that the cops
weren't his biggest problem.
They would never use a bomb.
This was a new player, one that
wasn't above going after his family.
[in Spanish] Don't worry, cousin.
We're going to kill them all.
[Steve] Second, and the one
that fucked with his head the most...
was that for the first time in his life...
someone had given him up.
And worse yet,
he had no idea who.
[phone ringing]
[in Spanish] Hello?
[man] Valeria, there was an attempted hit
at the Monaco building.
- Just now?
- Yes, a few minutes ago. A car bomb.
- Who was inside?
- We don't know.
[stammers]
What other information do you have?
That's all the information
we have right now.
OK, thanks.
[Fabio]
He always takes her to the same motel.
[approaching footsteps]
- Marina.
- Where are you going?
I'm going to the city.
I have to get out of this prison.
- Come here, Marina.
- Yes?
Have a good time.
Be safe.
Thanks.
[indistinct chatter in Spanish]
You know what he's going to do, right?
He's going to continue conducting
his business behind those walls
that are protected
by the Colombian government.
We should give him credit.
The man is a genius.
Well... all the more reason
that we should negotiate our surrender.
But you know that Pablo
took it upon himself to close that door.
So we need to take advantage
of your political contacts,
especially General Jaramillo.
Can you talk to him for us?
Yes, of course.
But I don't think it will be enough.
[Jorge]
What are you saying?
That you're going
to have to offer something more,
something that interests them enough
to make a deal with you.
Gustavo Gaviria.
He is the key to Pablo's business.
If that son of a bitch goes down,
the whole empire goes down.
Indeed, that could work.
That could work.
[Steve] It is often said
there is no honor among thieves.
That's doubly true of drug dealers.
The Ochoas, with the help of Cali,
made their own surrender deal.
No extradition, no stiff sentence.
The Colombian government
was willing to overlook their part
in the largest cocaine empire
on the face of the earth.
Instead, they would
serve reduced sentences.
- The charge?
- [in Spanish] Follow me.
Illegally importing bulls from Spain.
I shit you not.
They went to jail
with smiles on their faces,
'cause all they had to do
was use their sister as bait
to catch a fish the cops actually wanted.
[Marina in Spanish] Kiss me.
- You look pretty, baby.
- Yeah, sure.
What I mean is
you've always looked pretty.
Gustavo.
[Marina] What's happening?
[Gustavo] Nothing.
Nothing is happening here.
Isn't that right, Colonel Carrillo?
That's up to you.
- Say goodbye.
- [Marina] No.
No, no, no.
Gustavo, look at me. Gustav--
Does your family know where you are?
- Gustavo!
- Calm down, Marina.
[Gustavo]
You're making a big mistake, Carrillo.
We're already in negotiations
with the government.
- You have no reason to be doing this.
- You're right.
That's why I'm not here.
Then what the fuck do you want?
Don't act stupid.
Give me your cousin...
and I'll let you live.
[sighs]
All right.
Kill me, then, motherfucker.
I won't do that myself.
But I want to introduce you to some people
who would love to do it for me.
This guy? This is Lastia.
His sister died in a bookstore in Bogotá
in a bombing you coordinated.
She was 17 years old.
And this guy here...
this is Trujillo.
You killed his father
and his brother for being cops.
- That has nothing to do with me.
- No?
You know...
if you support evil, you are evil.
Look at them.
I just want you to look at their faces.
A few of the victims
you've left in your wake.
Tell me...
have you ever felt
the swift vengeance of justice?
Give me your cousin...
or I'll let these men
show you that vengeance with their fists.
Do it, then...
you sons of bitches.
OK, then.
We'll see how you feel...
after ten minutes.
Do it.
[grunts]
- [heavy punches landing]
- [Gustavo grunts, groans]
[shaky exhale]
[wheezing]
Tell me where your cousin is.
It doesn't have to end like this.
[sputters]
[coughing]
Tell me where your cousin is.
[panting]
We...
are bandits...
not snitches, motherfucker.
[Gustavo laughs]
[shouts] You're--
You're all gonna die, motherfuckers!
You're all dead, motherfuckers!
You, your families,
your wives are all dead, motherfuckers!
You're all dead!
Dump his body on the road to Sabaneta.
Colonel, they're going
to make us pay for this.
Report his death as a result
of a shoot-out with the police.
Make sure you report that he fired first.
But Colonel, he's all beat up.
That work for you?
There is nothing... more beautiful
and more important in my life than this.
We're all here together... united.
Now let's eat and enjoy
this marvelous food.
- Wait, wait.
- Oh, yeah, the beets.
- Tata?
- Boss?
Hello, son. Have a seat.
- Sit down--
- Boss, I don't know how to say this.
Tell me like a man.
- Gustavo is dead.
- What?
They found his body on the outskirts
of Sabaneta, badly beaten.
[Hermilda] How's that?
They also shot him, boss.
No, no!
How dare you come to my house saying that!
How dare you!
Leave! Get out of my house!
You... you are leaving right now!
Get out of my house! Go on!
No! Gustavo, no. Pablo...
Go on! Get out of here!
[whispers] It's OK.
Everything's going to be fine.
[sobbing]
Are you sure about this?
[softly] Yes, boss.
I want you to take him
to the funeral home...
and guard his body the entire time
until it's buried.
- All right.
- Go on.
[door opens]
How are you doing, son?
I'm going to miss him so much, Mama.
When...
you were nine... or ten...
do you remember?
How you would
ride around on your bicycles.
[chuckles]
You'd go up into the mountains
and just disappear.
The whole day would go by...
Oh, my.
And we would call you...
We seemed crazy,
yelling for you all over the place...
until finally you would appear.
Oh, my God.
"Where were you?"
"Where have you been, son?"
I would yell out.
"In the mountains, Mama."
"Higher than the clouds, Auntie,"
Gustavo would say, laughing.
He...
He always wanted to go farther.
He always did.
- But with you.
- [sighs]
Only with you.
I didn't think it would end this way.
[breath trembling]
Good afternoon.
[low murmurs]
Boss? Someone came
all the way out here to see you.
Miss Valeria.
Good day, ma'am. Pablo.
What's she doing here?
I'm here only because
I have important information.
I hope it's very important.
It's about Gustavo.
Tell us, then.
I've been told the Ochoa brothers
have been seen in Cali.
They are the ones
who turned Gustavo over,
in exchange for the cartel helping them
seal a deal with the government.
How do you know that?
You know me, Pablo.
I have my ways.
Who in Cali?
Pacho Herrera.
[Steve]
Pablo wanted to send a message to Cali,
so he ordered his sicarios
to hit them during a soccer match.
- It was very effective.
- [overlapping gunfire]
He did get 14 Cali men that day.
The problem was, everyone on
the soccer field was dressed the same.
[men grunting]
- [gun clicking]
- By the time the sicarios spotted Pacho,
he was already running away.
[somber Latin song playing]
[priest in Spanish]
"Will you hide yourself forever, Lord?
Will your wrath burn like fire?
Remember how fleeting is my life,
for what futility
you have created the children of men."
[Steve] Pablo had Gustavo
buried in the hills of Medellín,
- where the cousins had played as kids.
- [sniffling]
In his mind,
losing his best friend
was a price he had to pay
to defeat extradition.
So he ordered the burial
to take place at the exact same time
- that Congress was voting to repeal it.
- [inaudible dialogue]
Whether it was Gaviria's support,
Pablo's "plata or plomo,"
or maybe people
were just sick of the violence...
extradition was defeated by a landslide.
Hours after the vote,
a military helicopter
was dispatched to coordinates
just outside Medellín,
where Pablo was waiting.
[Eduardo in Spanish] As you know,
I come on behalf of President Gaviria
and the Colombian government.
This is the offer of our terms
for your surrender.
[Steve] Peña and I
had to go see it with our own eyes.
A terrorist, a drug dealer and a murderer
surrendering to a grateful nation
who gave him everything he asked for.
It was the closest we'd ever come to him,
and we never felt further away.
[Pablo in Spanish] All right, then.
Let me hand over my gun.
- You won.
- We both did.
Now Gaviria can announce
that Pablo Escobar has turned himself in.
Except that's not so true.
You and I know it's a big lie.
Mm.
Lies are necessary... when the truth
is too difficult to believe. Right?
[Steve]
It wasn't a fucking surrender.
Pablo wasn't succumbing to justice.
He was escaping it.
And all anyone could do was watch.
Once again, Escobar had used violence
to bend the world to his will.
They called it "la gran mentira,"
"the big lie."
And it was a lie.
Except as I watched him
fly away to his luxury prison...
I couldn't help but think
there was some truth in it.
[Steve mutters] Damn it. Fucker.
A truth that I hadn't
been willing to accept.
He'd beat us because
he was willing to do what we weren't.
Bad guys don't play by the rules.
That's what makes 'em bad.
Maybe that's what lets 'em win.
[Poison in Spanish] Lagarto,
are we gonna party tonight or what?
[in English] I got Poison at 400
to 1700 megahertz, gentlemen.
La Dispensaria.
So who do we give this to? DEA?
- Yeah. Let's give it to Javier Peña.
- Peña's an asshole.
- I'm gonna give it to the other guy.
- Sure.
[Steve] I made a promise to myself
that when the time came
that I could strike a blow
against Escobar,
even if it meant breaking the rules,
oh, I was gonna do it.
- Hello?
- [man] Hey, Central Spike here.
[Carrillo in Spanish] All right.
[up-tempo Latin music playing]
[Steve] You wanna tell me a good guy
wouldn't have pushed the buttons
on these motherfuckers?
You wanna call me a bad guy?
- [overlapping gunfire]
- [screaming]
Fine. But if you do, it just means
that you haven't met enough bad guys yet
to know the difference.
There's one thing I've learned
down here in Colombia,
- good and bad are relative concepts.
- [up-tempo Latin song plays]
? Yesterday, I fought the devil
Who they say is very brave ?
? I hacked him with my machete so bad
That even I got freaked out ?
? I jumped back, dodging his attack ?
? And in one fell swoop
I cut off his tail ?
[song continues]