A PAISA ROBIN HOOD
My name is everywhere.
Newspapers …
magazines …
Everyone is talking about
the “Paisa Robin Hood.”
Pablito, I’m sorry. If I had known that--
You’re going to have
to pay for that, my love.
Anything you want, Pablito.
Anything I want?
Yes, my love, whatever you want.
You sure?
Then …
you’re going to help me
get into Congress.
Yes, Pablo.
Yes.
Those shitty oligarchs …
those people, all of their lives …
don’t know what it’s like to wonder
where their next meal is coming from.
I come from nothing, Valeria …
and I have more money
than any of those sons of bitches.
If you run for Congress, you put yourself
in the public eye, you become a target.
“I made my money from taxis” isn’t going
to work when you face the press.
Pablo, you need a party that supports you.
You need a proper political campaign.
I buy the press, my love.
And as far as a political party,
I am quite sure
that I can buy one of those as well.
I don’t want to be good.
I am going to be great.
A PAISA ROBIN HOOD
WELCOME TO THE PABLO ESCOBAR
NEIGHBOURHOOD
A PEACEFUL ENVIRONMENT
I should have gotten
into the taxi business. Holy cow …
—Valeria, how are you doing?
—Well, thank you.
Mr Duque …
It gives me great pleasure to invite you
to the Hacienda Nápoles.
—Nice to meet you.
—Please, come.
After you, Valeria.
Please.
Look, I am not a rich person.
I am a poor person with money.
And for that reason, I think that …
Well, I think that I understand the people
to whom the New Liberalism
wants to give a voice.
The party clearly needs to hear
what you have to say, Mr Escobar.
There is a great deal of talk
about how you have made your money.
I need guarantees
concerning the origins of your fortune.
And Valeria told you …
how much I am going to donate?
—No, no--
—Look, I am not a politician.
I am not a successful lawyer like you.
I come from the street … brother.
I want to reassure you
that you will receive your piece.
—It’s not about that--
—Assuming your piece is ten percent,
your piece would be what?
Three hundred thousand dollars
just for you.
Does that seem like a sufficient guarantee
for the Justice Minister or what?
—Most definitely.
—All right, then.
Let’s go look at the hippos. Come on.
Blackie.
Pablo?
—And what about me?
—What about you?
I don’t get my piece?
No, my queen. The thing is that you …
you’re in this for love, right?
Look, Minister …
Escobar has founded schools, clinics.
He has created sources of employment
throughout Medellín.
The people love him,
and he loves the people.
And from a legal point of view,
his money is clean.
And according to Forbes Magazine,
he’s a drug trafficker.
Are you going to believe all of that
American imperialist propaganda?
Take a look.
These are property holdings papers.
Look.
He’s the owner of hundreds of properties
in Colombia and also the United States.
In addition,
this man has no criminal record.
If there was,
there would be proof of his background.
How much is he paying you?
I am thinking about our party, Minister.
Escobar is prepared to contribute
millions of dollars.
We already support Jairo Ortega
so that he can campaign in Antioquia.
Let’s let Escobar be his alternate.
What do you prefer …
rumours and insinuations,
or fewer representatives in Congress?
Who is the gringa?
A child of God, just like you.
Got it.
Let’s see, you are here for a cat?
This isn’t just any cat.
This is a gringo cat of the DEA.
And what you want
is for me to find a cat killer.
It was the narcos, Suárez.
We don’t take this shit lightly.
Your friend is a little crazy.
I don’t speak English.
Get me some information, Suárez.
Look, I don’t have enough people
to go through hundreds of hours
of chatter over a fucking cat.
If this was information
about the narcos, yes.
My people are interested.
But they won’t give a fuck about the cat.
But if you want to put
all my people to work
to find out who killed the fucking cat,
that is going to cost you more.
They broke into the house to kill his cat.
I think they made him
when he arrived at the airport in Bogotá.
Find out.
This gentleman is an employee of
the American Embassy in our country,
and he assures me that you gave out his
personal information to certain criminals.
That’s not true.
These guys killed his cat.
Maybe you don’t know this,
but the mistreatment of animals
is a federal crime.
Is this funny to you?
They can bring formal charges against you,
and you could lose your job.
Do you not need your job, Santiago?
Yes, I need it.
Mr Murphy, do you recognize these men?
—What?
—May I?
You both are being
accused of conspiring
against a federal agent
of the United States.
The cat is under the jurisdiction
of the American government.
And to kill it is the same
as to kill a police dog.
This is absurd.
Look, I’m a Colombian citizen,
and I know exactly my--
You will not disrespect them!
Is that clear?
If I open my mouth, they kill me,
and they kill my wife.
He’s having problems with his wife.
Shut up!
—Imbecile.
—OK, gentlemen.
This is quite simple.
I can get the phone number of the person
to whom you sent those documents,
and I can tell him that you accused him
of being the cat killer.
How does that sound?
I sent a copy of that passport
to a man they call …
“Poison.”
OK, Poison.
You’re going to take this money
to Fernando Duque in Bogotá.
And this is the address.
If they stop you on the road,
just salute the official,
give them a little bribe
and continue forward.
No violence.
And you call me every two hours.
—Of course, boss. Whatever you say.
—OK, then. No showing off.
No showing off!
—Nice and simple. Go unnoticed.
—Got it.
What the fuck are you doing?
Getting ready, right?
You are meeting up with politicians,
not with gangsters.
Aren’t they the same thing, boss?
Politicians scare easily.
You’re fine with just a pistol.
Go to it, then. Go to it, dumbass.
Hey, hey, hey, hold on. Sixty-five?
Sixty-five.
Hey, brother, that’s a lot.
You sure?
I counted every single son of a bitch.
All right!
Sure, but are you counting
what happened last night?
Of course, that was number sixty-five.
Don’t bullshit.
I was the one who shot that faggot.
—Bullshit.
—Bullshit …
if I was the one
who killed that little man.
You only shot him
once he was already on the ground, dead.
I shot him first.
Come in.
Did you give information about Poison
to the DEA?
So?
I’m still listening
to their phone conversations
and it’s not a shipment of drugs.
They’re carrying three million dollars
to Bogotá,
and if two guys from the DEA
stop that car,
Pablo is going to hang you by the balls.
—You don’t have 65, Poi.
—Yes, I do.
What are you doing, Gonorrhœa‽
Look, 65, man!
Now we’re going
to have to wash the car, man!
Son of a bitch.
Yes?
Hi, Pablo.
I have good news for you.
I’m going to help you
avoid an enormous loss.
And how much is it going to cost me?
Ten percent.
Three hundred thousand dollars.
How did you find out?
One of your men.
That Poison … he talks too much.
You should take his phone away.
Five percent.
Suspicious vehicle approaching.
Hello?
Poison?
You bring your fucking mouth
back here immediately!
—Yes. I’m sorry, boss.
—Now!
The son of a bitch policeman
tapped my phone!
—These fags.
—You have a very big mouth, Poison.
Pablo is really pissed off.
Shut that mug, or you will never reach 66,
you hear?
He has been called the “Paisa Robin Hood,”
but he is much more than that.
He is a man to whom the people
mean a great deal.
All of us.
I am tired … of the people with power
running this country.
This is a fight between the people
with power and poor people, weak people.
And this fight must begin here.
To have power does not mean
that one can abuse the poor.
If I am elected …
if my friend, Jairo, is elected …
those who have never had a voice
will have a voice.
Those who are hungry will have food.
Those who want to learn will have schools.
And those who have dreams
will see that there are no limits
to what you can achieve.
In me, you have a friend
whom you have always had,
the friend of today, the friend
of yesterday and the friend of tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
My friend, Jairo Ortega!
—You were marvellous, my love.
—Sure?
Yes.
Very good, Pablo.
There are a few things we can improve,
but we’ll work on them.
OK, whatever you say.
—Congratulations.
—Thank you so much, Valeria.
Congratulations, ma’am.
Excuse me.
To vote for Jairo Ortega
is to vote for the one and only Pablo!
What’s wrong?
Why does that woman need to know
everything about each step you take?
What are you talking about?
—Valeria Velez.
—My love …
She’s a newspaper woman,
a reporter, who follows the news.
And right now, I’m the news.
When you win, don’t disrespect me
anymore with that bitch.
Come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
Slowly. Come on.
Let’s go …
You are going to be the First Lady
of this country one of these days.
Therefore, you are going
to have to learn to deal with the press.
That woman is not on your level, Pablo.
She degrades you.
Please, don’t worry about Valeria.
Pablo!
A car, please!
A car to the hospital, now!
You know what, Pablo?
To me, it looks like
you are handling things very badly.
You need to start thinking more
about your family … and about business.
Thing is, you can’t be a politician.
Says who?
You can’t go strutting around
giving things to people
simply so they will love you.
We … are bandits.
If you run for Congress, find someone else
to manage the laboratories.
Señor Escobar?
Come meet your daughter.
God has blessed us with a girl, Pablo.
How beautiful.
Pablo is out of control.
Mother Mary, man.
What do you want us to do?
You can’t give Pablo Escobar a spanking
as though he were some spoiled brat.
Oh, no?
And why not?
Careful with the threat
you cannot execute.
You know what he’s doing, right?
According to Colombian law,
a congressman has total immunity.
Do you think he’s protecting himself
while we remain in the drift?
I do. He thinks he’s that fucking
“Paisa Robin Hood.”
So what do we do?
Well …
we fulfil our duties,
stuffing the ballot box,
and later we let Pablo receive
the applause, and take the risk.
We continue with our business …
in the shadows, like always.
Carlos, what are the guys saying?
I imagine that they’re worried, right?
They are not politically conscious,
brother.
How can you expect them
to understand your objectives?
You do understand me, brother.
Imagine … a state governed by us.
Immunity for everyone, brother.
We, Carlos, belong to the people.
I need you to use your influence with the
others to convince them that I am right.
If you win,
you don’t need to explain anything.
And if you lose …
there’s nothing to explain.
I like that.
—Hitler said it.
—Fuck off.
Yes.
He also said that no politician
should ever let his picture
be taken in a bathing suit.
Well, that’s what he said.
And if I tell you, Carlos …
that what I want, sincerely …
is to help the poor people
of this country …
do you believe me or what?
As soon as the results come out,
Jairo Ortega will resign.
I say he’s running toward his death.
—Sixty-six.
—Bullshit. I shot him first.
Ladies and gentlemen, with clear use
of my mental and physical faculties …
I wish to communicate to you my decision
to resign from my seat
in the Congress of the Republic …
for reasons of family and health.
But I am completely certain that
my friend Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria
is going to continue
our social and political ideas,
because Pablo is the voice of the people.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Jairo.
I will give my best effort.
Thank you very much.
Oh, unfading glory!
Oh, immortal jubilee!
Congressman Escobar …
Sir!
Excuse me.
Allow me to remind you
of the norms of etiquette.
You cannot enter the hall
if you don’t have a tie.
All right.
—What is your name?
—Juan.
Look, Juan …
that is a really nice tie.
—My girlfriend gave it to me.
—Really?
Yes.
Well, she’s in the history books now.
—Thank you very much, my son.
—Thank you, sir.
—Thank you.
—All right.
Good morning.
I inform you we have a quorum
to begin our session.
The Minister of Justice, Rodrigo
Lara Bonilla, is present here today
to address this honourable Congress.
I give the floor to you, Mr Minister.
Thank you very much.
Much has been made
of the issue of drug money,
“hot money,”
in our national political process.
I myself have been accused
of receiving campaign contributions
from the narcotics traffickers
who have bought influence in these halls.
To this charge, I plead guilty.
In my eyes, the sin of turning a blind eye
is as great as the sin
of outright corruption.
We are a nation of the blind,
and in our blindness,
we have sold our country
to the highest bidder.
It’s time for us to open our eyes
and to see the light.
Congressman Escobar …
you stated that your great fortune
was built from a taxi company.
This photograph clearly
contradicts your claim.
For this reason,
I demand your resignation.
You are not welcome in this chamber.
You don’t belong here.
Thank you very much, Juan.
Very kind.
What interests the narcos isn’t
just the fall of the Minister of Justice,
but also to impede the strategy
of the government to combat his interests.
His two arms: silver or lead.
I want to inform the people that
the Minister of Justice has 24 hours
within which to present concrete proof
regarding the insinuations he made
the day before yesterday
in the Hall of Representatives.
To the contrary, I will proceed
to denounce him legally
before the authorities
and before the Colombian justice system.
I am not looking for, nor do I long for a
confrontation before the Colombian people.
I look for peace,
I have always preached peace,
and have longed for peace and
the prosperity of the Colombian people.
It’s important to realize
that when members of Congress
can be threatened or bought at will,
we see with clarity the real dimension
of the drug problem here in Colombia.
What are required are honest men,
men who are able to put themselves
up against drug traffickers,
who with complete tranquility buy or kill
any person or government institution
who is against their interests.
Oh, Pablito. We knew
they wouldn’t accept you in that circle.
Damned bastards.
You’re too good for them, Pablito.
This is a fight
that you cannot win, cousin.
You need to think more
about your family and the business …
and abandon that ridiculousness
once and for all.
I will fix it.
Due to the vicious lies
and slander cast my way
by Minister Lara and his cronies,
I’ve decided to announce my resignation
from Congress of the Republic.
I ran as a representative
for the common man,
a voice for those who had no voice,
but that has happened
through much of our history.
The powerful have conspired to silence me.
I dreamt of doing good.
Those dreams are over.
But make no mistake …
I will not go quietly.
I will fight.
“The Men of Always” are mistaken
if they think they can defeat
Pablo Emilio Escobar Gaviria!
Thank you very much.
I brought this for your friend’s wife.
—I hope she likes it.
—No, gracias.
You’re fucking crazy, asshole.