(Peña) 'The Cali cartel is
an almost-perfect organism.
'Even though we had cut off its head,
the body kept right on going,
'making and selling cocaine.
'They stuck to the plan.
'And for a long time,
that plan had worked for them.'
(In Spanish) The guy's innocent.
He didn't do any of it.
Easy, honey, easy, okay?
Be careful.
- The glove.
- Screw the fucking glove, brother!
- That Fuhrman's a son of a bitch.
- He's an asshole.
- And he's been fucking the sister.
- Which one?
The sister! I don't even know her name.
Geraldo is fucking her, too.
(Peña) 'But no plan is perfect.
'Especially when you deal
with a substance as volatile as cocaine.
'At some point,
you're gonna make a mistake.
'And your enemies
are watching and waiting.
'They're gonna see your weakness
and make a move.
'See, that's the thing about plans.
'No matter how perfect
you think they are,
'however brilliant or audacious
they may be,
'well, they can still go to shit
when that one thing goes wrong.
'And once that happens,
there's no going back.
'It's all downhill from there.'
(♪ Rodrigo Amarante's "Tuyo" playing)
(Sighs)
Oh, hey, hey.
(Feistl) Think that's him?
(Van Ness) Has to be.
Let's go.
Close enough.
Lift up your shirt. Turn around.
- (In English) I'm unarmed.
- Approach slowly, hands out.
- You told nobody about this?
- (Van Ness) Nobody.
- And you weren't followed?
- We're clean.
You headed north to Yumbo
instead of east from Cali.
And then straight on to Rozo.
I had to make sure you are
who you say you are. That you're alone.
Get in the car.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're in the front seat.
I'm Chris Feistl. This is Daniel...
- Daniel Van Ness. I know your names.
- What about yours?
I don't want to be sitting here
more than two minutes.
This is the only time we're gonna
speak to each other face-to-face.
So you said you work
for the Rodríguez brothers.
I'm the chief of security
for the Cali cartel.
- You're the head of security?
- Yes.
I have valuable information for you.
In exchange, I want safe passage
for my family and myself to the States.
Once there, with full immunity,
I'll help you in any way I can.
Listen, here's the thing, man.
You're head of security for the cartel.
You have a lot more to offer us
than just testimony.
Like Miguel Rodríguez.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Besides the fact that
we're all gonna end up dead?
There's a security system
that I designed.
Safe houses, lookouts on every corner,
a radio communication system.
- We can work around all that.
- Maybe.
Then there's David, Miguel's son.
He personally controls
his father's security now.
- I don't even know where he is.
- But you can find out.
And if I do?
The police? The military?
You can't trust them. I pay them.
We can get guys we trust, all right?
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it? (Chuckles)
No. I'll testify. That's it.
Let me ask you something.
Why are you doing this? Talking to us?
I'm not a murderer. I'm not like them.
I want to get my family out.
Well, we'd love to help you
with that, but...
...we can't do that
unless you give us Miguel.
And honestly,
we don't need your testimony.
Bottom line, you have a better option,
you're free to take it.
I need to think about this.
Still didn't catch your name.
Jorge. Salcedo.
I think we found a gold mine.
Guy says he's head of security
for the cartel and he wants to roll?
They don't call it the Cali KGB
for nothing, Chris.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Franklin Jurado...
One testimony from him and he can
take down the entire Cali cartel.
He travels on multiple passports.
So, he gets on a flight, we lose him
who-the-fuck-knows-where.
I need him on a plane today
so that he's testifying in Miami tomorrow.
(In Papiamento) Okay, guys, listen up.
(In English) We will provide Agent Peña
and his men with any support they require.
(In Papiamento) Understood?
(In English) Okay, typically,
he goes to a cooperative credit bank
and then has breakfast.
- We sit on it and get him there.
- Hey, hey...
- You plan to take him at the bank?
- Mm-hmm.
You cannot do that, Agent Peña.
(Peña) 'So here's what you need
to know about Curaçao.
'It's a smuggler's paradise.
'And for the Cali cartel,
you can't beat the location.
'Only 40 miles separates
South American coast from Curaçaon ports,
'prized for centuries by smugglers,
slave traders, and now cartels.
'Cruise ships filled with old people
next to speed boats filled with cash.
'And what doesn't get smuggled through,
it ends up in banks. Hundreds of them.
'Way back,
some enterprising Dutchmen
'set up a financial system
cloaked in old-world secrecy.
'Their economy is so dependent
on money launderers parking their cash,
'that you can make an arrest,
just not at or near a bank.
'Of course, where do you think
Franklin spent most of his time?'
All right, we tail him. Then we catch him
somewhere that suits us both.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go.
(Salcedo) Good morning, gentlemen.
(All) Good morning.
As many of you know, since Córdova's
resignation, I am the head of security.
It's festival time.
That means the city will be crowded.
The festival is not an excuse
to party on the job.
One more thing. David and his team will
now be handling security for his father.
Let's make them feel welcome.
And help them any way you can.
That's all, boys. Get going!
Wow. Look at you. You're sliding
into your new job like a glove.
You're a natural.
Look, David, if we're going
to work together, we need to cooperate.
If you have questions or you want
to talk about your father's security,
I'm here.
Thank you.
I do have a question, Jorge.
How come none of your men
carry fucking guns? Huh?
Because we use our radios
if we have a problem.
For what? To say goodbye
when you're getting clipped?
Do me a favour, Jorge.
You do your thing, I'll do mine.
All right?
Boss, you didn't mention
the DEA agents that are in Cali.
That's something David
might be interested in.
Last thing we need right now is David
and his crew killing a federal agent.
Well, that's true.
For now,
we'll monitor the DEA ourselves.
Besides... I doubt they have much.
(Amparo crying)
I don't want to leave New York, Chepe.
- (Sobs) Why, Chepe?
- My love...
I know you don't want
to leave New York. I know.
I don't either.
But if they connect this lab to us,
we're going to have
every cop in the city after us.
Hey, look. Here it comes.
'Spokesmen for the DEA say that
the cocaine lab that exploded in Queens
'was operated by a Dominican gang.'
Exactly! Thank you, lady.
Fucking Dominicans!
'But Manuel de Dios, editor of "La Prensa"
has discovered another side to the story.'
'This lab, along with a number
of others in the area,
'was recently seized
by Colombian gangsters,
'led by a man going by the name
of Victor Crespo.'
- Motherfucker.
- 'In the next few days...
'we'll be publishing
an investigative series
'about this criminal enterprise,
including pictures.
'This operation is much larger
than it seems...'
"No speak Spanish", my ass.
- So that means we have to leave, right?
- No, my love.
This man,
he knows who you are, Chepe.
Don't worry.
We're not going anywhere.
Is that so?
So do me a favour and fix this.
You hear me?
Motherfucker.
(Miguel) So a new surrender deal.
(Nicolás) Three years in jail. All of you.
Turn in the illicit businesses,
and we can keep all of the legal assets,
as in the old plan.
It's a good deal.
He would've told you himself,
but he thought it was best for me
to explain in person.
Besides, I helped negotiate the deal.
I understand.
Thank you for coming, Nicolás.
Give me an update, Uncle Miguel.
An update?
On our efforts to maximise business
before surrender.
- So I can inform my father.
- Tell him everything's still on track here.
Pacho's settled new terms with Amado
Carrillo Fuentes and is coming back soon.
And this accident in New York?
Chepe encountered an obstacle,
but you know Chepe.
I'm not worried.
Are we done?
One last thing.
Our friends in Bogotáare concerned
about their exposure.
Too many people know
about the deal.
They worry about Mr. Pallomari.
My father would like you to handle it.
"Handle it"? Do you know
what you're talking about?
Do you have any idea? Hmm?
Pallomari's our chief accountant in Cali
and is not easily replaced.
He's too valuable to just kill.
Tell your father I'll take care of it.
He doesn't have to worry about Pallomari.
Thank you, Uncle Miguel.
Take care.
So now the little prince
is giving you orders?
His father's orders.
Have Salcedo put Pallomari
in one of the safe houses.
Keep an eye on him.
You decided if you're coming tonight?
Our Salsa Festival party, Dad.
It's important.
You know how I feel about parties.
That's Gilberto's thing, not mine.
Which is exactly why you should go.
Dad, you're the new boss here.
Please, show them.
Or at least have a good time
before we have to roll over and play dead.
(Peña) 'Now why would
a Cali godfather come out of hiding
'and risk getting captured?
'Because what good is being the king
if nobody knows it?
'The biggest thing to come out of Cali
wasn't cocaine.
'It was salsa.
'And every year, the two combined
at the annual Feria de Cali,
'a week-long extravaganza
of parties and salsa concerts.
'And the man who always presided
over the opening-night festivities?
'Gilberto Rodríguez.'
(In Spanish) Cheers, gentlemen!
(Peña) 'But with him in jail,
it was time for a new king.'
(In Spanish) How would you
like to be my date tonight?
Hmm...
Where would we go?
Come here.
Let's go dancing.
Do you like dancing?
As you discussed with Don Miguel,
he'd like you to keep working from here.
Yes, I know what needs to be done.
Come in.
Guillermo, what's this?
You've got to be kidding, right?
- You're playing me for a fool.
- What's this?
This is unacceptable.
I need to speak to Miguel.
Talk to whoever you want. This is
the biggest apartment we have right now.
- Three bedrooms. Two bathrooms.
- Uh-huh.
A/C. Kids seem to like it.
- Kids, do you like it?
- Yes!
Really, Patricia.
Are you going to smoke inside?
What's the problem? This is a dump.
- The boys are here.
- Now you're concerned about the boys?
Do not leave this apartment,
for your own safety.
Everything you've done for these people,
and this is how they repay you?
Yeah. Got it. Thanks, Stoddard.
All right, last hit
Duffy and López had on Salcedo,
he was deputy chief of security
for the cartel.
All right. So that much is true.
Had a degree in engineering.
Business license for a bio-diesel factory
that went belly up.
- Wonder why.
- Ex-military.
Served under a Carlo Córdova. Major.
Who became head of security
for the cartel.
Must've been how he got the job.
Wonder if he clipped his old buddy
to take his spot.
And he was connected to the purchase
of bombs in a plan to kill Pablo.
Oh, just that?
Does that sound like the everyman
who only signed on
- to protect Miguel's family to you?
- Okay.
So he's a scumbag. Last I checked,
he's our best bet to get Miguel.
Scumbags I can handle.
What I don't like are liars.
So when he calls back
with Miguel's location...
- how you want to play it?
- If he calls at all,
we ask the hard questions,
see how he holds up.
(Henao in Spanish)
I'm telling you, they're done.
Gilberto's looking
for some new way to surrender.
And you heard about this thing
in New York with Chepe, right?
And Miguel's in charge
of everything here.
'Better said, the Cali cartel is dead.'
(Amado) And you intend to...?
To do whatever I have to do
for the North Valley cartel.
Which is why I'm talking to you.
Funny how things change, isn't it?
So, Amado... what do you say?
(Sighs)
I say you're no fucking fun,
that's what I say.
But we both see the future
the same way.
Look, starting next week...
...I'll only be shipping product
for my new North Valley friends. Good?
And what about the other thing
we discussed?
(Sniffs)
(David) Look, I need you
to make room here.
And I want you to take care of the guests,
get them everything they need.
I also want a bottle
at each of these tables.
But I want the good stuff.
None of that shit you serve here.
Understood?
I was told you needed me.
I need to talk about something.
Leave your bitch down here.
Come on.
(Sighs)
You don't tell anyone about this, okay?
I was thinking about what you said
if I ever need your advice...
...and I could use your help.
- With your father's security?
- He's coming to the party tonight.
He's coming here?
Unless there's another fucking party
I don't know about? Yeah, here.
What do you want me to tell you, David?
- Public places are always bad.
- I know.
Too many people.
- When does he plan on arriving?
- I was thinking around eleven.
Well, what fucking time is best, then?
Well, I think ten is better.
It's less crowded.
Maybe I can take him up to the balcony.
You'll take care of it?
I knew I could count on you.
I just need this night to be perfect.
Everything has to go well.
You can relax.
I think we can manage that.
Boss, did you tell him
it isn't a good idea?
- Of course. You think he listened?
- He's an imbecile.
Pull over here.
Pinchadito said there's
a bad phone tap or something.
Stay here. I'll be two minutes.
(Phone ringing)
(Sighs)
- Hello?
- 'It's Salcedo. I only have a minute.'
- You got us both.
- Miguel's going to a party tonight.
'Libre Club. Carrera Ocho. Ten o'clock.'
It's gonna be crowded, so you have
to wait to get him until he's outside.
Is there any way we can check this, Jorge?
No. You're gonna have to trust me.
'And this promotion to security chief?
How'd that come about?'
That's... really complicated.
We're trying to understand why
you'd call us a day after you get a raise.
'We don't have time for this right now.
'He's going to be in the club
at ten o'clock. Carrera Ocho.'
Take him outside.
- (In Spanish) Hey. What's going on?
- Nothing, boss.
- Is he bothering you?
- (Woman) No, sir.
- I'm just buying fritters for my brother.
- Great, let's go.
- You want some?
- Sure.
"Complicated."
Everything with this guy is complicated.
Still, there's something about him
I believe.
Enough to walk into a cartel party blind?
For a chance
to get Miguel Rodríguez, maybe.
He's just stringing us along, Chris.
Or worse.
(Indistinct chatter)
Stop! Hey!
Hey! Come here!
(Horn beeps)
(Horn honks)
Get the back. Get the back.
Fuck!
(Groans)
Don't run.
(Crowd screaming)
Franklin Jurado...
Javier Peña, DEA. You're being extradited
for money laundering and racketeering.
- My wife. You need to make sure...
- She's in Bogotá.
She'll meet us in Miami.
(Secretary) 'Ambassador,
I've got Agent Peña, line one.'
- 'Peña?'
- We got him.
I'd like to get him into the United States
before the cartel knows he's in custody.
I spoke to the Prime Minister
this morning. Extradition papers are set.
As soon as he starts talking,
you let me know.
- 'I'll update Justice.'
- Yeah, will do, sir.
'Agent Peña. Good work.'
- (In Spanish) Let's see here.
- Zuelma prays every morning.
Very good. And here?
- The worm...
- Gotero...
- Dad!
- Hi, kids!
(Girls squeal)
- I need to speak to you.
- Okay. Girls...
Please, go to your room
and finish your homework.
Something came up.
- What is it?
- I know how hard this has been for you.
I just want you to know
that I've almost got it figured out.
- All right.
- I'll tell you more tonight.
But for now, I want you to get
everything ready to leave.
- Where are we going? How...
- Do you trust me?
My love...
Paola... do you trust me?
Yes?
Everything will be all right.
I promise.
Done. I'm finished.
I love that length on you.
Thank you. I like it, too.
And a little extra for you.
And I have a little extra for you, too.
- I'll see you later.
- See you later.
(Sniffs, coughs)
(In Spanish) You were the one
who approached my wife?
You enjoy it?
Using her to get to me?
(In English) You know what I'd be
thinking about if I were you, Franklin?
That if your wife wants to see you...
...she's gonna see you in jail.
Drive hours every week.
Get felt up by some sweaty guard
whose only highlight at work
is getting his hands
under your wife's dress.
(In Spanish)
You can say whatever you want.
- You can't scare me.
- No...
(In Spanish) I can just ruin your life.
You know the brothers.
Pretty well.
What do you think will happen to them
without Gilberto running things?
You're young, Franklin.
You have your whole life ahead of you.
You really want to spend it in a cell?
Talk to me. I'll get you a deal.
You and Christina... can start over.
Have a new life.
In the United States.
I'm not going to say a single word...
...until I see my wife.
Okay.
Then you'll have your witness.
(In Spanish) Stop. Stop here.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
Turn around.
(In English) Franklin.
His name is Franklin Jurado.
- Jurado or...
- (Man) 'Yes, ma'am.
'We've called his room several times.
We're unable to locate him.'
Okay, well, did he check out?
Have you seen him at all?
It sounds like you don't know anything.
'We haven't seen him
and he has not checked out.'
'I'm sorry, ma'am. I cannot help you.
'Thank you for calling
Baoase Luxury Resort.'
No, thank you.
Thank you for fucking nothing.
(Chimes ring)
(In Spanish) Manny.
Thanks for meeting.
Julia said you might have
something on Crespo?
Well, yes.
It's something I hope you like.
How can I help you, Mr. Crespo?
Or should I say, Mr. Santacruz?
(Chuckles) Well...
I was hoping I could help you.
Where are you from?
- Cuba.
- Cuba! Gorgeous.
When you were young,
did you ever think you would come
to this country and do something special?
(Chuckles)
Well, I did.
I imagined myself coming here
to the United States, to New York,
to build something important.
That was also my dream.
The dream of a young immigrant,
like yourself.
And that's why I want to help you,
to make whatever dream you have a reality.
Whatever it is.
Regardless how much it costs.
In dollars.
You think you and I are the same
because we came
to this country with dreams?
Well...
My family fled Cuba
because we believed in freedom.
You came to sell cocaine.
Yes, we are both immigrants,
but we have nothing in common,
Mr. Santacruz.
My story is going to print.
Okay.
Thank you for hearing my proposal.
Can I ask you a question?
How long will it take
to get to the airport from here?
I have no idea.
An hour or so.
(Chepe laughs)
I'll miss a lot about New York.
But not the traffic.
(Gunshot)
(♪ "Para Ti Caleña" playing)
- (Man) Good evening, sir.
- Good evening. How are you?
- (Salcedo) Good evening.
- Hello. How are you?
Good evening. Welcome.
Good evening.
(Man) Good to see you, David.
What's up?
Looks like the whole family
showed up.
Why don't we have a drink upstairs?
You know what? I don't want
this many people up here.
Good evening!
Welcome to the Cali Fair!
Let's give a warm welcome
to a friend of the festival,
and our patron,
Mr. Miguel Rodríguez!
Come. Come here.
Come! Come here!
Say a few words.
(Cheering and applause)
Thank you all for coming.
Please, enjoy the party.
(♪ "El día de suerte" playing)
(Laughs)
(Chuckles)
Your brother's a character.
His passion for tequila
exceeds his tolerance.
Well... my shift started already.
Bring me a pack of cigarettes
when you come back.
You're giving me a tip.
- (In English) I told you he'd be here.
- You came through.
I also said to take him outside.
It's too risky in here.
Tell your men to wait
until he's leaving.
- What men are you talking about?
- Your men standing by the DJ booth.
We came tonight to make sure
you were telling the truth.
We didn't bring any men.
- Fuck are you talking about?
- What?
- What's wrong?
- Fuck. You need to go. Go!
- (Gun cocks)
- Shh.
We aren't here for you.
Where is Pacho?
Pacho!
(♪ Music blaring)
I need to talk to you.
- Don't interrupt me...
- We have a problem. We have to leave.
- Relax. It's a fucking party.
- We need to leave now!
- I said calm down! I'll say when we go.
- What's going on here?
We have to leave, sir. Please.
(Darío) Get down!
Go! Watch out!
Pacho!
(Distant gunshots)
(Screams)
(Crowd screaming)
(Darío) Watch out!
Stay there!
- Keep going!
- Careful! Get out of the way!
- Get out of the way!
Keep moving.
- When I run...
- They're over here.
(David) Shit!
(Shooting continues)
Give me the gun.
Go ahead.
Are you all right?
Motherfucker!
Álvaro!
Shoot them! Shoot them!
Go!
Over there!
- Careful!
- Head down, sir.
Head down!
- Slow down.
- Move it!
Motherfucker!
- Go!
- Let's go! Move it!
This shit...
Little brother, I need you to shoot.
Your gun. Keep shooting at them.
Pacho...
- Head down!
- I'll drive, Enrique. I'll drive!
Over here!
Who drove the car?
You got here by car.
Who was driving?
- Me.
- Give me the keys.
Fuck you.
(Phone rings)
Peña.
(Christina) 'There are men
at my apartment.'
- Yeah, they're ours.
- Yeah, no shit.
'Are you with them?'
No. I saw them and I freaked out,
so I left.
They're meant to protect you.
Have you talked to anyone?
No, I tried calling Franklin,
but I couldn't get in touch with him.
'What the fuck is going on?'
- We arrested Franklin.
- You did what?
'Christina, listen to me.'
I... You fucking asshole.
- Listen to me.
- I told you I was gonna talk to him.
- I told you.
- Christina. You want it? This is it.
As soon as we hang up the phone,
you get yourself to the American Embassy.
'You don't talk to anyone,
you don't call anyone.
- 'You get yourself there.'
- Okay.
- (In Spanish) Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are we close?
- Yes. It's just around the corner.
Thank you.
You saved me. Really.
Just tell your friends about me.
But only the ones with money.
(Chuckles)
Why isn't this imbecile moving?
(Horn honking)
(Stylist) When is this car gonna move?
- Fuck!
- Oh, my God.
- (In English) Oh, my God.
- (In Spanish) God.
- Oh, my God.
- Go! Fucking drive! Oh, my...
We start with just the basics. Okay?
Where they move the money,
where they keep the money.
Let me guess.
It's his fucking lawyer?
(Knock on door)
Agent Peña.
Alan Starkman. Mr. Jurado's lawyer.
Yeah. Your client has indicated he's open
to a deal in exchange for testimony.
Before he learned that
his wife won't be joining him.
No. I've just spoken with his wife.
She's on her way to the embassy in Bogotá.
Now, I was informed she never arrived.
Oh, go ahead. Check with your people.
It's my understanding that she met up
with Mr. Jurado's employers... instead.
I guess she's had a change of heart.
Whatever deal you had with my client...
is off.
(In Spanish) Dad! Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- (Jorge) Let's go inside.
- It's those North Valley motherfuckers.
- We got one of the shooters.
- They shot Álvaro, too.
Pacho's okay.
They're on their way back.
Are you okay?
- Close the damn door.
- What a fucking night.
Darío, please take her upstairs.
I'm coming soon.
What happened there?
It looked like...
...like you knew
something was coming.
Jorge, you know what? I know why.
Because you are always working.
You saved my life tonight, Jorge!
- Dad, it wasn't my fault, I...
- One moment.
From now on, I want you back in charge
of my personal security.
Only you, Jorge.
Of course, Don Miguel.
And if you allow me, we don't know
if this will be the only attack or not.
So I need to know
where you are at all times.
Tomorrow is another day.
- (Miguel) 'Gilberto, it's me.'
- Thank God.
- How are you, brother?
- 'We're okay.
Look, Gilberto,
they tried to kill Pacho, too.
- 'Pacho? No, it can't be...'
- No, he's okay. He survived.
- 'He's on his way home.'
- Thank God.
These North Valley motherfuckers,
I'm going to kill them. Sons of bitches.
Listen to me, Miguel.
Now's not the time for...
Everybody's watching.
- 'It could ruin everything.'
- Look, Gilberto. They tried to kill me.
They tried to kill my son.
They tried to kill María.
They tried to kill Pacho.
Yes, I understand, brother, but...
...for now,
we can't afford to start a war.
Especially being so close
to the surrender.
What fucking surrender, Gilberto?
Before we can surrender,
they'll take everything from us.
- Brother, listen to me.
- Okay, no war. I understand.
You'll see.
Everything is going to be okay, brother.
Okay, Gilberto. Bye.
(Knock on door)
It's Salcedo.
- You alone?
- Yeah.
- Get the fuck in.
- How the fuck did you know where we were?
The same way I knew where to call you.
You think I would bring a gun here?
- We don't know what to think.
- Why didn't you have a team there tonight?
Because you never gave us
a straight answer.
- Did you know that was gonna happen?
- You're serious?
How's the North Valley
shooting up the place gonna help me?
You look like a hero,
escorting Miguel out the back.
I had to do my job.
You're still not telling us
the fucking truth.
They killed the guy I replaced.
And they killed his wife.
And they're gonna do the same thing
to me and my family.
And you two are the only ones that can
help me get them out. You understand?
Yeah.
Then we need to trust each other.
- Yeah.
Tell me you know where Miguel is.
This is a skypager. All right?
It's untraceable. Even by you.
We'll be in touch.
(Reporter in Spanish)
'Over 15 people were killed,
'with dozens more injured
and in critical condition,
'in a deadly shootout tonight
at the kick-off party for the Cali Fair.
'Police say it's too early to say
what caused the incident...'
(Door opens)
- I was worried.
- I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
- We're safe. We're safe.
- What happened?
It was the North Valley. I'm okay.
Where are we going?
Why do we have to leave?
What's going on?
Come with me. Come. Come. Come.
Tell me what's going on right now!
What I'm about to tell you
has to stay here.
You can't tell anyone, understand?
I'm working for the Americans.
It can't be.
I contacted the DEA.
I'm giving them Miguel.
In exchange, they will help us
get out of the country.
It's our only option.
There's no other way.
You're crazy.
They're going to kill all of us.
- You're insane. What were you thinking?
- Paola...
(Peña) 'Things don't always go
according to plan.
'You can use every hope and prayer
you have, take your shot,
'and everything still goes to shit.
'And when that happens, it's almost
like you never had a plan at all.
'That's when people get desperate.
And things get dangerous.'
(Miguel in Spanish)
I want to welcome Pacho, Chepe.
I'm sorry it's under these circumstances.
North Valley attacked us.
Their intentions were clear.
They saw us as vulnerable
without Gilberto.
Weak, with me in charge.
They're trying to destroy us.
Take what's ours.
I...
All of us know there's only
one appropriate response to this.
One way to react against these people
who want to take everything from us,
what we've worked so hard to build.
War.
This is Gilberto's decision?
It's...
...mine.
(♪ Porro music playing)