There’s no respect.
I couldn’t even grab the cigarettes.
I’m gonna shoot every fucking hostage
in the head. That’s right.
Who’s doing this?
Carrillo and Search Bloc,
I’m sure of it.
—In the middle of our negotiations?
—Either Gaviria is trying to catch me …
or Carrillo doesn’t give a shit
about the negotiations.
You know what we have to do, Pablo.
We have to close the deal fast …
before they find us and kill us.
Not before we build our own jail.
And that fucking pussy president
will have to agree to that,
even if I have to stick a bomb up his ass.
It’s so fucking cold.
Is there a jacket there for me?
—Check it out, fag.
—What’s up?
It’s a miniskirt with your name on it.
—“Gustavo Gaviria.”
—Give me that.
All right, let’s call the boys.
And what about you?
Are you all right?
OK, boys, we’re in the clear.
Pick us up at El Mariano pass.
Search Bloc, we are registering the
latitude and longitude at a fixed point.
The subject appears
to have stopped moving.
You’ve gotta be shitting me.
How nice to see
that you have made friends.
Careful, son.
This woman is very clever.
She can grab your gun
and shoot you in the head.
My apologies, boss.
How do you feel?
As well as one might expect.
I need you to record another tape for me.
No.
No, not until you free more hostages.
Maruja is very ill.
Ricardo has an ulcer.
I’m the only one you need to negotiate.
Then why does the Colombian government
keep trying to capture me?
Look …
I admire your bravery very much.
But Gaviria is a piece of shit, and,
with all due respect, so is your father.
And what did you expect?
To get into Congress like it was nothing?
Without it mattering that you,
in fact, traffic drugs?
I expected respect.
You had respect
when you built homes for the poor.
But when you didn’t get that respect
from a herd of egocentric bureaucrats,
you threw a tantrum.
I was going to do marvellous things
for this country.
If I have made myself into a monster,
like all of you say,
that is the fault of people
like your father …
and those politicians “of always.”
Those oligarchs and those people
were never going to tolerate
that little paisa from Medellín
who had more money
and was more intelligent than all of them.
Yes.
You would have done marvellous things.
And that is the saddest part.
Mr Escobar has promised
to free two more hostages.
But in exchange, he has asked that you
continue negotiations with transparency.
President Gaviria …
he knows what you are doing.
He knows.
If you insist on trying to capture him
with the help of the Americans …
they’re going to kill us all.
You are risking my daughter’s life!
No, Nydia. With all due respect,
we are not risking anyone’s life.
Our priority is the life of your daughter
and the lives of the rest of the hostages.
But our priority
is also to capture Escobar.
You cannot have both things at once.
Negotiate with Escobar
while trying to capture him?
Do you know what he is demanding?
That we call a constitutional referendum
to abolish extradition.
That he only plead guilty
to having trafficked drugs one time.
And worst of all,
he wants to build his own jail
and have his own guards
to watch over him.
This is a deal with the devil.
You are the president of a country
that became a living hell some time ago.
With whom else did you expect
to be making a deal?
Hello. It’s Gorilla.
Forgive me, Gorilla,
I don’t feel well.
Miss Diana …
why are you so unpleasant with the boss?
You are loyal like a sheep,
aren’t you?
That man is your kidnapper … and mine,
and that of the whole nation.
Here, you go first.
Hide in here, quickly!
Mr President!
You killed my daughter.
Let her pass.
Wait …
If you had accepted his terms,
my daughter would still be alive!
Give him whatever he wants.
Don’t let others go through the suffering
we’ve had to endure.
Mr President … we need to leave.
God be with you, Nydia.
There’s something
I want to make very clear.
You are not to blame for Diana’s death.
OK? That has to be clear.
Escobar has the resources
for this to go on forever.
Yes, and so do we.
We are the state.
We are going to fight, do whatever we have
to do, and we are going to finish him.
We have options.
For instance, why don’t we allow
the American military to come in?
I know-- We don’t like it.
I personally don’t like it.
But if it’s a specific, clear mission--
—No.
—Something covert.
No!
It’s time to end all of this.
Give Escobar what he wants.
Let’s go.
Well … at this time,
our friend, Fernando,
is going to tell us a little something.
The Colombian government is going
to allow Pablo to turn himself in,
accepting only one simple charge:
drug trafficking.
And …
they are going to let him build a jail
which the police
cannot be within three kilometres of.
At last …
we have liberated ourselves from tyranny!
Long live Colombia, motherfuckers.
Fernando …
thank you very much.
And do you know when Congress
is going to vote to abolish extradition?
Yes, it’s--
It’s a matter of … of weeks.
And at that time, you will be able
to turn yourself over to the authorities.
It pleases me very much to finish my work
with you with such a great victory.
No, brother. Now is when I am going
to need your services the most.
—How-- How’s that?
—Fernando …
now it’s time for us to find legal means
to reduce my sentence even more.
Right?
And what does this mean for us, huh?
It means, my love …
that now I have a jail.
And for you,
visiting days will be …
every day.
—I’m serious, Pablo.
—So am I.
The problem, Pablo, is that …
now that you have admitted
to trafficking in narcotics,
my image as a journalist
cannot be associated with yours.
So then …
now you think I am going to damage your
credibility as a journalist … is that it?
You understand what I’m saying.
Oh, yeah, sure. Of course I do.
I think that it’s time for me …
to set you free, so that …
you can find a boyfriend
who’s honest …
so that you can get a little house,
have little kids,
—little dogs …
—Don’t joke around, Pablo.
No, I’m not joking.
I just want you to know …
that you, Valeria …
are a bandit, just like me.
So don’t come to me with bullshit.
Looks like you got away with it,
eh, asshole?
Shit, I’d thought you’d gone crazy.
Geniuses …
are always branded as crazy.
—Am I right?
—Yeah.
—The Ochoas …
—The Ochoas what?
You can bet
they’re going to be pissed off.
Because of the treaty?
Or because you’re fucking their sister?
That was a stupid mistake, Gustavo.
Let’s hope they don’t
make you pay for it later.
The soccer field will be over here.
Here, I want to have
a little doll house for Manuela,
and downstairs,
a bar with a Jacuzzi for the guys.
My family will live in a house
down the hill.
I’m going to install a telescope
so I can look at them whenever I want.
Yeah, right. More like
you can look at other girls’ asses.
No. The family, the family.
To see my kids.
—What can we do to help you, Pablo?
—Well …
while we’re in prison,
Gustavo and me,
I will count on you, Moncada, and you,
Galeano, to oversee operations.
Thank you, Pablo.
We’re privileged to be given
that responsibility. You can count on us.
We’ve already spoken about the operational
plan and everything’s clear, right?
Yes. We won’t let you down, Pablo.
Did you tell them about the tax?
—No, I didn’t.
—The tax?
What tax is this?
Who paid for the war we fought?
You.
—You, Don Pablo.
—That’s right.
We have peace now.
You’re going to directly
benefit from that.
It’s only fair that you contribute
to the legal and security costs
that Gustavo and I will face behind bars.
And about how much will that be?
We agreed to what,
$200,000 a month, right?
Yes, 200 grand.
200 grand?
That’s a lot of money, brother.
A lot of money.
But consider it done.
And again … thank you
very much for this responsibility,
—and for considering us.
—All right, then.
Do you think that was a smart move, Pablo?
Why should I let them
reap the fruits of our labor
without compensating us for it, Gustavo?
I agree with you.
But right now, we really
need those two fags to be loyal.
And what?
You don’t think I inspire loyalty?
My loyalty?
Yes, you know you have it.
But I’m not sure about everyone else’s.
You know, the thing is, Pablo …
you won.
There’s no arguing that.
But you gave in.
And there are people
who will see that as weakness.
We’ve gotta keep our enemies close,
now more than ever.
Thank you.
It’s great to see you again, Valeria.
Likewise, Pacho.
I’m very happy to see you.
Although I must say …
it was a little unexpected.
We are worried about you.
And … why are “we” worried?
Pablo’s cutting a deal
with the government.
He’s going to have
to admit to certain things.
Things that may damage
your reputation by association.
If I’m good at anything,
it’s protecting my reputation.
Listen, this time it’s different.
Look … you helped create
that “Robin Hood Paisa” bullshit.
And when it all goes to shit, you’ll have
to take responsibility for that.
Maybe he tricked me, too.
Like the rest of the world.
You have enemies, see?
They’re not gonna
let you get away with it.
Look, Valeria …
we have a lot of connections in New York,
a strong presence, you could say.
You should go there,
at least for a little while.
And leave Colombia.
There are a million Colombians there.
A new audience.
And they don’t care if you shared your bed
with a monster or not.
Just for a while.
When this is all over, you’ll be able to
come back here with your head held high.
I guarantee it.
And not only that, you’ll have earned
a brand-new audience in the United States.
—Betrayal is not my style.
—What betrayal?
And what would you be betraying?
Your role as his mistress?
You remain loyal to a man who has never
thought you good enough to be his wife.
His wife? Me?
No, no, no,
you’re very much mistaken, my dear.
The last thing I want
is to be married to him.
Besides …
do you think I’d want to be his wife?
Do you think I want to be locked up,
waiting all day at the Monaco building,
while he’s out with …
with me?
No.
That’s too boring.
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
No, it was terrible.
It was terrible.
Every day in a different house …
worried about you …
the kids …
The truth is …
it’s very good to be home.
—You look happy.
—Of course.
That time has passed.
It’s the happiest face I’ve ever seen
on a man about to go to jail.
The kids!
The kids, Pablo!
—The kids!
—No, Tata!
—I have to go to them!
—Stay here!
—My children!
I’ll go get them. Stay here.
Juan Pablo!
—Are you OK?
—Yes.
Come on.
Go to your mother.
Come on, come on.
Don’t worry, cousin.
We’re going to kill them all.
Hello?
Valeria, there was an attempted hit
at the Monaco building.
—Just now?
—Yes, a few minutes ago. A car bomb.
—Who was inside?
—We don’t know.
What other information do you have?
That’s all the information
we have right now.
OK, thanks.
He always takes her to the same motel.
—Marina.
—Where are you going?
I’m going to the city.
I have to get out of this prison.
—Come here, Marina.
—Yes?
Have a good time.
Be safe.
Thanks.
You know what he’s going to do, right?
He’s going to continue conducting
his business behind those walls
that are protected
by the Colombian government.
We should give him credit.
The man is a genius.
Well … all the more reason
that we should negotiate our surrender.
But you know that Pablo
took it upon himself to close that door.
So we need to take advantage
of your political contacts,
especially General Jaramillo.
Can you talk to him for us?
Yes, of course.
But I don’t think it will be enough.
What are you saying?
That you’re going
to have to offer something more,
something that interests them enough
to make a deal with you.
Gustavo Gaviria.
He is the key to Pablo’s business.
If that son of a bitch goes down,
the whole empire goes down.
Indeed, that could work.
That could work.
Follow me.
Kiss me.
—You look pretty, baby.
—Yeah, sure.
What I mean is
you’ve always looked pretty.
What’s happening?
Nothing.
Nothing is happening here.
Isn’t that right, Colonel Carrillo?
That’s up to you.
—Say goodbye.
—No.
No, no, no.
Gustavo, look at me.
Does your family know where you are?
—Gustavo!
—Calm down, Marina.
You’re making a big mistake, Carrillo.
We’re already in negotiations
with the government.
—You have no reason to be doing this.
—You’re right.
That’s why I’m not here.
Then what the fuck do you want?
Don’t act stupid.
Give me your cousin …
and I’ll let you live.
All right.
Kill me, then, motherfucker.
I won’t do that myself.
But I want to introduce you to some people
who would love to do it for me.
This guy? This is Lastia.
His sister died in a bookstore in Bogotá
in a bombing you coordinated.
She was 17 years old.
And this guy here …
this is Trujillo.
You killed his father
and his brother for being cops.
—That has nothing to do with me.
—No?
You know …
if you support evil, you are evil.
Look at them.
I just want you to look at their faces.
A few of the victims
you’ve left in your wake.
Tell me …
have you ever felt
the swift vengeance of justice?
Give me your cousin …
or I’ll let these men show you
that vengeance with their fists.
Do it, then …
you sons of bitches.
OK, then.
We’ll see how you feel …
after ten minutes.
Do it.
Tell me where your cousin is.
It doesn’t have to end like this.
We …
are bandits …
not snitches, motherfucker.
You’re--
You’re all gonna die, motherfuckers!
You’re all dead, motherfuckers!
You, your families,
your wives are all dead, motherfuckers!
You’re all dead!
Dump his body on the road to Sabaneta.
Colonel, they’re going
to make us pay for this.
Report his death as a result
of a shoot-out with the police.
Make sure you report that he fired first.
But Colonel, he’s all beat up.
That work for you?
There is nothing … more beautiful
and more important in my life than this.
We’re all here together … united.
Now let’s eat and enjoy
this marvellous food.
—Wait, wait.
—Oh, yeah, the beets.
Boss?
Hello, son. Have a seat.
—Sit down--
—Boss, I don’t know how to say this.
Tell me like a man.
—Gustavo is dead.
—What?
They found his body on the outskirts
of Sabaneta, badly beaten.
How’s that?
They also shot him, boss.
No, no!
How dare you come to my house saying that!
How dare you!
Leave! Get out of my house!
You … you are leaving right now!
Get out of my house! Go on!
No! Gustavo, no. Pablo …
Go on! Get out of here!
It’s OK.
Everything’s going to be fine.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, boss.
I want you to take him
to the funeral home …
and guard his body the entire time
until it’s buried.
—All right.
—Go on.
How are you doing, son?
I’m going to miss him so much, Mama.
When …
you were nine … or ten …
do you remember?
How you would
ride around on your bicycles.
You’d go up into the mountains
and just disappear.
The whole day would go by …
And we would call you …
We seemed crazy,
yelling for you all over the place …
until finally you would appear.
Oh, my God.
“Where were you?”
“Where have you been, son?”
I would yell out.
“In the mountains, Mama.”
“Higher than the clouds, Auntie,”
Gustavo would say, laughing.
He …
He always wanted to go farther.
He always did.
But with you.
Only with you.
I didn’t think it would end this way.
Good afternoon.
Boss?
Someone came all the way out here
to see you.
Miss Valeria.
Good day, ma’am. Pablo.
What’s she doing here?
I’m here only because
I have important information.
I hope it’s very important.
It’s about Gustavo.
Tell us, then.
I’ve been told the Ochoa brothers
have been seen in Cali.
They are the ones
who turned Gustavo over,
in exchange for the cartel helping them
seal a deal with the government.
How do you know that?
You know me, Pablo.
I have my sources.
Who in Cali?
Pacho Herrera.
“Will you hide yourself forever, Lord?
Will your wrath burn like fire?
Remember how fleeting is my life,
for what futility
you have created the children of men.”
As you know, I come on behalf
of President César Gaviria,
and the Colombian government.
This is the offer of our terms
for your surrender.
All right, then.
Let me hand over my gun.
—You won.
—We both did.
Now Gaviria can announce
that Pablo Escobar has turned himself in.
Except that’s not so true.
You and I know it’s a huge lie.
Lies are necessary … when the truth
is too difficult to believe. Right?
So, Lagarto …
are we gonna party tonight or what?
La Dispensaria.
All right.