[Guard in Spanish] Stop!
[Chatter in Spanish]
Ok!
- How are you?
- Very well. How are you?
Your ID, please.
Certainly.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Baby crying nearby]
[In Spanish] Give me that.
How many times have I told you
not to throw the ball over there?
Are you trying
to scare your sister or what?
- She's crying.
- — of course she's crying.
Don't you see she's just a baby?
You yourself were a baby
not too long ago.
Yes, dad.
- What's wrong? — nothing.
- What's wrong, Juan Pablo?
- I want her to die.
Never say that.
We are a family and we have
to look out for each other, always.
- You hear me?
- [Phone ringing]
Hello.
[Gustavo]
Cousin, poison just took out some cops.
- Yes, go on. How many?
- Two.
Yeah, but two what?
Sergeants or officers?
Officers. You know poison.
- Officers are a million each.
- Ok, so two million?
- Yes, I'm writing it down here.
- Ok, talk to you later.
All right.
What were you talking about?
Just business.
I want to be a businessman like you.
[Sighs]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[Steve] Pablo's path was total war.
He established a bounty system for killing
cops and over 200 were slaughtered.
The police had to build a special morgue
just to hold the bodies.
The cops, they took vengeance.
[In English] My name is alba borraga,
born 1962 in popayan.
Father sandoval, mother Maria.
We own a large tobacco farm.
I graduated universidad del cauca
with an emphasis in chemical engineering.
Ok, try it again and look at me.
I've already done it 17 times.
You got me and my wife into this.
Now sit down and do it again
until you get it right.
[Elisa sighs]
My name is alba borraga,
born 1962 in popayan.
Father sandoval, mother Maria.
We own a large tobacco farm.
I graduated universidad del cauca
with an emphasis in chemical engineering.
What if they ask me
a question about chemistry?
- I hope you're good at bullshitting.
- _ ok...
Sit down. Do it again.
It's getting better.
[Steve] We were protecting Elisa
because she could tie Escobar
to the palace of justice...
But by protecting a communist,
we were traitors.
Go figure.
Let's go.
- [Connie] Are you ready?
- [Elisa] Yes.
[Steve sighs]
Honey, thank you.
- You better help us get Escobar.
- I want him dead, too.
Yeah, but we're not a death squad, ok?
You clearly don't know
your country's history in Latin America.
- Sorry, I didn't hear that...
- Honey, mellow out, ok?
Steve, I know you're mad,
but this is the right thing to do.
The right thing to do? I didn't really have
a choice in the matter though, did I?
[Connie] This is the only choice.
[Steve sighs] You should
think about going back to Miami.
They're in their car. Hold on.
Wow. Maybe I will.
Just get in the car, ok?
[Car door slams,
engine starts over radio]
Ok, ok, they're on the move.
- Go. Go, go, go.
- [Engine starting]
Should've never brought Connie down here.
She's not cut out for it.
- He's got that commie bitch with him.
- [Steve] Don't do anything stupid.
Just keep your head down
and this'll all be over soon enough.
We're gonna cut him off
up here on the left.
[Tires screeching]
Get out of the car, Murphy!
- Step away from the vehicle.
- You following me?
- Move him away.
- [Steve] Easy.
- Easy.
- Back!
- Come on. Move the fuck back!
- — get your hands...
- Get your fucking hands off me!
- — [Lou] Hey!
- You spying on me?
- Relax, Murphy!
Who the fuck were you talking to?
Where the fuck is she?
Stand down.
Who were you talking to, huh?
I got wife troubles.
- Wife troubles. — yeah.
[Elisa] Your husband was clever
to get them to follow him.
I hope he's ok.
Shit.
[In Spanish] Good morning, ladies.
Where are you headed?
[In English] I'm sorry, sir.
I'm American. I don't speak Spanish.
[In Spanish] You speak Spanish?
I asked where you are headed.
- Popayan.
- Popayan?
Your papers, please.
[In English] Uh, documents.
[In Spanish] Ms. Connie Murphy.
Alba borraga.
Have a nice trip.
- Thank you.
- Be well.
Gracias, senor.
[Starts engine]
[Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
[Sighing]
Ok, yes.
Ok, you got her to the orphanage.
Good.
Elisa's fine.
Oh, god.
No, I'm just glad you're ok.
Listen, I want you to be smart, ok?
I want you to call me
every other hour from the road.
Actually, call me every hour.
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
I love you, too.
I'm proud of you. Bye.
[Steve] Now that I knew Connie was safe,
I could focus on césar gaviria.
At the time, the only thing more dangerous
than being a Colombian cop
was being a Colombian
presidential candidate.
[Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [Metal detector beeps]
- [Overlapping chatter in Spanish]
Mm-hm.
[Steve] Gaviria had come out
in favor of extraditing the narcos
to the United States, and it was in our
best interest that he win the presidency.
- But to win...
- Gracias.
He had to survive until election day.
Uh, senor gaviria?
[Woman in English]
Through that door.
- [In English] You must be agent Murphy.
- Hola.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure.
I'm Eduardo sandoval,
head of security of Dr. Gaviria.
What can we do for you?
I'm hoping that our agency
can offer some resources
to Mr. Gaviria and your campaign.
Shouldn't the DEA be out
chasing traffickers or is just my thought?
- I think the two coincide.
- Agent Murphy.
- Pleasure, sir.
- The pleasure is mine.
Please, have a seat.
Your secret service
has briefed us on security measures.
No open-air speaking engagements,
different routes home every day.
As if, after the deaths of Lara and gala'n,
we needed an education on these things.
- Come on.
- Exactly.
These men will stop at nothing
to kill you.
I'm aware of that.
And we're taking every precaution.
Your government even offers
the use of an armored Cadillac limousine,
built for your president.
The thing is that driving around in Bogota
with an American-made tank
won't exactly endear us to the voters.
And to be honest...
We don't know how to respond to that one.
Somebody offered me a brand new caddy,
I'd say thank you.
Well, thank you.
And this?
What are we supposed to do with this?
Bullet-proof pants.
I suggest that you wear them.
Thank you, agent Murphy,
for your consideration.
And we'll keep in mind your advice.
Thank you for your time.
With gaviria
there will be a future
[Steve] César gaviria was riding
a wave of public support
for his stance on extradition.
This made him a target.
But we had a target of our own:
José Rodriguez gacha,
who we tracked to cartagena
through one of our informants.
[Gacha in Spanish] Have you heard
of this thing called a computer?
Some guy was trying to sell me a computer.
I don't know what it is.
[Boy] It's a new kind of technology
that's coming out.
- It's coming out now?
- Yeah, dad.
Hey, honey.
You look very beautiful today.
Relax, baby. Relax.
We don't bite. [Chuckles]
- Do you need anything else?
- I want you.
- [Gacha] Nothing more, thank you.
- Yes, sir.
I want to fuck her.
We have more important things
to worry about right now, my son.
Talk to me. What do you know?
Don gonzalo,
we have people all over the property.
It's secure.
- We've got a few men in town as well.
- [Grunts]
Now, what can you tell me
about medellin?
The same, boss.
Carrillo's entire search bloc
is out looking for Pablo.
[Gacha] Thank you, navegante.
- Here to serve, boss.
- — keep us safe.
Don Freddy.
Son... a question.
Are we sheep or are we wolves?
- We're wolves.
- We're wolves! Right.
I like it.
[Navegante in Spanish] They're in
a house outside of cartagena, right here.
Just know there are
a lot of people guarding him.
Navegante, you've been
working for gacha for many years.
I'm sure in that time you've
earned way more than we are giving you.
So tell me,
why do you want to betray him?
That fucker's crazy.
He's gonna get us all killed.
I don't believe him one bit.
What do you care
why he's doing it?
Because we have 23 agents with
outdated weapons waiting in Barranquilla.
And he has twice as many men
with brand new weapons.
And frankly...
I'm tired of sending young men
to face certain death.
So then we have to be smart.
We have to create a trap.
If we catch him alive,
he'll give us Escobar.
And the ochoas.
- The entire cartel.
- I don't give a fuck, Javier.
I want him dead.
He doesn't care about death.
He only fears rotting in jail.
- That's the real victory.
- Right, I forgot you're a gringo.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- What are you risking?
These aren't your men.
You have no family here to lose.
If this goes badly, there will be
more widows and orphans,
and I'll have to carry that
on my shoulders.
I trust his information.
And I trust you.
But if this turns out bad...
It'll be on your conscience.
[In English] What do we got?
Routine airport surveillance.
We tagged poison.
Who's this guy?
I don't know, but if poison
showed his face to pick him up,
he must be really important.
[Gustavo in Spanish]
Here's your payment, sir.
It'll be taken to the coast of Spain
on a cargo ship.
From there, our trucks
will take it to the basque country.
It's all set up.
5,000 kilos or I go back to Spain
on the first flight.
[Gustavo] What's that?
As far as I know, you and my cousin
have an agreement.
The agreement is for this amount.
What kind of bullshit is this?
5,000 kilos or no deal.
Then there is no deal. Who the fuck
do you think you're talking to?
Forgive my cousin, sir.
5,000 it is, then.
[Ana] We shouldn't go.
I want you in the us.
You'll be safe there,
far from all of this.
- What if something happens...
- Nothing is going to happen to me.
Let's go.
Please, protect him.
Don't worry, everything will be fine.
Come on, I'll walk you.
- [Engine starting]
- [Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
[Boy] Bye, daddy, I love you!
[Chatter in Spanish]
[Steve]
Gaviria's life was on the line...
My wife was with Colombia's
most wanted fugitive,
and my partner was in cartagena.
He had his own mission,
with a group of cops
who had seen their friends and relatives
die at the hands of gacha.
Like trujillo,
whose father and two brothers, all cops,
had died in gun battles with the cartel.
As hard as we were going after gacha,
the narcos wanted gaviria.
- [Up-tempo Latin music playing]
- [Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
It killed me to ask for help
from this guy.
Suarez was as slimy as a hagfish,
with none of the charm.
- [In Spanish] Hello, Suarez.
- Look who's here.
The golden gringo.
[In English]
You don't call, you don't write.
[In Spanish]
I called your office.
I only speak to pena.
[In English]
I need to know who this is.
[In Spanish] Ineed ".I need".
I need to know who he is.
[Laughing]
[Mocking in Spanish]
"I need to know who he is."
Don't make me laugh, faggot.
[In English]
The fuck back! Fuck back.
[Man in Spanish] Ok.
- [In Spanish] You work for me, asshole!
- [Grunting]
- Right? Clear? Is that clear?
- [Loud whimpering]
[In English] You know who he is?
Gonna tell me? Gonna speak? Yeah...
[Steve] Suarez knew exactly who
this guy was, and he wasn't the only one.
- Jesus Christ.
- Next time you wanna fuck somebody,
take 'em on a date.
What's going on?
I have reason to believe
the medellin cartel
is planning an imminent attack
against gaviria.
We have no intel to that effect.
Maybe you should do your job instead
of spying on other agency personnel.
- What's he talking about?
- Nothing, ambassador.
CIA's been so kind
to give us these documents,
but 90 percent of them
are too classified for us to read.
I need to get into the white room.
What's that?
Cut the shit.
You're gonna give me these files.
[Chuckling]
You've been reading too many spy novels.
Spy novels...
Have you read the spaniard?
[Lou]
Where the hell did you get that?
Ma'am, he has been in the country
for several days.
He's been escorted
by one of Pablo's top sicarios.
Let me see this.
[Steve]
I know the CIA has intel on this man.
Now, are you going
to give me access or not?
Technically, the room isn't white.
It's more of a... burgundy.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
- Agent schroeder, will you join us?
- Mm-hm.
[Steve] The white room
was a top secret repository
for the CIA's deepest,
darkest secrets.
80 secret, in fact, that its
very existence was never acknowledged.
[Lock clicks]
Sit here.
Agent schroeder
will watch you the entire time.
Where are the files?
[Door buzzes]
[Latin music plays on radio]
[Gustavo in Spanish]
I feel like he's still too soft.
[Pablo] He'll be fine.
I don't know, Pablo.
I feel like we need
to suspend the operation.
- It's too delicate.
- You worry too much, Gustavo.
That's the reason
your hair is falling out. [Chuckles]
- Very funny, motherfucker.
- [Laughing]
[Gustavo scoffs]
Keep laughing.
How's our boy doing, mom?
He's learning,
with a little tough love.
- What's up, aunt?
- What's new?
That's so he can mix
with the sons of the oligarchs, right?
- Yes, sir.
- So he can get us some information.
What about these clowns?
Are they treating you right?
More or less.
What do you mean "more or less"?
We treat you good.
Are we going to eat, Gustavo?
- Some rice?
- [Gustavo] Yes.
[Sighs]
Thank you.
Jaime.
Welcome to the family.
Thank you, boss.
Can't you do anything?
[Gustavo]
While we're at war,
we can't do anything.
This is bullshit.
People are turning up dead every day
and my friends
think my brothers are responsible.
Let's talk about something else, baby.
All right,
let's talk about running away together.
Let's get away while we can.
[Chuckles softly]
"Let's get away."
Listen to this.
[Marina sighs]
Why would you run away
with a criminal like me?
And why not?
[Scoffs]
I wish it was that easy.
- Ah.
- — I can't just leave like that.
I know.
- You say that because of your wife.
- — [sighs]
I don't give a shit about my wife.
I'm talking about your other wife, Pablo.
[Dry chuckle]
Who is the woman
in that relationship?
You?
[Steve] Gacha was always paranoid
when things were quiet.
And now, he began to wonder
about navegante.
[In Spanish] Hey, doll.
What are you doing?
I'm married, sir.
That's no problem.
I can make you a widow pretty quick.
Don't touch me! Don't touch me.
Freddy, leave her alone.
Come here.
What's up?
The search bloc is here,
not in medellin.
But navegante said they were over there.
Navegante... navegante is a liar.
He wouldn't betray you.
Freddy... think, think.
Everyone in the world has a price.
[Shouting] All right, let's go!
They want war, we'll give them war!
[Men shouting eagerly in Spanish]
[Sighs]
[Steve] The spaniard was a name
that got everyone's attention.
He was a member of eta.
Never heard of 'em?
They made bomb-making
a goddamn art form.
They were a group of supposed
freedom fighters from the basque country,
trying to secede from Spain.
Their specialty was
targeted assassinations of public figures.
- [Indistinct radio chatter]
- [Sirens wailing]
Eta was responsible for the assassination
of Spanish prime minister Luis blanco,
returning home from Christmas mass...
And a remote-controlled car bomb that
killed defense minister Alejandro Rivera.
The man behind those bombs?
You guessed it... the spaniard.
Whose real name is efram Gonzalez,
a celebrity now, for hire.
Expensive, but the best.
'Cause Pablo only hires the best.
That was Pablo's plan,
to blow up gaviria.
The question was,
where, when and how?
[In English] I appreciate your concern,
madam ambassador,
but canceling our campaign travel
is not an option.
Well, given the new information
that agent Murphy has uncovered,
I hope you'll reconsider.
He has appearances in Cali, boyaca,
and a dozen other cities.
You are a target in every one.
Yes, and... we've done everything
your secret service
and Spain's civil guard
have recommended.
We also have bomb-sniffing dogs
at every campaign stop, so...
I think we're good.
You think the spaniard
doesn't know that?
Yes, I know.
But tell me, agent Murphy,
how do you expect him to win the election
if he hides like a scared rabbit
behind all this violence?
Tell me, how?
How do you expect him to win
if he's dead?
I'm not telling your wife
you died on my watch.
This is not your watch, ok?
Thank you, agent Murphy...
But Eduardo's right.
I'll take my chances.
[In Spanish]
His name is Steve Murphy. He's DEA.
I hope you'll pay for this information.
[Slow Latin music playing]
[Sighs]
Suarez is talking to the DEA.
You know what you have to do.
[In Spanish] He got away.
They killed the goddamn maid.
[Man] Colonel!
Colonel...
They called from the road block.
They have a car stopped
and they're saying the driver's a senator.
- Does he have his identification?
- Everything checks out.
So what's the problem?
They found a machine gun in the trunk.
Let's go.
Look at my credentials.
No, I don't know this gacha person
you're referring to.
Why do you have a gun in the trunk?
[Chuckles]
Gentlemen, are you asking why a politician
in this country carries a weapon?
Please.
- It's my bodyguard's.
- — where's your bodyguard?
You're alone in the car, right?
Listen to me, officers...
If you don't let me go immediately,
you're going to regret it.
Thank you.
- Give us a moment.
- Go on.
[Softly] I don't believe him.
I don't either.
He could have bought his credentials.
What if it turns out he is a senator?
We'll pay for that.
I can't run that risk.
It's true.
- You can't.
- [Chambers round, fires]
[Screams]
The next one...
Goes in your head!
- All right, all right!
- Talk, bitch!
I'll talk, I'll talk!
[In Spanish] I love you, my sweetheart.
I love you.
You have a guest.
It's Don Pablo.
[Knocking]
Hey, Jaime.
- Don Pablo.
- This is your house?
- Your family?
- Yes, sir. Welcome.
Tell me about them.
This is my daughter marcela.
- Look at what a cute baby.
- — [chuckles]
- How proud you must be.
- Of course I am.
Of course.
Very soon, they will have the money
to buy everything they want, Jaime.
Thanks a lot, boss.
- May I please have a glass of water?
- Of course.
Thank you.
- What about you?
- Good, sir.
- How have you been?
- Good, thank you.
Guys.
All right, Jaime.
This is for you to wear
during your mission.
Thank you, ma'am. Very kind.
Seriously, Pablo?
Thank you very much.
Everything is so beautiful.
You have to be very careful,
and get by unnoticed.
For sure, sir.
I'm ready to do what you're asking.
All right, then, son.
These guys are going to give you
very specific instructions.
Tomorrow morning, you're boarding
the plane that is leaving for Cali.
We want you to record a conversation.
It's very simple,
nothing to worry about.
All right.
- How are you feeling?
- I'm... I'm very happy.
Thank you very much for the opportunity,
Don Pablo. Seriously. And for the clothes.
Really, for me,
it's an honor to work for you.
Thank you very much.
[Softly] Don't mention it.
Come here, give me a hug.
Thank you, Don Pablo.
Thank you.
- Ma'am, have a good night.
- [Woman] Take care.
Thank you very much.
See you later, boys.
- Take care.
- Yes, sir.
My love, look!
- Look at this jacket. Beautiful, right?
- It's beautiful. What did Pablo say?
You know what?
We're going to get ahead.
You, me and the baby
are going to get ahead.
Thank you, my love.
- Look at this.
- Let's go try it on.
[In Spanish]
I have some news about gaviria.
They're going to kill him
on the way to Cali.
[In English] Did you say Cali?
Hey, can I get a translate in here?
Suarez, ok.
I can translate.
[Knocking at door]
[In Spanish] Wait a moment.
Someone is at the door.
[Stammers] "Tu Puerta"?
- "Door."
- door.
Suarez! Suarez.
- [Gunshot]
- [Screaming]
[In Spanish]
Pablo doesn't like you talking to the DEA.
[Steve over phone] Suarez!
Talk to me, you bastard.
Suarez, hello?
Hello?
Hel...
- I want that call.
- Right away, sir.
[Steve] Carrillo and his men
arrived in tolu to kill gacha.
And pena still hoped
he could be taken alive.
[In Spanish] It was her fault, dad.
Are you still thinking about that?
Let it go, son.
All she had to do was say yes
and I wouldn't have had to shoot her!
Be a man!
[Man zips pants]
[Grunts]
[Shouts] Son of a bitch!
They found us!
- [Automatic gunfire]
- [Overlapping shouts in Spanish]
[Screams]
- Come on, son!
- [Overlapping gunfire continues]
[Men shouting]
[Gunfire continues]
- [Battle sounds muted]
- [High-pitched tone]
[Grunts]
[Sounds returning]
[Indistinct shouts in Spanish]
- Sir, are you ok?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- He's trying to get away!
- He won't get away.
Get me a radio, quick!
Correal, bring a radio!
Correal! A radio!
Dad, let's go! Hurry, dad, hurry!
Hurry!
[Gunfire continues]
[Man in Spanish] Stop!
[Grunts]
Pena!
Gacha is in a red Chevy pick-up!
[Chuckles]
What did I tell you?
We got out ok.
- I'm scared. — scared of what?
You're a wolf, right?
Yes, I am a wolf.
[Freddy] It's a helicopter! It's a
helicopter! They're going to kill us!
Nobody is going to kill us!
Don't talk like that!
Take this. Take it!
- I have a Chevy in sight.
- Stop him!
Don't let him get away!
Try and disable the vehicle!
- [Indistinct chatter over radio]
- [Man readies weapon]
[Javier] No good.
We 're going in again.
Stop him!
Do whatever you have to do!
- Don't leave me alone, dad.
- No, no. Never, son, never!
Breathe! Breathe!
Do you want this, asshole?
- Do you want this?
- [Gunshots]
[Javier] We're taking fire!
We'll circle around
and approach from another direction.
You don't need to worry about anything,
my son. Nothing.
[Carrillo] Don't take any chances!
We can't afford to lose him!
Copy.
Look. Look outside. Look outside!
[Carrillo] What's happening?
Pena, what's happening?
[Javier] We stopped him.
He's not moving.
Freddy. Freddy?
Let's go, Freddy.
Freddy?
[Soft whimper]
[Helicopter blades thumping above]
[Whispers]
You're a wolf. You're a wolf.
Asshole!
Asshole! Hey, asshole!
Freddy! Wake up, Freddy!
- Hey, asshole! What are you gonna do?
- [Gun clicks]
What are you gonna do? Asshole!
What are you gonna do?! Asshole!
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Javier] He's out of bullets.
We can take him alive.
[Carrillo] It's your call.
What are you gonna do?! Asshole!
Give him lead.
[Screams]
- [Gunfire continues]
- — [shell casings clinking]
[Gunfire ceases]
Affirmative. Maintain positions
and patrol the area again. Very good.
[Indistinct chatter in Spanish]
Are you ok?
[In English] I'll sleep tonight.
[Steve] This was the first successful
major operation by the search bloc.
It signaled to the country
and to the world
that the fight against the narcos
had moved to a new level.
[In Spanish] According
to recent polls, we're doing well.
We're gaining points
in six districts within Cali.
That's important,
because it means we could pull ahead.
- Don't put too much faith in the polls.
- I know.
The last time,
we fell five points in one day.
- Yes. We...
- [Steve] Dr. Gaviria!
Stop him!
Sir, we can't let you through!
[Eduardo] Relax. Let him through.
- [In English] Agent Murphy.
- What are you doing here?
- [Panting] No, no. He can't go, no.
- What?
There's gonna be a bomb waiting.
He goes, he dies.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you talking about?
This is your job, your call.
But I know something's gonna go down.
Do you have proof?
- I got my gut. — [scoffs]
You got your gut.
- What if you're wrong?
- I hope to god I am.
What if I'm right?
[In Spanish] You nervous?
[Jaime] A little bit, but I'm fine.
[Softly] Wait here, wait here.
You know what you have to do?
Yes, sir.
Remember, you have to record
the entire conversation. Don't forget.
- No, sir. — have a nice flight.
Aren't you coming with me?
No, the boss just told me
to bring you here.
Hey, but don't worry.
Tomorrow,
I'll come and meet you there.
- All right, then.
- All right. Don't be nervous.
You'll see how fun it is to fly.
All right?
Go on. The line is right there.
Good luck, then.
[In Spanish] It's up to you, Eduardo.
Whatever you decide, I'll do.
[Woman over pa] Avianca announces
the departure of flight 203 to Cali,
now boarding at gate 6.
[In English]
I'll follow your gut this time.
[In Spanish] I'll organize the exit.
You guys stay with him.
[In English] Well... it seems like
you and I are not the only ones afraid.
[Sighs]
[In Spanish]
Put on your seatbelt, please.
[Seatbelt clicks]
[Indistinct announcements over pa]
[Indistinct conversation in Spanish]