This is one of the largest
and most mysterious plane crashes
in Colombian history.
You know where Jaime is?
No, sir.
I don’t know where he is.
He left home and hasn’t returned.
—Have Pablo and his men come by here?
—No.
—Your name is Natalie?
—Yes, sir.
Natalie, your boyfriend, Jaime,
was he with Pablo’s sicarios?
—No.
—Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
Well, then, why do you
have this picture of Pablo in your house?
Nothing wrong with that.
Everyone in the comuna has one.
You think those thugs
are going to protect you?
You don’t understand …
that you represent a big problem for them.
We can help you.
We can protect you.
But you have to tell us the truth.
I don’t want to leave, my love.
I don’t want to leave.
But I must, for all our safety.
Did you do something wrong?
Your dad did nothing wrong.
These are people who are jealous of us,
who are trying to take what we have.
You have to be strong.
I want you to be strong.
You have to be strong
and never show weakness.
I promise I’ll never be weak.
And watch out for your sister.
I love you very much.
I love you all very much.
—Do not spoil this boy.
—But … what do you mean?
—Watch her.
—Just a few sweets and some pork rinds.
Be careful, son. Be careful.
—I love you.
—Me, too.
Take care.
And what about you?
Come on.
I’m going to take you with me.
I’m going to take you with me …
Take care.
You think he did it?
Surely not.
Blow up that plane?
Of course he did it, Hermilda.
But he had his reasons.
We’ve got everyone looking
for Jaime’s wife throughout the comunas.
I want you to find her and kill her.
And kill any motherfucker that
can connect me with that fucking plane.
Yes, sir.
… the functions of President of Colombia?
I swear.
Well, César, congratulations.
Not César … I mean, Mr President.
Excuse us.
As a former president to a new one …
what advice would you give?
Well … you’ll be asked
to make many difficult decisions.
I would say one thing …
do what your wife says.
I always do.
Trust your instincts,
and be confident in your decisions.
Yes …
but that’s easier said than done.
You’ll never be able to please everyone,
so find the solution
that rings true in your heart.
Thank you.
Another thing I did want to tell you,
about the Americans--
What about the Americans?
This will have to be off the record,
my dear.
I can’t have my opinions
broadcast on your television show.
No, no, no.
You have my word.
—The Americans …
—Yes?
Be careful.
—Pablo.
—What’s up, Pacho?
Thank you.
We have Miami …
and have left you alone in New York.
—Yes, for a price.
—Certainly.
Look, Pacho, we agreed that we would
share the Los Angeles territory …
and that hasn’t been happening.
It seems you are not
holding up our agreement.
—How’s that?
—Exactly what I’m saying, Pacho.
Look, Pablo …
you know that our partners
sometimes operate independently.
If Mr Galeano
and Mr Moncada are correct,
then you have my assurance
that it will be rectified.
Thanks a lot, Pacho.
Disputes between us
cause needless bloodshed.
Then fix it. A war between our groups
is the last thing we need right now.
It would seem you already have a war.
Maybe bombing that plane
was a step too far.
Careful, Pacho.
Careful.
The only difference between us
is our little misunderstanding
with the government.
And that will be resolved soon.
Besides, that’s the business,
for all of us.
Yes, it’s true for all of us.
The only war we are really fighting
is the war against extradition.
And the outcome of that
is something we’re all interested in.
It’s true, Gustavo.
Gustavo is right.
We have a common goal,
and that is to get rid of extradition.
The United States is big enough
for all of us to operate in.
Let’s figure out Los Angeles
once you take care of your business here.
You know what bothers me?
Your arrogance.
Your attitude, your air of superiority.
Careful, Pacho … that you don’t
get yourself killed for that.
Thank you for coming.
—I’m gonna kill that homo bastard.
—Come on, Pablo, let me kill him.
Stop talking shit, Moncada.
We’ll kill that fag later.
Right now, we can’t be out in the open.
If that son of a bitch
starts selling shit in Los Angeles,
I’m personally gonna put a gun up his ass
and pull the trigger. I swear.
That will make him fall in love with you.
I think it’s up this way.
I don’t want to shoot her.
Kill that cute girl?
And the baby, too?
I don’t know why the boss
wants us to kill that girl.
—What does she know about Avianca anyway?
—Just shut up and follow orders!
Does he think putting a bomb
on every street corner
is going to get the police
to quit chasing him?
Gustavo, we need to get away,
out of this country.
And go where?
We’ll be treated like criminals
wherever we go.
They’ll kill him, and you know it.
I just hope he doesn’t
take you down with him.
This isn’t our war.
This isn’t war.
It’s negotiation.
Don’t you understand
what an opportunity this is?
He’s willing to consider
terms of surrender--
Under what conditions?
My God, he just blew up a plane!
Eduardo, calm down.
Let the man speak.
We can end this violence with dignity.
It’s good for both sides--
Do you realize
how stupid you sound right now?
César, this is absurd.
—Eduardo, please--
—This is a farce.
Please.
Let me deal with this. Please.
Fine. Whatever you want.
We can at least begin a discussion, right?
Even though you never stated it,
surely you’d like
to see the bombings stop.
—Yes. Yes, I would.
—Exactly.
So if we begin a dialogue,
they will cease.
That affords us all some time,
including the Search Bloc.
Fernando …
you saw his money,
and it blinded you to his soul.
That son of a bitch has no soul.
If telling him we’re negotiating allows
the bombs to stop while we find him …
then be my guest.
Thank you.
Really, thank you.
Look, man,
Pablo’s turned into a saint.
Of course.
He sends people straight to heaven.
She’s not here.
She might have just left.
Let’s search the comuna.
Look, Poison, I’m telling you
Pablo is being paranoid.
Careful what you say, son.
One day,
he is going to ask me to kill you.
Would you do it?
If he asks me … of course.
There is no way around it.
Wouldn’t you?
All right, all right,
let’s just go find this girl.
We’ll look around
and see where she’s hiding.
What’s wrong?
Here you go.
It’s OK, Natalie. Don’t worry.
Before you know it, we’ll get you
some food. Right? Isn’t that right?
Thank you.
What then, Fernando?
Has the Colombian government
offered a truce?
The government
hasn’t been willing to offer anything
I would consider acceptable.
What did they offer?
They want you to admit …
that you’re responsible for Avianca.
And of course, I told them that--
That we can’t even--
Is it that you’re not negotiating a thing?
No, no, of course I’m negotiating--
Then why is Carrillo
stopping every car in the comunas
and killing my boys
with the help of the gringos‽
Why are the Americans helping them if we
are supposed to be negotiating, Fernando?
Gaviria doesn’t want the gringos to know
he’s willing to negotiate with you.
That’s it.
Be very careful, Fernando.
Yes, Pablo.
Yes.
You’ve got to stop the bombing, Pablo.
I don’t know what you’re thinking anymore.
I think we should …
reorganize a bit …
and start sending our boys out to burn
some houses down and do some damage …
to politicians and senators
all over the country.
And to the soldiers and cops in our way,
the judges who annoy us
and the reporters that watch us,
basically, we have to create a presence so
disruptive they’ll want nothing but peace.
That’s the only way
we’re going to get there.
Is that it? Is that what you want?
A civil war?
—You’ve gone crazy, asshole.
—We have to fight, brother.
Let’s put our hearts into this.
And if we all must die, so be it.
Well, yes …
The thing is,
I don’t want to die yet, Pablo.
Nor do I.
But the bombs make the public want peace.
And that will influence the politicians.
You’re the one who says the politicians
don’t give a shit about the public.
If you want to influence politicians,
you’ll have to narrow your focus.
You know what I mean?
What about her?
No, she is way too much of a princess.
Surely we would have problems with her.
My God, look at that face.
The media is going to love that fox,
right?
Sure they will, but so will our boys.
Just think what
they’re gonna do to her.
Well …
I say let’s start with her …
Move it!
… and this fag.
And this cute couple.
Family members of the most
influential people in the country
have been kidnapped
on the very streets they call home.
What does Pablo Escobar want?
I’ll see you tomorrow on the same channel
for a special report.
Is everything all right?
All the victims are my friends.
Excuse me.
The kidnapping of Francisco Santos,
the editor in chief of the most important
newspaper in the nation,
is the latest and most shocking
in a string of kidnappings
orchestrated by the Medellín cartel.
Reporting to you, I’m Valeria Velez.
—All right.
—First on the scene, right? As always.
Maybe if you actually
had to work for a living,
you’d be hungry enough to get here first.
I found out from Santos’ wife …
a half hour after
he didn’t show up for dinner.
You?
Who tipped you off?
It’s a pleasure to see you,
as always.
These are Pablo’s conditions
for the release of the hostages.
You’ve read them,
you can see they’re very reasonable.
“Very reasonable,” he says.
You are definitely an imbecile, Fernando.
And I’m going to tell you something.
You will get what you deserve very soon,
I assure you.
I’m also one of those hostages.
I myself could be walking around calmly …
but like them, I am not free.
Escobar is asking us to surrender,
but that will never happen.
If he releases the hostages
and turns himself in,
we will take this into account.
Gaviria isn’t going to bend.
Then I’m going to break him.
You, get up from there.
The body of Ofelia Hernandez was found
dumped next to the Presidential Palace.
One must admire President Gaviria.
I’m sure it can’t be easy for him
to stand by his decision
to not negotiate with Escobar.
What’s the plan?
A few more hostages and they will give in.
Their time is running out.
I’m talking about us.
What about us, Valeria?
I don’t have time
for that pussy shit right now.
Colombia’s sweetheart.
You know the only reason
this hag has any fame
is because her father was president.
I despise her.
And why do you care so much?
Your ratings are through the roof, right?
Hers are higher.
Open the door, quick!
Move!
Let’s go!
Hurry up!
Where am I?
Hello!
Tell me where I am.
Does my family know I’m alive?
How would I know?
Who are you?
You work for Escobar?
You can call me Gorilla.
Gorilla.
Very well … Gorilla.
Where’s my crew?
Did you bring them here as well?
I’m here to guard you. That’s it.
Ladies and gentlemen, excuse me.
We understand the frustration and pain
you must be feeling for your children,
but believe me,
we are doing everything we can
to make sure your children get home soon.
Our daughter was kidnapped
on her way to an interview.
They killed the bodyguard.
No one is safe.
As a former president, I understand
the terrible position you’re in.
But we’re here to find a solution.
I understand your frustration,
Dr Turbay.
But if we give in now, any criminal
can hold our government hostage.
This isn’t “any criminal.”
This is the worst criminal in the world.
—And he is laughing at all of us.
—Mr President,
you’re proceeding as you must, but we must
act as the parents of our children.
Let’s pray you find a solution.
Hands up!
—Why are you driving this car?
—I don’t know.
Someone paid me 50,000 pesos
to drive it around the city.
Pablo came to see me.
Why?
He wants to settle the dispute
we have in the United States.
The Los Angeles problems.
He has bigger issues
than that right now.
He’ll make a deal with the government.
He’s managed to secure
some very effective bargaining chips.
Of course,
he’ll look after you guys, right?
We haven’t talked to Pablo in weeks.
He’s in hiding.
Look at that.
What a beautiful animal, Jorge.
You like it?
Yes, of course.
I’m sure he’ll look after you.
After all, you’re partners.
Yes, of course. Partners.
You could always have your sister
put in a good word with Gustavo.
What do you mean?
Oh, I’m sorry,
I thought you knew.
It could be gossip.
You know how people like to talk.
You should eat,
because you’re going to be here a while.
You’re going to get very hungry.
I don’t feel well.
What’s wrong? Are you sick?
I can get you some medicine.
It’s not that kind of illness.
I want to congratulate you.
I know you’re a very good reporter.
Thank you.
Gorilla, how long have you been
working for Escobar?
Oh, it’s been a while.
So you know what’s going on out there,
don’t you?
The truth is, I don’t go out.
So I have no idea what’s happening.
What the fuck are you doing, Gorilla?
Why isn’t she wearing the blindfold?
I didn’t know you were coming.
Put it on, man!
We have to take her.
Put that on.
—Says who?
—Didn’t I tell you to stay quiet?
Just put it on.
Pleasure to finally meet you,
Ms. Turbay.
Sit down, please.
I suppose you want me to interview you?
Even better.
I’m going to interview you.
So you can tell the world about
the humane treatment you’ve received here.
Don’t you want your parents
to know you’re well?
That you’re alive?
I don’t want to become
a piece of propaganda for you.
Who do you think you are?
So what’s necessary, miss,
to have your cooperation?
Let one of the hostages go.
You and I know
that I’m the one you really want.
You see?
Two reasonable people
coming to an agreement.
Maybe we can convince President Gaviria
to do the same. Right?
Mr Escobar has shown
a willingness to negotiate.
This afternoon,
he let one of the hostages go.
President Gaviria …
I ask you to at least
consider discussions with Mr Escobar.
I don’t understand. I thought you said
he wouldn’t bend, but now he’s let one go.
Because he has your daughter.
And she’s worth more to him
than the rest of them combined.
If you knew all I know, you’d understand
it’s nothing more than a stunt.
Give him what he wants.
What he wants is an insult to us
and to this country.
I don’t care. I want my child!
I believe what my wife
is trying to say is,
we’d like you to make a deal with Escobar.
If you refuse,
we’ll have to take certain measures.
Financially, by robbing you of donors …
and politically,
by robbing you of whatever support
your legislative agenda needs.
Are you threatening me?
We all use the tools at our disposal.
You as a politician, me as a father.
I’m sorry.
Doctor …
you told me to follow my instincts …
and they tell me not to give in
to this criminal.
That was before they took my daughter.
I came over as quickly as I could.
I was told you needed me urgently.
What’s up?
You OK?
Tell Fernando …
I’m willing to open negotiations.
We’ll make a counter to Escobar’s demands.
I thought you weren’t going to negotiate.
I have to stop this madness.
But God willing,
we can catch him first.
Tell the Americans
they can put their planes in the air.
What?
Yes, we’re here in Campo Valdés.
We’re gonna score a quick goal
and then come back out.
All right, all right. All right.
Don’t kill me, please!
I swear I didn’t hear anything.
I’m not going to say anything.
Please, don’t kill me.
—I’m not--
—Hey! Hey!
—Please, don’t kill me.
—What?
I’m begging you, please …
You could have at least waited
till I got her off me. Look at me now!
You got blood all over my new shoes.
I don’t give a shit about your shoes.
Stop bitching.
I’m not.
What about her?
Put a bullet in her.
What? The baby’s not a witness, man.
I don’t give a shit.
—Pablo told us to kill everyone.
—Yeah, but it’s a baby.
She won’t say shit in court.
If she grows up and talks?
Really? Do you remember
what your mom told you when you were two?
Why is it so fucking difficult
for you to follow Pablo’s orders?
Drop the gun.
Now!
You’re under arrest,
you son of a bitch.
Let him go!
—Put the gun down.
—You put yours down.
I don’t want to have to kill you.
I will.
So those fags
want to sit and negotiate.
Well …
we have to spend some time in jail, right?
So what the fuck.
You won, Pablo. They gave in.
But that faggot president has yet
to accept our most important demand
before we turn ourselves in.
Which demand is that?
It’s been a while
since we’ve been up here, right?
Yeah.
We used to come up here
with our girlfriends and smoke a joint.
What does that have to do with anything?
I know every centimetre
of these mountains.
From here,
we can see anything coming.
And we have enough space
to build whatever we want.
We’re going to design it …
we’re going to build it …
and we will be protected
from all our enemies.
—You want to build a jail?
—Not a jail, cousin.
A castle.