It has been seven months since Spain
began implementing European measures
of dealing with
the scarcity of basic resources.
The "Not Enough for All" plan
has begun to take effect,
but for now, Spain,
as well as its neighbors,
will be unable to sustain
dependent citizens
without balancing out the resources.
We...
- This way.
- See you at the trucks. Careful, okay?
- You! This way.
- Come on, quickly. Quiet!
- Come on. Move it. Go!
- Go. Run.
- Move it!
- Let's go, sweetheart.
Come on.
- Come on, hurry.
- What?
Move it!
Move!
This way, come on. Quick.
Let's go.
- This way.
- Come on.
This way.
Come on!
Mia, come on. No time to hang around.
Come on.
- You okay?
- No.
Move, dammit!
Go that way. You first.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Don't worry.
- Nico!
- Here. I'm here.
- I won't fit.
- Yes, you will. You will.
- Push me.
- Come on.
- Are you okay?
- What?
- Hide!
Follow me.
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart.
Stay still.
Come on.
This way. Let's go.
Attention! This is the police…
- Stop right there. You're under arrest…
- Come on.
Let's go.
Wait here.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
You, here.
Don't worry.
What's wrong?
The conditions have changed.
More risk, more money.
No. We don't have any more money.
That's not how it works.
Sweetheart, give me your ring.
- No.
- Yes.
- Listen to me.
Not the ring. We've given them everything.
- We need to leave the country now.
- Here.
Come on.
Come on. We don't have all night.
Follow me.
Enjoy your trip.
We're almost there.
There it is. Our cruise ship.
Move, dammit!
Come on.
- Are you okay?
- No.
We supported the fight against shortages.
We supported sacrifices
for the common good.
We accepted it when they told us
the measures would be temporary.
Now what? Look where they've driven us.
First, they got rid of the elderly
in order to fight the shortages.
Now, they're going after the children
and pregnant women. Don't you see?
Children and pregnant women! This regime…
Nothing else on?
- Take it off.
- Okay.
Let's see. Wow…
- It's okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Here.
Your baby had better shut up.
Where did you get this?
Tell me.
It's a secret.
Don't eat it now.
We have to save it for when we get there.
- To celebrate, right?
- Yeah.
Do you think the regime will get there?
Ireland has always opposed it.
Whatever.
All governments are falling for it.
- You know something about the Irish?
- What?
You can't defeat them. They drink stout.
- Right.
- Ireland won't give in.
It's okay to be scared, you know?
It'll be fine. You'll see.
- You don't know that.
- The worst is over.
You don't know that either.
I know something for a fact.
What?
I love you more now than yesterday…
…but less than tomorrow.
What is it? Have we arrived?
We're leaving.
No more games.
Do you think she's pregnant
and traveling alone?
If she's pregnant, she's not alone.
How's our little Noa doing?
You named her already?
Noa.
- What name would you like?
- I hope it's not a girl.
I mean it.
It's not a girl. It's a warrior.
She kicks, just like you do.
I can't feel her.
What?
It's been two days since I have…
felt her move.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I don't know.
What are you doing?
Haven't you noticed she always kicks here?
I think this is a foot.
How do you do it?
Do what?
I don't know, you seem fine, as if…
as if nothing's happened.
You know that's not true.
You know that, right?
You brought my ducky!
What's ducky saying?
- Nico.
- What?
What if she's alive,
and we're leaving her behind?
Alone…
She's gone.
They took her away.
She's dead.
Open the doors!
Hey!
Nico!
- Mia!
- Please!
Quickly!
- Get up here!
- Come on!
- Stop!
- Nico.
- Mia!
- Stop!
Relax. There are lots of people.
A truck's coming now.
Half of you, get out, okay?
Mia!
- Nico!
- Mia!
Come on!
I want you out!
You. Are you deaf?
Come on, get down.
No.
- I was inside with my wife. Inside.
- Get out!
Nico!
Come on, out!
No!
You! Go to that truck.
Nico…
No…
Let's go!
Nico.
Nico!
107. Green.
No! Wait!
- Mia!
- Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
- Okay. Nico…
- Yes?
- How will we find each other?
- Relax. I'm in the truck behind.
I don't wanna be alone.
I really don't wanna be alone.
No. Listen to me.
Don't trust anyone. Okay?
Keep your things safe. Your phone,
the food… Be careful, sweetheart.
Did you hear me?
Are you there? Mia! Please answer me.
Listen, are you sure
they're taking us to the same place?
Yes. As soon as they stop, I'll escape.
There's only one boat this week,
and it's ours.
- Nico…
- Yes?
I want to be with you.
Me too, sweetheart.
Everything will be okay. Don't worry.
It'll be okay. We'll talk later.
I'll call you later, okay?
Don't hang up on me.
Sweetheart… We have to save
all the battery we can.
- Don't hang up on me.
- We'll be together soon. You'll see.
- Nico…
- Yes?
- What is it, honey?
- Don't be long.
- I won't. I promise.
- Okay.
Quiet!
Murderers!
GIVE US OUR CHILDREN BACK
No…
MURDERERS!
THIS IS NOT THE WAY
What?
- What is it?
- We have to go to the back.
Be quiet.
Hello there.
Hello.
- Get out of the truck. Bring your papers.
- Is that necessary? I'm late.
- What are you carrying?
- It's all in the papers.
Alright.
- Can you come to the back?
- Yeah.
- That's all you're carrying?
You don't know what it is?
Not really. It's in the papers.
I know what's in there, but you don't.
You don't know what you're carrying.
I do a lot of runs…
Stop!
Is there a problem?
Here's another truck.
Keep going.
Go ahead.
Get him to pull over.
Can I go?
Are you in a hurry?
If I'm late, I get penalized.
Yeah, but I have to look inside.
Is it necessary? I hardly have anything.
Don't worry. I'll write your boss a note.
Travis, stand over there.
Now!
Okay.
Come on out.
Don't be afraid. We're not gonna hurt you.
Don't you want out?
I know the measures against shortages
have been brutal
towards children and pregnant women.
I know it's hard to trust someone
on this side of the wall.
But who have you trusted until now?
The people who stuffed you in here,
condemned you to suffocation,
and took all the money you had left?
Those who promised you a better place?
That better place does not exist.
Come out, and you won't regret it.
Otherwise, I have orders to shoot.
Don't make me give that order, dammit.
I've done it too many times.
Oh well, I tried.
Give me your hand.
Hey!
Give me your hand!
Kill them all.
Doggy!
Clean up all this shit
and gather their things.
All done, boss.
Good.
Nico.
Nico, hide.
Hide. They killed them all.
Hide. They killed them all. Hide.
Hi, it's Nico.
I can't talk right now. Try me later.
Nico.
I'm at the port. Where are you?
Where are you? Why won't you pick up?
Pick up.
This way, run!
Watch out! It's coming loose.
Help!
Tie it down!
Come with me.
Watch out! You're going to fall.
Please.
Hey!
Help!
I'm in here. Please!
Tie them down!
Help!
This way, come on! Run!
Please help!
It's coming loose.
Please!
Is anyone there?
I'm here! Please!
Hello?
Help.
What…
What?
No…
No way.
Come on.
Come on!
ENTER PIN NUMBER
INCORRECT PIN
Come on.
PIN BLOCKED
Fuck…
Headphones?
No.
No…
What?
Hey!
Green 107.
Nico, I'm here!
No!
Nico!
Nico! Hold on!
Hold on!
Hold on. Where is…
Here.
Nico! Wait!
I'm coming.
Nico!
Pick up the phone. I'm here!
Please!
Nico! No!
No! Please!
Please! No!
Hi, it's Nico.
I can't talk right now. Try me later.
What?
No…
No.
Hello.
No!
What's happening?
Come on.
Yes!
Seriously? More Tupperware?
Goddamn Tupperware! Fuck!
Okay.
DAY 2
MAXIMUM
Okay.
Hello?
No signal.
What?
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Mia, sweetheart.
- Nico?
- Yes!
Finally!
- Thank goodness!
- I didn't know if you were still alive.
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
- I couldn't call. The battery died.
- Okay.
The driver screwed us.
He abandoned us outside the city.
- It'll take a while for me to catch up.
- Listen to me.
- What is it?
- I'm trapped. I can't get out.
- I'm coming to get you.
- No, wait, Nico. Listen to me.
- I'm not…
- What is it?
- I'm not on the ship.
- What do you mean?
I'm not on the ship.
My container fell off.
- Where are you?
- Floating in the sea.
I'm floating. I don't know… I'm okay.
But I don't know how long before
the water rises and the container sinks.
Motherfucker! Can you see outside?
Yes, I can see outside,
and all I see is water.
- Nothing else?
- Nothing. I'm in the middle of the sea.
Say something, anything.
Don't worry, my love.
I promise I'm coming for you.
- You have to hang in there, sweetheart.
- Nico…
- Hang in there.
- I can't do it.
- Do it for the baby.
- I don't think I can.
- Yes, you can.
- I miss her so much, Nico.
- No.
- I messed up again.
Not that. Not now. It wasn't your fault.
Do you hear me?
What happened to Uma wasn't your fault.
Okay.
You're the strongest person I've ever met.
Don't give up. Promise me?
- Yes.
- Mia…
Yes?
- I love you more than yesterday.
- But less than you will tomorrow.
I'll call as soon as I have a plan.
Keep the phone safe.
- Okay, bye.
- I'll find you.
Dad's on his way.
Hold on.
Not now.
Hold on a little longer.
What…
No.
Hold on a little longer, please.
Please, don't fucking do this.
Please, not now.
I asked you to wait!
Nico!
No!
What? Come on.
Come on.
Please, breathe.
Please.
Please, come on. Come on, breathe.
Breathe.
No, please!
DAY 2
DAY 3
Hey there, baby girl. Hey.
What is it?
Want me to change your diaper?
Okay, okay.
Okay, sweetie.
You have to eat, sweetie.
Come on.
Please, come on.
Come on, sweetie. Why won't you eat?
Come on, please.
Come on.
You have to eat, sweetie.
Okay.
It's okay, sweetie.
But I need to eat.
For fuck's sake.
Shit.
There, there.
Come on.
Come on, eat. Come on.
Why won't you eat?
Okay.
Listen to me. Listen.
You have to eat,
and I have to take care of you.
We'll get out of here. I promise.
Please, sweetheart. Come on.
Okay, enough!
Let me do this.
I have to do it to get out.
And to get help. Enough!
Please, enough. Be patient.
Okay.
I'm coming. Coming, sweetheart.
Coming. Okay. Don't cry, sweetheart.
Baby girl. It's okay.
You have to eat.
Did anyone ever tell you…
Come on.
Stop!
Stop! Please, stop!
You have to eat! You're going to die!
Do you want to die?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry.
It's not your fault. I'm sorry.
I know. I'm sorry.
Sweetheart…
Come here, sweetie.
Come here. Come to Mom.
Let's try this.
Let's try this, okay?
Let's see.
Here.
My good girl.
Good girl.
Come on. Almost there.
What?
What is it?
Please.
Come on.
What is it?
No.
No…
Come on!
Please, come on.
Come on.
No!
It's okay.
You're hot, right? Yes.
That's better.
That's better, sweetheart.
I'm here.
I'm right here.
It's okay.
Hush.
Go away!
It's okay.
I'm here.
It's gone.
DAY 5
DAY 6
Uma, sweetheart.
Please, come.
Come closer. Come. Let me see you.
Hello.
Let's leave, please.
Uma, I've missed you so much.
Why did you let them take me?
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I just wanted to play with the airplane.
I'm sorry. I messed up.
Uma.
Don't go.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I messed up.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't your fault, sweetheart.
I'll get you out of here, okay?
Okay.
Look.
This is the sea.
The sun and the sea.
And the sky.
And way over there is where we're going.
You feel better outside, right?
Yes, you're much happier
because you're in the sun and fresh air.
Let's see.
Come.
Come here.
Here… Come on.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'm…
I can't.
Don't worry.
Come on.
Come on. Come.
Come here, fishy.
Come.
Come!
Don't look at me like that.
You were desperate for a feed too.
MAXIMUM
DAY 9
Such a good girl. Good girl.
Hi, sweetheart.
Where are you?
Call me!
DAY 12
Look, that's me.
At school.
With the kids.
Did I tell you I was a teacher?
This is your dad.
His name's Nico.
Here he is, in the store.
Look how happy he is.
We had to close the store down
because supplies got so scarce.
In the end, we had nothing to sell.
But people still went in to see him.
That's why I know
he'll find a way to get us out of here.
Because…
he always thinks of something.
This is your grandma, Noa.
What do you think of that name? Noa.
I think it's nice.
It means "long life." It's also…
the feminine of Noah.
Noah's ark. They got there.
They were saved. They got to shore.
It's an animal story.
I'll tell you all about it.
This is Uma.
You want to hear about her, right?
You have the same eyes as her.
Exactly the same.
The same face when she was little.
She wanted to be a pilot.
An airplane pilot.
She'd say, "Airplane pilot."
You two would have got on well.
What happened was…
When the regime took over,
she and I had to lock ourselves in.
Dad would go out to get food.
The thing is time went by, and…
Uma wanted to go out because…
A little girl
can't be locked up for that long.
At home, there wasn't…
There wasn't much space.
So…
She kept asking me, on and on.
And one day we went out.
It was only for five minutes,
but they took her away.
It was my fault.
I messed up.
What is it? Are you okay?
You're frozen.
Okay.
You're so cute with my hat.
It suits you.
You'll be better tomorrow, okay?
Wrapped up.
All wrapped up.
Did anyone ever tell you
That no dream
Has time or space?
No possessor
No one
It's okay.
DAY 12
No…
MAXIMUM
Nico!
Come on, please.
Please, please.
- Nico!
- Mia!
- Can you hear me?
- Yes, finally.
Finally, sweetheart.
I couldn't call you. There was no signal.
My phone is broken. The screen is broken…
- Where are you?
- Listen to me.
What's wrong, Nico?
I can't come to rescue you.
You have to do it alone.
Promise me you'll do it. Promise me.
Nico, what is it?
Please, don't scare me.
Sweetheart, what is it?
I'm…
Nico…
I'm hidden in a container.
I got into a speedboat, but…
they found me, and…
I managed to get away, but they shot me.
Are you hurt?
I'm losing a lot of blood.
What?
Sweetheart…
I just wanted to say goodbye.
I promise you I tried.
I tried as hard as I could.
I promise. I'm sorry.
You were right. You always are. I was…
too optimistic.
It wasn't a good idea to go.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
- No, Nico, listen.
- I'm so sorry, sweetheart.
Listen to me.
You saved us both.
- Do you hear me?
- What?
You both?
Yes, sweetheart, she's here.
She was born. She's here with me.
She's so beautiful.
- She's beautiful?
- Yes.
A little girl, right? I knew it.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, we're fine.
- We're fine.
- I wish I was there.
You are here, Nico.
You're here. You were always here.
You were at the birth.
You were there
when I opened the container.
Nico, I promised you I'd fight,
and I fought. I swear I fought.
You're there when I sing to her.
You're always here with me.
What? You sing?
Yes.
My love… What's she like?
She's just like you. She's beautiful.
Strong and funny and she makes me laugh.
She looks after me. Just like you.
What am I saying? She's right here.
I'm going to put the phone close
so she can hear you.
- Okay.
- Sweetheart…
The voice you're going to hear
is your dad's. Talk to him.
Hello, Princess. It's Dad.
That guy who used to squeeze your foot
when you were in Mom's tummy.
Listen, my love…
I have to tell you a secret.
If things ever get complicated,
close your eyes
and snuggle up to your mom.
You'll see it's the best place to be.
Always.
Did you hear her? She's so clever.
Her name's Noa.
Noa?
Are you sure?
She looks a lot like a Noa.
I can't think of a better name.
Nico…
What?
Nico, I love you more than yesterday.
But less than tomorrow.
DAY 18
DAY 15
DAY 20
DAY 23
MAXIMUM
DAY 26
DAY 14
I'M SICK OF EATING FISH
DAY 20
SHE'S BEEN SLEEPING ALL DAY
DAY 24
I CAN'T STOP THE WATER
I HAVE TO LIVE UP TOP
Hush.
Noa!
A seagull!
Do you know what that means?
MAXIMUM
Okay.
What?
No!
Okay.
No.
No fucking way.
No!
Noa!
No, please.
Noa! No!
Noa!
I'm coming!
I'm here, sweetheart.
Not long now.
A little longer. We're almost there.
I know we're almost there.
We need to hold on a little longer.
Just a little longer.
We have to tell our story.
I know they won't believe us.
But we know it's true.
We know we fought, right?
We did all we could, right?
You saved me, sweetheart.
You saved my life.
Forgive me.
I was so scared.
But you made me strong.
I did all I could, right?
Right?
I did everything I could, right?
I did everything I could.
Everything I could.
My daughter? My daughter.
No, don't take it off.
Subtitle translation by: Winifred Donlon