- [LIGHT GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
- [RADIO TUNING IN]
ANNOUNCER: It has now been seven months
since Spain
began applying European measures
to tackle the shortage of basic resources.
The plan, called ''Not Enough for All,"
has started to produce results.
But for now, Spain,
as well as its neighboring countries,
won't be able
to sustain dependent citizens until--
[RADIO SHUTS OFF]
Get to your positions.
Come on. Same as last time.
- Let's do this.
- MAN #1: Let's go.
Meet back at the trucks.
Be careful, okay?
- Let's go. Quickly and quietly.
- Run fast.
MAN #2: Bring your things. Hurry. Come on.
Come on. Move it. Move it. Go, go, go.
- Come on. Come on, quickly.
- Come on, Mia. Let's go.
- MAN #2: Hurry up. Quickly.
- Where?
MAN #3: This way.
[WHISPERED CHATTER]
Move it.
You two, follow me.
This way, guys. Come on!
This way.
- Faster.
- [MAN #4 SPEAKING SPANISH]
MAN #2: Faster. Move it.
- [WOMAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
- MAN #2: Come on. Let's go.
- You okay?
- MIA: No.
Don't stop.
Let's go.
[SNARLING]
[BARKING]
That way.
Let's go. Come on. Move. You first.
- Okay.
- [DOGS CONTINUE BARKING]
[MIA BREATHES QUICKLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
[HELICOPTERS RUMBLE OVERHEAD]
- MIA: Nico.
- NICO: I'm here.
- I don't fit. Fuck, I don't fit!
- NICO: You can do it.
- Push me.
- NICO: Okay.
- [MIA STRUGGLES]
- NICO: Sorry.
- Are you okay? Yeah, you're okay.
- MIA: What?
- [HELICOPTER RUMBLES]
- MAN #2: Back up!
Let's go.
Come on.
Follow me.
Hold my hand.
Come on.
NICO: Let's go, love.
MAN #2: Stay back, don't move.
Now!
Through here.
Almost there.
[OVER MEGAPHONE] MAN #2: Attention!
Put your hands in the air!
- Stay where you are.
- [WOMAN WHIMPERS]
This is the police.
You are under arrest.
Give me the money.
You wait here.
- Are you okay?
- MIA: Okay.
[EXHALES]
Didn't tell me about these two.
Bring 'em over.
You, here.
It's fine.
- Is anything wrong?
- The conditions are riskier than expected.
I need more money.
No, no, no.
We don't have any more money.
I see how this works.
- Babe, give me your ring.
- MIA: No.
- Yes. You've got to.
- No. We gave them everything. Not my ring!
Mia, we've got to leave now.
Take it.
Come on.
Come on. We don't have all night.
Move it.
Good.
This way.
Safe travels.
NICO: We're gonna make it.
There it is.
Our luxury liner.
Move it, asshole!
- Come on.
- MAN #6: Let's go!
MAN #7: Now!
[MUSIC SWELLS]
MAN #8: Step to the back.
- Are you okay?
- No.
[MUSIC CRESCENDOS AND FADES]
[FLASHLIGHT CLICKS]
WOMAN #1: There's no food!
MAN #1: We accepted
the discourse about shortages.
We accepted that we had to make sacrifices
for the common good.
We accepted
that measures would be temporary.
But what now?
Look how far they've pushed us.
First, they exterminated the elderly
to deal with the shortages.
Now they're targeting
pregnant women and kids.
Don't you see it?
Pregnant women and kids!
The regime isn't ending shortages.
Is there anything else on?
MAN #1: There are alternatives
to this massacre.
Countries like Ireland,
Iceland, and Norway have managed to stop...
- NICO: Yeah, take it off.
- MIA: Okay.
MAN #1: Our country
must follow their example and help...
[MIA SIGHS]
NICO: Let me see.
Wow.
[CHUCKLES]
That's better.
- Okay? Here.
- Yeah.
[BABY CRIES]
WOMAN #2: Make him shut up.
[SHUSHES]
MIA: Where'd you get this?
Ah...
MIA: Tell me.
It's a secret.
Let's not have it now.
Let's save it
and eat it when we get there.
- To celebrate, right?
- Exactly.
[NICO SIGHS]
Do you think the regime will go there too?
Ireland has ruled in opposition to it.
Doesn't matter.
Governments are falling everywhere.
- I'll tell you something about the Irish.
- What?
It's impossible to overthrow them.
- They drink dark beer.
- Right.
Ireland won't give in.
You're allowed to be afraid, you know.
Everything will work out, you'll see.
Hmm.
- You don't know for sure.
- The worst part is over.
You don't know that.
There's one thing I do know.
MIA: What?
That I love you more than yesterday.
But less than tomorrow.
[DRILLING SOUNDS]
[TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
What's happening?
Are we there?
- [BRAKES HISS]
- [TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
We're leaving.
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- WOMAN #2: Turn off the games.
[WHISPERS] Do you think she's pregnant?
She's all alone.
If she's pregnant, she's not alone.
How's our little Noa doing?
I didn't know we decided yet.
- Noa.
- [SIGHS]
- What do you wanna name her?
- I hope it isn't a girl.
I mean it.
Well, I think she's a girl, a warrior.
Just like her mother.
I don't feel her.
What?
She hasn't kicked me in two days.
[SIGHS]
That's not good.
Why didn't you tell me?
Dunno.
What are you doing?
Haven't you noticed?
She always pushes right here.
I think this is a foot.
How do you do it?
What?
Act like everything's fine.
Like nothing's happened to us.
You know that's not true.
- You know, don't you?
- Mm-hmm.
[BABY CRIES]
[SQUEAKING SOUND]
GIRL: You brought my duck!
Hi, there.
What's wrong?
[WOMEN #3 SHUSHES]
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
No, no, no.
Don't cry.
- MAN #2: What does the duck say?
- WOMAN #3: Shh. Don't cry. You're okay.
- Shh.
- Nico.
NICO: Yeah?
What if she's alive,
and we're leaving her behind?
All alone.
She's not alive.
They took her away,
and they killed her.
MIA: Hmm.
- [TRUCK RUMBLES]
- [BRAKES HISS]
- [MAN WHISTLES]
- [GASPS]
- [PEOPLE ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
- [THUDDING]
- [CLAMORING]
- NICO: Hey! Hey! Hey!
MIA: Nico! Nico!
- [GRUNTS]
- Mia!
Come on, now!
Hurry up! Move it!
Move it! Get in there now! Come on!
What are you doin'?
Stop. There's too many. Back out!
- Nico! Nico!
- Mia!
- [GASPS]
- Listen up! There's too many of you.
There's another truck coming.
- Half of you get out. Now!
- You heard him! It's too full.
- Get some of 'em out!
- MAN #3: Come on! Come on! Get outta here!
Mia! Mia! Mia!
- Nico!
- MAN #4: Get out!
- Wait! Mia!
- Come on, keep moving. Hey, you!
- [GRUNTS]
- You can't stay!
Hey. Are you deaf or what?
Get off the truck.
No, no.
I was on this one, with my wife!
- Get out!
[GRUNTS]
- MIA: Nico!
- MAN #4: The rest move back.
- Stay back!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no! Please! No!
[GASPING IN DISBELIEF]
No. No, no, no.
Nico. No, no, no.
[GASPING]
Keep moving! Come on! To the back!
MIA: Nico. Nico.
[SOBS]
Nico.
No.
Nico, Nico.
One-zero-seven green.
- [TRUCK ENGINE REVVING]
- No. No, please. Wait, wait, wait.
[LINE RINGS]
- NICO: Mia.
- Babe, are you all right?
[PANTS]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- Okay, Nico.
- Yeah?
- How will we find each other again?
- We're okay. My truck is behind yours.
- I can't do this alone.
- What?
No, no.
I can't do it alone, I really can't.
Listen to me. You can't trust anyone.
Understand? Keep your things tucked away.
Be careful, my love.
MIA: Yeah.
[SNIFFLES]
- Did you hear me?
- [HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Mia, are you there?
Mia!
Nico, listen to me.
Are you sure they're taking us
to the same location?
Yes, and when they stop, I'll escape.
Our ship is the only one
setting sail this week.
- Nico.
- Yes?
I wanna be with you.
Me too.
I love you, Mia.
Don't worry,
everything's gonna be all right.
- Okay.
- We're gonna be okay.
- We'll talk soon, all right?
Don't go yet, don't hang up.
Love, we can't waste our batteries.
Please don't hang up yet.
We'll be together again soon, you'll see.
- Nico.
- Yeah?
Come soon.
I will.
As soon as I can.
Okay.
[INDISTINCT OUTSIDE CHATTER]
MAN: What makes you think
you're better than us?
[AIR RAID SIREN BLARES]
[CARS HONK]
[ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [BULLETS WHIZZING]
[WOMAN #2 SHUSHES]
Little girl, be quiet.
GIVE US OUR CHILDREN BACK
No, please, no!
No...
[HAUNTING MUSIC PLAYS]
MURDERERS!
THIS IS NOT THE WAY
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[IMPERCEPTIBLE]
[WHIMPERS]
[BABY CRIES]
- [BRAKES HISS]
- [GRUNTS]
[WHISPERS]
What's going on?
Hey.
- What's going on?
- [WHISPERS] Move to the back.
Don't talk.
[WOMAN #2 SHUSHES]
[BRAKES HISSING]
COP #1: How you doin'?
DRIVER: Good, thanks.
COP #1: Step outside.
Bring your documents.
DRIVER: Do I have to get out?
- COP #2: Transporting?
- DRIVER: Behind schedule.
COP #1: Very good.
Come with me to the back, please.
DRIVER: Uh, sure.
[MIA GASPS]
COP #1: This is the entire load?
Yes.
You can't tell me what you're moving?
DRIVER: Small load.
All in the manifest.
COP #1: I know what it says.
Problem is you don't.
DRIVER: Look, it's been a long week.
I log a lot of miles.
- Lots of shipments.
- [DOG WHIMPERS]
COP #3: Stop!
DRIVER: Is there a problem?
Another one's pullin' in.
He can park there.
Am I clear?
You in a rush?
Uh, it's just if-- if I'm late,
I'll be penalized.
Well, I'm required
to check inside the truck.
But is that necessary?
I'm barely carrying anything.
COP #1: Don't worry about it.
I'll write you a note.
[DOORS THUD]
[CLICKS FLASHLIGHT]
[COP #1 WHISTLING TUNE]
[HUSHED BREATHING]
Travis, back here.
[HUSHED BREATHING CONTINUES]
Do it!
- [GASPING]
- [WHIMPERING]
[BULLET RICOCHETS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
COP #1: Great, thank you.
Well done.
You can come out now.
Don't be afraid.
We won't hurt you.
[BABY FUSSING]
COP #1: You won't come out?
I know that the austerity measures
have been cruel.
They're especially hard
on women and children.
I understand
if you don't think you can trust me.
It's hard to know
who to trust, right? Hmm?
Not those who forced you
into this container.
They stuffed you in here
with barely enough air to breathe
and robbed you
of all the money you had left.
And they promised you...
[CHUCKLES]
...you could have a better life
in a better place.
They lied.
A better place doesn't exist.
So you should come out.
Because if you don't,
I'll have to shoot.
Damn it. Don't make me give that order.
I've had to give it so many times.
I can save your lives.
Well, I tried.
[SIGHS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[COP #1 TSK-TSKS]
Come.
Take my hand.
Hey! Good for you!
- [SCREAMING]
- Come on up! Take my hand!
All right, boys.
You know what to do.
[STIFLES SCREAM]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOG YIPS, WHINES]
Puppy!
[CHUCKLES]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [TOY SQUEAKS]
- [GASPS]
Get the bodies out of here
and get rid of all their shit.
[WALL PANEL MOVES]
COP #3: Take this one.
COP #2: Good enough. Let's go.
- All good, boss.
- COP #1: Great.
[DOOR THUDS CLOSED]
[SOBBING]
[SAD MUSIC PLAYS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
Nico. You've gotta hide.
Hide, Nico.
They killed everyone.
You've gotta hide.
They're gonna kill you. Hide, Nico.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[BRAKES HISS]
[OBJECT THUDS HEAVILY]
[MECHANISM WHIRRING, CLICKING]
[THUDS LOUDLY]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[LINE RINGS]
Hello, this is Nico.
I can't talk now, but try me again later.
[LINE HANGS UP]
- [SNIFFLING]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
Nico.
I'm okay and I'm at the port.
Where are you?
Why don't you pick up?
Just call me.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[FOGHORN BLARING]
- [HORN CONTINUES]
- [SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[SNIFFS DEEPLY]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [GASPS]
- [GROANING]
- [METAL CREAKING]
[WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH]
[GASPS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- MAN: Watch out, it's gonna come loose.
- MIA: Help!
[GROANS]
I need help!
[YELPS]
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
- MAN: Come on, let's go!
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS DESPERATELY]
MAN: It's gonna fall!
Watch out!
Please help!
- Hey! Hey! I'm in here!
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Let me out!
Please, I'm here!
Hey!
I'm in here!
[GROANS]
[WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH]
Help!
- Help!
- MAN: It's going to fall!
Please, help me!
- MAN: Is somebody there?
- Yes, I'm here! Help me, please!
- [SCREAMS]
- [SOUNDS FADE]
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS]
[WAVES LAPPING GENTLY]
[GASPS]
[GROANS WEAKLY]
[GROANS]
God.
[GROANING SOFTLY]
Help.
[SIGHS]
[METAL CREAKS]
[MIA GROANS]
- [METAL CREAKS]
- [MIA GASPS]
MIA: What?
[GENTLE GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
No, no, no, no. No.
No way.
[GASPING FEARFULLY]
MIA: Please.
Please.
Aw, come on.
[GROANS IN FRUSTRATION]
ENTER PIN NUMBER
[PHONE BEEPS]
[BEEPING]
INCORRECT PIN
PIN BLOCKED
- [METAL CREAKS]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[OMINOUS GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
[WAVES SPLASHING OUTSIDE]
Okay.
[GRUNTS]
Fuck.
Shit.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
[SIGHS]
[STRAINS]
Oh, no.
[INDISTINCT VOICES ECHOING]
[INDISTINCT VOICES SCREAMING]
What?
Hey!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Nico, I'm over here!
Nico!
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- Over here!
No, no, no!
Hey!
Nico!
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- Nico!
Nico!
Where are you?
Hang on! Just hang on! Wait.
Okay.
Nico!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Wait!
Wait.
Wait!
[LINE RINGS]
Nico!
It's me.
Come on, answer the phone.
Please, answer me.
No, no, no, no.
- No!
- [LINE RINGING]
No! Please, I'm here!
No!
Hello, this is Nico.
I can't talk now, but try me again later.
[LINE HANGS UP]
[GASPING]
[WHIMPERS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[SOBBING]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- [LINE RINGS]
Hello, this is Nico.
I can't talk now, but try me again later.
[LINE HANGS UP]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- [LINE RINGS]
Hello, this is Nico.
I can't talk now, but try me again later.
[LINE HANGS UP]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
- [LINE RINGS]
Hello, this is Nico.
I can't talk now, but try me again later.
[LINE HANGS UP]
[SNIFFLES]
[GROANS]
Huh.
Huh?
Are you there?
[MIA GASPS]
No.
[HEARTFELT STRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
Hi.
- [WHALE CALLS]
- [GASPS]
[CALL CONTINUES]
[WOOD CREAKING]
[THUD]
[CREAKING LOUDER]
[GASPS]
[TOYS SQUEAKING]
No! What?
What's happening?
[GASPS IN FEAR]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STRAINING]
[SCREAMS]
[SHOUTS]
[GASPING]
Okay.
[CRATE CREAKING]
[STRAINS]
Come on.
[STRAINING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUDS LOUDLY]
[GASPS]
Come on!
[GRUNTS HAPPILY]
[CREAKING]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
Really?
More Tupperware?
Fucking Tupperware!
Shit.
[DRAMATIC PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Brilliant.
[PIANO MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[GRUNTS]
DAY 2
MAXIMUM
All right.
[LINE RINGS]
Hello?
[NO CONNECTION SIGNAL]
MIA: No signal.
[PIANO MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGS]
MIA: What? Oh!
UNKNOWN NUMBER
- NICO: Mia. Mia, sweetheart.
- Nico?
- Yes.
- [LAUGHING] Oh! Oh!
Oh my God!
Thank God!
Nico, I didn't think you were alive.
Love, are you okay?
I'm sorry I couldn't call.
My battery ran out.
The driver fucked us over.
He left us outside the city limits.
It'll take a few days to catch up.
No. Listen to me.
Something's happening to me, Nico.
- What's wrong?
- I'm trapped in here and I can't get out.
I'm coming to you.
I'm coming. I'll be there soon.
No, no, no. You've gotta listen to me.
I'm not... You won't...
What?
What's going on?
I'm not on the boat.
- What do you mean?
- I'm not on the boat.
- My container's in the ocean.
- Wait. Your-- What? Where are you?
I don't know. I'm floating in the ocean.
I'm drifting. I don't know where.
I'm okay for now,
but the water's seeping in.
Oh my God, Mia.
Can you see anything outside?
Yes, I can see, but all there is is water.
There's just water.
- There's nothing else?
- Nothing. Just water.
- I'm in the middle of the ocean, Nico.
- Fuck!
Say something.
I'm scared.
Just don't worry, Mia.
I'll rescue you. I promise.
- Nico...
- Just try to hang in there.
- I'm trying, but I...
- Do it for the baby.
I don't think I can do this much longer.
- You can do it.
- I just miss her so much, Nico.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
- My love, don't do this. Not now.
- I messed up again.
It's not your fault.
Do you understand?
What happened to Uma was not your fault.
- Sweetheart.
- It wasn't?
You're the strongest person
I've ever known.
- Promise you won't give up?
- Yes.
- Mia...
- Yeah?
I love you more than yesterday.
But less than tomorrow.
I will call you
as soon as I figure out a plan.
- Find me. Bye.
- Don't lose your phone.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDING]
[GROANING]
Oh no, no, no, no, no. Not now.
Not now. Don't do this right now.
Just wait.
Help Mommy and wait.
Daddy's on his way.
Wait for Daddy to come.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[THUNDER CLAPS]
- [GROANING]
- [WATER DRIPPING]
No. No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, please wait. Wait a bit longer.
Please wait, please wait a little longer.
- [SCREAMS]
- [THUNDER CRASHING]
[SHOUTING]
I wanted you to wait!
[GROANING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Nico!
No!
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Ah! No, no, no!
[SCREAMS]
No!
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS IN FEAR]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
What? Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Breathe, please. Please.
Come on.
Come on, breathe.
Breathe. Breathe.
[GROANS IN PANIC]
Oh please, breathe.
- [NOA CRYING]
- [MIA GASPS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KISSES]
- [NOA CONTINUES CRYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[NOA CRYING]
[MIA SOFTLY]
Mm-hmm.
[MIA SHUSHES]
[NOA COOING]
[MIA GRUNTS]
Oh!
[NOA COOS]
[NOA FUSSING]
[SHUSHING GENTLY]
DAY 2
DAY 3
[CRYING]
MIA: Honey. Sweetie.
What's wrong?
Want a fresh diaper?
Yes?
[GRUNTS]
All right, all right.
It's okay. I can hear you.
You're so loud.
I know, I know.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Okay, it's coming. That's right. Hang on.
It's coming.
Come on, sweetie.
I know you're hungry.
Come on, lovie.
You're hungry, but you won't eat.
It's okay.
[SHUSHES, KISSES] Okay, okay, okay.
Everything's all right.
Mommy needs to eat too.
Mm...
No fucking way.
Fuck.
[NOA CRIES]
Yes, I know, I know, it's okay.
[SHUSHES]
All right.
Come on.
Honey, why won't you eat?
Okay...
Hey, listen, listen, listen, listen.
Your job is to eat,
and my job is to take care of you, okay?
We're gonna get out of here, promise.
Please don't be so sad, honey.
[SNIFFLES]
[NOA'S CRIES FADE]
[NOA CRYING]
Hey! That's enough now!
I have to do this so we can get out
of here and get some help. Okay?
Be quiet and let me work!
Try to be patient for me, please.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
Okay.
I'm coming.
Okay, my love.
I'm here.
Honey, it's okay.
Okay.
You're starving.
Honey...
[HUMS]
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on. Come on.
- [NOA WAILING]
- Be quiet! Stop! Stop this! Enough!
You have to eat or you will die!
You wanna die?
Huh?
Is that what you want?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, baby.
Mommy loves you.
I'm sorry. Forgive me. I didn't mean it.
I'm gonna take care of you.
I know, I know.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right.
[NOA CRIES QUIETLY]
[GASPS]
[NOA CRIES NORMALLY]
Come here, my little warrior.
Let's try again.
Okay?
Still hungry?
I know, and we're gonna try again.
You've been waiting for so long.
I'm sorry it took so long.
I know, I know, I know.
Ready?
Here we go, sweetheart.
That's it.
Latch on for Mommy.
[GASPS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[NOA FUSSES]
Keep drinking for Mommy.
Mommy's milk came.
Finally.
That's right.
[SHUSHES]
Good girl.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[FUSSING SOFTLY]
[MIA SHUSHES]
Mm...
Mm.
[MOANING SOFTLY]
[NOA COOS]
[STOMACH GURGLING]
[GROANS]
Come on!
[SIGHS]
[DRILL WHIRRING]
[GROANS]
All right.
Almost there.
Huh?
What's going on?
- [NOA FUSSES]
- No. Come on!
Please work.
Let's go.
Come on!
No.
No!
[GROANS WEAKLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
No...
[EXHALES]
[NOA FUSSING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[MIA SIGHS]
Yes!
Come on.
No.
Please work.
Come on, work!
Come back!
Please!
Don't do this to me!
Ugh! Come on!
No! No. no. no. Hey!
Ugh.
No!
- [SCREAMING]
- [NOA CRYING]
[NOA CRIES]
- [NOA CONTINUES CRYING]
- [MIA SHUSHES]
It's all right.
It's all right, sweetie. I know.
That's better, isn't it?
Shh, there, that's better.
Much, much better.
[MOANING SOFTLY]
[MIA'S STOMACH GURGLING]
MIA: Mm...
[GURGLING CONTINUES]
Hm...
Mm...
[GASPING]
Eh...
[SNIFFS]
- [MUNCHING]
- [MOANING SOFTLY]
[WHALE CALLING]
[NOA CRYING]
[GASPS]
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
[GASPS] Don't cry. It's okay.
I'm here, sweetie. Mommy's here.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
[SHUSHING]
Don't be afraid.
It's okay, it's okay.
[WHALE CALLS]
Okay.
[LOUD CRASH]
- [WHALE CALLS]
- [SCREAMING]
Go away!
Get outta here!
- [NOA CRYING]
- [WHALE CALL FADES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
It's gone.
I've got you.
I'm here.
It's gone.
DAY 6
[NOA CRYING]
[KNIFE RASPING ON METAL]
Huh?
[WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[BUZZES]
[MIA GRUMBLES]
[MOANS]
[MIA SHUSHES]
[NOA'S COOS DISTORTING]
[SOUNDS DISTORTING]
[WATER BUBBLING]
[NOA'S CRIES FADE]
[EXHALES]
[MOANING SOFTLY]
Mm.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[RETCHING]
[HAUNTING MUSIC PLAYS]
[MOANS SOFTLY]
[NOA CRIES IN THE DISTANCE]
- UMA: Mommy?
- Uma, my darling.
Uma, please come here.
Come closer. Please.
I wanna see you.
[HAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hi, honey.
Mommy, can we go home now, please?
I miss you so much, Uma.
Mommy, why did you let them take me away?
I'm sorry.
[UMA SOBS]
It was my fault.
I just wanted to play with the airplane.
I know, it was a mistake.
[WHISPERS]
No, stay.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I messed up.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
[WATER PATTERING]
[NOA CRIES]
[PLEASANT GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
MIA: Mommy will get you out of here, okay?
[GUITAR MUSIC CONTINUES]
[METAL CREAKING]
[GROANS]
[STRAINING]
- [GROWLS]
- [MUSIC SWELLS]
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
[COOING]
[SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sweetheart.
Look at the world.
Up above is the sky.
Down below is the sea.
And very far over there
is where we're going.
Nico, where are you?
Feels good to be outside, right?
Yeah, you seem much happier.
You like the sun and fresh air.
[GASPS]
This way.
Over here.
Here.
Come on. Over here.
This way.
[EXCITING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS WEAKLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
Here.
I'm here.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS IMPATIENTLY]
[GROANING]
[NOA FUSSING]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
[EXHALES]
Shh! It's okay, my love.
I'm here. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here.
[SCREAMS]
- [GROANING]
- [NOA CRYING]
[GROANING WEAKLY]
[GROANS]
Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God.
[INHALES]
[EXHALES]
I've got this.
[GROANS]
[NOA COOS IN THE DISTANCE]
[COOS]
- [NOA CRIES]
- Oh.
Don't worry, sweetie.
[GROANS]
[SHUDDERING]
[MIA HUMMING MELODY]
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come, come, come, come.
Come on.
[GASPS]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't give me that look. I'm desperate.
You know what it feels like.
MAXIMUM
DAY 9
[STIRRING GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOA CRIES]
MIA: Good job.
You're Mommy's big girl.
It's mini bath time.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are you? Where are you?
Call me. Come on, Nico. Call me.
Call me, please.
Call me!
DAY 12
[MUSIC FADES]
MIA: Look, this is me.
At school.
With one of my students.
Did I tell you I'm a teacher?
This is your daddy.
His name's Nico.
He's at work, in our store.
We were forced to close the store
because there wasn't much food to sell.
At the end, there wasn't anything at all.
But people came to visit him anyway.
Because he cared about them.
I know he'll find a way
to get us out of here
because...
he always knows what to do.
[SNIFFS]
This is your grandma, Noa.
Do you like that name?
Noa.
I think it's beautiful.
It means "long life." Spelled with an H.
But it's prettier without it.
In Noah's Ark, that's a story,
they survived and got to land.
There are animals in it.
I'll read it to you some day.
This is Uma.
You wanna know about her, don't you?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS]
Well, you know,
you have the same eyes as she did.
Exactly.
And when she was a baby,
the shape of her face was just like yours.
She wanted to be an airplane pilot.
She liked to say "airplane pilot."
You would've had fun with her.
What happened is that when...
[SHUDDERS]
...when the regime took over,
we were forced to lock ourselves
inside the house.
And your daddy would go out
to get us food.
At first, it was fine,
but as time went on...
Uma wanted to go outside because...
because a girl can't stand
being locked up for too long
in her house, you know.
There wasn't enough room to play,
so one day,
she kept begging me
and insisting we go out.
And, um,
I said, "Okay."
We were only outside five minutes,
but they took her.
It was all my fault.
I should've known better.
I messed up.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES]
[NOA COUGHS]
- [NOA CRIES]
- MIA: What's wrong?
- [COUGHS]
- What's wrong? Are you okay?
- You're freezing.
- [WAILING]
There we are.
You're snug as a bug in a rug like that.
My beanie looks cute on you.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You'll feel much better tomorrow, okay?
You're all bundled up.
Warm and cozy.
[HUMS MELODY]
♪ Has anybody said to you ♪
♪ Dreams that you dream ♪
♪ Live outside of space or time ♪
♪ And only in your mind? ♪
♪ La la ♪
[CHOIR SINGS]
♪ La la, la la, la la ♪
ont color="#ca004c">["NANA (CAP.9: CONCEPCIÓN)" BY ROSALÍA PLAYS]
[THUD ON WOOD]
[SONG FADES]
[THUDDING CONTINUES]
[SHUSHES] Sweet pea.
All right. I got you.
[THUDDING CONTINUES]
DAY 12
- MIA: No, no, no.
- [THUDDING CONTINUES]
MAXIMUM
[THUDDING CONTINUES]
[SHUSHES, GROANS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Nico!
Oh, come on, come on, connect.
Please, come on.
Please work.
Come on, connect. Connect.
[YELPS]
Nico.
- NICO: Mia.
- Can you hear me?
- [LAUGHS] Uh, yes, at last.
- It's finally you, my love.
I'm so sorry I couldn't call you.
I didn't have a signal.
And my cell is broken.
No, no, I mean the screen is broken.
Where are you?
- Listen to me, please, my love.
- What's wrong, Nico?
[NICO SIGHS]
I won't be able to come for you.
You'll have to make it on your own.
Promise me you will.
Promise.
- Nico, what's wrong?
- [NICO SNIFFS]
- Please, Nico. I'm scared. What's wrong?
- [NICO COUGHING]
My love, tell me.
[NICO GULPS AIR]
[NICO PANTING]
- Nico...
- I'm... I'm hiding in a container.
I snuck onto a ship, but they found me.
And when I ran, they shot me.
Are you hurt?
I'm losing so much blood.
- What?
- My love...
[NICO SNIFFLES]
- Honey?
- I just... I just wanted to say goodbye.
[NICO SOBS]
And I want you to know that I fought hard.
I fought hard.
As hard as I could.
I promise I did.
[SNIFFLES]
And... you were right.
You were always right.
I'm too optimistic.
We should've stayed.
[NICO SOBBING]
- No. No. Nico, listen to me.
- I'm sorry.
- Listen to me, Nico.
- So sorry.
Please, my love, listen to me.
- You saved our lives.
- How?
- Understand?
- How? You said "our lives"?
Yes, my love, she's here.
[NICO GASPS]
She's here, Nico.
She was born.
- [CHUCKLING]
- [NICO CHUCKLING, SOBBING]
She's a beautiful little girl.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
A girl, huh?
See, I knew it.
Are you okay?
- Yeah. We're both fine. We're both fine.
- I wish I were with you.
You're here, Nico.
You are. You've been here the whole time.
You were here during my labor,
you were here
when I finally opened the container.
I promised I wouldn't give up
and I fought.
I fought so hard.
And you're here when I sing to her.
You're always here with me.
- What? You, sing?
- Yes.
[NICO LAUGHS]
[SNIFFLES] Sweetheart,
what does she look like?
She looks like you.
She's so beautiful,
she's strong, and funny.
She makes me laugh,
she's caring just like you.
You know what?
She's right here.
I'll put the phone next to her
so she can hear your voice.
- Okay.
- Sweet pea,
your daddy wants to talk to you.
He's on the phone.
Say something.
Hello, how's my princess?
I'm your daddy.
I'm the pesky guy
who pushed your foot all the time
when you were in your mommy's tummy.
Okay.
Now listen.
I'm gonna tell you a secret.
If you ever feel sad
and confused about life,
close your eyes
and sit in your mom's lap for a while.
You'll see that when you're in her arms,
everything's all right. Always.
- [NOA COOS]
- [NICO CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFLES, STIFLES SOB]
[NICO CHUCKLES]
Did you hear her?
She's brilliant.
[LOW BATTERY BEEP]
Her name is Noa.
Noa?
Are you sure?
- She looks like a Noa.
- [NICO COUGHING]
So as it turns out,
Noa was the perfect name for her.
[NICO WHEEZES]
[LOW BATTERY BEEP]
Nico.
Yeah?
Nico, I love you more than yesterday.
But less than tomorrow.
- [LOST CALL BEEP]
- [TRAGIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[GENTLE, PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
[MUSIC FADES]
DAY 18
DAY 15
DAY 20
DAY 23
MAXIMUM
DAY 26
DAY 14
I'M SICK OF EATING FISH
DAY 20
SHE'S BEEN SLEEPING ALL DAY
DAY 24
I CAN'T STOP THE WATER
I HAVE TO LIVE UP TOP
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOA CRYING]
[MIA SHUSHING]
It's okay.
I gotcha.
[MIA SHUSHES]
- [SEAGULL SQUAWKS]
- [GASPS]
Hey!
Noa!
[GASPS]
That was a seagull.
You know what that means, honey?
MAXIMUM
Okay.
[METAL CREAKING LOUDLY]
Huh?
No!
[GASPING]
[STRAINING]
[GRUNTS, GROANS IN FRUSTRATION]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
No.
You're fucking kidding.
[METAL GROANING LOUDLY]
[WHIMPERS]
[GASPING]
What's happening?
No!
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GASPING]
[MUSIC RISING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
Noa!
[WHALE CALLS]
[GROANS IN FEAR]
Noa!
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WHALE CALLS]
No. Go away!
Noa.
Noa!
[WHALE CALLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [WHALE CALLING]
Noa!
Noa! Noa! Noa!
- [WHALE CALLING]
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[FUSSING]
[NOA CRIES]
Noa, I'm coming!
- Noa!
- [NOA SCREAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Noa!
- [GASPS]
- [WHALE CALLS]
[NOA CRYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIA GASPING]
I'm here.
Don't worry.
Noa. Noa.
[WHALE CALLS]
Everything's fine.
[SIGHING]
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Hm...
[SHIVERING]
[SHIVERS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
We're almost there.
We've almost made it.
Don't give up now.
Just gotta keep going
for a while longer.
Gotta hold on.
We've gotta live to tell our story, Noa.
Yeah, I know.
They'll think we're crazy.
But we know it's true, don't we?
We put up a good fight, honey.
We did everything we could, didn't we?
[NOA COOING SOFTLY]
My love, you saved me.
You saved my life.
Forgive me.
I was so scared.
But you gave me strength.
And I did everything I could...
didn't I?
I did everything I could.
I couldn't have done more.
[SEAGULL SQUAWKING]
[FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
[SPEAKS IN IRISH]
- [IN ENGLISH] There's no fish, Dad!
- Wanna try this?
Do you wanna say something?
No, no. I'm only joking.
No, we only use the radio...
[SPEAKS IN IRISH]
[IN ENGLISH] I told you.
I think you have to move.
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[SPEAKS IN IRISH]
[IN ENGLISH]
Do you see those seagulls?
Can we go a little bit closer?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPEAKS IN IRISH]
[IN ENGLISH]
What's that?
[SPEAKING IN IRISH]
[NOA CRIES]
[NOA COUGHS, COOS]
[IN ENGLISH]
Jesus Christ.
Hey.
Where's his family?
[BOTH SPEAKING IN IRISH]
[NOA COOING]
[NOA COUGHS]
Come on!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC SWELLING]
FISHERMAN: You can do it! Harder!
[MIA GASPS]
FISHERMAN: That's it.
That's it. Turn her over.
[GASPS IN RELIEF]
It's okay.
[SPEAKS IN IRISH]
- [IN ENGLISH] It's okay. It's okay.
- [COUGHING]
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- [COUGHING]
[FISHERWOMAN SHUSHES]
[FISHERWOMAN SPEAKS IN IRISH]
- [FISHERMAN IN ENGLISH] Get her over.
- [GROANS]
- Come on. Sit her up against there.
- FISHERWOMAN: Gently. There you go.
[SHUSHES]
- FISHERMAN: Okay. Just get her over here.
- Hey. [SHUSHES]
- [GROANS]
- [FISHERWOMAN SPEAKS IN IRISH]
- [IN ENGLISH] You're okay. You're okay.
- [MIA GROANS]
[NOA COOS]
My daughter?
My daughter.
- She's here, she's here.
- My daughter.
Mayday, mayday.
We have an emergency here.
We pulled a woman
and a child out of the water.
The woman's okay.
She has--
We've given her CPR and she's alive.
FISHERWOMAN: She's okay.
She's not hurt.
Hey.
She's okay.
FISHERMAN: Yeah, yeah.
We're on our way back now.
We should be back in port
in about 20 minutes.
Your jacket's soaking wet.
Need to take it off.
No, no. Please don't.
I want it on.
- Please. Please.
- It's okay. It's okay.
FISHERWOMAN: Are you hurt?
Do you have other children?
Were there others with you?
You're okay, you're safe.
Okay?
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[EXHALES]
["NANA (CAP.9: CONCEPCIÓN)" BY ROSALÍA PLAYS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]