(birds chirping)
(knocking)
- (knocks)
- CAN I HELP YOU?
(phone ringing)
- (rings)
- (sighs)
(soft moaning)
(Joe's voice)
I HAVE TO GO BACK A BIT.
I WAS 12 YEARS OLD
AND ON A SCHOOL TRIP
IN THE HILLS.
(birds chirping)
(faint conversation)
(low rumbling)
(shuddering)
(ragged breathing)
ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU HAVE THIS ORGASM,
NOT ONLY AN ORGASM,
- BUT A SPONTANEOUS ORGASM.
- YES, IT WAS AN ORGASM,
THOUGH THE DOCTOR
DESCRIBED IT AS A...
AN EPILEPTIC SEIZURE.
AND DURING THAT ORGASM,
YOU HAVE THIS VISION
OF THESE TWO WOMEN
ON EACH SIDE OF YOU?
WAS SHE HOLDING THE VEIL
WITH TWO FINGERS LIKE THIS?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHO
THESE WOMEN WERE, DO YOU?
NO, BUT ONE OF THEM DID
LOOK LIKE THE VIRGIN MARY,
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT.
WELL, IT WASN'T THE VIRGIN MARY,
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
FROM YOUR DESCRIPTION,
IT MUST'VE BEEN
VALERIA MESSALINA,
THE WIFE
OF EMPEROR CLAUDIUS,
THE MOST NOTORIOUS
NYMPHOMANIAC IN HISTORY.
AND THE OTHER WOMAN,
THE ONE ASTRIDE THE CREATURE,
THAT WAS NO ONE ELSE BUT
THE GREAT WHORE OF BABYLON
RIDING ON NIMROD
IN THE FORM OF A BULL.
YOUR STORY IS LIKE A...
BLASPHEMOUS RETELLING
OF THE TRANSFIGURATION
OF JESUS ON THE MOUNT...
WHICH IS ONE
OF THE EASTERN CHURCH'S
HOLIEST PASSAGES.
IT'S WHEN
THE HUMANITY OF CHRIST
IS ILLUMINATED BY
THE DIVINE LIGHT OF ETERNITY.
IF ANYONE ELSE WOULD HAVE
TOLD ME THAT STORY,
I WOULD'VE SEEN IT
AS A BLASPHEMOUS JOKE,
SPICED UP
WITH A BIBLICAL LIGHT
EMANATING FROM NOTHING LESS
THAN A SPONTANEOUS ORGASM.
AND THEN LATER, YOU LOST
YOUR ORGASM ALTOGETHER.
(opera music playing)
WAGNER.
"DAS RHEINGOLD,
THE DESCENT
INTO NIBELHEIM."
WAS IT THAT BAD?
TRY TO IMAGINE
THAT IN ONE FELL SWOOP,
YOU LOST
ALL DESIRE TO READ
AND ALL YOUR LOVE AND PASSION
FOR BOOKS AND LETTERS.
(Seligman) I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF I CAN IMAGINE THAT.
(sighs)
(soft moaning)
(sobbing)
(wails)
(Seligman's voice) THIS IS NOTHING
LESS THAN ZENO'S PARADOX.
YOU ARE ACHILLES
AND THE TORTOISE
IS THE ORGASM.
OH, COME ON.
BECAUSE YOU WERE
GIVING CHASE,
YOU COULDN'T REACH SATISFACTION.
THAT'S THE PARADOX.
I'M SORRY, BUT IT SEEMS AS IF
YOU'RE NOT TAKING THIS
VERY SERIOUSLY.
I'M TELLING YOU ABOUT THE WORST
THING THAT'S HAPPENED TO ME,
THAT I, AT THAT POINT
WITHIN SECONDS,
LOST ALL SEXUAL SENSATION.
MY CUNT SIMPLY WENT NUMB!
AND IMMEDIATELY
WE HAVE TO HEAR
ABOUT THIS RIDICULOUS
MATHEMATICAL PROBLEM.
IN FACT,
I'M IN DOUBT WHETHER
YOU'RE EVEN LISTENING.
WHY DO YOU DOUBT THAT?
WHENEVER I'VE TOLD OTHER MEN
ABOUT EXPERIENCES,
EPISODES IN MY SEX LIFE,
IT WAS EASY TO SEE THAT
THEY BECAME QUITE EXCITED.
I GOT EXCITED.
YES, ABOUT
THE MATHEMATICAL CRAP,
NOT ABOUT THE STORY.
WHAT KIND OF A PERSON
ARE YOU ACTUALLY?
I...
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW.
NO, BUT I CAN GUESS.
WHY DIDN'T I
GET THAT EARLIER?
THE FACT YOU DON'T GET EXCITED
OVER MY DIRTY STORIES
IS BECAUSE YOU CAN'T
RELATE TO THEM.
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
WITH A WOMAN.
THAT'S QUITE ACCURATE.
NOT WITH A MAN EITHER.
(sighs)
ARE YOU SORRY ABOUT THAT?
WELL YEAH, BUT...
OUT OF CURIOSITY.
NOT OUT OF LUST,
AS YOU WOULD THINK.
I CONSIDER MYSELF...
ASEXUAL.
OF COURSE I...
EXPERIMENTED
WITH MASTURBATION WHEN
I WAS A TEENAGER, BUT...
IT DIDN'T
DO MUCH FOR ME.
SO THERE'S NOTHING
SEXUAL ABOUT ME.
IT'S NOT AS UNCOMMON
AS YOU WOULD THINK.
AND OF COURSE I'VE...
I'VE READ A LOT
ABOUT SEXUAL SUBJECTS:
"CANTERBURY TALES,"
"DECAMERON,"
"THOUSAND AND ONE NIGHTS."
YOU NAME IT
AND I'VE READ IT WITH
GREAT INTEREST AND ENJOYMENT...
BUT ONLY LITERARY ENJOYMENT.
BUT I... BUT I THINK
MAYBE IT MAKES ME
A BETTER LISTENER
TO YOUR STORY.
I HAVE NO
PRECONCEIVED NOTIONS OR...
OR PREFERENCES.
I'M ACTUALLY THE BEST JUDGE
YOU COULD GIVE YOUR STORY TO.
AND WHEN IT COMES
TO DECIDING WHETHER YOU'RE
A BAD HUMAN BEING
OR NOT, I'M...
I HAVE NO PROBLEMS
WITH THAT.
BECAUSE I DON'T LOOK
AT YOU THROUGH THE GLASSES
COLOURED BY SEXUALITY
OR SEXUAL EXPERIENCE.
I'M A VIRGIN.
I'M INNOCENT.
(organ music playing)
(train rumbling past)
SHE'S LOOKING AT ME.
YES.
IT'S AN ICON.
IS IT RUSSIAN?
YES, IT'S...
IT'S A SKILLED COPY,
MAYBE IN THE MANNER
OF RUBLEV.
(Seligman)
ICONS ARE USUALLY CONNECTED
TO THE EASTERN CHURCH.
(Joe) THE EASTERN CHURCH?
I MIGHT BECOME
A BIT THEORETICAL.
YOU MAY.
I'D LIKE YOU TO TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR PICTURE.
ALTHOUGH
THE CHRISTIAN CHURCH
WAS SPLIT UP IN 1054 BECAUSE
OF DIFFERENCES IN OPINION
BETWEEN THE EASTERN CHURCH
AND THE WESTERN CHURCH...
WHAT WE TODAY CALL
THE ORTHODOX CHURCH
AND THE ROMAN CATHOLIC
CHURCH.
THIS IS A TYPICAL
EASTERN CHURCH ICON.
AND IT USUALLY
DEPICTS THE VIRGIN MARY
AND THE INFANT JESUS,
AND MORE RARELY,
FOR INSTANCE,
THE CRUCIFIXION,
WHICH IN THE WESTERN CHURCH
WAS MUCH MORE PREVALENT.
IF YOU GENERALISE,
YOU COULD SAY THAT
THE WESTERN CHURCH
IS THE CHURCH OF SUFFERING,
AND THE EASTERN CHURCH IS
THE CHURCH OF HAPPINESS.
IF YOU IMAGINE A MENTAL JOURNEY
FROM ROME EASTWARD,
YOU FEEL HOW YOU MOVE AWAY
FROM GUILT AND PAIN
TOWARDS JOY AND LIGHT.
BUT YOU SAY YOU DIDN'T
BELIEVE IN GOD.
NO, BUT THE CONCEPT
OF RELIGION IS INTERESTING...
LIKE THE CONCEPT OF SEX.
BUT YOU WON'T
FIND ME ON MY KNEES
WITH THE REGARDS TO EITHER.
LET'S CALL THIS CHAPTER,
UM, "THE EASTERN CHURCH
AND THE WESTERN CHURCH."
BUT IT WON'T BE...
IT WON'T BE A STORY
ABOUT TRAVELLING
EAST FROM ROME
TOWARDS THE LIGHT,
BUT RATHER THE OPPOSITE.
SO IN ORDER NOT
TO MAKE IT TOO SAD,
I'VE PEPPED UP THE NAME OF THE
CHAPTER WITH AN EXTRA TITLE.
IN SPITE
OF MY TIRELESS EFFORTS,
MY CUNT TOTALLY
FAILED TO RESPOND.
I HAVE TO ADMIT
THERE CAME A TIME
WHEN WE HAD FUN TOGETHER.
I'LL GIVE YOU A FIVER...
UH-HUH.
...IF YOU CAN PUT THIS
UP INSIDE YOUR CUNT.
(laughs)
A FIVER?
RIGHT.
(spoons clatter)
(laughs) SHIT.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
- DIDN'T GET ANY SPOONS?
- NO, WE DIDN'T.
(spoons clatter)
(clatters)
(clattering)
(laughing)
THE MOST GROTESQUE THING WAS
THAT IT WAS DURING THAT PERIOD
WHERE EVERY SEXUAL SENSATION
WAS DENIED ME...
A PERIOD,
I MUST ADMIT,
OF SECURE AND RESTFUL
DOMESTIC COMFORT...
WE HAD MOVED IN
TOGETHER AND SO ON...
THAT I BECAME PREGNANT,
BECAUSE I WAS CARELESS ABOUT
MY BIRTH CONTROL PILLS.
CONSCIOUSLY
OR UNCONSCIOUSLY,
IT WAS IMPORTANT FOR ME
TO HAVE A CAESAREAN.
I MEAN,
I WAS HOPING THAT
MY CUNT WAS GOING
TO FUCKING WORK AGAIN,
AND I HAD A FEELING THAT
A HAPHAZARD BIRTH WOULDN'T
MAKE THINGS BETTER.
I MAY HAVE BEEN
IMAGINING THINGS,
BUT AS I LAY THERE THE NOISE
FROM THE INSTRUMENTS
RANG OUT IN A CHORD LIKE
THE ONE FROM
THE LITTLE FLOCK.
- (clangs)
- YES.
AND IT WASN'T FEAR.
MORE LIKE A KIND
OF DISGUST.
(clangs)
(sloshes)
(Joe's voice) I COULD'VE SWORN
I SAW HIM LAUGHING.
A LAUGHING SON?
IN "DOCTOR FAUSTUS,"
THOMAS MANN DESCRIBES
THE BIRTH OF NOAH'S SON HAM,
WHO WAS LAUGHING
WHEN HE WAS BORN.
ANOTHER SATANIC OMEN.
INCIDENTALLY, THE INNOCENT
CHILD WAS NAMED MARCEL,
AFTER MARS,
THE ROMAN GOD OF WAR.
AND MOTHERHOOD?
I ASSUME MATERNAL LOVE
DIDN'T QUITE LIVE UP
TO ITS EXPECTATIONS.
NO, I DIDN'T HAVE
ANY EXPECTATIONS.
AND MATERNAL LOVE
WASN'T A PROBLEM.
IT WAS JUST
THAT EACH TIME
I LOOKED
INTO THE CHILD'S EYES,
I HAD THIS
UNSETTLING FEELING
OF HAVING
BEEN FOUND OUT.
- (rattles)
- (babbles)
(Joe's voice) I KNOW
IT'S PROBABLY A STRANGE THING
TO SAY ABOUT A CHILD...
THAT MY LOVE
WASN'T BEING RETURNED...
BUT IT WAS MY PERCEPTION.
(fusses)
(pants)
(moaning)
IF JEROME HAD HOPED
FOR A BREAK
FROM WHAT WAS FOR HIM
NOW MOSTLY STRENUOUS WORK,
HE COULD FORGET ABOUT IT.
FILL ALL MY HOLES.
I CAN'T, JOE.
I'M SORRY.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT IT?
OF COURSE.
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE
YOUR WILDNESS AND YOUR DESIRE.
I LOVE YOU, JOE.
AT THE MOMENT
I DON'T SEEM TO SATISFY YOU
IN THE WAY THAT I'D LIKE TO.
DON'T GET UPSET, JOE.
IT DOESN'T MEAN WE WON'T
CONTINUE WITH OUR SEX LIFE,
WHICH IS VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
(sniffs)
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
MMM, WHEN YOU BUY A TIGER,
RIGHT?
YOU ALSO HAVE TO FEED IT.
UM, SATISFY IT,
RIGHT?
(sniffs)
LONG STORY SHORT:
I HAVE A TIGER ON MY HANDS.
- YOU MEAN I'M TOO MUCH FOR YOU.
- NO.
YOU'RE JUST THE WAY
YOU SHOULD BE.
I WAS JUST THINKING
IF YOU WOULD CONSIDER
THAT I GET A LITTLE HELP
WITH THE FEEDING, THAT'S ALL.
YOU'RE SAYING I SHOULD
HAVE SEX WITH OTHERS AS WELL.
THAT'S A RATHER CRUEL WAY
OF PUTTING IT, JOE, BUT...
- BUT EXACT.
...EXACT.
(sighs)
(laughs)
(Joe's voice) FOR A LONG TIME
I'D BEEN PLAYING AROUND
WITH THE IDEA THAT THE CONCEPT
OF THE FUCK-ME-NOW CLOTHES
COULD BE IMPROVED...
YOU LOOK NICE.
...AND BECAME
THE PIANO TEACHER.
(Driver) YOU OKAY?
NO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WELL, I'M SUCH
AN IDIOT WITH CARS.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT TO DO.
DO YOU MIND HELPING ME?
(Man) WELL, OF COURSE
IT WON'T WORK.
SPARKPLUG CAPS HAVE
BEEN REMOVED.
YES, I DID THAT.
WAS THAT WRONG?
(Joe's voice)
FOR THE FIRST TIME I HAD
THE PLEASURE OF HAVING
AN 8-CYLINDER CAR.
THE POSSIBLE COMBINATIONS
OF EIGHT SPARK-PLUG CAPS
ON EIGHT SPARK PLUGS
ARE 40,320,
IF I REMEMBERED
MY MATH CORRECTLY.
AND ONLY ONE OF THESE
WILL MAKE THE CAR RUN,
WHICH GAVE ME
ALL THE TIME I NEEDED.
- ("Für Elise" playing)
- (Man) BEETHOVEN, HUH?
HE WAS CERTAINLY
VERY GOOD, BUT, YOU KNOW,
- HE COULDN'T WRITE A FUGUE.
- YOU THINK SO?
WELL...
YEAH, I THINK SO.
("Für Elise" continuing)
IT WOULD BE MORE PRECISE
TO SAY THAT BEETHOVEN
RENEWED THE FUGUE...
BUT HE WAS SUCH A VISIONARY
THAT THE OLD BACH PURISTS,
THEY ACCUSED HIM
OF NOT MASTERING IT.
GOOD DAY?
(tile shatters)
("Für Elise" continuing)
(Joe's voice)
AND NOW TO REACH THE HEART
OF YOUR SUFFERING
WESTERN CHURCH,
I HAVE TO JUMP AHEAD
THREE YEARS IN THE STORY
AND TALK ABOUT MY MEETING
WITH WHAT I WOULD CALL
"THE DANGEROUS MEN."
I WAS ALONE WITH MARCEL
A LOT DURING THIS PERIOD,
AS JEROME WAS TRAVELLING
MOST OF THE TIME.
AND WHEN HE WAS FINALLY HOME,
HE SPENT MOST OF THE TIME
ACCUSING ME
OF NEGLECTING MARCEL,
WHICH IN MY OPINION
WAS JUST A COVER
FOR HIS ANGER OVER MY LOVERS.
ANY SEXUAL SATISFACTION,
LET ALONE ORGASM,
WAS FURTHER AWAY
THAN EVER BEFORE.
(men speaking
foreign language)
I HAD TO MAKE A CHANGE.
AND SOMEHOW THE INSPIRATION
HAD BEEN RIGHT THERE
BENEATH MY WINDOW
THE WHOLE TIME.
I COULD FEEL THAT IT
TURNED ME ON ENORMOUSLY
TO IMAGINE
A SEXUAL SITUATION
IN WHICH VERBAL COMMUNICATION
WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
- HELLO.
I'M TOBIAS,
THE INTERPRETER.
HELLO, I'M JOE.
COME IN.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU MASTER
THE AFRICAN LANGUAGES.
I DO HAVE A BASIS.
WHO AND WHAT NEEDS
INTERPRETATION?
UM, THAT MAN...
THE ONE
WITH THE GREEN JACKET?
YOU ARE TO ASK HIM IF
HE WANTS TO HAVE SEX WITH ME.
YEAH? UM...
(no discernable dialog)
IS IT A GO?
(Tobias)
IT'S HARD TO SAY.
I'VE WRITTEN DOWN
THE TIME AND THE PLACE,
BUT, UM...
HONESTLY I WOULDN'T LIKE
TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE PRECISE WORDING
IN THIS CASE,
WHICH I THINK, UH,
ACCIDENTALLY MAY BELONG
TO A GREY ZONE
IN MY PROFESSION.
(Joe's voice) IT WAS THE ADDRESS
OF A CHEAP HOTEL.
(men arguing
in foreign language)
(Seligman's voice)
WHY WERE THERE TWO?
(Joe's voice)
MY WORDS EXACTLY.
APPARENTLY N HAD BROUGHT
HIS BROTHER ALONG.
VERY SORRY.
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
(chatting)
(arguing)
(sighs)
(grumbling)
- (moaning)
- (N speaking)
(men arguing)
(groaning)
(arguing)
(Seligman's voice)
WHY WAS HE SO ANGRY?
(Joe's voice)
CLEARLY IT WAS
SOMETHING PERSONAL
BETWEEN THEM,
BUT LATER I HEARD THAT
PERFORMING A SANDWICH
REQUIRES GREAT SENSITIVITY,
SINCE THE MEN APPARENTLY
CAN FEEL EACH OTHER
THROUGH THE TISSUE.
I IMAGINE THE QUARREL
HAD ALREADY STARTED
ON THE STAIRS AND THAT ONE
OR THE OTHER PARTY
HAD LAID CLAIM TO ONE
OR THE OTHER OF MY HOLES
IN CONFLICT WITH HIS NEGRO
BROTHER'S INTERESTS.
YOU SHOULDN'T USE THAT WORD.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU CALL
POLITICALLY CORRECT...
- "NEGRO."
- WELL, EXCUSE ME,
BUT IN MY CIRCLES
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN A MARK OF
HONOUR TO CALL A SPADE A SPADE.
EACH TIME A WORD
BECOMES PROHIBITED,
YOU REMOVE A STONE FROM
THE DEMOCRATIC FOUNDATION.
SOCIETY DEMONSTRATES
ITS IMPOTENCE
IN THE FACE
OF A CONCRETE PROBLEM
BY REMOVING WORDS
FROM THE LANGUAGE.
I THINK SOCIETY
WOULD CLAIM THAT...
THAT POLITICALLY CORRECTNESS
IS A VERY PRECISE EXPRESSION
OF DEMOCRATIC CONCERN
FOR MINORITIES.
AND I SAY THAT SOCIETY
IS AS COWARDLY
AS THE PEOPLE IN IT,
WHO IN MY OPINION ARE ALSO
TOO STUPID FOR DEMOCRACY.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR POINT,
BUT I TOTALLY DISAGREE.
I HAVE NO DOUBT
IN THE HUMAN QUALITIES.
(scoffs)
THE HUMAN QUALITIES
CAN BE EXPRESSED
IN ONE WORD:
HYPOCRISY.
WE ELEVATE THOSE WHO SAY
"RIGHT" BUT MEAN "WRONG"
AND MOCK THOSE WHO
SAY "WRONG" BUT MEAN "RIGHT."
BY THE WAY,
I CAN ASSURE YOU
THAT WOMEN WHO CLAIM THAT
NEGROS DON'T TURN THEM ON,
- THEY'RE LYING.
- SO DID THEY SATISFY YOU?
THOSE NE-NEGROS?
NO.
BUT THEY SHOWED ME
THAT THERE WAS A WORLD
FAR FROM MINE
I HAD TO EXPLORE.
AND THERE, OR PERHAPS
ON THE OTHER SIDE,
GET MY LIFE BACK.
(footsteps)
(door opens)
WHO ARE YOU?
I KNOW WHAT YOU DO.
I'D LIKE TO BE
ONE OF THE WOMEN
YOU SEE.
THAT'S OF NO INTEREST.
MADAME.
(door closes)
(footsteps approaching)
(door opens)
PRINCESS,
I SPECIFICALLY
SAID FIVE DAYS,
AND FIVE DAYS
HAVEN'T GONE YET.
SO...
YOU'LL HAVE
TO LEAVE.
I'M SORRY.
I, UM...
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS FOR YOU.
(Seligman's voice)
HOW MYSTERIOUS.
WILL YOU GIVE ME
A REASONABLE EXPLANATION NOW
OR SHALL WE WAIT?
I CAN'T GIVE YOU
AN EXPLANATION,
AND CERTAINLY NOT
A REASONABLE...
WHAT EXACTLY WERE
THE RUMOURS ABOUT HIM?
THAT HE WAS VIOLENT.
HOW CAN THAT BE
INCITING?
I THINK THE EASIEST WAY
TO UNDERSTAND IT
IS TO REFER
TO MY REBELLIOUS NATURE.
THIS BUSINESS OF K's WAS
SOMETHING I WAS
COMPLETELY AGAINST.
SO THE FACT THAT I WAS
NOW CONTACTING HIM WAS
A LAST, DESPERATE ATTEMPT
TO REHABILITATE MY SEXUALITY.
THE SYSTEM WAS
THE OVERRIDING FACTOR WITH K.
A SYSTEM OF VIOLENCE?
WELL, YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO INSISTED ON
THE WESTERN CHURCH, RIGHT?
AND I...
I SEEM TO REMEMBER
THAT THE SYSTEMATIC
APPROACH
TO THE CRUCIFIXION
IS OF A VIOLENT
AND NOT TO SAY
SADISTIC NATURE.
OH YES,
THE PASSION OF CHRIST
IS FULL
OF SYSTEMATIC VIOLENCE...
THE VIA DOLOROSA,
THE NINE STATIONS
OF THE CROSS
AND THE 39 LASHES.
(door opens, closes)
YOU ARE BEGINNING
TO IRRITATE ME.
STAND UP.
I JUST WANT YOU TO SIT
COMPLETELY RELAXED...
WHILE I HIT YOU
IN THE FACE.
NOTHING SPECIAL.
IT'S JUST A...
IT'S JUST A SLAP.
ARE YOU READY?
(grunts)
- (grunts)
- (yelps)
LET ME TELL YOU
THE RULES THEN.
(sniffs)
THE FIRST RULE IS
THAT I DON'T FUCK YOU
AND THAT THERE ISN'T ANY
DISCUSSIONS ABOUT THAT.
THEN WHAT DO YOU
GET OUT OF IT?
THAT'S MY BUSINESS
AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO MENTION IT AGAIN.
THE SECOND RULE IS THAT
WE HAVE NO SAFE WORD.
MEANING THAT IF YOU, UH,
GO INSIDE WITH ME,
THERE IS NOTHING
THAT YOU CAN SAY
THAT WILL MAKE ME STOP
ANY PLAN OR PROCEDURE.
YOU MUST BRING A BROWN
USED LEATHER RIDING CROP.
AND NOT ONE FROM A SHOP
SELLING SEX TOYS.
IT'S NOT A MASQUERADE.
THIRD RULE:
IF I CHOOSE TO LET YOU IN,
YOU HAVE TO BE
SITTING OUT HERE.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU...
YOU WON'T KNOW WHEN.
ONLY THAT IT WILL BE
SOMETIME BETWEEN...
2:00 AND 6:00 AT NIGHT.
I CAN'T STAY HERE
THAT LATE.
MY BABYSITTER'S
NOT RELIABLE AND...
I CAN'T LEAVE MY CHILD.
YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW MY NAME!
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN YOUR NAME.
HERE YOUR NAME IS...
FIDO.
(baby fussing)
(Babysitter)
MARCEL'S AWAKE.
D'YOU WANT TO SAY GOODBYE
TO YOUR MOM?
(kisses)
GOODBYE.
I'LL TAKE YOUR COAT.
I'D LIKE YOU TO HAVE
YOUR HAIR UP.
YOU CAN USE THIS.
JUST IN CASE
IT BECOMES NECESSARY FOR ME
TO HIT YOU IN THE FACE.
SHOULD I TAKE
MY CLOTHES OFF?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT TO DO...
AND WHEN.
NOW YOU MAY BEND DOWN.
HOW?
APPROACH THE CHAIR.
NOW BEND FROM THE HIPS.
LOOK FORWARD.
WITH YOUR HEAD UP.
HEAD UP.
KEEP LOOKING FORWARD.
(banging)
YOU MAY STAND UP.
WE HAVE TO USE
THE COUCH.
(grunts)
COME THIS WAY.
TAKE IT EASY,
TAKE IT EASY.
BEND OVER.
LAY YOUR ARMS
OUT STRAIGHT.
(heavy breathing)
TAKE IT EASY.
- TAKE IT EASY.
- (metal clicks)
(panting)
(whispers)
TAKE IT EASY.
NEXT TIME
DON'T WEAR KNICKERS.
(ragged breathing)
(sobs)
YOUR ASS IS
NOT HIGH ENOUGH.
I DON'T THINK
WE CAN DO THIS TODAY.
WHAT?
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU AGAIN
ON THURSDAY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
I THINK WE SHOULD
SEE HOW IT GOES ON THURSDAY.
(bangs)
(dials, rings)
(Babysitter's voice) Hi, I can't
come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message.
(beeps)
YES, THIS IS
MARCEL'S MOTHER AGAIN.
UH, IT'S NOW 1:30.
WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
I HOPE YOU GET THIS MESSAGE
AND COME AS QUICKLY AS YOU CAN.
UH, MARCEL IS SLEEPING.
UM...
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
BETTER.
ALSO SO MUCH BETTER.
SO MUCH BETTER.
I AM NOW GOING
TO HIT YOU 12 TIMES
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
YOU SCREAM...
(taps crop)
...'CAUSE NO ONE CAN
HEAR YOU DOWN HERE.
(screams, gasps)
THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S NOT HOW IT GOES.
MOST PEOPLE DON'T SCREAM
UNTIL I HIT THEM.
(gulps)
- (blow strikes)
- (whimpers)
(blow strikes)
(breathing heavily)
(moans)
OH!
(sniffling)
THAT'S IT.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE WE GET
OUR SEXUALITY FROM
OR WHERE TENDENCIES
OF THIS KIND COME FROM.
PROBABLY A PERVERSION
CREATED IN OUR CHILDHOOD
THAT NEVER MANIFESTED
ITSELF BEFORE.
WELL, ODDLY ENOUGH,
FREUD SAYS THE OPPOSITE.
HE TALKS ABOUT
THE POLYMORPHIC PERVERSION
OF A CHILD.
MEANING THAT IN A CHILD,
ALL KINDS
OF PERVERSIONS EXIST.
AND THEN WE USE
THE CHILDHOOD
TO DIMINISH OR REMOVE
SOME OF THEM.
BASICALLY A CHILD IS
SEXUALLY POLYMORPHIC
AND EVERYTHING IS SEXUALITY
IN AN INFANT.
AND YET IT WAS
DEEPLY BIZARRE
TO LIE THERE
AND ESPECIALLY TO WANT
TO LIE THERE.
IT IS AN INTERESTING POINT
THAT YOU ACTUALLY LUBRICATED
IN EXPECTATION FOR A PAIN
THAT YOU HADN'T
EXPERIENCED.
YOUR BODY PREPARED ITSELF
FOR AN INTERCOURSE THAT
YOU KNEW WOULDN'T HAPPEN.
(Joe's voice) I CAN ONLY DESCRIBE
THE MOOD AS SEXUAL.
AS I TWISTED AND TURNED
WHILE HE WAS WHIPPING ME,
I COULD FEEL HOW CLEVER
HIS KNOTS WERE.
IF I FOUGHT THEM,
THEY WOULD GET TIGHTER,
AND AS I RELAXED,
IT SEEMED THEY DID TOO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT KIND OF KNOT
K USED...
BUT I KNOW OF A KNOT
THAT TIGHTENS WHEN
FORCE IS EXERTED
AND VICE VERSA.
IT'S CALLED A PRUSIK KNOT.
IT'S AFTER A MAN CALLED PRUSIK.
HE WAS A MOUNTAIN CLIMBER.
AND HE AND A FRIEND
WERE OUT CLIMBING
AND THEY HAD AN ACCIDENT
AND HIS FRIEND DIED.
AND HE ENDED UP HANGING
AT THE END OF A ROPE
WITH NO POSSIBILITY
OF GETTING UP.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T CLIMB UP
A MOUNTAIN-CLIMBER ROPE.
IT'S TOO THIN.
BUT HE WAS
AN INTELLIGENT MAN,
AND WITH HIS BACK TO THE WALL
HE WAS A GENIUS.
AND HE TOOK THE SHOELACES
OUT OF HIS BOOTS
AND MADE TWO LOOPS
AND AFFIXED THEM TO THE ROPE.
AND HE COULD MOVE THESE UP
WHEN THEY WEREN'T
UNDER TENSION.
AND THEN HE COULD
STEP INTO THEM
AND CLIMB THE ROPE
AND SAVE HIMSELF.
(pebbles clattering)
PRUSIK.
I THINK THIS WAS ONE
OF YOUR WEAKEST DIGRESSIONS.
MAY I CONTINUE?
WELL, BE MY GUEST.
(coins clinking)
(exhales)
I SOMETIMES GIVE
A CHRISTMAS PRESENT.
BUT, UH, YOU HAVE TO DO
THE WORK YOURSELF.
THIS IS CALLED
A BLOOD KNOT.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
NINE ROPES
WITH THREE BLOOD KNOTS
ON EACH.
LET ME SEE YOU DO IT.
YOU DECIDE
WHETHER TO MAKE FOUR,
FIVE OR SIX TURNS
IN THE VARIOUS KNOTS.
(ragged breathing)
(plow beeping)
(ticking)
- (Marcel coos)
- (truck engine stops)
(beeping, engine starts)
(grunting)
(babbling)
(opera music playing)
(coos)
JOE?
HELLO.
MARCEL?
MARCEL!
(Marcel crying)
(wailing)
(scratches)
- ARE YOU FOND OF ME STILL?
- YES.
MORE FOND OF ME
THAN THE OTHERS?
- YES?
- (Joe) YES.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING OF LEAVING
AGAIN TONIGHT, ARE YOU?
- NO.
- NO?
- NO, NO. NOT AT ALL.
- ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
ARE YOU LYING
TO ME, JOE?
- NO.
- BE HONEST.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST FUCKING SAY IT.
NO, I... I JUST
WANT TO BE HERE.
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU LEAVE TONIGHT...
YOU'LL NEVER SEE ME OR MARCEL
EVER AGAIN IN YOUR LIFE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
(sobbing)
IS THIS GOODBYE?
- (continues sobbing)
- IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
MARCEL, GET UP.
- (Joe) STOP IT.
- IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
HERE, SO YOU COULD SEE HIM.
LOOK AT HIM, JOE.
LET'S FACE IT, JOE,
YOU'RE NOT A MOTHER.
- (sobbing)
- LET'S WAKE HIM UP.
MARCEL, BABY BOY,
- SAY, "BYE, MOM."
- (fussing)
- PLEASE PUT HIM BACK.
- IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
- HMM?
- (Marcel cries)
- MA.
- YOU SEE?
YOU SEE,
HE WANTS YOU.
COME.
IT'S CHRISTMAS.
IT'S FUCKING CHRISTMAS.
(footsteps)
(door opens)
WHAT IS THIS?
TODAY IT'S MADAME
WHO MUST WAIT.
MADAME, I'M VERY SORRY,
BUT I HAVE TO HAVE
A FEW WORDS WITH FIDO FIRST.
I REALLY OUGHT TO
SEND YOU HOME.
HAPPY CHRISTMAS, FIDO.
(pants)
(whispers)
I WANT YOUR COCK.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
(inhales)
I WANT YOUR COCK.
NO. NO, YOU DON'T.
- NO, YOU DON'T. NO.
- (sobs)
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU TODAY?
ON ACCOUNT OF THE HOLIDAYS
AND YOUR BEHAVIOUR TODAY,
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
THE ORIGINAL ROMAN MAXIMUM
OF 40 LASHES.
ARE YOU READY, FIDO?
I'M READY.
ONE.
TWO.
- (yelps)
- THREE.
FOUR.
FIVE.
SIX.
(panting)
(Joe's voice) I'D SEEN THROUGH
K's KNOT TECHNIQUE,
SO I WAS ABLE TO LOOSEN MY
POSITION A BIT TO MOVE MY PELVIS,
AND THEREBY
STIMULATE MY CLITORIS
AGAINST THE COVER
OF THE BOOK.
(gasping)
(loud moaning)
AND WHEN YOU CAME HOME,
JEROME AND THE CHILD
WERE GONE?
I HAVEN'T SEEN MARCEL SINCE.
(shatters)
THE SENTIMENTALITY OF...
I HATE IT.
WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S A LIE.
ARE YOU SURE?
(pottery scrapes)
JEROME UNDERSTOOD
THAT HE COULDN'T PRIORITISE
HIS LIFE ACCORDING
TO A CHILD EITHER.
SO HE PUT HIM
IN A FOSTER HOME.
MY ONLY CONTACT TO THE BOY
IS THE THOUSAND POUNDS
I PUT IN HIS ACCOUNT
EVERY MONTH.
ANONYMOUSLY.
AS A PENANCE.
AFTER ALL THIS SADNESS,
MAY I ASK...
WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE SILENT DUCK?
OH SHIT.
THE SILENT DUCK.
I'D FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT IT.
ONE NIGHT K HAD BEEN IN
WHAT WAS FOR HIM
AN UNUSUALLY GOOD MOOD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT CAUSED IT,
BUT HE DIDN'T HIT HARD
AND HE JOKED THAT
HE WOULD INTRODUCE ME
TO THE CONCEPT
OF THE SILENT DUCK.
(silent)
(Seligman's voice)
ONE HARDLY DARE IMAGINE
"THE QUACKING DUCK."
(loud quacking)
OH.
WELL, DEEP DOWN,
LITTLE K SEEMS TO HAVE BEEN
A JOLLY MAN
WITH VERSATILE TALENTS.
BUT HE GOT THAT BIT ABOUT
ROMAN PUNISHMENT
AND THE 40 LASHES WRONG.
BECAUSE IT'S TRUE THAT
THE HIGHEST PUNISHMENT
WAS 40 LASHES,
BUT IT HAD TO BE DELIVERED
IN SERIES OF THREE.
THAT'S WHY JESUS
ONLY GOT 39 LASHES,
BECAUSE THREE GOES INTO 39
BUT NOT INTO 40.
YOU HAVE A MIRROR.
YES.
IT'S LIKE A THOUGHT,
ISN'T IT?
ARE YOU READY
FOR ANOTHER CHAPTER?
GO ON.
(rattling)
(Joe's voice) SOME YEARS LATER,
THE BODILY ABUSE
BEGAN TO HAVE AN EFFECT.
FIRST, RARE BLEEDINGS
FROM MY CLITORIS,
BUT THEN THEY BECAME
MORE AND MORE FREQUENT.
(Woman) COME IN.
HAVE YOU HEARD ANY OF
THE RUMOURS ABOUT YOURSELF?
THEY SAY YOU SEE MEN
EVERY EVENING.
AND SPEND ALL NIGHT
WITH THEM.
THEY SAY YOU CAN'T BE TRUSTED...
ALL OF THEM.
WHY DO THEY SAY THAT?
I SUPPOSE
THEY'RE AFRAID THAT I...
I CAN'T KEEP AWAY
FROM THEIR MEN.
RIGHT.
- AND CAN YOU?
- NO.
I'VE SPOKEN
WITH A PSYCHOLOGIST.
HE SAYS YOU'RE ADDICTED,
BUT THAT IT'S NOT
THE KIND OF ADDICTION
THAT CAN'T BE TREATED.
THEY HAVE SOME GROUPS.
I KNOW ABOUT
THESE KINDS OF GROUPS.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY TO A PSYCHOLOGIST.
I'M NOT SUGGESTING THERAPY.
I'M DEMANDING IT.
EVEN IF YOU LEAVE US, IT'LL BE
THE SAME AT YOUR NEXT JOB
AND THE ONE AFTER THAT.
MY NAME IS JOE...
(Group) HI, JOE.
...AND I'M A NYMPHOMANIAC.
(Therapist) SEX ADDICT.
MY NAME IS JOE
AND I'M A NYMPHOMANIAC.
WE SAY SEX ADDICT.
HERE EVERYONE'S
THE SAME.
YOU SHOULD ONLY SPEAK
WHEN YOU FEEL YOU HAVE TO.
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS THAT
NO ONE CAN REMOVE
THEIR SEXUALITY
EVEN THOUGH IT'S DESTROYING
EVERYTHING FOR THEM.
I WOULDN'T SAY NO ONE.
BUT LET'S SAY,
AT MOST, ONE IN A MILLION
MANAGE TO LIVE A LIFE
WITHOUT SEXUALITY.
BUT YOU CAN'T BE
BASING YOUR THERAPY
- ON THAT ONE IN A MILLION.
- NO.
THE FIRST
AND MOST IMPORTANT STEP
IS TO REMOVE INCENTIVE
AND TO REDUCE EXPOSURE.
YOU HAVE TO ASK YOURSELF
WHAT KIND OF
INCENTIVES YOU HAVE
AND THEN MAKE IT
DIFFICULT FOR YOURSELF
TO COME INTO CONTACT
WITH THEM.
BASICALLY ANYTHING THAT
MAKES YOU THINK ABOUT SEX.
JOE HAS SOMETHING
SHE'D LIKE TO SHARE.
MY NAME IS JOE...
(Group) HI, JOE.
...AND I'M A SEX ADDICT,
BUT I HAVEN'T HAD SEX
FOR THREE WEEKS AND FIVE DAYS.
(applause)
TELL US
HOW YOU DID IT, JOE.
- YOU BROUGHT NOTES?
- YES.
"DEAR EVERYONE,
DON'T THINK IT'S BEEN EASY,
BUT I UNDERSTAND NOW
THAT WE ARE ALL ALIKE."
ARE YOU OKAY, JOE?
YES, YES.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A GLASS OF WATER?
THANK YOU.
WOULD YOU RATHER
SHARE ANOTHER TIME?
NO, I'D LIKE TO SPEAK.
DEAR EVERYONE,
DON'T THINK IT'S BEEN EASY,
BUT I UNDERSTAND NOW
THAT WE'RE NOT
AND NEVER WILL BE ALIKE.
I'M NOT LIKE YOU,
WHO FUCKS TO BE VALIDATED
AND MIGHT JUST AS WELL GIVE UP
PUTTING COCKS INSIDE YOU.
AND I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
ALL YOU WANT
IS TO BE FILLED UP,
AND WHETHER
IT'S BY A MAN OR BY TONS
OF DISGUSTING SLOP
MAKES NO DIFFERENCE.
AND I'M DEFINITELY
NOT LIKE YOU.
THAT EMPATHY YOU CLAIM
IS A LIE,
BECAUSE ALL YOU ARE IS
SOCIETY'S MORALITY POLICE,
WHOSE DUTY IS
TO ERASE MY OBSCENITY
FROM THE SURFACE
OF THE EARTH
SO THAT THE BOURGEOISIE
WON'T FEEL SICK.
I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
I AM A NYMPHOMANIAC,
AND I LOVE MYSELF
FOR BEING ONE.
BUT ABOVE ALL,
I LOVE MY CUNT
AND MY FILTHY,
DIRTY LUST.
♪ WATCH OUT ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT GET
WHAT YOU'RE AFTER ♪
♪ COOL, BABIES ♪
♪ STRANGE,
BUT NOT A STRANGER ♪
♪ I'M AN ORDINARY GUY ♪
♪ BURNING DOWN
THE HOUSE! ♪
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
I DIDN'T GET THAT...
WITH THE CAR THAT BURNED.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST
IN TOO MUCH OF A HURRY
TO GET TO THE LAST CHAPTER.
I UNDERSTOOD THAT SOCIETY
HAD NO ROOM FOR ME,
AND I HAD NO ROOM
FOR SOCIETY
AND NEVER HAD.
I'M SURE IT WAS
QUITE NATURAL FOR YOU
TO FURNISH YOUR ROOM
AS A MONK'S CELL,
BUT AS AN INSPIRATION FOR
THE STORY CHAPTER HEADINGS,
IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
THERE'S SIMPLY NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO USE.
WELL, I'M SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
BUT IF I MAY,
I CAN GIVE YOU A TIP.
YES, PLEASE.
YOU KNOW, I OCCUPY MYSELF
MOSTLY WITH TEXT,
BUT SOMETIMES THE TEXT
CAN SEEM SO...
SO EMPTY,
SO UNFATHOMABLY EMPTY.
IT COULD BE THE BEST TEXT
BY THE MOST FAMOUS AUTHOR.
THE SOLUTION MIGHT BE
TO CHANGE YOUR POINT OF VIEW.
I-I DON'T GET THAT.
THINGS HIDE...
WHEN THEY
BECOME FAMILIAR.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THEM
FROM ANOTHER ANGLE,
THEY MIGHT TAKE ON
A NEW MEANING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BEFORE THIS WAS JUST
THE STAIN
FROM THE TEA I THREW.
CAN YOU SEE
WHAT IT COULD BE?
(Seligman) A REVOLVER.
NO, A REVOLVER HAS
A DRUM THAT REVOLVES.
IT'S A PISTOL.
CAN YOU SEE
WHAT KIND IT COULD BE?
NO, I DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING LIKE THAT
FROM MY LITERATURE.
OH, BUT IT'S SOMETHING
I CAN REMEMBER FROM MINE.
IAN FLEMING.
NOT FAMILIAR.
IF YOU HAVEN'T READ THAT, YOU
HAVEN'T READ ANYTHING AT ALL.
THIS COULD BE,
WITH A LITTLE IMAGINATION,
A WALTHER P.P.K. AUTOMATIC,
THE SAME GUN
THAT WAS ISSUED TO BOND
AFTER HIS PREFERRED PISTOL,
THE BERETTA, HAD JAMMED.
IS THAT SOMETHING
YOU CAN USE?
OH YES, IT IS.
♪ BURNING DOWN
THE HOUSE! ♪
♪ HOLD TIGHT ♪
♪ WAIT TILL
THE PARTY'S OVER ♪
♪ HOLD TIGHT... ♪
(Joe's voice)
WHETHER I LEFT SOCIETY,
OR IT LEFT ME,
I CANNOT SAY.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD MAKE
AN ARGUMENT FOR BOTH SIDES.
♪ BURNING DOWN
THE HOUSE! ♪
I WAS ON MY WAY
TO THE SHADY SIDE
OF THE DEBT-COLLECTING
BUSINESS,
WHICH AMONG OTHER THINGS
INVOLVED STUFF
LIKE BURNING PEOPLE'S CARS.
I HAD FOR A LONG TIME
KNOWN ABOUT THIS MAN, L.
HI, MY NAME IS JOE.
I KNOW THAT.
COME IN.
I'M LOOKING FOR A JOB.
I'VE BEEN WORKING
IN AN OFFICE,
AND I WAS NEVER
REALLY GOOD AT IT.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
I MEAN,
WHAT'S THE POINT?
I BELIEVE I POSSESS
SOME QUALIFICATIONS
AND THAT I'M RATHER
UNSCRUPULOUS.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT
YOUR QUALIFICATIONS
AND THEY'RE EXCELLENT.
I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT YOU START
YOUR OWN LITTLE BUSINESS
WITH MY HELP.
I UNDERSTAND
YOU POSSESS
A GREAT DEAL OF INSIGHT
ABOUT A RATHER
BROAD SPECTRUM OF MEN.
THIS COULD BE... OR SHOULD
BE CAPITALISED ON.
I NEED SUB-CONTRACTORS
WHO CAN PUT
MODERATE PRESSURE
ON INDIVIDUALS
WITH WHOM MY CLIENTS
RIGHTLY OR WRONGLY
HAVE A BONE TO PICK.
UNDERSTAND?
EXTORTION.
NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I ALWAYS PREFER THE TERM
"DEBT COLLECTION."
- YEAH.
- I REFRAIN FROM JUDGING
WHETHER MY CLIENTS' WISHES
ARE LEGITIMATE OR OTHERWISE.
A POINT OF VIEW
I STRONGLY RECOMMEND
YOU FOLLOW.
(Joe's voice) MY MAIN
QUALIFICATION OF COURSE
WAS MY CONSIDERABLE EXPERIENCE
WITH MEN AND SEX.
BUT EVEN MY MORE SPECIALISED
SKILLS CAME IN HANDY.
(man panting)
(screams)
NO, NOW THIS IS NOT
HOW IT GOES.
YOU HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL YOU'RE HIT.
(cracks)
THE TWO HELPERS THAT L
HAD RECOMMENDED WERE OKAY,
BUT THEY WERE PREDISPOSED TO
A RATHER REPETITIVE TECHNIQUE,
WHICH CONSISTED OF CREATING
AS MUCH HAVOC AS POSSIBLE
WITH A PAIR OF IRON BARS.
(shards clatter)
DESTROYING YOUR THINGS DOESN'T
SEEM TO HAVE MUCH EFFECT ON YOU.
(Joe's voice)
HERE WAS A MAN
I WAS UNABLE
TO READ SEXUALLY,
SO I BECAME PERSISTENT.
TIE HIM TO THE CHAIR.
DON'T HURT HIM.
(tape ripping)
I CAN'T FIND A STAIN ON YOU,
BUT MY EXPERIENCE TELLS ME
THAT NO MAN IS SPOTLESS.
LUCKILY, YOU'RE EQUIPPED
WITH A VERY RELIABLE
TRUTH-DETECTOR.
(man grunts)
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
A FEW STORIES.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS LISTEN.
YOU'RE IN A BAR
WATCHING A COUPLE...
(Joe's voice) I NOW METICULOUSLY
WENT THROUGH THE CATALOGUE
OF SEXUAL DEVIATIONS
IN FICTIONAL FORM.
STORIES ABOUT
SADOMASOCHISM,
FETISHISM,
HOMOSEXUALITY,
YOU NAME IT.
BUT HE DIDN'T REACT.
AND I'D ALMOST GIVEN UP
WHEN I SAID:
ON YOUR WAY HOME,
YOU WALK THROUGH THE PARK.
AND SOMETHING
MAKES YOU STOP.
YOU HEAR SOMETHING.
(silent)
YES, THAT'S IT.
YOU CAN HEAR THE CHILDREN
ON THE PLAYGROUND.
YOU SIT ON A BENCH NEARBY
AND WATCH THEM PLAY.
THERE'S A LITTLE BOY
IN SHORTS.
HE'S PLAYING
IN THE SANDPIT.
HE LOOKS AT YOU
WITH HIS BLUE EYES.
HE SMILES AT YOU.
I THINK HE COMES TO YOU.
HE SITS ON YOUR LAP
AND LOOKS UP AT YOUR FACE.
HE SAYS
HE'D LIKE TO COME
HOME WITH YOU.
AT HOME
YOU CAN'T FIGHT THE IDEA
OF BEING NAKED TOGETHER.
HE CRAWLS ALL OVER YOU.
- YOU GET AN ERECTION.
- WON'T YOU PLEASE STOP?
HE LIES ON HIS STOMACH.
YOU PULL DOWN HIS PANTS.
I'LL PAY!
(sobbing)
YOU DID WHAT?
I GAVE HIM A BLOWJOB.
WHY?
THAT PIG?!
- I TOOK PITY ON HIM.
- PITY?
YES. I HAD JUST
DESTROYED HIS LIFE.
NOBODY KNEW HIS SECRET,
MOST PROBABLY
NOT EVEN HIMSELF.
HE SAT THERE
WITH THE SHAME.
I SUPPOSE I SUCKED HIM OFF
AS A KIND OF APOLOGY.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
NO, LISTEN TO ME.
THIS IS A MAN
WHO'D SUCCEEDED
IN REPRESSING HIS OWN DESIRE,
WHO HAD NEVER BEFORE
GIVEN INTO IT
RIGHT UP UNTIL
I FORCED IT OUT.
HE HAD LIVED A LIFE
FULL OF DENIAL
AND HAD NEVER HURT A SOUL.
I THINK
THAT'S LAUDABLE.
NO MATTER
HOW HARD I TRY,
I CAN'T FIND ANYTHING
LAUDABLE IN PAEDOPHILIA.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU THINK ABOUT
THE PERHAPS 5%
WHO ACTUALLY HURT CHILDREN.
THE REMAINING 95%
NEVER LIVE OUT
THEIR FANTASIES.
THINK ABOUT
THEIR SUFFERING.
SEXUALITY IS
THE STRONGEST FORCE
IN HUMAN BEINGS.
TO BE BORN
WITH A FORBIDDEN SEXUALITY
MUST BE AGONISING.
THE PAEDOPHILE WHO MANAGES
TO GET THROUGH LIFE
WITH THE SHAME
OF HIS DESIRE
WHILE NEVER ACTING ON IT
DESERVES A BLOODY MEDAL.
BUT THERE WAS ANOTHER REASON
FOR MY SYMPATHY,
WHICH YOU FIND
SO MYSTERIOUS.
I SAW A MAN WHO WAS CARRYING
THE SAME CROSS AS MYSELF.
LONELINESS.
WE WERE BOTH
SEXUAL OUTCASTS.
IN ANY CASE,
SOME YEARS PASSED,
DURING WHICH
MY BUSINESS GREW,
ENABLING ME TO STEP UP
MY ANONYMOUS DEPOSITS
TO MARCEL.
YOUR BUSINESS
IS DOING GREAT...
YOU COMPLETE ALL THE JOBS
I GIVE YOU TO PERFECTION
AND I HEAR ONLY WORDS OF PRAISE
FROM YOUR OTHER CLIENTS,
- BUT...
- BUT WHAT?
WE AREN'T
GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
OH.
NO, THAT'S FOR SURE.
I THINK YOU'RE GETTING
TO THAT AGE
WHERE YOU HAVE TO START
THINKING ABOUT A SUCCESSOR.
OH... I DON'T NEED
A FUCKING SUCCESSOR.
LISTEN, A PERSON SHOULD TAKE
THEIR CRIME SERIOUSLY.
YOU NEED SOMEONE
TO BE YOUR RIGHT HAND,
SOMEONE TO HELP YOU.
A CROWN PRINCESS.
THE NORMAL PROCESS
IS TO FIND OUT
WHAT COLLEAGUES
ARE IN PRISON
OR ARE DRUG ADDICTS,
AND THEREBY
UNABLE TO FULFIL
THEIR ROLES AS PARENTS.
THEN YOU FIND OUT WHERE
THEIR KIDS PLAY FOOTBALL...
AND YOU GET INVOLVED.
YOU CHEER THEM ON
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS
NO MATTER HOW BAD THEY ARE.
ACTUALLY, THE WORSE,
THE BETTER. THAT WAY
GRADUALLY YOU TAKE ON
THE ROLE OF THE PARENT
UNTIL IN THE END
YOU HAVE A LOYAL HELPER THAT
WILL WALK THROUGH FIRE FOR YOU.
EVEN DO TIME FOR YOU.
IT SOUNDS LIKE A...
KIND OF AN ENTRAPMENT
YOU'RE SUGGESTING.
- AN UNSAVOURY ENTRAPMENT.
- CALL IT WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT IF YOU BELIEVE AT ALL
IN THE EFFECTS
OF GOOD PARENTING,
THAT KID WILL HAVE
MUCH GREATER OPPORTUNITIES
WITH YOU AS A MENTOR
THAN WITHOUT.
AND SINCE I LIKE YOU,
I'VE BEEN LOOKING AROUND
FOR A SUITABLE SUBJECT.
SHE'S 15 YEARS OLD
FROM A FAMILY
OF HARDENED CRIMINALS,
AND SHE'S
BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
LAST COUPLE OF YEARS
SHE'S BEEN INSTITUTIONALISED.
HER FATHER IS IN PRISON AND HER
MOTHER DIED OF AN OVERDOSE.
SHE'S A SMART GIRL.
AND ALTHOUGH
SHE DOESN'T PLAY FOOTBALL,
SHE DOES PLAY BASKETBALL...
VERY BADLY.
SHE'S CHOSEN A TEAM SPORT
BECAUSE SHE'S LONELY.
I SAVED THE BEST PART
FOR LAST:
HER RIGHT EAR IS
SLIGHTLY DEFORMED...
WHICH SHE'S
VERY ASHAMED OF,
AND OF COURSE THIS SERVES
TO ISOLATE HER EVEN MORE.
IT MAKES HER AN EASY TARGET
FOR EVEN THE SLIGHTEST
BIT OF ATTENTION
OR SIGN OF EMPATHY
FROM YOU.
(Joe's voice)
DESPITE MY PROTESTS,
THE CLEVER L
SOMEHOW TALKED ME
INTO ACTUALLY HAVING
A LOOK AT P.
(cheering)
THE LONGER I WATCHED
THE POOR GIRL
WITH THE DEFORMED EAR,
THE MORE REPULSIVE
I FOUND THE WHOLE PLAN.
- (shouts)
- (applause)
(Joe's voice) BUT AS IF
L HAD FORESEEN THIS,
THE MEETING WITH P FILLED ME
WITH PITY AND EMOTION.
AND WITHOUT WANTING TO,
I FOUND MYSELF,
WEEKEND AFTER WEEKEND,
AT HER GAMES
SUPPORTING THE POOR PLAYER.
THANKS
FOR CHEERING ME ON.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU PLAYED
REALLY WELL TODAY.
- NO, I DIDN'T.
- YOU DID.
YOU REALLY IMPROVED
YOURSELF LATELY.
(Joe's voice)
I WAS PROUD TO INTRODUCE P
TO MY FATHER'S PASSION...
AND TO HIS WORLD.
IT'S ACTUALLY...
THE SOULS OF THE TREES
THAT WE SEE
IN THE WINTER.
I THINK THEY LOOK
LIKE HUMAN SOULS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THEY DO LOOK LIKE
HUMAN SOULS.
TWISTED SOULS,
REGULAR SOULS,
CRAZY SOULS.
ALL DEPENDING ON THE KIND
OF LIVES HUMAN BEINGS LEAD.
I FOUND MY TREE,
MY SOUL TREE.
THIS IS MY TREE.
(Young Joe)
IT'S NOT AN ASH TREE.
(Father)
NO, IT'S AN OAK TREE.
(chuckles)
MY FATHER FOUND
HIS SOUL TREE,
BUT I'VE...
I'VE NEVER FOUND MINE.
"YOU WILL KNOW IT
WHEN YOU SEE IT,"
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
(Joe's voice) WHEN P REACHED
THE AGE OF MAJORITY
AND I BECAME
HER PERSONAL ADVISOR,
I ASKED HER
TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
WITH YOUR HAIR UP.
IT'S SO PRETTY.
(breathing heavily)
(Joe's voice) ALL THIS TIME ALL MY
SEXUAL ACTIVITY HAD STOPPED.
MY GROIN WAS ONE BIG SORE
FROM MY ABUSE
THAT WOULDN'T HEAL
AND MADE
EVEN MASTURBATION IMPOSSIBLE.
I EXPERIENCED DEFINITE
ABSTINENCE SYMPTOMS:
FEVER AND CRAMPS.
(moans)
(glass shatters)
(breathing heavily)
JOE, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- (Joe) CAREFUL.
- WE NEED TO CLEAR THIS UP.
(whispers)
I JUST GET THIS SOMETIMES.
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY.
(Seligman)
PERHAPS SHE REALLY LOVED YOU.
I COULDN'T ACCEPT IT.
PERHAPS BECAUSE YOU REALLY
WANTED IT TO BE TRUE.
PERHAPS I HOPED IT.
IT'S VERY TOUCHING,
ALL THIS ABOUT P.
THEN YOU'VE PROBABLY
MISUNDERSTOOD
THE WHOLE THING.
(pills rattle)
DON'T.
I WANNA SEE YOU.
- DON'T.
- WHY?
- PLEASE DON'T.
- WHY NOT?
NO.
NO, I HAVE A WOUND.
- I HAVE A WOUND.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I HAVE THAT THING
WITH MY EAR.
I'M SO ASHAMED.
D'YOU LIKE ME?
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
(sobbing)
(train passing)
THERE'S ONE THING
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
DID SHE KNOW WHAT
YOU DID FOR A LIVING?
P WAS VERY DISCREET
AND A GIRL OF FEW WORDS.
ODDLY, ALTHOUGH
I WORKED STRANGE HOURS,
SHE NEVER ASKED
ABOUT MY WORK.
BUT ONE DAY
SHE HAD A QUESTION.
JOE?
WHY DID YOU START COMING
TO MY BASKETBALL MATCHES?
IT WASN'T A COINCIDENCE,
WAS IT?
NO, IT WASN'T
A COINCIDENCE.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU
BECAUSE I...
I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE UPSET...
AND THAT YOU'D
GET ANGRY AT ME.
I WON'T GET ANGRY.
WHAT I DO...
MY JOB
ISN'T A NORMAL JOB.
IT'S NOT LEGAL.
NO ONE IN MY FAMILY
DOES ANYTHING LEGAL.
A MAN THAT'S HELPED ME
IN MY BUSINESS
SUGGESTED THAT
I WATCHED YOU.
THE PLAN WAS THAT I...
I SHOULD LOOK AT YOU
TO SEE WHETHER ONE DAY
I COULD USE YOU
IN MY WORK.
I SHOULD
MAKE FRIENDS WITH YOU,
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU DIDN'T
HAVE A MOTHER OR A FATHER.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THAT?
DON'T YOU SEE
HOW EVIL THAT PLAN WAS?
I FELT TERRIBLE.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE IF YOU HADN'T...
WE'D NEVER HAVE MET.
I'D LIKE TO GO
WITH YOU TO WORK
- NEXT TIME.
- NO.
WILL YOU THINK ABOUT IT?
- YES.
(laughs) NO.
SHE DIDN'T TAKE NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
HOW DO YOU KEEP A WAVE
UPON THE SAND?
WITH THE RISK OF BEING
TOO CLEVER FOR MYSELF,
SOCIAL INHERITANCE
IS AN IRREFUTABLE FACT.
IF ANYONE KNEW ABOUT
THE LAWS OF THE STREET,
IT MUST'VE BEEN P.
YOU'RE MORE RIGHT
THAN YOU KNOW.
- (man yelling)
- LET'S SHOOT THE FUCKER.
STOP! STOP!
WE DON'T USE FIREARMS.
- I'D LIKE TO HAVE THE GUN.
- THE OTHERS HAVE WEAPONS TOO.
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
BUT IN ANY CASE,
YOU'RE NOT TO HAVE ONE.
BUT GUNS AREN'T DANGEROUS.
IT DEPENDS ON HOW
YOU USE THEM.
YES, EXACTLY.
I WASN'T GOING TO SHOOT HIM.
WE WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN ANY
MONEY OUT OF HIM THAT WAY.
CAN I HAVE THE GUN?
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE EVIL.
(Joe's voice) AND NOW I'M AFRAID
ONE OF THOSE COINCIDENCES
YOU HAVE SUCH
A HARD TIME WITH
OCCURRED
WITH A VERY SPECIAL PERSON.
IT WAS P's JOB TO TAKE US
TO THE DEBTORS,
SO UNTIL I SAW
THE NAME ON THE DOOR,
I HAD NO IDEA
WHOSE HOUSE WE WERE AT.
- SURE THIS IS THE RIGHT PLACE?
- YEAH.
I WAS THINKING
MAYBE IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO DO
THIS ONE ON YOUR OWN.
YEAH?
THANK YOU, JOE.
I DON'T WANT
ANYTHING DESTROYED
AND I DON'T WANT
ANYBODY HURT.
OKAY?
YOU JUST SHOW YOURSELF
AND OFFER HIM
A REASONABLE PAYMENT PLAN.
IF YOU SAY SO.
OF COURSE THAT'S HOW
I'LL DO IT.
(doorbell rings)
(Joe's voice)
WHETHER THE FEELING
WHEN I SAW JEROME AGAIN
WAS LOVE, I COULDN'T SAY.
BUT IT WAS A FEELING,
AND FAR STRONGER
THAN I LIKED.
I WAS ACTUALLY WALKING HOME
THROUGH THE ALLEY HERE.
NO TWO NEIGHBOURHOODS
ARE TOTALLY DIFFERENT
BUT STILL SO CLOSE TOGETHER
THAT THE SHORTEST ROUTE
FROM JEROME'S HOUSE
TOWARDS THE CENTRE
WAS THROUGH THE ALLEY.
(rustling)
(door closes)
HELLO!
HOW DID IT GO?
BRILLIANT.
YEAH, REALLY WELL.
I MADE A REASONABLE PAYMENT
PLAN LIKE YOU TOLD ME TO.
HOW DID HE LOOK?
SCARED.
HOW OLD DID HE LOOK?
- (unzipping)
- I DUNNO.
ANCIENT?
(laughs)
(Joe's voice) JEROME WAS
TO PAY OFF HIS DEBT
IN SIX PAYMENTS.
EVERY TIME P WENT
TO JEROME TO COLLECT,
I PACED AROUND RESTLESSLY
UNTIL SHE WAS
BACK HOME AGAIN.
I EVEN HAD TO FIND MY MOTHER'S
SAD OLD SOLITAIRE CARDS
IN ORDER TO MAKE
THE HOURS PASS.
EACH NIGHT I WAS LESS
REASSURED BY HER COMING HOME
THAN THE NIGHT BEFORE.
THE QUESTION OF WHETHER
JEALOUSY IS THE FEAR OF SHARING
OR THE FEAR OF LOSING
WAS OF LITTLE INTEREST TO ME.
BUT YES, IT WAS A FACT
THAT THIS UNWORTHY FEELING
I HAD MANAGED TO SUPPRESS
FOR SO LONG
WAS CREEPING UP ON ME.
THE EVENING SHE WAS
TO COLLECT THE FINAL PAYMENT
SHE DIDN'T KISS ME.
I TOOK IT
TO BE FORGETFULNESS,
BUT THE HOURS PASSED
AND SHE DIDN'T RETURN.
EVERY TIME
I SAW CAR LIGHTS,
I THOUGHT IT WAS P
BEING DRIVEN HOME.
(crickets chirping)
(soft snoring)
(Joe's voice)
I HAD DECIDED TO FLEE.
I COULDN'T STAY IN THIS TOWN
WITH HER AND HIM.
I HAD COWARDLY MADE A PLAN
TO ESCAPE AND HEAD SOUTH,
LIKE FROM SOME ICE AGE
I DIDN'T HAVE THE GUTS
TO TURN AROUND AND FACE.
BUT THE GOODBYE WAS SAD
AND STRANGELY UNFULFILLING.
AND SOMETHING CALLED ME ON
TO SEEK FURTHER UP
THE MOUNTAIN.
IT'S SAID TO BE DIFFICULT
TO TAKE SOMEONE'S LIFE.
I WOULD'VE SAID THAT
IT'S MORE DIFFICULT NOT TO.
FOR A HUMAN BEING,
KILLING IS THE MOST
NATURAL THING IN THE WORLD.
WE'RE CREATED FOR IT.
WONDERFUL.
(Jerome laughs)
(groaning)
(Jerome) NO, GET OFF!
- (P yelps)
- (laughs) SORRY.
- (Jerome sighs)
- (laughs)
FIREMAN'S GRIP.
(both grunt)
- (P moans)
- (mutters)
(ragged breathing)
- (blows thudding)
- (Joe whimpers)
- (moans)
- (panting)
OH. OH YEAH.
(whispering)
(spits)
(both groaning)
FILL ALL MY HOLES PLEASE.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHY
THE GUN DIDN'T WORK.
I DID CHECK TO MAKE SURE
THAT THERE WERE BULLETS
IN THE MAGAZINE.
IT SIMPLY MALFUNCTIONED,
JUST LIKE BOND'S BERETTA.
I THINK I KNOW ENOUGH
TO SAY THAT
EVEN IF YOU HAD ROUNDS IN THE
MAGAZINE OF THE WALTHER P.P.K.,
AND YOU'D TAKEN OFF
THE SAFETY...
YOU CANNOT SHOOT
UNTIL YOU RACK THE GUN.
YOU PULL AND RELEASE
THE SLIDING MECHANISM.
AND P HADN'T DONE IT
BECAUSE, AS SHE SAID,
SHE HAD NO INTENTION
OF SHOOTING THE MAN.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT BOND, BUT
I ASSUME IT HAS TO BE APPARENT
FROM HIS BOOKS
AND HIS FILMS THAT
YOU HAVE TO RACK
AN AUTOMATIC PISTOL.
OF COURSE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'VE SEEN IT IN FILMS
A THOUSAND TIMES.
IT'S MORNING.
AND THE SNOW IS GONE.
SO THE SUN MUST BE OUT?
YES, THERE IS SUN.
I'VE NEVER MANAGED TO FIGURE
OUT WHERE IT COMES FROM.
IT MUST BE SOME INTERPLAY
BETWEEN WINDOWS
AND TOWERS
AND HIGH BUILDINGS.
IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT IT'S THE SUN YOU GET
HERE AT MY PLACE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
(Seligman's voice)
IN THE BEGINNING YOU SAID THAT
YOUR ONLY SIN WAS THAT
YOU ASKED MORE OF THE SUNSET.
MEANING, I SUPPOSE,
THAT YOU WANTED
MORE FROM LIFE
THAN WAS GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU WERE A HUMAN BEING
DEMANDING YOUR RIGHT.
AND MORE THAN THAT,
YOU WERE A WOMAN
DEMANDING HER RIGHT.
DOES THAT PARDON
EVERYTHING?
DO YOU THINK
IF TWO MEN
WOULD'VE WALKED DOWN A TRAIN
LOOKING FOR WOMEN,
DO YOU THINK ANYBODY WOULD
HAVE RAISED AN EYEBROW?
OR IF A MAN HAD LED
THE LIFE YOU HAD?
AND THE STORY ABOUT MRS. H
WOULD'VE BEEN EXTREMELY
BANAL IF YOU'D BEEN A MAN
AND YOUR CONQUEST WOULD
HAVE BEEN A WOMAN.
WHEN A MAN LEAVES
HIS CHILDREN
BECAUSE OF DESIRE,
WE ACCEPT IT WITH A SHRUG,
BUT YOU AS A WOMAN,
YOU HAD TO TAKE ON A...
A GUILT, A BURDEN OF GUILT
THAT COULD NEVER
BE ALLEVIATED.
AND ALL IN ALL,
ALL THE BLAME AND GUILT
THAT PILED UP OVER THE YEARS
BECAME TOO MUCH FOR YOU,
YOU REACTED AGGRESSIVELY...
ALMOST LIKE A MAN
I HAVE TO SAY...
AND YOU FOUGHT BACK.
YOU FOUGHT BACK AGAINST
THE GENDER THAT HAD BEEN
OPPRESSING
AND MUTILATING
AND KILLING YOU
AND BILLIONS OF WOMEN.
BUT I WANTED TO KILL
A HUMAN BEING.
(Seligman's voice)
BUT YOU DIDN'T.
(Joe)
BECAUSE OF A CHANCE EVENT.
YOU CALL IT
A CHANCE EVENT.
I CALL IT
SUBCONSCIOUS RESISTANCE.
ON THE SURFACE
YOU WANTED TO KILL,
BUT DEEP DOWN YOU
CELEBRATED HUMAN WORTH
AND A VEIL OF FORGETFULNESS
DRAPED ITSELF
OVER YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF
HOW TO RACK A GUN.
(snorts)
ALTHOUGH ALL THIS SOUNDS
FRIGHTENINGLY CLOSE
TO THE CLICHÉS OF OUR TIMES...
(chuckles)
...AND I'M PREDISPOSED
TO KNOCK HOLES
IN YOUR ARGUMENTS...
I'M TOO TIRED.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
WHY DON'T YOU LAY DOWN?
YES.
LET ME JUST SAY
THAT TELLING MY STORY
AS YOU INSISTED...
OR PERMITTED...
HAS PUT ME AT EASE.
AT THIS MOMENT
MY ADDICTION IS
VERY CLEAR TO ME...
AND I'VE COME
TO A DECISION.
EVEN THOUGH
ONLY ONE IN A MILLION,
AS MY DUBIOUS
THERAPIST SAID,
SUCCEED IN...
MENTALLY, BODILY...
AND IN HER HEART
OF RIDDING HERSELF
OF HER SEXUALITY,
THIS IS NOW MY GOAL.
BUT IS THAT A LIFE
WORTH LIVING?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I CAN LIVE IT.
I WILL STAND UP
AGAINST ALL ODDS...
JUST LIKE A DEFORMED TREE
ON A HILL.
I WILL MUSTER
ALL MY STUBBORNNESS...
MY STRENGTH...
MY MASCULINE AGGRESSION.
BUT MOST OF ALL
I WANT TO SAY THANKS
TO MY NEW,
AND MAYBE FIRST FRIEND.
THANK YOU, SELIGMAN...
WHO PERHAPS IS HAPPY
WHEN ALL IS SAID AND DONE.
I'M HAPPY AT ANY RATE
THAT THE SHOT DIDN'T GO OFF
AND MADE ME A MURDERER.
IF I MAY,
I'D LIKE TO SLEEP NOW.
I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU WON'T BE DISTURBED.
(footsteps)
GOOD NIGHT, JOE.
GOOD NIGHT, SELIGMAN.
(breathing heavily)
NO!
(gun cocks)
(Seligman) BUT YOU'VE FUCKED
THOUSANDS OF MEN.
(gunshot)
- (body thuds)
- (clatters)
(rustling)
(zips)
- (shoes clatter)
- (footsteps)
- (door closes)
- (footsteps departing)
(rock music playing)
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ WHERE ARE YOU GOING
WITH THAT GUN IN YOUR HAND? ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ I SAID WHERE ARE YOU GOING
WITH THAT GUN IN YOUR HAND? ♪
♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SHOOT MY OLD LADY ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I CAUGHT HER MESSING
AROUND WITH ANOTHER MAN ♪
♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SHOOT MY OLD LADY ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I CAUGHT HER MESSING
AROUND WITH ANOTHER MAN ♪
♪ AND THAT AIN'T TOO COOL ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ I HEARD YOU SHOT
YOUR WOMAN DOWN ♪
♪ YOU SHOT HER DOWN NOW ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ I HEARD YOU SHOT
YOUR LADY DOWN ♪
♪ YOU SHOT HER DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ YES, I DID,
I SHOT HER ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I CAUGHT HER
MESSING AROUND TOWN ♪
♪ YES, I DID,
I SHOT HER ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I CAUGHT MY OLD LADY
MESSING AROUND TOWN ♪
♪ AND I GAVE HER THE GUN ♪
♪ I SHOT HER ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ WHERE YOU GONNA
GO TO NOW? ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ WHERE YOU GONNA
GO TO NOW? ♪
♪ I'M GOING
WAY DOWN SOUTH ♪
♪ WAY DOWN TO MEXICO WAY ♪
♪ I'M GOING
WAY DOWN SOUTH ♪
♪ WAY DOWN
WHERE I CAN BE FREE ♪
♪ AIN'T NO HANGMAN GONNA ♪
♪ HE AIN'T GONNA PUT
A ROPE AROUND ME ♪
♪ HEY, JOE ♪
♪ YOU'D BETTER RUN ON DOWN ♪
♪ GOOD NIGHT ♪
(vocalising)
(music fades)