FIRST PLACE
Having fun is important to me.
Doing something fun makes me happy.
Happy people are healthy people.
Which is why,
for the sake of my health and happiness,
I only do stuff I think is fun.
There's nothing
that I love more than sports
and esports.
Know why?
Because I always win.
♪ I know you'll be around ♪
♪ Shortsighted and undecided
You know where I'll be found ♪
♪ Another day smoking cigarettes ♪
♪ Apathetic, just plain pathetic
Feels like the day we first met... ♪
♪ And it's just my luck that I'm broke
And standing with you again ♪
♪ We're not growing up ♪
♪ And it's just my luck that I'm broke
And standing with you again ♪
♪ I know you'll be around ♪
♪ Shortsighted and undecided... ♪
♪ You know where I'll be found ♪
♪ Another day smoking cigarettes... ♪
♪ Apathetic, just plain pathetic
Feels like the day we first met ♪
♪ We're not growing up ♪
♪ And it's just my luck that I'm broke
And standing with you again... ♪
Defeat!
Red wins!
Are you all right?
You did awesome.
Yeah.
Go ahead, I'm going in. One down.
Two bite the dust.
Okay.
Dang, I'm out. Come on, back me up.
Ah! They dropped a smoke screen.
I can't keep 'em out.
- Ah, I died!
- He's moving in.
I'll shoot 'em down. Move over.
Okay, I'll take the stairs then.
No, I died. They're closing in on you.
They're all gonna die.
Go, Diarrhea! Go, Diarrhea!
- I'll take them out!
- Go, Diarrhea!
- Assholes!
- Diarrhea!
Fuck! I can't concentrate, you guys!
Oh! Fuck yeah!
DAD
- That was fun!
- Hello?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
- I'll be right back.
- Be quick.
Yep.
MIGHTY CHICKEN
- Be safe.
- Yep!
Sun-jung emo.
Chicken is here.
Aw, thank you so much.
This is a freebie.
Are you, like, a psychic?
Oh, hey! Come by next week.
- Touch up the blonde.
- I need to?
Thank you. Thank you.
Hold on, I'm almost there.
We're playing now.
And make it quick.
- Uh-huh.
- Speed pedal.
Okay.
Stop, that's enough.
- Why are you messing with me?
- Stop!
Hmm?
- Oh.
- Stop fighting.
What's going on?
Son of a bitch!
Come here, you little...
Come at me. Goddamn it!
Whoa.
Asshole!
Oh, huh.
- Get off me! Get off me!
- Stop fighting me.
I said, get off! Fuck you!
Let go...
Fine, I'll go with you.
Damn it.
- I won't cuff you, so let's go quietly.
- All right.
Fucking shit!
Fuck!
You fucker!
Hey, hey!
Asshole!
- Fucker!
- Hey, stop, stop!
Break it up! Break it up!
- He's really hurt.
- What the fuck do you want?
Son of a bitch!
- You piece of...
- That's enough.
You want some?!
What's his deal?
Oh.
- Whoa. Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Thanks for your help.
- Sure.
This could have ended very differently.
I can't thank you enough.
It was no problem at all.
On the count of three.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROBATION OFFICE
One, two, three.
- He's tall and buff as hell.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you for all you've done.
- Of course.
- Get home safely.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'd like to introduce you to my director.
- Hello.
- Welcome, Jung-do-ssi.
- Oh.
I'm in charge
of the Electronic Monitoring Division.
I'm Director Kim Sun-min.
It's great to meet you.
Likewise.
Would you be able to spare me
a few minutes right now?
Uh-huh.
There are about 5,000 former inmates
wearing electronic ankle tags nationwide.
People who have committed violent crimes,
like homicide and sexual violence.
And many are re-offenders.
Which is why
there are probation officers like me.
We monitor the re-offenders 24-7,
utilizing electronic anklets, with GPS.
Ah, so then the guy that I helped was a...
That was Supervisor Cho
you previously helped.
He's our martial arts officer.
The former inmates we monitor can
cause trouble every now and again though.
Mmm.
When something like that happens,
we have to get to the spot fast,
to ensure that everyone is safe.
Ah, but as we get up there in age...
...we're not all as physically capable
of catching them as we'd like.
Mm.
So therefore, each officer teams up
with a strong young partner.
Typically, they're called
martial arts officers.
Ah, martial arts officer. Oh.
Jung-do-ssi, may I ask
what do you do for work?
I deliver.
My abeoji runs a chicken shop.
That's surprising because Supervisor Cho
made it sound like you do tae kwon do
or judo professionally,
you were so impressive.
- Do you?
- Not for a living.
But in both tae kwon do and judo,
I'm a third dan.
- Wow.
- Kendo too.
- I'm a third dan.
- Wow.
Can I please ask you a favor?
No.
Of course. Yes, please, ask away.
The thing is,
the martial arts officers in our division
are currently on
a triple-shift rotation schedule.
But because of Supervisor Cho's injuries,
the two other martial arts officers
now have to pull 12-hour shifts.
Mmm.
That means they have to work for 12 hours
and come back to work
12 hours later, on repeat.
- Yeah, that's pretty intense.
- It is.
The work we do is somewhat difficult.
Realistically, it's near impossible
to find someone
to fill in just for the five weeks
Supervisor Cho is recovering.
But he told me, when he saw you
and how you were... handling
the former inmate with such ease,
he thought that it would be
nothing short of a miracle
if you might be willing to help us out.
Oh. Uh, but would I even qualify though?
Yeah, you're pretty much in.
Tae kwon do, hapkido, judo, or kendo,
and because you have
a third dan behind you,
you'll definitely be in.
Jung-do-ssi, your skills
are more than enough.
Uh, but is it
something I'll have fun doing?
That's the most important thing for me.
Well,
something "fun" can be defined differently
for each individual.
But I can say, it's such a rewarding job
and work we're proud of.
What we do helps keep civilians safe.
But...
Is that, um, something cool?
Yeah, it is.
It's something where you'll learn a lot,
and by working with us,
you could have fun too.
Hmm.
I know about this because
I've done research for my writing.
You get an anklet because of murder
or another violent crime.
Most of what you'd do is chase
and catch people. It might be a good fit.
- Why?
- Adrenaline.
- I think you'd like it too.
- For sure.
What do you think about me
filling in for a martial arts officer?
The triple shift sounds pretty rough.
- Why do you think it'd be rough?
- It'll ruin his sleep cycle.
Diarrhea is in great shape.
- I'll be fine.
- Might be too intense.
Can you stop changing your mind?
- Stop telling me what to do.
- Go ahead and try.
Thank you.
They told me I'd have to chase
and catch the guys if necessary.
But what do you think?
I'd be happy to see you take on
a new challenge and learn things.
You got a commendation,
and I'm proud of you.
You are?
Yeah, and, uh, I'm on board.
I'll be able to manage the restaurant,
so worry about you.
Sounds good.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROBATION OFFICE
Can I have everyone's attention?
Meet Lee Jung-do.
While Supervisor Cho is recovering,
he'll be helping us out.
Let's welcome him
with a warm round of applause.
Hello.
This is our senior martial arts officer,
Huh Dong-won.
Hello.
Supervisor Huh will be showing you
how to use the program.
- Great.
- Take good care of him.
- No worries.
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
These numbers here
are the former inmates we monitor.
Oh...
The people here include
someone who raped a ten-year-old boy
and someone who killed his own parents.
JANG HO-SIK
87%/HOMICIDE
When the anklet battery drops to 30%,
those green icons turn yellow.
And when that happens,
we call them and persuade them nicely
to charge up their anklet.
So, uh, what do you think's the next step
if they won't comply?
Go there?
- Nice.
- We go there.
Right.
You'll be overwhelmed
if I explain everything at once.
For now,
if you're unsure of anything,
just ask Director Kim.
I will. Thanks.
No problem.
Hey there, I'm calling
because your battery's down to 30% now.
It would be good to charge it.
Oh, you're out with a friend?
I think he's doing better
than we expected.
Really? I'm so glad to hear that.
Hmm?
LOW BATTERY DETECTED
LEE YANG-HO
30%/SEX CRIME
DATE OF BIRTH: MAY 24, 2003
He's 20?
How did it go?
Choi Jong-hwa-ssi swore at me
and pushed me when I told him to go home,
so you could say I struggled a little.
I was hoping he would just listen to me.
I wish he would seriously stop doing that.
- Hello?
- Oh.
- Is this... Lee Yang-ho-ssi's phone?
- Yes.
I'm just calling as a reminder
to make sure that you charge...
- Who is it?
- I didn't order jjajangmyeon.
Hello?
Jjajangmyeon?
REDIAL
Oh, the call got disconnected.
I heard you the first time,
fucking bitch. Hang up.
Hello?
This customer is
not receiving calls at this time.
Please leave a message after the tone.
- Extra charges may apply.
- Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
- Try texting.
- Okay.
- Also...
- Director Kim.
We should go. He's ignoring me.
Who? And go where?
Lee Yang-ho-nim, he... hung up on me twice,
and now he's not answering my calls.
- When was Lee Yang-ho released?
- Three months ago.
He seemed to be on his best behavior.
I met with him the other day.
- All right, give Jung-do his equipment.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll meet you at the parking lot.
- You got it.
- Come with me.
- Oh, sure.
- Put this armor on.
- Whoa.
It's heavy.
- So this vest can really stop a knife?
- It prevents slashing injuries.
But if the point is direct,
you'll probably bruise.
Your bodycam needs to be
turned on before you get started.
- Oh.
- Here's your Taser.
I'm allowed to use one?
Director Kim has to give you the go-ahead.
- Cool.
- Put this in here.
How'd he end up in jail?
He raped a middle-school girl.
Whoa.
Do you think I could shock him a little?
Only if it's absolutely necessary.
Our priority is to keep watch
over these guys and... prevent trouble.
Ah, right.
What is it?
Did you see something, Jung-do-ssi?
Right there. 201.
It's probably there.
I've delivered to so many buildings
that I can roughly figure out the layout.
See that window?
No security grille.
But that window has one.
He removed it,
so it's easier for him to run away.
I bet if you knock on his door,
he'll probably jump down there,
and that's where I can pounce on him.
And what if he runs out the front door?
Then I'll meet you there.
Yeah?
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
Yang-ho-kun.
- Open the door.
- It's nothing. Ignore it.
I know you're inside.
- I know that you're in there.
- Goddamn it!
What the fuck does he want?!
Yang-ho-kun, I know you're...
Fuck!
You son of a bitch!
I told you to leave me alone.
- Please help!
- I'm trying to sleep!
- Once I open this...
- Open the door!
Why don't you get lost,
you stupid piece of shit?
Open the door!
What's going on in there? Hello?
O... open the door!
Ahjussi, please help me!
- Ah, shit.
- Please.
Fuck.
Whoa, man!
Wow.
Oh, Director Kim.
Lee Yang-ho-ssi, you're under arrest
for failing to comply with
electronic monitoring conditions
and for disobeying the guidance
of your probation officer.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law,
and you do have the right to an attorney.
ABNORMAL MOVEMENT DETECTED
LEE JONG-IN
82%/SEX CRIME
HIGH-RISK AREA: CHILDCARE FACILITIES
Director Kim!
JUNGANG DAY CARE CENTER
Oh, oh. Stop.
- Huh?
- Oh shit.
Hey!
Oh shit, man!
Ow!
Ow! Shit!
Son of a bitch.
Just... just let me go!
- Let you go?!
- Yeah. What's your fucking problem?
- You crazy...
- Calm down.
Just try to hit me!
Look at me. Hey.
He's trying to provoke you.
You need to calm down.
I'm not trying to provoke you,
you piece of shit. Don't hold back!
- Hey, shut your big mouth!
- Stop! Don't.
Calm down, please.
I won't repeat myself.
I know. I get it. I understand. Please.
Calm down.
I know. I get it.
Jung-do-ssi.
- I know. I'm sorry.
- Why are you sorry?
That was cool.
Thank you.
That was a long day, yeah?
Can I buy you dinner?
Oh. Uh...
I'm, uh, supposed to meet up
with my friends soon.
- Oh, some other time, then.
- Could you take us all out for a meal?
Oh, sure!
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Oh man, it's no big deal. Come on.
Diarrhea's boss is
taking us out for samgyeopsal.
Yay!
CAST IRON KIMCHI AND PORK BELLY
Hello.
Oh, yes. Hello. Hi.
I'm Writer K.
I've heard so much about you.
Yes, I'm Kim Sun-min.
It's so nice to meet you all.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello, I'm Moisture.
- Thank you for inviting us all.
- Sure.
How did you get "Moisture"
as your nickname?
His nose always looks wet.
Hence the nickname.
It does.
It's grease, or maybe it's sweat,
but nobody knows.
I'm pretty sure
it's half-sweat, half-grease.
I see!
This is Earthworm.
- "Earthworm"?
- Because I squirm when I'm stepped on.
Like an earthworm.
He's too nice for his own good.
- He will never get angry at you.
- Oh!
All right, I think It's time to eat.
- Yeah.
- Please, sit.
- Yes, thank you.
- Go ahead.
What are you in the mood for?
We can start with the combination
of delectable minari
and flavorful samgyeopsal,
then segue into the spicy kimchi jeongol
before we wrap it up
with the delicious crispy bbokeumbap.
A perfectly balanced meal,
rich in healthy carbs, protein, and fat.
Yes, please, order all that.
- Thank you.
- No prob.
He described it like a story.
- Twenty servings?
- Yes.
And we'll get five servings
of kimchi jeongol.
Twenty-five in total?
Including the five servings
of the jeongol.
Hand me your glass.
Oh, I don't have
the enzymes to break down alcohol.
Oh.
And I'm more fun sober than anyone wasted.
Okay. Here.
- This looks so good.
- Thank you.
It's so nice to meet you, Moisture-ssi.
- You too, Earthworm-ssi.
- Same.
- All right, shall we drink up?
- Yes.
- All righty.
- Cheers.
I did some research on probation officers
while I was working on one of my scripts.
Oh, nice.
I know that it's a very stressful job
that involves many dangerous tasks.
Why did you decide to go into probation?
I was in a car accident when I was little.
Ah...
Our car wasn't even moving.
But someone suddenly came
and crashed into the back of our car.
The rear doors all caved in,
and I couldn't even move my legs
because they were completely stuck.
Whoa.
And the engine caught on fire. Whoa.
I was only ten years old.
A ten-year-old had to
think about death in that moment.
"Whoa! This is how I die?"
I would've played video games nonstop
instead of studying
if I knew I'd die like this."
I couldn't stop thinking about
all my New Year's money
I had stashed in my drawer.
I was so upset about it!
Anyway, um...
...some cops arrived to save us,
and they ripped the whole door off,
working to save me.
Oh...
I decided that I would become
a police officer,
to save people and pay forward
the help I had received that day.
- Mm.
- But I had an issue.
The growth plate in my leg
was damaged in the accident.
- Oh man.
- So my left leg is shorter than my right.
Because of that, I knew I wouldn't be able
to run around and catch criminals,
and...
...and then I wondered...
what would come second?
So then
I learned about probation officers.
Mm.
The fact that I could contribute
to reducing recidivism
got me deeply motivated to do this work.
Then once I got married
and became a father,
um, my job became more meaningful to me.
Why?
There were a lot
of sex offenses involving children
among the formerly incarcerated
that we monitor.
It's my dream
that we can have a world where
children are always protected and safe.
- Wow.
Oh!
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
All right. Let's eat!
Uh, we're wondering
if we might be able
to call you our hyung-nim.
Garlic.
But the thing is,
you have to pass a little test first.
This lettuce wrap is
filled with our loyalty,
our sincerity, and friendship.
And all that we need
is for you to eat this in one bite.
- Say ah!
- Ah!
Ah!
Hyung-nim,
hyung-nim, hyung-nim...
This is way too big!
...hyung-nim,
hyung-nim, hyung-nim,
hyung-nim, hyung-nim, hyung-nim,
hyung-nim, hyung-nim...
Yeah!
LOW BATTERY DETECTED
HAN JUN-GU
30%/KIDNAPPING
...receiving calls at this time.
Yo, Han Jun-gu-ssi's battery is at 30%,
but his phone is off.
What is this?
Who is it?
MIN DO-WOONG
That was such a great meal.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing?
- Thank you for the dinner, hyung-nim!
- I'm blushing.
I can't imagine if I had bought you steak.
There's a beef restaurant
just up the street if you want!
ASSISTANT MANAGER YOON DONG-JU
Mm-hmm?
Director Kim, where are you right now?
What's going on?
One of the former inmates is MIA,
so we have to go track him down,
but Min Do-woong-ssi broke the rules
and is somewhere in Seorin-dong,
but when I call, he's not answering me.
Actually, I'm in Seorin-dong now.
I can go.
Um, what was it he did time for?
He served 20 years
for second-degree murder.
Released three months ago.
Do you know
anybody he has a grudge against out here?
That I haven't figured out yet,
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it. I got it.
Hyung-nim, we can probably get there
in five minutes if we run.
How about one minute?
Ooh! Oh!
CRIME CATEGORY: MANSLAUGHTER
You guys stay in the car. You hear?
- Yes.
- We'll be back.
- That way?
- Yes.
- What's happening?
- He's cut off the anklet.
How do we track him down?
- We go to the address.
- Okay.
Do! Here.
He cut it off with a knife.
Should we call the police?
No, he can't be far,
so let's catch him quickly.
Hyung, Moisture has a drone.
Why don't we try that?
- Think it would help?
- It's worth a shot.
- Oh, here. You can follow it here.
- Oh.
Whoa!
This way. Can it go this way?
Yup.
This must be him.
Where's he going?
I'll go after him, hyung.
- I'll tag along.
- No, no.
I'll run and get him. I'll be quick.
He's got a knife!
Don't you worry about that.
After all, it's my duty
as a martial arts officer
to protect my partner.
I'll be back.
Dumbass.
Put an earbud in.
This way, I'll give directions.
Oh, okay.
I'll be right back!
Be careful.
Go straight ahead. Keep going.
Make a left.
You passed it. You passed the alley.
Go back, back, back.
- Hurry, faster.
- Keep going?
Yes, keep going.
Hey, Jung-do, I'm sorry.
But can you go a bit faster?
You're really close,
almost there.
A little faster and you'll make it
to him in no time. Go to the right.
On your right.
On my right? Right, where is he?
Where? Which right?
Do you see the two buildings
with rooftops on your right?
You'll see him past those buildings.
- Two rooftops? Where?
- You don't see them at all?
One, two. Okay.
You bastard!
Come out, you son of a bitch!
Come out!
Ji Hyeok-jun, die, die, die!
Come out and face me!
I'm gonna kill you! Come out!
Min Do-woong-ssi!
What?
Hi.
I'm a mar...
martial arts officer.
And?
I'm here to finish it all off tonight.
Yeah, that's why I'm here.
Let's go back quietly.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Goddamn it!
Jung-do, what's wrong? Jung-do-ya?
Are you all right?
You can come now, hyung.
Coming now. I'll be right there.
Ow, shit.
Hey!
Leave or I'm gonna kill myself.
Hyung, I need your help.
What's going on?
Um, right now,
he's holding a knife to his throat.
Jung-do-ya, I need you to be my voice.
What?
Relay my words to him.
Leave!
Uh-huh.
Min Do-woong-ssi.
"Min Do-woong-ssi."
It seems like your day was really hard.
"It seems like your day was really hard."
Did you
get into a fight with a friend?
"Did you get into a fight with a friend?"
Late... lately,
I swear I'm trying really hard
to be a good guy lately.
But that son of a bitch,
he kept making fun of me
in front of the others,
for wearing that damn ankle tag,
and... it's really unfair.
It makes me so angry
that I can't even sleep.
And I wanna kill him off,
and then I'll die!
Do-woong-nim.
"Do-woong-nim."
"I understand you."
"Life was already so difficult."
And more piled on top of it all,
it really tested your limits.
"If you give up your life,
you'd be wasting
those twenty years you spent repenting."
"Wouldn't that be unfair to you?"
You might've slipped up
and needed a drink too.
I'll write a report that's light.
You'll only get a minor penalty.
"I promise, I'll do my best."
"Can I ask you to drop the knife?"
You mustn't repeat the same mistake.
"You have to win at your life."
"Hang in there just a little longer."
"That day will come
when you can remove the anklet."
"Until that day arrives,
I promise I'll be here."
I mean that.
"I mean that."
- I'm home.
- Hey, you.
- How was work?
- Not too bad.
Well, my director...
He's really
kinda cool.
I'm glad.
- Go wash up. Let's eat these apples.
- All right.
Beginning in May 1998,
Kang Ki-jung has managed to elude
the police dragnet for four years.
During that time, he sexually assaulted
15 young girls under the age of 13.
Oh man, what a sick piece of work.
And given the fact
that he has committed sexual offenses
against these young children,
we can say that Kang Ki-jung has
a higher rate of recidivism upon release,
even when compared to other sex offenders.
We need a task force. Any ideas?
Three teams with a probation
and martial arts officer
on a triple-shift rotation schedule
to monitor Kang Ki-jung around the clock.
A triple shift?
Each of our probation officers
has to monitor
over twenty former inmates at the moment.
If we have to monitor Kang Ki-jung
on top of that,
we won't be able
to closely monitor the others properly.
I know that you're all
already working overtime.
The problem is that it's not that easy
to get a budget increase,
but I'll push harder for it.
Thank you, come again.
Have a nice day.
Emo.
Hey, long time no see!
How are you?
I'm very good, of course.
Did you come in
for your root touch-up today?
Uh, no, no.
Hmm? Oh, then what?
I want a clean cut, emo.
SAEMGOL CHARCOAL GRILLED ENTRAILS
- Supervisor Huh.
- Hey, Jung-do.
- Hi.
- You're in pretty early today.
I am.
You changed your hair.
- Uh, yes.
- Nice. It looks great.
Thank you so much.
KIM GUM-NAM
79%/SEX CRIME
CRIME CATEGORY: SEX CRIME
HIGH-RISK
Can I get another bottle?
Yes.
KIM GUM-NAM
79%/SEX CRIME
Hmm? Oh.
- Hello, hello.
- You changed your hair. Looks nice.
- Thank you so much. Director Kim. Chief.
- Hey.
I saw a suspicious guy on my way here.
Could I borrow you for a sec?
He touched a young server.
She looked uncomfortable,
and now he's on the move.
Shouldn't we go there just in case?
It might end up being nothing.
- Let's try calling him to check.
- Right.
It's playtime.
Today, I'm gonna do
whatever the fuck I want.
You were right. We have a problem.
Huh?
Did he cut it off?
I think he's somewhere with no connection.
Where was he when you saw him last?
Uh, sorry for barging in.
Was this man here in this restaurant?
Uh-huh.
Which way did he go?
Left or right?
I'm sorry, but I don't know.
Oh, right.
He told me that today was his birthday
and invited me over to his place,
but I declined.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for your time.
I'll go down here. You go there.
Uh-huh. Got it.
- Hey, Jung-do-ya!
- Yes?
Check shops where there's
only one woman working.
Okay, yeah.
If it gets too hot,
just let me know, okay?
I will.
- Hello.
- Excuse me, hi.
You... you're okay, aren't you?
What?
Nothing, nev... never mind, take care.
May I help you?
Why did you lock the door behind you?
What do you want?
Oh yeah!
Sh.
Earlier, you told me to come again,
so I'm here.
Emo! Sun-jung emo!
Fucking stop that!
Emo, are you all right? Are you okay?
Uh-huh? Okay.
Oh shit.
Oh shit. Shit.
Shit.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Oh shit.
You have...
you have, uh...
uh, the right to...
It'll be used against you...
used against you and...
Mm.
Emo. Emo.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm really sorry that I'm late.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's all right.
You saved me.
You came.
- There you are.
- You're awake? Why so early?
To make you breakfast. Come on.
Unusual.
Sun-jung-ssi dropped by the restaurant.
She said you saved her.
How is Sun-jung emo's face?
It looked a little bit swollen,
but she'll be okay.
- That's a relief.
- Try this.
Mm-hmm. Ooh!
I'm not sure how it'll taste.
Mmm, pretty good.
- It's okay?
- Yeah.
Appa,
when you were my age,
what made you happiest?
When I was your age...
I was my happiest when I was on stage.
Rehearsing with my friends,
sweating together,
spraying saliva on each other
while acting passionately.
All the hard work.
Seeing how the audience enjoyed themselves
watching my work brought me joy.
Even if you're doing things
to make yourself happy,
inspiring others is much better.
It's an incredible feeling
when the passionate energy
that's in your heart
can be connected and shared
inside someone else's heart too.
That's the best feeling.
Mm.
Huh.
Mm!
The head office will send
two probation officers
for the task force
in charge of Kang Ki-jung.
And the Ministry of Economy and Finance
will increase budget
for two additional martial arts officers.
I asked for more
to help lighten our load a little,
but it was denied.
I'm sorry.
Fourteen out of fifteen sexual offenses
Kang Ki-jung committed
all took place immediately before
or after school hours.
Whoever monitors him
during the day is the most important.
I will take on the responsibility.
But
will you be all right with a double shift?
What about your kid?
This is one way I can protect my child.
- Director.
- Hello.
- Chief.
Make sure you post the job openings today.
I'll get started right away.
- Hello.
- You working tonight?
Can I borrow you?
Why don't you go ahead?
- See you later.
- Uh-huh.
Hyung.
About this job...
Yeah?
I wanna keep helping.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Jung-do-ya.
In ten days from now,
I'll be transferring to the task force
who'll be monitoring a serial rapist.
Ah. Uh-huh.
Would you like to be my partner?
Hyung, I'm honored you want me
on your team. Of course I'll follow you.
We are invincible together.
Kang Ki-jung,
a man who served a 20-year sentence
for sexually assaulting 15 children,
will be released today.
For the next ten years, he will wear
a GPS-enabled electronic tracking device.
Jung-do-ya.
What is that?
- Try it on.
- This is mine?
Hold on.
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
PROBATION & PAROLE
I appreciate this.
JEONAN PRISON
Kang Ki-jung-ssi,
you must never deliberately remove,
damage, or disable the ankle monitor
by jamming signals
or manipulating our data, and so on.
You will be under 24-hour surveillance
from our probation officers
following your release, and we may track
your movements whenever we decide.
Is that understood?
Yes.
Put your foot up,
whichever one you prefer.
You may now put your shoes on
and stand up.
You can use this phone
until you have the means to buy one.
We're leaving now.
Kang Ki-jung, sex-offender of children,
will soon return to society
upon completing his 20-year sentence.
Many residents and members of civic groups
have been waiting in front of his house
since the early hours of the morning.
The police are also on the scene,
preparing to prevent
any altercations that may take place.
Send Kang Ki-jung to Jeju Island!
Don't let that monster
in our neighborhood!
This is dangerous. Please stay calm.
Let us pass through. Move to the side.
Give him the death penalty!
Move to a different country!
Please move back!
Please stay calm.
Get out of the way.
- It's dangerous. Make way.
- Asshole!
Give Kang Ki-jung
the death penalty!
Are we paying taxes so rapists like him
can get a comfortable ride home?
Fuck that!
Death penalty!
Death penalty! Death penalty!
Stay back, stay back!
What are you...
You guys see this? What the hell?
I'm not the criminal! Let me go!
Death penalty!
Death penalty! Death penalty!
Death penalty! Death... Get off me!
Don't let him go!
- You fucking seeing this?!
- What's that guy doing?!
Move!
Get out of my way!
Please move back. Everyone, back.
Kang Ki-jung-ssi, is there anything
you'd like to say to the victims?
- Kang Ki-jung-ssi! Kang Ki-jung-ssi!
- Move it. Walk faster.
Answer me. Please answer
the question, Kang Ki-jung-ssi!
What are you looking at?
Keep it moving.
- Get him inside.
- Come on.
This used to be
a quiet, peaceful neighborhood.
I know.
- All clear?
- Yes, I think so.
Hey, come on.
- Let's patrol this block one last time.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Did you see him earlier?
- He's hard to miss.
- And his face is intimidating.
- It is.
All the residents in this area
must be terrified with him moving in.
What happened to you?!
You beefed up.
It helped me with my stress.
Here, put this on. It's a cool jacket.
Oh.
Let's go smoke on the roof.
Yeah, right.
Hey, I've been wearing this
for three years.
They can't detect your movements
going up or down in the same building.
You can go wherever you want
if it's under ten meters.
The GPS... is kind of a joke in accuracy.
- Man.
- Have you thought about it?
About the thing I wrote in my letter.
Yeah, let's do it.
He's on the move.
- Where's he going?
- Hyung, would it be okay if I go tail him?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
I think if we wait around,
we'll... end up behind.
I want you to always be careful.
Always keep your earphone in.
I'll be monitoring.
Okay.
I can't see him yet, hyung.
Kang Ki-jung hasn't stopped anywhere.
He's still walking.
Let me know when you spot him.
I will.
There he is.
- Could you turn right here, please?
- Sure.
Slow down. Please slow down
and drive slowly.
Hyung, Kang Ki-jung is
entering a building.
- I'm getting out.
- Okay, okay. Just be careful.
I will. Thank you.
Uh-huh.
I have no idea which way he went.
Can you tell me what you spot around you?
From the second to the fifth floors,
it's all kids' academies.
It's too early.
The kids will still be in school.
I don't think he went up.
I'll check underground.
I'll get straight to the point.
I distribute a very specific type
of video content.
You'll be creating videos with children,
and I'll take care of all the distribution
on the dark web.
I'll pay you ten million won
per ten-minute video.
Byung-soon-ssi will help you
record and edit the videos.
And as for the children,
we'll procure them for you.
You have absolutely
nothing to lose.
Sounds good to me.
Someone's here.
Who's that?
He must've followed me
because of the ankle monitor.
He can't see inside the car,
so don't move.
Jung-do-ya, you still okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm still looking.
Five times five is 25.
All good.
I think that prick saw our license plate.
You'll take care of him, right?
I'll handle him quietly.
What's up? You find anything?
I can't find him. The parking lot is huge.
What should we do?
Jung-do-ya, I'll call Kang Ki-jung.
I'll put it on speaker,
so listen carefully.
Got it, yeah.
Hello?
Kang Ki-jung-ssi?
- I'm calling from the probation office.
- Yes, hello.
Uh, it took you quite a while
to answer the phone.
Oh, sorry.
I'm not used to carrying one around,
so I didn't know you were calling.
Oh, I see.
Could you please tell me where you are?
Uh...
Of course. I just stepped out
to have some gimbap.
Ah, gimbap, huh?
I'll go there now. Buy me some time.
Oh, well, um, Kang Ki-jung-ssi,
about your anklet.
If it's uncomfortable at all for you,
we can adjust the fit for you, no problem.
Would you like to make any adjustments?
No, it fits fine.
Also, as a service,
we can provide support and resources
to help with your job search.
What kind of job
do you think you might be looking for?
I'm good on jobs.
He's sitting in the gimbap place.
Hmm, well, all right.
Enjoy your meal, and, uh, from now on,
please make sure
you answer your phone a little faster.
Sorry about that.
I appreciate the call.
Take care.
I checked on my way back.
There are a lot of gimbap places
near Kang Ki-jung's house.
- The wheels in his head must be spinning.
- Yeah.
It makes me anxious.
We can't tail him
every single time he leaves the house.
I know, but I'm gonna try my best.
I mean it.
- Director Kim.
- Oh, Min-jo-ya!
- You're here!
- Hello.
- There he is.
- Welcome back.
- You all healed?
- Yes.
I'm coming back to work tomorrow.
And I hear you're working with us
from here on out.
Oh. Uh, yes.
Ah. Here.
What's this?
It's for you. I figured you'd need it
while you're working.
That's so nice.
- Can I open it?
- It's a pair of tactical gloves.
Wow. This is awesome.
They look nice.
- I'll use them well. Thank you.
- Make sure you don't get hurt, all right?
I'll be careful.
Task Force! I believe in you.
- We got this!
Hi! Aw, you're so cute.
Why are you out here all alone?
Can we be friends?
Your name is... Wawa.
You're Lee Yang-ho, yeah?
How's the location? Sweet, yeah?
Shit.
We've gotta do it here,
otherwise your anklet will give it away.
Shouldn't we seal the door
and the windows so no sound escapes?
Don't you worry about that.
All righty. We've found our actress,
and here's your signing bonus.
Just don't make any mistakes tomorrow.
That's our next step.
- If you fill this out, and this.
- Okay.
- Both?
- Yes, sign all those lines.
LEE YANG-HO
- Got it.
- Fill everything out.
This customer
is not receiving calls at this time.
KANG KI-JUNG
77%/SEX CRIME
Director, you know Lee Yang-ho?
Yeah. Why?
His battery is at 30%. His phone's off.
He lives in Seorin-dong,
but he's in Dongrin-dong.
One minute.
LEE JUNG-DO
BIG BRO SUN-MIN
Hey, hyung.
Hey, where are you?
Just watching him get a haircut.
Mm. Hey, is it okay if I step out
with Min-jo to see Lee Yang-ho?
Uh...
Yeah, I think it'll be fine.
He has to be home
in less than an hour anyway.
I'm aware.
Make sure you call me if anything happens.
Will do.
Please let me go!
Please don't kill me!
Please, just let me go. Please!
Just let me go.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Oh jeez.
Don't kill me, please. Please, I beg...
My, my. Ya here to fight?
Man, you're dead meat, you fucking prick.
- You little shit.
- You good?
I told you that I would kill you,
fucking son of a bitch.
- What are you looking at, fucker?
- We should get out of here.
Let's get of here. Run!
Whoa!
- He's gettin' serious!
- Wow, I'm so scared.
Fuck!
Hey, get him!
What the fuck?
- Son of a bitch!
- Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
Hey, come here!
Hey, you little...
You moron! Fucking asshole!
- Fuck!
- Min-jo-ya!
- Please just get out of here, sir!
- Min-jo-ya...
Hey, I said I'd kill you, fucking moron.
Shit.
Fucking idiot!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck, you little shit!
- Hey, asshole!
- You piece of shit!
I can't get out!
Are you dead? Hey.
Wake up, fucker.
How can you already be dead? I barely...
Director, are you all right?
That piece of sh...
Idiot! Get that shithead!
- Come here!
Bastard.
Son of a bitch!
You dumb fuck.
You bastard!
Shit! Get him!
- You little shit!
- Son of a bitch!
Shithead!
Damn it!
Shit.
You son of a bitch!
- Shit.
- Hurry up and go after him, damn it!
You fucking prick.
Shit, fucker!
Die, motherfucker!
Hey, you asshole!
You think you can...
BIG BRO SUN-MIN
This customer is not receiving calls
Here comes Actor Kang.
Excuse me! Did something happen?
- Call the police, now!
- Oh, okay, okay!
Hey!
Son of a bitch!
Die, damn it!
It's okay.
Everything's all right.
Ah, shit!
Let's go. Come on!
- We have to go!
- Let me go!
Shit! There's no time for this!
It's over there. Right there.
Shit.
Freeze, Kang Ki-jung.
Move, and I'll fire. Stay where you are!
If you move, I'll shoot you!
Patrol 15.
An unidentified man and officer are hurt.
Kang Ki-jung... Kang Ki-jung's on the run.
Requesting backup immediately.
Sir, are you all right?
Which division are you from?
Martial arts officer.
Hello, sir.
I called you.
I'm Supervisor Han Dong-hoon.
Oh, hello.
What happened to my son?
He was stabbed at the scene of the crime.
Sorry? S... stabbed? W... what do you mean?
We apologize.
Jung-do-ya. Jung...
Jung-do-ya.
You said it was only minor.
You call stabbing a minor injury?!
My apologies.
I didn't want you to worry
before you got here,
so I tried to avoid too many details.
Why did you have my son respond to
someone who was swinging a knife?!
We apologize.
Appa.
Jung-do-ya.
Are you okay?
Has Kang Ki-jung been captured?
He was able to remove the monitor,
but the police are tracking him down.
They're on the move now,
so we'll get him soon.
What about the girl?
Resting at home.
How's...
how's Director Kim?
Director Kim's neck was broken,
and... he's undergoing surgery.
But doesn't breaking his neck mean
that he'll be paralyzed?
Thankfully, the injury didn't damage
any nerves, so he'll be all right.
It'll take him a while to recover though.
Jung-do-ssi.
Cho Min-jo's been
declared brain-dead.
The police have launched an investigation.
He suffered
from cardiac arrest.
Supervisor Cho
had signed consent for organ donation,
and his family
would like to respect his decision.
This wraps up
the Brave Citizen Award Ceremony.
Thank you all for joining us today.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
You're... Min-ju's savior.
Ah, uh...
Right, sorry, I'm her emo.
Ah.
Hello.
I apologize for not coming sooner.
Oh, no. No worries.
I wanted to, uh,
to thank you
for saving Min-ju's life the other day.
Oh.
Uh...
Thank you.
Oh, and one more thing.
This is from Min-ju.
She asked me to give you this.
Uh...
HELLO, UNCLE
I'M MIN-JU, THE GIRL YOU SAVED
BEFORE YOU SHOWED UP, I WAS REALLY SCARED
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER SEE MY PARENTS AGAIN
BUT THANKS TO YOU, I COULD SEE THEM AGAIN
YOU EVEN GOT HURT SAVING ME
THANK YOU
Is Min-ju doing all right now?
She's still too scared
to leave the house for any reason.
She relives what happened in her dreams.
Even so,
when I talk about you with her,
she just perks right up.
She's staying strong.
I came by to thank you for saving her.
I can't thank you enough.
Many people are saying that the punishment
for serial rapist Kang Ki-jung
was far too light.
What's your take on it, Professor Kim?
It is true that our penalties
for sex offenders
are considerably lighter when compared
to those of other countries.
- Right.
- A few years ago, attempts...
- Hi!
- You're here!
- Hey, dude. Have some pizza.
- I'm back.
No, I'm not hungry.
...concerned that it might lead
to over-punishment.
Mm-hmm.
I think we can all agree
that sexual assault,
especially sex crimes against children,
should never be tolerated
or forgiven, no matter what.
Hyung.
You know how I rescued that little girl?
I met her emo today.
She's always home,
still too scared to go out.
The thing is, she did nothing wrong.
Kang Ki-jung sexually harmed children
while evading the police dragnet
for over four years.
He won't be easily caught.
I'm on your side.
But... you're still recovering.
You can't get hurt again.
Let the police handle it.
Hey, guys.
Shouldn't we still try to do
what we can to help out?
That's what I was thinking
the entire time
you were having that conversation.
Mmm.
Even the police are
struggling to track him down.
Would we get in their way though?
That's why we should help,
not hinder them.
Sometimes, it's ordinary people
who catch the criminals.
I saw a car while tailing Kang Ki-jung.
But the windows were so tinted
that I couldn't get a good look.
The fact I couldn't see inside
keeps bothering me.
What was the car's make and plate number?
Range Rover, 100-TA-5525.
"100-TA-5525."
All right, I'll go ask my hyung.
Okay.
I can go home next week,
so get me some equipment, guys.
Send a group text of what you need.
Okay.
VEHICLE SEARCH
LICENSE PLATE NUMBER
- Will this fit Diarrhea?
- Yeah.
VEHICLE OWNER SEARCH
KIM MIN-WOOK
VEHICLE REGISTRATION CERTIFICATE
1.1 million won.
Plug this in,
and I can control it remotely.
Nice.
- I'll be able to do that. No problem.
- Can you let me up?
- Oh, it's open.
- We'll make a great team.
I'll talk to you soon.
FISH SAUCE
Is this fish sauce?
It'll be useful.
All right.
Hey, hey. You're sure you can open it?
YouTube had a tutorial.
- Okay.
- Mm.
- Oh shit!
- What the hell?
- What was that?
- What?
I don't know.
I'll try again.
- Ooh! Oh, oh.
- What's that sound? What's that?
Hey, we better leave.
Hurry up. Let's go.
What the hell?
What the fuck is my door doing?
Stop it.
Shit.
BRO
Yeah, got it.
Hey, I got it.
MY LITTLE BRO
I see a shit ton of files.
20130924_F_LONG HAIR
Shit! What the hell's going on?
This guy's computer has
a bunch of videos of kids that...
Damn it.
Hey, guys.
This bastard has a terabyte
of child exploitation videos.
Hand over the Taser.
- Now!
- Uh, here.
Hey, J... Jung-do-ya.
You had Kang Ki-jung
make the video, didn't you?
Where is he?
Use it.
You don't think I will?
Do it.
- Fucking bastard. Fucker!
- Jung-do-ya! Don't.
- Let go.
- No way.
- Right now!
- You need to calm down, Jung-do-ya.
Don't do this.
- Let me go.
- Please stop.
- Let go!
- Calm down, please!
Shut up and calm down.
Dude, I can't believe
you actually used it.
I think blood's coming out
of his eye. What if he goes blind?
- I told you to hold back, dude.
- Oh man.
Just a sec.
Look at your eye.
You could go blind if you don't
go to the hospital right away.
Tell us where Kang Ki-jung is,
and I'll call you an ambulance.
Please nod if you're going to tell us.
Help me sit him up.
Now tell us.
I have...
...a debit card
with a borrowed-name account I opened.
Kang Ki-jung's using it.
On my phone, there are text messages
that tell you where he used the card.
About an hour ago...
another text popped up.
I bet you'll find him
if you go there.
CHINESE PAVILION
I told you everything, so...
Ugh, just get me to the hospital now!
Is there another video Kang Ki-jung filmed
in the past four weeks?
Oh yeah!
There is?
Hey, calm down! Seriously!
- Hey, stop.
- You piece of...
- Get off me.
- Don't do it! Stop!
Hey, hey!
- Stop!
- Calm down.
112. What's your emergency?
A man's been making
pornographic videos of minors.
- Could you come get him?
- Where are you?
See all the red circles?
These are the places Kang Ki-jung used
Kim Min-wook's card in the past two weeks.
And each one is
surrounding this cluster of motels.
In my opinion,
he's probably in this area now.
All right.
You brought your drone, right?
- Yeah, in the car.
- Okay.
Listen up, guys.
Don't get hurt.
Also,
sorry I got mad at you.
Don't worry about it. We get it.
Not gonna lie, I was scared.
Winner Winner...
Chicken Dinner!
Oh, it's cold.
Huh?
Where you headed?
Not allowed. Nothing dangerous.
- Appa...
- Hey!
You were stabbed.
You could've died
if the knife had gone in any deeper!
Hey, guys, go inside for a sec.
- Huh?
- Oh, okay.
Uh, yeah, take your time.
Three months ago...
I'd never heard of
an electronic ankle tag, you know?
But now I know it all.
Maybe too much.
I don't wanna forget what I've learned.
Let the police handle it.
You don't need to be involved anymore.
You know,
that young girl I saved that day...
can't even leave the house
because she's terrified.
She's only ten.
Ten years old.
She's too young and was so scarred
that she shut herself off from the world.
You know what else I found out today?
That evil bastard hurt
another child after his release.
The police do their job.
I'm sure they're all working very hard.
I want to do everything in my power.
No regrets.
I need to do the best
that I possibly can for that little girl.
So please, for God's sake, let me go.
I know I'll be able to catch that bastard.
Even as we speak,
another ten-year-old girl
could be out there,
scared and shivering,
waiting for me to help out.
I wouldn't care if I didn't know.
But how can I do nothing
when I know everything?
I won't get hurt again,
so don't worry about it.
I'm confident I'll get him, appa.
Wish me luck, won't you?
See you later.
Let's go.
Okay.
Be careful, all right?
I will!
Ready.
VOICE CALL
I've started a group call.
If anything happens,
let me know right away.
And do not step in. Got it?
Let's go.
Earthworm, you start from here
and go straight.
Got it.
Hello?
You go that way. I'll go this way.
- Okay, be careful.
- Yeah.
- Sorry to bother you.
- Yes?
Have you possibly seen this man
at your motel recently?
No, I've never seen him before.
Have you seen this man, by any chance?
Excuse me, ma'am,
but have you seen this man?
I've never seen that man.
Could you please look again?
I... don't know.
Thank you.
- He's definitely not one of our guests.
- Sorry to bother you. Thank you anyway.
Hey, guys,
I'm in front of Daewon Inn right now.
It's at the end of the alley
where we started.
There's Chinese takeout containers
piled up out front
and a bunch of men's shoes inside.
Come meet me here.
Okay.
Hey, over here.
- Over there.
- Where?
Hey.
I saved your life in jail.
Don't tell me you forgot.
I'm sick of hearing that.
How much longer
you gonna guilt trip us with that?
Ki-jung-a!
Let's open the window.
Yeah.
You guys go wait.
- I'll handle the rest.
- Be careful.
Call if you need backup.
- Good luck.
- You got this.
Hmm.
Kang Ki-jung, you little shit. Come out!
- What's going on?
- Oh, I'm sorry about that.
- It's dangerous. Please go back in.
- Oh, okay.
Who are you, motherfucker?
I will crack your skull open,
you fucking prick.
That son of a bitch... Hey!
That dickhead. Why, you...
Fuck!
Ow, ow! He threw gochujang!
It's burning my eyes!
Fuck.
- Come here!
- You have a death wish or what?!
My hand!
Hey, asshole. Come here!
Oh!
Hey, you fucking piece of shit!
Huh?
Hmm!
What the hell?
Moisture!
I'll follow him.
- Hey, asshole, stay over there!
- Don't let him go inside!
Son of a...
Argh! It stings! It stings!
You little...
Fuck, not gochujang!
I'm saved. It's only doenjang.
Fuck off, you asshole.
Moisture, which way?
To your right!
Okay.
Make a left.
Now turn right.
He spotted us.
Did he know we were following?
Yeah, I guess so.
He scared the shit out of me.
Ha!
Fuck.
Shit.
You're dead.
Die!
Bring it on. Come on!
Let's go, big guy.
How do we help him? Shit!
Hey!
- Oh, nice!
- Yeah!
Get up.
You little...
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can...
can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
SILENT, AGAINST YOU, ATTORNEY
And you also have
the right to an attorney.
Wow.
"I present this award to you
for your contribution
to the betterment of society
through all your good deeds
and exemplary service to others."
"January 15, 2024,
President of the Republic of Korea."
- Here.
- Oh.
Thank you.
You saved lives.
You're a very brave man.
Thank you very much.
It is now time
for the president to take pictures
with the award recipients.
You did good.
Oh, oh.
One moment, please.
Min-ju-ya.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay now.
Glad to hear it. That's great.
You're my hero.
You're a brave girl.
TRACKING DEVICE DAMAGED
MARTIAL ARTS OFFICER
LEE JUNG-DO
OFFICER BLACK BELT