♪ There is a taste of peace ♪
♪ Every night we dance in my dreams ♪
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
Sing it, girl.
Chante, ma belle.
Mom. Now I can't.
Maman ! Je peux plus, maintenant.
Her spontaneity has been stripped from her.
Ça lui a coupé sa spontanéité.
I'm sorry. You have such a beautiful voice.
Désolée, tu as une si belle voix.
I can't wait to hear it when you're older.
Je me demande comment elle sera plus tard.
Will this place have scuba diving?
Il y aura de la plongée sous-marine ?
How old does a child have to be to do scuba diving?
À partir de quel âge on peut en faire ?
I don't know, Trent.
Je ne sais pas, Trent.
- I think you're a bit too young. - You're a baby.
- Mais toi, tu es trop jeune. - Bébé.
You said five minutes. Technically, it's been way, way more than five minutes. Are we close?
Vous aviez dit 5 min. En vrai, ça fait beaucoup plus. C'est encore loin ?
Stop wishing away this moment.
Arrête de vouloir aller trop vite.
Look out the window, look how pretty it is.
Admire le paysage, regarde comme c'est beau.
Prisca.
Work stuff?
C'est le boulot ?
Yeah.
Lead by actions, Mom.
Montre l'exemple, maman.
Wow.
This is much better than Cancún.
C'est beaucoup mieux qu'à Cancún.
Mr. and Mrs. Capa, welcome to our version of paradise. Wow.
M. et Mme Capa, bienvenue sur notre bout de paradis.
Hello!
So, this is Madrid. She'll take care of you.
Voici Madrid, qui va vous accueillir.
From your food and beverage preferences you selected,
D'après vos préférences gustatives,
we've made you cocktails to welcome you.
nous vous avons préparé ces cocktails.
Wow.
- Thank you. - Look how big you guys are.
Merci. Comme vous êtes grands !
We have a drink fountain for you two.
Il y a une fontaine à boisson pour vous.
- Can we go? - Mmm.
On peut ?
- Yeah. - Let's go, let's go.
Viens.
Can you believe I found this online?
Tu sais que j'ai trouvé ça sur Internet ?
It's gorgeous.
My favorite thing, open 24 hours,
Ce que je préfère, qui est disponible à volonté,
the candy station.
c'est la table à bonbons.
Oh, my God. Come on, Trent.
Génial ! Viens, Trent !
Mix the vanilla and strawberry in it.
Il faut mélanger la vanille et la fraise.
Say hi, Trent.
Dis bonjour, Trent.
Hi.
Bonjour.
I'm Idlib. My uncle's the resort manager here.
Je m'appelle Idlib, mon oncle dirige l'hôtel.
He's Trent, I'm Maddox.
Lui c'est Trent, moi c'est Maddox.
I can do a thousand-piece jigsaw puzzle, which is a considerable thing to do.
Je fais des puzzles de 1000 pièces, ce qui est une prouesse.
My dad and I put clear glue on them and then hang them on my wall.
Après, avec mon père, on les accroche dans ma chambre.
I collect conch shells.
Je collectionne les conques.
I have 42 conch shells.
J'en ai 42.
Amazing.
Impressionnant.
- I might need a little help with this. - Okay.
Je veux bien de l'aide.
Right, so you do strawberry and vanilla?
Fraise vanille, alors ?
Hi.
Thank you. Yes.
Merci.
Okay. Okay, I got it. Okay, come on.
C'est bon, je la tiens.
Thank you. Heh.
Merci.
Great job helping. Yes.
Heureusement que tu m'aides.
- You! - I touched your jacket, that... Hey!
À toi ! Je t'ai touché en premier.
There's 250,000 furniture-related injuries in the United States per year.
Il y a 250 000 accidents dus au mobilier aux États-Unis chaque année.
25% of those, coffee table injuries.
Dont 25 % avec des tables basses.
Hey. Hey!
- Fine. - Okay.
D'accord.
Warren and Warren must be affiliated with this resort.
Warren & Warren doit avoir un partenariat avec l'hôtel.
They must have conventions here.
Ils font sûrement des congrès ici.
We love this pharmaceutical company at work.
On adore ce groupe pharmaceutique, au boulot.
We're considering asking our clients to use Warren and Warren drugs as a way to lower their insurance rates.
On pense faire un prix aux assurés qui prennent leurs médicaments.
Ah. Hmm. Yeah.
"No kids allowed on the beach"?
"Enfants interdits sur la plage" ?
What? Hold on.
Quoi ? Mais...
- "No Kids Week"? - That's not true! Let me see that! It says no ki... Prisca, you should've checked. - Let me see that! - It's your mom's fault. No, really, no. It says this, no... - Let me see! - She should've checked. It says this. - Let me see! - Yes, of course.
"Semaine sans enfants" ? C'est pas vrai ! Prisca, t'as pas vérifié. C'est la faute de votre mère, c'est vrai... Elle aurait dû vérifier, c'est écrit là.
I know this is very painful news for you all to bear.
Je sais que c'est très dur à accepter.
But now, now I've got the power.
Yes! And you have to do it. Yeah, you have to understand. It's like this. - Daddy! - Life is like this.
Il va falloir être forts et comprendre. C'est comme ça, c'est la vie.
It's tough and sometimes it doesn't go the way you want it to.
Come on! Blue team is winning.
What's your name and what do you do for a living? Hey, guys. I'm Annette. What's your name?
C'est quoi votre nom et votre métier ? Bonjour, moi c'est Annette. Et vous ?
I'm Trent. This is Idlib.
Trent et Idlib.
Hey, nice to meet you.
Enchantée.
- Bye. - Bye.
Au revoir.
Bye.
Hi, I'm Trent. This is Idlib.
On s'appelle Trent et Idlib.
What are your names, and what do you do for a living?
C'est quoi votre nom et votre métier ?
Well, I'm Sophia Watson.
Sophia Watson,
I'm a chef.
je suis cheffe.
I'm Greg Mitchell. I'm a cop.
Greg Mitchell, policier.
Cool.
Cool !
And I'm Malin Mitchell. I'm a dancer. Wow. That's cool.
Malin Mitchell, danseuse. C'est cool !
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
Au revoir.
- Hey, let's go over there. - Bye.
Come on, let's go over there.
Truth-telling game. Go.
Jeu de la vérité. À toi !
I can't do a push-up. Go.
Je suis nul en pompes. À toi !
I don't have friends.
J'ai pas d'amis.
I'm your friend.
Tu m'as moi.
You'll leave.
Tu vas partir.
My mom might let me FaceTime you.
On s'appellera en visio
Then we can be friends.
et on restera amis.
You can come over to my house and make up stories.
Tu viendras chez moi, on inventera des histoires.
Then we can go to the same college together
Après, on ira à la même université
and become neighbors with mortgages.
et on empruntera pour habiter à côté.
Cool.
It's weird.
C'est bizarre.
I know.
Je sais.
It's hanging over me. I can barely eat.
Ça me pèse, j'arrive pas à manger.
And I don't feel anything?
Tu crois que ça me fait rien ?
We agreed.
On s'est mis d'accord,
We'd give them one last vacation before telling them.
c'est nos dernières vacances ensemble et on leur dit.
I can't understand why we don't take into consideration...
On devrait quand même tenir compte de...
That shouldn't affect anything.
Ça n'a rien à voir.
The doctor said it's a non-factor.
Le médecin a dit que ça n'avait pas d'incidence.
It's probably been there for years, he said.
C'est sûrement là depuis des années.
We were on a course to separate.
On avait déjà décidé de se séparer.
That's confusing enough for us.
C'est assez bouleversant comme ça.
Let's not bring an irrelevant medical condition into this.
N'allons pas y mêler ce problème de santé.
Let's get through this, Guy.
On doit le faire, Guy.
Compartmentalize.
Cloisonne,
It's only for three days.
ce n'est que pour 3 jours.
You found a place? Yes.
Tu as trouvé un appartement ?
Oh, Prisca. Come on.
Prisca, s'il te plaît.
You're always thinking about the future!
Faut toujours que tu sois dans l'après !
It makes me feel not seen!
Comme si j'étais pas là, maintenant !
You're always thinking about the past. You work in a goddamn museum!
Faut toujours que tu sois dans le passé, comme dans ton musée !
I think they stopped.
Je crois qu'ils ont arrêté.
Why don't you play?
Tu fais pas ton jeu ?
Pour Trent de la part d'Idlib
Concours de mangeur de glaces demain
Good morning. What would you like for breakfast?
Bonjour, que désirez-vous ce matin ?
I'll have the Calcium Bomb juice drink. I have a calcium deficiency.
Un Calcium Molotov. J'ai une carence en calcium,
So, is it really calcium rich or just a catchy name? It has all calcium-rich vegetables, ma'am.
alors il y a vraiment du calcium dans votre truc ? Il n'y a que des légumes riches en calcium.
- Sit up, Kara, honey. - Okay.
Tiens-toi droite, Kara.
You don't wanna be hunched when you grow up, baby. It's very unattractive.
Sinon tu seras toute bossue plus tard, et c'est très vilain.
Boys will get turned off.
Ça fait fuir les garçons.
Give me the Calcium Bomb juice.
Je vais prendre un Calcium Molotov,
And maybe you could recommend one of these.
avec... Vous avez une suggestion ?
This one.
I recommend the granola parfait.
Je vous suggère le parfait au granola.
It's a good choice. Okay.
C'est un bon choix.
So, how is the Capa family?
Comment va la famille Capa ?
Any plans today?
Que faites-vous aujourd'hui ?
Well, one of our kids wants to do Jet Ski. And the other one wants to do anything but that. Aha.
Un des enfants veut faire du jet-ski et l'autre... tout sauf ça.
Well, there's, um...
there's a private beach on the nature preserve side of the island.
Il y a une plage privée dans la réserve naturelle.
It's impossible to find.
Totalement cachée,
It's surrounded by stunning rocks, very unusual minerals.
dans une superbe baie à la roche très particulière.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
On ne voit ça qu'une fois dans sa vie,
A natural anomaly.
c'est une rareté de la nature.
I only recommend it to certain guests.
Je n'en parle qu'à certains clients.
But I liked you guys immediately. All right?
Mais vous m'avez plu tout de suite.
You're a nice family. So I could arrange a van to take you, if...
Gentils comme vous êtes, je peux vous réserver un van...
Yeah.
Sounds like a great memory for us.
De beaux souvenirs en perspective.
It's our little secret. I'll make all the arrangements.
Ce sera notre secret. Je m'occupe de tout.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay, so I think we should get the Calloway Kale-away for Trent.
On devrait prendre le Super Kale, pour Trent.
Idlib, what did I tell you about being in here when you shouldn't?
Idlib, je t'ai déjà dit de ne pas venir ici.
You can't... You know, I told you so many times.
Tu n'as pas le droit, tu le sais.
You know, we have certain rules...
I'm a doctor.
Je suis médecin.
My wife has epilepsy.
Ma femme est épileptique.
I'm a nurse. My name is Jarin.
Je suis infirmier, je m'appelle Jarin.
Right, she's having a grand mal seizure.
C'est une crise grand mal.
Keep things away from her, please.
Éloignez les objets d'elle.
Patricia?
Patricia ?
Doll.
Mon coeur ?
Jack, I think if you just leave her lying here for a while, put something under her head. I think she'll be fine.
Jack, qu'elle reste un peu allongée, la tête surélevée.
Thank you, Doctor. It's Jarin, by the way.
Merci, docteur. Je m'appelle Jarin.
For my next act, I'll spin my head around 360.
Pour mon prochain show, je tourne la tête à 360°.
I'm sorry I ruined everyone's breakfast.
Désolée d'avoir troublé le petit-déjeuner.
You always want to be the center of attention.
Tu veux toujours te faire remarquer.
My goodness. Let's get you something to drink? Yeah.
Eh bien... Vous voulez boire quelque chose ?
Idlib.
Can't be that secret a beach. We were told to keep it quiet.
On croyait que c'était une plage secrète.
- So were we. - Sit down, Gustav. Good boy.
Nous aussi. Assis, Gustav. Gentil chien.
Good boy. Stay.
Okay, guest checklist.
Check rapide.
Books, sunscreen.
Livres, crème solaire...
Did everybody leave their passports in their safes? - I don't want anybody to lose anything. - Yeah.
Vos passeports sont bien à l'hôtel ? Il ne faut pas les perdre.
What are your names and occupations?
C'est quoi vos noms et métiers ?
Réserve naturelle protégée
Interdiction d'entrer sous peine de poursuites
It's very rocky here.
Okay, my friends.
Bien, les amis.
You can just call us, and we'll pick you up whenever you're ready to come back.
Appelez dès que vous voulez rentrer.
Or I'll pick you up at 5:00 p.m.
Sinon, je vous attends ici à 17h.
Just follow the path down to the beach.
Vous n'avez qu'à suivre le sentier.
- Is that also food? - Yeah.
C'est le pique-nique ?
Wow, that's a lot of food.
Il y a beaucoup.
Well, kids eat a lot of food. And you got three of them with you. Okay.
Les enfants mangent beaucoup. Et vous en avez 3 avec vous.
Seems like a waste, but thank you.
Il y aura du gâchis, mais merci.
Could you help us carry some of these bags, please?
Vous pourriez nous aider ?
We've got an elderly person here and a child.
Il y a une dame âgée et une enfant.
I'm sorry. I gotta get back. But it's not far. Just walk down. You'll see a beautiful slot canyon. Walk through that, and in a few minutes, you'll be there. Enjoy, everybody!
Je dois repartir. Mais ce n'est pas loin, juste après un très beau canyon, à quelques minutes d'ici. Profitez bien !
- Do you think there's... - Come on.
- Do you think there's snakes? - Of course.
Il y a des serpents ?
Cool. I wanna see one.
Je voudrais en voir un.
- Gorgeous. - Wow.
Okay.
You okay? Yeah?
Ça va ?
Could someone please tell me what just happened?
Look out.
- This is so exciting! - Careful now.
Attention.
- Let's go! - I'm gonna win! Whoo!
- On court ! - Je vais gagner !
Wow. I just got chills.
J'en ai des frissons !
Come on, darling. Let's show Gustav the sea.
Viens mon chouchou, je vais te montrer la mer.
Hey, Maddox, help your mom. Listen, I... Let's move somewhere else. I think it's much nicer closer to the water, right? - Yeah, but I... - No, it's... Look. It's beautiful.
Maddox, aide maman. On va se déplacer, on sera mieux près du bord. Regarde, c'est beau.
I got you!
Have you ever seen anything like that?
They were right to send us.
On a bien fait de venir.
Lie down.
Couché.
Yeah. Good boy!
C'est bien !
Kids, look at the beautiful coral.
Les enfants, regardez le corail !
- What are you going to do? - Now I'm gonna splash you.
Tu vas faire quoi ?
Just keep on reading, I guess. You just splashed me.
Je vais bouquiner.
Stop! I didn't mean you could splash me.
Guy?
Guy.
Yeah.
What book am I reading?
Qu'est-ce que je lis ?
I don't know.
Je sais pas.
Why?
Pourquoi ?
No reason.
Comme ça.
Prisca, I wanted to tell you something.
Prisca. Je voulais te dire...
No, never mind.
Non, rien.
I'll tell you later.
Je te dirai plus tard.
Oh, my God.
That's Mid-Sized Sedan. What? Mid what? He's a rapper!
C'est Mid-Sized Sedan ! - Mid quoi ? - Le rappeur !
"More Dough for the Cookin" '?
More Dough for the Cooking !
- Mid-Sized Sedan? - Let's begin an activity.
Mid-Sized Sedan ?
Dad, I have to, okay? I have to! - No. Leave him. Because it's a private... - Sounds like fun.
Faut que j'aille le voir ! Laisse-le, il a le droit de...
- But, Dad, stop! I need to say hi. - He's on vacation, he's on vacation.
Je veux lui dire bonjour ! Il est en vacances.
What's his surname? Sedan?
Son nom de famille, c'est Sedan ?
Whoo!
Oh!
Whoa, all right. Here's a big one. Wow.
En voilà une grosse !
Help me with this.
Aide-moi.
We should have a housewarming party.
On va faire une crémaillère.
Isn't our house so beautiful?
Elle est belle notre maison, hein ?
- Boo! - Aah! You!
- Come! Come back here! - No!
Tu vas voir !
Not gonna get me! Kara, you know, I'm gonna get you right now.
Tu m'attraperas pas ! Si, je vais t'attraper !
Come on.
Not gonna get me! Oh, I am.
- Tu m'attraperas pas ! - Si !
Come on, Kara.
Oh!
Oh, my God. Got you.
Touchée !
You're never gonna catch me.
Honey, I'm home.
Chéri, c'est moi !
I told you, I don't wanna live like this.
Je ne veux pas de cette vie-là.
I'm gonna live in a condominium.
Je vais prendre un bel appartement.
I'm going for a drive to calm down.
Je sors me calmer.
I'm really, really hungry.
J'ai super faim.
Me, too. My stomach's growling.
Moi aussi, j'ai le ventre qui gargouille.
Me, too.
Moi aussi.
Wow.
Who would leave this?
Qui a laissé ça ?
Hey, Mom!
Maman !
From the hotel.
Ça vient de l'hôtel.
They're so rusted.
C'est tout rouillé !
Put that down!
Ne touchez pas.
You can get infected or you'll cut yourself!
Ça peut s'infecter si vous vous coupez.
Come away.
Partez de là !
Next activity. - What's happening? - Let's play hide-and-seek. I don't know. They found stuff from the hotel in the sand.
Et maintenant, cache-cache. Ils ont trouvé des vieux trucs de l'hôtel.
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
18, 19...
- No fish. - Ready or not, here we come!
Pas de poisson. On arrive !
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Maman !
Mom!
- What is it? What is it? - Trent!
Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
Someone over there. Over there.
Il y a quelqu'un là-bas.
Come on. Give me a hand. Get the legs.
Aidez-moi, prenez ses jambes.
Yes.
- Make your list. Make your list. - Okay.
Fais une liste.
Red and orange.
Rouge, orange.
Red, orange. Come away from here, babies.
Rouge, orange. Venez.
Let the doctor try and help this lady. Yeah?
Le docteur va aider la dame.
- Green. - Green.
- Tan. - Tan.
Marron.
- Purple. - Purple. - What happened? - It's okay.
Violet. Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
Blue. Blue is good. And then? - Green. - Green, yes. - Yellow. Purple. - Yellow. I love yellow. Call the police, right?
Bleu. Et puis ? Vert, oui. Jaune ! J'adore. Il faut appeler la police.
I'll get my mobile.
Je vais chercher mon téléphone.
Oh, damn.
Merde.
What happened to her, Mom?
Qu'est-ce qu'elle a ?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
I'm still hungry. Me, too.
- J'ai super faim. - Moi aussi.
Was she with you?
Elle était avec vous ?
I was waiting for her.
Je l'attendais.
She swam out by herself, yo.
Elle était partie nager.
I don't know what the hell happened.
Je sais pas ce qui s'est passé.
I ain't saying nothing else.
Je peux rien dire d'autre.
Did you strike him? I don't need to know the context of...
Vous l'avez frappé ? Juste pour savoir.
What? No. Of course not.
Bien sûr que non.
So why's your nose bleeding?
Pourquoi vous saignez du nez ?
I told y'all, I ain't got nothing to say to you.
Je vous répète, j'ai rien d'autre à dire.
My chest feels funny.
J'ai une drôle de sensation dans la poitrine.
Well, you know, we should've gotten a yacht like I suggested, Agnes.
Vous voyez, on aurait dû louer un yacht comme j'avais dit.
You shouldn't have fought me on that.
Il fallait pas me contredire.
You see? Now we're mixed up in some island issue. I mean, I...
On se serait pas retrouvés dans cette sale histoire.
Mom, my swimsuit is hurting. I have to take it off. Well, just loosen your...
Maman, mon maillot me fait mal. Je veux l'enlever. Desserre...
We're from Philadelphia.
On vient de Philadelphie.
I'm on a break here with my wife and kids. That's them.
On est en vacances en famille,
Well, yeah, over there.
ils sont là-bas.
And for the record, I know most people who die on vacation die from sun exposure, overexertion,
Vous savez, la plupart des décès en vacances sont dus à une insolation, à l'épuisement,
overindulgence of food or alcohol,
à l'excès de nourriture ou d'alcool,
or a mixture of all of the above 99.4% of the time. - How you know all this? - I'm an actuary. I calculate people's insurance rates based on their risk profile.
ou aux 3 à la fois, 99,4 % du temps. - Comment vous savez ? - Je suis actuaire. Je calcule le tarif des assurances en fonction des risques.
I ain't do nothing, man.
J'ai rien fait.
She was into me.
Elle me kiffait.
Somebody will figure this out.
On va comprendre ce qui s'est passé.
We'll just have to wait for them to get here.
Il faut juste attendre de l'aide.
No reception at all.
Il n'y a pas du tout de réseau.
I guess our beach day's over.
Notre petite virée est terminée.
We've gotta keep an eye on him and the body.
Surveillez ce type et le corps.
Whoo!
Oh, my goodness.
C'est magnifique.
Wow.
Did you just get dropped off by the resort?
L'hôtel vous a déposés ?
Yeah. We were supposed to come earlier, but we rested in the room first.
Oui, on devait venir plus tôt mais on s'est reposés d'abord.
Great. We have to get the resort people before they leave. I think we will all have to leave this beach.
Parfait. Rejoignons vite le van, il faut partir d'ici.
Wait. Why? They left already.
Pourquoi ? Le van est reparti.
What happened?
Que s'est-il passé ?
We really don't know what happened.
On sait pas ce qui s'est passé.
Well, I think this man had something to do with it.
Cet homme y est pour quelque chose.
Man, if I was involved, why would I be standing around, bro? Damn. His nose is bleeding. I think he got that when she was trying to defend herself. I don't like this dynamic at all. My nose has been bleeding for hours, man. I don't know why it's doing that.
Pourquoi je serais resté là, dans ce cas ? Elle a dû le blesser en se défendant. Je n'aime pas du tout cette ambiance. Je saigne du nez depuis des heures.
Charles, something's wrong with your mother. She's asking for you, honey.
Charles, ta mère se sent mal, elle te demande.
Well, we're all in this now.
On doit tous se sentir concernés.
We are responsible for that woman.
On est responsables de cette femme.
And I've got nothing against this man. I'm just doing what needs to be done.
Je n'ai rien contre ce type, je fais simplement le nécessaire.
No cell phone reception on this beach.
Ça ne capte pas.
You stay here. I'll go to the clearing in the jungle where they dropped us and try to call. They obviously have a signal out here. How else do people call to go back?
Reste ici, je vais au point de rendez-vous. Ça capte sûrement là-bas, sinon comment on appellerait pour rentrer ?
Oh, my God.
You stumbled back out, you were holding your head. You looked like you were in pain, babe.
Tu es ressorti la tête dans les mains comme si tu avais mal.
You blacked out.
Vous vous êtes évanoui.
I felt this pressure in my head.
J'ai senti une pression.
I'm fine, Charles.
Ça va, Charles.
I think it's the shock.
Ça doit être le choc.
Try to help Gustav or he'll be sick.
C'est plutôt Gustav qui m'inquiète.
Yeah, of course it's the shock. I'm gonna get a van to take us back to the resort, but first I've got to deal with all this, all right?
Oui, c'est le choc. Je vais demander qu'on nous ramène quand j'aurai réglé ce problème.
Are you okay?
Ça va, toi ?
Yeah.
I know you've been stressed.
Je sais que tu es tendu,
Don't let this upset you.
ne te laisse pas trop perturber.
Help these people through this, Charles.
Va aider ces gens, Charles.
So, what did you hear?
Qu'est-ce que tu sais ?
Help these people through this, Charles. Excuse me.
Aide-les. S'il vous plaît.
Excuse me. I saw you were talking to my husband.
Vous étiez avec mon mari,
I know you're dealing with a lot with that woman right now,
je sais que vous vous occupez de cette femme,
but something is wrong with my son. Some kind of reaction.
mais mon fils fait une sorte d'allergie.
Is it severe? I don't have time for this.
C'est grave ? Je n'ai pas le temps.
What kind of doctor are you?
Vous êtes quel genre de médecin ?
I'm a cardiothoracic surgeon and chief medical officer.
Chirurgien cardiaque et chef de service.
You don't know me.
On ne se connaît pas.
I curate exhibits for museums.
Je suis commissaire d'exposition.
I'm telling you this because I want you to trust me and not think I'm being hysterical when I say
Si je vous le dis, c'est pour être écoutée et prise au sérieux,
there's something very wrong with my child.
mon fils a vraiment un problème.
He seems fine to me. He's playing with my daughter.
Il va bien, il joue avec ma fille.
You look different, too.
Toi aussi, t'as changé.
How?
Comment ça ?
Huh? I don't know. You just look different.
Je sais pas, mais t'as changé.
Hold my hand.
Donne-moi la main.
Okay.
Willow, Japanese maple.
Saule. Érable du Japon.
- Evergreen. - If you get scared, just tell me, okay?
- Conifère... - Si t'as peur, dis-moi.
What do you keep looking at?
Tu regardes quoi ?
- There. - Where?
- Là-bas. - Où ?
Way, way up there on the side of the hillside.
Tout là-bas, en haut de la colline.
What do you see?
T'as vu quoi ?
I thought I saw something shiny.
Un truc qui a brillé.
Here comes Mom.
Il y a maman.
Charles! She stopped breathing!
Charles ! Elle respire plus !
She stopped breathing!
Elle respire plus !
I didn't do anything, Charles.
J'ai rien fait.
You guys, you just walked away,
Vous êtes partis
and she just stopped breathing all of a sudden.
et tout à coup, elle a arrêté de respirer.
I mean, she was peaceful.
Elle était calme.
Can you step back, please?
Reculez !
We'll take the kids away from here.
Éloignez les enfants.
Is this happening?
Comment c'est possible ?
She couldn't take the shock.
Elle n'a pas supporté le choc.
She saw a murdered woman and her heart couldn't take it.
Elle a vu cette femme assassinée et son coeur a lâché.
What are your names and occupations?
C'est quoi votre nom et votre métier ?
I'm Jarin. I'm a nurse.
Jarin, infirmier.
I'm Patricia. I'm a psychologist.
Patricia, psychologue.
He remembers everyone's names and things about them.
Il retient le nom des gens et des détails sur eux.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Ça va aller.
What's your name?
Comment tu t'appelles ?
I'm Trent. This is my sister, Maddox.
Trent. Et elle, c'est ma soeur Maddox.
How old are you guys?
Vous avez quel âge ?
I'll guess. I'm good at this.
Je vais deviner, je suis fort.
You're 11, right, Trent?
Tu as 11 ans, c'est ça ?
I'm six.
J'ai 6 ans.
No. Really, are you 10, 11?
En vrai, 10 ou 11 ans ?
He's not lying. He's six.
Il ne ment pas, il a 6 ans.
I'm specifically six and a quarter.
6 ans et quart, pour être exact.
She's 11.
C'est elle qui a 11 ans.
They're feeling unsafe. There is a lot going on here.
Ils sont angoissés par la situation.
They're playing with us. Let's leave it.
Ils se moquent de nous. N'insistons pas.
Okay, what's your best friend's name?
Comment s'appelle ton meilleur ami ?
Maddox.
How sweet.
C'est chouette.
Have you seen my children?
Vous avez vu mes enfants ?
Is everyone trying to play a joke on us?
Vous êtes tous de mèche ?
- What? - Aren't these your children?
Ce ne sont pas vos enfants ?
I'm right here, Mom.
Je suis là, maman.
Mom?
Maman ?
Mom.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Pourquoi tu me regardes comme ça ?
Prisca, I think we should leave.
Il faut partir,
Get the kids back to the resort.
ramener les enfants à l'hôtel.
Guy...
- Maddox? - Yeah. Dad, it's me.
- Maddox ? - Oui, papa, c'est moi.
What's going on?
Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
You see? You see?
Tu vois ?
Holy...
Damn.
- How did we get here? - Take it easy.
Il s'est passé quoi ?
Intense cranial pressure. It's like being deep underwater.
Une pression dans le crâne, comme quand on plonge profond.
- I can't... - Can you get up? Whoa. Whoa. Take it easy.
Vous pouvez vous lever ?
Charles?
- Yeah, no, I'm all right. I'm fine. - You okay?
Ça va, je vais bien.
We're leaving right now, and we're taking our kids.
On s'en va avec nos enfants.
For some reason, people are blacking out going this way. Three people have blacked out now.
On s'évanouit, par là. On est 3 à s'être évanouis.
- That's ridiculous. Come, move. - No, I saw it, Prisca. I saw Jarin black out.
C'est absurde. Viens. C'est vrai, je l'ai vu.
What I know is that we have to get these kids to a hospital. Now.
Il faut qu'on emmène les enfants à l'hôpital tout de suite.
Look, let's stop talking about it. The kids are scared. I can stay here with them. But everyone else should try and find a different pathway off this beach.
C'est pas le moment de discuter. Les enfants ont peur. Je vais rester avec eux, mais vous tous, cherchez comment partir de cette plage.
Break off into groups of two in case people black out.
On fait des groupes de 2 au cas où on s'évanouirait.
Chrystal, go with me.
Chrystal, avec moi.
- Okay. - Whatever you do, just stay close. I'm feeling very uncomfortable right now.
Ne t'éloigne pas trop.
Don't get up too quickly.
Je me suis levé trop vite ?
Kids, let Mom and Dad talk for a second.
Les enfants, maman et papa doivent parler.
No. Mom, we're scared.
Non, on a peur.
Please. Stay right here.
S'il vous plaît, restez là.
Okay?
- If I cry, please don't let them see. - I won't.
- Si je pleure, cache-moi. - D'accord.
- Your hands are shaking. - Yeah.
Tes mains tremblent.
- Yeah. - Yeah, they are. Yeah. You okay?
C'est vrai. Ça va ?
We're on a beach with two unrelated dead bodies. That is just statistically impossible.
Ces 2 cadavres non liés entre eux, c'est statistiquement impossible.
All three kids are reacting to something. Only the kids.
Les enfants sont les seuls à faire une réaction.
I mean, look at the doctor's daughter.
Regarde la fille du docteur.
The kids are reacting to something they ate.
C'est quelque chose qu'ils ont mangé
Or they caught something.
ou une saleté qu'ils ont attrapée.
We're on a remote, undeveloped island, but we have a doctor here.
Il n'y a rien pour les soigner ici mais on est avec un médecin.
So, let's get the doctor to look at the kids.
Alors, demandons-lui d'examiner les enfants.
I still can't get any reception.
J'ai toujours pas de réseau.
Doctor, before we do anything else, can you take a look at our children, please?
Docteur, vous pouvez examiner nos enfants, s'il vous plaît ?
Oh!
He's got a knife!
Il a un couteau !
There's a damn hole in my cheek!
Il m'a troué la joue !
- Oh, my God! Are you okay? - Put that down right now, Doctor.
Posez ça tout de suite.
Watch out, Jarin.
Attention, Jarin !
Listen, I don't know why I did that. I thought he was gonna hurt me.
J'ai cru qu'il allait m'attaquer.
Sorry.
Pardon.
- Sorry. - What's he talking about, "sorry"?
- Pardon. - Je m'en tape de ton pardon !
- Let me see that laceration. - That's assault, man!
- Faites voir. - C'est une agression !
Calm down.
Calmez-vous.
What's your name?
Comment vous vous appelez ?
Mid-Sized Sedan.
I must be in shock. I'm numb. I'm not feeling the pain no more.
Ça doit être le choc, je sens rien, j'ai pas mal.
Please. Let me see.
Laissez-moi regarder.
No, this is not making any sense, Prisca. I need to get my ass to a hospital now.
C'est insensé. Faut m'emmener à l'hosto.
What's with all y'all faces?
Pourquoi vous faites cette tête ?
It's hard to explain.
Je sais pas comment dire.
This is messed up, man. Where'd it go?
C'est quoi ces conneries ? Il m'arrive quoi ?
This is some kind of parlor trick.
C'est sûrement un trucage.
Yo, I know I tried to dip, but I am freaked, man.
C'est vrai, j'ai essayé de me tirer, mais là, je suis en panique.
I just wanna go back to my hotel room.
Je veux juste rentrer à l'hôtel.
This was supposed to be a zen trip, man.
Ça devait être un voyage tranquille.
She and I only started talking because she was sick, and so am I.
On s'est mis à parler parce qu'elle était malade, comme moi.
She had just been diagnosed with MS, so we started rapping about that.
Elle avait une sclérose en plaques.
I didn't do nothing to that girl, man.
J'ai rien fait à cette fille.
She was like Michael Phelps swimming out there, backstroking and whatnot.
Elle a nagé comme Michael Phelps, genre en dos crawlé,
She swam way the hell out. What did you say? No, I don't know, man. Maybe it was butterfly stroke. I don't watch the Summer Olympics like that.
elle est allée super loin. Vous avez dit quoi ? C'était peut-être la nage papillon, j'y connais rien.
You came vacationing here because you were sick, - and so did she? - I thought that was a cool coincidence. Maybe this is some kind of group psychosis. I've studied this.
Vous étiez tous les 2 malades ? Oui, c'était cool comme coïncidence. C'est peut-être une sorte de psychose collective.
We're all emotionally shaky from our lives.
On est tous fragiles en ce moment
We don't believe we can leave this beach.
et on n'arrive pas à imaginer qu'on peut partir d'ici.
Mom.
Maman.
Is there any more food? I'm still hungry. - Well, she's definitely aged. - How can you still be hungry? We just...
Il reste à manger ? J'ai encore faim. Elle a grandi.
I'd put her biological age somewhere between 12 and 13,
On lui donne entre 12 et 13 ans,
and she turned six two weeks ago on Tuesday.
alors qu'elle a eu 6 ans il y a 2 semaines.
What?
We're older?
On a vieilli ?
Am I okay?
Je vais pas bien ?
I don't know what's happening to the three of you, sweetheart.
Je ne sais pas ce qui vous arrive.
But for now, I have another swimsuit in my bag, and maybe you should change into that.
Mais j'ai un autre maillot dans mon sac, tu devrais le mettre.
It might be a virus, maybe.
C'est peut-être un virus,
Could be mosquitoes where... The way they behave on this part of the island.
un truc transmis par les moustiques d'ici
Something's happening to her that's triggering her hormones.
qui déclenche une réaction hormonale.
The dog has died! - Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
Le chien est mort !
He was only just alive. - Kara, hold on to me, baby. - What's happening?
Il allait bien. Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
Who thinks they can swim
Qui pense pouvoir nager
a hundred lengths of a pool against currents,
100 longueurs de piscine à contre-courant,
and then turn and swim an unknown amount along the coast
puis continuer à nager pendant un temps indéfini
till we find another shore?
pour trouver une autre rive ?
That's what I'm guessing the distance is to swim out and get around this cove.
Je crois que c'est ce qu'il faut faire pour sortir de la baie.
It looks too far. Babe, it's not safe.
C'est trop loin, trop dangereux.
My name is Brendon.
Je m'appelle Brendon.
I went to private school. My mom is an attorney, and my dad is a dentist.
Je suis allé à l'école privée, mère avocate, père dentiste.
- Yo, I just wanted somebody to know that. - Okay.
Je voulais que quelqu'un le sache.
I have a problem with my blood. A rare issue with its clotting.
J'ai une maladie du sang, il coagule trop.
I came to this island to see the ocean and remember I'm connected to something bigger.
Je suis venu ici pour voir l'océan et me reconnecter à plus grand que moi.
That's beautiful, Brendon.
C'est très beau, Brendon.
I don't feel the same way I felt yesterday or this morning,
Je me sens différente d'hier et de ce matin,
and I don't think my parents would understand.
et mes parents ne comprendraient pas.
My thoughts have more colors in them now.
Mes pensées ont plus de couleurs.
Yesterday, I had a few colors and they were really strong,
Hier, j'en avais peu mais très vives,
and now I have more and they're quieter.
et là, j'en ai plein mais plus douces.
Okay!
Everyone, gather!
Venez tous !
Come on, come on, come on!
Allez !
Everyone needs to have a voice here.
Tout le monde doit s'exprimer.
Are you sure we have time for this?
C'est vraiment le moment ?
We will make destructive decisions if we don't feel safe with each other. I know we don't have time, but why don't we start with you two?
Il faut apprendre à se faire confiance, même si on a peu de temps. Si on commençait par vous ?
Why are you here?
Pourquoi êtes-vous venus ici ?
- We've been having a tough time... - Chrystal.
On traverse une période difficile...
We've been going through something.
un moment un peu dur.
He's under a lot of stress as a doctor. He needed some time away.
Il est stressé, il avait besoin de repos.
Everyone does. I'm not unusual in that.
Comme tout le monde.
Charles, it's okay. I'm not gonna say anything else.
Ne t'inquiète pas, je m'arrête là.
Good! It's nice to hear from you both.
Parfait ! C'est important de parler.
How about you guys?
Et vous ?
Prisca?
Prisca ?
It's nothing.
C'est rien.
We just have to make a decision.
Il faut prendre une décision.
The kids are reacting to something. It's a virus. It's probably a virus.
Les enfants font une réaction, c'est probablement un virus.
I just need to catch my breath. I just started feeling weird a minute ago.
J'ai un peu de mal à respirer, je me sens bizarre.
Are you okay, Mom?
Ça va, maman ?
- Mom? - What's wrong? Are you okay, Mom? I don't think it's the...
Qu'y a-t-il ? Ça va, maman ? Je ne pense pas que ce soit...
- She has a tumor. - What?
Elle a une tumeur.
But it's benign. They said it's benign. Oh, my God.
Mais ils ont dit que c'était bénin.
Mom?
Is it... Where?
Elle est où ?
- Mom? - It's okay.
- Maman ? - Ça va.
Can I...
Je peux ?
I can feel it. It's the size of a golf ball. No, it's supposed to be three centimeters.
Ça fait la taille d'une balle de golf. Non, elle fait 3 centimètres.
All right. Let me see. - Whoa! Prisca! - Mom!
Faites voir.
- She's gonna faint. - Prisca.
Mom.
- Let her get some air! - Wake up, Pris. Don't do this.
Réveille-toi ! Me fais pas ça.
It's there.
Elle est là.
It's been there for a while. It's the size of a softball.
C'est gros comme une balle de tennis.
Jesus.
- It's grown. - What?
Ça grossit.
- What's happening to Mom? - What's going on?
Elle a quoi, maman ?
- Dad! Dad, what's happening to Mom? - It's okay.
Papa, elle a quoi ?
Trent, why don't you two guys go play somewhere else on the beach, okay? Okay? Mom's a little bit tired. Would you do that for me, tiger?
Allez jouer un peu plus loin. D'accord ? Maman est fatiguée. Vas-y, mon chat.
The first adult is being affected.
C'est la 1re adulte touchée.
What if we cut it out?
On peut l'enlever ?
- Dad! - Not possible. Actually, it is. But it's Guy's call. No! No, no, no! No!
- Impossible. - Si. Mais c'est à Guy de voir.
I don't wanna make this decision. No. No, I...
Je veux pas prendre cette décision...
I don't know what to do.
Je sais pas quoi faire.
- Do we have alcohol? - Yes. Some bottles from the minibar. I cannot be held responsible. You understand?
On a de l'alcool ? Oui, des bouteilles du minibar. Je décline toute responsabilité.
Yes.
Okay. Well, does anyone have a needle and thread? - We have to sew this up. - Yeah, yeah. Uh...
On a du fil et une aiguille pour recoudre après ?
Here. Here. Is this the right decision? - Maybe we should all talk about this. - I can't think. This tumor is going to kill her.
Tenez. C'est vraiment la seule solution ? Je sais pas, la tumeur va la tuer.
Did you know that Jack Nicholson did a film with Marlon Brando? Oh, no.
Vous savez que Jack Nicholson a fait un film avec Marlon Brando ?
What is he saying?
Comment ?
- What was the name of that film? - Charles, breathe.
- C'est quoi, le titre ? - Charles, respire.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Ça va ?
- Will you let me do my job, please? - Is he okay?
Laissez-moi travailler. Il va bien ?
Cut her again.
Ré-incisez,
We'll keep our hands in there to keep the incision open.
on va maintenir ouvert avec les mains.
Guy, I can help, brother.
Guy, je peux t'aider.
No, I'll take care of her.
Non, c'est à moi de le faire.
Does anyone know the name of that film? It was with Jack Nicholson and Marlon Brando.
Vous avez vu ce film ? Avec Jack Nicholson et Marlon Brando.
- Both. - Try again, Doctor.
Ensemble ! Recommencez.
Oblique incision on the side of the belly, four to six inches. You can do this.
Une incision oblique sur le côté de 10 à 15 cm, allez.
Put your fingers inside the incision.
On insère les doigts.
Okay.
Can you open it a little wider, please?
Écartez un peu.
It's closing around my fingers.
Ça se referme.
Keep pulling it apart. That's it.
Continuez d'écarter. Voilà.
I'm lifting the tumor out.
Je soulève la tumeur.
Wow! It's the size of a cantaloupe!
La taille d'un melon !
Wait!
Attendez.
It's attached to something.
C'est accroché
- Muscle tissue. - Okay.
à du tissu musculaire.
Could you hold the incision open a little wider, if you would?
Écartez un peu, si vous voulez bien.
I'm so sorry, Pris. Just cutting underneath the tumor.
Pardon, Prisca. Je procède à l'ablation...
Okay. Got it.
Je l'ai.
Mom.
Prisca?
Mom?
It's okay.
Ça va.
I just fainted.
Je me suis évanouie.
We took the tumor out.
On t'a enlevé la tumeur.
It was going to kill you.
Elle allait te tuer.
Your husband made a fast decision.
Votre mari a décidé très vite.
Guy, I feel better.
Je me sens mieux.
Damn!
Come on, y'all, look at this!
Venez voir !
Hurry!
Vite !
Damn.
Come on, y'all!
Venez !
Can we all agree I didn't do that?
On est d'accord que ça, c'est pas moi ?
What happened to her?
Qu'est-ce qui s'est passé ?
The body has decomposed.
Le corps s'est décomposé.
- How quickly can that happen? - A long time.
- Ça prend combien de temps ? - Longtemps.
Mom knows this stuff.
Maman doit savoir.
I'm not a forensic pathologist,
Je ne suis pas médecin légiste,
but from excavations for the museum,
mais d'après nos fouilles pour le musée,
I know that it varies based on soil and temperature.
je sais que ça dépend du sol et de la température.
My best guess, an exposed body,
En tout cas, un corps exposé à l'air libre
the flesh will be gone in approximately seven years.
met en moyenne 7 ans à se décomposer.
And this happened in, what, three hours?
Là, c'est arrivé en 3 heures.
I know.
Oui.
And bones, we've found, will disintegrate in 30 years more.
Et normalement, les os se désagrègent en 30 ans.
What the hell, man?
C'est dément.
On this beach, less than 20 hours after you die, you just return to dust.
Ici, tu redeviens poussière moins de 20 h après ta mort.
What exactly are we saying?
Ça veut dire quoi ?
Something is going on with time on this beach.
Que le temps déraille, sur cette plage.
Time?
Le temps ?
You have wrinkles.
Tu as des rides.
I'm scared.
J'ai peur.
It's best to focus on specifics in the present in unsettling situations.
Il faut se concentrer sur l'instant présent quand on se sent pas bien,
- Mm-hmm. - Like breathing.
par exemple sur sa respiration.
What's happening to us?
Qu'est-ce qui nous arrive ?
Are we sick, too? No, I don't think so.
On est malades aussi ? Je crois pas.
I think we're just growing.
On grandit, c'est tout.
Going by Trent and Maddox's ages and the time we spent on this beach,
Vu l'âge de Trent et Maddox par rapport au temps passé ici,
half an hour is equivalent to something like one year of our lives.
une demi-heure équivaut à une année de notre vie.
This must be true for all of us, we just don't see it on everyone.
Ça vaut pour nous tous, mais ça se voit moins chez certains.
It's the first time they wished they were Black. Mm-hmm. The kids are eating so much because their mass is growing.
Pour une fois, ils voudraient être noirs. Les enfants ont faim car ils grandissent,
They need to grow an enormous amount of mass quickly.
ils ont besoin de beaucoup d'énergie pour grandir si vite.
We're staying roughly the same mass. Our cells are just aging.
Nous, on ne grandit pas, mais nos cellules vieillissent.
I don't feel the same.
Je me sens différente,
It's like my mind is changing, too.
comme si mon esprit changeait aussi.
I'm getting many thoughts at the same time.
Je pense à plein de choses en même temps.
It's weird.
C'est bizarre.
I'm not as scared about what's happening to us.
Je n'ai plus aussi peur de ce qui nous arrive.
What about our hair and nails?
Nos cheveux et nos ongles
Shouldn't they be growing at an abnormal rate? Maybe it has to do with the fact that the cells
ne devraient pas pousser plus vite ? C'est peut-être parce que les cellules
in hair and nails are dead, and they aren't reacting in the same way.
des cheveux et des ongles sont mortes, alors elles réagissent autrement.
On this beach, 60 minutes is two years.
Sur cette plage, 60 minutes valent 2 ans.
We'll age almost 50 years in one day here.
On vieillit de presque 50 ans en une journée,
Almost a lifetime.
c'est presque une vie.
I think it could be the rock that surrounds this beach.
C'est peut-être à cause de la roche.
If our cells are being affected,
Si nos cellules sont touchées,
speeding up in their processes,
si leur cycle est accéléré,
then us trying to leave is like swimming to the surface too fast after being deep in the ocean.
alors essayer de partir, c'est comme remonter trop vite en plongée,
Our bodies can't reacclimate.
nos corps n'ont pas le temps de se réadapter.
That's why we go unconscious when we try to leave.
C'est pour ça qu'on s'évanouit.
Maybe we could slowly walk through the canyon,
Peut-être qu'on pourrait marcher lentement dans le canyon,
take a step, stand still.
nous arrêter, ne plus bouger,
Do it over eight to ten hours.
pendant 8 ou 10 heures,
Let our bodies acclimate.
le temps que nos corps s'habituent.
But, according to Prisca's timeline, who would be willing to give up 20 years of their life trying?
Mais si les calculs de Prisca sont bons, qui voudrait perdre 20 ans de sa vie ?
I'm sorry, this is nonsense.
C'est absurde.
Let's not shut down everyone's experience.
Ne soyez pas si méprisant.
Wait. Where are the kids?
Où sont les enfants ?
Trent!
Trent !
Kara!
Kara !
Answer us now! We need you here!
Répondez ! Revenez !
There they are.
Ils sont là-bas.
- Want some? - No, I'm not hungry.
T'en veux ? Non, j'ai pas faim.
Hey.
Mom! Dad!
Maman, papa !
Kara.
- What did you do? - We were just playing. It's okay. I just got a little fat. Mom, you're better.
Qu'est-ce que tu as fait ? On a joué, c'est tout. Et j'ai un peu grossi. Maman, t'es guérie.
Maddox?
- Maddox? - It's okay, Trent.
- Maddox ! - Ça va.
Just let Mom and Dad figure this out.
Maman et papa vont arranger ça.
My God, Guy.
Mon Dieu, Guy...
It's okay, right, Mom?
Ça va. Hein, maman ?
Jack Nicholson and Marlon Brando were in a movie together.
Jack Nicholson et Marlon Brando ont joué dans un film ensemble.
If she walked into the emergency room, I'd say she's about five months pregnant.
Si elle arrivait aux urgences, je dirais qu'elle est enceinte de 5 mois.
- What? - What?
Just stay calm, Trent.
Du calme, Trent.
She'll only be pregnant for about 20 minutes from the time of conception.
La grossesse devrait durer 20 min.
Why do you keep looking at me like you wanna steal my wallet? - Do you want me to punch you in the face? - Calm down. - I have no idea what you're talking about. - All right. Let's just concentrate on the issue at hand.
Qu'est-ce que t'as, tu veux mon portefeuille ? Je vais t'en mettre une. Du calme, je ne comprends pas ce que vous dites. Ne perdons pas de vue notre problème.
Do you know about movies? Dad, Mom tells you to sit down when you get like this. Hey. We need to get her help. Okay? - This cannot happen here. - It's gotten bigger. - Kara? It's Kara, right? - Yeah. Yeah.
Vous aimez le cinéma ? Papa, maman dit de t'asseoir quand ça te fait ça. Il lui faut de l'aide, ça ne peut pas arriver ici ! - Ça grossit. - Kara, c'est bien ça ?
Lay down on a blanket. It's gonna be okay. There's a lot of people here that can help you. We're all like your family now.
Viens t'allonger. Ça va aller, on va t'aider, on est comme une famille.
Oh, God.
Ohh.
Our cells are aging very fast here. Something to do with the rocks around the beach, we think. Just lay down on the sand, okay? Whatever would have happened to us is happening to us really fast, okay?
Nos cellules vieillissent très vite, ici. C'est peut-être lié à la roche. Tout nous arrive en accéléré.
I know.
What you did is how babies are made.
Vous avez fait un bébé.
I know, but I thought you had to do that ten times or something. - Take deep breaths. I'll breathe with you. - Did I get that wrong?
Mais je croyais qu'il fallait le faire 10 fois. J'avais mal compris ?
- Baby, come on. - It can happen after only once.
Il peut suffire d'une fois.
We didn't get a chance to talk about all this.
- Are Trent and I having a baby? - Did I get it wrong?
Trent et moi, on va avoir un bébé ?
Only a couple of minutes left if we're right.
Plus que 2 minutes !
- Is that the baby? Mom. - You got it. Okay.
C'est le bébé ? Maman.
- Charles! - Kara?
Charles !
I need to think about what to do. No! I need to help her.
Je réfléchis à la marche à suivre. Il faut que je l'aide !
- Mom! I'm scared! - It's okay.
Maman, j'ai peur !
- Kara, wait. Stay with me. - I'm here, baby. - Stay with me. - Just take my hand.
Je suis là.
Come on. Baby, can you hold her hand?
I've decided I'm gonna marry her.
C'est décidé, on va se marier.
And we are never gonna yell at each other and we are never getting divorced!
On se criera jamais dessus et on divorcera jamais !
Trent, listen to me. She's going to feel pain. Intense pain.
Trent, écoute-moi, elle va avoir mal, très mal,
Okay? Like she never felt before.
comme jamais auparavant.
But then it's going to pass. Okay? It's going to pass. - You did it, girl! - Mom!
Mais après, ça ira, d'accord ? Ça ira.
- All right. - Chrystal.
Chrystal.
Chrystal!
Hey, you blacked out. You can't go that way.
Vous vous êtes évanouie, on ne peut pas passer par là.
Come on. You're okay now. Come on.
Venez, ça va aller.
Get up. Get up.
- Come here. - No.
Look.
You're okay. Come on. Come on.
Tout va bien, venez.
- Babies crying helps them breathe. - It's here. We looked that up. Remember, Mom?
Il pleure pour mieux respirer, comme on avait vu.
You see?
We put him on the towel to clean him up.
On l'a posé sur la serviette,
He looked around and closed his eyes.
il a regardé autour de lui et il a fermé les yeux.
We had him on the towel for one minute.
On l'a laissé qu'une minute.
He died from lack of attention. Things are moving too fast here for a baby to survive.
Il est mort par manque de soins. Ça va trop vite pour qu'un bébé puisse survivre.
No. No, you're lying. You're lying! You're all lying! You're lying!
Vous mentez. Vous mentez tous !
Shut up, Trent. - Hey. Hey! - You're lying!
Calme-toi !
Maybe we should all talk about what just happened.
On devrait peut-être tous en parler ensemble.
Charles, get us out of here!
Charles, sors-nous d'ici !
Get us out of here now! You were supposed to protect us! You didn't protect us. Kara's hurt!
Sors-nous d'ici, tu devais nous protéger ! Tu nous as pas protégées ! Kara souffre !
I will make these decisions. Just give me a second.
Je vais prendre une décision, une petite seconde.
I used to see you in our neighborhood. Who are you?
Je t'ai déjà vu rôder dans le quartier, t'es qui ?
I'm Jarin!
Je suis Jarin !
I don't know where you live.
Je sais pas où vous habitez.
Don't condescend to me.
Pas de condescendance.
Put some makeup on your face.
Remaquille-toi.
I'm sorry about the baby.
Je suis désolée pour le bébé.
When I was your age, I was in love with a man.
À ton âge, j'étais amoureuse d'un homme.
His name was Giuseppe.
Il s'appelait Giuseppe.
He wasn't very handsome, and I left him.
Il était pas très beau et je l'ai quitté.
We looked silly together, he and I.
On avait l'air ridicule, ensemble.
He had nothing to offer.
Il avait aucun avenir.
For some reason, I think about him a lot here.
Je sais pas pourquoi je pense autant à lui, ici.
Leave me alone.
Laisse-moi.
- No, Charles! - Stop!
Non, Charles ! Arrêtez !
Stop!
He's gone.
Il est mort.
Oh, God.
I'm just going to take it.
Je vais le prendre.
- Now... - It's okay.
Ça va.
Everything will be okay.
Tout va bien.
I'll find another beach and I'll try to find help.
Je vais essayer de passer par la mer.
She needs her medicine.
Il lui faut son médicament.
We're lucky she hasn't had a seizure yet.
Même si elle a pas eu de crise.
It must be the beach. Whatever it's doing to my body.
C'est peut-être la façon dont mon corps réagit ici.
Guy, I was on the swim team. I'll make it.
J'ai fait de la natation, ça ira.
I'll make it.
Ça ira.
Watch him.
Surveillez-le.
Maybe I could climb that rock.
Je peux essayer d'escalader.
Maybe the effect, the blacking out, doesn't happen if you go up.
Peut-être qu'on ne s'évanouit pas en passant par le haut.
You can't do it.
T'y arriveras pas.
- I'll do it. - Yeah, he's strong. He can do it. - Yeah. - No.
J'y vais moi. Oui, il est fort.
I won't allow my son to do that.
Mon fils ne fera pas ça.
Prisca's right. It's too dangerous.
C'est trop dangereux.
It's a last resort.
Ce sera en dernier recours.
Mum...
Maman,
I do feel... overwhelmed.
c'est vrai que je me sens débordé.
I'm managing, but no one must know.
Je contrôle, mais personne doit savoir.
They'll try to stop me from working.
Ils voudront m'empêcher de travailler.
What should I do?
Qu'est-ce que je dois faire ?
Mum, tell me what to do.
Maman, dis-moi.
Prisca, something's bothering me.
Je pense à quelque chose.
Charles's family knew he had some kind of mental disorder.
Charles a une sorte de maladie mentale.
Someone in each group was sick.
Il y a un malade dans chaque famille.
How did you first hear about this place?
Comment tu as connu cet endroit ?
I don't know. I fell upon it.
Je ne sais pas, par hasard.
A random sweepstakes. It came with a receipt at the pharmacy.
Il y avait un jeu-concours sur un ticket de pharmacie.
I just followed it up online, started getting emails.
Je me suis inscrite et j'ai reçu des mails.
They know our medical condition. They chose us.
Ils ont nos antécédents médicaux, on a été choisis.
They have our passports. We could just disappear.
Ils ont nos passeports, on pourrait disparaître.
They sent us a special car to the airport. A plane.
Ils nous ont emmenés à l'aéroport, c'était leur avion.
They can make it look like we never left the house.
Ils peuvent faire croire qu'on n'est jamais partis.
You were thinking about leaving Dad.
Tu voulais quitter papa.
Weren't you?
Pas vrai ?
Yes.
I didn't want you two to suffer.
Je ne voulais pas que vous souffriez.
Was there someone else?
Il y avait quelqu'un d'autre ?
Did Dad know?
Papa savait ?
Maddox.
Maddox,
Please.
s'il te plaît.
I found out about this tumor and I got scared.
J'ai appris que j'avais une tumeur et j'ai eu peur.
I stare at the remains of nameless people in glass cases
J'ai vu toutes ces dépouilles anonymes au musée
and I kept thinking I'm going to be one of those people. Does that make any sense?
et j'ai pensé que j'en serais bientôt une. Tu comprends ?
I feel different than I felt yesterday.
J'ai l'impression de ne pas être la même qu'hier.
What I did feels like an illusion, I swear.
Ce que j'ai fait, j'ai l'impression de ne pas l'avoir vécu.
You hate me now.
Tu me détestes.
I just need some time, Mom.
Il me faut un peu de temps, maman.
We don't have that, baby.
On n'a pas le temps.
Look at you.
Allez.
You're an adult.
T'es adulte.
Be strong for everyone.
Sois forte pour les autres.
Connect to something bigger.
Connecte-toi à plus grand que toi.
Here, here, hold on. Lay him down, lay him down.
He must have gone unconscious swimming.
Il a dû perdre connaissance en nageant.
Brendon didn't do anything to that woman.
Brendon n'avait rien fait à cette femme.
We can't swim out, Prisca.
On ne peut pas passer par la mer.
We're not getting off this beach.
On ne partira jamais d'ici.
We never had a prom, or a graduation.
On n'a jamais eu de bal de fin d'année ou de remise de diplôme.
There are so many memories we didn't have.
Tous ces souvenirs qu'on n'a pas.
It's not fair.
C'est pas juste.
He needs to rest now.
Il faut lui dire au revoir.
Kara!
Wait. What if you get dizzy up there? - You might black out. - Trent, we're in charge now.
Tu risques de t'évanouir. C'est à nous d'agir, maintenant.
My dad could hurt more people.
Mon père peut recommencer,
I have to get him off this beach. Kara! Don't climb that. Come down! We'll find another way.
il faut le faire partir d'ici. Ne fais pas ça, descends ! On va trouver un autre moyen.
No! Don't! Trent! - Listen to Mom. - I have to go with her! Kara, wait! Don't climb. Let me get your mother. - Kara! - That's not the way.
Non, Trent ! Je vais avec elle ! Kara, ne fais pas ça, je vais chercher ta mère ! Arrête.
She's panicked and desperate. Talk to each other.
Elle est paniquée. Parlez-vous.
Kara, you and I should just stay together.
Kara, toi et moi, on doit rester ensemble.
What if we spend this whole time trying to get out of here and we still don't make it?
Tu veux perdre le temps qui nous reste ?
It'll be too short if we don't try.
Je veux plus de temps, justement.
No, Kara, please!
Kara, s'il te plaît !
Please just stay with me, please!
Reste avec moi.
If she makes it to the ledge, she might have a chance.
Si elle arrive en haut, ça peut marcher.
Go to the ledge and rest!
Vas-y et repose-toi en haut !
Oh, shit.
There has to be a way out.
Il y a forcément un passage.
It's a mathematical certainty. There must be a way out.
C'est mathématique, il y en a forcément un.
No. Why is she stopping?
Pourquoi elle s'arrête ?
No.
No, Kara. Kara, wake up! Kara, wake up! Wake up!
Kara, réveille-toi ! Réveille-toi !
Oh!
Kara?
Daddy...
Papa.
Let's all stay together.
On reste ensemble.
Nobody in this family goes alone anywhere.
Personne ne part tout seul.
I think I figured it out. I'm using these to swim out.
J'ai trouvé, je vais partir par la mer avec ça.
I have a sister.
J'ai une soeur.
She's a therapist, too. I need to get to my sister.
Elle est thérapeute aussi, il faut que je la voie.
We never talk. We had a fight a long time ago. She's older, but now I am.
On s'est brouillées il y a longtemps. C'est l'aînée, mais... maintenant, c'est moi.
The fighting seems ridiculous now.
Notre dispute me semble ridicule, aujourd'hui.
Patricia.
No.
What's happening to her?
Qu'est-ce qu'elle a ?
She was fine. What's happening?
Elle avait l'air d'aller bien.
She keeps stopping and starting.
Ça s'arrête pas.
Dad, do something.
Papa, fais quelque chose !
No.
Oh, no.
Kara?
Kara, where are you?
Kara, tu es où ?
Somebody's done this to us, Kara.
Quelqu'un nous a fait du mal.
I can't protect you anymore.
Je ne peux plus te protéger.
Kara!
No, you don't know. Jarin went in a different way. He went... And I'm a better swimmer than he is.
Jarin est parti dans l'autre sens. Je nage mieux que lui.
He's older than me. I could probably swim left...
Il était plus vieux, je peux...
Trent, stop it. No. No.
Trent, arrête.
- No, you're not a better swimmer. - Let me try.
- You're not even gonna let me try. - Listen. Listen.
Listen.
- ...then I can get on the rock. - We're not gonna let you. Stop. It won't work. I don't wanna give up. I really don't wanna give up. - We're not giving up. - If you let me try...
On te laissera pas y aller, arrête ! Ça marchera jamais. Je laisserai pas tomber. Je veux essayer.
My back.
Mon dos !
I need my calcium. Chrystal?
Il me faut mon calcium. Chrystal ?
Chrystal, stay with us.
Restez avec nous.
Don't look at me.
Me regardez pas.
Prisca, I have to tell you something.
Prisca, il faut que je te dise quelque chose.
I saw your text messages one day.
J'ai vu tes textos, un jour.
He says romantic things.
Il est du genre romantique.
I'm sorry.
Pardon.
I don't know who I would have been okay with. But with that guy?
Je sais pas qui j'aurais pu accepter, mais lui ?
He's a joke, he's a pretend person.
C'est une blague, il y a rien de vrai dans ce type.
You deserve someone so much better than that.
Tu mérites beaucoup mieux.
I should have said something when I saw it.
J'aurais dû réagir.
I hide from everything. I'm a fucking coward.
Je suis qu'un planqué, un lâche.
This was no one's responsibility but me.
Je suis la seule responsable.
Your anger should be aimed at me, just me.
Si tu dois être en colère, c'est contre moi.
There's no place I want to be but with you.
Le seul endroit où j'ai envie d'être, c'est avec toi.
Do you believe me?
Tu me crois ?
I want to be here...
J'ai envie d'être ici
right now.
et maintenant.
It's notebooks.
C'est des cahiers.
Well, maybe we can use some of the empty pages for the fire, keep Mom and Dad warm.
On peut prendre des pages blanches et faire un feu pour papa et maman.
Whoever it was wanted to be a science-fiction writer. It's full of story ideas.
C'était à un amateur de science-fiction, il a noté ses idées.
"Birds that can make you black out when they scream,
"Les oiseaux dont le cri peut faire s'évanouir
fly too close to an Emirates commercial plane one day."
finissent par voler trop près d'un avion de ligne."
He realized he was never getting off this beach.
Il a réalisé qu'il ne s'échapperait jamais d'ici.
He was trying to figure out what's going on.
Il essaie de comprendre.
"Magnetism of this exact spot on the Earth
"Le champ magnétique en cet endroit précis de la Terre,
with the rocks on this beach,
combiné à la roche de cette baie
submerged beneath the ocean for millions of years,
immergée depuis des millions d'années
deposited with special minerals,
et aux minéraux spécifiques,
are causing our cells to age at a rapid rate.
provoquent le vieillissement accéléré de nos cellules.
Are there other places like this?
Existe-t-il d'autres endroits comme ça ?
Who found this place?"
Qui a trouvé cet endroit ?"
Maybe we can make a metal tube that we can get in that stops the effects on our cells.
On pourrait fabriquer un tube en métal qui protégerait nos cellules.
Like at a dentist's office when they put a metal vest on us before an X-ray.
Comme le tablier de protection quand on fait une radio des dents.
I mean, then we could just walk out with it on us and... We'll get dizzy at first, but slowly we'll get used to it and we can leave, right?
On pourrait partir avec... Au début, on aurait la tête qui tourne mais on s'habituerait.
Where are we gonna make a metal tube?
Comment on fabriquerait ce tube ?
He wrote down a list of all the names and the addresses of the people with him on the beach.
Il a fait la liste de tous ceux qui étaient ici avec lui.
Maddox, that's a camera.
C'est une caméra.
They're recording us.
On est filmés.
Why would they do this?
Pourquoi ils font ça ?
Oh, no.
Who is that?
Qui est là ?
Prisca, who is that?
Prisca, c'est qui ?
You're gonna tell them what I did.
Tu vas tout raconter.
The man with the tattoos,
L'homme aux tatouages,
he was gonna steal things from my home.
il voulait entrer chez moi et me voler.
Guy!
- Aah! - No! I can't let you tell them.
Je dois t'empêcher de leur dire.
I'm a good doctor.
Je suis un bon médecin.
He was gonna follow us, he was gonna steal things from our home.
Il allait nous suivre et nous voler des choses.
Why don't you believe me?
Il faut me croire.
I stopped him.
Je l'ai empêché.
Tell me where the knife is, Prisca!
Dis-moi où est le couteau !
I keep having these thoughts.
J'ai tout le temps ces pensées.
Listen, they keep coming to me.
Don't tell anyone.
Leur dis pas.
Prisca, hide the kids! I'll protect you!
Prisca, cache les enfants, je le retiens !
Yes.
Maddox!
Trent!
I need you two to go and find somewhere to hide now! Somewhere where someone can't find you. I need you to go right now! - Mom, what? Wait. - And don't ask any questions! Now, go! Hide!
Partez d'ici, allez vous cacher là où personne ne vous trouvera ! Maintenant ! Ne posez pas de questions ! Vite, cachez-vous !
Go!
Shh.
There's someone in here with us.
Il y a quelqu'un.
My body hurts to move.
J'ai mal quand je bouge.
I miss Giuseppe.
Giuseppe me manque.
Don't look at me!
Me regardez pas !
Turn off the light!
Pas de lumière !
I don't wanna be seen!
Je veux pas qu'on me voie !
Argh.
Kara's dead, isn't she?
Kara est morte, hein ?
Whoever did this killed her, didn't they?
C'est ceux qui font ça qui l'ont tuée ?
Kara died.
Kara est morte.
But it was an accident.
C'était un accident.
Aah!
Don't look!
Regardez pas.
God, it's already healed in the wrong position.
Ça s'est ressoudé à l'envers.
Turn off the light!
Pas de lumière !
Turn the light off.
I'm chief medical officer of my hospital!
Je suis chef de service dans mon hôpital !
I am not gonna let you
Je te laisserai pas
take it away from me!
m'enlever ça !
Argh.
It's rust.
Il est rouillé.
It acts like poison when it gets into your bloodstream.
Ça va se répandre comme du poison dans votre sang.
I'm sorry you were on this beach.
Je suis désolée pour vous,
But this is my family.
mais c'est ma famille.
Dad, Mom, you guys gotta stay hydrated.
Papa, maman, il faut vous hydrater.
Mom.
Maman.
Are you warm enough?
Tu as assez chaud ?
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason to remain ♪
♪ I will remain ♪
Were we fighting about something?
On était en train de se disputer ?
We were.
Oui.
Well, whatever it was, I'm not mad anymore.
Ce n'est pas grave, je ne suis plus fâché.
I can't remember.
Je ne me souviens pas...
Why did we want to leave this beach?
Pourquoi on voulait partir d'ici ?
So beautiful.
C'est tellement beau.
It doesn't matter.
Ça n'a plus d'importance.
It's funny.
C'est drôle.
I forget...
J'ai oublié
the word.
le mot
It's about my feelings for you.
pour dire ce que je ressens pour toi.
I know.
Je sais.
- Dad? - Dad.
Papa.
Mom?
Maman !
Oh, Mom.
We have about 13 hours left, do you think?
Il nous reste quoi, 13 heures, tu dirais ?
Hmm.
We just got three days older while you held my face.
On a vieilli de 3 jours le temps de cette caresse.
Should we keep trying to get out?
On essaie encore de partir ?
I guess so.
Il faudrait.
Wanna make a sandcastle first?
On fait un château de sable, d'abord ?
I wonder if everybody continues to feel like a kid
Je me demande si tout le monde reste un enfant
when they're our age or...
une fois grand,
is it because we were kids yesterday?
ou si c'est parce qu'on était enfants hier.
Idlib sent me a message I never decoded.
J'ai un message d'Idlib que j'ai pas décodé.
Yeah, we thought we were so smart.
On se croyait super malins.
Decode it.
Décode-le.
Each symbol means a letter.
Chaque symbole correspond à une lettre.
We thought we were like spies.
On se prenait pour des espions.
What was the big message?
Alors, ce message ?
What's it say?
Il dit quoi ?
Mon oncle n'aime pas le corail
The coral might protect us from the effects of the rocks.
Le corail bloque peut-être les effets de la roche.
Maybe that's like our metal tube.
Comme notre tube en métal.
Maybe we're just making up what we want to hear.
Ou peut-être qu'on rêve.
Maybe he heard they took people to this beach.
Il a pu entendre parler de la plage.
Idlib heard something he shouldn't have.
Idlib a entendu quelque chose.
He has no idea what it means, but he knows it's bad.
Il comprend pas mais il sait que c'est pas bien.
He's trying to help us.
Il essaie de nous aider.
Wait.
Attends.
I need to get something.
Je vais chercher quelque chose.
Both of them drowned.
Ils se sont noyés.
For a second, I thought they were gonna get through the coral.
Ils ont failli passer le corail.
I don't know how they suddenly thought about going there. Theo, are you sure they didn't make it? We can't have another incident.
Je ne sais pas comment ils y ont pensé. Theo, tu es sûr ? On ne veut pas de nouvel incident.
Sidney, relax. I watched for a minute and a half.
Sidney, j'ai attendu 1 minute et demie.
And the person who got through last year ended up drowning anyway.
Et celui qui est passé l'an dernier s'est noyé ensuite.
We're fine.
On est bons.
Final members of Trial 73 are deceased.
Les derniers sujets de l'essai 73 sont décédés.
Observations complete.
Observation terminée.
Bringing drives back, returning to base.
Je rapporte les disques durs à la base.
À la mémoire de l'expédition disparue
All rooms for this trial have been cleared.
Les chambres ont été nettoyées
Uh, home computer devices have been wiped.
comme tout le matériel informatique,
Three home computers still waiting to be scrubbed.
il reste 3 ordinateurs aux domiciles.
Hello. Uh...
a moment of silence for the members of Trial 73.
Un moment de silence pour les sujets de l'essai 73.
Thank you.
Merci.
Um... I'll try not to be dramatic.
Je vais essayer de rester mesuré.
Because of this beach,
Grâce à cette plage,
we have been able to save hundreds of thousands of lives
nous avons sauvé des centaines de milliers de vies
with new medicines.
avec de nouveaux médicaments.
Before we're done, it will be millions.
À terme, ce sera des millions.
As you know, we do trials and fail constantly.
Comme vous savez, chercher, c'est se tromper sans cesse.
But not today.
Mais pas aujourd'hui.
Tell them, Sidney.
À toi, Sidney.
One of this cohort was a woman with the epileptic seizures.
L'un des membres de cette cohorte était une femme épileptique.
Her name was Patricia Carmichael. She suffered debilitating seizures her whole life.
Elle s'appelait Patricia Carmichael et souffrait de crises invalidantes.
Nothing could help her.
Rien ne la soulageait.
The medicine we gave her when she arrived turned out to be the exact mixture.
Ce qu'on lui a donné à son arrivée s'est avéré être la bonne molécule.
She didn't have a seizure for 8 hours and 17 minutes.
Elle n'a pas eu de crise pendant 8 heures et 17 minutes.
Sixteen and a half years.
Soit 16 ans et demi.
We cured her of her epilepsy.
On a l'a guérie de son épilepsie.
We'll now fast-track trials,
Nous allons donc accélérer les essais
make that medicine and share it with the whole world.
pour fabriquer ce médicament et l'offrir au monde entier,
Every single person that needs it.
à tous ceux qui en ont besoin.
Nature made that beach exist for a reason.
La nature a créé cette plage dans un but précis.
Warren and Warren was meant to find it on their research expedition.
Warren & Warren était destiné à la découvrir
We were meant to test medicines in one day, instead of a lifetime.
pour pouvoir tester ses médicaments sur un jour plutôt que sur une vie.
Lots more work to be done, everyone.
Il nous reste encore beaucoup à faire.
Let's do what nature wanted us to do.
Accomplissons ce que la nature attend de nous.
Mr. and Mrs. Brody will arrive at 11:00 a.m. with six non-targeted guests.
M. et Mme Brody arrivent à 11 h avec 6 clients neutres.
Joseph Brody has early-onset Parkinson's.
Joseph Brody présente un Parkinson précoce.
Florence Brody will be accompanying him.
Florence Brody sera avec lui.
I'm gonna be a broken record about this, Nils.
Au risque de radoter,
We should separate the pure medical subjects from the mental illness subjects.
il faut séparer les maladies physiques des maladies mentales.
Our violent schizophrenic patient cost us the data on our blood clot patient. Sidney, I doubt we'll alter protocol at this point, but put it in a form and submit it to Warren and Warren again.
Le schizophrène a détruit nos données sur les caillots sanguins. On ne changera pas le protocole à ce stade, mais soumets de nouveau ta demande à la direction.
How are you?
Ça va ?
Those kids went home. They don't matter.
Les enfants d'hier sont rentrés, oublie-les.
I tell you which kids you can play with. You have to trust me
Je sais avec qui tu peux jouer, fais-moi confiance.
and don't ask questions. Okay?
Et ne pose pas de question. D'accord ?
- Okay. - Good.
Bien.
Now, those kids are fine. See, you can play with them.
Eux là-bas, c'est bon, tu peux jouer avec eux.
- Okay. - Good.
You're a police officer.
Vous êtes policier.
Yeah.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Brody.
M. et Mme Brody,
Welcome to our version of paradise.
bienvenue sur notre bout de paradis.
Thank you.
Merci.
- It's lovely. - Thank you.
C'est un bel endroit.
This is Madrid.
Voici Madrid.
From your food and beverage preferences that you selected,
D'après vos préférences gustatives,
we've made you cocktails to welcome you.
nous vous avons préparé ces cocktails.
- Sorry. - No worries, Mr. and Mrs. Brody.
Ce n'est rien,
We'll just make a new set. It'll only take a few moments.
nous allons les refaire, ça ne prendra qu'un instant.
I wouldn't take anything they give you.
N'acceptez rien de leur part.
They left us all to die.
Ils nous ont tous laissé mourir.
My name is Trent Capa.
Je m'appelle Trent Capa.
I'm Maddox Capa.
Et moi, Maddox Capa.
All three are missing persons?
Tous les 3 disparus ?
Sending you the rest of the names now.
Je t'envoie les autres noms.
Our parents are Guy and Prisca Capa.
Nos parents sont Guy et Prisca Capa.
We live at 707 Pine Street, Philadelphia, USA.
Nous vivons au 707 Pine Street, à Philadelphie.
Also with us was Jarin Carmichael, who was a nurse.
Il y avait avec nous...
Listen, we have to get security. What's happening? Are you listening to me?
Il faut appeler la sécurité. Vous m'entendez ?
Gentlemen. Hey, hey, hey!
Messieurs !
Gentlemen, we have a problem. We need your assistance immediately.
On a besoin de vous tout de suite.
Two of our guests need your attention.
Please solve this problem, now.
They've arrested everybody here.
Tout le monde a été arrêté ici.
Subpoenas are being served at Warren and Warren's headquarters this week.
Les responsables de Warren & Warren sont cités à comparaître.
Let's get them to the airport.
On les dépose à l'aéroport.
Your aunt will be waiting for you when you land.
Votre tante vous attendra à l'arrivée.
How's she handling things?
Comment elle réagit ?
How would you feel if a 50-year-old man called and told you he was your six-year-old nephew?
À un homme de 50 ans qui l'appelle en disant être son neveu de 6 ans ?
We'll be okay.
Ça ira.
♪ Somewhere on the edge of sleep ♪
♪ There is a taste of peace ♪
♪ Every night we dance in my dreams ♪
♪ The cupid's an archer ♪
♪ His violent departure ♪
♪ Leaves us at the altar ♪
♪ Wounded, weak and ready to bleed ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪
♪ Through comfort and pain ♪
♪ Till I wash away ♪
♪ You are all that I can see ♪
♪ Alone I'm obsolete ♪
♪ Every flight is purgatory ♪
♪ Stripped of the armor ♪
♪ We plead and we barter ♪
♪ We stray from my harbor ♪
♪ Searching for some false remedy ♪
♪ I'll wash away someday ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪
♪ Through comfort and pain ♪
♪ Till I wash away ♪
♪ I could never leave you ♪
♪ You are my first and last love ♪
♪ Every day I'm near you ♪
♪ I have enough ♪
♪ I'll wash away some day ♪
♪ No monuments made in my name ♪
♪ There is no life I'd trade ♪
♪ You are my reason ♪
♪ To remain ♪
♪ And I will remain ♪
Adaptation : Chloé Leleu
Sous-titrage DELUXE MEDIA Paris
French
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412