Yes Sir, I redrafted the contracts
with the new stipulations.
- Where are they?
- I'll fax them right the way.
Did you make the changes that I ask?
Yea, I included the 4% increase
in the extra 10 million.
No, no, it's 4% of one million.
No, no that's not what I was told.
- Who told you to do this?
- Their lawyers...
Those idiots, you have to change it,
it's a total lack of communication.
No, no it's okay, I have
everything right here.
Ok, that's what I want you to do.
- Okay, can you just hang on for a second.
- All right.
Thank you... Hi Jody.
Mr. Harper wants to
see you in his office.
- OK.
- Can I do something?
You know what, it's okay, I have
a few more things to get done yet.
- You should go home.
- Are you sure?
Yea, it's late, I don't
want your parents to worry.
get out'f here, ok.
- Merry Christmas Angela.
- Merry Christmas Jody.
Hello, Lorraine, of course I will...
Just... just let me call you back okay.
In a few minutes I promise, okay.
Still working on the contract?
What can I do for you. Jim?
I mean...
Look, I feel terrible
about what happend...
It's all right, it's fine.
Just let's not worry about it, okay.
No... it's not okay.
I feel like a real jerk.
I had to many drinks,and... you know
how these christmas parties can be.
And we had a baby last year...
and it's been just a hard year.
I'm sure it has.
I... I simply wanted to tell you that
I'm just realy realy sorry, okay..
Apoligy excepted.
Thank's... thank's.
Merry Christmas Angela.
You too, Jim.
You're calling me from work?
I thought you went home first.
Well, I have everything
with me, don't worry.
- Then you'll come here, Angi.
- Yea sure.
You pick up the Santa claus
costum, I hope you didn't forget it?
I didn't forget it, it's in the car.
I believe we have everything
done, and the kids are all excited.
Believe me I can't wait to
get out there and see you guys.
Jimmy put that back,
we're having dinner later.
I wanna eat now.
- I want it.
- Just wait.
- Please, don't be late.
- I won't, I promise, I won't.
- Ok, bye.
- Bye.
My God.
Sorry... I was just
locking up the floors.
I didn't know anybody be working
this late, on christmas eve.
- Yea, me neither.
- Sorry I'll come back later.
Actualy if you wouln't mind waiting...
I'll lock up my office
and I can go down with you.
- Ok, sure.
- Ok, two seconds.
- You work all night?
- Yea...
Well, they're closeing the
building for next 3 days.
Besides there giving me new years off.
Oh well, that's good.
Well, I hope to get home on time,
for the girls, to open there presents
- How are they?
- Great.
- Come on, your parents can't stand me.
- You're wrong about that, they love you.
So where are you going this evening?
I'm going to my
sister's house in Jersey.
New Jersey? I thought of you
more as an Upper East Side girl.
Yea, Upper East Side of Main, actualy.
- I grew up on a farm.
- A farm?
Now I'm having trouble believe'ing that.
Don't let the fancy clothes deceive you,
I'm a farm girl realy, I grew up on a farm.
So Is that what you
call it, even if it is.
- Good night, Carl.
- Merry Christmas, Angela.
- You too, I'll see you soon.
- Yea...
Yea, I promise you,
I'm leaveing right now.
I know... I know, I'm
sorry, I'm in the elevator.
25 minutes tops.
I can't hear you, what?
Lorraine, you're breaking up, hello?
You got to be kidding me.
Oh, God... not now.
I guess I just leave the car.
Hello.
Jesús.
Rocky... Rocky, what're you doing?
Stay down, down.
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay.
Ah... look, can you onlock
the door to the elevator room.
My car wont start I need to
go upstairs and get a cab.
Yea, I can...
I got to find my key cards
Where are they? I got to
do my round anyways so...
- Ok.
- What happend to your car?
- I have no idea.
- You know, you probably left the lights on.
No, I don't think so, I'm usualy
pretty good about that kind of thing.
People do it all the time, they
drive down here in the dark...
you know, it happends.
Here they are.
Great.
You know actualy I just thought,
I have a charger in the back,
So if It is your battery
probably, you can use that.
Oh, thank you, but I realy should
get a cab, I'm so late already.
No, i don't know about getting
a cab it's Christmas eve.
So, it's up to you what ever you want.
- How long will it take?
- Just a few minutes, give me one second.
So, where's your car?
Over there.
Working late hugh...
Well, I know how you feel.
These are pretty reliable
cars for the most part.
They're supose to be.
Right, positive.
Negative.
All right, try it, turn it over.
That's strange.
Okay, hang on, can you
turn your headlights on?
Okay, try with the key again.
Shit.
All right, turn the head lights off.
You know what, that's it, I...
You've been a great help, but I give up.
I'm sorry about that, I
don't know what happend.
I thought I could do something about it.
That's okay, you've been great, can
you just get me the elevator now.
I was just trying to help.
I know, and I appreciate it, thank you.
Listen, I know your upset
about the car, and I'm sorry.
It's the holydays, you
know, time to be thankfull,
Yea, you know what you're
right, I should be thankfull.
I...
I prepared this small
Christmas meal for myself.
You can join me if you like.
- I'm just kidding.
- Oh... yea realy... i'm acausted.
But realy, thank you for the help.
Oh, your welcome, maybe some other time.
Yea, Sure.
You can handle this by yourself?
You sure you don't want
me to call you a cab?
Yea, I got the number.
All right suit yourself,
Merry Christmas.
Carl?
Hi, can I get a cab at
2370 Park Ave, please?
Are you sure? Well, that's
okay I'll wait, thank you.
Hey, Lorraine, you're not
gonna believe what happend.
No, actualy my car wouldn't start.
Look... just start without me, and I'll
be there in an hour and make it up to them.
Ok, I'll see you soon, bye.
Hello... oh, oh great,
thank you, thank you.
This is not happening.
No, no, you got to be kidding me.
Carl! Carl where are
you? Is anybody here?
Ok, go, go.
What the...?
One second ok, I'll be
right back, one second.
Hello, can you hear me?
I got a cab waiting for me outside,
can you open the front gate, please.
Hello?
No, no, no, no, no, wait please.
Damn, don't leave me here.
No service.
Wake up, damn it, the cab just left.
Hey, I am still in here, wait.
great...
Hello?
Ok, don't be gettin' paranoid.
I got to get the feel of this.
Hello?
Oh... oh... fuck...
Ho, ho, ho, Merry Christmas,
you've been a good little girl.
Ok, you're all right, right, okay.
Ok. you're okay? take it easy,
Okay.
What happend to me? What time is it?
You just fell, you'll be all right.
I don't feel well,
I'm gettin' realy sick.
Hold on, I'll get you
some water, all right.
You got to be careful, okay.
or you gonna hurt yourself.
Just try to stay calm.
Ok.
Oh, ok, here.
Ok, I will help you up, ok then.
Here we go, ok.
All right now... ok,
Just try to relaxe and
I will clean this up.
Ok.
All right... I'll be right back.
Are you hungry?
I... have turkey, mashed potatoes...
a little clam bake, and
I even have some... corn bread.
Oh, I'm sorry about this.
I was just kidding...
I didn't mean to scare you.
good it's still warm.
If not, I have a microwave so...
Are you feeling any better?
What happend to my clothes?
Like I said, you fell and
your clothes got dirty, so...
Maybe... maybe you like some wine...
to... relax a little bid.
Look, I don't know what you're doing,
but you better just fucking untie me.
This is a California wine...
It's from Sanoma county, that's where
I'm from, it's beautyful up there.
Where're you from?
What'd you want?
I wanna know where you from?
I'm from Wheatfield.
Wheatfield... where is that?
Why don't you just
tell me what you want?
I just wanna know everything.
I want you to relax.
Cheers.
Ok, I... I'll make a toast.
Here is to good friends,
and home towns and...
Wheatfield, where...
where-ever that is.
- Ahh... listen...
- Tom.
Tom... I have some place to be.
You know I'm starting on my vacation.
Yea, I know.
And way to many, you don't have time for yourself,
you don't need to be everyones backin call.
Maybe we just... can
do this next year?
I prepared everything, it's all here
I know... and it looks realy good.
Yea, great.
Well let's eat, I'm... starving.
Tom this is realy sweet, but...
But you know, my whole family is
excpecting me, and I've got plans...
I guess some plans
are made to be broken.
You wanna say grace, or should I?
Hell, let's forget it.
I'm not to religious anyway.
Bon Appetite.
What'd you like to do?
You know, after work and
stuff... there's hobbies,
I know it's a mundane question, I guess people
ask them to get to know each other, right?
I read... right now
I'm reading Hemingway.
The Sun Also Rises.
You realy should eat this,
it's gonna get cold.
So anyway, in this book, this
guy loves this girl so much...
That he's willing to forgive...
everything that she does.
Even her infidelities.
That's a pretty intense story, but...
that's what love supose to be, right?
My boyfriend's gonna get worried,
he's gonna come looking for me...
If I don't show up, he's gonna come
looking for me, he knows where I work.
How long you've guys been
dating... hanging out?
- 2 years.
- 2 years?
- Do you guys live together?
- That's none of your fucking buisness.
That's not a very nice way to talk.
Yea, we do live together, ok.
2 years...
that's more then a
boyfriend, that's a...
...sounds more like wedding bells.
- You guys got any plans?
- Yes.
What does... what's your fiance do?
He's a journalist.
Journalist? See, I knew
he had to be smart.
- What kind of journalist?
- Sports.
Sports... what paper?
- The Post.
- The Post? I read the post.
- What's his name?
- Mark Clayton.
Clayton? Clayton? I
don't remember that name.
Well... I have one right here.
It's online, it's the Post online.
You know what... it is amaizing, that
you're able to keep a relationship...
...with all the hours that you work!
He must get realy lonely, when
you have to work late, right?
Do you love him?
Does he love you?
I'm only asking because... I'm
worried how quick he's gonna get here.
I'm sure he's already on his way.
Right...
he's probably on the
highway as we speak.
- What kind of car does he drive?
- I don't...
You don't know... you don't know
what kind of car your fiance drives?
- A Toyota, I think...
- Toyota?
That's a fast car, he can be here
a lot sooner then I was thinking.
He'll be coming down this
ramp right now as we speak
You know, you haven't been,
very talketive since we've met.
But now...
...you'll tell me all
about'm... your boyfriend.
No sorry your fiance.
So either we become best
friends over dinner...
...or you're lying to me?
Let me guess... you're lying to me.
You don't you really
have a boyfriend, do you?
But you want one,
...you want somebody
that cares about you...
...who worries about you.
Please, don't.
You've got a... you got a great family,
You know you got... Lorraine.
Little Jimmy, Rose, and they love you.
They probably are worried about you.
Maybe we should give them a call.
Yea... tell them you're okay.
What'd you think?
What should we say?
I know... I know, we should
say you made other plans.
No, you already said that one.
You know what, you should think
of something, you're a good liar.
Go ahead... go!
No.
Hello, hello?
Hey Rosie, can you get
your mommy on phone.
Who's calling please?
It's auntie Angi.
- Mommy it's aunt Angi.
- Give me a second, okay.
Hey, where are you? Angela?
I not feeling well.
What'd you mean? We're
all waiting for you.
- She says, she doesn't feel well.
- She said that the last time.
Can I speak with my sister, please?
So where are you Angi?
Angela?
At home, I went home.
- What's wrong? where is she?
- I realy don't understand.
Last time I talked to you,
you said you were on your way.
What about the costum?
What's the big deal, you should
know your sister by now.
Angela, you know, you should try to
put your family ahead of yourself.
Give me the phone.
Angi what's wrong?
Hello? I can't hear her? Hello!
Sweety, can you hear me?
Hi mom, I'm here.
Honey, what happend? Where are you?
I don't know, I think I got the flue
You sound terrible, are
you sure you're okay?
- Honey.
- Yes.
I just need some rest.
Ok, well rest up and hopefully you
feel better for lunch tomorrow.
And sweety don't worry
about the costum, ok?
Merry Christmas, Ángel, I love you.
I love you too, mom.
That's the best Christmas
present anyone has ever given me.
Thank you.
And now I have a present for you.
Go ahead, open it.
Aren't you even curios?
Come on, open it.
Yea, yea, yea.
I'll bet you're curios now, yea?
Ok, enough torture.
Watch, okay.
Why are you showing this to me?
Wait...
You fuckin' male asshole.
Sorry you had to see that.
You wanna go for a stroll?
These guys... they always
do... whatever they want.
Here we go.
Stay... stay down, stay.
Hold still...
Why did you do that?
Rocky, shut the fuck up...
- Let me to help you up.
- Don't.
Don't be silly, I'm not
gonna hurt you, all right?
You're hurting my arm.
Because you wont let me help.
- Come on.
- Where we're going?
I wont tell you, just ...
now... I need to show you something.
Nobody behind us, yea.
Here we go.
Oh, oh... I think I drank to much wine.
I realy shouldn't be driving.
I'm just kiddin'.
I've seen you drive
out here so many times.
It's strange actualy to
be in the car with you.
In fact it's nice.
I thought you said we where taking a drive.
We are.
Then why are we going down, Tom?
It's freezing out there.
Besides... this is gonna be much better.
Why are we down here, Tom?
Tom?
Oh my God.
What're we gonna do... what is this?
This is my present to you.
Takes this and show him.
Show him what?
Show him you're not a slut.
Take this and teach him, he can't
be touching every woman he wants.
Are you talking about what
happend in the elevator?
Oh, Tom... no, no, no, you don't
understand, that was a mistake.
That was a stupid mistake.
What?
He try'd to rape you.
No, he just got a litle out'o hand at
this party,Tom.
He was hardly trying to rape me, look...
he was drunk, he apoligized.
Ohh... he apoligized, ohhh...
You think that you're the
first one he did this to?
I've seen him trying to touch
every women in this building.
He is a pervert, he is a degenerate.
No, he's not.
He's a good man, Tom... he's
a good man, just look at him,
He has a family, and he has a wife,
Tom please. Tom...
Stop, don't keep calling
out my name, all right.
I know what you're tryin' to do.
You're trying to humanize yourself,
like you're some poor victum.
I told you, I'm not gonna hurt you.
All right? Stop calling out my name.
All right... enough with this,
Tom, Tom, Tom.
What did I say... look,
I know you're a person...
I know you're a person, okay.
I'm a person too.
I know you have feelings.
I have feelings too.
I care about your feelings.
He's the one you should be scared of.
He's the one who has no feelings.
Look... you wanna help him.
Take this and teach him a lesson.
I told you... he apoligized.
He apoligizes and
then he'll do it again.
And he'll apologizes again.
You better put a stop to this,
before he's having his way with you.
Tom...
Please believe me, it was
just a misunderstanding, Tom
Stop calling out my name, I told you.
- Didn't I?
- Yes, yes, yes.
You're scaring me.
Jesús, when will you understand?
I'm here to help you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Ok.
I'll do it.
You untie me and I'll do it.
No... no, no, no...
You're a good person.
You're a good person too.
I should never have ask
you to do this, I'm sorry.
No, it's okay... it's ok,
Because I want to...
You just have to untie me, and i'll do it.
No, no, no, it's my job... it's my job.
No, Tom listen to me,
it's not... it's not.
Please, don't do anything.
Don't try to run away, ok?
Can I trust you?
You can trust me.
Don't do it...
don't...
So you like to touch girls, do you?
No, no, no?
Look at her, I said look at her.
Does she look happy to you?
Yea, yea, you messed
with the wrong girl, ha...
What makes you think, you deserve her?
What gives you the right?
You're something else, you know that.
You pretensges ivy leauge, piece of shit.
You don't own the world,
and everyone in it.
That's what a guy like you thinks only...
puts his hands...
...all over a girl, who
obviously is not interested?
Who is obviously not a slut.
That's what you do think they are, right?
Yea... I can't hear you.
What'd you say? Hey... what... what?
Hey can you speak up...
Because you can't talk your way out
of this one can you?
Why I even wasting my time with you?
No...
Why Angela, he deserves it?
He don't have this coming, please...
Nooo...
No Tom... stop it.
Very Merry Christmas, asshole.
Look, he wont be bothering you again.
Where're we going? We
can't just leave him there.
No we can't.
Why are you defending him?
No I'm not.
You like it, you like to be touched?
You like it when he touches
you in the parking garage?
You wanna get laid there?
You know that's not true.
So what, what is it? is it a career thing?
Did you fuck him to get a promotion?
Leave me alone.
You're right, You're right, I'm sorry.
We shouldn't leave him here.
What you're doing?
We're just gonna take him for a little drive.
What're you doing? Stop it...
Don't Tom, no, please, stop it, stop it.
Please Tom, please...
stop it... stop it.
Please, what're you doing Tom?
No, no, don't.
Oh, my God.
Tom don't do it, please don't.
No, don't.
You're a good person.
Please, don't do this, please,
No, don't, stop it... stop it,
Hey, hey, hey...
Hey... hey, where're you going?
Angela... Angela, come back.
You broke your word now... liar.
Hey... down here.
Hey, can you hear me? Help...
I'm down here! Can anybody hear me?
Shit!
Good boy.
Ok, good boy, just wanna take the bag.
Help me!
Help me, please!
Help, please!
Help me, please! Somebody
is trying to kill-me!
Help me, somebody is trying to
kill-me! Please somebody help me.
NO SERVICE
NEXTEL
Angela...
Please, if anybody can hear me, I'm trapped
in the underground parking section...
in the Arcadia Building at 2370 Park Ave.
Someone is trying to kill me.
Angela, come out!
Shit!
Angela...
Can't we talk about this?
Looks like somebody is
playing games. Hey Rocky?
Angela?
Exit.
Elevators.
Please!
Come on, lobby... lobby!
Open the fucking lobby.
Angela!
Hello...
Hello help! somebody...
can somebody hear me? Hello!
Please, hello... Please, anwser
help me... please, please...
This is Mayflower security, hello...
- Hello...
- Yes, yes, yes, I am here can you hear me?
- I can hear you fine, how can I help you?
- I've been kidnapped, I work at...
Brighter Smith & Steinberg,
at 2370 Park Ave.
I'm hiding in the elevator...
please can you call 911?
OK, calm down miss, is the
kidnapper with you right now?
No, no... he's outside, he's in the parking
garage, he already killed someone else.
- Did you see him do it?
- Yes...
he's name is Thomas, and he's the
parking attented in my building.
If you just please hurry, I'm in danger.
Ma'm just try to relax you and
take a deep breath.
How in the fuck you expect me to relax?
This man is trying to kill me, can you just...
please try to understand and call the cops,
Please just call 911!
The police? No, I'm sure he's just
trying to help you out.
Correct?
Angela!
Angela you still there?
You can fuck me, and don't call the cops, I'm gonna
stay downhere as long as it takes, till they get here, so you can just get the fuck out!
I just wanna talk to you Angela... that's why I pretendet to be someone else, Ok... don't be upset.
Will you come out? I was just kidding.
You can go to the hell!
Angela, don't you understand, I did it
for you, that guy showed you no respect
Why won't you talk to me Angela?
Just give me a chance.
You know if you would give us a chance,
things could realy work out.
You gonna like me, you know that's usualy what happends when 2 People being forced together, in a desperate situation
They have to depend on one another,
and then suport each other...
and they starting to like each other...
and some times they even fall in love.
Angela...
Angela, please, don't do this...
Why won't you talk to me?
You know? I wish you had just a little
bid more respect for yourself
I wont move... you hear me?
I'm not fucking moving!
What is this... Carl?
Carl...
Carl... no...
come on... Carl... let's go...
Please...
Angela...
It's freezing out here.
Angela.
What a mess!
Angela...
I think Carl is hurt.
Angela, shouldn'd we call
him an ambulance?
That way he can go back to his kids and
his family, and you can go to your sisters...
and I can stay here, in this parkinglot,
all by myself... cause...
that's all... and that's what
everybody wants.
Angela...
I just can't keep chasing you around
all night... Angela,
Besides... the whole place is locked.
Angela?
Angela! Where you gonna go
if you get away?
It's freezing out there.
Angela?
Angela!
Very, merry christmass... Carl.
Thank you.
You are wonderful.
Do you want make-up?
Do you? Ok.
You have the most beautyfull lips,
i have ever seen.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
You have a wonderfull body... and it's
so good to be here, baby...
me and you ...
Angela, honey... your skin is so...
it's... so soft...
Honey, oh, I love you, I do love
you... Angela you know that, right?
Hello! Shit, shit!
Hello, I'm down here, can you hear me?
It's okay.
Hello Officer, can I help you?
Open up the gate, please.
Yes Sir, I'll be right up.
I'm sorry, I have to do this,
I'll be right back.
Hey... sorry about that, I was on the
bottom floor doing my rounds.
What's going on tonight?
We got a call about a disturbings at this
address, you know anything about that?
No, it's been real quiet all night.
See anything, hear anything suspicios?
No, no, like I said, I was just doing
my rounds, and...
... it's been realy quiet, I haven't
seen anybody down here.
Any cars in there.
Yea, well, it's a parking garage.
Now there's a few cars scatterd over here, on
this level, on the second level is a rental thing...
I mean, like I said there's been nobody
around tonight, except me and Rocky.
There's 2 of you working here tonight.
Yea, kind'o, he's my dog.
He's down in the office right now.
We gonna take a look around, man...
get in the back, we'll give you a ride.
Yea, that's a great idea.
I just gotta close this gate, there's
a lot'o homeless people around here.
OK, thank's for the ride.
Oh, if you guys wanna check the other floors,
just keep going around this way...
but be careful on P3, there's a
brocken water main, okay.
- We'll see you around.
- OK.
What the hell's going on here, man?
Help me! Help! Help!
Help me! Help!
Help me!
You sure, you haven't seen anything
weird tonight?
No, no, everybody left pretty early tonight.
You're have-ing a party in there?
No, it's just me and Rocky,
not having a party.
Do you have somebody coming over
to visit, you know, for a little action?
Me? No, no, the company would fire me
if they find anyone down here tonight.
Especially at this hour.
Oh, well, we don't wanna break
any rules, right tiger?
- No, not on my watch.
- Ok, well let's go.
Help me!
All right, well, I got to open the gate,
so I'll just take the stairs.
Let's do it.
Open!
Wait...
Wait!
You guys stay warm.
- Well, you keep your eyes and ears open.
- Oh, yea, you bet.
Wait! Wait!
- Merry Christmas!
- You too, buddy.
Wait! Wait!
- 911...
- Please, help me...
all our lines are busy, please hold
someone will be with you shortly.
- Hello...
- Thank you.
911, all our lines are busy, please hold...
911, all our lines are busy...
Rocky? Rocky!
Why? Why would you do that?
He's just an animal.
Angela!
Why did you kill a defenseless animal?
After all I did for you.
To help you...
this is what I get?
You killed my dog!
Angela!
You serious you got to bother me!
Hello, hello, are you there? Hello...
this is the police, is somebody there?
Is somebody there? If this is an emergency
and you can hear me...
please say something, or tab the
phone, so I know you're there.
Hello, hello... This is the
police this is 911, are you okay?
Are you there? Hello...
You're trying to get me fired
aren't you?
I bet you realy like that.
But... but...
honey, what're we gonna do then?
We couldn't just live of off your salary...
Angela!
Shit, shit, shit!
Let's fucking do this.
You gonna fuck with me, let's fucking do this.
Come on!
Come on, you piece of shit, let's go!
Angela?
Let me help you out, OK?
"Help me! You gonna help me!"
Why don't you let me help you for a change!
You motherfucker!
What're you doing?
Angela, come back, come here, let me go
Come over here and cut me loose, right now.
Why are you doing this Angela, wait?
Angela...
Angela, I just... I just...
I just wanted to be friends.
I 'm... alone, I'm always... alone.
Why couldn't we spend more
time together?
Angela? Wait, wait... why?
Why?!
Why can't we be friends?
Why can't we just spend
Christmas together?
You hear me! You stupid fucking cunt!
Angela, I didn't mean... wait,
Merry Christmas Thomas.
Oh no, no, no no...