Yes. I redrafted the contracts
to include the new stipulations.
- Then where are they?
- I'm faxing the revisions now.
Did you make all the changes I asked for?
- Yes, I included the 4 % increase...
and the extra two million.
- No. If it's a 4 % increase,
then you have to add
at least three million dollars.
No. That's not what I was told.
- And who told you that?
Their lawyers.
- They're all idiots.
This is a total lack of communication.
- You know what? If's ok.
I had no way of knowing, sir.
- Ok, look. This is what I need you to do.
Sir, can I put you on hold for a second?
- Ok.
Thanks. Hi, Jody.
Mr. Harper wants to see you in his office.
- Great. Of course.
You still want me to fax those?
- It's ok. You don't have to.
I'm not even done yet. You should go home.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. It's late. I don't want your parents
to worry. Get out of here.
Ok. Merry Christmas, Angela.
- Merry Christmas, Jody.
Hi, Lorraine.
Yeah, of course I'm going to make it.
Just let me call you back. Ok?
In a few minutes. I promise. OK.
Still on the Morgan deal, hm?
- What can I do for you, Jim?
I...
I don't know how to...
Angela,
I feel terrible about what happened.
It's ok. It's fine.
Let's just not worry about it, ok?
No, no, no. It's not ok.
I acted like a real jerk.
I'd had too many drinks and...
you know
how these Christmas party's can be.
You know we had a baby last year.
And it's been a hard year.
- I'm sure that it has.
I simply want to tell you
that I'm just really, really sorry. Ok?
Apology accepted.
Ok. Thanks.
Merry Christmas, Angela.
- You too, Jim.
You calling me from work?
I thought you were going home first.
I brought everything with me. Don't worry.
- God, I am so late with this dinner.
Did you pick up the Santa Claus costume?
I hope you didn't forget it.
I didn't forget it. It's in the car.
I think Dad is more excited than the kids.
Believe me, I can't wait
to get out of here and see you guys.
Jimmy, Put that back.
Do you want Santa to come tonight or not?
- Hey, Mommy. I want Santa to come.
- Well, then help me set the table.
Ok. Please don't be late.
- I won't. I promise. I won't.
Ok, bye.
- Bye.
Ok.
Jesus!
- My God.
Sorry, Angela.
I was just locking up the floors.
I didn't know anybody would be working...
this late on Christmas Eve.
- Yeah, me neither.
Sorry. I'll come back later, alright?
- Actually, if you wouldn't mind waiting,
I'll lock up my office
and I'll take the elevator down with you.
Ok. Sure.
- Ok. Two seconds.
Do you work all night?
- Yeah.
But they're closing the building
for the next three days.
Besides, I get New Year's Eve off.
- Oh, that's good.
Yeah, I hope to get home in time
for the girls to open up the presents.
How are they?
- Great.
Come on, your parents can't stand me.
- You're wrong, Doug. They love you.
So, where are you going this evening?
- To my sister's house in Jersey.
Jersey? I thought of you more
as an Upper East Side girl.
Yeah, upper east side of Maine, actually.
I grew up on a farm, Karl.
Now I'm having trouble believing that.
- Don't let the fancy clothes fool you.
- I keep it real. Come on.
- If that's what you call it, ok.
Keeping it real.
- Good night, Karl.
Merry Christmas, Angela.
- You too. I'll see you soon.
Yeah.
Yes. No. I promise you.
I'm leaving right now. I know. I know.
I'm sorry, but I'm in the elevator.
25 minutes tops.
I can't hear you. What?
Lorraine, you're breaking up.
Hello?
You've got to be kidding me.
You've got to be kidding. Ok.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
Oh God. What am I going to do?
I'm going to get out of the car.
That's what I'm going to do.
Shit.
Hello?
Jesus.
- Rocky. Rocky. Rocky.
What are you doing? Heel. Stay.
Down. Down.
Sorry about that.
- That's ok.
Look, can you unlock the door
to the elevator room? My car won't start.
And I need to get upstairs and get a cab.
- Yeah, I can.
I just have to find my key cards. Sorry.
Where are those darn keys?
I was about to do my rounds, anyway. So...
Ok.
- What happened to your car?
I have no idea.
- You probably left the lights on.
No, I don't think so. I'm usually
pretty good about that kind of thing.
People do it all the time.
It's instinctive.
I mean, you drive down here and it's dark.
It happens. Ah. Here we go.
Great.
- You know, actually, I just thought.
I have a charger in the back, so if it is
your battery we could probably...
You could use that.
- Oh, thank you.
But I really should just take a cab.
I'm so late as it is. - I don't know.
It'll probably take longer to get a cab.
It's Christmas Eve, so, I don't know.
It's up to you. Whatever you want.
- How long will it take?
Just a few minutes. Give me one second.
It doesn't look...
like New Yorkers are actually going to be
able to celebrate a white Christmas.
Maybe next year. Now, with the beautiful
metropolitan opera in the background,
let's check out the temperatures
for the tri-state area...
Alright. Which way to your car?
- Over there.
Ok.
Working late, hm?
Yeah, I know how you feel.
Yeah, these are pretty reliable cars
for the most part, right?
They're supposed to be.
Right. Positive.
Negative.
Ok, alright. Try it. Turn her over.
- Ok.
Strange.
Ok. Hang on.
Can you turn your headlights on?
Weird. Try turning the keys again.
Damned.
- Ok. I guess turn the headlights off.
You know what? That's it.
I...
You've been a great help, but I give up.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I don't know what happened.
I thought I could do something about it.
- That's ok. You've been great.
Can you just let me in the elevator room?
- I was just trying to help.
I know, and I appreciate it. Thank you.
Hey, listen, I know you're upset
about your car not starting,
but it's the holidays, you know?
It's time to be thankful.
No. You know what? You're right.
I should be thankful.
I...
I prepared
a small Christmas meal for myself.
You could join me if you want.
I'm just kidding.
- Oh, yeah. Sorry. I'm exhausted.
But really, thanks for your help.
Oh, you're welcome.
Maybe some other time, yeah?
Yeah, sure.
Alright. Here you go.
You don't want me to call you a cab?
- No. I've got a number in my bag.
Alright, suit yourself. Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
Karl?
Hi. Can I get a car
at 2370 Park Avenue, please?
Are you sure? No, that's ok.
I'll wait. Thanks.
Hey, Lorraine.
You're not going to believe what happened.
No. Actually, my car wouldn't start.
Look, just start without me.
I'll be there within the hour
and I'll make it up to them.
Ok. I'll see you soon. Bye.
Hello?
Oh, oh, great. Thank you. Thank you.
Ok. Ok.
Oh, come on. What?
This is not happening. Is this a joke?
No, no. You've got to be kidding me.
Karl? Karl, where are you?
Is anybody here?
Come on, come on, come on.
What?
Just one second. Ok?
I'll be right back. One second.
Hello. Can you hear me? Look,
I've got a cab waiting for me out front.
Can you open the front gate, please?
Hello?
No. No. No, no, no, no. No.
No. Damned.
Why would you leave me here?
Wake up, damned. The cab just left.
Hey! I'm still in here. Wait!
Great.
It's ok. Just...
Hello?
OK. Stop being paranoid.
Just go down to the office.
Hello?
Ah. Oh, fuck!
Goddamned!
No!
Ho, ho, ho. Merry Christmas.
You've been a good little girl.
Oh, it's ok. It's ok. You're alright.
You're alright. You're alright. Ok?
Alright?
You're not looking so good. Are you ok?
Take it easy. It's ok.
What happened to me? What time is it?
You just fell. You'll be alright.
I don't feel good. I'm going to be sick.
- I'll get some water.
I'll get you some water.
- Watch out! Be careful!
You're going to hurt yourself.
Try and stay calm. Oh, oh.
Ok.
It's ok. It's ok. Here. Here.
Ok? Alright?
I'm going to help you up. Ok, now?
I'm going to help you up.
Here you go. Ready?
Alright. Here you go. It's ok.
Alright. Ok. Try to relax.
I'm going to clean this up. Ok.
Clean this up. Ok. Ok.
Alright. I'll be right back.
Hungry?
I got turkey,
mashed potatoes. I got cranberries
and I even got some cornbread.
Oh man. I am... I'm sorry about this.
I was just teasing.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Oh man.
I hope it's still warm.
If not I have the microwave, so...
Are you feeling any better?
What happened to my clothes?
Like I said, you fell,
and your clothes got dirty, so...
Maybe you'd like some wine.
It'll help you relax a little, you know?
- Look, I don't know what you're doing,
but you'd better just fucking untie me.
This is a California wine.
It's a Sonoma County.
That's where I'm from.
It's beautiful up there.
Where are you from?
What do you want?
- I want to know where you're from.
I'm from Readfield.
Where's that?
- Why don't you tell me what you want?
I just want to know where Readfield is.
And I want you to relax.
Cheers.
Ok. I'll make a toast.
Here's to good friends and hometowns
and Readfield, wherever that is.
Listen.
Tom.
- Tom.
I have some place to be.
You know, I have obligations.
Yeah. I know.
Way too many. You don't make time
for yourself, you know?
You don't need
to be at everyone's beck and call.
So, then maybe we should get a drink
in the new year.
Now, look.
I've already prepared everything.
It's all here.
- I know, and it looks really good.
Yeah? Great. Well let's eat.
I'm starving.
- Tom, this is really sweet of you.
And I mean that, but my whole family's
expecting me. I have plans.
I guess some plans are made to be broken.
Do you want to say grace, or should 1?
Hell, skip it.
I've never been religious, anyway.
Bon appetit.
What do you like to do?
You know, I have to work and stuff.
It's hobbies.
That's a mundane question, but I guess
people ask that just to get...
to know each other, right? I read.
Right now I'm reading Hemmingway,
"The Sun Also Rises".
And...
You really should eat.
It's going to get cold.
Anyway, so, in the book,
this guy, he loves this girl so much...
that he's willing to forgive
everything that she does.
Even her infidelities.
That's a pretty intense story, but...
that's what love is supposed to be, right?
My boyfriend's going to get worried and
he's going to come looking for me, Tom.
If I don't show up he's going to come
looking for me. He knows where I work.
How long have you guys
been dating or hanging out?
Two years.
- Two years?
Do you guys live together?
- It's none of your fucking business.
That's not very nice dinner talk.
Yeah, we live together. Ok?
Two years.
That's more than a boyfriend, that's a...
It sounds like wedding bells.
Do you guys have any plans?
Yes.
- What does your fiancé do?
He's a journalist.
- Journalist.
See, I knew he had to be smart.
What kind of journalist? - Sports.
Sports? What paper?
- "The Post".
"The Post"? I read "The Post".
What's his name?
Mark Clayton.
- Clayton? Clayton.
I don't remember that name.
You know, I have one over here.
- It's online. It's "The Post online".
You know, it is amazing that you're able
to keep a relationship...
with the amount of hours that you work.
He must get really lonely
when you have to work late, right?
Do you love him?
Does he love you?
I'm only asking, because I'm worried
about how quickly he's going to get here.
I'm sure he's already on his way.
Right.
He's probably on the Harlem River Drive
as we speak.
What kind of a car does he drive?
- I don't know.
You don't know? You don't know
what kind of car your fiancé drives?
Toyota, I think. I don't know.
- Toyota, what a fast car.
He could be here a lot sooner
than I was thinking.
He could be coming down this ramp
right now as we speak.
You know, you haven't been
very talkative since we met,
but now...
you're telling me all
about your boyfriend.
Oh, sorry, your fiancé.
So either we've become best friends
over dinner or you're lying to me.
I'm going to guess.
You're lying to me.
You don't really have a boyfriend, do you?
But you want one.
You want somebody who cares about you,
worries about you.
- Please, don't.
You've got a great family.
You know, you've got Lorraine.
And Jimmy and Rose. They love you.
They're probably
getting worried about you.
Maybe we should give them a call.
Yeah?
Tell them you're ok.
What do you think?
But what shall we say?
I know, I know.
We should say you made other plans.
No. You probably already said that one.
You know what?
You should think of something.
You're a good liar.
Go ahead.
Go!
No.
Hello.
Hello?
Hey, Rosie.
Can you get your mommy on the phone?
Who's calling, please?
- It's Auntie Angie.
Mommy, it's Aunt Angie.
Give me a second. It's Angela.
Hey. Where are you?
- Angela?
I'm not feeling well.
- What do you mean?
We're all waiting for you.
She says she's not feeling well.
- That's what she said the last time.
- Can I talk to my sister?
So, where are you, Angie?
Angela?
I'm home. I went home.
- What's wrong? Where is she?
- I really don't understand.
Last time I talked to you,
you said you were on your way.
- What about the costume?
- You know what? Let's just eat.
Angela, you know it would
be nice if you tried to put your family...
- ahead of your work sometimes.
- That's enough. Give me the phone.
Angie, what's wrong?
Hello? I can't hear her.
Hello, Sweetie. Can you hear me?
- Hi, Mom. I'm here.
Honey, what happened? Where are you?
I don't know.
I think it's the flu.
- You really sound terrible.
Are you sure you're ok? Honey?
Yeah.
I just need some rest.
Ok, well, rest up and hopefully
you'll feel better for lunch tomorrow.
And Sweetie,
don't worry about the costume. Ok?
Merry Christmas, Angel. I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
Hey.
That's the best Christmas present
anyone's ever given me.
Thank you.
Now, I have a present for you.
Go ahead.
Open it.
Aren't you even curious?
Come on. Open it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I bet you're curious now, yeah?
Ok, enough torture.
Watch. It's all cued up.
Why are you showing this to me?
- Wait.
You fucked up now, asshole.
Sorry you had to see that.
You want to go for a stroll?
These guys always do whatever they want.
Here we go.
Rocky, sit! Stay down.
Stay still. Stay still. Give me your arm.
Give it.
Why? Why? Why did you do that?
Rocky, shut the fuck up!
Let me help you up. Don't be silly.
I'm not going to hurt you, alright?
You're hurting my arm.
- That's because you won't relax your arm.
Come on now.
- Just let me go. I won't tell anyone.
Oh, yeah. I believe you.
I will show you something.
Alright.
Let's put that all behind us, yeah?
Here we go.
I think I drank too much wine.
I shouldn't be driving.
I'm just kidding.
You know, I've seen you drive
out of here so many times.
It's strange actually
being in the car with you.
- It's great, actually.
- You said we were taking a drive.
We are.
Then why are we going down, Tom?
- It's freezing out there.
Besides, this is going to be much better.
Why are we down here, Thomas?
Tom.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Tom. What is this?
This is my present to you.
Take this and show him.
Show him what?
Show him you're not a slut.
Take this and teach him he can't
be touching every woman that he wants.
Are you talking about
what happened in the elevator?
Oh, Tom. No. No, no, no.
You don't understand. That was a mistake.
That was a stupid mistake.
- What? What? He tried to rape you.
No. No, he got a little out of hand at
a party, Tom. He hardly tried to rape me.
Look, he was drunk.
He apologized.
Oh, he apologized. Oh, you think you're
the first woman he tried to do this to?
I've seen him trying to touch every woman
in the building. He's a pervert.
He's a degenerate.
- No. No. He's not.
He's a good man, Tom.
He's a good man. Just look at him.
He has a family. He has a wife. Tom.
Please, Tom, just...
- Tom. Stop calling out my name, alright?
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to humanize yourself...
like you're some poor victim. I told you.
I'm not going to hurt you. Alright?
Stop calling out my name, alright?
Enough is enough. Tom. Tom. Tom.
Every time just the same.
Ok.
Oh.
I know you're a person, ok?
I know you're a person. Ok?
I'm a person, too.
I know you have feelings.
I have feelings, too.
I care about your feelings.
He's the one you should be scared of.
He's the one who has no feelings.
So, if you want to help him,
take this and teach him a lesson.
I told you.
He apologized.
What? He can just apologize and then
he can do it again?
And he's just going to apologize again.
You've got to stop letting these assholes
have their way with you.
Tom, just please believe me.
It was just a misunderstanding, Tom.
Tom. Tom. Stop calling out my name.
I told you.
Ok.
- Didn't 1?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry, but you're scaring me.
- Jesus. When are you going to understand?
I'm...
I'm here to help you.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Ok.
I'll do it.
You untie me and I'll do it.
No, no, no.
Whoa. You're a good person.
- You're a good person, too.
I should have never asked you to do this.
I'm sorry. - No. No, it's ok.
It's ok, because I want to, I just...
You just have to untie me and I'll do it.
For you.
It's my job. It's my job to protect you.
- No, Tom. Listen to me. It's not.
It's not. Please don't do anything.
- Don't try to run away, ok?
Can I trust you?
-Yes.
You can trust me.
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
So.
You like to touch girls, do you?
No? No? Look at her.
I said look at here.
Does she look happy to you?
Hm?
Yeah.
Yeah. You messed with the wrong girl, hm?
What makes you think you deserve her?
Hm? What gives you the right?
You're something else, you know that?
You pretentious, Ivy League,
piece of shit.
You don't own the world
and everyone in it.
I mean, what is a guy like you thinking
when he puts his hands all over a girl...
who obviously is not interested,
who is obviously not a slut?
Because that's what you think they are,
right? Yeah?
I can't hear you. What did you say? What?
Hm?
Can you speak up, because you can't talk
your way out of this one, can you?
Why am I even wasting my time with you?
- No!
What the hell? He deserves it.
- Don't do anything, Thomas. Please.
No!
Thomas, stop it.
No.
Way to ruin Christmas, asshole.
Well, he won't be bothering you again.
- Where are we going?
We can't just leave him there?
- Why? Why are you defending him?
I'm not.
- Why? Did you like this?
Do like to get touched? Hm? You like it
when he touches you in the parking garage?
You want to get laid here?
- No. You know that's not true.
So what? What is it?
Is it a career thing?
Did you fuck him to get a promotion? Hm?
You can't leave him here.
You're right. You're right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We shouldn't leave him here.
Thomas, stop!
What are you doing?
- We're going to take him for a drive.
What are you doing? No, Thomas.
Stop the car. Stop.
Please, stop. Please.
Stop it. Stop it.
What are you doing, Tom? No! No!
No. No. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Don't do this. Please. Don't. Don't. No.
Thomas, please don't do this.
No.
Thomas. No.
Please, don't do this. No.
No. No!
Hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Where are you going?
Angela.
Angela. Come back.
You're fucking a great liar.
Liar.
Hey! Down here!
Hey, can you hear me? Help!
Down hear. Can't you hear me?
Oh shit.
Good boy.
I just take my bag.
Stay right there.
Help me!
Help me, please. Help!
Help me, please. Help! Someone's trying
to kill me. Please help me.
Help me.
Somebody's trying to Kill.
Please somebody help.
- Where are you?
Come on. Please.
Oh no.
Angela.
Please. Please. If anyone can hear me,
I'm trapped in the underground parking...
of the Arcadia building.
It's 2370 Park Avenue.
- Someone's trying to kill me.
- Angela.
Angela, come out.
Shit.
Angela. Angela.
No.
Can we talk about this?
Looks like somebody's playing game,
hm, Rocky?
Angela?
Come on. Close. Come on.
Lobby.
Come on. Lobby. Lobby. Come on.
Why is it fucking locked?
Angela.
Hello.
Hello. Can anyone hear me?
Please, hello? Please answer.
Please. Please.
Yes, 5 Buroughs Security. Hello.
Hello?
- Yes,. I'm here. Can you hear me?
I can hear you fine. How can I help you?
- I'm being kidnapped.
I work at Brighter, Smith and Steinberg.
It's 2370 Park Avenue.
And I'm hiding in the elevator.
Please can you call 911? - Calm down.
Is there someone with you right now?
- No, he's outside.
He's in the parking lot.
He already killed someone else.
Did you see him do it?
- Yes, his name is Thomas.
He's the parking attendant in my building.
If you'll please hurry. I'm in danger.
Ma'am, you have got to relax.
- How do you fucking expect me to relax?
This man is trying to kill me. Can you
just please try to understand...
and call the cops? Please, just call 911.
The police? No.
I'm sure he's just trying to help you.
Right?
Angela.
Angela, are you still there?
Listen, you fuck face, I called the cops
and I'm going to stay down here...
as long as it takes until they get here
so I suggest you get the fuck out.
I just want to talk to you, Angela.
That's why I pretended to be someone else.
Ok? So don't be upset.
Will you come out? I was just kidding.
Just go to hell.
- Angela, don't you understand?
I did it for you.
That guy showed you no respect.
Why won't you talk to me, Angela?
Just give me a chance.
You know, if you just give us a chance,
it can work out.
You'll grow to like me.
You know, that's usually what happens
when 2 people are forced to be together...
in a stressful situation.
They have to depend on one another,
and eventually they support each other,
and like each other.
Sometimes they even fall in love.
Angela.
Angela, please, please don't do this.
Hm? Why won't you talk to me?
You know, I wish you had just
a little bit more respect for yourself.
I want to go out. Do you hear me?
What are you doing? You fuck!
No.
Oh, what did he do? Karl.
Karl. Karl.
Karl.
Oh my God.
Angela.
You must be freezing out here.
Angela!
What a mess.
Angela.
I think Karl is hurt.
Should we call him an ambulance?
Hm?
Yeah, that way he can go back
to his kids and his family.
And you can go to your sister's
and I can stay here,
in this parking lot, all by myself,
because that's obviously
what everybody wants!
Angela.
I just can't keep chasing
you around all night, Angela.
Besides,
the whole place is locked.
Angela.
Where are you going to go if you get away?
It's freezing out there.
Angela.
Angela?
Way to ruin Christmas, Karl.
I'll have a blue Christmas
without you.
I'll be so blue
just thinking about you.
Decorations of red
on a green christmas tree.
Won't be the same dear,
if you're not here with me.
And when those blue
snowflakes start falling,
That's when those blue
memories start calling.
You'll be doin' alright,
with your Christmas of white.
But I'll have a blue,
blue blue blue Christmas.
You'll be doin' alright,
with your Christmas of white,
But I'll have a blue,
blue blue blue Christmas.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I love you.
I'm so fond you.
...to find a way out.
He will pay for it.
So, what do you think?
That's so easy.
That's very good.
Oh, I think...
So, you want make-up?
Hm? Ok.
You have the most beautiful lips
I have ever seen in my life.
You're beautiful.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
You have a wonderful body.
It was meant to be, baby.
Me and you.
Angela, your skin is...
It's so soft.
Honey.
I love you. I love you.
Angela, you know that, right?
Hello.
Shit, shit. I'm here. Hello.
Can you hear me?
It's ok.
Hello, officer. Can I help you?
Can you open up the gate, please?
Yes, sir. I'll be right up.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I have to do this.
Hey.
Sorry about that.
I was on the bottom floor doing my rounds.
What's going on tonight?
- We got a call of a disturbance...
at this address.
Do you know anything about that?
No. It's been real quiet all night.
- See anything, hear anything suspicious?
No. Like I said, I was just doing
my rounds and it's been real quiet.
I haven't seen anybody down here.
- Any cars in there?
Well, it is a parking garage.
Well, there's a few cars scattered
over here on this level,
but on the second level,
there's a rental thing and then a...
I mean, like I said, there's been no one
around tonight, except me and Rocky.
Two of you working here tonight?
- Yeah, kind of. He's my dog.
He's down in the office right now.
- We're going to take a look around, man.
Get in the back. We'll give you a ride.
- Yeah, that's a great idea.
Yeah. I've just got to close this gate.
You know, there's a lot
of homeless people around here.
Ok, thanks for the ride.
Oh, if you guys want to check out
the other floors,
just keep going around this way,
but be careful on P3.
There's broken water main. Ok?
- We'll come back around.
Ok.
What the hell's going on here, man?
Help me! Help! Help!
Help me! Help!
Help me!
You sure
you haven't seen anything weird tonight?
No. Everybody left really early tonight.
Are you having a party in there?
- It's just me and Rocky. Not a party.
Got anybody coming over to visit?
You know, a little action?
Me? No, no, no. The company would fire me,
if I had anyone down here in the night.
Especially at this hour.
Yeah, well, we don't want
to break any rules, right, partner?
Not on my watch.
- Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Help me!
Help me.
Alright. Well, I've got to open the gate,
so I'll just take the stairs.
Let's do it.
Open.
Wait! Wait!
You guys stay warm.
- You keep your eyes and ears open. Hm?
Oh yeah. You bet.
Merry Christmas.
- Yeah, you too, buddy.
Wait. Wait!
- 911.
- Yes. Yes, please. I need your help.
All of our lines are busy at the moment.
Someone will be with you shortly.
Hello?
- Thank you.
911. All our lines are busy at the moment.
Please hold...
Rock? Rocky!
Why?
Why would you do that?
Hm? He's just an animal.
Angela?
Why would you kill a defenseless animal?
After all I did for you,
to help you,
this is what I get?
You kill my dog?
- Answer. Answer. Please answer.
- Angela!
Please.
- You're really starting to piss me off!
Angela.
Hello. Hello. Are you there?
Hello. This is the police.
Is somebody there?
Is this an emergency? If you can hear me,
please say something.
Tap the phone.
Let me know if you're there.
Hello. Hello. This is the police.
This is 911.
Are you ok? Are you there? Hello?
You're trying to get me fired, aren't you?
I bet you'd really liked that.
But...
But honey,
what are we going to do then?
We couldn't just live off of your salary.
Angela.
Shit. Shit.
Shit.
Let's fucking do this. You want to fuck
with me, let's fucking do this.
Come on!
Come on, you chicken shit. Come on!
Angela.
Let me help you out. OK?
You're going to help me? Why don't you
let me help you for a change?
Mother fucker.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Angela. Come back. You hear? Let me go.
Come over here and give me that right now.
Why are you doing this, Angela? Why?
Angela.
Angela, I just wanted to be friends.
I'm alone.
I'm always alone.
Why can't we just
spend more time together?
Angela.
Wait. Wait. Why?
Why?
Why can't we be friends?
Hm? Why can't we just spend
Christmas together?
Do you hear me? You stupid fucking cunt!
Angela, wait. Wait, wait, I didn't...
- Merry Christmas, Thomas.
No. No. No. No. No.
You alright, lady?