Clear that shit.
Clear it.
All right. Take her.
Shit!
Outside. Till it's done.
Till it's done, brother.
Easy. Easy!
Linda!
I would've taken your bullet.
I deserve the bullet.
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth!
Linda! Linda, look at me.
Linda, you've got a kid.
If you die, he'll come to us to raise.
You hear me?
I used a Derringer.
-All right.
It's still in there, right above the bone.
Mr Shelby, your guests...
Get him out. Arthur. Family only!
Get him out!
-Mr Shelby, on your behalf--
-Get out!
Lizzie, go to the kitchen,
get some iodine.
Now! Go!
All right.
-Linda. You'll have to bite on this.
Linda. Arthur.
Bite! Come here.
All right.
Now it's really going to hurt.
-One, two, three.
All right. All right.
-All right. Almost there.
- Hold her.
Is she going
to be all right, Tom?
Is she going to be all right, Tom?
- Yeah.
Oh, Jesus.
Arthur, come here. Come here.
If you love her, go to the library,
get some opium.
Go on. She'll be fine. Go, soldier.
Right.
Actually, you can use mine.
Brought a bit to celebrate
the wedding proposal.
Oh!
He proposed, eh?
One knee.
Congratulations, Pol.
Linda. Linda.
You'll have to drink this.
-No, I don't want anything you've touched.
-Twenty-five seconds.
Twenty-five seconds
and the pain will be gone.
Even the pain in your head.
All right, here you go. Drink.
Cushion, Pol.
All right.
- Never again.
Jesus Christ!
Arthur.
She's going to be fine.
I gave her something to get her to sleep.
You should have...
You should have let her do it, Pol.
You should have let her do it.
Arthur, come on.
-You should have let her do it.
-Look at me, brother!
Look at me.
You got things to do.
-You've got a kid.
-Yeah.
We need you. All right?
-You understand?
-Yeah.
Aberama wants you as best man.
You hear that?
I save his life, he hugs him.
Oh.
I'll do it.
I'll take it.
Right, fine. Let him be. Let him be.
Oh.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I would like to extend our gratitude
to the musicians and the dance company
for your wonderful performance.
This has been a wonderful evening.
Yes, it has.
And not only for the music
and the dancing.
It has also been about us,
the people gathered here.
English people
in the very heart of England.
There are no people
I would rather be among,
no place I would rather be
and no time I would rather be alive.
Well said!
Because ever since
the terrible events of October,
when the money markets betrayed us all...
Disgrace!
...I have known that change is coming.
The human species has never faced
such immense possibilities, such choices.
In the lives of great nations,
there are moments of destiny
which have swept aside
small men of convention
and discovered men of the moment.
-And our host...
- Yes.
...is such a man.
For him...
For him, the little calculations
of little men mean nothing.
He is a man well suited to the mighty mood
that England is now in.
Hear, hear.
The only reason I say this now,
at this moment on this stage,
is because I have some news.
Good news, I think.
I'm sure our host will forgive me
if I use this platform,
this gathering of friends and like minds,
to give you, his trusted allies,
an early announcement
of a long-overdue event.
I want to tell you good folk first
that with the dawn of a new decade,
I will be setting a new course,
setting up a new political movement
-here in the very heart of England.
And Mr Shelby will be with me,
shoulder to shoulder.
It will offer a new conception of politics
in which the great character
of the British, our true character,
will be reborn.
Many of you lost fortunes
in the recent stock market crash.
The men of money,
the capitalists in New York,
the Jews,
the money-power, they...
They run an international system
in which the infinite mobility of money,
its capacity to create
financial chaos and panic,
can bring down any government that dares,
for one moment, to oppose it.
For generations, the efforts
of hardworking men like you
have equipped our competitors against us.
The cotton mills of India,
the cotton mills of Asia,
created with British money
but used for the destruction
of Lancashire and Yorkshire.
-Disgraceful.
- The usurers of New York,
the sweated labour of the Orient,
combining to destroy
the iron and steel factories
of Warwickshire and Staffordshire.
These are policies that could not
be pursued by British statesmen
unless they were mad
or the servants of Jewish finance.
Right words. I second that.
They are the ones who took your money,
but it is I and those who know this truth
who will light a flame
the atheists cannot extinguish.
The ranks of our heroes of the Great War
have been betrayed again and again
by politicians!
But hear this, those of you
who fought the Jew war for nothing,
you brave men,
you will join hands with the angry youth
of Birmingham and Manchester
and London and Liverpool
and declare that England lives tonight
and marches on!
Yes, yes!
Well said!
I say all this to you now
because I believe it is
in places like this with people like you
that we will have to pass on
our message directly.
Our message can be summarised
with these words:
"Britain first."
As it should be!
And because this is our message,
I doubt it'll be reported fairly
in the press.
I'm afraid the newspapers of this country
are owned by the same vested interests
who took your money.
They sell to the people false news
to raise the interests of the faction
and the section above
the interests of the nation.
Good man.
So hear my words and pass them on
to those with ears to hear,
and be reminded
that when the new decade begins,
there will be the birth of a new
political party which will speak for you!
Yes! At last.
This party, this new movement,
this revolution
will be called
the British Union of Fascists.
Well said!
What the fuck are you doing
dealing with a man like that, Tommy?
Yeah... You're going to have to trust me.
Again.
I'm going to fuck the Swan.
Somebody go and tell her
to come to my room.
How do you know she'll come?
Because they always do.
Now, forgive me. I'm going to borrow
your husband for a little while.
This way.
Things like tonight,
that shooting, a family dispute in public,
things like that will have to stop.
It's very lower-class.
It's all been cleared up, Mr Mosley.
So, did you learn anything
from my speech tonight?
Yes.
Yes, I learned many things.
Religion was a beast,
but it's dead.
You have to ride the new thing
when it comes.
Like a horse.
You grab it.
I looked into the audience
and I saw medals
and Savile Row suits and bitterness.
They are my people.
Your people will be different.
Oh, do see the funny side, Shelby.
I do.
I do see the funny side.
Do you enjoy strategies?
Yes, I do.
Things will begin to happen now.
So...
there are some things we need to discuss.
I have been looking into your companies.
The Shelby portfolio.
Your company lawyer is a Jew.
He will have to go.
-Of course.
-Also,
our friend, Jimmy McCavern,
has asked for control of the racecourses
north of Wincanton.
I decided it is a trifling thing,
considering our new enterprise,
so I said yes.
In return for what?
No return.
None.
When our campaign begins,
the country will be divided
into distinct areas.
McCavern and his men
will be our soldiers in the north,
controlling rallies
and breaking up demonstrations.
In the midlands, it'll be you.
The south, well...
I have yet to decide.
Please understand what I'm offering you
as we go forward, Mr Shelby.
When we succeed,
even the king will not be above us.
Power.
Like plugging into the mains.
A lighthouse beam.
Your millions of dollars
safe in Switzerland,
and access to every dirty-minded Swan
in England.
Hmm.
Oh, and also, Shelby,
drink less.
♪ I am the key to the lock in your house ♪
♪ That keeps your toys in the basement ♪
♪ And if you get too far inside ♪
Put it on.
Put the costume back on.
♪ It's always best with the covers up ♪
♪ I am the pick in the ice ♪
♪ Do not cry out or hit the alarm ♪
♪ You know we're friends till we die ♪
♪ And either way you turn... ♪
The ballerina and I were wondering
whether perhaps
you might want to join us.
If I told Tommy,
you wouldn't see the morning.
I doubt that very much.
You see, he has been seduced,
just as you were.
Tommy.
Tom!
What...
Lizzie?
What?
Tommy, I swear to God, you're bad.
That man is fucking evil.
Lizzie...
I'm only doing this
to bring the bastard down.
Yeah, but why?
Tommy, why?
I'm supplying the British government
with information on his organisation,
and in return they are giving me
favourable terms on defence contracts.
No.
You're doing it because you think
somebody should stop him.
-I saw your face when he was speaking.
You're doing it because you think
it's the right thing to do.
All this time, you just did things
that feel nice because you can afford it.
Lizzie, please, please, please, stop.
Don't scare me
by saying you see things in my face.
I still want things that feel nice.
-Linda.
-Arthur.
Linda.
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's leave.
Let's get in the car.
We'll go and pick up Billy.
We'll drive to the docks.
Any dock you want.
We'll get on a boat.
We'll sail away.
You and me.
Any destination.
Be careful, it's...
It's broken everywhere.
We leave tonight. Hmm?
We leave this place.
We never come back, Linda.
We never come back.
I mean that.
We go before it gets light.
Say yes.
-I've got a better idea.
-Yeah?
You stay here...
living inside your head,
inside your knife, inside your war.
I'm glad I didn't shoot you.
It would've been a kindness.
Now, get out.
-Oh, please.
An evening with
a bunch of fucking Gypsies.
I will shoot!
Peter! Peter! Kick it here!
Kick it here, mister!
This is a cheque guarantee.
Signed by Mosley
on behalf of a man called Jimmy McCavern.
A cheque for what?
Well, I said it was
for the sale of a gin distillery.
But it doesn't matter.
It is direct evidence
of a link between Mosley
and the head
of an organised criminal network.
A relationship he will try to deny
after the bonfire of all conventions.
It also contains the names of MPs
who have signed up to the movement.
And those MPs who are sympathetic
but will not show their hand until
the organisation is announced officially.
On the second of January.
In Grosvenor House.
You might want to write some of this down.
I am experiencing resistance
from my superior officers, too.
This isn't intelligence, Younger.
This is evidence.
Give it to the Branch.
Special Branch?
Half of whom spend their lives defending
the Union against Fenians,
and the other half who spend their lives
defending men like Mosley
against socialists.
I heard about his speech
at your house the other night.
It was favourably reported as
the passionate and spontaneous outpouring
of a man moved by
the emotions of a ballet.
-Reported where?
-Daily Mail, Morning Post, Daily Mirror.
It's upper, middle, and working class,
all united in admiration.
Also, I'm being asked the source
of my information on Mosley.
-Which you don't divulge.
-No.
As a result, my six-monthly review
was unfavourable.
They're talking about moving me to
a black and coloured desk in Johannesburg.
I also suspect there are specific threats
to me personally
from an organisation called "Section D".
I believe you've had a dispute
with them in the past.
Sit down, Younger.
We are now Section D.
I fucking beat them.
You're a soldier, I'm a soldier.
There are elements within the state
who are prepared to kill.
We need to meet them unafraid.
Spoken like a true believer.
My superiors also ask why the information
on Jessie Eden and the communists
has apparently dried up.
Why has it dried up, Mr Shelby?
Your sister has an interesting theory.
She thinks perhaps at last Tommy Shelby
has actually started
to believe in something.
Younger.
Please don't listen
to my sister's opinions of me.
They are always...
hopeful.
Therefore, they are always wrong.
Can you hear me? Look at me.
You're going to be all right.
I'll be back.
You'll be okay.
Look at me. It's okay. It's all right.
Fuck.
Call an ambulance! Call Moss!
Find out where I can reach him.
Come on, love. Up you get.
Good girl. Come on.
Take her. Take her.
Come on. Up you get.
Up you get. Good boy.
Come on. In you go.
Inside. Stay inside.
Tommy?
Let's sit down, Ada.
What's happened?
Here.
Sit down, eh?
Ben Younger is dead.
Someone put a bomb in his car.
I don't know how you felt about him
or how bad this is going to hurt,
but whatever happens, just remember
you have a baby inside of you.
God.
Anyone you touch.
Which means anyone I touch.
Which means anyone any of us touch.
He never knew I was pregnant.
I hadn't told him.
God, I didn't love him.
But I liked him.
He was decent and good.
And I wasn't going to marry him.
The baby was a mistake, but that's okay...
because I didn't
ask anything of him.
God, he didn't deserve us.
Well, I've spoken to his family.
They're going to take care of the funeral.
It will go down as an IRA assassination
of a British military officer.
And what was it really?
It was...
a consequence of good intentions.
My good intentions.
I pushed him to report on the fascists.
I thought it was the right thing to do.
And as a result, Section D or the Branch
or Intelligence had him killed.
There was a kid,
died in the explosion.
He was ten years old.
It's funny...
isn't it? How it works?
No, Tommy.
Don't give yourself this excuse.
He was ten years old.
If I would have stuck to what I do,
he'd still be kicking
a ball in the street.
It's funny, isn't it?
Push the button,
unlock the door, and come home to me.
Chinese lanterns! Brass on deck!
God fucking help us.
Chang will be waiting
at the dock with the cargo.
We weigh it, we load it, we fuck off.
Where the fuck is Chang?
Isiah, take point.
Look lively.
Right. There's your lanterns.
Where the fuck are the Chinese?
All right.
Arthur, it's Chang.
Get over. Get over! Get over!
I knew we shouldn't trust these fuckers
and their fucking lanterns.
If it's police, hold fire.
Chang, where's the stuff? Where is it?
They didn't look like police.
Smelled of gin.
They said they were taking the opium
on behalf of the king.
Then they saw your boat coming.
So, were they Italian?
-Were they Italian?
-Irish.
-Irish, I think.
-Oh, fuck.
Fuck!
Curly, my gun. Give me the gun.
Give it up! That's it.
Listen. Listen to me!
They're Titanic boys out there, all right?
They're out of Poplar.
In the war, they were very capable.
Very capable soldiers.
So was I.
I was a fucking capable soldier, too.
Hey!
Hey, you fucking bastards!
Arthur! Arthur! Stop firing!
Arthur, they're gone.
To any of you still alive,
you do not fuck
with the Peaky fucking Blinders.
Oh.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Hmm.
Chang.
Purest ever in Europe.
Arthur, there's a dead man
in a copper's uniform.
Should I throw him in the cut?
No.
No, he'll float, won't he?
Even Irishmen fucking float.
No. Go and find a...
Go and find a kiln or something.
But there are men working them.
Why do you carry a gun, Isiah, eh?
Or razor blades in your cap?
Because you're a Peaky fucking Blinder,
that's why.
You take that body
and you burn it to the bone.
And if anybody speaks to you on that,
you offer them the chance
to burn in that furnace with him.
All right?
Yes, Arthur.
Yeah.
Do we know the people
who tried to trick us?
The uncles will be mad.
Fuck your uncles. And your aunts,
your cousins, all of them. Right?
Curly, load this up onto the boat.
Let's get back to Birmingham, eh?
Get back to fucking civilisation.
And find out who's been talking. Yeah.
Now, look. The Titanic heard
about this, right?
That means every gang from Poplar
to Birmingham will be here.
Well, let them come.
Let them come, Aberama!
Yeah.
Oh, let them fucking come.
♪ Walk in silence ♪
♪ Don't walk away ♪
♪ In silence ♪
♪ See the danger ♪
♪ Always danger ♪
♪ Endless talking ♪
♪ Life rebuilding ♪
♪ Don't walk away ♪
♪ People like you find it easy ♪
♪ Naked to see ♪
♪ Walking on air ♪
♪ Don't walk away ♪
♪ In silence ♪
Hat and coat off.
Stand up against the wall.
For your own safety,
I need to search you for items
that could potentially be used
as weapons against you.
Oh, that's nice.
He was my friend.
Yeah, well he's nobody's friend anymore.
He's a fucking animal.
Laces out of your shoes.
Table.
Barney! Visitor.
This one's real.
You can wait here.
No. I can't.
It's your funeral.
I'll have to lock you in.
Yeah.
Hello, Barney.
Arthur says to say "hello".
Sergeant Major?
You're alive?
Arthur's alive, John's dead,
Danny's dead, Freddie's dead,
Jeremiah preaches the gospel barefoot.
Yeah.
And I'm alive.
Thems who're gone are the lucky ones.
Thanks for the letters
you send, Sergeant Major.
Yeah, Arthur mostly writes them. I just...
just sign them.
How the fuck do you write back?
With your fucking teeth?
No, they stick a pen up me arse.
Someone in here said your name.
They said out there
you are a politician now.
Sometimes, yeah.
Didn't know if it was real, comrade.
I see rats coming out of bodies
like at the black wood.
The shit they give me in here...
Hey, Barney. Look at me.
Barney, this here is opium and cyanide.
Bring on a heart attack.
They won't even check the cause.
You won't feel a fucking thing.
So, here.
You're in here forever, brother.
Don't have the use of your fucking hands.
You're still in the tunnels.
I can give this to you now.
You want it?
No.
Why not?
I know.
You still remember that French waitress.
You still going on about that, Tom?
Yeah.
Did you fuck her before me?
Because whoever did
gave me the fucking clap,
and I'm guessing it was you.
-Yes, I fucked her before you did.
-Yeah.
She was beautiful.
She was. She was.
And I reckon I was second best
after Barney.
Why did you bring the capsule, Tom?
You're in here, Barney.
You have no hands.
There is no daylight.
And you don't want to die.
No, I don't.
Because one day things might change.
Yeah.
Things might change.
Maybe they already have.
Come here, Barney.
Come here.
What if I could break you out of here?
Why would you break me out?
See, the trouble with the people in here
is the fucking meds they keep you on.
Ten years since we're back.
Barney, ten fucking years.
Maybe the storm has passed.
Passed for you then, has it, Tom?
What would the world do with me
if I was out?
I have a job for you.
-Fuck.
-Barney.
Barney, you were the best fucking sniper
in our company. Never missed.
I can use that man.
Get you the latest BSA,
fucking telescopic sights.
Who am I shooting?
The fuck do you care, Barney?
Get that fucking thing off.
Get you free.
- You all right in there?
Grand in here.
What do you say, Barney?
I'll come for you
after midnight on Wednesday.
I don't keep track of days, Tom.
Don't have to.
You'll know it will be Wednesday
because there'll be a big fucking bang.
All right.
Big fucking bang.
♪ Generals gathered in their masses ♪
♪ Just like witches at black masses ♪
♪ Evil minds that plot destruction ♪
♪ Sorcerers of death's construction ♪
♪ No more war pigs have the power ♪
♪ Hand of God has struck the hour ♪
♪ Time will tell on their power minds ♪
It's fucking Wednesday!
Big bang on Wednesday!
They called from the Black Boy in Knowle.
They'll be here any minute.
I hear you agreed to give up the north.
I hear there needs to be some certainty
in the south.
Some of my people were attacked
by members of the Titanic.
They've heard about the cargo.
Mr Mosley is open to suggestion
regarding who he can rely on
to offer him support in London.
Well, I would suggest the most competent
organiser of men in the south
is Alfie Solomons.
He's dead.
And he's Jewish.
And I'd say as far as our boss
is concerned,
him being dead would be less
of an obstacle than him being Jewish.
I think he'll give London to the Italians.
He likes Italians.
That'll mean more concessions
on your part,
but you're going to have to accept it,
tinker boy.
I like Wincanton.
It's a grand old racecourse.
That brother of yours,
the one who lent me a hand grenade...
he'd be the first
of you tinkers I'd go for
if our truce should end
and the whistle blew.
Good.
He's in the mood for a quarrel.
We had a brush with the Titanic, Tom.
Yeah, I heard.
Yeah.
Fun night.
Got noisy, though.
And to think they all said I was mad
to take me dad with me, eh?
Your dad? Who's your dad?
This is my fucking dad.
Right here.
Where's Aberama?
He got off at Solihull.
Said if he sees Billy Boy here,
he'll cut his fucking throat.
Tell the tinker he's welcome
to come and try at any time.
Hmm.
Is it all aboard?
Yeah.
It's all there.
We weighed it at the wharf.
We used Cockney scales.
I wouldn't trust them,
they're probably crooked.
But, er...
I reckon seven tons.
Curly!
Put ten sacks of flour
onto Mr McCavern's boat.
Tom...
I don't think it's really flour.
I know, Curly. Just do as I say.
Yeah. Yeah.
Curly.
Hey, Arthur.
Someday, yes?
You and me?
Oh, Tommy, eh?
Fascists. Hmm?
Look at them.
I fucking hate them,
always have done.
But you?
You, Billy Boy.
Oh, you're special.
You know, I fucking like him, Tommy.
I like you.
I do. You're a man after me own heart.
-Someday, Mr Shelby.
-Yeah.
-Someday.
Yeah.
You just tell me when, Tom.
You just tell me when.
So...
-So, you spoke to Barney Thomason, eh?
-Yeah.
Barney Thomason...
is going to kill Oswald Mosley.
Shoot him in the fucking head.
Yep.
While he's onstage.
While I'm stood next to him.
And then I will take over
as the leader of the party,
and you and Aberama
can take care of that bastard, McCavern.
I had more complicated strategies
in mind for Mr Mosley.
Then he spoke badly to my wife.
It's going to be
a busy few weeks, brother.
Yeah.
♪ On a gathering storm
Comes a tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat
With a red right hand ♪
♪ A shadow is cast wherever he stands ♪