I intend to do business
with Billy Kimber.
Is there any man here named Shelby?
I am planning an expansion.
Onto the racetracks.
It would be an honour
to work with you, Mr Kimber.
Nobody works with me.
People work FOR me.
'Danny, you are a good man
and a good soldier.'
Yes, Sergeant Major.
Freddie Thorne is at the very top
of my list.
Well, cross him off.
He won't be returning to this city.
We're not going anywhere, Ada.
We are going to stay here
and we'll marry here, with our baby.
I'm not afraid of Tommy Shelby.
Thomas, you sell those guns
to anyone who has use for them,
you will hang.
Dump them somewhere
the police can find them.
No.
Thomas Shelby is now the beginning,
middle and end of your mission.
So what shall I do?
You must do everything you can
to get close to him.
Dig out a nice dress.
I want to take you to the races.
I warn you, I'll break your heart.
Already broken.
This programme contains some violent
scenes and some strong language.
Give me a bottle of whiskey
and three glasses please.
Scotch or Irish? Irish.
I've decided not to go.
To the races.
Not unless you give me two pounds,
ten shillings towards the dress.
I've already given you three.
How much did you pay for the suit
you'll be wearing?
Oh, I don't pay for suits.
My suits are on the house
or the house burns down.
So you want me to go
looking like a flower girl?
What I want makes no difference.
It's not me you're dressing up for.
Subtitles by s}http://UKsubtitles.ru.
You'll forgive me, Mr Shelby,
if I indulge a little.
Please.
It takes a lot for a man
from Sparkbrook
to step inside this pub.
Anyone with money
and good intentions
is welcome in the Garrison.
Now... you said you had business.
It's delicate, Mr Shelby.
It's a question of who knows what
about what.
It concerns the factory
down the road, at the BSA.
As you might know,
most of the paint shop there
is Irish.
Big old place like that,
rumours get started.
Rumours that there was a robbery.
Robbery of what?
Guns, Mr Shelby.
A serious amount of guns.
What business is that of mine?
When it comes to speculation,
you can't beat a factory night shift.
Some say there was word
from the proofing bay
it was the Peaky Blinders
who took them.
Your night shift must be dreaming.
Maybe they are.
Maybe they're not.
What we are trying to say is,
Mr Shelby,
that if you were to hear about
the whereabouts of said items...
..we'd pay good money.
You have good money?
We have collections from the pubs.
For who do you speak?
The people of Ireland.
The Irish Republican Army.
For a fact?
For a fucking fact.
You think we're jokers?
Am I laughing?
♪ Oh, father, why are you so sad
♪ On this bright Easter morn'... ♪
Maguire, will you shut up?
♪ When Irishmen are proud and glad
♪ Of the land
Where they were born? ♪
Maguire, away and shite man,
we're trying to talk business...
♪ Oh, son, I see sad mem'ries view
♪ Of far-off distant days
♪ When being just a boy like you
♪ I joined the IRA. ♪
Bravo!
♪ Where are the lads... ♪
All right, boys.
If I hear anything about who knows
what about what, I'll let you know.
♪ Gra mo chree, I long to see
♪ The boys of the old IRA... ♪
I thought you only allowed singing
on a Saturday.
Whiskey is good proofing water.
It tells you who's real
and who isn't.
And what did my countrymen want?
They're nobodies.
They drink in The Black Swan
in Sparkbrook.
They're only rebels
because they like the songs.
You have sympathies with them?
I have no sympathies
of any description.
Their accents were so thick,
it's a wonder you could
understand them.
Next time, I could translate.
You'd work for me?
I thought I already was.
So you are coming to the races?
Two pounds, ten shillings.
Ten shillings.
Buy something red.
To match his handkerchief.
Whose handkerchief?
Ada, what the hell?
I dared myself to run through
their territory in my dress.
Are you mad? Yeah.
Mad as hell with all of them.
I love you.
I love you too.
The more they try to stop us,
the madder I'll be.
Come on, princess,
the vicar's waiting. Wait...
How do I look?
Like an angel.
Moss?
What do we know about
The Black Swan?
An operative has provided
intelligence
that it is a place
where IRA men gather.
It's just a lot of drunken navigators
singing songs, sir.
The IRA wouldn't go near them.
Then why are two of them
looking to buy guns?
Do you have names?
Must she do everything for you?
"She", sir?
One female operative
has proved more useful
than any of you great lumps of men.
We are regular police officers, sir.
Not spies.
We can only act
when a crime has been committed.
Perhaps I should send some men down
to The Black Swan to ask questions.
And scare them all into hiding?
Not the best of tactics, Sergeant.
My tactics come from my experiences
in France.
Most of my great lumps of men
served in France too, sir.
I serve my country every day.
That will be all, Sergeant.
Away and shite!
Fancy me, do ya?
What are you? A copper?
Oh!
Proddy bitch!
I've seen you. I've seen your face,
serving in the Garrison.
Come here...
I am taking you in for interrogation
on behalf of the Irish Free State.
All right?
Are you armed?
No.
Then I'll tell you.
Ada and Freddie Thorne
were married today.
They defied your orders,
they haven't left the city.
I'll deal with it.
Thomas... I'll deal with it.
Where are they?
Freddie's comrades have safe houses.
Why do you want to know?
I want to send them flowers.
Why do you think?
Would it be so bad if they stayed?
I promised I'd run Freddie
out of town.
Promised who?
I told the coppers
Freddie wouldn't come back.
It's part of the deal.
What bloody deal?
What happened to family votes?
What happened to meetings?
If you let me deal
with Ada and Freddie,
it'll end in peace.
Christ knows
you've had your fill of war.
You get Freddie out of town, Poll.
Or else I'll deal with it myself.
The victim had been drinking
in The Black Swan pub, sir -
the pub you told me about.
And a neighbour said
she saw a young woman
leaving the street
where the body was found.
A woman, sir. I was wondering
if there was a connection.
A connection with what, Sergeant?
You said your spy was a woman, sir.
I wondered if now there was now
a policy.
Shoot to kill.
Like there was in Belfast.
The Republicans
are famously factional.
He was killed by one of his own.
That will be all, Sergeant.
And they're not called spies.
They're called operatives.
Operatives, sir. Right, sir.
It's how you say things. Yeah...
What the bloody hell
is she doing here?
ã200, Freddie.
For what?
For us. For a honeymoon
that goes on for ever.
Where did it come from?
Family fund.
The pockets of widows
and desperate men.
See sense, Freddie.
Tommy is not going to let this rest.
Times like these, a communist
in the family is bad for business.
You have to leave the city.
You think I can't handle
Tommy Shelby? You can't.
I'm having trouble these days
and I'm twice the man you are.
I went into town.
The Cunard office.
I booked you both tickets
on the next boat
from Liverpool to New York.
America, Freddie.
They've already had
their revolution.
You won't have to bother.
Will you ladies at least
let a man sleep on it?
You had no business...
Observe and report.
That is your remit.
I decided we needed
to know where he lived.
I warned you not to let
your personal history
cloud your judgment.
You went after him
because he was IRA.
I followed him because I thought
he might have information.
According to the rules,
I should pull you out of
Garrison Lane immediately.
No. Cheltenham is tomorrow.
You take too much upon yourself.
This is an active military mission -
your words.
I'm doing my job.
Grace, the death of a base Fenian
doesn't concern me.
Your welfare does.
Killing a man affects the heart.
And as for my heart...
I know that because of
our family connections,
you take my progress personally.
But I don't need you
to be my father.
I will be thinking of you.
Mr Shelby, sir. Mr Zhang.
That suit is sold, sir.
It's being collected this morning.
I know.
Please, gentlemen.
No fighting in here.
It's all right. I come as a friend.
You're collecting your suit
for Cheltenham - it's very nice.
How the bloody hell do you know?
I know a lot of things, Mr Kimber.
And as I told you before,
I know the Lee brothers.
And I know they're going to be
at the Cheltenham races as well.
They're going to lose a lot of money
on fast women and slow nags.
No. They're planning on showing up
in numbers and robbing your bookies.
Running chalk and rafflers.
You think I can't handle the Lees?
Just a word of warning
from a friend. That's all.
I'll see you at Cheltenham.
I'll wave at you from my box.
If you're coming to the races,
bring that pretty barmaid of yours.
Already invited.
Comrades -
as you know, to even gather
like this today is illegal.
Chief Inspector Campbell has ordered
that we are not allowed to assemble
in groups of more than three people.
So, to comply with the law,
please now clump together
in groups of three.
You hear that, boys?
The same whistles they used to blow
to send us over the top,
they now blow
to try and break us up.
So before the Specials get here,
raise a hand,
all those who want to strike...
Now disperse!
Disperse and take the message home!
United, we will never be defeated!
Tommy! Oi, Tommy.
What the hell's been happening?
The police had just raided
a rally at the factory.
You thinking Freddie Thorne's back?
I know he is. And he's with Ada.
How hard can it be to find
the only girl in Birmingham
with four-inch heels, eh?
She's with the commies.
They have little rat holes
all over the city.
I just want to know where she is.
Tommy, you'd best have a word
with Arthur as well.
What's wrong with bloody Arthur?
He's got the Flanders blues again.
People keep asking me questions
that I don't know the answer to.
"Is it true your Ada got married?"
I say, "I don't know."
"Where is she living now?"
"I don't know."
"Arthur...
"..who killed the Paddy
from The Black Swan?"
I go, "What Paddy?"
They say...
.."Is it you, Peaky Blinders,
who stole the guns from the BSA?"
What guns, Tommy?
Arthur, after your beating,
I thought you needed a break...
What bloody guns, Tommy?!
Arthur, I was going to tell you.
You were going to tell me.
Arthur, listen to me.
You've had a hard time
these past few years.
God knows you have.
You deserve some rest.
We had some luck. Some bloody luck.
It fell off a wagon into our laps.
And all you need to know is, it's us
that has the machine guns now.
And it's them that's in the mud.
All right?
Come on. I have a surprise for you.
Come on.
A surprise? Where is she?
What is it you've always wanted,
Arthur? Eh?
When we were in France,
you used to say,
"When I get back to England,
I want to own my own pub."
Well...
You've gone soft.
You've gone soft, Tommy.
How do we know it's for sale?
Everything's for sale to us, Arthur.
We're making a lot of money
these days.
We need a legitimate business
to pass the money from the shop.
I wouldn't know what to do.
You've spent two-thirds of your life
in pubs.
Just pour it instead of drinking it.
But I can still drink it, right?
Your pub - you do what you want.
Ah - sorry, gentlemen,
I didn't hear you come in.
What can I get you?
Bloody kids.
The other one's punctured as well.
Mr Campbell wants an explanation.
Today, some rabble-rouser Union man
brought the BSA out on strike.
It was Freddie Thorne.
I thought you promised
he wouldn't come back.
I know he's in town.
I'm dealing with it.
Inspector Campbell thought
you controlled your territories.
Yeah.
I said I'm dealing with it.
I heard that, er...
..Freddie married your sister.
Some family you've got, eh?
Bet you can't wait for Christmas.
Deliver Freddie Thorne to us
or we'll take your sister
in as an accomplice.
She'll get four years for sedition.
Or you can turn him in
and your sister goes free.
I'll say good night then, Tom.
Have you seen Freddie Thorne?
No. Or Tommy? Ahh!
I have to find Freddie.
Drink this first.
No, I have to find them, I think
they are going to kill each other.
Who is going to kill who?
We need to talk.
What exactly is it
that you want, Freddie?
I came to tell you...
..that's not going to work, Tommy.
Polly came round. She gave me that.
Well, Polly must have had
a rush of blood.
Or port wine.
Your honesty is appreciated.
Now, if you're not going
to use that thing...
I'm not finished. Sit down.
Sit down. Sit.
Talk to me about the guns.
Do you remember we used
to jump in here,
see who could swim the fastest...?
I'm here to talk business, Tommy.
Do you reckon we could still do it?
Ah!
You loaded Ada with your bastard
because she's a Shelby.
You thought it'd mean
you'd be somebody.
I won't let you fuck up
my sister's life for your cause.
My God.
You actually believe that.
I love her, Tommy.
I've loved her since she was nine
and I was 12.
And she loves me the same.
You even know the word?
This marriage will not stand.
Shh...
Freddie didn't want your money.
And now the coppers are saying
if we don't turn Freddie in,
they'll put Ada
on the arrest warrant as well.
That's where your compassion
gets you, Poll.
From now on, we do it my way.
Or what?
Ready?
They're getting closer.
I'll lead. Watch yourself, Danny.
Tommy.
Be careful, Danny.
Tommy!
Aargh!
Arrrggghhh!
Tommy!
Tommy?
It's open.
Private Whizz Bang reporting, sir.
At ease.
So, what news from London?
I was in a pub -
it was called Mother Redcap.
An Irish pub.
I got talking to some old bloke
about Birmingham.
He said there's been trouble.
An IRA man shot.
He said a lot, but the only bit
I heard... was that their high command
think it's the Peaky Blinders
who shot him.
Came up on the next boat to warn you.
Is it true?
No.
But lies travel faster
than the truth.
Get a message to them.
Tell them to send someone to parley.
Tell them there's been
a misunderstanding
and we don't want any trouble.
You've got enough trouble -
right, Tommy?
A whisky and a smoke.
I can smell it in the air.
I use it sometimes myself.
I call it "my sweetheart".
They gave us the worst job, Tommy.
Yeah...
..and we fucking volunteered.
Sometimes, it lasts all night.
I lie here and I listen
to the shovels and the picks
against that wall there.
And I pray the sun will come up
at the curtains
before they break through.
'No, I don't pray - I hope.
'And sometimes, it happens.
'The sun beats them.
'But mostly...
'..the shovels beat the sun.'
Your sister was here.
She was worried. You and Freddie.
It had made her sick...
She's all right,
but in her condition,
she needs peace.
Women talk.
That is something they do.
She talked about you.
She said you keep everything
locked up.
Well, that's what men do.
Your sister's nice. I like her.
It can't be easy for her.
Her brother and her husband,
fighting over the same thing.
Men should talk, too.
To you?
Why not? I'm a barmaid. It's my job.
Men always tell their troubles
to a barmaid.
What is it you and Freddie
are fighting over?
I'll meet you here at nine o'clock
tomorrow morning.
Did you buy a dress?
Yes. I bought a dress.
How does it look?
He's changed the oil
and greased her up.
So will it get me
all the way to Cheltenham, Curly?
He's good with motors,
but it pains him.
No heart in motorcars.
I can't talk with them.
Yeah - Tommy might need
to make a fast getaway.
The Lees will be all over the track.
And Kimber's men. And his coppers.
They control the law down there,
Tommy.
Give her a turn for me, Charlie.
This car only seats four.
You'll need more men than that
if you're to come back alive.
It'll be just me and a girl.
Is it just the two of us
going to the races?
Something like that.
Attention!
Right.
This is what was known as the final
briefing before going over the top.
60 miles down that road
is Cheltenham racetrack.
Johnny, what's our mission, boy?
To stick it to the Lee family,
Arthur.
That's right. The Lees are skimming
money off legal bookies.
Running chalk, selling rafflers,
beating up them as won't buy.
But today, we're going to stop them.
What about Kimber's men?
I thought he had his own protection.
Kimber's let his troops go rotten.
They're on the take from the Lees
to look the other way.
We are going to show Kimber
how it should be done.
Now take what you're good at.
Those of you with guns,
keep them out of it,
unless a gun is pulled on you.
We want this done quietly.
So when do we share out the cash?
We don't.
We're not keeping the cash.
You're in Tommy's army now, boys.
Trust only kin.
Let's go.
Are you sure we're allowed in here?
Well, I prefer to come to the races
the back way.
It keeps me out of trouble.
Tracks are lawless places.
I can't stand petty criminals.
This way.
Will we get to lay a bet?
No - gambling is for mugs.
This way...
You're lucky you're with me
or you'd be wasting your money
on fixed races.
I always wondered,
how do you fix a race?
How should I know?
OK, you do the talking. What?
Tell security
you are Lady Sarah Duggan...
Excuse us, excuse us...
..Lady Sarah Duggan of Connemara.
You got lost when you went
to look for the boy
riding your horse - Dandy Flower.
If they ask about me,
say I'm Prussian
and don't speak a word of English.
Come on, posh girl.
Earn your three quid.
I still prefer the Garrison.
Do you dance?
If I'm asked properly.
Lady Sarah of Connemara,
will you dance with me?
Roberts.
The Peaky Blinders are here.
I told you, Mr Kimber.
He's got some balls, that one.
And she's got some body, that one.
Chalk for your blackboards.
Five pounds a stick.
It's a pleasure doing
business with you.
Hello, Raz. How's business?
Argh! Ugh!
Fucking... get up!
Fucking...
ARRGGHH!
Stay still, Raz,
or I'll take the whole ear off.
And you're going to need
your ears to listen.
No more chalking
on Billy Kimber's boys.
Right?
We're the protection now.
I commandeer this stolen money
by order of the Peaky Blinders.
Agghh!
Either your left leg
is stronger than your right
or we're making a getaway.
Neither. I hope this doesn't involve
razor blades.
I've decided to move up
in the world.
Become a legitimate businessman.
My gosh. You're serious.
I'm always serious.
We chased the Lees across the track,
right the way down the Devon road.
We got every penny back.
Nice dress.
You can wear that to my pub.
Buy the boys a drink. Anybody hurt?
A few cuts and bruises.
Off we go, Lady Sarah.
Steady on...
Excuse me.
Your money, Mr Kimber.
Rescued from the Lee brothers
and returned to you
with a request for a fair hearing.
Your own protection is failing,
Mr Kimber.
Your boys are taking cuts.
I want to suggest that from now on,
you contract out your racetrack
security to the Peaky Blinders.
We would be saving you
a lot of money, Mr Kimber.
A lot of money.
In return, you give us...
..5% of the take
and three legal betting pitches
at every race meeting
north of the River Severn,
rising to six after one year
if we are all satisfied
with the service.
What do you say, Mr Kimber?
I say you talk business
to my accountant.
I want to dance.
Your man said it was all right
for me to have this dance.
How many men can you put
in the field at one time?
There's a lot of men out of work
at the moment.
Two guards for every bookie.
At every meeting?
We have contacts with good people
among the gypsies.
We'll always know where the Lees
plan to attack.
With all the strikes and troubles,
you can't depend on the police.
Anyway... we're more honest.
Looks like you two
are making a deal.
We are making progress.
Then let me throw a small condition
into the mix.
So, listen... we're going to go
for dinner at Kimber's house.
He has a place
a couple of miles away.
I have some business to settle first
with his accountant, so...
You go on ahead, with Kimber.
Just me and him?
Yeah... until I'm done here.
Is that all right?
I'll throw in an extra three quid
for your extra time.
You think I'm a whore?
Everybody's a whore, Grace.
We just sell different parts
of ourselves.
You said you wanted to work for me.
To do that, you have to sharpen up.
The deal is I give him
two hours with you.
He thinks he's a ladies' man.
He thinks he can seduce you.
Whenever you want,
just kick him in the balls.
I'm a clause in a contract.
If you want to be part
of my organisation,
you have to make sacrifices.
Do we have a deal?
As a sweetener,
you can try your luck with mine.
Yes, we have a deal.
Two hours? Yeah.
Side bet. Ten pounds says
I'll have her fucked in one.
Mademoiselle.
I bet he said you could have me,
didn't he?
While he has her.
That's the arrangement, isn't it?
Yours might be a prostitute,
but I'm not.
I was a milliner when I met him.
I was independent.
I made this hat.
I was a good milliner.
It's a very pretty hat.
It really is.
So is she a prostitute?
God's honest truth?
I don't know what she is.
You showed me up
back there at the races.
Why don't you teach me
how to dance properly?
The music is too slow.
Put on a Charleston.
Then we'd be far away.
I want to dance like this.
Come on. You weren't so stiff
back there, were you?
You ever been in a house this big?
Hm?
Look at you.
You look like a bloody film star.
I want a cigarette.
Oh, look, I dropped something.
Pick it up.
Pick it up yourself.
You're a fucking barmaid.
If I drop a glass on the floor,
you pick it up.
I want to watch you pick it up.
Right, you little slag.
I have tried to be nice.
If I drop a glass on the floor,
you bend over and fucking pick up
the fucking glass, OK?
What?! No, sir... no.
What are you doing here?
I've got another hour.
Just wait - listen to me.
Just listen to me.
I was going to let you go through
with it, but in the end,
my conscience got the better of me.
She looks good on the outside...
..but she has the clap.
Yeah. Syphilis.
When you took a shine to her,
I thought I'd use her.
Somebody told me she had syph
and I thought, "What the hell?"
Call it my better nature.
She's... she's a whore.
Just go and wait in the car.
I can walk on my own!
Can we shake hands
and forget this ever happened?
Start of the day,
I was Lady Sarah of Connemara.
By the end,
I was a whore with the clap.
You're a fucking bastard,
offering me like that.
But then you changed your mind.
Why did you change your mind, Thomas?
Subtitles by s}http://UKsubtitles.ru.