♪ Take a little walk
To the edge of town ♪
♪ And go across the tracks ♪
♪ Where the viaduct looms ♪
♪ Like a bird of doom ♪
♪ As it shifts and cracks ♪
♪ Where secrets lie
In the border fires ♪
♪ In the humming wires ♪
♪ Hey man, you know ♪
♪ You're never coming back ♪
♪ Past the square
Past the bridge ♪
You shoot at his eyes...
[speaking in Italian]
He may try to surrender.
[in English] But remember...
I'll fire the final shot.
♪ A tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat with ♪
♪ A red right hand ♪
Stay inside, ma'am.
[gunfire]
Come on!
Go, go, go!
[speaking in Italian]
Don't let him get away!
That bitch lied to me.
Come on.
It's all right, ma'am. It's all right.
Come inside. Come inside.
Stay inside, don't come out.
[gunfire]
Get away from the window.
Right, stay inside and stay down.
[baby crying]
Everyone stay indoors! Stay down!
-By order of the Peaky Blinders.
-Come on!
[baby continues crying]
[snaps fingers]
Come here.
[breathing shakily]
Which way?
Which way did he go?
You sure? Yeah?
[panting]
[indistinct voices approaching]
-[gunfire]
-[man grunts]
Oy!
[panting]
[screams]
Luca.
[speaks Italian]
No.
We should let go. Why?
We have him.
[groaning]
[speaking Italian]
What are you trying to do?
Get yourself killed?
[in English] Hey! I know you own the cops
in this dirty fucking town.
But you'll dead before they get here.
Come on, me and you, Tommy.
Come on.
[speaking in Italian]
Vengeance is yours. My father.
Look at me.
Vengeance... is yours too.
-[gunshot]
-[men clamoring]
[policeman] Stop what you're doing!
[overlapping shouting]
Go back, mate, you moron!
[grunts]
Enough!
No. Now, get out of it. Get away!
Enough.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Saving your life. Or his.
I am a police officer, Tommy.
I am a fucking police officer, right,
doing my duty. Stopping all this!
There are three bodies need cleaning up.
No. Enough.
Tell the people who live in these houses
that they are free
to go about their lawful business.
Tell them that the rule of law
has been restored.
Haven't you heard, Tommy, eh?
Soldiers are coming.
[pouring drink]
[Polly] Do you know, I remember the very
first time you head-butted a policeman.
But after you got your AP from the King,
I didn't think there would be a next time.
What do you think
you're going to tell Arthur?
I will tell them the truth.
[clears throat]
[Polly] They are here. [Arthur] So...
what the fuck happened today, Tom?
We all heard.
Shooting in Artillery Square.
Yeah, there was.
Today I killed three men.
Now our enemies will have to wait.
I suppose they, uh...
I suppose they took
you by surprise, did they?
No. I knew they were coming.
Just after Christmas I received a letter
from Luca Changretta,
offering to spare my son
if I gave up Tommy.
And I gave Tommy up.
Because that was the plan
that Polly and I agreed on.
I knew that Luca would want
to pull the trigger himself...
[sniffs]
So I used the set up
as bait to bring him in.
You are a fucking idiot, Tom.
Look, I dint get Luca,
but I got three. All right.
That's it. That's what happened.
-Come here, you.
-[man] Happen he's right, huh?
I mean I thought you'd gone soft.
[chuckles]
-So, you got three?
-Yeah, I got three.
Well, I drink to you Tom, you mad bastard.
[all laugh]
Pretty soon you are gonna get the shakes
when your blood cools down.
Let's go get a drink.
Dad, you got three what?
I got three shillings
for a two-shilling horse.
Now, my boy, you come with us, huh?
[door opens]
Want a drink, Lizzie? I've had a hard day.
I don't drink whiskey or gin anymore, Tom.
Why not?
Because they say it harms the baby.
Yes. It can only be yours.
That day by the canal when you were
fucking somebody else in your head,
except it wasn't her that got pregnant.
Have a seat, Lizzie.
[sighs]
All right, I know a woman, Lizzie.
You know lots of women, Tommy.
If you don't know this already
you don't know me.
I am keeping it.
Who's gonna run me fucking office?
You will find somebody.
Well...
you better put a fucking advert
in the paper then.
I'm not laid up yet.
You'll not go to work
with a child of mine inside of you.
Fuck, now me hand shakes.
It's okay, Tom.
It'll be okay.
All this death, Lizzie.
Fuck, let's have some life, right?
I got three. [clears throat]
I know, Tom.
[sighs]
One of them point-blank.
A baby. A little you and me.
Point blank, Lizzie.
And he looked up at me.
[clears throat]
[glass thuds]
You will get an allowance
every week from the company.
Business is booming.
I will buy you a nice house, eh?
Come on, I will drive you home.
I'm just looking.
[glass shatters]
[snorts]
[cap twisting]
Hmm?
[door shuts]
[footsteps approaching]
-Fuck.
-Linda.
Arthur, you scared me to death.
Linda.
[groans]
Linda, you saved me. Again.
You are drunk. Again.
I'm drunk again. I am drunk again.
I need you to save me.
Tell me what you said to me this morning.
[stutters] Tell me again. Tell me.
Say it, say it, say it. Tell me.
We'll be back in our garden
before the time comes
to plant anything out.
Just one winter.
Come to bed, Arthur.
[grunting]
They're coming, boys.
No.
No fucking way.
Have you ever eaten hedgehog, Michael?
[laughter]
I'm getting back in this car.
Michael, you are number two
on Luca Changretta's hit list.
Yeah, and I will stay in a hotel.
You stay in a hotel,
I'll know where you are,
so will the people who take you there,
so will the people who work in the hotel.
And hotels don't move around.
They don't even know
where they will be tomorrow.
They follow the patrin and the crows.
And if anyone should come
for you, Michael,
the Palmers and the Boswells
will put up a fair fight.
[Polly] Take your medicine.
I'll take them.
Your painkillers.
But the healers up there
will heal you much quicker.
Fucking witches, the lot of them.
Show some respect, Mr. Gray.
They've agreed to welcome you
on account of your blood.
Take your medicine.
Take the gun.
I won't be able to contact you.
So, you phone me.
We'll make a plan.
Tommy says it won't be long.
Then we'll be free.
You might learn something.
Tell them your grandmother
was a gypsy princess.
Name of Birdy Boswell.
You're royalty up there, Michael.
[horses neighing]
[Aberama] Is that true, Mrs. Gray?
What?
Don't I look like royalty?
Well, now that you've mentioned it,
you do.
I've been cooped up
in Small Heath too long.
I can smell spring in the air.
Do you know a longer way back, Mr. Gold?
I know ways back that would take forever.
Get in, your majesty.
I thought you were a busy woman.
Do you have time for this?
-Is it a buck?
-It is a buck.
Good. Bucks taste better.
In the smoke, I'm 16 again.
You know, when the police were after him,
my dad used to take us out.
We'd be gone for days
living on what he caught.
Oh!
Do you have a sharp knife?
I hear you have second sight.
I heard that you speak with the dead.
Yes.
Your wife is often around you.
She watches you.
She watching me now?
No.
Your family were healers?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Came back when I put my head
in the noose.
It's like putting your head through
a window and seeing the whole world.
Give me the rabbit and the knife.
You know, Polly...
I believe it's you that has kept
Tommy Shelby alive all these years.
Oh, we've kept each other alive.
But I didn't just put my head
through that window.
I climbed through it.
At first, I thought it was madness but no,
when you put your head
out of that window...
you can do anything you want.
'Cause there are no rules. 'Cause there are no risks.
Now, give me the knife.
Now, come here.
I can do whatever I want
whenever the mood takes me
and you're a strong handsome man
and this is a beautiful place
in the world.
And it is... this time.
But let me make
one thing clear, Mr. Gold,
I just gave Michael a little speech
about how no one
would know where to find him.
But you would know how to get him.
If any harm comes to Michael,
you shall have me as your enemy
and none of your knives can kill me.
Do you understand?
Oh, I understand.
[speaks in Romani]
Mr. Solomons.
Hmm?
My little cousin was born blind.
As a result,
I now donate a considerable
sum of money to a charity
which gives dogs with eyes to blind Jews.
The chairman of the board
recommends that those of us
who are blessed with the gift of sight
and that we spend at least half an hour
of our day with our eyes closed
so that we may...
We may have a better understanding
with the darkness and also
to increase our donations and that.
Hmm.
What time is it?
Twenty-nine minutes past eight.
Right, well then, I have another minute
to go actually but you...
you can begin, go on.
[smacks lips]
I'm Luca Changretta.
Oh, yeah, I know who you are. Hmm.
You are a bit of a failure, aren't you?
You come all the way over here
to this country
in order to kill Tommy Shelby,
but I mean...
Well, he is not dead is he, so...
-No.
He ain't.
How much time have I got left, mate?
Ten seconds. Nine seconds, eight seconds,
five, four, three,
two, one.
Right. Hello.
How can I help you?
I have a proposition for you.
Mmm... Yeah. I already know what you want.
-Yeah.
-I just want to hear you say it out loud.
So I can check how ridiculous it is.
[speaking in Italian]
I am losing my patience.
[Matteo] Luca.
-[grunts]
-[speaking Italian]
That's the way he is.
And we need him.
[in English] There is gonna be
a little fight, a boxing match.
Between your boy and Tommy Shelby's boy.
-Right, Birmingham?
-Mmm-hmm.
And the whole Shelby family
is gonna be there.
Mmm-hmm.
And you, Mr. Solomons,
you too will be there.
[stutters]
That's it.
I tell you what, right.
Here is a gift. It's free.
Souvenir of your visit here.
Goodbye, trot on.
Down there is Bonnie Street.
You know they say you're a smart guy.
[chuckles]
You already know
what we want before we say it.
That's funny 'cause now I believe
I know what you want
even before you say it. Yeah.
So, are you gonna taste it?
[speaking Italian]
Damn fucking straight, mate.
Otherwise, you wouldn't still be breathing
my oxygen, would you?
Because I have 200 barrels a month.
Yeah, cleared by your people,
distributed through your teams...
Thing is that people want gin these days.
Well, the exit is still out there.
Right on Bonnie Street. Yeah?
[Luca chuckles]
[Luca] Oh,
you fucking crazy, you know that?
Two hundred barrels, huh?
[speaks Italian]
[Alfie] And also, I want some cash.
Don't worry, 'cause I've broken it
down here. I've got here a list of costs
pertaining to the assassination
of a dear friend. All right.
Now, your normal dispatch,
well, it's £500 cost,
but you're gonna have to add
another 100 to that
because Tommy Shelby, like me,
is from an oppressed people.
Then, I need you to put
another ton on top of that
because his brother is a fucking animal
and he will come after me.
Yeah. And then you'll need to put
another 100 on top of that
because, well,
you are a fucking wop, mate.
Hmm? And you.
And then... we have to deal
with the ugly business
of which I've been incredibly clear of,
before I'll need another £500
because like I stated, Tommy Shelby
is a very, very good friend of mine.
Total is down there in black and white.
All right? Crack on.
It's okay.
Mr. Solomons,
I'm gonna be very fucking clear with you.
I don't need you to kill anybody.
I have people that I trust, okay?
So you are gonna take my boys
and you are gonna bring them
to the ring as seconds.
Well, in order to qualify
as my seconds, right,
they would first have to qualify
as being Jewish. Yeah?
And in order to do that
they would have to replace
their natural Italian fucking arrogance
with a Jewish air of absolute certainty.
You see, my good friend, Tommy Shelby,
he will know the difference.
These days, back in the old country,
a lot of the...
You know, the Jewish people,
they... [chuckles] are having to pass
themselves off as Italian.
[laughing]
All right, well, you'll have to add
another ton onto your bill
for being a cunt, mate.
All right?
[snaps fingers]
You will bring my men to Birmingham?
You will circumcise them?
Yeah, you will have to circumcise them.
Because the peakys will check, yeah?
[speaking in Italian]
Motherfuckers.
Okay, any other requests?
Two hundred fucking barrels,
we have a deal.
Uh...
[exhales]
-What's the matter?
-Mmm. Well...
I said we have a deal.
Eh, you just made a deal
without a negotiation, didn't you?
Huh.
Yeah, Tommy Shelby
was right about you, wasn't he?
[speaking Italian]
You plan to kill us all.
[clicks tongue]
-[officer] Ada Shelby?
-No.
[keys jangling]
[door opens]
She was armed when we picked her up, sir.
So we strip searched her.
-That will be all.
-Yes, sir.
[Colonel Ben Younger]
I apologize, Miss Shelby.
-The territorials can be over-zealous.
-[door opens and shuts]
Your men watched.
And they will be reprimanded.
They won't see Saturday.
A naked woman alone making threats
against the entire British Army.
Significant indicator of character.
I'll turn my back while you dress
and perhaps we can talk.
I have a dossier
on each member of your family.
I know your family's
extraordinary history.
[chuckles] Fuck you.
And I also have a totally blank page
on which together we can write
your family's immediate future.
You rehearsed your speech.
Significant indicator
of a lack of confidence.
-What rank are you?
-Colonel.
-Well...
-May I turn?
Not unless you want to get blinded.
I'm sorry this has got off to a bad start.
What is this?
Three days ago, you were seen at a meeting
for the Stetford Communist Party.
You were then seen talking
to a woman called Jessie Eden.
Turn around.
I'm leaving.
And you can burn this.
It's history.
Ada Shelby,
a person of interest and under
the surveillance of the special branch
since you joined
the Birmingham Communist Party
in June 1919.
I'm no longer a member
of the Communist Party.
I know. Irrelevant.
Most of the more active subversives
shed their official allegiances
to avoid detection.
[scoffs] Look... okay.
Let me explain it to you.
I'm no longer a member
of the Communist Party
because I'm no longer a believer
in the cause of socialism.
Now, open that door.
[Colonel Ben Younger] So, in the past,
you were blinded by love?
No. Blinded by faith.
I believed people deserved justice.
They don't.
So, you've arrested me
because I had a drink with Jessie Eden?
Whiskey with ice for you
and a beer for her.
I met Jessie Eden
to settle an industrial dispute.
Head of acquisitions?
So, you swapped sides.
If you know what I drink,
you know what I do for a living.
Miss Shelby,
you must understand
that these are extraordinary times.
A general strike is certain.
Attempted revolution perhaps.
Soldiers on the streets very soon.
They are already drilling.
And here stands you.
A woman with her foot in both camps.
It's potentially very useful.
Useful to who?
Maybe you should ask your brother, Thomas.
[door opens]
[man] Put some fucking effort into it,
the fight's in two days.
Get used to the reach.
Get used to the long arm on him.
Get under it.
That's it, under his body, boy.
Talk to me about Colonel Ben Younger.
What about him?
He has just made me a proposition.
You're in my chair.
He said you knew about it.
[pours drink]
And remember
I know when you are lying.
Ben Younger was an officer
in the Warwickshire Yeomanry in Flanders.
The only Calvary man
who could ride a fucking horse.
I was strip searched.
Two soldiers watched.
I am sorry, Ada.
That...
The arrest was so the neighbors
would see and word would go around.
Younger is all right.
Younger came to me for help.
[groans]
He has been given Birmingham.
Given Birmingham. By who?
By Churchill.
By the fucking King.
By people who want to stop a revolution.
[scoffs]
No one is laughing anymore, Ada.
The home office is making provisions.
This is part of those provisions.
And how is Tommy Shelby, OBE,
going to stop a revolution?
Jessie Eden has accepted
my invitation to dinner.
[scoffs]
Of course. I'm sorry.
Tommy Shelby is gonna stop
the revolution with his cock.
It's not her the military
are interested in,
it's the people around her.
The people like you used to be,
like Freddy used to be.
People who want an armed revolution. If I get Jessie Eden's trust,
she gives me the names of the instigators,
I give them up to the crown forces.
Tommy. Tommy, sweetheart.
Why would a man whose medals rust
at the bottom of the Saltley canal
want to help the British military?
[sighs]
Because I have been offered
three five-year contracts
to supply military vehicles
to the British forces in India,
Ceylon, Singapore and Burma.
Total value £2 million.
Wouldn't be no strikes in your factory
'cause Jessie Eden would be in your bed.
Tommy, this can only happen
if you are still alive.
Planning on staying alive.
If I'm dead you can all go back
to being what you were.
The British army came to me, Ada.
I said, why not.
I'll put that on your grave, Tom.
Tommy Shelby, "Why not."
[sighs]
Are you gonna help me or not?
[door shuts]
[clattering]
Other way around.
And... will they want music, Charlie?
We have that gramophone we found
abandoned inside that gentleman's car.
No, they don't.
Tommy said they are here to talk.
[door creaks open]
Charlie, Curly, this is Jessie Eden.
Jessie, this is my uncle, Charlie
and my whatever Curly is.
This is actually lovely.
We were just wondering
if you'd like some music?
-No, we weren't.
-Actually, Jessie likes music.
-Don't go to any trouble.
-No, Curly, go to some trouble.
Go on, then.
Right.
[clears throat]
Don't I get a choice?
I want an opinion. Try it.
I don't really drink gin.
Then you're perfect.
My gin is for women
that don't really drink gin.
Your gin?
Let's drink to something.
You choose.
To the revolution.
Why not?
-To the revolution.
Right, well, since I have invited you
for dinner I thought I'd cook.
These two beauties were shot this morning
by a poacher friend of mine
on Lord Packwood's estate.
I thought you would like that.
These here...
these were stolen from under his trees.
Mr. Shelby, I came to talk business.
Yes.
So did I.
Wage cuts withdrawn.
Parity between men
and women guaranteed. You can instruct your members
to return to work tomorrow.
And all I have to do in return is tell you
everything I know about socialism?
That's what your sister said.
You don't like your gin?
It's okay.
What do you want to know about the cause?
I'm approaching
the current political crisis
as I would approach a horse race.
Assessing the runners and the riders.
Now, the favorite
is of course the King's horse.
But the King's horse
was also the favorite in 1913,
when Emily Davison
threw herself in front of it.
You know the names of the suffragettes?
I'm impressed.
Oh, everyone laughed at them at first,
but now look.
Women with serious faces everywhere.
When I study a horse race,
I study form...
and the other horse, the one
that wants to beat the King's horse.
Let's call her Dangerous, shall we?
She's has no form.
That's what makes her so dangerous.
Russia. Isn't that form?
No. The Russians aren't like
the English with beer.
They're petrol.
That's why I invited you here for dinner.
I'm guessing you know the people,
people that want to make this fight real.
With guns and ammunition.
So before I place a bet
on who is gonna win,
I need to know how strong they are.
How serious they are.
Your concern
is that if the unthinkable happened,
you would find yourself
on the wrong side of the barricades.
Well, as you can see...
my natural side of the barricades
is the same as yours and as you know...
I once believed.
But the war changed you?
Yeah.
The man I loved couldn't speak
when he got back. Not one word.
I've said very few true words since.
The men who blew the whistles
in France are our enemy.
And you count yourself
among those who want a real fight?
I do.
-Well, well.
-Yes.
Not just in my dreams, in the day now.
And you're not alone.
I'm not alone.
Well, well.
I researched you.
We have researched you.
You've never been
a friend to the government.
They've used you.
And I imagine you have found out already
that no amount of money allows you
to pass through the steel sheets
-that separate class from class?
-[scoffs]
Yes. Yes, that I have learnt.
A man like you would terrify them.
Better than them at what they do.
[chuckles]
Would I change the odds, do you think?
[footsteps approach]
[Curly] It's all wound up, Tom.
Uh, just put the needle on
and let her spin,
and there are some
popular records, mostly romantic.
Uh...
Thank you, Curly.
Dinner's nearly ready.
Let's speak before we dance, shall we?
So we are going to dance?
I think so.
[record snaps in]
[clicks]
[soft music plays]
[Jessie chuckles]
[Tommy] I swear to God.
She gave me sixpence.
She sends me to the shop
for margarine, eggs and bread.
When I came back...
...with a top hat and a coconut.
...and that was all the money we had
for the whole fucking week.
And me mum beat me
with a fucking frying pan.
Why the hell did you buy
a top hat and a coconut?
'Cause I thought she deserved it.
I thought we all did.
And I could never understand...
why people like us
only had bread and fucking lard.
And I wanted to be different.
That's what I wanted.
And you are?
No.
When I showed you that photo
of Greta Durruti, your face changed.
She wanted everything to be different.
Her whole world.
As do I.
Shall we hear some more music?
[clears throat]
[gramophone clicking]
You were married but she was killed?
"Bye, bye Blackbird"
reminds you of your sweetheart, eh?
I guess.
You want it fast or slow?
Absolutely slow.
Would you just sit, I'm drunk.
[record crackling]
Come on.
[music playing]
Will you help us, Tommy?
Soon. Soon.
Arrange a meeting
with the appropriate people
and I will be there.
[crowd chattering]
[sniffing]
[Arthur] Billy, come on, boy.
Get over here, you lazy bastard.
There, what's all that. Hey.
[laughs]
The room is clean, Mr. Shelby.
Right. Lock it all down.
All right, boys, lock it down.
[man] No weapons!
No admission if you've any weapons!
[grunts] Go on!
Arthur! Can I open the book?
All right. Open it up! You.
Gentlemen.
You put all your money... You hear me?
It's fucking fun-day. Clear the way.
[man] Come on, boys.
Come place your bets with me,
Honest Johnny Dodds.
The only show in town in order
of your special constable brothers,
the Peaky fucking Blinders.
Bonnie, boy. Here we go, boy.
Bring out that fucking tiger, eh. Go on.
Tiger is already out.
Fair enough.
[Aberama] Bonnie...
Rest assured you will get a 20% cut
if you put Goliath down
in the fourth round.
[Arthur] Been kind of too long, brother.
If the women are gonna have fun,
so am I.
[chattering]
♪ On the gathering storm comes ♪
♪ A tall, handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat with ♪