[Ada] My brother apologises
for not being here
and would like to invite all of you
to his home for a meeting.
[Tommy] All you have to do
is sit with Jack Nelson
and talk to him about a new golden age.
-If anyone's going to kill Tommy Shelby...
-It will be you.
The future belongs to us.
Your daughter has consumption.
Consumption is a very infectious disease.
[Lizzie] While they are X-raying Ruby,
they have to X-ray us.
It's the girl's mother who laid the curse.
Perhaps she waited
till your little girl was seven.
So you'd know how it feels.
[Tommy] Now that I'm without whiskey,
I can hear the spirits clearly,
they are saying Ruby will be well
if I make amends.
She's gone, Tommy.
[latch clanks]
["In This Heart" playing]
[woman] ♪ In this heart ♪
♪ Lies for you ♪
♪ A lark ♪
♪ Born only for you ♪
♪ Who sings ♪
♪ Only to you ♪
♪ My love, my love, my love ♪
-[woman]♪ I am waiting ♪
-[man] ♪ Waiting ♪
-[woman]♪ For you ♪
-[man]♪ For you ♪
-[woman]♪ For only ♪
-[man]♪ For only ♪
-[woman]♪ To adore you ♪
-[man]♪ To adore you ♪
-[woman]♪ My heart is for you ♪
-[man]♪ My heart is for you ♪
-[woman]♪ My love, my love, my love ♪
-[man]♪ My love, my love, my love ♪
-[woman]♪ This is my grief ♪
-[man]♪ This is my grief ♪
-[woman]♪ For you ♪
-[man]♪ For you ♪
-[woman]♪ I will have you ♪
-[man]♪ I will have you ♪
-[woman]♪ With me ♪
-[man]♪ With me ♪
-[woman]♪ In my arms only ♪
-[man]♪ In my arms only ♪
-[woman]♪ For you are only ♪
-[man]♪ For you are only ♪
-[woman]♪ My love, my love ♪
-[man]♪ My love, my love ♪
-[woman]♪ My love ♪
-[man]♪ My love ♪
Arthur.
I've written some words.
I can't speak 'em.
[grunts]
You're the oldest.
You speak 'em for me.
[Arthur] I'm sorry, brother.
I can't do it.
[weeping]
[sighs]
We could have afforded a golden carriage.
She deserved a golden carriage.
But we didn't
afford ourselves that luxury...
because gold doesn't work.
That was the last lesson
that Ruby taught us.
This place was her favourite place
in the whole world.
And she used to say,
"Dad...
you never know
what's gonna come down the river."
And it's true.
'Cause little Ruby's fate
came a thousand miles too soon.
But in her name
and in her memory, things will change.
[sniffles]
And whatever comes down
that river from now on,
we will make good...
We will make peaceful and honest and good,
and send it on down the river
better than it was.
In her memory, we will do this.
[sniffles]
But for now,
we send her on
to wherever it is you go.
In the hope
that if there is a destination...
...that it's a yard like this.
With horses and boats for her to play on.
[sighs] Tom.
-I've got the petrol.
-[sighs]
Who will light the flame?
Jeremiah.
Jeremiah, you made her laugh.
You light the flame.
No! No!
-Lizzie.
-[Lizzie] No!
You won't burn her! No!
Lizzie. [shushes]
[Lizzie sobbing]
-I just want to see my baby.
-We'll go and see her together. Come on.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-We'll go and see her together.
[sniffles]
[exhales]
Oh, my baby.
The devils who did this will pay, Ruby.
Tommy, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
Where're you going?
[inaudible]
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[vehicle approaching]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Riley.
I think the police are here.
[Tommy] Evadne Barwell?
Yeah.
Who's asking?
[Tommy] I'm here on behalf
of the blue sapphire.
[gunshots firing]
[people shrieking]
[woman] Don't shoot. There are babies!
Go! Come on.
[baby crying]
[woman] We have to go. Come on!
[Tommy breathing heavily]
["Lullaby For Cain" playing]
♪ From the silence ♪
♪ From the night ♪
♪ Comes a distant lullaby ♪
♪ Cry, remember that first cry ♪
♪ Your brother standing by ♪
♪ And lot... ♪
[grunting]
♪ Of loved ♪
♪ Beloved sons of mine ♪
♪ Sing a lullaby ♪
♪ Mother is close by ♪
♪ Innocent eyes ♪
♪ Such innocent eyes ♪
[groans]
♪ Envy stole your brother's life ♪
♪ Came home... ♪
[sobbing]
♪ Murdered ♪
♪ Piece of mind ♪
[sobs]
♪ Left you nightmares on the pillow ♪
[engine running]
[engine stops]
[sighs deeply]
[door closes]
Gold dust.
Our business is done, Esme.
Get out of the car.
[Esme] Not quite done, Tommy.
Thought this'd be a good time.
In fact, it's the perfect time.
Some business is still unfinished.
Christians say, "The Lord gives,
the Lord takes away."
Our spirits are the same.
Spirits just took away your child.
-Get out of the car, Esme.
-[engine starts]
The same spirits want to
give you a different child, Tommy.
[sighs] What child?
[engine stops]
A daughter lost,
a son found.
Before you went to France
a long time ago, at Appleby Fair,
you slept with a girl.
Her name was Zelda.
I met her.
She said you slept together
under a hazel tree in May 1914.
When she fell pregnant
her father threatened to kill you.
But you'd already joined the army
and gone away to France.
You remember the girl
and the hazel tree, don't you, Tommy?
Whoever the boy is, Esme...
Whoever he is, our business is done here.
I brought you to this camp for a reason.
And I brought him as well.
He is yours.
A boy born with hazel eyes.
He calls himself Duke.
His mother is dead. He's a thief.
He works the fairground,
but he says he wants more to life
than big wheels and carousels.
If the losing of Ruby's
left a hole in your heart,
I'll send him to you.
If you give me a bit more gold.
I'll tell him Tommy Shelby can offer a man
far more than big wheels and carousels.
[exhales]
Is our business done or not, Tommy?
[Lizzie] I know where you went.
[exhales]
I'll spend more hours working
in the Commons with Mr Churchill.
His fight is my fight.
I sat like a stone and thought about you
killing someone in her name.
The Shelby institutions will be expanded.
I will set up a fund to research
the causes and cures of consumption.
Did the woman you killed have children?
Ten thousand children
die every year, Lizzie.
Go to bed, Tommy.
I've been reading about new research.
-Stop and close your fucking eyes.
-I will not...
I will not stop!
What is this "good" that you will become?!
[exhales]
I killed a woman.
I killed a woman and three men.
And their bodies will be thrown
aboard the boat like all the other bodies.
But I am stepping off that boat
and onto another boat.
Do you understand?!
Yeah.
The doctor from the sanatorium called
and said that he needs
to speak with you urgently.
But I think you're now
beyond the help of doctors.
Lizzie...
[Lizzie breathing heavily]
Frances said Arthur's here.
[door slams]
[switch flicks]
[Arthur] Tommy?
-Tom?
-[Tommy] Yeah, it's me.
[Arthur] Ah, fuck.
[Tommy exhales]
Arthur, give me a light, will you?
I can't find my lighter.
[exhales]
[sniffs]
Sorry I didn't speak at the wagon, Tom.
Don't be sorry.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for this fucking cup to fill up.
Nearly empty, this barrel.
[scoffs]
Plenty of barrels, Arthur.
Start another barrel.
I thought maybe
they were all full of fucking blood.
[breathes deeply]
The junk, Tom.
Fucks up your mind.
You know, Arthur,
you was already fucked up.
[exhales]
[Tommy] You was fucked up
since you was a kid.
This is my theory.
[clicks tongue]
It's from that time I gave you a beating,
when you was 12 and I was nine.
We were fighting over cigarettes.
Maybe while I had you down on the ground,
I gave you one too many to the head.
It was a draw, though, Tom.
Nah.
I beat you.
I had you pinned.
You actually didn't.
[chuckles softly]
We both agreed.
You're so fucked,
you can't remember, brother.
I do.
I do remember these little things.
[Tommy] I know you do.
So do I.
The fog and the gas is clearing, eh?
[coughs]
[lighter clicks]
Your cup's nearly full, pass it here.
But, Tommy...
[exhales]
You don't drink this stuff any more.
Eh?
You don't drink no more, Tom.
[clicks tongue]
Hell, when Polly was gone, Arthur,
I thought I could just march and march.
I just kept up that fucking left-right,
left-right, left-right,
left-right fucking rhythm.
I'd never have to stop.
Then Ruby went...
and I stumbled and crashed.
Now here I am...
sat on my arse,
on the ground,
like a fucking tunneller...
with my old comrade Arthur.
[exhales sharply]
Yeah.
Remember The January, Arthur?
-The family boat?
-Yeah.
A whole family living on something
the size of ten of these fucking barrels.
Hmm.
Remember that night
at Tile Cross?
Sixteen of us sleeping on the boat.
The coppers come.
We all swim like rats.
Except for Arthur.
Arthur holds them off
with a boat hook, all on his own.
And I remember,
I climbed back up on the lock
and I looked back,
and I saw you
waving that fucking boat hook
in the coppers' faces...
[chuckles]
...on your own.
That's when I realised...
when I had you on the ground,
all them years ago,
it's 'cause you let me win.
[Arthur laughs]
You wanted me to win.
You've wanted me to win ever since.
What chance do I have if you...
start doing that again?
Huh?
You'll stop.
You'll stop
'cause the family needs you to.
[exhales]
It's like that long tunnel
on the Dudley stretch.
Remember Dudley Canal, line number one,
3,172 yards of fucking pitch blackness?
-And rats swimming?
-Yeah.
And then we come round the corner
and there'd be a shaft of light,
and then we'd know.
Yeah.
And then, you and me, we'd both know
it was nearly done.
That's where we are now, Arthur.
Just a few more yards to go.
And you will change your ways.
And I'll change the fucking world.
["Stone Towers" playing]
♪ Like a slumber ♪
♪ In the moss ♪
♪ I could display ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ I have loved you ♪
♪ From the start ♪
♪ But there's cold veneer ♪
♪ Near the cloud of you ♪
♪ Of you ♪
♪ Sit on back in thrones of blue ♪
♪ And inlay black, so righteous you ♪
♪ Bear cold decree ♪
♪ It's dead to me ♪
♪ Sit on through
While your mistakes loom ♪
♪ You're stone-dead blind
And it's drowning all ♪
♪ Your company... ♪
We assumed, at this late hour,
you'd have had dinner.
There are drinks
and sandwiches if you want.
We're not here to eat.
Mr Shelby will be down shortly.
Please tell Mr Shelby on behalf of us all
that changing the world can wait.
[man] He doesn't want to wait.
There is champagne.
Oh, goodie.
Charles?
I heard cars.
[door opens]
-[Frances] Mr Shelby, the guests are...
-I know.
Dad, there's a Bentley and a Rolls Royce.
Yeah.
Go to bed, Charles.
I can't sleep.
I see her when I shut my eyes.
Go to your mum.
She'll be awake.
-She holds on to me.
-[Tommy] Let her hold on to you.
Hear me?
Always let her hold on to you.
Go on.
[Frances] Mr Shelby, the guests said
they would understand...
-Have you served them drinks?
-[Frances] Yes.
Yeah.
I'm okay, Frances.
The agenda is in my head.
I'm okay.
Do I look okay?
If someone touches you, you won't shatter.
Sing it.
Sing it. I love that song.
I...
I can't be singing rebel songs
in a house in grief and mourning.
Sing it to me softly.
Breaks my heart.
Don't look at him, he's English.
He can block his ears.
Darling, should she sing
her rebel IRA song while we wait?
Or would that be inappropriate?
[lighter clicks]
[sniffs] You know, I went to a meeting
of similar intent to this in Berlin.
Attended by the chancellor himself.
And Göring, and Himmler.
It lasted until the sun came up.
We spoke about the future
of the world in a serious way.
When the first rays of light
entered the room,
we all stood and stared at it
as if it were the world to come.
There was no singing, no giggling.
And when breakfast was served
on the terrace overlooking the mountains,
they brought up some Jews.
And while we ate our eggs,
they were forced to eat grass.
And we watched as we sipped our coffee.
We should all remember
this is serious business.
[Mosley clicks tongue] Well, Diana...
Now look what you've done.
You've killed the mood.
[chuckles]
Let her sing her fucking song
to raise our spirits. Go on, please.
♪ In a neat little town
They call Belfast ♪
♪ Apprentice to trade I was bound ♪
♪ And many an hours sweet happiness ♪
♪ Have I spent in that neat little town ♪
♪ A sad misfortune came over me... ♪
["Blackbird" playing]
♪ Blackbird ♪
♪ Sit on my shoulder ♪
♪ And tell me a song... ♪
[chuckles]
Did it break?
-We'll fix it for you.
-[glass shatters]
♪ When I cry ♪
♪ Do you hear in colour ♪
♪ Or black and white, bird? ♪
[indistinct shouting]
♪ The morning is new ♪
♪ But the feeling is old ♪
♪ Intervene, blackbird
And shorten the road ♪
♪ Blackbird, the way I imagined ♪
♪ Love was wrong ♪
♪ I've come ♪
♪ To love him
Like I couldn't fathom, blackbird ♪
[inaudible]
♪ Tap away ♪
♪ I fear and I long ♪
♪ Intervene, Blackbird... ♪
[inaudible]
♪ Shorten the road ♪
[gunshot fires]
♪ Blackbird ♪
♪ Slip into my slumber
And show me a song ♪
♪ When I dream ♪
♪ Do you see in colour ♪
♪ Or at all, bird? ♪
♪ The picture is peaceful
But I dream alone ♪
[horse trotting]
♪ Intervene, blackbird ♪
♪ And shorten the road ♪
She's so beautiful.
[sobbing]
♪ Her eyes they shone like diamonds ♪
♪ I thought her the queen... ♪
-[Mosley] Mr Shelby...
-[Tommy] No, please. No condolences.
Thank you all for coming.
Now let's try and find out how this
new world of ours will look, shall we?
Perhaps, Mr Mosley, we can turn to
what practical things Mr Nelson can do
to further our cause
while he is in the country.
It's me who has the ear
of the president of the United States.
Which is kind of why I'm here, right?
We do indeed have things for you
to whisper into the president's ear.
Tell him we are England.
We are the mood England is in.
And in Ireland,
appeasers to the English abound,
but we represent the true liberated spirit
of the country that populated your own.
I hear about communists in both places.
We are the bulwark against them.
When it comes to the working class,
we could move our people
from republicanism to fascism
with just a nudge.
They trust us.
You ride with hounds, Mr Mosley.
Will you hunt communists?
Oh, my hounds are baying.
Shelby, you run as a socialist.
Mr Shelby has one of the largest
Commons majorities in England.
In the heart of England.
When the time comes,
he'll resign his party whip
and run as an independent.
But underneath, do you truly believe
in the cause, Mr Shelby?
I'm here.
[smacks lips] Mr Nelson,
I'm here four nights...
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Four nights after, and I'm here.
In this room, in this meeting.
I'm here and I'm serious.
Prove it to him.
Prove it, physically.
Perish Judah.
That thing is going to get us killed.
Go to bed.
At school, they've stopped talking to me.
[scoffs]
They say the Black rubs off.
When they come to power,
they'll take her off you.
They're gonna separate us all out.
They'll send her to Africa.
Yeah?
And where will they send you?
Where will they send you, Karl?
You're half Gypsy, so to Egypt maybe?
Something I never told you before
because it wasn't important.
Maybe now it is.
Your dad was Jewish.
He was the son of a tailor in Stechford.
They changed their name to Thorne to stop
the bricks coming through the window.
So where will they send you, Karl?
Mr Nelson, you can
report back to your president
that the aristocracy and the meritocracy
are united in their conviction
that a new order is coming.
Also, Mr Nelson, at present,
our weapons are coming from Germany.
The British are closing
our supply lines down.
We would value a supply from Boston.
[Nelson] Weapons I can give you,
if they're to be used in a good cause.
And while on the subject
of import and export,
Mr Shelby,
in light of our new relationship,
and since you have proven your commitment
in a most extraordinary way,
Boston is now officially open
for the importation of your merchandise.
Good.
[suspenseful music plays]
[music intensifies]
If we have established
what we came here to establish,
perhaps we should all say good night.
[Mosley] Absolutely.
[screaming]
[typewriter clacking]
[Lizzie] That's the same typewriter
you bought me all those years ago.
To help me become more respectable.
Remember?
Yeah.
[typewriter clacking]
[Lizzie] This arrived.
It's from the sanatorium.
I've already paid Ruby's medical bills.
I don't think it's a bill.
It says it's urgent.
From the senior consultant.
[typewriter clacking]
Why didn't you come to bed?
[typing stops]
I'm typing up
my recollection of the meeting.
If I... If I do it straight away,
I can quote people word for word.
The information is more useful
to Mr Churchill if it is word for word.
[typewriter clacking]
[exhales]
I burnt her chair.
[sobbing softly]
The paint on the wood
left a smell in the air.
I didn't open the window.
I quite like the smell.
[sobbing]
[Tommy] Not yet. Not yet.
I have this work to do
'cause now I know that I will change.
That I have to change.
And change for good, Lizzie.
Not just yet.
[typing continues]
[distant telephone ringing]
Hello?
Oh.
[both breathing heavily]
["Do You Love Me?" playing]
♪ She had a heart
Full of love and devotion ♪
♪ She had a mind full
Of tyranny and terror ♪
♪ Well, I try
I do, I really try ♪
♪ But I just err, baby
I do, I error ♪
♪ So come and find me
My darling one ♪
♪ I'm down to the grounds
The very dregs ♪
♪ Here she comes
Blocking the sun ♪
♪ Blood running down
The inside of her legs ♪
♪ The moon in the sky
Is battered and mangled ♪
♪ And the bells in the chapel ♪
♪ Go jingle-jangle
Jingle-jangle ♪
♪ Jingle-jangle
♪ Do you love me? ♪
[banging on door]
I saw him leave.
He keeps this apartment
expressly for this purpose, doesn't he?
[door closes]
Are you following me, Mr Shelby?
I'm flattered.
But why?
When I do business with someone,
I make it my business
to know their secrets.
Mosley's reputation is no secret.
Not him, you.
[lighter clicks]
How did you know I'd come here?
I know things.
I read people's minds, you know...
Little glances across tables. It's a gift.
The whole family.
Witches and sorcerers.
Your uncle will disown you.
Fucking his business partner
behind his back.
[Gina laughs]
You think he has morals?
He's a Catholic.
Men do what they want,
women do what they are told.
Will you tell Michael?
Michael is family.
We are a family healed.
You have no interest in me
or in Michael.
So why don't you just tell me
what you actually want?
[exhales]
You will be with Mosley
when he's in Berlin.
You'll be in the room when he meets
senior members of the German government.
I want to know what is discussed.
And I want to know what is decided.
And if I lie?
I will know.
You know, Michael thinks you're the Devil.
And I think he might actually be right.
That's the other reason I came here.
What are Michael's real intentions
towards me, Gina?
And if you lie, I will know.
Tommy, he intends to complete the deal.
And then you both walk away.
[chuckles softly]
[door closes]
Fuck.
[pen drops]
[sighs]
[exhales]
[fly buzzes]
[knock on door]
Come.
Mr Shelby, Dr Holford.
Send him in.
You said it had to be in person.
Here I am.
You might want to sit down.
[sighs]
Mr Shelby, I know that you are
still grieving for your daughter,
but I have news that cannot wait.
When you were X-rayed and examined
at the sanatorium, ten days ago,
there was no TB found in your lung.
But I am afraid they found something else.
Something related
to your daughter's illness.
They tried
to speak to you at the hospital,
but you were not cooperating.
After your daughter's death,
you could not be found
to be informed in person.
Eventually, as your personal doctor,
they called me.
I didn't offer you tea.
You look like death. Do you want tea?
No.
At the sanatorium,
they conducted blood tests.
The tests suggest
that the shadow you can see
at the base of your skull is not cancer.
It is tuberculoma.
A tubercular growth
caused by the same bacteria as TB.
You may have picked it up
from your daughter.
Once this disease
enters a household, it can run wild.
It can be transmitted with a simple kiss.
It seems the Shelby household
is no exception.
Mr Shelby, as I say,
I am aware that you are still grieving.
But you must understand
this is very serious.
From the size of the tumour,
expansion must have been rapid.
I have no doubt that you are
already experiencing symptoms.
Have you recently suffered seizures?
Bouts of weakness?
Dissociation? Hallucinations?
-[grunts]
-Why didn't you come and see me?
I have work to do.
Am I a danger to others?
No.
Unlike TB, tuberculoma is not infectious.
Mr Shelby, it is not infectious,
but in your case,
I am afraid it is inoperable.
The growth is in your brainstem.
Any attempt to remove it would result
in trauma and brain haemorrhage.
Whilst you were refusing my calls,
I showed your X-rays to three
of the best surgeons in the country.
They all said they would not operate.
That it would be futile.
Of course, you will want
a second opinion for yourself.
Dr Helen Rutherford at St Thomas'.
She is a friend.
[clears throat]
This...
How bad will it get?
As the tumour grows,
the rate of physical
and mental deterioration will increase.
Eventually, you will need
people around you constantly
who love you very much.
How long?
I understand that you have
defeated many enemies, Mr Shelby.
Now you have a new one.
Inside you.
You cannot defeat it.
But you can keep it at bay for a while.
If you live correctly,
if you are determined, and if you fight...
I asked you a question.
So I want an answer.
I don't want your fucking platitudes.
How long before I need people around me
who love me very much?
[door opens]
-Sorry.
-[Tommy] It's fine, Lizzie.
My accountant here was just leaving.
[clears throat]
I will telephone you
when I get back to London.
No, don't have enough time.
You're an accountant,
give me a fucking number now.
[Holford] One year.
Perhaps 18 months.
[clicks tongue] That's fine.
That's all I need to know.
I will adjust
my finances accordingly. Thank you.
I will write you,
explaining the full implications.
Yep, thank you.
Good day.
Something serious?
No. No, just a...
Just a bill I wasn't expecting, and I...
I'll have to pay it.
Can you give me
a minute on my own, Lizzie?
Yeah.
[door closes]
I'm not a devil.
Just an ordinary, mortal man.
[Polly] There will be a war in this family
and one of you will die.
[Tommy] Polly...
Just give me enough time
to do what I have to do.
[Polly] Kill and kill...