[pistol clicks]
[thuds]
Arthur took the bullets out.
On the way back.
He said you stopped
at a crossroads to throw up.
You're not even a soldier any more, Tommy.
You didn't check your weapon.
You're not a soldier, you're a coward.
I heard you pull the trigger.
Leaving your family behind
without a goodbye.
If you still need a way out,
here are six of them.
[mud squelching]
[bullets clink]
[sighs]
Mother...
They let you pass through.
They wouldn't let me pass.
As if there were to be
another consequence.
[breathing heavily]
[telephone ringing echoes]
[telephone ringing]
Hello.
[Laura] Mr Shelby,
I imagine you are curious
as to who it was who prevented
the assassination last night.
If you look out your window,
you'll see a flag of truce.
It's a unit of volunteers
bringing the bodies of your dead to you
to send to heaven in your own way.
Last night's operation
was carried out by soldiers
from three Dublin brigades
of the Irish Republican Army.
We need to keep Mr Mosley alive.
That's all you need to know.
Also, you should know
that saving Mosley's life
wasn't our only intervention last night.
We've made some changes
to the structure of your organisation.
[sawing rope]
[sighs]
Ever since you began to build your empire,
you've had a crutch to lean on.
Last night we kicked away that crutch.
From now on,
it will be us that you lean on.
Please be aware, Mr Shelby,
that the deaths of your people
are your own responsibility,
because you consistently fail
to understand your own limitations.
[phone slams]
[knife slashes]
[sighs]
[sobs softly]
[inhales deeply]
[music box playing]
[fire crackling]
[crackling continues]
Mum...
It was the ambitions and strategies
of one man that caused this.
I swear in the name of Almighty God,
no matter what it takes,
no matter how many lies I have to tell...
...I will take revenge on Tommy Shelby.
Sir.
[in French] The island of Miquelon.
[Tommy in French] The commissioner said
to give us two hours. Someone may die.
If it's me, tell them to call my brother.
[bell rings]
[barman in French] I'm coming.
[bottles rattling]
My name is Thomas Shelby.
I have the meeting room booked.
Uh...
Last night, some drunks broke my windows.
Pigeons got inside the big room.
My wife is clearing them out.
I'm early. I'll wait.
[in English] You want a drink?
I'll have a glass of water, please.
Windows got broke because
a lot of people here are drunk and angry.
You know...
Half the men on this island
made their living bootlegging until today.
The other half fixed their boats.
Maybe you should
take your water into the hall.
[clicks tongue]
[in French] Another bottle of whiskey.
You work for the whiskey company, right?
I'm here on private business.
Where did you learn French?
[Tommy] In France.
[in English] Yeah,
I learned a lot of things in France.
Island is crawling
with you fucking commissary men.
Closing our warehouses down.
Throwing men out of work.
[in French]
Jean-Claude, leave the man alone.
[in English] Ten years
our boat ran whiskey,
down the President Roads to Boston.
-Now we have fucking nothing.
-[cork thuds]
And you sit in front of us
and order fucking water.
Is that meant to be a joke?
No.
I ordered water
because I no longer drink alcohol
of any kind.
[in French] Jean-Claude, please.
Leave it alone.
[in English] You, my friend,
are going to drink a toast.
You will raise your glass
to the poor people of Miquelon
whose lives you bastards have destroyed.
Drink it.
Hey...
Drink.
You're not leaving this bar
until you have raised a toast
to the people of Miquelon.
Okay.
[Jean-Claude gulps]
[Tommy] Okay.
[inhales]
I understand that today,
of all days, you would be angry.
But if you had read my card
instead of burning it,
you would realise
that this is a misunderstanding.
Now, I've been very patient,
given the circumstances,
but you need to sit down
and let me read my newspaper.
[scoffs]
[Jean-Claude in French]
He's a good one, isn't he?
[both grunting]
[Tommy in English] Before this goes
any further, let me explain.
I will not drink your toast
because four years ago I forswore alcohol.
[in French] Fuck!
[in English] No. Don't.
[gunshot fires]
Since I forswore alcohol, I've become
a calmer and more peaceful person.
[in French] What happened?
[in English] Get in.
[sighs]
Sometimes, in moments
of personal conflict,
I can resort to my old ways.
If this were to happen now,
it would indeed
be a black day in Miquelon.
Now, my guests will be arriving shortly.
I need to prepare the room.
Can you show me where?
[telephone thuds and rings]
[Michael in French] Excuse me,
where is the Hotel Robert?
[spits]
[Connor in English] They think
we're distillery men
here to take our whiskey back.
We're late.
He's always early. Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[door opening]
[Polly] There will be a war
and one of you will die.
But which one, I cannot tell.
[footsteps approaching]
Hello, Tommy.
There's a man out there
having his face stitched back up.
That was a misunderstanding.
Hello, Michael.
I wasn't sure what I'd think
when I saw you again, Tom.
Oh, yeah? What do you think?
Since my mother
passed away four years ago,
Tommy and I haven't even spoken.
[Tommy] Well, we've both been very busy.
You've been too busy
to punish the people who killed her.
You know, Michael, when you're dealing
with a very powerful enemy,
taking revenge sometimes requires time.
You have to pick your moment.
That moment will come.
But now we have
a business interest in common.
And any bad blood will be diluted
by time and a practical self-interest.
Well, Tommy, we're all keen
to hear what you have to say.
I'm looking forward to working with
you again, Michael. You look very well.
You too.
How is the family?
[children chattering]
This projector is a gift
from Charlie-fucking-Chaplin.
And he sent it all the way from Hollywood.
Now sit down and watch the film!
Oh, God. No, Elizabeth, don't do that.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
Yes, hi. Is that the Bell Tavern?
If there's a Gypsy in there
called Johnny Dogs,
can you tell him to come
and round up his fucking kids?
It's Christmas. A time for family.
[receiver thuds]
Mum, I was watching that.
Okay, everyone. Okay.
[girl] When's he coming?
We're having this Christmas party early
because tomorrow, me and Charles and Ruby
are going on a big ship to Canada.
-[boy whispers] Canada.
-To be with their daddy.
But we told
Father Christmas about the party
and he brought you all presents.
[children] Yes!
[Ada laughs]
[boy] Race you!
Ada, where the fuck is Father Christmas?
I don't know.
He was supposed to be here by now.
-Yeah.
-Where the fuck are you, Santa?
[imitates gunshots]
[imitates gasping]
[exclaims]
You've got me.
But I've got a gun. You better run!
You'd better run!
[Tommy] Gentlemen, today is
the last day of Prohibition.
But rather than see it
as the end of something,
I believe that,
for men like us, it can present
a new beginning, a new opportunity.
An opportunity I would like to share
with people I know I can trust.
For the last twelve years,
the men of this island
have been making their living
from bootlegging whiskey,
from navigating the waters
and avoiding American border patrols.
But now that whiskey
is about to become legal,
the trade will fall back into the hands
of capitalists from New York,
Boston and Toronto.
But...
when one door closes...
...another one opens.
We can take advantage of the systems
that are in place on Miquelon Island
and offer selected boat crews
the opportunity to carry on working.
But this time with a different cargo.
-You want me to pour?
-No.
Now it's all over the fucking island.
This is an island
with no morals and no opinions.
Just a load of fucking boats
with nothing to carry and nowhere to go
Reason why Miquelon was used
to run whiskey in the first place
is 'cause it sits outside
the territorial waters of both America
and Canada.
Technically, it's French territory.
The FBI, the RCMP have no jurisdiction.
Where do you get this stuff?
I've established a supply chain
over the last four years
with associates in Belfast.
We decided it was time
to break into the American market.
That, my friend,
is the finest opium in the world.
Delivered to my warehouse
in Liverpool directly from Shanghai.
Michael, when it comes to this shit,
you're the expert.
I trust him.
What about the French police?
I've been in communication
with the Miquelon Prefect de Gendarme.
We fought in
two of the same battles in France.
We consider each other comrades.
I have offered my comrade
twelve million francs
if the boats between
Miquelon and Boston keep running.
We will have to take your proposal
to Uncle Jack in Boston.
Perhaps we can meet after
you've spoken with Uncle Jack, Michael.
Who I believe is your wife's uncle?
-Jack Nelson.
-[Connor] Hey! [chuckles]
The guy knows things
that can get him killed,
and he says them out loud.
I have a high regard for Mr Nelson.
He has a history not unlike my own.
Jack Nelson's past is forgotten.
[Connor] Not forgotten.
Fucking gone.
[Tommy] No, not gone.
Just erased from the records like my own.
Give him my regards, will you?
You haven't touched your drink, Tom.
You know, since we last met, Michael...
Well, I've become a better man.
I now realise that whiskey is just fuel
for the loud engines inside your head.
[men laughing]
Catch yourself on.
What is this guy, a fucking poet? Huh?
Oh, I do read poetry,
but I don't yet write it.
They say the fog is going to get worse.
Better get off this island
before it traps us here.
Just understand,
Uncle Jack decides everything. Okay?
And I decide when the meeting is over.
So sit down till I say.
[scoffs]
[clears throat]
[liquid pours]
[in French] My brother.
[in English] Put some fucking hair
on your chest? Huh?
Good boy.
[men chuckle]
Now, give us all a poem before we go.
Want to hear a poem? Want to hear a poem?
What about you?
Brainbox?
[sighs]
I was angry with my friend
I told my wrath, my wrath did end
I was angry with my foe
I told it not
My wrath did grow
It's from The Poison Tree
by William Blake.
You won't have heard of him.
Meeting over.
Oh, and by the way,
my friend, the police commissioner,
told me that he'd spoken
to his FBI liaison officer,
and he told him that there is an informant
in your organisation in South Boston.
I tell you this
in the spirit of corporate hygiene.
Here you are, Michael.
Beware the man
with a bleeding-heart tattoo
with "Maria" written in red.
Have a good day, gentlemen.
[man] Don't bother.
This time, don't burn it.
[in French] Every catastrophe
is also an opportunity.
[Ada] Arthur.
[clicks tongue]
Come on. Come on.
God.
God. If Polly was still here,
she'd never have let it get this bad.
Come on.
Come on, Arthur.
Arthur!
I'm not Polly,
but I am still your fucking sister.
You swore to me you would stop using.
[Arthur sniffs]
It's Christmas Day, Ada. Christmas Day.
Yes, it's Christmas.
So where the fuck
are the fucking presents?
I'll be all right in a bit...
[Ada sighs]
Great.
My brother off his face on junk.
[Arthur groans]
Every day is a question without an answer.
A leak without a bucket.
Me without a clue what to do.
Fuck!
[Arthur] I love you, Ada.
[children chattering]
[man] Children, Father Christmas has been.
[children] Father Christmas!
[boy] Go. Go on.
[girl] What did you ask for?
[man] What have we got?
Father Christmas got
stuck up the chimney again, did he?
[Ada] Mmm.
What ship are you on tomorrow?
[sighs]
Oh, the best, most expensive one.
And then we'll get there.
And Tommy will say,
"Hello, Lizzie. Hello, children."
In that dead voice.
Come on, Lizzie.
He'll be on holiday.
Being away might change him.
Even on holiday, Ada.
Even on top of a rocky mountain,
he'll be the same way
he's been since Polly died.
No more Polly,
no more whiskey, no more Tommy.
[Tommy sighs]
[bird chirping]
[in French] Put me through
to Detective Lawrence
at St John's Harbour Marine Police.
[in English] Yeah, I'm calling from
Miquelon Island. From the police station.
There is a boat leaving the island
now, heading across the border.
When it docks at St John's,
a man named Michael Gray
will board a ferry to Boston.
Listen very carefully.
He's wearing a dark coat, a blue suit
and carrying a black briefcase.
Inside the briefcase
is five pound of pure, refined opium.
A concerned citizen.
Yeah, my name is Mr Jones.
[receiver thuds]
[sighs]
[commissioner in French] You want a drink?
-[rubs hands]
-[in English] Yes, I do.
But I don't drink any more.
[commissioner in French] Why?
[Tommy sighs]
I have business.
I need to get off this island.
[telephone rings]
[Ada] You shouldn't be in here, Karl.
[telephone ringing]
Are you gonna answer it?
No, I don't work for him any more.
It might be important.
[Ada] That's why
I don't want to answer it.
[ringing continues]
-Can I answer it?
-No.
[Ada sighs]
Hello.
Mmm-hmm.
Fuck!
[indistinct chattering]
Do you know who this man is?
[sighs]
All right. Come on, Arthur.
Ada...
[Arthur groans]
Hey, that tickles.
His brother, Thomas Shelby,
says don't serve him opium ever again.
Or someone will write Arthur Shelby's name
on your chest with a bayonet.
So... What the fuck?
I can't talk about anything in here.
I just wanted to see your face
and smell your perfume.
Tommy Shelby steps back into your life
and right away, this is what happens?
-No names in here.
-Sorry.
-Let's just call him the Devil.
-Take a seat.
[sighs] How is Laurence?
Oh, you know, missing his father.
What the fuck happened, Michael?
-It's in hand.
-Whose hand?
No, really.
Whose fucking hand, Michael?
Huh?
Like everything else in this city,
it's in the hand of your Uncle Jack.
I need him to get the charges lifted
and get me out of here.
I already talked to him.
He told me what the Devil proposed.
Tommy Shelby wants
to do business with Jack Nelson?
He wants to take on Boston?
No one is taking on anyone.
It's in hand. There are deals
being made at a high level,
but there are some people at the middle
and lower levels who cannot be trusted.
-Michael, this sounds fucking...
-Shut up and listen.
It was Tommy himself
who warned us of the informant.
We're guessing that the informant
tipped off the police about me.
Then the Devil's plan has already begun.
What's the point of ships and planes
if you can't get away?
Gina, in today's paper,
you'll read about a man
being fished out of the Boston Harbour
with a bleeding-heart tattoo
and the name "Maria" written on his arm.
Single shot to the head.
Yeah, I know. I read it already.
His death will lead to others.
For this business to work,
we must only use men we trust.
And while the clean-up
is being carried out,
you must keep things to yourself.
You talk loose to anyone,
it'll be me in the harbour
and you'll be the Maria
with the bleeding heart. Understand?
Michael, I just want the truth.
No, fuck that. I need the truth.
Why are you doing business with him again?
Gina, tell me what you're thinking
of getting Laurence for Christmas.
There are plenty of men
who can supply powder all over the world.
I don't understand why it needs to be him.
[Michael sighs]
Some of my business
with Tommy Shelby is unfinished.
This is my opportunity to finish it.
So speak to your uncle
and get me the fuck out of here.
[upbeat music playing]
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Who?
Sure.
Why the hell not?
[chuckling]
[music continues]
I heard you were in town,
and I thought, "Well, hey..."
"Little man hitting the big time."
-You like jazz?
-[Tommy] No.
[jazz music plays louder]
[music stops]
What do you want, whiskey?
Water.
I don't have any water.
What else do you want?
I have a message for your Uncle Jack.
[Gina] Tommy, relax.
Have a fucking drink.
You know, my uncle is planning on buying
the United States import licence
to all the best Scotch
and Irish whiskey distilleries?
[glass thuds]
He's on his way to London
right now to make those deals.
Every drop in every state
will be another dime for Uncle Jack.
Yep. He's a very powerful,
very impressive man.
I've only seen photographs
when he was young.
Police mug shots.
And more recently
in high society magazines.
I think this represents progress.
[Gina] Yeah.
And before you tell me
what you want me to tell him,
I have a message from him to you.
No deal.
Hmm.
In England, when someone gets this close
to Tommy Shelby, it's, "Oh, the horror."
"Oh, the desire."
To fall on your knees,
open your mouth and say, "Yes, sir."
"Please, sir."
So it's Uncle Jack
you fall on your knees for, eh?
Not Michael?
He says no deal, Mr Shelby.
You smell of jail, Gina.
-And you drink too much.
-[chuckles]
Yes, but booze is legal.
Your white powder is not.
Jack has friends in the government now.
You have any idea of how far he's risen?
All the way to the fucking top.
Can't have white powder
on his shiny, black boots
when he's meeting
the president of the United States.
'Cause, yeah, that's where he goes now.
So he can't really be taking
such a big risk on such a little deal.
Go home, boy.
Bye-bye, Mr Shelby.
Yeah, you have another whiskey, Gina.
Another dime for Uncle Jack.
You mind if I smoke?
If it's legal, it's okay.
Before I go,
you should know...
that it was me
who tipped off the border police
about the contents of Michael's suitcase.
I'm the reason he's in jail.
I wanted to give your uncle a dilemma.
His favourite niece's husband
banged up in Boston for smuggling opium.
What does he do?
If he intervenes, has him released,
how'll that play in the Oval Office?
If he does nothing,
how does that play in South Boston?
Oh, fuck you.
Fine.
Stay here.
Deal here, die here,
for all I fucking care.
[music starts]
Die at whose hand, Gina?
[music stops abruptly]
My message to your uncle is this.
If he doesn't want to buy my opium,
I will sell to the East Boston Jews.
[Gina] Oh, baby.
Do you want to start a fucking war?
With that amount of opium,
the balance of power
between the Irish,
the Jewish and the Italians
would shift heavily in favour of the East.
I have excellent contacts
with the family that runs East Boston.
The Solomons family.
Maybe you've heard of 'em?
Once you people have accepted
that you must treat us as equals...
then I think our families
will work together very well.
Have a good day, Gina.
[kicks speaker and music resumes]
[telephone ringing]
[sighs] Yep?
Yes, I'll accept the call.
[Tommy] Hello, Lizzie.
Tommy...
It's Ruby, she's not well.
She's got a temperature of 101.
Doctor's just left.
What did he say?
He says he thinks it's flu.
But he's gonna come later to check on her.
She's been coughing, and...
[sighs]
Tommy, he said it's...
not a good idea for us to travel.
We can't board that ship to Boston today.
That's all right, Lizzie, don't worry.
Don't worry, you just stay there
for now and get her better and...
[clears throat] Can I speak to her?
She's sleeping.
Yeah. Well, let her sleep.
Let her sleep.
Lizzie, I've a bit more
business to do here.
Look, you just book a new passage
when Ruby's feeling better.
Doesn't matter if you're not here
for Christmas. Just get here.
And then I'll get this business done.
You get here with the children,
and then no more.
And it'll just be us
and the clean air out in the West.
I found a place in the mountains.
There'll be snow.
Tell Ruby I'll build her a snowman.
[Lizzie chuckles]
[Tommy sighs]
How long has she been coughing?
A few days. She's been out
running wild with Johnny Dogs' kids
out in the cold by the river.
[sighs]
Are you okay, Tommy?
Your voice, it sounds different.
It's just cold.
I'll get this business done in Boston.
That'll be the end of it.
Then I just want to...
I just want to pick Ruby up
and hold her in my arms, you know?
I miss the weight of carrying her.
I gave her her presents early.
She loves them.
Last night she was burning up.
She was delirious. She kept talking.
Johnny's kids have been
teaching her to speak Gypsy.
[chuckles]
Teaching her to rob and steal, more like.
[chuckles] Yeah.
When she was delirious,
she kept saying these Gypsy words...
"Tickner Maura, Tickner Maura,
O Beng, O Beng." Over and over again.
What? Lizzie, what...
What did you say? What did Ruby say?
Tickner. Tickner Maura...
Something like that.
Did she say any other words
that you didn't understand?
O Beng. I don't know...
No, Lizzie, did she say any other words
in Romany? Fucking listen to me.
I don't know Romany words, Tommy.
I don't think so.
Just "Tickner Maura" and "O Beng"?
Yes.
She see anything when she was burning up?
-What could she see?
-Fuck.
Please just answer the fucking question!
She said she could see a man.
A man with green eyes.
She was delirious. She was burning up.
What the fuck is the matter?
All right, listen, Lizzie,
I'm coming home.
It's just a fever, love.
I'm coming home on the next steamer.
You keep her out of school,
and you keep her away from...
-Tommy...
-Keep her away from the river.
Don't let her ride a horse
or go near a horse.
Tell Johnny Dogs and his wives
the words that Ruby has been saying.
Do you hear me? Tell Johnny's eldest wife
to put a Black Madonna around her neck.
You listen to Esmeralda
the same way you listen to a doctor.
-You hear me?
-Fucking Gypsy stuff.
Yes, it is Gypsy fucking stuff, Lizzie!
Yes, it fucking is!
-[scoffs]
-And you get Curly there.
Tell him to stay in the stable
with Ruby's horses.
And you do everything that Johnny Dogs
and his wives fucking tell you.
Do you understand me?
I'm sorry, Lizzie. Do you understand?
Okay.
I'll do it.
All right, I'm coming home.
[receiver bangs]
[sighs]
Polly?
They know I'm trying to get out.
Pol, they're coming for me.
[footsteps echo]
-You son of a fucking bitch.
-[Tommy] You sound American, Michael.
I have to go back to England early.
Let's make this quick, eh?
-You just fuck people up and you run away.
-No, this business will continue.
Jack Nelson is also travelling to England.
To London and to Edinburgh
to buy import licences.
How do you know
where Jack Nelson is going?
Well, I have copies of his itinerary.
Of his personal correspondence.
Letters from the president of
the United States and his many mistresses.
I have contacts in his organisation.
An Irishman with a mortgage
is a powerful resource, Michael.
You're dead, Tommy.
You're out of your fucking depth.
You're dead already.
You threatened to sell to the Jews.
I have contacts in this prison. These boys
will look after you during your stay.
I don't need your people to look after me.
-Jack Nelson's getting me out of here.
-[Tommy] Yeah?
Is he?
This is a letter...
Here, give him this letter, will you?
This is a letter
from the president's personal secretary,
suggesting Jack Nelson
keep you in here for a while longer.
Just until the press
lose interest, Michael.
Fuck you.
[Tommy] You'll be released eventually.
And then you can execute
your business with me as before.
Our business being five million dollars
for a shipment of powder.
And when the exchange is done,
we can shake hands
and go our separate ways once more, eh?
So, you didn't learn.
When my mother died
at the hands of your ambition,
you didn't learn your limitations.
I have no limitations.
Oh, and by the way, Michael,
according to
Jack Nelson's personal accounts,
he bought passage for five people
from Boston to Liverpool.
Five people. His wife, his mistress,
President Roosevelt's son, himself,
and Gina Gray.
Gina's coming to London, Michael.
Where I'll be happy
to show her the sights.
Fuck! You fucking bastard, Tommy!
-Spirits, Boston-Irish, Uncle Jack.
-[Michael] You're the Devil!
-The fucking Devil!
-I'm ready for the conversation.