Mr Churchill...
If there are bodies to be buried,
dig holes and dig them deep.
Don't do this in here.
You're taking me away from my baby!
Freddie! Ada!
It wasn't me
who shopped Freddie Thorne.
He trusts me. I told you that.
I think I know where
the guns are hidden.
I want your word that
Thomas Shelby will not be harmed
if the guns are recovered.
It would be an honour
to work with you, Mr Kimber.
Nobody works with me.
People work FOR me.
A black star? What does that mean?
Black star day is the day we take
out Billy Kimber and his men.
Grace...will you marry me?
You deserve better.
Is it him?!
Where is he? He left.
With the barmaid.
Service.
HE KNOCKS AT DOOR
We don't open two more hours.
You come back later.
Police.
Inspector Campbell, sir.
Any trouble, sir?
Look...
I know.
That is, I am given to understand
by several of my officers...
HE CLEARS HIS THROAT
..several of my officers,
that people come here...
..that men come here for...
a certain purpose.
MUSIC: "Red Right Hand"
by Nick Cave and The Bad Seeds
Arthur? Arthur, wake up.
Get home, get bathed.
Check your kit, check your weapons.
Why?
What's going on?
We're doing it today.
♪ Where secrets lie
in the border fires
♪ In the humming wires
♪ Hey man, you know
you're never coming back... ♪
Fetch the wagons, Charlie.
It's today.
♪ On a gathering storm
comes a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat
♪ With a red right hand... ♪
BOY: Dad? Our Katie's done
a wee in the bed again.
I'll be there in a minute, mate.
BANGING AT DOOR
John, I've told you
to keep the doors locked.
I could've been anyone.
Get dressed.
We're doing it today.
As a matter of fact,
he's doing me today.
Make sure he's done you by nine.
You should learn to knock!
It's not a day for knocking.
Dear Lord, make this day pass well.
Let none get hurt
and make them that do not Shelbys.
Watch John,
cos he has so many
depending on him.
Watch Arthur
because he's as likely to hurt
himself as anyone else.
Watch Thomas.
I know how he is.
But he does what he does for us.
I think.
Amen.
I used to do that every
morning during the war.
I hoped I'd done
it for the last time.
Today will be the last time, Poll.
After today,
there'll be no need for prayers.
We'll be set.
Family meeting, half ten.
I'm sorry I kept you.
It is so early.
Yes. I-I...
I didn't sleep last night.
Mr Zhang said you are special,
special customer.
Do you want to sit?
Do you want to take off your boots?
Yes.
And...this.
So tight.
We can also clean and press
your shirt while we do this.
That's a very efficient service.
You never been to
a place like this before?
It's OK.
Sometimes old men who have
lost their wives, they come here...
all the time.
Old men?
I am so old?
No! I mean I am young.
Anyway...
I'll make you young as well.
Whore.
'Dear Grace.
'I write this letter to you
with a heavy heart.
'I know exactly what you did,
and with whom.
'I will not mention
any of it in my report.
'However, you should be aware that
I know you gave yourself to the man
'who is our sworn enemy.
'That is not only treason,
'it is disgusting
beyond all measure.
'Your father would be
ashamed of you.
'And as for myself...
I am beyond desolation.
'You have betrayed every principle
'and standard of honour
that was your birthright.
'And for what?'
THEY GASP
Love.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
Did I do that?
It's OK.
You are special, special customer.
Would you sit with me for a moment?
Please.
ZHANG AND CHIN SPEAK IN CHINESE
For the suits.
You want to hear something funny?
WHISPERS: Campbell was in the back
room with one of my girls.
GUN COCKS
I am unarmed.
It's curious, Inspector.
I thought you came here
to clean up the city.
Not to sleep with its whores.
You're no different from any other
copper that came before you.
I'm no different from those
who would follow
should I choose to leave.
You've no reason to stay.
You have what you came for.
Yes. I have what I came for.
I have a meeting with
Mr Winston Churchill at midday.
And no doubt he intends to
congratulate me
on finding those stolen guns.
And you still don't know
how we found them, do you?
Good.
Oh, you got lucky.
Did I?
Yeah.
One thing I have learned...
..is that you and I are opposites,
but also just the same.
Like an image in a mirror.
We hate people.
And they in turn hate us.
And fear us.
Before the day is over,
your heart will be broken...
..just the same as mine.
Men like us, Mr Shelby...
..will always be alone.
And what love we get...
..we will have to pay for.
You forget, Inspector.
I have my family.
Enjoy your day.
BABY CRIES
Oh, little one...
You're much better
with him than I am.
He settles quicker with me
cos he can't smell the milk.
You're tired. Let's put him down.
Mine were terrors for the tit.
Both of them.
Well, you never knew
my children, did you?
No, I was a child myself, then.
You never talk about them.
Never had reason to.
My heart breaks even
when I think about them.
But today...
I do have reason to.
Sit down, Ada.
They were three and five years old.
Sally was three,
Michael was five. Well...
two weeks away from being six.
It was Sunday morning.
I was at church.
"You're not forgiven."
This...pinch-faced bitch said
to me, "You're not forgiven."
You see, some sheets I washed
and hung on the line
had the name of a hotel on them.
They'd been stolen in a robbery,
and they said some porter
at the hotel had been coshed.
And a woman from round here told
the police about the sheets -
jealous, you see, of the new sheets.
And when the police came,
they found a spirit still
for making a few drops of gin.
And for that...
..they took my children from me.
And they never told me
where they took them.
And they did it cos they could.
And cos I was weak.
But they will never take
your baby away from you.
Do you know why?
Cos Tommy wouldn't let them.
Cos Tommy won't let them
walk all over us.
Now it is Tommy who has given
strength and power to this family.
Cos he knows...
..you have to be as bad as them
above in order to survive.
I'm telling you this
cos I want you to forgive him.
How can I?
When my Freddie's rotting
in jail because of him.
There's something about today
you need to know.
KEY CLANKS IN LOCK
All right, Freddie, time to go.
I want to get a message to Campbell.
I can't let them move me to Brixton.
If I go to Brixton,
they'll kill me.
Freddie.
You're not going to
get as far as Brixton prison.
On your feet.
I told the Prime Minister personally
that the guns had been retrieved
and he actually heard me
and listened,
and I'm pretty sure
he gave me a half smile.
He never usually smiles
unless a political opponent dies.
HE CHUCKLES
I plan to put your name forward
in the New Year's Honours list...
That would be too much, sir.
Nonsense. You deserve it.
As I recall, you wrote to me several
times about an undercover operative.
A woman.
Was she involved in the discovery?
Does she deserve
some kind of commendation?
Yes.
She was instrumental.
A truly loyal servant of the crown.
And that is what
the record should state.
And what of the men
who actually stole the guns?
The Peaky...
Blinders, sir.
If we were to make arrests,
the whole thing would
end up in open court,
and I know we wish to keep
this matter confidential.
So they'll go free?
Not quite, sir.
You see, I have plans
for the Peaky Blinders.
All right.
All right. All right, mate?
Leave that, boys,
come back to it later.
Right.
I've brought you all here today
because this is the day
we replace Billy Kimber.
This is the day
we become respectable.
The day we join the official
National Association...
of Race Course Bookmakers.
But first...
we do the dirty work.
We've all known it's been coming.
I just haven't told anyone the date.
We're going to the Worcester races.
The track opens at one,
we get there at two.
Now, Kimber thinks we're going there
to help him fight the Lee brothers.
But thanks to the efforts
of our John,
and his lovely new wife Esme,
the Lees are now our kin.
I interrupted those efforts
this morning, and, er...
LAUGHTER
I can assure you all,
John is making great sacrifices
in the cause of peace.
Yeah, all right.
So, it'll be us and the Lees
against Kimber's boys.
We take them out,
then leave the bookies.
I expect a swift victory which will
send a signal all the way to London,
that we believe in letting
legitimate businesses run peacefully.
And, er...
What about Kimber himself?
I'll deal with Kimber.
Any other questions?
Yes.
Oh, does anyone object if I bring
a newcomer to the meeting?
Come on.
I'd like to introduce the newest
member of the Shelby clan.
Welcome home, Ada.
We named him Karl.
After Karl Marx.
LAUGHTER
Karl bloody Marx?
Let me get a look at him.
Oh, here we go.
Eh, look.
He looks just like me, look.
LAUGHTER
That's his arse looks like you,
Arthur. He's all right.
He's a Shelby.
Well, Ada?
Am I forgiven?
If what Aunt Polly says is true,
you are.
It's true.
Thank you, Tommy.
So, who the hell are you?
Someone who wants to keep his eyes.
They came to my house.
Told me to volunteer for this.
Who did?
Peaky blinders.
MUSIC: "The Prowl"
by Dan Auerbach
Tommy, Tommy, Tommy...
♪ I see you walkin after dark
♪ Trading looks with other men
♪ But I'm the only one you need
♪ And I know just where you've been
♪ Oh, can't you see the tears I cried
♪ And soak them up like a towel... ♪
Get out of the way!
What the bloody hell is that?
Looks like your friends are here.
Stay down on the ground.
Or the next one's for you.
Make it look good.
I am sorry about this, comrade.
Holy shit.
Danny, you're dead.
Nah. I've been living in London.
Same thing.
In you get.
All right, lads, listen up.
You have a pint and a chaser,
no more.
On the house.
Right. Let's get pouring.
Do you have the enclosure tickets?
And the register of book-keepers
on the track?
In me coat.
You did a good job, Grace.
That's what it is, innit?
The next family meeting,
I'll make sure you're there.
If I were family. But I'm not.
That could change.
Tommy... We'll talk about it more
when I get back. All right?
When will you be back?
Oh, is this how it's going to be, eh?
You waiting at home for me, saying,
"What time do you call this?"
The barrel needs changing.
Go on, Tommy, go out the back,
give her a good seeing to
before we go.
THEY CHUCKLE
Grace...
Hey, Grace, I was joking.
JOHN BANGS ON THE BAR
Tommy, we need more mild!
Just help yourselves.
Tommy, the truth is
when you come back from the races,
I won't be here.
What are you talking about?
All right, look.
Grace, I know you weren't born
to be with a man like me...
But I'm turning things around.
And when I get back here tonight...
I will have one of the biggest legal
racetrack syndicates in the country.
And I'm going to close down
some of that other stuff.
Maybe open a club, hey?
Like in London.
And another thing.
You have a contract of employment.
With a real limited company.
You remember?
I remember everything, Tommy.
I am going to make a success of this.
I am going to make a success of it.
I am. I know. I know.
And I'm not talking about marriage.
I'm...
We know each other. We can talk.
We're the same...
Tommy, I have done
something terrible to you.
DOOR OPENS
Right, tell him
what you just told me.
Just heard there's two vans driving
up the Stratford Road.
An old corporal of mine
said he recognised some of the men.
He said it's Kimber boys,
and they're heading this way.
Ada, wake up.
You and the baby get into the Bull
Ring, where there's lots of people.
What's going on?
We've been fucking betrayed.
Someone let slip.
Kimber's men are on their way here.
Yeah, but you can handle them,
Tommy? It's just us.
All the Lees are on their way
to Worcester. We're outnumbered.
Fuck!
Who else knew today was the day
you were moving on Kimber?
You said you kept it a secret.
Who else did you tell?
There's only one thing can blind
a man as smart as you, Tommy.
Love.
It was that barmaid.
I'll deal with Grace.
If you set eyes on her again,
you might kill her.
Going for good?
I heard there was trouble.
Instinct's a funny thing.
See, normally I can tell about
a person. But with you...
Look, the fighting's about to begin.
We should get out of here.
We know who you are.
Tommy knows as well.
Turned out that copper as good
as told him this morning.
But I wanted to hear
it from your own lips.
I am an agent of the crown.
I have the power to arrest
and the right to use force.
So, please, step out of my way.
Like I say,
instinct's a funny thing.
You fell for Tommy for real,
didn't you?
This gun is loaded.
I'm not afraid of you.
I feel sorry for you.
Slip of a thing.
Thought you'd come in here
and stitch us all up.
I mean, we've had some copper's
narks in here, but you?
You're the queen of them all.
So, who are you?
Rich girl, I'd guess. Unionist.
Ulster Volunteer.
You thought Fenians,
communists, low people...
they're all the same.
Scum.
Then you met Tommy.
I'll fight you with my fists
and show you how a rich girl fights.
I'm from a tough family, too.
Nah.
We women have more sense.
Why don't you pour us both a drink?
So, am I right?
Did you fall for Tommy?
Yes. Then I pity you.
I think he'll try to kill me.
He's too soft. Soft?
Soft. Like you.
You saved his life
the night the coppers came.
That's why we're drinking,
not fighting.
We owe you.
What was he like...before France?
He laughed, a lot.
He wanted to work with horses.
He won medals.
Threw them in the cut.
Ah, not a single man
came back the same.
You know, after all this is over...
..he might forgive you.
He might take you in.
You can never tell with men.
They go for whoever
their dicks point at,
and there's no changing their minds.
But I should tell you something.
I will never forgive you.
Or accept you.
Or take you in.
And it's me who runs the business
of the heart in this family.
And as far as I'm concerned,
you're a snitch from the Parish.
And if you're not gone
from this city by tomorrow...
I'll kill you myself.
Now, go.
Maybe what really upsets you
is the thought that one day
you might lose him.
Tommy.
We've had word from Nipper
at Hay Mills,
and he says the police
are letting them through.
And how come all our police
have disappeared?
Because it was the police
who told Kimber about our plan.
And who told the police?
You know what, John?
For all I think I'm the smart one...
I'm guessing it was me.
All right, men...
..you were mostly in the war,
so you know that battle plans
always change and get fucked up.
Well, here it is.
Things have changed.
We fight them here. Today. Alone.
Now, they're going
to come for the pub.
They're going to try
to break us up for good.
And we'll have no help
from the law today.
That pub there is called
the Garrison.
Well, now it really is one.
And it belongs to us, right?
ALL: Right!
How many are there?
Jeremiah says two Riley vans.
So I reckon we're outnumbered
three to one.
Ah... Fuck.
But it's us, boys. It's us.
The Small Heath Rifles.
Never lost a fight yet, did we?
ALL: No!
All right. Jeremiah.
I know you vowed to God to never
pick up a weapon again.
But can you ask him from me
if you can help us today?
God says he don't deal
with Small Heath, sir.
Good man.
Arthur, Scudboat.
You take the flanks.
Just like at St Marie. Sir.
Curly, if any Shelby man dies
here today, you bury us side by side.
All right. We've about ten minutes.
Make your peace with whoever.
We've had a report of a large
group of men in vehicles
heading towards the city.
Most of them
are known to the police, sir.
We think a gang fight's
about to break out.
I want all officers and constables
stood down in the following areas.
Bordesley, Small Heath,
Shard End, Greet...and Hay Mills.
Stood down, sir? Immediately.
And the vehicles approaching
the city should not be impeded.
What the hell is going on?
Let dog eat dog.
Let the beasts devour each other.
And then we shall pick the bones.
She's gone, then?
You're not accustomed to not getting
what you want, are you, Tommy?
You wanted my pub and you took it.
You got a fair price.
What I got was an ultimatum.
Like you give to everybody.
Do it, or else.
And yet, it's funny.
Everybody round here,
they want you to win this battle.
I think, what it is...
you're bad men,
but you're our bad men.
Will you go looking for her?
She's in the past.
The past is not my concern.
The future is no longer
my concern, either.
What is your concern, Tommy?
The one minute.
The soldier's minute.
In a battle, that's all you get.
One minute of everything at once.
And anything before is nothing.
Everything after...
nothing.
Nothing in comparison...
to that one minute.
Didn't you get enough
minutes over there?
Seems not, doesn't it?
DOOR OPENS
Tommy, they're here.
Get your weapons out, boys,
and load 'em up.
Take your time.
Hold 'em up in the air
so as they can see what we've got.
All guns and no balls, right,
Billy boy?
So, what do we do now?
Just give the order.
The men that have arrived in
Garrison Lane are armed with rifles.
Did you hear me?
Their methods of self-destruction
are not my concern.
Well, we've also had report
of machine gun fire in Saltleigh.
The ravings of an old soldier
with shell shock.
We only found 24
of those 25 Lewis guns.
If they were to get
to use the one...
You know, when, er...
when you came here from Belfast
I was overjoyed.
I was sick of this force, and I was
sick of all the corruption.
When you made that speech
about cleaning this place up,
I gave a little cheer inside.
You said it was the devil's work
to look the other way.
I am not looking the other way,
Sergeant Moss.
I am looking directly
at the events of the day.
And I like what I see.
It doesn't have to be
like this, Kimber.
Too late for all that.
You've bit off more than you can
chew, you little toerag.
And now I'm going to take over
this shithole. Oh?
We have to use guns...
let's use proper guns.
Sergeant Thorne
reporting for duty, sir.
You were saying
something about being out-gunned.
ADA: Move!
BABY CRIES
What are you doing?
I believe you boys call
this "no-man's land."
Ada... Shut up and listen.
Have you lost your mind?
I said shut up!
Now, most of you were in France.
So you all know what happens next.
I've got brothers and a husband here
but you've all got somebody
waiting for you.
Now, I'm wearing black
in preparation.
I want you to look at me.
I want you all to look at me.
Who'll be wearing black for you?
Think about them.
Think about them right now.
And fight if you want to,
but that baby ain't moving anywhere.
And neither am I.
KIMBER: She's right, you know.
Why should all you men die?
It should just be them
who's caused it.
VOICES ECHO
Don't shoot!
You're all right, son.
You're all right.
Ada, move away.
Don't shoot!
Hold your guns up!
Enough.
Kimber and me fought
this battle one on one.
It's over.
Go home to your families.
Scudboat, Curly...pick him up.
DOOR OPENS
I want to ask you one question.
Then I'll leave.
Tommy knows who I am.
What did you say to him?
I told him...
..that his heart would be broken
before the day was over.
So, it seems...
..you've broken two hearts, Grace.
As well as my own.
That's it, Tommy, that's it.
Bite it, Tommy.
Take it. Take it!
Hold him still. That's it, lad.
Come on. Come on!
That's it.
There! I still have the knack.
Have a drink.
Right, deep breath.
Augh!
That's it. It's done.
Now we can bury him properly
in the grave we dug for him.
Yeah.
It's high on a hill. He'll like that.
To Danny Whizz-Bang. Danny.
May we all die twice.
To Danny Whizz-Bang.
Danny Whizz-Bang.
Come on.
The day is ours, let's celebrate.
Well?
Who won?
A Mr William Kimber has been found
dead with a gunshot wound.
So, I'm guessing that means
the Peaky Blinders won.
Sir.
Also, the communist agitator
Freddie Thorne
was taken from his transport
by armed men.
Since there were no police officers
on the street at the time...
following your orders...
he managed to escape easily
and is now at large.
The prison officers said they
recognised the men.
They were Peaky Blinders
as well, sir.
I mean, we could go down there
and make a few arrests
but, er, no-one will have
seen anything.
And there were no officers there
to witness, so...
..the Shelbys will get away
with murder.
Just like they always have.
Some things never change.
Eh, sir?
ROWDY CELEBRATION
Get us some of that!
Come here, son.
Wey! Keep it going!
A toast...
A toast, to Shelby Limited!
ALL: Shelby!
He's got sons.
Should we find work for them?
No. Let them be.
Let them find ordinary work
like ordinary men.
Could you put me through
to Mr Churchill, please?
Yes, sir.
Sir...
I have made a decision
about my future.
Everyone's leaving town.
Tommy, you're hurt. I'm fine.
What exactly can I say?
I don't know, Grace.
I could tell you who I really am.
I think I know who you are.
And you know who I am.
The circumstance is not important.
Circumstance? Is all it is.
Just uniform.
Yeah.
Someday I will throw
this gun in the canal.
Why not now?
Here it comes, Tommy.
I love you.
And there it goes, Grace.
Away it goes.
We can say it as much as we like...
..but there's no chance.
I'll be in London one week.
This address.
Finish your business here
and join me.
I have an idea.
DOOR OPENS
There he is... Tommy. Drink?
Not whisky.
If you check behind the bar...
you will find a bottle of champagne.
The one she bought.
Today was a good day.
All of Kimber's men were busy here,
so the Lee boys took all the pitches
at the Worcester races.
It couldn't have gone better
if we'd planned it.
Shelby Brothers Limited
are now the third largest legal race
track operation in the country.
Cheers! Only the Sabinis and the
Solomons are bigger than us, boys.
And all my family is here
to celebrate.
To Shelby Brothers Limited.
Shelby! Brothers!
Cheers.
There'll be others.
To the others.
All of them.
MUSIC: "Love Is Blindness"
by Jack White
♪ Love is blindness
♪ I don't wanna see
♪ Won't you wrap the night
♪ Around me
♪ Oh, my heart
♪ Love is blindness... ♪
'Dear Grace...
'Without a secretary,
I write my own letters
'and I write without malice.
'I learnt long ago
to hate my enemies.
'But I've never loved one before.
'The idea of New York
is interesting
'but I have worked
so hard for this day,
'for this victory.
'I have responsibilities here
'for people I need to protect
and people who I love.
'Before the war, when I had
an important decision to make,
'I used to flip a coin.
'Perhaps that is what
I will do again.
'Polly tells me
you fell in love for real
'and Polly is never wrong
about matters of the heart.
'I will give you my decision
within three days.
'All my love. Thomas Shelby.'
♪ Oh, I'm too numb to feel
♪ Blow out the candle
♪ Blindness. ♪
GUNSHOT
♪ Love is blindness
♪ I'm so sick of it
♪ I don't wanna see
♪ Why don't you just take the night
♪ Wrap it all around me, now?
♪ Oh, my love
♪ Blindness
♪ Oh, love is blindness
♪ Oh, I'm too numb to feel. ♪