[Polly] There will be a war in this family
and one of you will die.
Please be aware, Mr Shelby,
that the deaths of your people
are your own responsibility.
[Michael] Since my mother passed away
Tommy and I haven't even spoken.
I'm looking forward to
working with you again, Michael.
That, my friend,
is the finest opium in the world.
Why would you sell?
[Tommy] The Irish are being difficult.
The Italians are not an option.
-You're going to America?
-To Canada.
To collect payment for the shipment.
[Diana] Elizabeth,
you are a very lucky woman.
To have each day
what I have only sampled once.
[doctor] Mr Shelby,
your daughter has consumption.
[Lizzie] She's gone, Tommy. She's gone.
A daughter lost, a son found.
This is my son. They call him Duke.
[Holford] It is tuberculoma.
I am afraid it is inoperable.
-How long?
-Perhaps 18 months.
My associates are gonna
take care of Thomas Shelby
and you are gonna give us his brother.
What are Michael's real intentions
towards me, Gina?
And if you lie, I will know.
It is my intention to kill Tommy Shelby.
[instrumental music playing]
[Michael] It was the ambitions
and strategies
of one man that caused this.
I will take revenge on Tommy Shelby.
You want a drink first or a whore first?
I want to see my wife first.
After you've fucked your wife,
you're going to kill a man, right?
[Lizzie sniffs]
[sniffs]
The smoke from your daughter's funeral
is still in your clothes...
and you slept with someone.
Not just someone.
[inhales sharply]
The enemy.
Every enemy we ever had in one woman.
There are some things that I do...
You're not so good
at lying any more, Tommy.
These days, the truth gets in your eyes.
-I have to go to Canada, Lizzie.
-[scoffs]
-I need to know where you will go.
-See? You just accept it.
You don't fight it.
You are cursed, Tommy.
Never to understand the limits
that other people will accept.
Never to be allowed in
where everybody else is.
A curse never to be lifted.
I will be away, Lizzie.
-And while I'm gone, I know a place...
-Always gone. Always away.
[sniffles]
Well, now your rings are gone.
Your rings are away.
I'm already packed.
[breath trembles]
Now leave me to say goodbye to Ruby.
[Tommy] I have to go away
for a bit, Charlie.
Look at me.
Hey, look at me.
Mum already told me she's leaving.
And she told me why.
Mum, where are you going?
[Lizzie sighs]
A hotel.
And then your father will get me a house.
Mum,
I'll come with you.
I'd rather be with you.
Wherever it is.
You're not my mum,
but you're more my mum than he's my dad.
He's never here.
I'd be on my own here.
[Lizzie] Oh, Charles, love.
I don't think your father
would allow that.
[horse sighs and stomps]
You can go.
You can go, son.
I know a good place, Lizzie.
I'll arrange that place.
And, Charlie, you can take him, eh?
They have stables at this new place.
After a while, he'll listen to you.
He'll forget about Ruby.
That's how horses are.
And you'll be here all alone?
I'm buying land, Lizzie.
I'm buying up land.
This place I've bought, I was going to
knock down, but you can go there.
Dad...
Where will you go?
This is the Peaky Blinders' armoury.
We have a very good relationship
with the BSA factory in Armoury Road.
Two dozen machine guns,
half a dozen submachine guns,
BSA sniper rifles,
three boxes of hand grenades.
For what purpose?
For eventualities like the one
that is about to occur.
When men come to us with bad intentions,
family come together.
Tommy says it's time
you joined the family.
But you're not just going to be a soldier.
You're going to be a general... someday.
So, I need to ask you some questions.
What have you ever fired?
[Duke] Shotgun.
-[gun clicks]
-Pistol. .22.
What have you ever killed?
A few rabbits.
Pheasant, partridge, stag.
Arthur tells me,
when they were taking care
of some business at the betting shop,
you ran away.
It was unfair.
Fairness is not a soldier's concern.
You do what you do.
I already have done.
Fair and square.
I have killed a man.
Tommy's always right.
We were outside a hospital in Bridgnorth.
In the Black Country.
My mother was dying.
And the orderly wouldn't give her a bed.
She was a Gypsy.
She had no insurance.
She never saw the sunrise.
Nor did that man who denied her.
Just one more thing
we need to know about you.
Can you keep a secret?
[door slams]
[Arthur] I know, brother.
I know.
I stole your keys.
Tuberculoma.
In your brain.
[smacks lips] Yeah. But I still have time
to do what I need to do.
Fuck you, Tommy.
I don't need anyone to know, Arthur.
No, you don't, do ya?
-You don't need anything, do ya?
-No, I don't need anything.
I don't need anything.
How long have we been dead for, eh?
You and me. How long?
-At least now I'll have a certificate.
-[scoffs]
Wherever it is, I'll get the drinks in
and I'll wait for you.
-Fuck's sake.
-Yeah.
All them bullets that missed.
It's funny, Arthur.
It's funny is what it is.
So don't you fucking weep.
Weep.
When everyone is taken care of financially
I'll take myself away. On my own.
I don't want anyone... [inhales]
Anyone who may or may not love me...
to have to see me crawl...
and grow insane and helpless.
That would be a cruelty to me and to them.
By the time people know the truth,
I will be gone.
What about Lizzie?
I have some papers I need you to sign
on behalf of the company.
Told Lizzie?
I'm working with the housing minister.
I will be allocating contracts,
construction contracts,
worth ten million pounds.
You haven't told Lizzie?
Some contracts I'll be allocating are with
companies in which we have an interest...
Fuck you and your contracts!
So the Shelby Company Limited
will continue to earn money.
But mostly, Arthur, I'm doing it
because it's a good thing.
-Building houses.
-Oh.
-Yeah, for ordinary working people.
-Yeah. Good for you. Fucking...
[Tommy] In the interests
of a fairer future.
Before that,
I will be going to Canada
to collect payment for the shipment.
Five million pounds!
Five fucking million!
Which I will share
among the Shelby family.
And that will be my legacy.
Instead of me, there will be money.
Because for most of the people
who are close to me, that is what I am!
Fucking money. That is my agency.
Is that all you think you are, eh? Hmm?
Stand up.
You heard me.
Stand up. On your feet.
-On your fucking feet.
-Arthur.
On your feet, soldier. On your feet.
Stand the fuck up! Come here! [grunts]
Arthur!
No! Enough!
You hear me? Enough!
Enough!
Now you know.
You tell no one else
until I'm gone.
Until you're gone, yeah.
[Arthur breathing heavily]
When the time comes, I'll call you.
I'll tell you where. It'll be a wagon.
Fuck your wagon!
You light the flame.
You bring Charlie
and Curly and no one else.
Get drunk.
Rake the ashes for silver and gold.
Fuck you!
And your fucking plans!
That time I did let you fucking win.
[groans]
John.
[glass thuds]
[Arthur] Fuck you, John.
[sobbing] Fucking both of you.
Arthur. Arthur.
Come here. Come here.
-Let me see your eyes.
-I'm clean, man.
The dragon's fucking gone.
Thanks to you.
Fucking thanks to you. [sobs]
[emotional music playing]
You all right? Come on.
You're fucking...
Hey, I am still fucking here.
Pull yourself together, come on.
We have work to do.
Come on!
[indistinct shouting]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
Are you sure you want Billy?
I had to shut up the shop.
[Tommy] Yes. We want Billy.
[Arthur] Sit down, Billy.
Thank you for inviting me, Mr Shelby.
[Arthur] Good to see you again.
[Finn] No.
Mary says not until after six o'clock.
He said to tell his father
he feels okay about it.
[Tommy] Good.
Shut the door, Duke.
Now, we are all gathered, and those...
[in Romani] who know the truth...
will know to be cautious.
[in English] Apologies, Mr Shelby,
I still don't speak the lingo.
[Tommy] Well, Finn here
never even bothered to learn it.
I heard "tachipen". Truth.
You said something about the truth.
[Tommy] Truth. The truth is
I called men here that I could trust
because I will be going away.
I have to collect payment
for a shipment of goods
which left Liverpool ten days ago.
[Finn] Payment from who?
[Tommy] South Boston Irish, Finn.
Bootleggers.
Are you going alone?
Johnny Dogs already sailed for Canada.
Michael will be there.
Michael is family.
And Michael will be
my guarantee of safety.
While I'm away, I have a job for you all.
I need you to go to Arrow House.
I will be leaving Arrow House for good.
And there are things that need removing.
I need men that I can trust.
There is cash. There is valuables.
There's information about important people
that has more value than gold.
There are also
bodies buried on the grounds
which need digging up
before the contractors start moving earth.
Isiah, you'll be in charge.
In Arrow House, there is a wine cellar.
In that wine cellar,
there are fine French wines
that are worth more than a man's life.
You're welcome to them, boys.
It'll be like a...
Like a farewell party.
You ready for the party, son?
[in Romani] I know the truth.
[Finn in English] "Tachipen".
The fucking truth again.
What truth?
You'll need shovels, you'll need boxes
and you'll take the bones to Mr Patches
to put in the furnace at Greenhams.
Got it?
All right. Any questions?
Yeah. If it's a party, can we bring girls?
[chuckles]
[Tommy] No, Billy.
All the fun will be laid on for you.
So when is the party, Tom?
Mr Shelby.
Party's next Sunday, Billy.
You mean this Sunday?
Yeah.
[Arthur] While you're digging
fucking holes,
I'll be here
drinking champagne with my wife.
It's our wedding anniversary.
Right.
[Tommy] Oh, and, Finn...
By the way, please explain to, um...
What's her name?
-[Finn] Mary.
-Mary?
-[Finn] Yes.
-Is it Mary?
Please explain to Mary
that you are a Shelby.
It says it here on the back
of your watch. Have a look. Shelby.
Look.
This means you own the watch,
the watch doesn't own you.
The clock strikes six
when you fucking tell it to.
Have a whiskey.
Enjoy the party, boys.
[jazz music playing]
[Gina sighs]
You want a drink, baby?
No.
-Drinking water like Tommy, huh?
-[sighs]
Until this thing is done,
I need a clear head.
[liquid pours]
[telephone ringing]
Leave it.
Yeah.
Good.
That's good.
Look, I've got to go.
Good news, Michael.
Listen.
That was our informant in Birmingham.
The Shelby men
will all be together on Sunday.
But Arthur will be
having dinner with his wife
at the bar at The Garrison Tavern.
As I recall, the Shelby table
is right next to the windows, correct?
Every table's a Shelby table.
Yes, but...
Maybe our people could just drive by
and shoot Arthur through the glass
without even getting out of the car.
Michael.
We've talked about this.
There's no other choice.
This business is between me and Tommy.
Yes.
And when you kill Tommy,
Arthur will come after you.
He has to die too.
If Arthur's in a bar, he'll be drunk.
Or worse.
At least he'll die without pain. [sighs]
[lighter clicking]
Who'll do the killing?
Tommy's working with a faction of the IRA.
Connor has connections.
They made a deal.
A favour in return for guns.
But, Michael...
whilst the assassin's in the city...
Tommy has a son.
He's a kid.
Kids grow up.
We don't kill women
and we don't kill kids.
The informant also mentioned
a new boy named Duke.
Do you want a fucking bloodbath, Gina?
I know about the new boy.
I've decided that the illegitimate son
is not a threat. My decision.
Only Arthur.
Michael, baby.
Everything's been agreed.
[cigarette fizzles]
Everybody wants the same things.
How many men do you think
they killed with bullets and blades?
[Michael sighs]
That's how Tommy became king.
And in three days' time,
that's how you will become king.
Deep down, Arthur and Tommy
wanna be dead anyway.
On Sunday, we'll just...
give them what they want.
[tense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Diana] Oswald was called away.
He sent me instead.
Actually, that's not true.
I sent Oswald away and elected myself
to be his representative.
What was it you wanted?
[Tommy] I'm planning on bringing
my housing bill before Parliament.
You'll need to start drawing up a list
of all your land-owning families
with gambling debts, drug addictions,
any other drain on their resources.
I will deliver offers
to buy the surplus land
using treasury bonds.
Thomas, why don't we fuck here.
On these benches.
Right now.
We wouldn't be the first.
I hear your wife left you.
Over the last few months,
I've had some associates of mine
break into some of your pals' houses.
They stole paperwork.
Letters, bills, bank statements...
Are you not upset?
[clicks tongue]
This is a list
of all land-owning families
facing foreclosure.
[Tommy sighs]
And to answer your question...
No.
No, I am not upset that my wife left me.
And, yeah, if you want to fuck, I'll fuck.
But you'll have to cross the floor
'cause I refuse to fuck on Tory benches.
Mr Shelby.
I was going to have this delivered to you,
but I decided to bring it in person.
It's an invitation
to mine and Diana's wedding.
It's in Berlin.
We're going to get married
in the presence of the Führer himself.
Were you having fun?
Making paper aeroplanes.
I'm afraid... [sighs] I have business.
I will be in Canada.
Pity.
Oh, and, uh...
the other reason I wanted to...
bring this in person
was to tell you that after our wedding,
you must understand, Mr Shelby,
that if you so much
as look in my wife's direction,
I will have you killed.
Come, Diana.
Just think,
very soon, crumbling old institutions
like this one will be swept away
and become a thing of ancient memory.
Fly safe.
[sighs]
[inaudible conversation]
Be careful with this baby.
You see any potholes,
you drive round them.
[engine starts]
[Frances] Mr Shelby called to say
to expect you.
Yeah, we've come to do a bit of gardening.
We're hearing so many rumours
about what's happening to the house.
Tommy says your second-best quality,
after your baking,
is you don't ask questions.
Get everybody away
from the house until Monday.
Okay. Let's find these bottles of wine
worth more than a man's life.
[glasses clinking]
There's only one guest here.
The rest of the rooms are free
if you want to use them while you wait.
Our friend will be here
by the time it gets dark.
There was a storm last night.
Last of a hurricane.
Boats all came in.
He's not coming by boat,
he's coming by plane.
Then your friend is dead. Wind was like...
[imitates wind howling]
Maybe God's done your job for you, Mickey.
My name is not fucking Mickey,
there is no fucking God
and Tommy will be here.
Another one.
[thunder claps]
[Polly] There will be a war
and one of you will die.
Which one, I cannot tell.
[Nelson] You're a brave man, Mr Shelby.
[breathing heavily]
[Lizzie] Where the fuck were you?
She's gone, Tommy. She's gone.
[Tommy] The devils
who did this will pay, Ruby.
[Holford] Tuberculoma.
I am afraid it is inoperable.
-[Tommy] How long?
-[Holford] Perhaps 18 months.
[Tommy] I will change. Change for good.
[Lizzie] What is this "good"
that you will become?!
Kill and kill...
[aircraft rattles]
[indistinct chattering]
[Finn] What's going on?
[Billy and Finn laughing]
Hey.
-Hey. Hey.
-[Finn coughs and sniffs]
What the fuck is this? I thought
it was meant to be a fucking party, lads.
It is, now you're here.
[hesitates] Where's the fucking booze?
[Duke] In the kitchen.
All the booze is in the kitchen.
[Billy] All right.
[Lazarus] God gives a man wealth,
possessions and honour.
But God steps in and says,
"No! This is grievous, mindless evil!"
Where is he? Jeremiah?
In heaven, looking down.
[coins clink]
God tells us the blood
is given to Him from us...
[Finn] Why don't you turn
the fucking lights on?
[Isiah] There's no longer any power
in the house of Thomas Shelby.
[Finn] Why not?
What do you mean? What happened?
[Billy] I thought
there would be girls here.
[Duke] Who need girls
when you're in a house bound for hell?
[Finn] Fuck do you mean?
Hey! What the fuck do you mean?
[gun cocks]
[Billy] Fuck!
Fuck!
We can do whatever we want in this house.
It's got a death sentence.
[scoffs]
I don't want a drink. I want to go
dig up those fucking bodies, yeah?
-Billy?
-Yeah.
Got to wait until
all the bodies are buried
before you start digging them back up.
What the fuck does that mean?
I'm a fucking Shelby.
So am I.
He's here.
[aircraft rattling]
[exhales deeply]
Step back and give me
a bit of light there, boys.
[exhales]
The charge is set to blow in 30 minutes.
That's at exactly 16:20.
Everyone got that?
I'll do it.
This is between me and Tommy.
I'll do it with my own hand.
I'll come with you.
Yeah, don't slam any doors.
[door closes]
Easy.
[car boot clicks]
It's just a pity you didn't have the guts
to shoot him face-to-face.
My mother was a Gypsy. She saw the future.
She always said it won't be
a bullet that will kill Tommy Shelby.
[Connor] Hey, lads.
Over by the bridge.
Big, big fish.
[in French] Fish. Big.
[in English] Go on.
[breathing heavily]
[Duke] Take the gun, Finn.
Arthur says if you don't do it
then you can
walk away from this family for good.
What the fuck do you know about family?
You're not family.
You're the son of a fucking whore.
[Duke] Just take the gun and do it, Finn.
[Billy whimpering] Take the fucking gun.
Now you have the gun, Finn.
You have the gun.
Use it on these fucks.
[grunts]
[gun clicks]
[grunting]
[Duke] Charlie Strong told me,
"When you give Finn the gun,
make sure the first
two chambers are empty." [chuckles]
Good old Uncle Charlie.
[breath trembling]
You are no longer a member
of this Shelby family.
By order of the Peaky fucking Blinders.
[Finn] I will come for you.
I will fucking come for you!
[breathing heavily]
[Lazarus] ...that find me faulting,
them, who govern like dogs
in Garrison Lane and Artillery.
Hear this. Then came Jesus forth,
wearing the crown of thorns
and a purple robe, and Pilate said,
"Behold the man. He is the man."
Not the Peaky Blinders.
We see them in their automobiles,
with their whores...
...and their pity for us.
Cast down...
[watch ticking]
[Arthur grunts]
[Lazarus continues preaching
indistinctly]
[telephone ringing]
[door opens]
[telephone continues ringing]
[ringing stops]
[gun cocks]
Order your man to drop it.
Order him.
Empty the fucking gun. Tell him.
[bullets clatter]
-[Arthur] You all right, Charlie?
-All good here, Arthur.
Let's move.
Take you out to the street.
I don't wanna spoil my pub.
You'd shoot us like dogs?
No, I don't shoot dogs.
I shoot fucking fascists. Move.
[gunshot fires]
[crackling]
[footsteps echo]
[footsteps]
[exhales]
[gun cocks]
Fuck.
[body thuds]
[gasps]
[Laura whistles]
Oh, Lord!
Time for the chosen one to reveal himself!
[breathing heavily]
[baby crying]
[kid shouting indistinctly]
[woman] No, kids, no. Come here.
I said come here!
Come here now.
What have I told you about running off?
Don't. Put it down.
Come here, come on!
-Emily? Emily, come on!
-[metal clinks]
If you get lost in the fog,
the Peaky Blinders will get you.
[baby crying]
[Arthur] Jeremiah.
Let's show 'em the old keepsake
from Passchendaele.
[rattling]
Fuck.
[gasping]
[coughing]
[coughing and gasping]
[cannister rattles]
[Laura coughing]
[gasping]
Come here. [shushes]
[Laura gasping]
Breathe. Breathe.
Her name was Elizabeth Gray.
She was my Aunt Polly.
My Aunt Polly.
Vengeance is for the Lord...
Not in Small Heath, it ain't.
Rest in peace, Pol.
Leave us, Uncle Charlie.
We're still in France.
[Pat] Okay.
I see him coming out of the fog.
[glass thuds]
[door opens]
[door closes]
How was the flight?
[Tommy] They say it's the future.
I'm not so sure.
Whiskey.
[Michael coughs]
Hello, Michael.
Tommy.
[sighs]
Give me another.
We want you to take us
to where the opium is being stored.
[Connor] And then we will provide you
with a banker's draft for the full amount.
Five million dollars.
[Sam] Let's go.
[Michael] I'll go with Tommy.
You boys follow behind.
Shit.
Forgot my cigarettes.
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass shatters]
[exhales]
Mum.
It's done.
It's over.
May God forgive me.
[breathing heavily]
Johnny!
Johnny, where are you?
I switched the ticker like you said, Tom.
Tell me I've done a good thing here, Tom.
Goodbye, Michael.
Goodbye, Johnny.
You're a good man.
I'm gonna go look at the fog, Tom.
Speak to me.
Speak to me, Michael.
You killed her.
-Polly made her own choices, Michael.
-No.
No one close to you
makes a choice without your opinion, Tom.
Not Arthur, not me, not Ada.
We can't escape you.
Your lethal hand
is always on our shoulders.
Polly was half of me.
Still visits me in my dreams.
She'll visit me no more.
[Michael thuds]
I have no limitations.
[door closes]
[Alfie] I smell the smell
of roasting Irishmen.
Oh, yes. Hello.
-[playing piano]
-I also smell the smell of tobacco.
Which is forbidden
in my presence for all except for one,
my new wife, Edna.
The Irish being rendered smoke and fat,
I now own half of Boston.
So, out of respect
for my restored authority,
put the fucking cigarette out now, Tommy.
Hello, Alfie.
I heard it was a good wedding.
Yeah it was, actually. Thank you.
Edna's from a family circus.
So, after the ketubah
and the old swapping of rings
and the smashing of glass,
we left aboard elephants.
Yeah. It was quite a thing.
They had to shut down Camden High Street,
and even the gentile,
what normally fucking hate me,
they waved with their hankies.
Justice.
And housekeeping.
Long overdue.
Yeah, look at that little cunt ascending,
he is ascending to the heavens.
Right in front of us.
Before our very eyes.
And I can see with this eye.
I'm not blind.
This eye is the eye of a dead man.
Dead men can see through life
like it was a curtain that billows
with the flicker of truth upon it.
And I can see with this eye, Tommy,
that your nephew is ascending
and he will be forgiven.
Unlike you,
who, on judgement day,
is probably truly fucked
when the other shoe drops.
[Alfie] Hmm?
You all right, Tommy? How are you keeping?
You know, Alfie,
[clicks tongue]
so many people, so many times,
going to so much trouble to kill me.
I'm fucking dying anyway.
Well, we're all dying anyway.
No.
Not a bullet, not a bomb, not a knife.
Is it clap? Is it clap?
No.
Not even that noble.
[Alfie] What are you trying to say?
I'm about to sign over
half of fucking Camden Town to you,
as part of the deal,
and you're saying you're just gonna
die in your bed?
I'm not going to die in bed, Alfie.
Who fucking dies in bed?
Good people die in their bed, Tommy.
Good people.
-Good people, eh?
-Mmm.
Good people.
And yet here we are, Alfie.
After all this time, just you and me.
And I crossed the line.
Michael...
Polly...
Ruby...
Tommy, if you are about to
express profound emotion,
you might be better served expressing it
to someone who gives a fuck.
Or perhaps to somebody
who is being paid to pretend to have to.
Like a fucking nurse or a priest. Someone.
And, as for death,
speaking as someone
who has been dead for a number of years,
I can only heartily recommend it.
Well, Alfie,
your opera is complete.
[sighs]
Shall we go and witness the final act?
Whenever you're ready, boys.
[inaudible conversation]
That's enough. [clears throat]
Thank you all for coming.
Well, at least I can say that, er,
I am one of those rare politicians
who actually makes good on his promises.
Country estate,
requisitioned to make way
for houses for working people.
I improved my own home
with good intentions
and 1,500 pound of dynamite.
Now I'm back where we began.
With horses and caravans...
vagabonds and thieves.
Frances, sit down, please.
I'd like to raise a toast.
A simple toast.
-To family.
-[man] To family.
Sometimes,
it is shelter from the storm.
Sometimes, it is the storm itself.
Planning on going away for a bit.
After I'm gone...
Ada,
in this family,
it was you who was
born to be a politician, not me.
Remember that.
And if ever a seat is to become available
in this ugly old city, you should run.
[chuckles softly]
[Tommy] Where's Arthur?
[Linda] He went for a walk down the river.
He said he's not good at farewells,
so he decided to go catch a trout instead.
He told me to tell you that...
"Where you're going, Tommy,
there will I be."
"Very soon."
"Love, Arthur."
How does Arthur know
where you're going, Tommy?
You watch him, Linda.
You love him.
Charles.
I want you to look after your mum.
You tell her I'm sorry, you hear me?
I want you to be the...
Exactly how long
are you going away for, Tommy?
[Tommy] Thanks, Curly.
[whispers inaudibly]
[Curly] Tom, the horse...
[Charlie] Shut up, Curly.
[Tommy] Is she hitched, Johnny?
Tommy, you tell me right now,
where are you going?
You have to carry the bucket
on your own this time, Ada.
Tommy, you come to me with everything.
You always come to me.
Not this time. Not this one, sister.
What the fuck does that mean?
Where are you going?
Tommy!
♪ My eyes are open wide ♪
♪ And now I see you ♪
♪ Without your robes on ♪
[crow caws]
♪ Without your crown ♪
[caws]
♪ I don't want to hate you ♪
[exhales]
♪ I don't want to bear ♪
♪ The kind of fascination ♪
♪ That gets in my way ♪
♪ The door that opens wide ♪
♪ My high up altar ♪
♪ Oh heaven, help me ♪
[grunts]
♪ Is that the time? ♪
[groans]
♪ Beginning ♪
♪ Without end ♪
♪ Never lost ♪
♪ Never die ♪
♪ Unending ♪
[horse snorts]
♪ Beam of light ♪
♪ A tunnel ♪
♪ In my mind ♪
♪ As it opens wide ♪
♪ With a filter on the lens ♪
♪ She sees everything I do ♪
♪ And without my shoes on ♪
♪ Over broken glass ♪
♪ I am dancing for pennies ♪
♪ I am staring straight ahead ♪
♪ A view that is so wide ♪
♪ It's gonna break ♪
♪ It's like it holds me in its gaze ♪
♪ If I go ♪
♪ It's because ♪
♪ It's happened once before ♪
♪ And now it's starting all again ♪
♪ As it opens wide ♪
♪ Forget everything you knew ♪
♪ Like a newborn child ♪
♪ A child ♪
[gun clicks]
♪ Like a child ♪
♪ A child ♪
[Tommy] In the bleak... midwinter.
[Ruby] Dad, come outside!
Dad, it's me.
Did Polly send you? Did Polly send you?
Or am I dead already?
[Ruby] No.
You're not dead.
You're not even sick.
But I am, my darling.
I am sick.
Sick like you was.
No. Not true.
I know it. You've got to live, Daddy.
You let the fire go out.
Light the fire again and get warm,
and you will see that you must live.
[Tommy sighs]
[sniffs]
[twigs snapping]
-[Ruby] You're not even sick, Daddy.
-[horse grunts]
[toilet flushes]
[magazine thuds]
Fucking Gypsies.
Have you thrown
the tinkers off the top field yet?
No. I went to the caravan, sir,
but there was no one there.
Go back up there
and set fire to the fucking thing.
Yes, sir.
Have you filled the car with petrol?
[metallic clunking]
I said, have you
filled the car with petrol?
[grunting]
How was the wedding in Berlin?
I hear Chancellor Hitler himself
was the best man.
You've been my doctor now for three years.
I never knew you were so well connected.
Oh, and the doctor at St Thomas',
who you sent me to for the second opinion,
second set of X-rays.
A maid of honour at the same wedding.
Also very well-fucking-connected.
[Holford breathes shakily]
On your knees, Holford.
[Holford exhales]
I'm guessing you people all decided
that the only person
who could ever kill Thomas Shelby
is Thomas Shelby himself.
You made me believe death was coming.
Let my nature do the rest, eh?
You may not have tuberculoma, Mr Shelby,
but you are sick.
I know you.
You are sick with guilt.
Sick of death at your own hand.
Sick of who you were.
You are no longer the kind of man
who would kill another man in cold blood.
Tommy, you have been on a journey.
From the back streets
to the corridors of power.
You can't go back.
You are a different man.
The gun no longer belongs in your hand.
Oh, but I am back.
Back from under the ground.
Close your eyes. Close your eyes.
[bell tolls]
[Holford whimpering]
The eleventh hour.
Armistice.
Peace at last. Peace at last.
-[gunshot rings]
-[Holford gasps]
[Holford sighs]
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I... ♪
[petrol canister thuds]
♪ ...any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪
♪ All the tired horses in the sun ♪
♪ How am I supposed to get
Any riding done? ♪