My brother sends his
apologies for not being here
and would like to invite
all of you to his home
for a meeting.
All you have to do
is sit with Jack Nelson
and talk to him about
a new golden age.
If anyone's
going to kill Tommy Shelby...
It will be you.
The future belongs to us.
Your daughter has consumption.
Consumption is
a very infectious disease.
While they're X-raying
Ruby, they have to X-ray us.
It'll be the girl's mother
who laid the curse.
Perhaps she waited
till your little girl was seven
so you'd know how it feels.
Now that I'm without whisky,
I can hear the spirits clearly,
and they are saying that Ruby
will be well if I make amends.
She's gone, Tommy.
Arthur?
I've written some words.
I can't speak 'em.
- You're the oldest.
- You speak 'em for me.
I'm sorry, Brother.
I can't do it.
We could have afforded
a golden carriage.
She deserved a golden carriage.
But we didn't afford ourselves
that luxury...
...because gold doesn't work.
That was the last lesson
that Ruby taught us.
This place was her favourite
place in the whole world.
And she used to say...
..."Dad...
..."you never know what's
going to come down the river."
And it's true...
...cos little Ruby's fate...
...came a thousand miles
too soon.
But in her name and in her
memory, things will change.
And whatever comes
down that river from now on...
...we will make good...
....we will make peaceful
and honest and good
and send it on down the river
better than it was.
In her memory we will do this.
But for now, we send her on...
...to wherever it is you go...
...in the hope that
if there is a destination...
...that it's a yard like this,
with horses
and boats for her to play on.
Tom?
- I've got the petrol.
Who will light the flame?
Jeremiah?
Jeremiah, you made her laugh.
You light the flame.
No, no!
- No!
- Lizzie, Lizzie...
No, you won't burn her! No!
Shh, shh, shh, shh...
I just want to see her.
I just want to see her face.
We'll go and see her together.
Come on.
Yeah.
Oh, my baby.
The devils who did this
will pay, Ruby.
What do you mean?
Where are you going, Tommy?
Riley! I think
the police are here.
Evadne Barwell?
Yeah. Who's asking?
I am here on behalf
of the blue sapphire.
Don't shoot! There are babies!
- BABY CRIES)
Gold dust.
Our business is done, Esme.
Get out of the car.
Not quite done, Tommy.
I thought this would be
a good time.
In fact, it's the perfect time.
Some business
is still unfinished.
Christians say, "The Lord
gives, the Lord takes away."
Our spirits are the same.
Spirits just took away
your child.
- Get out of the car, Esme.
The same spirits want to give
you a different child, Tommy.
What child?
A daughter lost...
...a son found.
Before you went to France, a
long time ago, at Appleby Fair,
you slept with a girl.
Her name was Zelda. I met her.
She said you slept together
under a hazel tree in May 1914.
When she fell pregnant, her
father threatened to kill you,
but you'd already joined the
Army and gone away to France.
You remember the girl and the
hazel tree, don't you, Tommy?
Whoever that boy is, Esme...
...whoever he is,
our business is done here.
I brought you to this camp
for a reason,
and I brought him, as well.
He is yours.
A boy born with hazel eyes.
He calls himself Duke.
His mother is dead.
He's a thief.
He works the fairground,
but he says he wants
more to his life than
big wheels and carousels.
If the losing of Ruby has left
a hole in your heart...
...I'll send him to you.
If you give me
a bit more gold...
...I'll tell him Tommy Shelby
can offer a man
far, far more than big wheels
and carousels.
Is our business done
or not, Tommy?
I know where you went.
I'm going to spend more hours
working in the Commons
with Mr Churchill.
- His fight is my fight.
- I sat like a stone
and thought about you
killing someone in her name.
The Shelby institutions
will be expanded.
I will set up a fund
to research the causes
and cures for consumption.
Did the woman you killed
have children?
10,000 children die
every year, Lizzie.
- Go to bed, Tommy.
- I've been reading
- about new research.
- Stop and close
- your fucking eyes.
- I will not...
I will not stop!
What is this good
that you will become?!
I killed a woman.
I killed a woman and three men.
And their bodies will be
thrown aboard the boat,
like all the other bodies,
but I am stepping off that boat
and onto another boat.
Do you understand?!
Yeah.
The doctor
from the sanatorium called
and said that he needs
to speak with you urgently.
But I think now you are
beyond the help of doctors.
Lizzie...
Frances said Arthur's here.
Tommy?
- Tom?
- Yeah, it's me.
Ah, fuck.
Arthur, give me a light,
will you?
I can't find my lighter.
I'm sorry I couldn't speak
at the wagon, Tom.
Don't be sorry.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for this fucking cup
to fill up.
Nearly empty, this barrel.
There are plenty
of barrels, Arthur.
Start another barrel.
I thought maybe they're all
full of fucking blood.
The junk, Tom...
...fucks up your mind.
You know, Arthur...
...you was already fucked up.
You was fucked up
since you was a kid.
This is my theory.
It's from that time
I gave you a beating
when you was twelve
and I was nine.
We were fighting
over cigarettes.
Maybe...when I had you
down on the ground...
...I gave you one too many
to the head.
It was a draw, though, Tom.
Nah.
I beat you.
I had you pinned.
You actually didn't.
- We both agreed.
- You're so fucked
you can't remember, Brother.
I do.
I do remember little things.
I know you do.
So do I.
The fog and the gas
is clearing, eh?
Here, that cup's nearly full.
Pass it here.
I thought you...
Tom, you don't want
stuff any more.
Eh?
You don't drink no more, Tom.
Even when Polly was gone,
Arthur...
...I thought I could just march
and march.
If I just kept up that fucking
left, right, left, right,
left, right, left, right
fucking rhythm,
I'd never have to stop.
Then Ruby went.
I stumbled and crashed.
Now here I am...
...sat on me arse...
...on the ground...
...like a fucking toddler...
...with me old comrade Arthur.
Yeah.
Remember the January, Arthur?
The family boat?
The whole family
living on something
the size of ten of
these fucking barrels?
Remember that night
at Tile Cross...
...16 of us
sleeping on the boat?
The coppers come.
We all swim like rats.
Except for Arthur.
Arthur holds them off with
a boathook all on his own.
And I remember...
...I climbed back up
at the lock and I looked back
and saw you waving
that fucking boathook
in the coppers' faces...
...on your own.
That's when I realised.
When I had you on the ground...
...all them years ago...
...it's cos you let me win.
You wanted me to win.
You've wanted me to win
ever since.
What chance do I have if you...
...start doing that again? Eh?
You'll stop. You'll stop
cos the family needs you to.
It's like that long tunnel
on the Dudley stretch.
You remember Dudley Canal,
Line Number 1?
3,172 yards
of fucking pitch-blackness
and rats swimming.
- Yeah.
- And then we'd come
round that corner and
there'd be a shaft of light.
And then we'd know.
- Yeah.
- And you and me
would both know
it was nearly done.
That's where
we are now, Arthur.
Just a few more yards to go.
Then you will change your ways.
And I'll change
the fucking world.
We assumed, at this late hour,
you would have had dinner.
There are drinks
and sandwiches, if you want.
We're not here to eat.
Mr Shelby will be down shortly.
Please, tell Mr Shelby
on behalf of us all
that changing the world
can wait.
He doesn't want to wait.
There is champagne.
Oh, goodie.
Charles?
I heard cars.
Mr Shelby, the guests are...
I know.
Dad?
There's a Bentley
and a Rolls-Royce.
Yeah.
Go to bed, Charles.
I can't sleep.
I see her when I shut my eyes.
Go to your mum.
She'll be awake.
- She holds on to me.
- Let her hold on to you.
You hear me?
Always let her hold on to you.
Go on.
Mr Shelby, the guests said
they would understand if...
Have you served them drinks?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
I'm OK, Frances.
The agenda is in my head.
I'm OK.
Do I look OK?
If someone touches you,
you won't shatter.
Sing it.
Sing it. I love that song.
I...can't be singing
rebel songs
in a house
in grief and mourning.
Sing it to me softly.
It breaks my heart.
Don't look at him.
He's English.
He can block his ears.
Darling?
Should she sing her rebel
IRA song while we wait,
or would that be inappropriate?
You know, I went to a meeting
of similar intent to this
in Berlin
attended by
the Chancellor himself...
..and Göring and Himmler.
It lasted until
the sun came up.
We spoke about the future
of the world in a serious way.
When the first rays of light
entered the room, we all stood
and stared at it as if it were
the world to come.
There was no singing,
no giggling.
And when breakfast was served
on the terrace,
overlooking the mountains,
they brought up some Jews.
And while we ate our eggs,
they were forced to eat grass.
And we watched
as we sipped our coffee.
We should all remember
this is serious business.
Oh, Diana.
Now look what you've done.
You've killed the mood.
Let her sing her fucking song
to raise our spirits.
Go on. Please.
# In a neat little town
they call Belfast
# Apprentice to trade
I was bound
# And many's an hour's
sweet happiness
# Have I spent
in that neat little town
# A sad misfortune
came over me... #
Did it break?
Mum will fix it for you.
She's not here any more.
# Her eyes, they shone
like diamonds
# I thought her the Queen... #
Mr Shelby...
No, please, no condolences.
Thank you all for coming.
Now, let's try to find out
how this new world of ours
will look, shall we?
Perhaps, Mr Mosley, we can turn
to what practical things
Mr Nelson can do
to...further our cause
while he's in the country.
It's me who has the ear of the
President of the United States.
Which is kind of
why I'm here, right?
We do indeed have things
for you to whisper
into the President's ear.
Tell him we are England.
We are the mood England is in.
And in Ireland, appeasers
to the English abound,
but we represent
the true, liberated spirit
of the country that populated
your own.
I hear about communists
in both places.
We are the bulwark
against them.
When it comes
to the working class,
we could move our people
from republicanism
to fascism with just a nudge.
They trust us.
You ride with hounds,
Mr Mosley.
Will you hunt communists?
Oh, my hounds are baying.
Shelby...
...you run as a socialist.
Mr Shelby has one of
the largest Commons majorities
in England.
In the heart of England.
When the time comes,
he'll resign his party whip
and run as an independent.
But underneath, do you truly
believe in the cause,
Mr Shelby?
I'm here.
Mr Nelson,
I'm here four nights...
...four nights after,
and I am here...
...in this room,
in this meeting.
I am here and I am serious.
Prove it to him.
Prove it physically.
Perish Judah.
That thing is going to
get us killed.
Go to bed.
At school, they've stopped
talking to me.
They say the black rubs off.
When they come to power...
...they'll take her off you.
They're going to
separate us all out.
They'll send her to Africa.
Yeah?
And where will they send you?
Where will they send you, Karl?
You're half Gypsy, so...
...to Egypt, maybe?
Something I never
told you before...
...because it wasn't important.
Maybe now it is.
Your dad was Jewish.
He was the son
of a tailor in Stechford.
They changed their name
to Thorne
to stop the bricks
coming through the window.
So where will they send you,
Karl?
Mr Nelson, you can report back
to your president
that the aristocracy
and the meritocracy are united
in their conviction
that a new order is coming.
Also, Mr Nelson, at present
our weapons are coming
from Germany.
The British are closing
our supply lines down.
We would value
a supply from Boston.
Weapons I can give you,
if they're to be used
in a good cause.
And while on the subject
of import and export,
Mr Shelby,
in light of
our new relationship
and since you have
proven your commitment
in a most extraordinary way...
...Boston is now
officially open
for the importation
of your merchandise.
Good.
If we have established
what we came here to establish,
perhaps we should all
say goodnight.
Absolutely.
That's the same typewriter
you bought me
all those years ago...
...to help me become
more respectable.
Do you remember?
Yeah.
This arrived.
It's from the sanatorium.
I've already paid
Ruby's medical bills.
I don't think it's a bill.
It says it's urgent.
It's from
the senior consultant.
Why didn't you come to bed?
I'm typing up
my recollection of the meeting.
If I... If I do it
straight away...
...I can quote people
word for word.
The information is more...
...useful to Mr Churchill
if it is word for word.
I burned her chair.
The paint on the wood
left a smell in the air.
I didn't open the window.
I quite like the smell.
Not yet.
I have this work to do,
cos now I know...
...that I will change...
...that I have to change.
And change for good, Lizzie.
Not just yet.
Hello?
Oh.
I saw him leave.
He keeps this apartment
expressly for this purpose,
doesn't he?
Are you following me,
Mr Shelby?
I'm flattered...
...but why?
When I do business
with someone,
I make it my business
to know their secrets.
Mosley's reputation
is no secret.
Not him, you.
How did you know I'd come here?
I know things.
I read people's minds,
you know?
Little glances across tables.
It's a gift.
The whole family...
...witches and sorcerers.
Your uncle will disown you...
...fucking his business partner
- behind his back.
- You think he has morals?
- He's a Catholic.
Men do what they want,
women do what they are told.
Will you tell Michael?
Michael is family.
We are a family healed.
You have no interest in me...
...or in Michael...
...so why don't you just tell
me what you actually want?
You will be with Mosley...
...when he's in Berlin.
You'll be in the room
when he meets
senior members
of the German government.
I want to know
what is discussed...
...and I want to know
what is decided.
And if I lie?
I will know.
You know, Michael thinks
you're the devil...
...and I think he might
actually be right.
That was the other reason
I came here.
What are Michael's real
intentions toward me, Gina?
And if you lie, I will know.
Tommy...
...he intends
to complete the deal.
And then you both walk away.
Fuck!
Come.
Mr Shelby? Dr Holford.
Send him in.
You said it had to be
in person. Here I am.
You might want to sit down.
Mr Shelby, I know
that you are still
grieving for your daughter...
...but I have news
that cannot wait.
When you were X-rayed
and examined
at the sanatorium
ten days ago...
...there was no TB
found in your lung.
But I am afraid
they found something else...
...something related to
your daughter's illness.
They tried to speak to you
at the hospital
but you were not co-operating.
After your daughter's death...
...you could not be found
to be informed in person.
Eventually, as your personal
doctor, they called me.
I didn't offer you tea.
You look like death.
Do you want tea?
No.
At the sanatorium,
they conducted blood tests.
The tests suggest
that the shadow you can see
at the base of your skull...
...is not cancer...
...it is tuberculoma...
...a tubercular growth caused
by the same bacteria as TB.
You may have picked it up
from your daughter.
Once this disease enters
a household, it can run wild.
It can be transmitted
with a simple kiss.
It seems the Shelby household
is no exception.
Mr Shelby, as I say, I am aware
that you are still grieving...
...but you must understand
this is very serious.
From the size of the tumour,
expansion must have been rapid.
I have no doubt that you are
already experiencing symptoms.
Have you recently
suffered seizures?
Bouts of weakness?
Dissociation?
Hallucinations?
Why didn't you come and see me?
I have work to do.
Am I a danger to others?
No.
Unlike TB, tuberculoma
is not infectious.
Mr Shelby,
it is not infectious...
...but in your case...
...I am afraid
it is inoperable.
The growth is
in your brain stem.
Any attempt to remove it
would result in trauma
and brain haemorrhage.
Whilst you were
refusing my calls,
I showed your X-rays
to three of the best surgeons
in the country.
They all said
they would not operate...
...as it would be futile.
Of course, you will want
a second opinion for yourself.
Dr Helen Rutherford
at St Thomas'.
She is a friend.
This...
How bad will it get?
As the tumour grows,
the rate of physical and mental
deterioration will increase.
Eventually, you will need
people around you constantly...
...who love you very much.
How long?
I understand
that you have defeated
many enemies, Mr Shelby.
Now you have a new one...
...inside you.
You cannot defeat it...
...but you can keep it at bay
for a while.
If you live correctly,
if you are determined
and if you fight...
I asked you a question.
This time I want an answer.
I don't want
your fucking platitudes.
How long before I need
people around me
who love me very much?
- Sorry.
- It's fine, Lizzie.
My accountant here
was just leaving.
I will telephone you
when I get back to London.
No, I don't have enough time.
You're an accountant,
give me a fucking number now.
One year.
Perhaps 18 months.
That's fine.
That's all I need to know.
I will adjust my finances
accordingly. Thank you.
I will write to you, explaining
the full implications.
Yeah, thank you.
Good day.
Something serious?
No. No, just a...
...just a bill I wasn't
expecting, and I...
...I'll have to pay it.
Will you give me
a minute on me own, Lizzie?
Yeah.
Not a devil...
...just an ordinary mortal man.
There will be a war
in this family...
...and one of you will die.
Polly...
...just give me enough time
to do what I have to do.
Kill.
Kill...