Ever since you began to build your empire,
you have had a crutch to lean on.
[Michael] Mum, I swear
in the name of Almighty God,
I will take revenge on Tommy Shelby.
That, my friend,
is the finest opium in the world.
Perhaps we can meet after you've
spoken to your wife's uncle, Jack Nelson.
Tommy Shelby wants
to do business with Jack Nelson?
So speak to your uncle
and get me out of here.
If he doesn't want to buy my opium,
I will sell to the East Boston Jews.
It's Ruby, she's not well.
I'm coming home.
[Polly] There will be a war in this family
and one of you will die.
[Michael] You've been too busy
to punish the people who killed her.
How is the family?
[Ruby] Daddy!
Hello, Ruby.
[Ruby laughs]
[Tommy] Come here.
Let me see you. I missed you.
I missed you.
-That's the Black Madonna. [kisses]
-[Charles] What presents did you get us?
[Tommy] Son.
She's all better, Tommy.
You came back for nothing.
But I'm glad you're back.
Right, before we do anything else,
we're going to go out for a drive.
-Okay? Let's go.
-What about me?
Yeah, you come too. Come on.
A drive where?
I've asked the driver
to take us to see Dr Robert.
-To have a look at Ruby.
-Why?
The appointment is in one hour.
You can stay here or you can come.
Right.
[Tommy] Right. Let's go.
[children playing]
[grunts]
[gags and spits]
[coughs]
[door creaks open and shuts]
[Lizzie] Tommy?
Yeah?
It was all good. Everything was clear.
[exhales]
That is a relief.
-That's a relief.
-Yeah.
-Driver's bringing the car around.
-[Ruby] Dad.
[Lizzie] Hiya.
Come here.
When did you last sleep?
Not much since we last spoke on the phone.
Now you know Ruby is all clear,
you can sleep.
Yeah.
Lizzie, I'm very happy
that Ruby's results are clear.
But still you won't sleep.
I will speak to Johnny
and I will speak to Esmeralda.
[sighs]
[sighs] We could be on holiday.
We could be up a mountain in America.
That wouldn't have been possible.
The man I'm dealing with
is coming to London. I need to be there.
[exhales] No escape.
We will escape, Lizzie.
One last deal to be done.
It'll be difficult.
-[Lizzie sighs]
-Difficulties are to be expected.
This is why I must move from item to item.
Do you feel that?
Do you feel anything?
You know, you talk as if
you're watching everything on a screen.
When we go home... When we go home,
we'll give the kids to Frances,
and then you and me will go to bed.
And I will be the next item.
-That's how it feels now, Tommy.
-[sighs] Yeah.
Everything on a list.
-Hey, baby.
-[Ruby] When are we going home?
[thunder rumbling]
[glass shatters]
[thunder cracks]
[Lizzie] Tommy? Tommy?
[both grunting]
[Lizzie] Tommy? Tommy, what's happened?
Oh, fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
-[Tommy grunting]
-Come here, come here.
[Tommy gasps]
[Lizzie] What's happening?
Tommy!
-Love.
-[both gasping]
[exhales sharply]
It is four years,
one month, six days, since I had a drink.
My head is clear.
I am myself.
Is this the first time?
Once on the ship back. Not as bad.
Tommy.
You need to see a doctor.
I have work to do.
[scoffs]
It's the work that's to blame.
The people you meet,
the lies that you tell.
We've got to keep going
until this Boston business is done.
Then we rest.
Then we Peaky Blinders fucking rest.
[rain pattering]
[woman] Comrades,
before we end this planning meeting
and send you out into the rain...
[crowd laughing]
...we have a surprise.
He just arrived back
from a trade mission to America.
He came back early and he has insisted
on addressing you volunteers in person.
[crowd exclaims]
[woman] Comrades, your Labour
representative for South Birmingham,
-Mr Thomas Shelby, MP, OBE.
-[crowd cheering]
I bring with me,
on the train from London,
a message from Westminster.
No! No, no, no. Not a message.
Not a message.
An instruction, in fact.
[crowd mutters]
You must be silent.
[crowd exclaims]
You must say nothing!
Say nothing
about the present situation in this city.
Say nothing about hunger.
Say nothing about jobs.
Say nothing about pay.
But those in greener pastures,
they may speak.
[crowd exclaims]
They may raise their voices!
[crowd shouts]
But here in the smoke, you men and women,
Irish and Italian and English,
who support the socialist cause...
Even your socialist
cats and dogs and canaries...
[crowd laughs]
You must hush
because the king
and all the king's horses
and all the king's men...
[crowd laughs]
...want you to be silent.
But it is you, my friends,
who must suffer the cuts in wages
-and in welfare and in dignity!
-[crowd exclaims]
And you must not complain
'cause that would be unpatriotic.
You soldiers who have fought in France,
you are traitors if you speak up.
You veterans of their wars
and their booms and their busts,
it is you who must take the blows
and carry the burdens
for the sake of those in greener pastures
who bellow at you...
[slams fist]
"Silence!"
[crowd yells]
Well, watch this, comrades.
I will not be silent.
[man] Never again.
Not this Englishman.
[crowd exclaims and cheers]
No silence from me!
No silence from me
because I have heard your voices
when you come to me and tell me
about the cries of your hungry children.
And I will gather up
every single one of those cries
and I will take 'em with me
on the train back to Westminster.
And I will let 'em out of the bag
in the House of Commons,
and let them try and silence that, eh?
[crowd cheers]
[Tommy] Shouldn't that involve
some sharing of the burden?
All of us taking
a smaller slice of the cake, eh?
After all, it's bloody us
who bakes the cake
and makes the cars and melts the metal.
And the king, remember him?
The man who ordered all of this.
Shouldn't he be taking some of the cuts?
Some of the blows? Some of the pain?
No or yes?
[crowd exclaims] Yes!
-[shushes]
-[exclaiming stops]
Hush, you working men and women.
Silence.
Good.
Save your voices.
You're gonna need 'em
on Saturday when we rally together,
at the Bull Ring Market!
[crowd cheering]
And together we will raise the roof,
break the damned silence,
and bring down this broken government!
[crowd cheering]
[chanting] Tommy! Tommy! Tommy! Tommy!
Thank you.
Laura McKee.
-Battalion Commander, Fermanagh, IRA.
-You missed the first and second act.
-[woman] Thank you for coming, Mr Shelby.
-Thank you.
[Laura] The third act was enough.
You both have reasons to hate me and to
want to seek revenge for the killing...
[shushes]
Gypsy tradition.
We do not mention the name
of the dead in company.
Laura McKee, in the Shelby family,
business comes before issues of vengeance.
Our beloved departed
would understand and approve.
Let's go, boys.
Our agreement was
we meet in a crowded place.
No need for crowds.
We need you alive.
After you.
You know, Mr Shelby, even though
we've been doing business for a while,
we've never met in person.
You spoke with passion and compassion.
You understand forgiveness.
And you drink water.
Yet I heard from many reliable sources
that you have a reputation
for moral turpitude.
[chuckles and clicks tongue]
"Moral turpitude."
It's a good name for a racehorse.
-You don't know what it means?
-I know what it means.
It means you fuck people.
Fuck people over. Don't give a fuck.
It means you covet and steal
and burn all principles
for the sake of self-interest.
Well, I'm changing, Laura McKee.
And my organisation is also changing.
So what happened in Boston?
Jack Nelson said no.
Are we accepting "no" as an answer?
These are letters...
[clears throat]
...written to and by Jack Nelson
over the last three months.
This...
This is a private letter
from the president of the United States.
Where the fuck did you get this?
[Tommy sighs]
My racehorse "Moral Turpitude"
is just one of many in my stables.
Sometimes, even now,
I'll take her out for a run,
if there is a good cause
that requires her services.
Jack Nelson's coming to London.
Officially, he's coming
to buy liquor import licences.
Unofficially, he's on
a fact-finding mission.
He's coming to measure the strength
of support for fascism in Britain.
He'll report back to the president.
And how does that help us?
In this letter to his son,
Jack Nelson expresses
strong support for fascism.
In this letter,
to a friend in Berlin, he says
some interesting things about Jews.
He's not coming to Europe to find facts.
He's coming to find proof
that fascism will prevail.
And you and I
are going to help him in that task.
I thought you were a socialist.
[inhales]
Well, since I've entered politics,
I've learned that the line doesn't go out
from the middle to the left and the right.
It goes in a circle.
I'll show you.
You go far enough left,
eventually, you'll meet someone
who's gone far enough right
to get to the same place.
Working-class socialists like me,
working-class nationalists like you.
The result...
National Socialism.
And that's me.
In the middle.
Just a man trying to make
an honest living in a very dark world.
You have friends in Dublin, Laura McKee,
who are actively fighting
for a fascist Ireland.
And you are acting
on their behalf, ain't you?
When Jack Nelson comes to London,
I can give him access to Oswald Mosley
and to fascist sympathisers
in the House of Commons
and the House of Lords.
Both sides of the divide.
Fascism is quite the thing
among the very best people.
And with your help,
I can also offer him Dublin.
And you think this will allow us
to ship our merchandise to Boston?
Perhaps.
There may be other benefits
for your cause.
All you have to do
is sit with Jack Nelson and talk to him
about a new golden age,
and let him put a pin
in the map of Ireland
for the president of the United States.
[thudding]
I came to collect Arthur
and put him to bed.
Found him in Garrison Lane
with a syringe in his hand.
[sighs]
"A friend loves at all time,
a brother is born for adversity."
Proverbs 17:17.
Well, I have two brothers in need.
But yours is the more urgent, Tommy.
Will you come with me?
So, Laura McKee,
are you going to help me change the world?
Mr Shelby, this meeting
is not what I expected.
Never is.
Is that a yes or a no?
My answer is yes.
[scoffs]
The answer's always yes.
[Tommy] The back door is unlocked.
You can let yourself out.
And tell your friends back home,
Tommy Shelby has changed.
[train screeching]
[Tommy] Where is he?
[Ada] When I found him,
the syringe was empty.
He's sleeping it off on the cobbles.
Shit, Tommy.
Shit.
-It's all under control, Ada.
-I'm not under fucking control.
I'm not you, Tommy.
And I'm not Polly either.
Even though I'm trying to be.
She would have stopped this.
-We will pull Arthur through this.
-I'm not talking about Arthur.
I'm talking about you. I heard
everything you were saying in there.
Ada, this will be the end of it.
Hear me? This is the way out for us.
And along the way, I will be doing good.
No, along the way, you're gonna
make yourself a lot of money.
All right, fair enough.
Any incidental rewards
for my good work will be welcome.
-But you will get your fair share, sister.
-[scoffs]
And by being among the fascists,
by being among them, I can undermine them.
Polly would approve.
Beneath all the gold and diamonds
and fucking mink and lace,
she was a solid socialist.
[Ada] Look, I know
it's too late for this, Tom, but...
This doorway...
This same fucking doorway.
We used to come here for Dad's beer.
And we were so little,
it took two of us to carry one bucket.
Yeah, I remember.
Look at us now, eh?
Yeah. Fucking look at us.
Take a good look, Tom,
'cause one of us
isn't gonna be here for long.
Fuck! Opium and presidents.
Ada, if you don't want
to help me carry the bucket...
I wouldn't blame you.
But this is my mission.
And I will have no limitations.
Where are you, Tom?
Hmm?
My big brother?
You know, you used to stop
sometimes and laugh.
Do you even remember this place?
You walk into the Garrison like a stranger
and you sip fucking water.
I'm alive, Ada.
Yeah.
And you're still looking for trouble
big enough to kill you.
Well, I think you might have found it.
I have children, Tommy.
You have to carry this bucket on your own.
One brother half-dead
in the rain in Garrison Alley,
and the other has no limitations.
[distant opera music]
[lift thuds]
[Tommy] I'm expected.
[man] Oh.
And Mr Solomons no longer tolerates
the smoking of tobacco in his presence.
[opera playing over record player]
[music crescendos]
[music fades]
[vinyl hiss]
I always thought that opera
was just fat people fucking shouting.
[Tommy] Yeah? What do you think now?
[Alfie] I think the sound
of a tenor in full passion
reminds me of
the crying out of Italian soldiers
when they had my bayonet inside of them.
Ever since my own death,
I have been somewhat haunted by it.
Dear me.
But, instead of fighting these voices,
I decided to write their songs down
and turn them into an opera of my own.
Do not light that. No, no.
Were you not told I have a condition?
What I was told, Alfie...
is that you have withdrawn
and that you spend your days alone...
obsessing about opera singers.
[Alfie] Opera is not
fucking singing, is it?
It's not singing. It's the sound
that people make before a word.
And I do not allow smoking
because I do need to see fucking clearly.
All right?
What, do you sense
weakness in the Israelite?
Not a sense of weakness, no, Alfie.
A certain knowledge of it.
Since you have been sat here
writing your opera...
a member of your family has died.
Charles Solomons, your uncle.
He ran all the narcotics,
bootlegging, prostitution,
gambling syndicates out of East Boston.
But last January, poor old Charlie, well...
He was shot in the Cotton Club,
in the lavatory,
by men that you know,
and yet you did nothing, Alfie.
Now my opera is called "America"!
America is my fucking masterpiece!
The truth is, your uncle is dead.
Boston is gone.
And you,
once the big man who ran Camden Town,
now can't even extinguish
another man's cigarette.
Let alone his fucking life.
You need favours, Alfie.
I need a fucking final act, right?
Just a final fucking act for my opera.
Yeah?
Alfie,
I think I may have written your final act.
Why don't you sit down
and have a listen, eh?
I have five tons of pure, refined opium,
sitting in one of
my warehouses in Liverpool.
I have safe storage
off the coast of Canada.
I have men willing to distribute it
in Toronto, Quebec, New York and Boston.
The income would be immediate
and will shift
the balance of power in Boston
back in favour of the Solomons family.
[Alfie exhales]
In the final act
that I'm giving you, Alfie,
it is you who takes the revenge.
Why would you sell?
The Irish are being difficult.
The Italians are not an option.
Also, Alfie, you are my friend.
-Would you give me credit?
-No.
I will take property.
You own half the warehouses in Camden.
I'll take 'em and knock 'em down.
Build houses
for the needy and the deserving.
Hmm. Oh.
Hmm.
Yeah, well, the...
The Irish have always
been difficult, Tommy,
they have for about fucking 700 years.
[sniffs]
You know that I once saw an Irishman
arguing with the statue
of Oliver Cromwell in Parliament Square.
The argument went on for quite a while.
It went into the night
as his little voice echoed
all around the Houses of Parliament
as he got more and more angered.
Oliver Cromwell was reluctant, somewhat,
to answer his legitimate questions.
So angered, in fact, that eventually,
he punched the statue on the nose
and broke his fucking hand.
And there it is, you know,
the Irish Question.
How come you can remember so much
about what happened 200 years ago,
but you just can't remember
what fucking happened last night?
[sighs]
How much is a ton?
[door opens]
Johnny?
[door shuts]
Only me today.
Jack says a few more weeks...
[lock opens]
...and you'll be free.
When do you travel to London?
Tomorrow.
I came to say goodbye.
When you go to London,
stay away from the Devil.
Block your fucking ears if you have to.
I'll be with you, Michael.
I've been thinking about you.
Only you.
And don't worry about Tommy Shelby.
I have no interest in a dead man.
Jack says he has to die.
Well, you tell Jack to wait.
-If anyone's going to kill Tommy Shelby...
-It will be you.
I know.
I told Jack.
And Jack said, "Okay, let the kid do it."
And in return
he can collect the cash that Tommy won't.
Five million dollars.
The Devil will be dead.
The future belongs to us.
Oh, and, Michael...
Every night,
midnight in Boston, 5:00 a.m. in London,
I'll be wide awake in my big, wide bed,
and you'll be
wide awake in this prison cell.
And our souls will come together.
And we'll fuck.
I won't need an alarm clock.
And you won't sleep until I'm done.
Midnight fucks, 5:00 a.m.
Every day.
Because we trust each other.
Hmm.
[clamouring]
[man] You're a fucking traitor, Shelby!
You're a fucking scumbag! Bastard!
[Mosley] Darker.
[mechanical squeaking]
Bluer.
Sharper.
[thudding]
And also from below.
Darling, how's that?
You look absolutely terrifying, my love.
[Mosley and Diana chuckle]
Fuck lipstick.
Fun.
To launch the ship.
To a long and terrible journey, Diana.
Don't fucking let me down.
[man] Mr Shelby? Mr Shelby?
Daily Mirror.
-Sir...
-Fuck off!
May I ask why a socialist MP
would attend a fascist rally, sir?
[Tommy] Let him in.
Let me answer the question.
Mr Mosley's constituency borders my own.
We've worked together in the past.
He was once a socialist himself.
My role here tonight is to...
To act as a bridge between ideologies.
I'm in the middle.
Mr Shelby, you once shared
a platform with Mr Mosley.
Will you be sharing
the stage with him tonight?
No. I'm simply here
to remind my friend, Mr Mosley,
that the way of
the British people is compromise.
You can print that, pal.
Fucking rag.
[Lizzie sighs]
[Tommy sighs]
Lizzie, you should know
that Mosley's wife died six months ago.
So, give him your condolences, will you?
Tonight, he'll be with his mistress,
who is apparently a lady of some standing,
and has given him great comfort
in his time of grief.
[Arthur] Fuck off, you dozy bastard!
Move out of my fucking way!
What is Arthur doing here?
Mosley invited him. I agreed.
Arthur made me a promise,
which he appears to have broken.
[Arthur] Move!
I said fucking move!
-Move, I'm on the fucking list!
-I've tried my best.
-[Arthur] Get the fuck off me!
-He's hid some junk in his sock.
-Okay.
-[Arthur] Move it along!
Get out of my fucking way!
Oi!
Tommy!
-Come on. You're in.
-Tommy.
[Tommy] You're in. Come on, you're in.
-[Arthur] My brother, Tommy.
-[Tommy] Yep.
[Arthur] Johnny Dogs.
Mosley invited me.
-He said, "Wear a black fucking shirt."
-Here you are.
I said, "I'd look like
every other bastard."
-Lizzie!
-Come on.
[Arthur] You're an angel.
I know I've fucking let you down.
I've fucking let you down.
I know I have, all right?
I've fucking said sorry a million times.
I'll say it again. I'm sorry.
-[Tommy] Yep.
-[Arthur] Fucking sorry.
Look at Johnny Dogs,
look at the fucking state of him.
He looks like a fucking waiter.
-[Dogs] Shut up!
-Get me a fucking drink.
Johnny, take your shirt off
and give it to me.
For fuck's sake, Tom.
Take your fucking shirt off
and give it to me now.
Get it off!
Arthur, this is my fault.
-This is my fault.
-Yeah.
Remember, we voted on getting
involved in the opium trade, you voted no.
-I said no.
-Remember?
I overruled you.
-I've been away.
-Where you been, Tom?
Ada tells me you've been
hanging out with Mosley?
-Yeah, in Smethwick.
-Yeah?
At his big, beautiful fucking house.
And they have parties there in Belgravia.
And they give me fucking respect.
And what do you give them?
Snow and junk from the company.
Look at you, brother.
Half of you has gone.
-[Arthur] The fuck!
-[Tommy] Rag and bone.
You fucking slapped me.
You slapped me.
I have to remain unresolved.
Do you understand? Unresolved.
Unresolved in everything!
I have to move between
left and right, light and shade,
and maintain the trust of both.
And I cannot have my brother
wearing a fucking black shirt
on the cover of the Daily Mirror.
If anyone takes my picture in this,
they'll find their fucking camera
under my heel, Tom.
They're throwing petrol bombs
out there, Tommy.
-I thought Ada was taking care of you.
-Ada's got decisions to make
about working with us.
She doesn't know what she wants.
I'll speak to Ada.
-Listen, I'm going home...
-No, you stay there.
I have something for you.
Lizzie, you go with Johnny.
Johnny, take Lizzie to her seat.
I don't have an invitation.
You're wearing a black shirt,
you can do what you like. Go on.
I'll follow you. Go on.
Go on, Dogs.
Get me a fucking drink while you're there.
[groans]
[distant music and cheering]
I know, Tom, look at me.
Arthur, before I went
to America, I wrote a letter.
Yeah? Who to?
To Linda.
And in that letter, I wrote,
"Linda, as a Christian woman,
do you believe in forgiveness?"
This is what I got back.
Two days ago. Have a look.
"As a Christian woman,
I do believe in forgiveness."
Yeah, and the word "do" is underlined.
Arthur, I'm no Christian,
but I also believe in forgiveness.
Get yourself clean.
Stay clean for two weeks.
I'll write Linda another letter.
'Cause I know where she is.
First, I need you back.
I need my brother.
I've a lot to do.
Need someone to do the real work.
Yeah, look at you smile, Tom.
Look at your smile, brother.
It's been so long.
Come on, let's see
what this bastard has to say.
Come on.
-All right.
-Come on.
[Arthur] Yeah, I'm coming.
He is a bastard and all, Tommy.
Black shirts and Jews. Here we go.
Here we fucking go.
You stay in the middle
and do nothing, Tom.
But not fucking me!
Me and you, you Nazi bastard!
[men grunting]
[Arthur] You! You!
Come here, man.
I'll take your fucking eye.
[Tommy] Not here! Not here!
[grunts]
Come here. You've had your fun.
-Now let's go home.
-[Tommy] We have business.
[Lizzie scoffs]
[Tommy] Johnny, you get him home.
This time, check his fucking socks.
[Dogs] For fuck's sake.
Tommy, we should get out now.
Forget this American business.
We've got enough.
Not yet enough.
Here she comes.
Remember to smile.
-Come on.
-Shit.
[glass clinks]
Ladies and gentlemen, tonight,
he has truly earned your adulation.
The future prime minister
of this great country, Sir Oswald Mosley.
[crowd applauding]
[man] Fuck you, Mosley!
Fuck. I look terrible.
You look beautiful, Lizzie.
I need to impress this woman,
so I will act as if
she is beautiful as well.
Mosley.
Diana, this is Tommy Shelby, MP, OBE.
Mr Shelby, Lady Diana Mitford.
Oswald's most recent
and last ever mistress.
And this is my wife, Lizzie Shelby.
Beautiful earrings.
[Tommy] I stole them from Tiffany's.
Actually, he bought the earrings in Paris.
We were in Paris on our honeymoon.
-God, I hate Paris.
-[Tommy] Mmm.
I hear you prefer Berlin.
Oswald and I are going
to marry there, aren't we, Oswald?
Mosley, I have business to discuss.
Perhaps you and I
could find somewhere a bit quieter, eh?
Darling, Mr Shelby just made
the astonishing suggestion
that we men go off and discuss business
while you women
wait around looking glamorous.
[laughs] Goodness. What year do you
think this is, Mr Shelby, 1807?
In Birmingham,
the centuries grind by quite slowly.
But, Mr Shelby, if it's business,
Diana is the engine of my enterprise.
It's the modern way, Mr Shelby.
Yes, we know. I am company director.
I will join the meeting as well.
But of course,
you must come as well, Elizabeth.
By the way, I really don't like "Lizzie."
I prefer "Liberated Elizabeth."
She must be part of this.
She's been all the way to Paris,
so she is a woman of the world. Bravo.
Do you know,
Oswald's told me everything about you.
[Mosley] Only three
because I know
these days Mr Shelby doesn't.
[Diana] Our friend in Berlin
doesn't either.
Well, they have that in common, at least.
[Diana] I imagine
they have lots in common.
[Mosley] Hmm.
[smacks lips]
Report to me, Shelby.
Officially, Jack Nelson is in London
to buy import licences.
And unofficially, he's Roosevelt's envoy.
[Tommy] As you can see
from this private letter,
he is far from a neutral point of view.
Look at the bottom
of the second paragraph.
"Individually, Jews are fine,
but as a race, they stink."
[Mosley] Hmm.
Elizabeth,
do you even know why the bridge
to President Roosevelt is so important?
Actually, no.
I don't really know
much about this business at all.
[glass thuds]
But I have fucked your future husband.
So I know lots of things about him.
Tommy, I'll be outside.
Well done, Elizabeth.
-[door closes]
-[Tommy clears throat]
Do you people want to meet Nelson or no?
Mr Shelby...
From now on, can I call you Thomas?
[Tommy] If you like.
Of course we would.
And we are very grateful for your efforts.
[Mosley] But, Mr Shelby,
before this enterprise goes any further,
you really must
do something about your wife.
Mr Shelby?
Yes. Mr Nelson.
I came early.
I wanted to come and take a look
around this beautiful church.
You're Catholic, Mr Shelby?
I hoped that by suggesting
we meet in church,
it might make us both
more cautious with lies and truth.
Well, then, your hope would be forlorn.
There ain't no one listening here.
You don't believe in God?
No.
It was the way the Catholics are treated
in my country that made me angry.
Made me what I became.
What made you angry?
Slowness in anything.
I wanted to have everything already.
Two working-class Catholic boys.
Did they mess with you
when you were small?
Some man in the shadows.
I carried a screwdriver and a blade.
And everyone believed
I had the power to lay curses.
[Nelson] And do you?
[Tommy] Yes, I do.
[Nelson] First man I killed was a priest.
You?
[Tommy] A Prussian boy with green eyes,
who was already underground.
[Nelson] When'd you last kill
a man, Mr Shelby?
[Tommy] Four years ago.
His name was Tommy Shelby.
He drank whiskey.
You want me to allow you to enter my city
and deal narcotics that'll kill people?
You deal in whiskey, Mr Nelson.
I recently read a report,
by the Vatican, actually,
which said that whiskey
disproportionately kills
more of our Catholic brothers and sisters.
Whereas opium
is the sedative more often chosen
by Protestants and atheists.
In return, there are people in England
who you think I should meet?
Yes.
Yes. Like minds.
I'm here to buy import licences for booze.
The booze of the blue blood elite.
In America, we...
We like labels.
And aspiration.
Well, I have a brand
of my own vodka and gin.
You can add that to your portfolio.
I hear Shelby labels
are favoured by the working class.
Indeed. A fact of which I'm very proud.
They say you're a poet too?
No. I only read it.
There are some people in this country
who I'd like to meet.
Fascists.
Not the ones in boots and black shirts.
The ones in tuxedos.
I know men who are friends of the cause.
I also know men
who are enemies of the cause.
For many years now, I've been working
closely with Winston Churchill
in many different capacities.
I have his trust.
He's opposed to the rise of fascism.
You, I believe, see it as inevitable.
Well, I can give you men of influence
who support your cause.
I can also offer you a full report
on Churchill's strategies.
All this in return
for access to South Boston?
Alternatively, you can take on Churchill
on your own without my intelligence.
And I can sell my opium to the Jews.
You're a brave man, Mr Shelby.
A war hero, I hear.
Every war hero I ever met,
they're just someone
who wanted to get themselves killed.
[chuckles]
Do we have a deal, Mr Nelson?
I'll think a great deal
about what you've said.
Ruby, have you finished
your spelling, love?
Ruby? Ruby?
Ruby?
Ruby? What are you doing, love?
I can hear voices.
Coming from up the chimney.
What voices?
The grey man.
[man] Gentlemen,
Mr Thomas Shelby, Birmingham South.
Mister Speaker, I was raised in a family
that endured living conditions
that would test the morality
of even the most virtuous.
Indeed, even the best of us
would have our virtues
trounced and thwarted
by life and the meanness
and the bitterness
of an overcrowded British slum.
What would you know about virtue?
[clamouring]
[Lizzie] Quickly, please.
[Lizzie breathing heavily]
Therefore, Mister Speaker,
I intend to put before this house
a bill which will offer radical reform
in housing policy in this country,
in which slums are cleared,
new houses are built,
with new standards in health and hygiene.
Westminster 245. House of Commons.
[telephone ringing]
The time has come for change.
The people have had enough.
[giggles]
Let's open the windows, let in new light,
build a new Jerusalem,
brick by government-owned brick.
[all cheering]
Into there.
[Ruby coughing]
Good.
Doctor?
Yeah, Westminster 245.
Mr Shelby.
[Lizzie] "Tickner Maura, O Beng, O Beng,"
over and over again.
-[Michael] How is the family?
-[Polly] One of you will die.
-[Ruby] He's staring at me, Daddy.
-[Lizzie] A man with green eyes.
Can you stop the voices?
[Lizzie] There are no voices, my love.
[Ruby] It's the grey man.
He says he's coming for me.
And he's coming for Daddy as well.
-[man grunts]
-[Tommy gasps]
[telephone ringing]
[both grunting]
[man yells]
-[knife pierces]
-[screams]
[knock on door]
[man] Mr Shelby?
Is everything all right in there?
[knocking continues]
Mr Shelby?
Everything's fine. Everything's fine.
[telephone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Lizzie] Tommy?
Tommy. She has a temperature
of 101 and nothing is working.
-Just get here now.
-Lizzie?
-Please.
-Lizzie...
[sighs]
[breathes heavily]
Where is she?
She's with the doctor upstairs.
Listen, Tommy.
He said we shouldn't
come close to her in case...
In case of what?
When she coughs, there's blood.
Madonna, put me through to the number
I gave you for Esme Shelby-Lee.