A vacancy has appeared
and you're going to fill it.
From now on, Mr Shelby,
you shut your gypsy mouth
and listen to your instructions.
CAMPBELL: I know it was you who carried
out the murder of Mr Duggan.
-(GUNSHOT)
-You are on my hook, Mr Shelby.
-Name?
-Harold Hancox.
-Have you ever been arrested?
-No.
TOMMY: Arthur, we can stand him up.
Last night, one of our men had
his throat cut in Winston Green.
I'm not real!
Gentlemen? This is your cousin.
Polly's son, Michael.
-I want to go with them.
-Over my dead body.
Do we hear 800 guineas? 850.
MAY: May Car let on.
I breed race horses and train them.
-So will you consider me?
-I will consider you.
Thomas Shelby?
(GUNSHOT)
POLLY: Did they behave themselves?
They were really amazing.
(CHURCH BELLS RING)
You might think this is a curious
place for me to suggest a meeting,
but...
your surprises have only just begun.
You look a little unsteady, Mr Shelby.
Take a seat.
You're working together.
Blowing up the Garrison was your idea.
You chose me.
It's funny, I thought the
Fenians had a policy...
-Enough.
-Eh? Of not mixing
the personal with the political.
-I said enough.
-I think
I will decide on what is enough.
Who's in charge here then, eh?
Who's in charge?
Right, let me understand this.
-You answer to an agent of the Crown.
-CAMPBELL: Perhaps we can just...
-Very interesting.
-Perhaps we can stick to the agenda.
-Whose agenda?
-There is a form of words here.
-Whose words?
-Arrogant bastard.
I'm not accustomed
to being spoken to like that.
CAMPBELL: Just come to order.
I am here to listen,
but not to the fucking infantry.
Enough! Jesus!
Now...
Some weeks ago, Mr Shelby
carried out a military mission
on behalf of pro-treaty Republicans
here in Birmingham.
You...
Working for the King.
-There is a unique political situation.
-Yeah? How does that feel?
-Let us...
-Tell me. How does that fucking feel?
...stick to the form of words.
-Temporarily, we have a shared interest.
-Oh, I see.
-Shall we just stop him laughing?
-You want me to stop laughing?
Explain this, pal.
Following the success of your mission...
-We're going to make you do it again.
-Will you shut up?
Can we just conduct
ourselves here, please?
-Conduct ourselves!
-Please.
No one in this room wants to breathe
the same air as anyone else.
-Nevertheless...
-Nevertheless the pro-treaty Paddies
and the King want the same man dead.
Am I right?
-Why him?
-Did you ask why in France?
-Yeah.
-So, it's the same answer, because.
Why me?
-Because.
Because if anybody connects me to this,
it will be assumed
that it was a criminal act
and not a political one.
No, you need not fear being
connected to the killing
because I will see to it that
no connection is ever made.
You will have complete
immunity after the fact.
But, in the execution, you will get
no help from agents of the Crown.
And we can't be seen to be involved.
You have been chosen, Mr Shelby,
and there really is no choice.
No equals bang,
and your man here will shed no tears
as he looks the other way.
Nevertheless...
I say no.
CAMPBELL: Mr Shelby?
What about your export licence,
Mr Shelby?
You had a deal with Mr Churchill.
The one with the mouth,
Donal Henry, he is a spy.
He is working for the Irregulars
against the pro-treaty Paddies.
He reports every fucking
word back to them.
No, it's not possible.
They've both been security vetted
by my own department.
I have men in places your men can't go.
Donal Henry meets the
anti-treaty Paddies in the back room
of the Mother Red Cap in Saltley,
sometimes twice a week.
These Irish enemies are
fucking brothers and cousins.
You are stepping into a world
you don't understand.
If what you're saying is true,
he'll be dealt with.
Bring me proof the spy is dead
and we have a deal.
Mr Shelby.
-Billy boy.
-Watch it.
Now on you go.
Right, boys, let's go!
(SCREAMING)
(BOTTLE SMASHES)
Fuck you!
Mario!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Come here.
Sabini's day is done.
I'll protect you now.
Oh, shut up!
Stop fucking whingeing.
Due to my razor blade,
and a few complaints from the neighbours
about the terrible fucking music...
Do you want to tell them or should I?
This place is under new management.
By order of the Peaky Blinders.
(WOMEN GIGGLE)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
-(CLEARS THROAT)
-(KNOCKING)
TOMMY: Yes?
Somebody to see you, Mr Shelby.
He says he's come about the
position of accounts clerk.
Send him in.
-WOMAN: Just through here, sir.
-MICHAEL: Thank you.
Michael...
Vacancy's been filled.
Not according to this morning's paper.
At school, I was top of the
class in mathematics,
and I did a night school course in
accountancy at Worcester College.
Mum says you've had
six different accountant clerks
in the last six months.
When respectable men see the
other things you do, they leave.
But I, like Lizzie out there,
already know what you do.
Mum says you want to be 80% legal
within two years.
-Three.
-I can help.
I know both sides and
you know you can trust me.
I want to help you, Tommy, become legal.
Do the right thing.
I want to be proud of this family.
Does Polly know you're here, Michael?
I'm 18 on Friday, I go where I please.
You phone your mother.
Good luck.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
We're not open for winnings yet.
MAY: I'm here to see Thomas Shelby.
I have an appointment.
Come in.
-May Car let on.
-Mr Shelby has his proper meetings
in his other office.
This was the address that he gave me.
-He gave you this address?
-He said it was a gambling den.
I told him that I'd wanted to see one
since I'm always reading
about them in the papers.
Quite the big scandal
in The Telegraph lately.
Anyway, he said that
I could come and have a look.
And now I feel like a bit of an idiot
because I'm early and he's late
and I have no idea how to behave.
In a gambling den?
I'll wait in the car.
If I open the door again,
they'll all want to come in.
Like flies.
So what are you?
(STAMMERING) What am I?
To Thomas?
I'm going to train his racehorse...
For Epsom.
You know horses?
Yes. You?
Born riding.
I slept in a manger when I was a baby.
I was born riding, too.
(DOOR OPENS)
JOHN: There's a fucking
great Riley parked out there
and nobody's watching it.
John, this woman says
she's training Thomas' horse.
He's told us a lot about you.
Don't know where he is, do you?
(DOOR OPENS)
Sorry I'm late.
There was a family matter.
Esme, keep it locked up for a minute.
-Yes, Thomas.
-I'll show you around.
So, be my guest.
That's my brother Arthur's office.
Down there is my brother John's office,
that's where we slate
the runners and the riders.
It's so out in the open.
What about the police?
What about them?
When I drove into Small Heath,
I thought I was going to get murdered...
Then I mentioned your name.
It was like being escorted
to see a king.
-You came here to get my girl, right?
-Right.
She looks in very good condition,
considering she's not been
out on the gallops.
Curly's the best horseman in England.
I have a man called Mickey
who'd argue the point.
Ah, Curly here is half horse himself.
She's blessed. Very blessed.
Well, she's from the best stock.
But I'd rather have a coloured pony.
Mixed blood is stronger.
Not to win the Derby, Curly.
Don't like them racing, Tommy,
not the way they beat them.
-She's all yours.
-Thank you.
TOMMY: He gets sad when one leaves.
-What time is your box van coming?
-Midday.
Maybe you've got time to take
the lady to the Garrison,
show her the spa and the tearooms.
I'd like that, why not?
TOMMY: I just had it done up.
There was a fire.
It's...
Yeah.
What do you drink?
So early, but gin.
Goodness. With something?
Like what?
Tonic water or...
Erm... We have, erm...
Cordial.
There's not much room in there but...
You want to fuck me, Mrs Car let on?
Perhaps because I...
Perhaps because I would represent
something to you?
We should have this conversation
before the booze
starts talking for us.
You have a horse.
Yes, I have a horse.
The horse is why I'm here.
Purely that.
And because you're paying me a
lot of money to train your horse,
that's why I'm here.
Purely that.
Good.
Good. Well, a toast, then.
To the horse, to the Derby.
-Cheers.
So is that what you say to women?
Only if I don't know what they want.
And what if they don't want to fuck?
Then life is simpler.
You want a simple life?
Do I look like a man
who wants a simple life, eh?
So what do you want?
For what I'm paying you, Mrs Car let on,
I want a horse that'll pay out
at Epsom on an each-way bet.
Before I took your account,
I did some credit checks on you.
Apparently, you don't exist.
My existence is questionable.
Gypsies don't like registers.
You see, I'm not gypsy like you mean.
But you did register for France.
I also sent your name to the War Office,
I have friends there.
You won two medals for gallantry.
Does that really impress you,
Mrs Car let on?
Call me May.
Charlie says the box van's here.
Thank you, Finn.
You know, I still don't know what
you're going to call your horse.
The horse will be called Grace's Secret.
Grace's Secret.
I told him he definitely
can't take the job.
He said, "All right,
I'll move to London, then."
I said, "I won't give in to blackmail.
No is no."
Well... That settles it, then.
I'll give the job
to the other candidate.
He's much better qualified anyway.
Michael did City and Guilds, six months.
Yeah, but he doesn't know racing, Poll.
He knows horses,
but he doesn't know racing.
This other boy, he knows racing.
He's good. He's a fast learner.
What if Michael really leaves?
You just got to let him go, Poll.
He'll get a job in an office in London.
I'm sure he'll write to you.
He made a big speech
about wanting to help you
build up a respectable business.
Oh, he's like his dad,
he could make me cry.
There are trains to London.
So I just let him leave?
Every month or so he'd be back.
Unless, of course, he meets a girl.
Then, who knows?
Oh, my God.
You want him to do this job.
Polly, I want what you want.
What about this other more
qualified candidate?
Mmm...
Well, I lied, there isn't one.
How much you paying?
-The advertised rate.
-Like hell.
-Three bob.
-Three and six.
-Four.
Four it is.
-I love him, Tom.
-I know.
That's why I'll keep him away
from the old business,
put him charge of the new. Agreed?
Agreed.
Well, Finn, you've got two choices,
mild or mild.
-Mild.
-There you go.
-(DOOR OPENS)
-Here he is, look.
(CHEERING)
Happy birthday, Michael.
Eighteen years old. You're a man today.
Give him a drink, John boy.
-There you go, lad.
-And after that,
we'll go to find you
a lady of the night.
Arthur!
TOMMY: Michael. (CLEARS THROAT)
What's that?
TOMMY: So you're never late for work.
ARTHUR: Welcome to the business,
Michael.
-Welcome to the business.
-Thank you.
Right, come on, let's get him drunk.
Come here, you.
All right, whisky.
No whisky, he's at work tomorrow.
Give him only dark mild.
A toast.
-ARTHUR: Toast.
-To Michael.
ALL: To Michael.
(DOOR OPENS)
You all right?
-What is it? Just us?
-Just us.
POLLY: We celebrating?
TOMMY: Just taste this.
What do you think, Arthur?
Yeah, it's good.
Good stuff, really nice.
Too good for the Garrison.
I suppose we could shift it
to the toffs at the Eden Club.
Why? What is it?
That is part of an export drive.
We now have a secure warehouse
in Camden Town
and secure passage to the Poplar Docks.
So, on Monday morning,
we'll be sending out
our first export crates.
A crate of Riley car spares,
bound for Halifax, Nova Scotia.
Where there's prohibition.
Where there is prohibition.
All over Canada and America,
people are making their own booze
in bathtubs.
But rich people in New York,
in Toronto and Boston
are still paying a lot of
money for the real stuff.
So, on Monday,
the first Shelby company crates
will contain a thousand
Riley carburettors.
But hidden in the packing
will be 500 bottles
of the finest quality
single malt Scotch whisky.
And we Shelbys, have a licence
granted by the
Minister Of The Empire himself,
which means our crates
won't be searched.
And, Polly, all of the whisky
will be packed at the docks,
so Michael can do the books
without being involved.
Like I've been telling
you all for a year now,
motor cars are the future.
So, how is your life then, Tom?
On the up, Johnny, on the up.
But, Tom, really, come on, how is it?
You know I hate to
see you not even married yet.
I have a fine looking cousin,
she'll make your life hell.
You deserve her!
(CHUCKLING)
We haven't had a good old
wedding in a long time.
Rather look inside these boxes,
then, Johnny?
What do I want to look
at car parts, Tommy,
when I haven't even got a car?
Faith in family's a fine thing, eh?
And I wouldn't even be counting.
Twenty-five becomes 24, then 24 it is.
Oh, you know I'm no good
with numbers, Tom.
And if 24 ever became 23,
then that'd be tax.
We don't pay tax.
No, Tom.
Good man.
KITCHEN: I put an iron door on,
and we've put iron bars on the
windows and across the skylights.
TOMMY: Good.
So what will you
be keeping in here, Tommy?
Temptation, Billy. Temptation.
(DOOR OPENS)
Morning, Arthur. I was just passing.
ARTHUR: I think I'm in fucking love.
Drink!
She don't know where to look.
Whisky, Tommy?
No, I've got a long drive ahead.
You off home?
Mmm-hmm. Eventually.
To Birmingham.
What's this?
Olives.
Yes, it's miscellaneous.
It's, erm, olives.
Sticks, you know, with little bits
of fucking onion and things.
That's what that is.
We've taken 600 pounds on olives.
Yeah, with little bits of onion.
I told you, Arthur...
The dealers sell the cocaine,
we take a cut.
We don't sell direct.
The Home Secretary's cracking down
and I don't want this,
to fuck up everything else,
you understand?
I understand.
How much of that 600
came out of your pocket?
It's under control.
I put you down here cos people
are scared of you, Arthur.
But if you don't straighten up,
it'll be John's turn in London.
No need.
I can handle it.
It's under control?
It's under control.
Fucking tidy profit, though, eh?
It's happening, Tom.
Good.
TOMMY: Straighten up, soldier.
Yes, sir, Sergeant Major.
What's your business?
Sorry, I'm, er, I'm lost here.
Yeah, well, you can't stop here.
-Move on.
-All right.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Twenty-three seconds.
It's all right, Ada,
it'll be Andrew for me.
Oh.
I'm looking for Ada.
Who are you?
Ada.
I asked you a question.
It's all right, James.
This is my brother.
Who's he?
He rents a room.
You need to rent out rooms?
Actually, she doesn't charge rent.
He's a writer, which means he's skint.
You get up late these days, Ada.
Mmm. I go to bed late.
TOMMY: Yeah? Where's Karl?
What do you want, Tommy?
Oh, God, before you start
sizing him up for a wedding suit,
he's not interested in me.
-Or in girls of any kind.
-Ada!
What? Tommy won't judge you.
He sure as hell won't go to the police.
Look, I'll go and get dressed.
James...
I'm Thomas.
Pleased to meet you.
Can I have a minute
with my sister, please?
Yes, of course.
So, does your lodger know your name?
Yeah. Thorne.
You think I'd tell anybody
anything else?
Your Brummie boys
are all over the papers.
Just one last push, eh?
Then you'll go legit?
Just one more obstacle to get round,
then it'll all be straight?
Actually, yes.
(GIGGLING)
Personally, I find it quite amusing.
Men like you are becoming
very fashionable down here.
No society party in London
is complete without a gangster
for the girls to go giddy for.
Anyway, what is it that you want?
I don't have any children, Ada,
so I have set up a trust fund.
The beneficiaries
will be John's kids and Karl.
In order for Karl to benefit,
I need your signature.
I've set up an account.
The money will be transferred
in the event of my death.
It'll set them up for a new life.
Are you sick?
I'm just doing
what any ordinary man would,
putting my affairs in order.
DARBY: Did you know they was
going to take the Eden club?
ALFIE: I know about the Eden club, yes.
Did you know they were going
to do it before they did it?
Because that's someone
who's in charge, isn't it?
The one who knows before it happens.
I know what I know, you know.
If you don't know,
then you don't fucking know, do you?
Did you know they was going
to take Wimbledon Docks?
Harringay? The trotting tracks?
Talk, all right?
I genuinely want to hear you.
You've lost control, Alfie.
ALFIE: Have I?
MAN: Everybody knows.
-Talk to me, Alfie.
-Talk to you?
All right, I'll talk to you.
I'll fucking tell you how it was, right?
What happened was this.
All the time you were talking about
dirty fucking Jews.
All the fucking time,
dirty fucking Jews, dirty Kikes,
dirty dustbin lids...
-Everyone makes jokes.
-You want to talk about
-not getting into places?
-Everybody makes fucking jokes.
I didn't know you had
no sense of humour!
And I ain't going
to fucking mention, right,
the great big fuck off elephant
in the room.
Look, Alfie...
How many of my bookies
worked Epsom this last May?
None. None.
Not one.
So, for a few fucking jokes and Epsom,
you fucking invite
a tribe of savages into the city
and just fucking
unlock the fucking gates!
I'm sorry, what are you saying, mate?
I'm saying...
I'm sorry about the Jew thing.
-You saying you're sorry?
-Yeah.
-You're sorry about the Jew thing?
-Really?
-Yeah.
I want that in writing.
Write that down. He said, "I'm sorry".
And also write down
that all our bookies
can go back to Epsom.
-He didn't say that.
-Who's asking you?
Eh.
Write it down.
It's all right. Come on.
Alfie's an old friend.
My friend.
Now, admit it,
the Peaky Blinders is out of control.
Yeah, they're out
of fucking control, mate.
They come down the canal,
they spread like the fucking clap.
Right. So now they're
-everybody's problem.
-Yeah.
-Alfie.
-Mmm.
You and me, we've been fighting
-since we was at school.
-Yeah.
All right? Now, also,
-we've been friends.
-Mmm, yeah.
You know,
it goes backwards and forwards.
How much better is it
when we're friends?
Oh, it's much better, mate, yeah.
You write that down.
Mmm.
So what we're doing here, right,
is we're writing down some
kind of a deal thing, right?
-Yeah, a written deal.
-Written deal, good.
Well, why don't we discuss
the border between the Italians
and the Jews going back
to Farringdon Road.
-Farringdon Road...
-Yeah, Farringdon Road.
Fuck! That's ancient history.
-Write down Farringdon Road.
-No, no, no, write down Camden Road.
-Farringdon Road.
-Camden Road.
-Write down Farringdon.
-Camden.
-Farringdon.
Write down Camden Road.
Just write down "peace".
Just write down "peace", right,
between the Jews and the Italians.
And war against the gypsies.
Fuck.
(DOOR OPENS)
MAID: Mr Thomas Shelby, madam.
Nice house.
Would you like a whisky?
Scotch or Irish?
Irish.
(GLASSES CLINKING)
Sorry for the short notice.
I was passing.
We're not quite on the Birmingham road.
It was a small diversion.
Sixty miles, I checked.
That's a small diversion these days.
So, I'm a small diversion.
Good.
Your horse is still out on the gallops,
but I had Mickey prepare this report.
You can read it now if you'd like,
then we can go see her.
-(CLEARS THROAT)
-ls there enough light for you to read?
Yes, it's fine.
It's getting quite late.
Mickey says she has
the lungs of an elephant.
She's nimble in the heavy going,
but bounces a little on the hard ground.
Sorry, I'll let you read.
So, he thinks she'll favour
good to soft ground, eh?
-A little juice in the grass.
-Mmm.
Well, that's good for Epsom.
Does he think she's
not good enough for Epsom?
She needs a lot of work.
The race board will need convincing.
-I imagine you have some influence.
-Mmm.
That's the suggested program me
for the next two months.
Your glass is empty.
It's fine.
Are you hungry?
Yes, a bit.
I can prepare something.
Do you have engine oil?
Before I set off for Birmingham,
the car needs oil.
I'm sure my husband
kept some in the garage.
I can get someone to do it.
This evening or tomorrow?
Well, we're so far from anywhere,
people usually stay over.
Especially before cars,
when it was just carriages,
people used to stay over all the time.
But I have a car.
Yes.
And you have engine oil.
Probably.
But it would be very usual.
What would?
For a guest to stay.
We have a whole wing
called the guest wing.
Oh, you...
You have a guest wing.
Well...
May.
(BREATHING UNEVENLY)
Have a smoke.
Thank you.
Ignore this. It's actually all right.
I put all his photos
in a drawer and locked it...
As if that was going
to make a difference.
I'm like a fucking lighthouse keeper...
Out here on my own...
Keeping his flame burning.
But, of course,
when anyone sees a lighthouse
they steer clear, don't they?
Now, do you have a map?
Of the house. Do you have a map?
Because I'm not going to be able
to find my way in the dark.
You see, at midnight,
I'm going to leave my wing
and I'm going to come find you.
And I'm going to turn the handle
of your bedroom door
without making a sound
and none of the maids will know.
You don't know maids.
They hear a pin drop?
If there's a man in the house,
they listen.
They take turns.
So, let them listen.
Right. Day rate, seven shillings.
Loading, unloading.
Night rate, three. Total ten.
Let's go and get a drink.
No, I'm all right.
Come on, it's payday.
Everybody has a drink on payday.
Not me.
You think your mum
don't have a drink on payday?
You think the Lord Almighty
Man, it's on fire out there,
women from the BSA offices, honest.
They go out on their own
without their men these days,
in twos and threes now.
Mickey, they go out in twos and
threes and buy their own drinks.
The Marquis,
that's where the BSA secretaries go.
Look, they won't serve a black man
without a Shelby by his side.
So you're using me?
Yeah.
Come on.
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
I told you, I fucking told you,
this city's gone mad.
Girls go out on their own now.
Two pints of dark mild, please.
Fuck that. We're Peaky boys.
Two whiskies.
You get used to it, then you can't stop.
(WHISTLING)
I don't drink with blacks.
Here we fucking go.
Paddy, they're okay.
Not with me, they're not.
I don't drink in pubs with blacks.
So leave.
Look, my dad is the preacher round here.
He has connections, ask anybody.
I couldn't give a fuck who he is.
I'm telling you to leave it, Paddy.
And I'm telling this darkie
to get out of here.
You know something? Fuck off.
It's all right, Isaiah, come on,
leave it.
-We'll go to my cousin's pub.
-I like it here.
You fucking nigger.
(SHOUTING AND SCREAMING)
Paddy! The white kid's a Peaky Blinder!
He's Polly Shelby's son!
Are you fucking suicidal?
Sir...
Sir, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Get out!
Get out the fucking pub.
I clearly didn't know.
Fuck, let's go. Let's go!
We ordered some drinks
and we're going to drink them.
His face, man.
Did you see his fucking face?
You punch like a fucking kangaroo.
I seen one once in a circus,
you punch like that.
All right, anyway,
I need a fucking drink.
-It's on you.
-It's on me? You just got paid.
Yeah, from you.
You can get a whisky,
maybe even a dark mild.
Fucking hell,
it's packed in here, isn't it?
JOHN: So it's as easy as that?
Easy as that, John boy.
London, you wouldn't believe it.
Finn, stick your head in a bucket.
No.
The women, John boy, the women...
I've got this one,
she's a dancer, right?
She can do things with her...
If Finn would just piss off,
I'd explain a little bit better.
Well, if it's so good, why are you here?
Decent pints.
The cockneys can't get that right.
He misses us, Finn, that's what it is.
Here they are, look, junior Peaky boys.
What's happened to you?
You been scrapping?
Some idiots at the Marquis of Lorne.
Tried to stop me and Isaiah
from drinking, but it's all right.
We fought them off.
Arthur, we had to stand
our ground and we did.
The Marquis, eh? Where's your dad?
-Preaching.
-Right.
Don't nick any of me chips, Finn!
-Where are you going?
-ARTHUR: We won't be long.
Where are they going?
The Marquis of Lorne.
Shame.
It was a nice pub.
(MOANING)
Eh-up. Bet the big bastard got cut.
You didn't have to do that for me.
We didn't do it for you, Michael.
We did it for the good name
of the company.
None of this happened, all right?
Come on, let's go and get that drink.
(DOOR SLAMS OPEN)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
CAMPBELL: The date has been set.
Three weeks from today.
You checked out his house?
There's coppers all over it.
You'll take care of them?
No. That would arouse suspicion.
You'll have to deal with them yourself.
And if a copper gets killed?
There will be no consequences
for you, I have given you my word.
Which I know to be worthless.
That is why I have been settling
my affairs in the event of my death.
(CHUCKLING) And making your peace
with God, perhaps?
Well, good luck with that.
I have made arrangements
with men I trust.
If I should die,
then you will die.
Know that.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
Ritz Hotel. (CLEARS THROAT)
London, Piccadilly.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
-Who was that?
-Call got cut.
I guess the telephone lines
in England are not so good, huh?
Hm.
http://hiqve.com/