A daughter lost, a son found.
He is yours.
[Tommy] Evadne Barwell?
-[gunshots firing]
-[women scream]
[Nelson] Since you have proven
your commitment,
Boston is now officially open
for the importation of your merchandise.
Jack says a few more weeks,
and you'll be free.
The stories about you come up the canal.
Once you walked fine alone,
now you need a stick.
[Tommy] Stay clean for two weeks.
I'll write Linda another letter.
[Holford] Have you recently
suffered seizures?
It is tuberculoma.
I am afraid it is inoperable.
[pulsing music playing]
Mr Shelby, I only gave
opium to your brother
because he give me big trouble.
He attacked my wife.
[timer ticking]
I'd like a pot of green tea, please.
[ticking continues]
[clears throat]
It's taken me ten years
to build this business.
Your business will be safe
if you do what I say.
How much opium do you have in your cellar?
Five pounds.
Bring it to me.
Four minutes against the clock.
[exhales]
[Tommy] As a Member of Parliament...
for this constituency,
it is my duty to take responsibility
for the welfare of my constituents.
The clock is still ticking.
Consumption of opium
is very prejudicial to health.
Women give it to their children
so they can leave them untended
while they work in the factories.
Men lose their jobs
when they become addicted.
[clicks tongue] From now on, you will sell
only cigarettes, cake and tea.
If I hear that you're selling opium again,
time will indeed run out
very quickly for you, understand?
Yes. I understand. I will stop.
Mr Shelby, the clock is still ticking.
[in Chinese]
I don't think it's a real bomb.
[in English] Please tell
your suppliers and your customers
that from now on,
there will be no more opium
in Small Heath or in Bordesley.
Thank you for the tea.
[Li in Chinese] You see.
It was not a real bomb.
[water splashes]
[people screaming]
[dogs barking]
[Tommy] You can let 'em through now.
[officer] Yes, sir, Mr Shelby.
You tell the pub and cafe owners
on Montague Street,
if there's any further trade in powder,
there will be no more Montague Street.
I'll have it demolished
and replaced by apartments.
By order
of the Birmingham Urban District Council.
[machine whirring]
Sorry, I'm late.
They closed Montague Street.
There was a gas explosion or...
It would be nice if just one thing
could happen in Birmingham
that wasn't our fault.
I've gathered you all here today
because there is news.
It is of interest to the whole family.
First of all,
I'd like to welcome
Finn's new wife, Mary, to the family.
[smacks lips] I'm very glad
that I dragged myself out of bed for this.
[sighs] There is
one more item of business.
-Johnny.
-Tom.
[footsteps receding]
Come on. Come on, will you?
Everyone,
this here is Erasmus.
Nobody calls me that.
[clicks tongue] They call him Duke.
[sighs] Twenty years ago,
at Appleby Horse Fair, I met a girl.
We shared the shade of a hazel tree.
[Ada exhales]
Nine months later, this lad was born.
[clicks tongue]
This is my son.
His mother died on the road.
Up until now, I never tried to find him.
But I'm trying
to look at life in a different way.
A child is a precious thing.
So I'm bringing him...
Into the fucking family
with a snap of his fingers.
[Tommy] No. Bringing him into the fold.
He'll have to earn
membership of the family.
For the moment, welcome, son.
You have a seat, go on. Sit down here.
There are some mistakes I've made
that I can never redress.
Some I can.
Some wounds I can try to heal.
New wounds you can open up.
Anyway, that's the business of the day.
[Tommy clears throat]
Is it too early for whiskey?
There you go.
Shelby breakfast for you, son.
I don't drink.
And I'm not a Shelby.
-All right? I'm a Duke.
-[Dogs scoffs]
[chuckles]
You're a fucking Shelby, all right.
Don't worry about that.
[grunts]
I think we'll need Curly and a strong rope
to break this one in, Tom.
Arthur, open up the shop.
Put the kid here on the blackboard,
writing up the odds.
I can't write.
Put the kid here on the blackboard,
wiping off the chalk.
[Arthur snorts]
Go on, son.
Come on, then.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Lizzie.
Come on.
[Duke] My father
was the Duke of Saxon Shore.
My mother was a Romani queen.
[Arthur] Who told you that, your mum?
I don't allow people
to talk about my mother.
Good for you.
So let's get this right, then.
You can't read.
You can't fucking write.
Nothing wrong with that.
What can you do, eh?
I can tell the time.
Tell the time.
Here, he can tell the time.
Ain't that clever?
It's a lot more
than what you can fucking do.
[Arthur] What did you just say to me?
What time is it, Mr Shelby?
That's what I can do.
You little bastard.
[chuckles]
Here. Keep it.
Stop you from being late in the future.
[footsteps approaching]
Is there forgiveness in your heart
for Arthur Shelby?
No.
But there may be forgiveness from God.
[clicks tongue]
And you will do God's work.
God is interested in you as well, Tommy.
God will be with you on your journey.
Every step of the way.
He may not need to take many steps.
So tell me this, Linda.
Is God interested in me
or in my money?
[exhales]
I believe you run a foundation,
and that your foundation
has many missions across the world.
But in these times of financial crisis,
funding is hard to come by.
[sniffs] So, perhaps,
your God's plan is a practical one.
Perhaps he would like me
to make a donation to your foundation.
And in return, he would like you
to help my brother
on his road to redemption.
Now, I know
that in a place of worship such as this,
you would never ask how much.
So I will tell you plainly.
I will write your foundation
a check for £10,000...
Praise the Lord.
...if you agree to look kindly
on Arthur and to help him.
I need to look after
everyone in the family.
Do we have a deal?
Your money will be spent
to do good around the world.
And a mission will be named after you.
[scoffs]
But I'm only agreeing to help him,
not sleep with him.
No.
No, I imagine the negotiation
for that particular favour
would take a considerable amount of time.
And I have an appointment.
[Tommy] God bless.
[indistinct chattering]
[seagulls squawking]
Apologies for
the initial misunderstanding.
My brother dealt with it.
[clicks tongue]
For the care you took.
Even though I succumbed to temptation?
Part of the reason my brother is back
dealing with it, is down to you.
You spoke to him.
As a comrade.
The beating is still owed to you.
Do you still do that kind of work
yourself, Thomas Shelby, MP?
Mr Stagg, you see,
I can use a man like you.
I have friends that are in need of guns.
Soon there will be a shipment
of Thompson submachine guns,
coming here from Boston.
I need you to unload
and store those weapons.
There will also be ammunition.
Like this.
You have a good look.
And I need you to take better care
of the guns and ammunition
than you did of the powder.
You understand?
Previously,
all of my import and export
went through Belfast docks.
Now we're dealing with Boston...
I am considering shifting
my supply line to Liverpool.
You'd be a very rich man.
Don't you ever say thank you?
Thank you.
Is that why you do it, Mr Shelby?
Is that why you keep all this going?
To help people say thank you?
You could close all this down.
You could leave the sport behind.
You could live
like an ordinary, mortal man.
On your gravestone.
"An ordinary, mortal man."
But instead,
you still go around collecting "please,"
and "thank you," and "sorry,"
and "forgive me, Mr Shelby."
That what it's all for?
You want to know?
You want to know why I've carried on...
[inhales and exhales]
...all these years?
It's so I can do this.
And then
do this.
Feel it?
I feel it.
Junk doesn't even come close.
[sighs]
Soon, Mr Stagg,
when my last bit of business is done,
I will, indeed,
be an ordinary, mortal man.
You have a good day.
[Finn] Arthur.
We've got a problem with the referee.
He's not taking the money.
He's fucking religious or something.
[Arthur] Jesus Christ.
With Tommy away, you're in charge
of gambling, Arthur. What should we do?
"And this they said to him,
that they may have some charge
to bring against him."
Arthur.
This referee is threatening
to go to the police...
"Jesus bent down
and with one finger,
he wrote on the ground."
Arthur. [sighs]
Brother.
People are laughing at you.
So, I just phoned our holy referee again.
He basically told me to fuck off.
Not even basically, actually.
He literally just told me... to fuck off.
[Arthur] Is that right?
So, do you know?
[Finn sighs] For fuck's sake.
-Do you know what he wrote on the ground?
-No.
-Do you know? You don't know, do you?
-No. No, I don't.
Billy, do you know what he wrote
on the ground?
-I...
-Hmm?
Do you know what Jesus wrote
on the ground?
He bent down and with one finger,
he wrote on the fucking ground.
You know? Do you know what he wrote?
-Come on, Billy.
-[groans] No.
[Finn] Arthur, what should we do?
[Arthur] Go and get me the referee.
Bring me the fucking referee.
[Finn grunts]
[both breathing heavily]
[Tommy exhales]
[Lizzie exhales]
[Tommy] I know she's here with us.
Always.
But still it's just you and me.
I thought it would be good
if we were in a different place.
I hate that house now.
I wish I could blow it up.
There was a time
when we'd say nothing afterwards
because we didn't have to say anything.
But now we've got nothing left to say.
There's business.
What business?
The American.
He's coming to Birmingham.
He's stopping over
on his way to Liverpool.
He's staying with us tomorrow night.
Frances knows. She's making up a menu.
And then,
we have to make a move.
Do you want to know
what that move is, Lizzie?
No.
I know enough.
Your book of regrets.
23, 24, 52, 55.
Combination to the safe.
Regrets.
And I'm on there.
I'm on the list.
On the very top of the list.
[glass clinks]
[Tommy clicks tongue] Yep.
Yes, you are.
I regret marrying you, Lizzie.
Because I put you through so much.
Put you through all of this.
Ruby.
Everything that is to come.
When you married me, you married a man
and you married a curse.
You have shared my fate.
That is my regret.
But know this, Lizzie.
In this moment,
in this room...
I love you.
You sound like
you're ticking a fucking box,
and I don't know what's inside the box.
Never have you let me in.
Even though I know
the combination to the safe.
[Lizzie breathing heavily]
[Arthur] So this is him, is it?
You're the one
that likes to be fucking difficult, eh?
When I leave this place,
I'm going straight to the police.
-[Arthur] You are?
-This man pointed a gun at me.
-Who? Him there?
-[Wilfred] Yeah.
Well, let's phone the police, eh?
Don't worry.
We'll have this sorted out for you.
Hello. Yes.
Get me the police.
Reports of a man
with a revolver on Watery Lane.
There you go.
And you ask for Inspector Moss.
Chief Superintendent Moss.
He's in charge of Watery Lane
and Bordesley Green.
That's right.
And you see this?
That's his betting credit with us.
He makes a lot of money
from football matches
because we give him the results
before the match.
[slams dossier]
[receiver bangs]
On Saturday afternoon,
you take this whistle and you blow.
You give a penalty
to Birmingham City in the final minute,
the goalkeeper
will let the penalty go by him,
and Birmingham City will win one-nil.
All you gotta do is...
[clears throat]
[blows whistle]
[snorts]
No.
I won't do it. If the police won't listen,
I'll go to the newspapers.
I'm not afraid.
I was in France.
Phone Tommy, Arthur.
You shut up.
We're not phoning fucking Tommy.
-I am dealing with this, okay?
-I'm leaving.
You're not going fucking nowhere.
[Wilfred] It's time one of us
stood up to you.
It's not right what's been happening.
I will not take money to cheat.
Fucking hell.
-[Arthur breathes heavily]
-In France, I ran at the wire,
and I was not afraid.
I am not afraid.
I won't do a bad thing.
I've seen too many bad things.
A beating will make no difference.
I know that
'cause I can see it in your fucking eyes.
Oh, fuck.
In the bleak midwinter...
Holy Mary, Mother of God.
-[exclaims]
-[Arthur] All right, Billy boy.
You've been in the family long enough.
Yeah. It's time for you to get bloodied.
-Arthur, you can't.
-[Billy] Arthur, please.
-You've been with us for long enough.
-Fuck, Arthur! Jesus Christ!
Look, I can't be that man, Arthur, please.
[Arthur] Either two men
die today, Billy, or one.
You fucking decide.
[Billy groans]
-Hate him, Billy, you hate him.
-[Billy whimpers]
Come on. You don't know him, Billy.
He's fucking laughing at you. Come on.
Hate him.
-Look him in the eyes.
-[Billy] Please, no!
-I can't. I can't!
-[Arthur] Look him in the eyes.
Hate him!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
-[Billy grunts]
-[Wilfred chokes]
[Billy screaming]
[Wilfred gurgles]
Enough. Enough. Enough.
All right. Billy, come on.
-[shushes]
-[Billy sobs softly]
It's all right. It's all right.
Look at you. Look. Look at you. Look.
You're bloodied now, Billy.
You're bloodied now.
You're not going to heaven no more.
They won't let you in.
Isiah, you take him to the foundry,
you ask for Mr Patches, all right?
You tell him
we got some fuel for the furnace.
[footsteps]
[whistling tune]
[whistling approaches]
[footsteps approaching]
Who the fuck are you?
[Billy screams]
-I hear...
-Please.
...you're the informant
inside the Shelby organisation.
No.
And who the fuck I am
is the man you now work for.
[breath shaking] Please.
I have something I need you to do
and I want to impress upon you.
-To impress upon you...
-[Billy screams]
-[Billy moans]
-...the seriousness of my intent.
'Cause, you see, I used to do
this kind of thing for a living.
And sometimes, I kind of miss it.
Just like Mr Shelby.
I miss the wave of electricity
you get under your scalp.
I miss the taste, like metal,
on the tip of your tongue.
I'm about to give you an instruction.
You do as I say, you stay a man.
Fail, and I will send people to serve
your balls to you on a china plate.
I'll do what you say.
A decision's been taken.
My associates are gonna
take care of Thomas Shelby
and you are gonna
give us up his brother, Arthur.
Do you understand?
Yes, yes. Fucking yes. Please.
[panting]
Only information leading to the murder
of Arthur Shelby will save you
from an Italian death.
'Cause it was the Italians
that taught me that above God,
above children, above his wife
and above his mother...
Most of all, a man loves his balls.
[Billy whimpers]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[sobs]
[door opens]
[keys clatter]
[breathing heavily]
[liquid spills]
[sniffs]
[object thuds]
[sniffles]
Hello, Arthur.
I think we should pray.
-That's how we begin this.
-You'd like to pray.
The prayer I've chosen
is the Act of Contrition, version two.
Are you Catholic now, Linda?
You're Catholic.
Quakers don't pray.
Bow your head, Arthur,
and close your eyes.
Recite the prayer. You know it well
from when you were a boy.
My mind's all dried up with junk, though.
And shot full of fuck...
Shot full of holes. It's...
Linda, please.
[Linda] It's in there somewhere, Arthur.
It's like a song.
[Arthur] Yeah.
-Somewhere.
-Together, we'll find it.
Digging for the words
will help clean your soul.
I'll begin it.
"Forgive me my sins, oh, Lord,
forgive me my sins."
"The sins of my youth..."
"The sins of my youth, the sins of my age,
the sins of my soul."
"The sins of my body..."
"The sins I know, the sins I know not."
"The sins I have concealed for so long."
"For so..." Fuck...
"For so long."
Caught him stealing a car.
And he's got a stack of cash
from the betting shop.
Steal from who you want.
Don't steal from me.
Here you are.
Get a train to wherever the fuck
you want to go and get out.
-I don't ride trains.
-[Tommy] That a fact?
Well, Curly has a two-wheeled wagon.
What am I, a tinker?
I need four wheels.
All right? And a horse for the hills.
Which hills?
All of them.
All the hills of England.
[scoffs]
Why do you want to leave?
I didn't take to that work
in the betting shop.
Well, you heard him, Charlie.
Get my dad's old four-wheeled wagon
and two strong ponies.
All right.
[Charlie] Curly. Get here.
Before you go, you want to know
the truth about yourself?
No.
Who does?
Right, well, I'm gonna tell you.
That spring in Appleby Fair,
your mother stole my watch and chain.
You're from a long line of thieves.
The watch had the words
"Saxon Shore" carved in it.
Stole it myself
from a drunk when I was a kid.
I imagine she told you, your dad
was the Duke of the Saxon Shore. Well...
[clicks tongue] I am the Duke.
It was my watch.
I'm your father.
That's the truth.
When her dad found out, he shot me
in the chest with a squirrel gun.
A scar, a stolen watch
and a story she made up.
That's all you need to know about yourself
before you get on the road.
Esme tells me the spirits favour you.
That the spirit is in you.
She tried to sell me like
one of those horses, didn't she?
How much did you pay for me?
I have no use for gold any more.
But if you are a horse,
you're in the right place.
Curly!
Curly, hurry up!
This boy has hills to climb.
I remember that watch.
Oh, yeah?
She used to wear it over her heart.
We buried it with her.
Tom.
The old wagon's
right front wheel is fucked, Tom.
Standing in the wet.
Put a new wheel on, Curly.
They fix wagons here.
Good families come from the New Forest,
get their wagons fixed,
and fresh horses before the fairs.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like it here.
Like it better than that betting shop.
[Tommy] Why?
People.
People piss me off.
There are a lot of people
in that betting shop.
So far, here, what? I've only counted two.
[Tommy] Mmm-hmm.
Charlie and Curly.
The rest is dogs and horses.
Curly's half horse himself.
[Duke] Dogs are okay.
Horses are better than people, mind you.
There's work here
for a man who knows horses.
Unknown.
I want to remain completely unknown.
You'd be in the right place for that
as well. No one knows anyone here.
Hey, mister, save that wheel a minute.
Where would I stay?
The stables.
With the other stallions.
Now that Finn is married off,
plenty of girls around here.
Fathers are mostly unarmed.
I have a future for you, Duke.
You already have a son.
My business has two sides.
Light and dark.
I'll need someone for each.
And I'm dark, am I?
I've realised we don't get
to choose which one we are.
Dark knows dark.
And my affairs, both light and dark,
will need settling soon.
Curly?
Find a shovel
for the Duke of the Saxon Shore here.
-Get him shovelling shit.
-[chuckles]
[Tommy] And put some petrol in the boat.
I have to meet a lady in Solihull.
["One Silver Dollar" playing]
♪ One silver dollar ♪
♪ Bright silver dollar ♪
♪ Changing hands, changing hands ♪
♪ Spent for a beer he's drinking ♪
♪ Won by a gambler's lust ♪
♪ Pierced by an outlaw's bullet ♪
♪ And lost in the blood red dust ♪
♪ One silver dollar ♪
Take a look at her.
Now imagine ten people living on-site.
Step on, have a look inside.
I've had a response
from the Guinness Trust
about building charitable housing
on two sites along the canal network
between London, Birmingham and Liverpool.
This lock here will be one of the sites.
I have the permission.
Just need the finance.
I know that you and your husband,
Bryan Guinness, are estranged.
But I understand you still have
influence in the Guinness family.
[scoffs]
Your support might help them
make their decision.
Will you help me?
I've booked a suite in a hotel
a mile from here.
My chauffeur will take us there.
You look quite the thing
dressed like that, like a working man.
They'll probably show you
to the coal house to make your delivery.
Yep, they probably will.
Oswald has fucked your wife, so,
my suggestion is about
balance and proportion.
It would be only fair.
Can I assume
I have your support?
This isn't about charitable housing,
this is about changing the world.
It's about a different kind of trust.
Absolute trust.
We have important work ahead of us.
It's much harder to lie with your body
than with your words.
This I have learned.
Mostly, I do whatever I want to do.
Sometimes I do things for the cause.
In this case, it's both.
Come.
[both breathing heavily]
Oh, my God!
In the interests of absolute clarity,
that is simply the English aristocracy's
way of shaking hands.
[exhales]
So...
Welcome.
[exhales]
["Unmade" playing]
[vocalising]
♪ Come under my wings, little bird ♪
[grunts]
[gasping]
♪ Unmade ♪
♪ I swear that there's nothing ♪
♪ Up my sleeves ♪
♪ And then back again ♪
♪ I swear there's nothing ♪
♪ Unmade ♪
[lighter clicks]
♪ There's no faces ♪
♪ Won't grow back again ♪
[gasps]
♪ Broken pieces ♪
[Polly] If you do this thing,
the possibility of war
you have to consider.
[Michael] It was the ambitions
and strategies
of one man that caused this.
[Polly] There will be a war in this family
and one of you will die.
♪ Nothing ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ Won't grow back again ♪
♪ I swear there's nothing ♪
We need to leave early
to catch the first train to Liverpool.
-Yes?
-[Tommy] Yep.
So we eat early, finish early.
You changed the combination of the safe.
Why?
Have you got new secrets?
With this new business at hand,
there are some things that I cannot share.
What things?
[glass thuds]
What are those tablets?
Doctor gave 'em to me.
Painkillers?
-Yep.
-What pain?
Any pain that comes, Lizzie. [sighs]
When you're ready, I want you to tell me
everything that's going on.
It's like the clock stopped ticking
and I'm waiting for the bomb to explode.
We're in that quiet minute.
Tommy?
That's where we live now.
When I know everything,
I will tell you everything.
[Nelson] No, Gina's running wild, you see.
Harrods, dope, amphetamines,
lords and ladies,
the whole English aristocracy thing.
Fuck wine. Whiskey.
-Shelby, you having whiskey?
-I'll stay on wine.
[Nelson] Fuck wine.
More whiskey. I'm celebrating.
Celebration, you know?
Getting off this fucking island.
You see, the thing with England...
The currency here, it's not money.
Nah. You got bored of money
a long time ago.
'Cause, anyone can have money.
You can fucking...
You can fucking find money in the mud.
You can forge money.
Mr Shelby, you can steal money,
am I right?
The currency here,
it's blood.
And Mr Shelby knows that
better than all of them.
Blood here is like wine,
like vintage wine in that bottle.
It's the label.
It's the terroir.
It's the grape that makes the wine.
Who fucking cares
about the glass around it?
And you, my friend, you're an American.
You fucking smash the glass,
you spill the blood and you spend
their currency to get what you want.
Am I right?
When you come to America,
I will show you things.
You're going to America?
To Canada, Lizzie,
to collect payment for the shipment.
I need to do it myself.
And who will be going with you?
Michael will be there to watch his back.
Another journey, Tommy?
Five million dollars, Mrs Shelby.
Worth a little cruise, don't you think?
You know, whiskey does talk,
Mr Nelson, and sometimes whiskey is
very eloquent.
But five million dollars, Mr Nelson...
Now that is a legacy.
And when I come back,
I will know everything.
I see myself
so clearly in you, Thomas Shelby.
You are a man
with a bright and glittering future.
-[door opens]
-[footsteps approaching]
[Frances] Mr Shelby,
there's a car coming up the drive.
A Rolls Royce.
Were you expecting more guests?
No.
Excuse me.
We were on our way
to my constituency in Smethwick
and I heard our American friend
was in Birmingham and he was coming here.
So we came to say one last farewell.
Champagne. We have much to celebrate.
It's not that I thought Mr Shelby
wouldn't give you an excellent send-off,
I just felt,
since telegrams and wires and letters
can so easily be intercepted,
we might confirm all that we've achieved
during your visit over champagne.
It is remarkable how quickly
our relationships have developed.
So many triangles in this room.
Everyone, except for Mr Nelson,
is the point of a triangle.
How am I part of a triangle?
Mr Nelson, you have all that you came for?
I have confirmation
that the future of Europe
is in the hands of men like yourselves.
And that urgent conversations
between Washington, Rome
and, of course, Berlin can now begin.
A two-week visit
may have changed the course of history.
We all got what we wanted.
Yes.
And I got what I have wanted
from the moment I set eyes on it.
Elizabeth, you are a very lucky woman.
To have each day
what I have only sampled once.
[scoffs]
[exhales]
Forgive us, Mr Nelson.
That was a necessary bit of housekeeping.
Thomas,
we do so hate to be indiscreet,
but we have told you many times,
if you were to seek power in these days
of shiny magazines
and society photographs,
sooner or later, you will have to find
a spouse who's more suitable.
A woman with Lizzie's past
and personal history
really isn't suitable.
She doesn't deserve you, Mr Shelby.
You know, the thing is, Mosley,
you're right.
You're right, she doesn't deserve me.
She doesn't deserve what I am.
She doesn't deserve what I will become.
What will you become?
Truth is, I belong here at this table
with fuckers like you.
She doesn't.
For all I try to hide it...
[scoffs] I'm just one of you.
Could there be a sadder ending, eh?
♪ Take a little walk
To the edge of town ♪
[clicks tongue]
♪ And go across the tracks ♪
♪ Where the viaduct looms ♪
♪ Like a bird of doom ♪
♪ As it shifts and cracks ♪
♪ Where secrets lie
In the border fires ♪
♪ In the humming wires ♪
♪ Hey man, you know ♪
♪ You're never coming back ♪
♪ Past the square
Past the bridge ♪
♪ Past the mills
And the stacks ♪
♪ On a gathering storm comes ♪
♪ A tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat with ♪
♪ A red right hand ♪
[priest] I'm here
on behalf of your wife, Gina,
and Jack Nelson.
Mr Nelson's prepared
to get you out of here.
But first he needs
an answer to a question.
If the answer is yes,
you'd be released.
If the answer is no,
you'll stay.
I have consulted my mother.
Your mother's dead.
Nevertheless, I've consulted her.
And, yes,
when I'm released,
it is my intention to kill Tommy Shelby.
♪ He's a god, he's a man ♪
♪ He's a ghost, he's a guru ♪
♪ And they're whispering his name ♪
♪ Through the disappearing land ♪
♪ But hidden in his coat ♪
♪ Is a red right hand ♪
♪ You don't have no money? ♪
♪ Well, he'll get you some ♪
♪ You don't have no car? ♪
♪ He'll get you one ♪