They didn't come back
Arthur Shelby is still alive
Wire his village and tell them
You walk around this little place
dressed like big city hoodlums
None of my clothes fit anymore
I can't eat anything,
it's all shit
It's inedible, it's disgusting!
Spotted Dick? What is that?
I don't want to eat that. Why would I?
with all due respect...
You're right
Let's get this business finished
then we can all go home
then we can eat some decent food
We found another enemy.
This family has lots of enemies
She lives inside their territory
She says he's crazy in the head
To compensate her, they look
after her and her other kids
She thinks if she asks one of
the brothers to come to her house
They would come
So she says
People in this place hate forever
Like Sicilians