TOMMY: The pro.treaty Paddies
and the King want the same man dead.
CAMPBELL: You've been chosen, Mr Shelby.
The Epsom Derby, Pol.
We'll be drinking with the bloody King.
For the last 10 years,
Sabini's made it his race.
If we're gonna take him down,
might as well make it there.
It's good to see you, Grace.
Tommy, do you have someone?
MAY: The horse will come fifth or sixth.
But I will win you.
Mr Churchill was impressed.
He has asked that the Colonial Office
grant him an Empire export licence.
I want my son out of prison now.
CAMPBELL: He can be freed
by tomorrow morning.
I'm talking about
a simple transaction here.
TOMMY: I will carry out
your assassination
at a place of my choosing.
Epsom.
Derby Day.
My name is Thomas Shelby,
and today, I'm going to kill a man.
Today is Derby Day.
The murder will take place
this afternoon,
at the Epsom races.
It may be that I am able to escape
after the killing.
The odds are not good,
which is why I am writing this letter.
I've been forced by agents of the Crown
to carry out this murder.
In the event of my own death,
I want the following facts to be known.
My family are innocent
of any involvement.
Who are we?
(ALL SHOUTING)
-Let's go.
-(INDISTINCT TALKING)
TOMMY: And while some of them
maybe guilty of other things,
I've not shared details of this mission
with any of them,
and no company assets were used.
Agents of the Crown joined forces
with pro.treaty Fenians
to arrange this murder.
I believe the governments intend
to falsely blame the anti.treaty IRA.
Therefore, the bullet I fire
this afternoon
will be the starting gun
for civil war in Ireland.
(MAN PANTING)
TOMMY: The man I have been
instructed to kill
is Field Marshal Russell.
Formerly a Black and Tan commander
who committed many atrocities
in the county of Cork.
(MOANING)
TOMMY: There is no remorse in my heart
at the prospect of his death.
However, the conspiracy
behind the killing
is cause for international concern.
Such is the gravity
of my secret mission,
that after I have served my purpose,
I believe they intend to kill me.
Do you want tea?
TOMMY: I therefore want to name
a particular individual in this letter.
The agent who has initiated
and orchestrated this crime
is Major Chester Campbell of
the British Secret Intelligence Service.
He chose me for this dirty business
as an act of vengeance,
prompted by hatred of long standing.
In the event of my death,
it is imperative
he be brought to justice.
If you are reading this,
then I am dead already.
I hope that, living as you do
in a truly free country,
you will be able to make the above facts
known to the world.
Yours sincerely, Thomas Shelby.
Did you one anyway, you ignorant git.
Ada, sit down here for a minute.
Ada, if anything happens to me today,
I need you to post this letter.
The stamp's already on.
Don't ask any questions,
it's to do with insurance.
Look, Tommy,
whatever it is you're involved in,
just tell us.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
God, you never let anybody in.
We love you, Tom.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
What are you doing up
at 6:00 in the morning?
(CLEARS THROAT)
-Ready?
-ADA: What the bloody hell's going on?
-Little errand.
-What errand?
-You just have to stand there, Ada.
-Stand where?
-Let's go, come on.
-James, what's going on?
Don't listen to him, James.
He'll get you killed.
What errand?
JAMES: For the cause, Ada.
The good old cause.
(DOOR OPENING, DISTANT)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
Hands off cocks, on with socks.
One at a time.
One at a time, that's all I ask.
You're getting out, Mr Shelby.
(SIGHS)
All 10 witnesses against you
withdrew their statements,
last night.
All at once. 9:00.
Don't ask me why, because I don't know.
The next 10 minutes, you don't do
or say anything I haven't told you.
All right?
-All right?
-Yeah.
TOMMY: Hello, Ollie.
Well, hang on. Just you, yeah?
He stays out here.
Uh, you stay here.
Johnny fucking Dogs.
(SIGHS) How did they get me
out of there?
I need to get you to a telephone.
You need to make a call.
It's all part of Tommy's plan.
-(ENGINE STARTS)
-Apparently.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
That'll probably be for you, won't it?
Hello?
Arthur.
You're out.
Right, so that'll be your side
of the street swept up, won't it?
Where's mine?
What you got for me?
Signed by
the Minister of the Empire himself.
Yeah? So it is.
This means that you can put
your rum in our shipments,
and no one at Poplar Docks
will lift a canvas.
You know what? I'm not even going
to have my lawyer look at that.
-TOMMY: I know, it's all legal.
-You know what,
mate, I trust you. That's that. Done.
So, whisky...
There is, uh, one thing, though,
that we do need to discuss.
-What would that be?
-It says here, "20o/o
"paid to me of your export business."
-As we agreed on the telephone...
-No, no, no, no, no.
See, I've had my lawyer
(CLEARS THROAT) draw this up...
...for us, just in case.
(CLEARS THROAT)
It says that, here, that 100o/o
of your business goes to me.
-I see.
-It's there. Right.
Don't worry about it, right,
'cause it's totally legal binding.
All you have to do is sign the document
and transfer the whole lot over to me.
-Sign just here, is it?
-Yeah.
I see. That's funny. That is.
-What?
-No, that's funny.
"I'll give you 100o/o of my business."
Yeah.
Why?
Ollie, no. No, no, no.
Put that down.
He understands, he understands.
He's a big boy, he knows the road.
Now, look,
it's just non-fucking-negotiable.
That's all you need to know.
So all you have to do
is sign the fucking contract.
-Right there.
-Just sign here?
-With your pen.
-I understand.
Good. Get on with it.
Well, I have an associate
waiting for me at the door.
I know that he looks like a choir boy,
but he is actually an anarchist
-from Kentish Town.
-Tommy...
I'm going to fucking shoot you.
All right?
Now, when I came in here, Mr Solomons,
I stopped to tie my shoelace.
Isn't that a fact?
Ollie?
I stopped to tie my shoelace.
And while I was doing it,
I laid a hand grenade
on one of your barrels,
Mark 15, with wired trip.
And my friend upstairs...
Well, he's like one of those anarchists
that blew up Wall Street, you know?
He's a professional.
And he's in charge of the wire.
If I don't walk out that door
on the stroke of 7:00,
he's going to trigger the grenade and...
...your very combustible rum
will blow us all to hell.
And I don't care...
...'cause I'm already dead.
He tied his lace, Alfie.
-And there is a kid at the door.
-From a good family, too.
Ollie, it's shocking what they become...
What were you doing when this happened?
He tied his lace, nothing else.
Yeah, but what were you doing?
I was marking the runners in the paper.
What are you doing?
Just checking the time. Carry on.
Right, Ollie, I want you to go outside,
yeah, and shoot that boy in the face
from the good family, all right?
Anyone walks through that door
except me, he blows the grenade.
-He tied his fucking lace...
-I did tie my lace.
I bet, 100 to 1,
you're fucking lying, mate.
That's my money.
Well, see, you've failed
to consider the form.
I did blow up me own pub...
-...for the insurance.
-(SIGHS HEAVILY)
ALFIE: OK right...
Well, considering the form,
I would say 65 to 1. Very good odds.
And I would be more than happy
and agree
if you were to sign over
65o/o of your business to me.
-Thank you.
-Sixty-five? No deal.
-Ollie, what do you say?
-Jesus Christ, Alfie.
He tied his fucking lace, I saw him!
-Mmm-hmm.
-He planted a grenade, I know he did.
Alfie, it's Tommy fucking Shelby...
(OLLIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
You're behaving like a fucking child.
This is a man's world.
Take your apron off,
and sit in the corner like a little boy.
Fuck off. Now.
-Four minutes.
-All right, four minutes.
-(TOMMY CLEARS THROAT)
-Talk to me about hand grenades.
The chalk mark on the barrel,
at knee height.
It's a Hamilton Christmas.
I took out the pin
and put it on the wire.
(EXHALES)
Based on this...
...forty-five percent.
-Thirty.
-Oh, fuck off, Tommy.
That's far too little.
In France, Mr Solomons,
while I was a tunneller, a clay-kicker.
179.
I blew up Schwaben Höhe.
Same kit I'm using today.
It's funny, that.
I do know the 179.
And I heard they all got buried.
Three of us dug ourselves out.
Like you're digging yourself out now?
Like I'm digging now.
Fuck me.
Listen, I'll give you 35o/o.
That's your lot.
Thirty-five.
-You're late.
-Hey, it's my business.
(ARTHUR GROANS)
How the fuck did you
get me out of that?
I need you today, brother.
I pulled some strings.
-You all right?
-I am now.
So Arthur's back in charge now?
He's in charge of you,
and you're both in charge of him.
Look-out duties only today.
-Tom, I'm getting sick of this...
-Finn.
You don't obey orders, you don't come.
-Johnny Dogs.
-Tommy.
-TOMMY: Your boys will meet us there?
-Well, at least they'll be there,
Captain.
-Captain?
-Ah, we promoted you.
Well, the boys decided you're no longer
like a Sergeant Major.
Fucking those rich women
and using those fancy words.
I'd say you're more like a captain
these days.
Fine, well, I'll take it
as a compliment.
Just don't bloody shoot me.
Let's go to the Derby, boys.
All right, then! Load 'em up!
-(INDISTINCT TALKING)
-(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello.
No, I'm afraid Mr Shelby is in London.
-He can't be reached.
-(DOOR OPENING)
-No, he won't be back today.
-(DOOR CLOSING)
He's at the races.
The Epsom races, the Epsom Derby.
Can I ask who's calling?
I'm going to the station.
(SIGHS)
-What's that?
-That money's yours.
You take the money, you get a train,
you start a new life in London.
I don't want to see you here
when I get back.
If I get back.
Everything's an "if"
in this Birmingham life.
You can write on Sundays
and visit on holy days.
But I want you to wash this city
out of your hair and your clothes.
It's what I should have done
at the start.
Now I've got business to attend to.
I do love you, Michael.
I love you too.
You'll miss your train.
Me beloved greyhounds.
Behold.
Today's rabbit.
When I give you the signal, I want you
to send that man to his maker.
I decided to use you men
because I couldn't trust
the hearts and the livers
of the English pansies and posies
they'd given me as operatives.
Right. (CLEARS THROAT)
This is a man of some capability,
but I expect no excuses and no failures.
The Red Right Hand
of the Ulster Volunteer Force
will not let you down, Mr Campbell.
The Red Right Hand.
Good luck, gentlemen.
TOMMY: Gentlemen, today,
we are not fucking about.
I hope you've all obeyed instructions
and brought loaded firearms with you.
-(ALL AGREEING)
-Very good.
You will all know that if you are lifted
on a racetrack these days
with a loaded weapon, you get 20 years.
That's all right.
Today, you won't get lifted.
Because today, there will be
no coppers around to lift you.
At exactly 3:00, there will be
an incident in the owners' enclosure
and all the coppers on the track
will be diverted. All of them.
They will be looking for someone.
-So you will be free to operate at will.
-Looking for who?
Me. They will be looking for me.
Now, while the coppers are busy with me,
you will make your move
on Sabini's pitches.
You will confiscate his takings,
you'll destroy his licences,
and you do it at gunpoint.
He usually has police protection,
so they won't be armed.
We should aim to complete the takeover
without a shot being fired, understood?
And remember, the licences are
more important than the takings.
All right. Before the fun begins,
you can all lay 10 bob
on Nom de Guerre.
-I hear she's going to win.
-(ALL CHEERING)
Only beer beforehand, boys, and plenty
of time for rum and whisky after.
And remember,
do not make a move until 3:00.
When the coppers leave. That is all.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Incident? What are you going to do
that's going to make every copper
at the Derby look the other way?
Trust me, brother.
(INDISTINCT COMMENTARY
OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Ten, please.
(LAUGHTER)
(HORSE SNORTS)
(DISTANT MUSIC PLAYING)
She threw a shoe coming out of the box.
TOMMY: Eh?
She looks in fine shape.
Hello, hello, hello.
I missed you, buck. Missed you, buck.
-Should I be worried?
-You should not.
Go and drink, enjoy the day. I'll come
and find you when the race is done.
Hmm, that's nice. Is that yours?
My mother wore it to the Derby in 1895.
She was presented to Queen Victoria.
After the race,
I'll change in the horse box
and then come and join you up there
with the toffs, what do you say?
Hmm. Yeah.
You don't want me to join you.
It's fine.
I'll stay down here in the mud.
Whatever happens today, it was good.
You mean, win or lose?
Yeah. Win or lose.
You know, I never watch the race.
Can't stand it.
I always like to find somewhere
dark and quiet.
Tommy?
If you can't find me up there,
I'll come and find you later.
What do you mean?
Whatever happens, May,
no regrets. No regrets.
And I will find you.
All right.
Remember that.
Bye.
Put this on Nom de Guerre.
Good day, sir.
There he is.
Fucking meatball blokes.
Right, let's go.
(INDISTINCT)
I have to talk to you.
-Grace. What are you doing here?
-I have to talk to you.
Grace.
This is not a good time.
What's all this about? Please excuse us.
Whatever it is, Grace,
it'll have to wait.
It can't wait.
It wasn't me who is at fault.
I'm pregnant.
The baby's yours.
Better believe...
Make your husband believe that it's his.
Is that what you want me to do?
Grace, I seriously have things to do.
It's not worth the toss
of a coin this time?
Grace, I have things to do.
When they are...
When they are done, I will decide.
-When will that be?
-After the race.
After the race?
After the fucking race, Tommy?
When the race is over
I will decide what to do.
What to fucking do, all right?
But Tommy...
I was right not to tell him?
I could have phoned him and lied,
but I didn't.
Just tell me that I was right.
Not to phone and lie.
Agree with that, Tommy.
Yes. Yes, Grace.
Because the thing is...
...I love you, not him.
That is a thing.
A baby, Thomas.
Yes.
-Go to your race.
-Where will you be?
I'll be waiting.
I'll wait where they lay their bets.
(BAND PLAYING
IT'S A LONG WA Y TO TIPPERARY)
Found a lost sheep.
Come on, Lizzie.
-What do you think?
-About what?
-About the dress?
-Undo two buttons. Come on!
(SIGHS)
LIZZIE: Oh Tommy, I never thought
I'd see the like of this.
TOMMY: Yeah.
LIZZIE: But I do know that
I'm here to work,
so you may have noticed
I haven't taken a drink.
TOMMY: Well, here.
Take this. You might need it.
What's the work you want me
to do here today, Tommy?
Is it taking notes in a meeting?
No, Lizzie.
You're not here to take notes.
My shorthand won't be required.
Lizzie...
There's a man here
and I need him separated from the crowd
-and taken to a quiet place.
-A quiet place...
-Lizzie, I know what I said.
-Yeah, you know.
You know, you told me I shouldn't
do that kind of work any more.
I just need you to isolate him, is all.
No exceptions, you said.
I've drawn a map, all right,
of where exactly you need to take him.
For months I made no exceptions
because you told me not to.
Lizzie...
Just keep him busy.
I have the place marked with an "X"
and I'll get to you before it can start,
I promise. All right?
I mustn't smudge my eyes,
he might not like that.
Lizzie...
...this is the only time.
After this, never again.
All right, I'll pay an extra five...
Do not talk to me about money now.
Not right now, I swear
I'll break this glass in your eyes.
(INDISTINCT)
LIZZIE: No exceptions,
there's been no hardship.
You know why?
Hmm?
Doesn't matter.
Who is he?
-To your right. Soldier.
-(LIZZIE SNIFFLES)
TOMMY: Smoking a cigarette.
Just be alone with him at 3:00.
When the race starts,
and I'll do the rest. Yeah?
Got a piece of chalk?
-Chalk?
-It's how the soldiers know.
It doesn't matter,
just give me the fucking chalk.
Lizzie, it's gonna be all right. Eh?
I'll get to you, I promise.
Before it can start.
I will be there.
(DOOR OPENING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Keep them fuckin' guns ready.
Keep them guns ready.
(INDISTINCT)
JOHN: Coppers aren't moving.
Stood there like fucking gargoyles.
Keep your wits about you,
boys, all right?
MAN: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Ladies and gentlemen,
the race will begin in four minutes.
So please make your way track side.
CAMPBELL: Shouldn't you be busy?
TOMMY: When you've planned
something well,
there's no need to rush.
CAMPBELL: Do you know something?
I actually trust you to do this.
Do you think there might be some...
...measure of respect
developing between us?
MAN: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Ladies and gentlemen,
runners and riders are coming to order,
please take yours eats.
Old foes that have grown
to admire each other,
and see each other's
professional virtues.
Personally, I think not.
I think not.
Well, I drink to that.
MAN: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Ladies and gentlemen,
please be upstanding
for the national anthem.
It's always the plan
that you'll stay together forever.
(ANTHEM PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
Or perhaps she'll whore for you,
take her husband's money.
Is that the plan?
How wrong I was about her.
TOMMY: I was wrong about her as well.
You once said to me,
that men like us can never be loved.
She loves me. She told me.
She loves me.
And all you got was a bullet
and a fucking wolf head cane.
Well. Bully for you.
This I know.
Ahead of you is damnation,
but I have the love of God,
and the certainty of salvation.
-(ANTHEM ENDS)
-(CROWD CHEERING)
I know what you did to Polly.
I know what happened
to my uncle in jail.
Today, it'll be me dead,
or you, but whoever it is,
gonna wake up in hell tomorrow.
MAN: (OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Ladies and gentlemen,
the runners and riders
are under starter's orders.
.And they're off!
-(CROWD CHEERING LOUDLY)
(INDISTINCT COMMENTARY
OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Come on girl, come on.
At least make a showing.
Come on, Tommy.
(LIZZIE LAUGHING)
What a pretty dress.
(INDISTINCT COMMENTARY
OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Take it off.
Let's take this off first, shall we?
Lift up your dress
and show me that you're clean.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Do as you're told!
We should take it slow, we've got time.
(MOANS)
-This area's closed off.
-What?
The King will be coming this way
after the race.
-This area is secure!
-But I need to...
-You'll have to go round.
-(SIGHS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(LIZZIE GROANING)
-LIZZIE: Get the fuck off!
-You bitch!
LIZZIE: (CRYING) Fuck off!
Get the fuck off me!
-(GRUNTING)
-(SOBBING)
-Hey!
-(GRUNTS)
(LIZZIE SOBBING IN DISTANCE)
-Russell!
-(GUN CLICKS)
Fuck!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GUN COCKS)
LIZZIE: Stop it!
(TOMMY GRUNTING)
(COMMENTARY CONTINUES
ON LOUDSPEAKER)
(GUN CLICKS)
(GROANING)
(GUN FIRES)
(CROWD CHEERING LOUDLY)
-Lizzie...
-Where were you?
-Where the fuck were you? (SOBBING)
-Give me the gun, Lizzie.
Lizzie, Lizzie.
-I'm sorry.
-Fuck off, fuck off!
Just go.
Go on, go!
(FIRES THREE TIMES)
Officers. Officers!
I was taking a shit
and I heard voices, Irish voices
and I heard a shot.
I swear to God,
there's a soldier lying dead in there.
Get every man in uniform
around the King.
Every man in uniform around the King.
Right now!
The IRA are on the course.
MAN: (SHOUTING) Everyone to the King.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
All right, my pretty boys. This is it.
Right. Ready.
You get round the back.
Come on. Don't bunch.
Right, you stay with us.
I want you to stay back!
MAN: Let's go!
Put your hands in the air!
Turn around!
Is there a problem?
Fenians on the course.
A soldier's been shot, someone said
there was an Irishman in here.
That is correct.
Very sorry, sir.
Check the security to His Majesty.
I will now take your mind off
the situation.
(DOOR OPENS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
TOMMY: Mr Sabini, you're late.
Have a seat.
What happened to your nose?
You want to have that brother
of yours put down.
Oh, I tried that. He bit the vet.
I've told the coppers that you're
a fucking gypsy racketeer Peaky Blinder.
They're coming.
They're gonna throw you out.
Before the King comes up here.
Well, from what I saw
the police are a bit busy right now.
Did you win any money today, Mr Sabini?
Where are the coppers?
Said to that sergeant, "one minute",
he said, "two", it's fucking ten!
Like I told you, they're a bit busy.
Same as my boys.
-What the fuck does that mean?
-What does that mean?
Well, my boys are on the track.
They're having a little bonfire.
Gaming licences, you know.
(CHUCKLES)
Fuck!
You place too much reliance on
the police for your security, Mr Sabini.
That was a mistake.
You're gonna now
think about who you are,
think about where you are.
You pull a weapon,
you are the King's assassin.
Now sit down, stay calm.
Good.
Now your next mistake, Mr Sabini,
was breaking your promise
with Alfie Solomons.
Hmm. You promised Alfie
that his bookies could come to Epsom.
He was very hurt when you said no.
He was very hurt.
That's why me and Alfie
are back in business.
(SIGHS)
-(SHATTERS)
-(CROWD GASPS)
Hold it! Hold it!
TOMMY: It's all right,
it's all right, Officers.
He's just a bad loser.
What the fuck? Hey!
You fucking lose,
you fucking gypsy bastard!
You lose!
What the fuck are you looking at?
OFFICER: Step back, move.
You're now a prisoner
of the Red Right Hand.
Now, take his hat and gun.
Get him up.
Easy.
Take a seat.
Sit down!
(TOMMY SIGHS)
That's it.
You make yourself nice and comfortable.
We're just going for a wee drive,
Mr Shelby.
Let's go.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
I guessed and then John confirmed it.
Guessed what?
Who are you?
I'm May Car let on.
I train Tommy Shelby's horse.
And you're the woman who he said
was going to sail away.
I see he didn't tell you about me.
He did tell me about you,
I wonder if that's significant.
Tell me what about you?
Do you have any idea where he is?
I'm waiting for him here.
There's been trouble on the track.
All the bookies have had
their licences burnt.
Shouldn't you be down with the horses?
Which means they'll have to re-apply
for their legal pitches.
It's all part of Tommy's plan
for the future.
What do you know about Tommy's future?
The applications will be denied,
of course.
Then all the pitches will be
allocated instead to Tommy's bookies.
I know because I'll make sure of it.
I have influence with the board.
-There's business and there's love.
-Is there?
There's Thomas Shelby.
-What do you want from him?
-Same as you.
I want to feel alive.
Did he tell you my name?
My name is Grace.
In your statement
to the House, sir,
I believe that you should say
that witnesses
heard the killer say that
they were members of the IRA
and that the killing was in retribution
for actions of the Field Marshal
in County Cork.
Oh, our friend from Birmingham?
(CHUCKLES)
He's been taken care of.
Oh...
A very good day, sir.
-Thank...
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Sorry, I must go.
Goodbye.
Polly.
POLLY: Tommy told me you'd be here.
And I told Tommy it should be me
who finishes you.
(GUN COCKS)
Small and weak.
That's how you like it, isn't it?
Well, this time small and weak
has got a gun.
No, you wouldn't do that here.
No.
Do you see any coppers?
Well, I don't.
They're all around your precious King.
Ah.
(POLLY BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
Polly, Polly...
-Some part of you...
-I have no parts.
Some part of you wanted me as well.
I know that, I felt it.
And sure as hell some part of me
wants you still.
And not just that part, but...
some part of my soul.
Some part of my soul.
Curious how that is to me
and curious that it should be you.
Opposites perhaps.
Opposite, and that... (CHUCKLES)
That thing sticking in my heart,
you own, you own part of that heart,
you do.
You do, Polly. You do.
(GUN FIRES)
-(GASPING)
-(POLLY CRIES)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
Don't fuck with the Peaky Blinders.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT COMMENTARY ON LOUDSPEAKER)
Let's get you home.
Come on.
ARTHUR: Look at this place, we own it!
Put your money away
before I take it off ya.
-Fuckin' clean up!
-Get up!
Lizzie, what the fuck
are you doing here?
-Working for Tommy, same as all of us.
-You work for the Blinders.
-What happened to you?
-LIZZIE: Fell over.
Oh, don't fuckin' give me that.
Lizzie...
Come here, come here.
-(CRYING)
-Eh? Were you working?
Yeah?
Thought you'd earn yourself a few bob
at the races, eh?
It's gotta stop, Lizzie.
It's gotta stop,
Tommy's already told you.
Toffs at the races are the worst,
you know that.
Hey, come here, come here.
Look at me.
Cheer up.
We won.
We fucking took Epsom.
We kicked the Cockneys' fucking arses.
Congratu-fucking-lations.
ARTHUR: We fucking beat them,
all right.
John didn't even shoot his gun!
We're kings! Kings of the fucking world!
John, I don't see the same thing
in your eyes that I see in Tommy's.
You should get out.
Where is Tommy, anyway?
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SIGHS)
TOMMY: Any of you boys in France?
You know, I wouldn't mind a cigarette.
The Somme.
Black Woods.
Somme, the Bulls.
Smoke.
So fucking close.
Oh... And there's a woman.
Yeah.
A woman...
...who I love...
...and I got close.
Nearly got
(SHOUTING) fucking everything!
(GUN COCKING)
Oh, what the fuck?
Get it done, boys.
Comrade,
we have our orders,
you know how it is.
I know how it is.
In the bleak midwinter.
At some point in the near future,
Mr Churchill will want to speak to you
in person, Mr Shelby.
(PANTING)
He has a job for you.
We will be in touch.
Get out of the grave, tinker.
Be on your fucking way!
(GRUNTS)
Fuck!
(GROANS)
(CROWD TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to raise a toast.
(CROWD CHEERING)
-To the Small Heath Rifles.
-ALL: Small Heath Rifles.
To the Lane Boys.
(CROWD CHEERING)
And to the Peaky fucking Blinders.
(ALL CHEERING)
Who's gonna stop us, eh?
Nobody.
(THUDS)
Polly and I had a bet.
(GROANING)
One of us bet
you'd take the money and go.
And one of us bet you'd still be here.
She wants me to stay.
Mmm, you know something, Michael?
What Polly wants
will always be a mystery to me.
I've decided.
I want to make real money
with you.
I've got some ideas, Michael.
For the future of the company.
And also,
I'm planning on getting married.
http://hiqve.com/