People keep asking me questions
that I don't know the answer to.
It's us that has the machine guns now.
And it's them that's in the mud.
Guns, Mr. Shelby.
We'd pay good money.
-For who do you speak?
-The Irish Republican Army.
What are you? Copper?
[GUNSHOT]
You went after him because he was IRA.
I followed him because I thought
he might have information.
CAMPBELL: The difficulty
with undercover work, Grace,
is to remember what you are.
[GROANING]
Your sister's in there giving birth,
there's one man should be here.
TOMMY: You're right, Pol.
On my oath. Tell Freddie it's safe.
Welcome to the world, son.
-Freddie!
-THORNE: Ada!
Polly! Polly!
The police came
and took his father away!
[SPITS] You liar!
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
and go across the track
♪ Where the viaduct looms
like a bird of doom
♪ As it shifts and cracks
♪ Where secrets lie in the border fires
♪ In the humming wires
♪ Hey man, you know
you're never coming back
♪ Past the square, past the bridge
♪ Past the mills, past the stacks
♪ On a gathering storm comes
a tall handsome man
♪ In a dusty black coat with
a red right hand ♪
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Open up, love.
I brought more things
for you and the baby.
Got some fresh eggs and bread.
-[BABY CRIES]
-Shh...
POLLY: I'll leave it here.
[BABY CRYING]
Ada, think of the little one.
Babies don't have principles.
[DOOR OPENS]
Did you speak to her?
She didn't speak back.
Did you tell her?
I'll only tell her
what I know to be true.
It's the last time
I'm going to say this.
It wasn't me who shot Freddie Thorne.
Tommy,
I'd ask you to swear on the Bible
but you can't swear on that, can you?
Nothing you hold sacred.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
There's tea.
A new system.
Everything in the diary, eh?
Mmm-hmm.
Black star.
What does that mean?
Black star day...
is the day we take out Billy Kimber
and his men.
No one knows this.
Not even your family?
Grace...
Everyone in my family hates me.
Why would I tell them?
[DOOR CLOSES]
He's off the bloody rails
is what he is.
[MEN CHEERING]
If he'll turn nose on his best mate.
Bloody neighbors, John.
Snitch behind the curtain.
Yeah, well, if you think that,
you're the only one who does.
Look at this. Look.
Bloody rakin' it in!
Who's running this carny?
Name of Marsden. Intends on wintering
in Small Heath at this ring.
-Does he?
-Only heard.
Nobody in Small Heath craps in a pot
without the decree of Tommy Almighty.
Mr. Marsden, I believe!
The ring master!
Proud I am to say so.
Yeah, well, these here
are civilized parts.
Man wants to set his stall up
with fellas lampin' each other.
He needs himself a license.
A license?
For a fee.
From those in charge.
[CROWD CHEERING]
I'll tell you what.
How about I keep my money and you
shove a license up your ass crack?
You don't want to speak to me like that.
And who the bloody hell
do you think you are?
[MAN SHOUTING] My name...
is Arthur Shelby!
Dad?
Jesus.
Thank you. You're a good boy.
[SIGHS]
Bless the father for these bounties
we're about to receive...
Jesus Christ.
Please, woman.
Let me be.
Finish your sandwich
and sling your hook.
Polly Anna, I'm a guest
of the head of this family.
So why don't you maybe tend to your
mangle or your scuttle?
The head of the family ain't here.
Tommy, uh,
sometimes helps me with, uh,
with business.
[DOOR OPENS]
-[DOOR CLOSES]
-Aye, well, speak of the devil.
How are you, son?
Get out.
Come on, son.
I'm a changed man.
This family needed you 10 years ago.
And you walked out on us.
Not now.
Get out of this house.
-Tommy, he's different.
-Shut up.
It's all right, son.
Arthur Shelby...
never stays where he's not welcome.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Quite something you've become.
Bye, son.
[DOOR CLOSES]
-He's our dad.
-[SCOFFS]
He's a selfish bastard.
You calling someone a selfish bastard?
It's a bit rich, Tommy.
I mean, thanks to you,
we're already down a bloody sister.
You want to see him, Arthur?
You want to see him?
You go with him.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Grace.
I'm taking five pounds
from petty cash, all right?
We don't have five pounds
in petty cash.
Then I'll take what we've got.
Count it and leave a receipt.
Arthur, there are things in these books
I don't understand.
Likewise.
Every week we pay one pound,
ten shilling by postal order
to a Daniel Owen
-in London.
-Danny Whizz-Bang.
Hangs around in the pubs
in Camden Town Wharf for us.
Keeps his ears open for business.
He's a good man.
I thought Danny Whizz-Bang was dead?
Then you thought wrong, didn't you?
But I've seen his grave. He was shot.
That was a show to satisfy the wops.
Tommy just shot
some sheep's brains at him.
Who's buried in his grave?
Now look, Grace.
You know what's good for you.
You don't ask questions about things
that don't concern you.
Never, right?
That's for you.
Don't tell Tommy I took this.
The boy needs a good hiding
if you ask me.
Yeah, well, I'm this close
to giving him one.
John and Ada too, sounds like.
Nah, John moans on bloody principle.
But if you saw his missus...
Ah...
You have a girl yourself, son?
Perhaps when it suits, Tommy, eh?
Yeah, well.
He's been different.
-You know, since the war.
-Yeah, well...
A war can change a man.
Speaking for myself, anyways.
Where did you fight, Dad?
Ah, all over, son.
-All over.
-Yeah, all over.
And the salvation of Jesus Christ
spread his light over me.
And as a pilgrim,
I come to visit a new world.
America.
Where I beheld the future.
Casinos.
Money factories, son.
Look, I've been studying
the competition.
Their schemes,
their systems.
-Look at that. It's all there.
-Show me.
There's a fortune to be made here.
I'm an old man and my
heart's a battered vessel.
But within,
there still beats a fluttering
pulse of a dream.
The Shelby...
Casino and Hotel.
Gents and dames will come flocking
from all corners.
New York, Chicago, Boston,
to the Shelby.
Where I can stand proudly with
my dear children by my side.
And the women there?
Like fresh peaches.
Thou could have a dozen.
We'd all of us be kings.
How much? How much to get started?
The oak needs but an acorn.
Let's do it.
Let's do it. Let's bloody do it.
It would make my heart beam, but
I don't want to cause any discord
between the brothers. So please,
why don't you talk to Tommy first?
No, now, I'm sick of taking
orders from him.
Tommy's not the only one in the
family with a head for business.
And Shelby money
is Shelby money.
I thank God for my wonderful sons.
This is cause for a celebration.
-Yeah.
-Sláinte.
Sláinte.
On your feet, soldier.
On your feet.
[RAUCOUS SHOUTING]
Look, I don't wanna fight you, Dad.
Come on, boy!
I'm old enough to be your father.
[GRUNTS]
MAN: On your feet!
Get up!
All right!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTING]
Is that all you got, boy?
Get up!
[SHOUTS] This here...
is Arthur Shelby junior!
My son!
I love him and I'm proud of him!
And he can fight any
one of youse in here!
[CROWD CHEERS]
You did good, son.
You did good.
I love you, Dad.
I love you!
Mr. Shelby?
Who's asking?
My name's Burn.
I had word from your man in Camden town
you wanted a parley.
Then parley it is.
Few months ago,
a man named Ryan came to this place with
a view to buying some goods from you.
Mr. Ryan met with an accident,
he was shot.
TOMMY: I heard.
BURN: He was a man with a quick mouth.
I know that.
Wondered if he made
any enemies in here?
None that I know of.
Not the kind of place to make enemies.
-All are welcome here, Mr. Burn.
-Including Irish?
Oh, especially Irish.
Ryan told you he was a member
of the Irish Republican Army.
Was he still welcome?
Like I say. Any man who buys
beer is welcome.
Perhaps you didn't believe him?
In pubs, sometimes people say things.
Sometimes it's the whisky talking.
It's hard to tell which is which.
As a teetotal man, I find that amusing.
Except when it ends in tragedy.
Would you like some water
and cordial, Mr. Burn?
You see, Mr. Shelby,
Ryan, for all his quick mouth,
was indeed connected.
Very well connected to our brotherhood.
By membership in blood.
He was my cousin.
I'm from South Armagh.
I'm a man of influence there.
Cordial and water will
be grand, Mr. Shelby.
Grace, bring some water and cordial.
Come this way.
Yes, Mr. Shelby.
My cousin came to buy guns.
And I told him I have none.
Your man Danny Owen
talks a lot when he's drunk.
He says the Peaky Blinders
do have the guns,
brought from the factory down the road.
He boasted about a stack
of Lewis machine guns,
and enough belts of ammunition
to hold up God's trousers.
Yup, that sounds like our Danny.
-He has an imagination.
-[DOOR OPENS]
Like I say, sometimes it's
the whisky does the talk.
He says only your brothers
know where the guns are kept.
Well, Danny also says he sees German
infantrymen on the back of mill carts.
And he shoots them with his broomstick.
We have men in the BSA factory.
They said you has 'em.
And we have men that work
in the police station.
Every finger, Mr. Shelby...
Every finger in this city
points in one direction.
Please don't mistake me for a fool.
Let me get to the point.
I don't care what kind of half-assed
tinker operation you have going here.
But I can assure you,
I represent a very different
category of organization.
My cousin was shot.
I am judge, jury, and executioner.
I find you guilty and I pass sentence.
You deliver the guns to me,
or I deliver death
and hell's fury to you,
and your little tribe of heathens.
Am I making myself clear?
Let me confess something to you,
and only to you.
I have the guns, but they have
become a burden to me.
Perhaps it is time
to unload that burden.
For the right price.
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
[TOMMY CLEARS THROAT]
CAMPBELL: Malachy Burn.
Brigade Commander
of the South Armagh IRA.
You hooked yourself a big fish there.
With these guns as bait,
who knows what we'll catch?
We?
Are you suggesting that you and I
could work together as a team?
Perhaps we have more in common
than you think, Inspector.
-Can you deliver him?
-With your help.
And I want word put out in Ireland
that I was not involved.
CAMPBELL: So I'd be solving
a problem for you.
TOMMY: And I'd be
winning you that medal.
[LAUGHS] If I get a medal, I will have
your initials engraved on my backside.
Oh. My initials on your backside.
That's quite an image.
Inspector, since we're
getting on so well...
can you answer me a question?
Who gave you Freddie Thorne?
Well, as everyone in the city knows...
It was you, Mr. Shelby.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Hello, son.
-It's all there.
It is indeed. We're gonna build
something with this, son.
-Something magnificent.
-When do we start, Dad?
-Hungry for work, are you?
-Yeah!
Ship sails Friday.
Meet me at the boxing ring.
-Good. Friday.
-Friday.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
No, leave that open.
[TOMMY PANTING]
-No.
-Are you expecting trouble?
-Yeah.
-At this hour?
-Midnight is as good an hour as any.
-What the hell is going on?
When the St Andrews' bell
strikes midnight,
two IRA men are going
to come through that door.
When they have what they want,
they plan to kill me.
It's your job
to stop that happening.
Could have given me
some more warning.
I just got the message myself.
They want to meet here, alone.
-And barmaids don't count?
-No, barmaids don't count, no.
You're going to be in that back room.
I'm going to be sitting there.
When I make a toast, you're going
to come out with that thing raised.
You don't shoot, you just point.
I'll do the rest.
-Will you kill them?
-No. The police want them alive.
-The police know about this?
-Look, just hold it up.
Just point, right?
-[BELL TOLLING]
-Right, go, go! Go on, go!
[BELL TOLLING]
We'll hold back here.
If damage is done to either side,
it's no concern of ours.
-Lost your thirst, eh?
-Just show us where.
Give me the cash.
You're gonna need a shovel.
[CHUCKLES]
You thick fucking tinker.
Do you think we'd let you live?
Make your peace, Mr. Shelby.
TOMMY: I'll make my peace my own way.
To barmaids who don't count.
[MEN GRUNTING]
[GRACE GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[MAN SHOUTING]
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[BONES CRACKING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Why did you shoot?
Why did you shoot, Grace?
I didn't know I had it in me
like that. I didn't... [SOBS]
Now you've seen me.
And you've seen me.
I'm sorry.
[DOOR OPENS]
You were supposed to come
on the sixth chime.
on the fucking sixth chime!
They refused to surrender.
They fought well, they were brave men.
Well, he looks like he was killed
by a wild fucking animal.
Still. This never happened.
They were never here. Who cares?
Get the bodies out of here.
Ah, right. Are they making
the lady uncomfortable?
I'll leave you two
love birds to it, then, eh?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
First of all, let me say...
I had no idea he would
involve you in this ugly business.
If I had, I never would
have let it happen.
He trusts me. I told you that.
You didn't believe me.
Fine.
Sergeant Moss made a report,
which, of course, I burnt.
He said that when he entered
the room, you were embracing.
[SCOFFS] Is that your primary
concern, now? An embrace?
-No, my concern is for your welfare.
-It was me who killed them.
-I had no control.
-You've been living with beasts.
It was the beast that tried to stop me.
I believe, last night,
something inside me changed.
I no longer feel the need
to avenge my father.
The hatred that I brought
here with me is gone.
And therefore my reasons
for joining the Service.
You want to resign?
I think our mission has come
to a natural end.
I think I know where
the guns are hidden.
You do? So tell me where!
If I'm right and the guns are found,
you have no more business
with Thomas Shelby. Is that not so?
Our military mission will be over, and
we can leave the city as we found it.
Are you trying to do a deal with me?
Because if you are,
you must be explicit.
I want your word
that Tommy Shelby will not be
harmed if the guns are recovered.
Your word as a gentleman.
Will you give it?
Now, why would you want to save him?
-Residue of sympathy.
-Sympathy? You mean, sentiment?
Yes. In his way, he has been kind to me.
-Sentiment.
-Yes.
You're too good-hearted for this work.
Perhaps.
So, for my sake, will you spare him?
You have my word.
GRACE: A week after the robbery, there
was a burial at St Andrews' churchyard.
I have found out that the man
supposed to be buried is alive.
Arthur is quite concerned.
I learned that the funeral
was attended only by the brothers,
and the grave that they dug
was far deeper than your average,
and lined with lead
to keep out the damp.
The guns are buried in that grave.
Then tonight we will dig up that grave.
GRACE: ♪ When my family thinks
♪ That I'm safely in my bed
♪ Oh, from morn until night
♪ I am stretched out at your head
♪ Calling out unto the earth
♪ With tears hot and wild
♪ For the loss of a boy
♪ That I loved as a child
♪ So I am stretched on your grave
♪ And I'll lie here forever
♪ If your hands were in mine
♪ I'd be sure they would not sever
♪ My apple tree, my brightness
♪ It's time we were together
Well done, boys!
♪ For I smell of the earth
♪ And I'm worn by the weather ♪
All but one gun accounted for.
Then, sir, I resign my commission.
Good... Good.
So, I am no longer
your superior officer,
and you're no longer my subordinate.
And therefore...
Regulations permit me
to offer you this.
I'm a simple man, but a good man.
And my admiration for you
has turned to love.
I don't ask for love in return,
just recognition that
we are like minds,
with shared values.
Grace...
Will you marry me?
Mr. Campbell...
You deserve better.
Is it him between us?
Is it the beast that dug that grave?
[LOUDLY] Is it him?
My resignation will be
with you in the morning.
[TRAIN WHISTLES]
Dad?
Hello, son.
May I ask who gave you my whereabouts?
Marsden. Said you left him last night
with a bill for your whores.
Well... At least we got
to say goodbye, son.
And bid a fond adieu to
your dear brothers, would you?
-How could you do this to us?
-Do what, son?
All that stuff you said about...
Shelby Casino...
-And Atlantic City.
-Hmm, well, if the truth be told,
I'm not so acquainted with that
promised land as I had thee believe.
You're a fucking liar.
And a thief.
Now you give me back
my fucking money!
Do not despise the thief
who steals to satisfy his starvation.
That's in the Holy Bible, son.
And I have starved for so very long.
Fair thee well, son.
I waited for ya.
I waited.
[SHOUTS]
Listen to me, boy.
You're not in the prize ring now.
Never put your hands on me again
or I'll cut your fucking throat
and spread you on these tracks.
[DOOR OPENS]
Where's your father?
I'm assuming he's frittering away
the 500 you took from us
and put into his
thieving, whore-groping hands.
What were you thinking?
How dare you do something like that
without talking to Thomas or me?
Does Tommy know?
No.
But you're going to tell him.
You may take satisfaction
in a great victory.
A terrible consequence has been avoided.
Those guns that we dug up will never
be used to murder the innocent,
or usurp the status quo.
But even though we have solved a crime,
we have, as yet,
failed to punish the criminal.
This man who dug this grave
has also dug his own.
He has proved a deadly menace
to the King's peace.
And tonight we will strike him down.
We will drive our swords
through his black heart.
We will pursue him into
the rat holes that he infests.
And finally,
we will rid this city of his kind.
Justice will be done.
And will be seen to be done.
Amen.
There's going to be trouble now, Finn.
You look after yourself, do you hear me?
I'm gonna be gone away for a while.
Right. Go on.
Right!
Who wants to fucking fight?
Fighting's over.
We're closing up and moving on.
I said, "Who wants to fucking fight?"
My name is Arthur fucking Shelby.
Who dares fight me?
Go home, lad.
Before you catch yourself a spanking.
My brother in Digbeth
just said the police are coming down
from Deritend, in numbers.
Asking for Tommy Shelby, by name.
Shit.
-I'm gonna have to lie low for a while.
-Why?
I lost my bargaining power.
This copper, it's just me and him now.
When I get back,
I wanna tell you some things.
Harry said the police
are already in Digbeth.
-Yeah.
-You took a chance coming here.
Why?
The police are in the lane, Tommy.
Come with me.
I'm looking for Thomas Shelby.
Never heard of him.
You'll never find him.
Go home.
Perhaps I should ask
that question again.
On your knees.
[GRUNTS]
Aye.
Understand this, barman,
I don't care if you live or die.
I don't know!
[HARRY SHUDDERS]
[GUN CLICKS]
He left.
With the barmaid.
He left with Grace.
I think they were going to her place.
Call it off.
I don't understand, sir,
we should find the barmaid and...
Call it off!
All of it.
Get in!
It's not much of a place.
It's all right.
-Want tea?
-Tea, no.
I have rum.
Actually, tea it is.
-Trying to impress me?
-Yes.
And do you have biscuits?
No, they attract mice.
People look different at home.
In what way?
Off guard.
Should I be on my guard?
No.
I'm a man who drinks tea.
When the trouble dies down, I'll go.
When will it die down, do you think?
Late, I'd say.
So not until the morning then.
Yes, I'd say I'll be here till morning.
You have a gramophone.
It's broken.
We could still dance.
Yes, why not?
I know you like to be asked properly.
Grace, can I have this dance?
GRACE: Are you okay?
TOMMY: I don't hear
the shovels against the wall.
What shovels?
Will you help me?
Help you with what?
With everything.
The whole fucking thing.
Fucking life.
Business.
I found you.
And you found me.
We'll help each other.
[♪ TIME BY TOM WAITS PLAYING]
[CRIES OUT]
Our father,
who art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[CHOKES AND COUGHS]
[CHOKES]
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello? [CLEARS THROAT]
Send a telegram to Mr. Churchill.
I have news, very good news.
Tell him the business I came
to attend to is now complete.
I'll be leaving the city.
There's just one matter
I need to tidy up first.
[BELL TOLLING]
[DOOR OPENS]
So Polly told ya.
Yup.
You should've used a gun.
Are you laughing at me, Tommy?
Yeah.
Just when things are
starting to go right, Arthur,
you try and do this.
Don't you like fancy parties?
Or, um...
Champagne? Or fast cars?
And how about this?
Your name on a business card.
"Shelby Brothers, Limited."
"Arthur Shelby."
"Associate bookmaker."
[SCOFFS]
I just had them picked up
from the printer's this morning.
You are one of three shareholders.
Me, you, John.
And according to the law,
we are equal partners.
And it is written in
the paperwork in black and white.
A third, a third, a third.
[TOMMY EXHALES]
But the thing is, uh...
Well, me and John, we quite fancy
splitting your share, so...
Just next time, use a gun, man.
[LAUGHS]
Our men at the station tell me
that copper is leaving town.
We're in the clear.
We are on our way
up in the world, brother.
Believe me.
[♪ BRING IT ON BY NICK CAVE PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town
and go across the track ♪