I want you to see this as me
introducing myself to you.
He said Mr Churchill sent him
to Birmingham.
Something about a robbery.
Thomas, you are a bookmaker,
not a fool...
You sell those guns to anyone who
has use for them,
you will hang.
I am just a poor communist frog
with a big mouth.
I'm with you cos you're the only man
round here not scared of them.
The only difference between you
and me, Freddie, is that
sometimes my horses stand
a chance of winning.
Tommy!
You fixing races now?
I'm here about the job as barmaid.
Are you in position?
I am, sir.
I thought you said we were going to
the fair.
We have business first. Come on.
Bring your wits.
What business?
That's the Lee family.
Tommy!
Johnny Dogs.
Tommy, how the hell are you?
All the better for getting the city
smoke out of me lungs.
I thought you became a bit
too grand for us.
I've been busy.
I'm riding with the Lee family now.
I heard.
Myself, I'd rather live among pigs.
Come on, Tommy. No disputing.
So, your first fair since France...?
What do you know about France, you
war-shy Gypsy bastard?
So this is the horse.
And that's the car.
Hang on a minute.
You are not swapping the family car
for a bloody horse.
Of course we're not swapping it.
Huh?
That would be mad.
We're going to play two-up.
Subtitles by s}http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Here you are.
I knew it. I knew it.
Tommy, you bloody idiot.
Shut up, Arthur, I won.
I promised Johnny I'd let him have a
spin in the car if he lost.
All right.
Are you Lee boys
laughing at my brother?
Are you?
Eh? Tommy...
Tommy.
I asked you a question!
Tommy, come on, it's just the
craic...
Get your family out of here and go
and enjoy yourselves at the fair
before they start a war. Huh?
Yeah, but his mother was
a Didicoy whore.
We will take them before last night's
beer turns to piss
and wakes the devils up.
We will leave no stone unturned.
Every gun, every bullet will
be brought to me for inspection.
Now...
take your positions.
Don't hit me! Get off me!
Freddie!
You're sure your
brothers are at the fair?
If it was them they wouldn't knock.
Mr Thorne...
What is it?
The police are rounding up
the communists.
Come on, Ada, if the cops find me
we are screwed.
Fuck...
Freddie Thorne, open up!
Ada...
You have to jump, Ada.
I'll catch you.
Come on.
Look at this.
A prescription for iron tablets...
for Ada fucking Shelby.
Mrs Donovan, I need that favour.
Come in and be quick.
I'm not coming in. She is.
Holy Jesus, it's the Shelby girl.
You have not seen her with me,
Mrs Donovan.
Give her a cup of tea and let her
stay until the police have gone.
She's the sister of those
Peaky Blinder devils...
And yet she is an angel.
Come on, Ada.
What are you going to do, Freddie?
Me? I'm going to have to leave town
for a bit.
A gentleman would take off his hat...
and put out his pipe.
I see you Specials
only dare to come here
when you know the boys
are away at the fair.
You mean your nephews...
with their guns and their razors?
Is it them
you're lighting candles for?
No.
I am lighting candles for the boys
from the Garrison who
lost their lives in France.
There's a list there.
Look...
I hear you didn't make it to
France, Inspector Campbell.
You've heard of me.
I've heard of you.
Is it the Holy Grail you're
looking for...?
As a matter of fact...
it is the Holy Grail
I'm looking for.
Something precious.
Something stolen.
Perhaps you know what I'm
talking about.
Sorry, I misunderstood
your intention
when you pushed me to the wall.
Turn the place upside down.
Arthur Shelby said
you people would help us.
If we don't know what you've lost,
how can we help you find it?
But I've found out subsequently that
I was speaking to the wrong man.
Next time I want to
talk to the boss.
The Lickey Tea Rooms.
Friday. Ten o'clock.
And when I say the boss,
I mean Thomas.
Come on.
The scum of the Earth...
Now what the
bloody hell's been going on here?
Jesus Christ.
The coppers told everyone
Arthur had agreed to it
when he was arrested.
They said the Peaky Blinders had
cleared out to the fair
to let them do it.
I never said nothing to that copper
about smashing up bloody houses...
All right... which pubs did they do?
The Guns, the Chain, the Marquis.
All the ones that pay you
to protect them.
The only one they didn't touch
was the Garrison.
Make sure people think
we were in on it.
He's smart, this copper.
So, go on.
Drink your beers, get out.
You'd better show people you're
still the cocks of the walk.
Hand out some cash to the
landlords of the pubs.
Pay some veterans to fix
the places up.
Oi, Nipper. Give us the bag.
So, what about you, Tommy?
I have to go to Charlie's to
stable the horse.
She looked foot-sore in the box.
Let them see your faces.
So we both know what
they were looking for.
You don't read the papers.
Racing papers.
So let me tell you the odds.
I reckon it's three to one
there'll be a revolution.
I wouldn't bet on that.
That copper's betting on it.
He's not going to let it rest till
he gets those guns back.
Did he talk to you, Pol?
In the church.
Did he try to find our Ada?
She was sleeping.
Where was she sleeping, Pol?
I thought you didn't care for
women's business.
He knows you're the boss.
He wants to meet you.
Will you talk to him?
No...
you don't parley
when you're on the back foot.
We'll strike a blow back first.
Finn, lad? What are you doing?
We're having a fire.
Two bob for your picture
of the King.
What?
Bring it to Watery Lane.
All right, Finn, lad.
All right, Scud.
We are blocking the entrance, mate.
Come on, keep making your way
through. Come on.
Come on, gentlemen.
Now come on...
Chuck them on, boys.
Well, I hope to God
you know what you're doing.
I'm a reporter with
the Birmingham Evening Despatch.
I had a phone call.
Someone called Thomas Shelby.
Come with me.
Come on, folks,
give us a bit of room.
Tommy.
Move back for us, please, folks.
You're Mr Shelby?
All the way back, please.
I am.
You said I would be protected.
You're protected.
What's going on?
There are some things
I want you to write down.
Now, first of all...
it's not that people round here are
disloyal to the King.
It's the opposite.
You see, we don't want our beloved
King looking down
and seeing the things
that are being done to us.
So we are taking down his pictures.
But why are you burning them?
We went through hell for our King.
Walked through the flames of war.
Write all this down...
And now we're being
attacked in our own homes.
These new coppers over from Belfast,
breaking into our homes
and interfering with our women.
We don't think our King would
want to see that happening.
So, we're lighting fires to
raise the alarm.
May I ask you, in what capacity
do you speak?
No capacity.
I am an ordinary man.
I won gallantry medals at the Somme.
I want you to write in your paper
what's going on here.
Go on, go.
Come in.
Here, eh...
there's a telephone call for you,
sir, on the London line.
There is? It's almost midnight.
It's Mr Winston Churchill, sir.
Yes, sir?
Inspector Campbell?
I hear there has been
a bonfire in your city.
There was a small fire reported
around nine o'clock on Watery Lane.
But it was certainly nothing to
trouble you about, sir.
Ah,
but I'm afraid it has troubled me.
Half an hour ago I received a
wire communication
from the editor
of the Birmingham Evening Despatch.
It seems one of his reporters was
invited to the fire
and discovered that they were
burning pictures of the King.
Of the King?
Any newspaper report which may cause
embarrassment to His Majesty
is always referred first
and as a matter of routine to the
Home Office.
I will go down there immediately
and arrest those involved.
No, you most certainly will
not make arrests.
If there are arrests
there will be trials,
if there are trials there will be
more newspaper reports,
which will necessarily mention the
burning of the King's likeness.
I put you in Birmingham for one
very specific reason.
Are you any nearer to finding
those stolen guns?
We are making steady progress...
We need results.
Good night, Mr Campbell. Sir...
Could I at least ask,
does this report
name any of those involved?
It names a Mr Thomas Shelby.
The report mentions
he is a war hero.
Good of you to join us.
Where have you been all day?
In bed.
I couldn't sleep.
Then I couldn't wake up.
Then I was cold
and then I had to go for a wee.
Then I was with this bear on a boat,
but that was a dream.
Then I was hungry.
Why are you reading the paper?
Why wouldn't I be?
I've never seen you read the paper.
I've only ever seen you light
fires with them.
The BSA are on strike.
The miners are on strike.
IRA are killing our boys ten a day.
What?
Stand up.
Why?
Just stand up.
Side on.
Hoi! What are you doing?
Ada...
how late are you?
One week.
Five weeks.
Seven if you count weekends.
I think it's a lack of iron.
I got some tablets.
But they didn't work?
No.
You can get dressed now, love.
So, am I or not?
Keep bloody walking, Ada. If anybody
sees us here they'll know.
I'm not getting rid of it, Aunt Pol.
Just come home
and we'll talk about it.
You get off me or I'll scream out,
I swear.
All right, if you want to do
this on the street, let's do it.
Whose is it?
If I tell you, you'll tell them
and they'll cut him to pieces.
Not if he marries you they won't.
Will he marry you?
I don't know.
I don't know where he is.
Jesus Christ, Ada. He's gone away,
but he said he'd come back.
Yeah, but they all say
they'll come back.
He's not like that. He's a good man.
He promised.
He will come back,
Aunt Pol, I know he will.
Get me down a Spanish saddle, Curly.
Yes, Tom, a Spanish saddle.
He's a beauty, Tom.
Yeah, yeah, a beauty, Tom.
A fine beast you got there, Thomas.
But is he worth falling out with
the Lee family over?
Just passing it on...
a declaration of war -
the whole Lee clan.
The guns and now this.
The guns are not spoken of.
Right?
Tommy...
you mind how you speak to me.
Forgive me, Uncle.
It's Thomas Shelby against the
whole bloody world, right?
Easy...
Easy, easy.
Whoa.
Easy, boy.
Shh, shh, shh, shh...
Shh.
In France we used to say...
Shh...
In France we used to say it's
just the music hall band turning up.
Shh. It's just trombones and tubas,
that's all.
It's just noise. Shh. Shh. Shh.
It's just noise.
Hey. It's just noise.
You get used to it.
It's just noise. Good boy.
Good boy.
You have some pain there, boy, hey?
I'm so sorry, Mr Shelby.
I'm Grace, by the way.
I know who you are.
What's his name?
He doesn't have a name.
Poor boy deserves a name.
You have something to say to me?
The other night you came
into the pub and I was singing...
You said singing wasn't allowed.
I'd like there to be one night a week
when there's singing.
I think it would be good for
everyone...
Saturday nights.
Harry was too afraid to ask you,
so...
But you're not.
I am.
But I love to sing.
You sound like one of those
rich girls who comes over
from Dublin for the races.
Do you like horses?
How do you fancy earning
some extra money?
Doing what?
Dig out a nice dress.
I want to take you to the races.
Monaghan Boy two to one.
Get your bets in now before
he goes evens.
We've got a couple of changes coming
in, John. Rock Ferry down to eight.
That's for you. Thanks, mate.
Get your bets in now.
20-1.
There you go, take that to
the twins, yeah? Yeah.
Down to tens. That's right.
Doubles?
OK, friend, Monaghan Boy.
You want to push out, mate,
cos it's going to go evens soon.
Good one. Change of ã35...
I've told you...
Sorry, Mr Shelby.
Go on!
All right, Mr Shelby, how's it going?
Hello, Frank, how's the leg?
Not bad. Not bad.
Good. Nice to see you, son.
Morning, Charlie.
All right, Scudboat,
how are we looking?
Looking good, Tommy.
Grand stuff.
Tommy,
they are all here for Monaghan Boy.
That's what
I like to hear, Johnny Boy.
And Aunt Pol wants to see you.
Tell me the man's name, Ada.
Rudolph Valentino.
Get out! All of you!
Go on! Now!
I said, tell me his fucking name.
Freddie fucking Thorne!
Yeah.
Your best mate since school!
The man who saved your life
in France!
So go on!
Go on, cut him!
Cut him up and chuck him in the cut.
Oi! I'm a Shelby too, you know.
Put my fucking film back on!
So Monaghan Boy finally lost.
Third time unlucky.
We took money
from all over the city.
Yeah, but you'll pay it back
to people round here.
Buy your popularity back.
Already done.
I taught you well.
And you fixed this race without
the permission of Billy Kimber.
Obviously, I didn't teach
you well enough.
Rule one,
you don't punch above your weight.
Billy Kimber is
there for the taking...
Says who? Says Tommy
and his parliament of one.
I ran this business for five
years...
Yeah, while I was away fighting,
remember,
where I learnt some things,
such as
you strike when your enemy is weak.
I thought you came here
to talk family business.
I'll deal with it.
You're too busy taking over the
world... Polly...
If it's about Ada, I need to know.
Ada wants you to give
Freddie this letter.
She wants Freddie to know she's
having his baby.
He deserves an opportunity to
do the right thing.
I say we give them a chance.
For a woman who's had a
hard life with men,
you're still full of romance, eh?
What do you think Freddie
sees in our Ada?
That's Freddie's business...
No.
No. I'll tell you what he sees.
He sees machine guns, and rifles,
and ammunition,
and some glorious revolution.
What is it you really
don't like about Freddie?
She'll have no life with
a man on the run.
If you can't see that,
you can't see much.
Damn them for what
they did to you in France.
Tell Ada Freddie went to America.
Or Russia.
Polly, it would do no good for Ada
to bring a baby into the world
alone.
Pol, listen.
The truth is you would have hit me
with that thing
if it weren't for the fact
that you know I'm right.
I thought I heard someone knocking.
Couldn't get back to sleep.
The longer you leave it...
the worse it gets.
Believe me...
I know.
I was 16.
And I didn't dare tell anyone.
Polly, Freddie will come back...
In the end I did it myself.
I did it to myself...
and I almost died.
And he didn't come back.
They don't. Why should they?
You know the words.
You're a whore,
the baby's a bastard...
but there's no word for the man
who doesn't come back.
One day...
on your wedding day...
you'll have a good man
on your arm...
and you'll say, "Polly...
"thank you for common sense."
This woman is in Cardiff.
We'll take the train tomorrow.
Go to the castle
afterwards for a treat.
I chose this place because it is
outside both our jurisdictions.
Do you want tea?
Inspector, I responded
to your invitation
because I want us
to understand each other.
I am a businessman.
I want to make my business
successful.
And I want my city
to run peacefully.
Well, if the city is peaceful,
business can thrive.
So we are on the same side?
I think perhaps we could be.
How can we be on the same side
when I see things like this?
My men found this in the bedroom
of a known communist.
It has your sister's name on it.
It was obvious she had been
sleeping in his bed.
Are you also in bed with
the communists, Mr Shelby?
I do not share their fantasy.
And, as for my sister, I have
already dealt with the situation.
Freddie Thorne is at the very
top of my list. So cross him off.
He won't be returning to the city.
I'll make him part of our deal.
What "deal"?
You and your Specials will leave
my businesses alone from now on.
No more raids into our territory,
no more smashing up pubs
and no more lifting my runners.
You will turn a blind eye to
all my gambling operations.
Also, I am planning an expansion.
Onto the racetracks.
I intend to do business
with Billy Kimber.
He runs most of the legal track-side
betting outside of London.
He has policemen on his payroll.
I want you to put in a word with
the Chief Inspector at
Gloucestershire that his men should
leave me alone when I make my move.
Forgive me.
I don't seem to have a pen
to write down this rather
long list of demands.
And what do I get in return?
I have what you're looking for.
I have the guns.
What guns?
I'm not here to play games...
Wait, wait.
25 Lewis machine guns,
50 carbines,
10,000 rounds of ammunition -
all in a crate bound for Libya,
stolen from the BSA
factory proofing bay.
I'm guessing they sent you to
Birmingham to get those guns back.
Well, it's me that has them.
I have left word with men I trust
that if I am taken into police
custody for whatever reason, those
guns will be shipped to Liverpool.
From there they will be sent
directly to Belfast
and sold to the
Irish Republican Army.
All your good work in Ireland
would be undone.
Each stolen weapon is
numbered and marked.
If I sell them to the IRA,
it won't be long
before Mr Churchill finds out.
I imagine you got into enough
trouble over
the burning of
the King's photographs.
That was just a taster.
If those guns reach Belfast,
your life in the force is over.
When I have achieved what
I have set out to achieve,
I will let you know
where to find the guns.
You'll be a hero.
You'll probably get a medal.
I'm a fair man.
It's a fair offer.
Do we have a deal?
I need an answer.
Right now.
Very well.
But I'd prefer
if we don't shake hands on it.
Now why would I shake
the hand of a man who didn't even
fight for his country?
Grace.
I have new information.
'Thomas Shelby is now
the beginning, the middle'
and the end of your mission.
So what shall I do?
It hurts me as much as it
would a father sending his own
daughter into a whorehouse but...
no matter how repugnant it may be,
you must do everything
you can to get close to him and...
find out where the guns are hidden.
Of course, when I say everything,
I don't mean...
You underestimate me in every way.
Here.
'You are now active
in a military operation'
on behalf of the Crown.
I wish to God
circumstance hadn't chosen you.
It's what I'm trained for.
I'm late for my shift.
Grace...
my heart is with you.
Tom. Tom!
Tom, you better come quick. Tom!
Curly, tell me.
It's a curse, Tom.
Curly, Curly, shh, shh.
Curly, Curly.
Tell me.
Tell me, Curly, what's
wrong with your horse?
You bought her at the fair
in bad feeling.
The Lees put a bad seed in the hoof,
got an old woman to put a spell...
So those Lee bastards cursed her.
Whatever it is, he says
it's spread to the other feet.
It's going to his heart
by tomorrow, I'd say.
Seen curses like this twice.
Can't take them back, Tom. No.
I told you, Tommy.
Better enemies to have than
black-blood Gypsies.
Get out.
Get out, Curly.
I'm sorry.
We're closed, Mr Shelby.
Just get me a drink.
Should I leave you alone?
I came here for company.
Where's Harry?
He took the night off.
He went to the pictures.
How's your beautiful horse?
I just put a bullet in his head.
Was he lame?
He looked at me the wrong way.
It's not a good idea to look at
Tommy Shelby the wrong way.
What a waste. Yeah.
A waste is what it is.
You know, in France...
In France,
I got used to seeing men die.
I never got used to
seeing horses die.
They die badly.
I dug out a dress like you asked.
Thanks.
Is it Cheltenham
you're talking about?
Cheltenham's a grand affair,
is it not?
The King will be there.
King George?
No.
King Billy Kimber...
and all his men.
And what must I do?
For two pounds, you'll do
what I ask you to do.
I want three.
If I'm meeting a King,
I won't be wearing a cheap dress.
And I asked you to let me sing.
That's part of the deal now too.
Since when?
Since you nearly smiled.
Saturday nights, open and easy.
Everyone gets to sing their song
just like we did in Dublin.
You never worked in Dublin...
so don't lie to me.
I asked around about that pub
you said you used to work in.
I have friends over there.
No-one has heard of you.
My guess is...
you're a girl from a good family
who got herself pregnant.
It's not something I want known.
And bringing a child into the world
alone ruined your life.
Right?
So I'm right...
and Polly is wrong.
Right about what?
It doesn't matter.
It looks like it matters to you.
Family business.
You won't tell anyone my secret.
Do you think I tell people things?
So what do you sing?
Anything you want. Right.
Get up on a chair.
Happy or sad?
Sad.
OK.
But I warn you,
I'll break your heart.
Already broken.
♪ In a neat little town
they call Belfast
♪ Apprentice to trade I was bound
♪ Many an hour's sweet happiness
♪ Had I spent in that
neat little town
♪ A sad misfortune came over me
♪ Which caused me to stray
from the land
♪ Far away from my
friends and relations
♪ Betrayed by the black velvet band
♪ Her eyes, they shone like diamonds
♪ I thought her the queen
of the land
♪ And her hair,
it hung over her shoulder
♪ Tied up with
a black velvet band. ♪
You OK? Yeah, I'm fine.
I think there are some carriages over
there that are going to be empty but...
Jesus.
Freddie?
You came back?
I got a tip-off.
Freddie, Tommy will kill you.
It was Tommy who tipped me off.
Maybe he's got half a heart
after all.
Tommy got a message to me.
It said "Get out of town
and take her with you."
So...
Ada Shelby...
will you marry me?
Yes.
Right, get on that bloody train
and get out of here.
Come on, both of you.
Freddie, come on.
Freddie, Cardiff's OK.
Anywhere but here's OK.
We're not going anywhere, Ada!
We're going to stay here
and we're going to marry here.
I'm not afraid of Tommy Shelby!
♪ Give me your smile
♪ The love light in your eyes
♪ Life could not hold... ♪
Shuffle these cards... Terms of
play, John boy, terms of play.
Go and play snap with Finn.
Did you want whiskey as well?
No, just beer.
Why no whiskey, Tommy?
Are you expecting trouble?
Jesus Christ, Tommy, what the
hell made you let them sing?
They sound like they're
strangling cats out there.
All right, 20 to play. Come on.
What did make you
change your mind though, Tommy? Mmm?
Yeah, I mean,
it's about time, Tommy.
Time for what?
Time you took yourself a woman.
Just play the bloody hands.
You stay the way you are, Tommy.
Remember what Dad used to say -
"Fast women and slow horses...
"..will ruin your life."
Coppers.
No.
♪ Come, Josephine,
in my flying machine
♪ Up she goes
♪ Balance yourself like a bird... ♪
Holy shit.
It's Billy Kimber.
Is there any man here named Shelby?
I said,
is there any man here named Shelby?
Harry, get these men a drink.
Everyone else, go home.
You, go home.
But Mr Fenton said...
I said go home.
I've never approved of women in pubs
but when they look like that...
You said you wanted men called
Shelby. You've got three of them.
Right, I'd never heard of you,
then I did hear of you,
some little Didicoy razor gang.
I thought to myself, so what?
But then you fuck me over
so now you have my
undivided attention.
By the way, which one am I
talking to? Who's the boss?
Well, I'm the oldest.
Ha... clearly.
Are you laughing at my brother?
Right, he's the oldest,
you're the thickest.
I'm told the boss is called Tommy
and I'm guessing that's you
cos you're looking me up and down
like I'm a fucking tart.
I want to know what you want.
There were suspicious betting
patterns at Kempton Park.
A horse called Monaghan Boy.
He won by a length twice
and then finished last
with ã3,000 bet on him.
Which one am I talking to?
Which one of you is the boss?
I am Mr Kimber's advisor
and accountant.
And I'm the fucking boss, OK?
Right, end of parley, you fixed
a race without my permission.
You fucking Gypsy scum what
live off the war pensions of these
poor old Garrison Lane widows!
That's your level!
I am Billy Kimber, I run the races
and you fixed one of them
so I'm going to have you shot
against a post.
Mr Kimber.
Look at it.
That is my name on it.
It's from the Lee family.
You are also at war with the Lees,
Mr Kimber, am I right?
The Lees are attacking your bookies
and taking your money.
Your men can't control them.
You need help.
Perhaps we should listen to what
Mr Shelby has to say.
Before we make our decisions.
Right, the Lees are doing
a lot of talking at the fairs.
They have a lot of kin.
They're saying the racetracks are
easy meat
because the police are
busy with strikes.
Now, we have connections.
We know how they operate.
You have muscle.
Together we can beat them.
Divided, maybe not.
Mr Kimber, perhaps we should take
some time for reflection.
Possibly make arrangements
for a second meeting.
I admire you, Mr Kimber.
You started with nothing
and built a legitimate business.
It would be an honour to work
with you, Mr Kimber.
Nobody works with me.
People work for me.
Pick it up, pikey.
Sit. Sit down.
That's for your ceiling.
Thank you, Mr Kimber.
We will be at Cheltenham.
As will I.
So you picked a fight with
the Lees on purpose.
Tommy, we can't mess with
Billy fucking Kimber.
Get yourself a decent haircut, man.
We're going to the races.
Subtitles by s}http://UKsubtitles.ru.