[Laura] Jack Nelson's coming to London.
There are some people in this country
who I'd like to meet.
Fascists.
Not the ones in boots and black shirts,
the ones in tuxedos.
[Mosley] Mr Shelby, Lady Diana Mitford.
Oswald's most recent
and last ever mistress.
Officially, he's coming
to buy liquor import licences.
And unofficially, he's Roosevelt's envoy.
By being among the fascists,
by being among them, I can undermine them.
Still looking for trouble
big enough to kill you.
If you don't want to help me
carry the bucket, I won't blame you.
You have to carry this bucket on your own.
Do we have a deal, Mr Nelson?
You're a brave man.
Every war hero I ever met,
they're just someone
who wanted to get themselves killed.
-If anyone's going to kill Tommy Shelby...
-It will be you.
The Devil will be dead.
The future belongs to us.
[Lizzie] You need to see a doctor.
We got to keep going
till this Boston business is done.
[coughs]
-Hello?
-Tommy, she has a temperature of 101
and nothing is working.
Just get here now.
[laboured breathing]
Move away! Move away!
-No. Where's the doctor?
-[Lizzie] Can you get the doctor?
-I need to speak to a doctor.
-[doctor] Mr Shelby. Mr Shelby.
Your daughter has consumption.
Consumption is a very infectious disease.
There are procedures
that must be followed.
Please, hand over the child.
-[Lizzie] Okay. It's all right.
-[Tommy] Lizzie.
[Tommy] Right, you take her. Be gentle.
Look after her.
That's my daughter. Do you hear me?
I need to be with her.
-[nurse] Stop.
-I need to be with my daughter!
[Lizzie] Tom.
[exhales] Okay. Come on.
They are X-raying Ruby,
they have to X-ray us.
We might have it as well.
Fuck us, Lizzie. Fuck us! Fuck you and me!
Who brought this on?
We've brought on this curse!
Stop, Tommy! Fucking stop!
[both panting]
They wouldn't let me pass.
-[Lizzie sighs]
-They did it on purpose.
To punish me.
Tommy, stop it, please.
All right.
[sighs] All right.
My husband is very sorry.
Okay.
My husband is very sorry
and he is calm now.
He's recovering from addiction.
Sometimes...
he's a horse in a crate,
kicking the crate.
[breathes deeply]
It's just the crate I'm kicking.
I'm sorry.
-Lizzie.
-[Lizzie] Yeah?
Tell me what I have to do.
[nurse 2] This way, sir.
Sorry.
[Lizzie] Thank you.
[mechanical whirring]
[woman] Mr Shelby, you'll need
to keep still for a moment.
[equipment shifting]
[door slamming]
To see what's inside.
Wait till you see...
God.
[rapid clicking]
God knows what's inside.
God help her.
[footsteps approaching]
She has a tubercular infection
in her left lung.
They've caught it quite early.
They'll do more tests.
They do this thing. "Pulmonary" something.
Where they collapse the lung, let it rest.
Sometimes the lung cures itself.
If that doesn't work, they use gold.
What?
Gold?
Yeah, gold salts.
Doctor said he explained
the methods to you
when you cut the ribbon
to open the institution.
Can't remember, I wasn't listening.
Yeah, well...
Gold salts.
Salt with 37% gold.
[sighs]
They say it helps,
but it will make her more sick at first.
Did they say... [exhales]
Did they say what the chances are?
No, they don't say.
[Tommy] Mmm.
But she's small.
And with TB, that's not good
because the disease is big and fast.
[sobbing]
I'm so sorry, my darling.
I will deal with it.
I will make it go away.
I will strike a bargain.
[door opens]
[Lizzie] You should be wearing a mask.
I am.
[kisses]
You can try gold.
I will try something else.
[telephone dials]
[Tommy] Mayfair, 244.
Ada? Listen to me.
I need you to be me in London.
No, it's important.
I know you want nothing
to do with my business.
But Ruby is very sick.
I need five days of your time.
[telephone drops]
So she dresses well.
Go to the door and take her coat.
-[man] Yes, ma'am.
-Uh...
And make a note of the label.
[man] Of course, ma'am.
Oh, Thomas, where the devil are you?
[suspenseful music playing]
[car stops]
[lever clicks]
[knock on door]
Mrs Ada Thorne, ma'am.
I thought you were all called Shelby.
I'm a widow.
My husband didn't have
the good grace to die.
He lingers yet.
Your husband's a member
of the Guinness family, I believe.
They do a lot of good work
on behalf of the poor.
The poor who are only poor
because they spent so much
of their income on Guinness.
Please.
I think the causes of poverty
are a little more complex than that.
Yes, I believe it is to do with genetics.
Huh. Beautiful vase.
My grandfather stole it
from a brothel in Cairo.
Egyptian. 18th dynasty, I think.
How do you know
so much about Egyptian vases?
-I collect antiques.
-Hmm.
A tribe of Gypsies
settles on a clearing in a factory town.
Children, of course,
ensue in their hundreds,
but one of them
becomes a gangster and a politician.
The other a collector of antiques.
It is quite extraordinary.
A result of genetics, I think.
My dear, you researched me
and I researched you.
If this was 1919,
you would have come through my front door
carrying a revolver and a Molotov cocktail
and would happily have blown off my head.
[chuckles] Isn't it wonderful how time
changes everything? Where is the American?
-He'll be here later.
-Where's Mosley?
He heard Thomas wasn't coming
so he decided to sulk. You know men.
Where is Thomas?
His daughter is sick.
Does he not employ a governess?
Hmm. It's a class thing. A genetic thing.
He puts his daughter's welfare
before business.
Even the business of changing the world?
I thought today was purely social.
Now that it's just you,
I suppose it will be.
[laughs]
[Diana chuckles]
You should know
your brother has altered my life.
The men here just bounce up and down
in their saddles in a rising trot,
never even galloping.
Thomas is the man
on the horse on the vase.
That's why I put it out
for you to look at.
According to recent interpretations,
the black rider on 18th-dynasty vases
is meant to signify approaching death.
So, yes, I suppose it resembles Thomas.
Tell me, why is he
so emotionally mutilated?
Well, because he's a character
in a novel, of course.
One of those novels
ladies like you like to read.
All about wild men.
[scoffs] Well, I don't read novels.
I read only pornography and politics.
In the absence of the men, shouldn't
we ladies be engaging in small talk?
Very well. Small talk.
[inhales deeply]
You know, I like
to fuck women as well as men.
[chuckles]
Tommy was right.
He says that everything is a circle.
A lady in Eaton Square
as coarse and honest as an Aston whore.
Just realised I haven't even
offered you a drink.
[bottle clinks]
Ada, before the dreary business
of changing the world begins,
I want you to know something.
When the time comes
for the great cleansing,
I myself will personally argue the case
that the Jews must be dealt with,
but that the Gypsies should be spared.
[scoffs]
Let's drink whiskey
and wait for the American.
[both chuckle]
[gravel crunches]
[dogs barking]
Who the fuck are you?
I am the owner of this Colt pistol
and the bullets within it.
And I'm in a hurry.
I followed the patrin signs
of the Lee family.
I'm looking for Esme Shelby-Lee.
Never heard of her.
[in Romani] She is my brother's widow.
I am very anxious to speak to her.
[in English] Esme's husband was
a fucking dirty didicoy.
He was a Peaky Blinder.
[Tommy] Yeah?
Well, I am the elder and more terrible.
And as I said, I'm in a hurry.
Where is she?
Put your gun away, Thomas.
There's children around.
You only found me
'cause I let you find me.
I heard you were looking. And I'm curious.
If any of these men is your man,
please tell him I want no trouble.
[Esme] I don't have a man.
What use is a man?
Horse pulls the wagon.
Dog keeps me safe.
Cat keeps me warm at night.
And if anyone's gonna
give you trouble, Tommy Shelby,
it'll be me.
What do you want?
Tell 'em to leave.
What, you think I'm in charge here?
Oh, I'm sure of it, Esme.
[in Romani] Leave.
The poor boy is scared.
[dogs barking]
[horse neighing]
[in English] Didicoy's too grand
to put his arse on the grass these days?
I have a daughter, Esme.
Her name is Ruby.
She's fallen ill, suddenly.
She's very sick.
And I can tell, by saying her name
and looking in your eyes,
that I've wasted petrol, time and hope.
[Esme] Wasted petrol on what?
Oh!
Tommy Shelby, OBE, MP,
running around the mountains
in pursuit of a Gypsy curse, is that it?
I thought you had
Polly deal with the spirits.
Polly is dead.
Bullet or blade?
Still speaks to me in my dreams.
It was her who told me to come find you.
Polly.
[scoffs]
That name, like the ringing
of a school bell.
"Come and do as you're told."
Fuck.
So glad I'm not in your camp any more.
Made of bricks and bars.
[Tommy] My daughter is dying, Esme.
Some people go to France.
To Lourdes. I hear they sell trinkets.
I need more than fucking trinkets.
I can tell from your reaction,
this is not your doing.
Sorry for troubling you.
[clock ticking]
[door opens]
The butler says
our American friend is parking the car.
He also says,
in answer to your inquiry, Diana,
that the coat our exotic friend
is wearing is made by Chanel.
That's a very expensive label.
Yes, it is.
But the perfume
I can smell on you is very cheap.
[Mosley clears throat]
I'm deeply, deeply annoyed
that Thomas isn't here.
[Diana] It is a family emergency,
apparently.
We only have Ada, the sister.
Well, would the sister
like some more champagne?
-The sister is allowed to speak?
-She thinks this lunch is purely social.
[laughs]
The sister is here
because there's sickness in the family.
Thomas wanted someone
from the Shelby organisation
to introduce Mr Nelson to you,
and to offer
all three of you an invitation.
Ooh.
What invitation?
[Ada] The invitation can wait.
And please remember that
in this moment, in this room,
it is the Shelby family
that holds the power
because we have the information
and the incentives
that will make Mr Nelson
do what you require him to do.
So when I speak,
please keep your fucking mouths closed.
Because although I'm reluctant,
I am actually quite good at this.
And, yes, I will have champagne.
-[Gina chuckles]
-[Mosley] Ah!
Take care of this.
Okay, so before these
dull introductions begin,
I just have to tell you something
that my niece, Gina, just told me.
[Gina] No, Jack...
She said the Shelby family
are all witches and sorcerers
who speak freely with the dead. So...
who here is a Shelby?
-[Ada clears throat]
-Is it true?
-[Ada] Gina.
-Hello, Ada.
Michael sends his regards.
You're the sister.
Yes, it seems I am, indeed, the sister.
[Nelson] I did some research.
You were a communist once,
but diamonds and lipstick now?
Actually, I'm a socialist.
She's Mr Shelby's political advisor.
And you're the future prime minister
of Great Britain and its dominions.
Indeed, I am.
And you, Lady Diana Mitford.
Talk of London,
with her amphetamines and emeralds.
[laughs]
It's her sharp mind that I'm in love with.
Men bore me.
Ada, do you have a man?
My husband died.
But, of course, we speak often.
Between this sparkling conversation,
could I get a drink of some kind?
So this little kid, Gina, she runs out,
she marries a gangster,
and now here we all are.
Oh, Jack, please. You're so blunt.
Yes, it's wonderful.
A man who is not careful with his words.
I'm not careful.
Just say it first and then clear up
the broken glass with my bare hands.
[Mosley] Here you are.
I don't seem to have a drink either.
Well, I have Scotch or Irish.
Thomas drinks Irish.
Where the hell is he?
Irish.
-He's been unavoidably detained.
-Nothing is unavoidable.
[Mosley] His daughter is unwell.
He doesn't have a wife?
[bottle clinks]
You know, I did some research
on you too, Mr Nelson.
Ada here is the smart one of the family.
When you were young, you lost
a brother and a sister to consumption.
No ice?
Well that same awful illness
has entered our family.
And Thomas has very little faith
in current medical practices
regarding tuberculosis.
Man, he has that right.
He's gone off in search of alternative
approaches to curing the disease.
Experimental work that he hopes
will save the life of his daughter.
[Nelson] In his shoes,
I would do the same thing.
Your brother intrigues me.
Yes, he often has that effect on people.
Yes, and my future husband has that effect
on 20 million people in this country,
who attend his rallies
and listen to his broadcasts.
[Nelson] It's amazing...
what English upper-class women can do
with just skin, bone and arrogance.
[Ada] My brother sends his apologies
for not being here
and would like to invite all of you
to his home for a meeting.
A meeting where
the real business will be done.
And where you can meet
like minds from Ireland.
Who'd also like to discuss
the future of Europe.
But as you say,
this lunch is purely social.
And looking at my glass,
I see I still don't have champagne.
Michael told me
the sister had gone straight.
Yes, but her brother is the Sun.
The rest just orbit around him.
Gina tells me lots of things,
but I want to hear it from you, Ada.
What exactly does
the Shelby Company Limited do?
[suspenseful music playing]
[car engine sputters]
Fuck!
[sighs]
[knock on window]
You used to have eyes
in the back of your head.
How can you change so much
and not change at all?
I have other lines of inquiry.
Give me the spark plug. Give me the...
Give me the fucking spark plug.
Give you the spark, give you hope,
is that what you want?
[Esme scoffs]
[in Romani] I do know things
about this matter.
[in English] Something you should see.
Someone dead.
Someone grieving.
A lot of hate against you.
You were wise to come to me, Thomas.
Open the bonnet, would you?
What hate?
What hate? What grieving?
I can't explain
where it is you have to go.
So I'll take you there.
I hope the suspension's good.
We're going to a wild, old place.
[Tommy sighs]
[car engine starts]
[bottles rattling]
[typewriters clacking]
[Edna] Mrs Thorne, Mr Shelby isn't here.
[sighs] I know. I am.
Do you know where he's gone?
He's gone up a mountain,
looking for a miracle.
[Edna] No one is allowed to go in
if he's not here.
Just bring me the keys. All of the keys.
[keys jingling]
Do you want tea, Mrs Thorne?
Whiskey.
Mr Shelby doesn't allow whiskey
in the building any more.
Then have someone go and fetch some.
Until Mr Shelby comes down
off his mountain, I'm in charge.
Yes, Mrs Thorne.
[door closes]
[sighs]
Fuck.
[indistinct chattering]
Mickey, I've gotta go.
The boss's sister is here.
For the next five days,
I'm not the boss's sister,
I'm the boss.
Where is Arthur?
We locked him in the cash safe.
When he gets the yamps really bad,
he tells us to lock him in the safe.
Stop him from slipping down to China Town.
What are "the yamps"?
When you lose your head.
When you can't control yourself.
Young people say it.
Hmm.
Arthur gets the yamps a lot?
A lot is twice a day.
Arthur gets them three times a day.
It smells in here.
Arthur sleeps on the floor.
We lock him in at night.
On your feet.
Sit down.
Nice perfume.
[drawer shuts]
Tommy likes you, Isiah.
Believe I'm suited to this life.
I'm not so sure about you.
I was given to understand that
you are no longer part of the company.
[scoffs]
You speak well.
I was going to be an accountant.
But everybody said
I would be wasted counting money.
Instead of stealing it.
What's the name of that perfume?
I've got a girlfriend with a birthday.
I want you to go to Liverpool.
Well, then I will go to Liverpool.
We have opium in storage
at the Salthouse Docks.
Word got out among the dock workers,
they started stealing cupfuls,
now it's by the bucket.
By the bucket?
The audacity of it.
The sale of the stolen opium
is being organised by a union convener
called Haydn Stagg.
In the envelope
you'll find details of where to find him
and what to do to him when you do.
There's no black star on the envelope.
I decided not.
You decided?
The name of the perfume
is "know your fucking place," soldier.
-I decided he'll just take a beating.
-[telephone rings]
And also that you're gonna
take Arthur with you.
[ringing fades]
Arthur?
Ten days clean, I'm gonna take him
into a warehouse full of fucking opium?
Can be your job to look after him.
Why take him at all?
It's his reputation you're taking.
The beating can be conducted
in a civilised way.
No one would dare fuck with Arthur Shelby.
But they would fuck with me?
Yes.
He is Arthur Shelby.
You're Isiah... Who?
I'm just Isiah.
Who is keen to learn, Ada.
Keep him clean.
Deal with Haydn Stagg,
bring Arthur back in one piece,
and in return,
I won't tell Tommy that you're laying
private bets on races that we've fixed.
I'm just trying
to make a few extra pennies.
Buy that birthday present
for my girlfriend.
Mmm.
Lucky girl.
[door closes]
[keys clatter]
Lock the door, Lizzie.
There are people around here who start
drinking this early in the morning.
No.
Need to stay myself. [sighs]
-Be strong.
-No. Come on. Not with me.
You can let it go with me.
I can't cry, Ada.
If I start, I'll fall apart.
I need to stay strong for Ruby.
Tommy says it's just in one lung.
[sighs] No.
They now think it's in both.
It's moving quickly.
They collapsed the left lung,
but it made no difference.
Starting her on the gold salts tomorrow.
You know somebody who died
on the gold treatment, yes?
Half the people I tell
look like you just did
because they know someone
who died on the gold treatment.
The person I knew was old.
Old and young, the same.
You've given up, Lizzie?
[swallows loudly]
No.
I'm being strong.
At her bedside, on my own.
While Tommy is up in the mountains
to be among the Gypsies.
In truth, it's a blessing
he's not around at the hospital.
Because all he wants to do
is fight people and blame himself.
And I've never felt so ashamed of him.
Christ, 'cause right now, I...
I need a normal man.
It's me sitting there,
taking away the bloody rags
and watching her disappear.
Do you know when he's back, Ada?
He gave me instructions, not information.
[exhales]
Can you get a message to him?
He'll be out of reach.
Ada, I thought you might know things.
[sighs] I've been away from all this.
You're still Gypsy.
Yeah, well, the mystery leaves you.
What mystery?
Lizzie, is there anything practical
that I can do?
Before he left,
he was looking for a number for Esme.
[scoffs] What's Esme got to do with this?
I thought you might know.
Esme's a Lee.
What does that mean?
The Lees and the Barwells,
they're wild tribes.
Where do they live?
They're Gypsies.
-They live where they like.
-Fuck.
Fuck, Ada...
[scoffs and sighs]
Tribes in the mountains.
It's 1934, and the doctors
know what it is.
They know what causes it.
But no, my husband, he knows better.
Not a normal man, your brother.
He's up in the mountains
with fucking horse thieves and sorcerers,
while I'm here on my own.
Not a normal man.
[Lizzie sighs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
It's okay, Arthur. I'll look after you.
Yeah.
And Ada said it'd be okay
if I recruited my cousins.
Off the streets of Alum Rock
and looking for the big time.
What do you say, Arthur?
[sighs]
I say big-time boys
don't ask for permission.
I think he means you're in.
Let's go.
Can you still ride bareback?
[car engine stops]
[car door closes]
[knife slices]
[horse neighs]
[Tommy] We're a long way
from anywhere, Esme.
I find out you've been wasting my time,
I'll use that rope to fucking hang you.
Right, hold up. Hold on. Hold on.
Listen, you know what you gotta do, right?
You've got your orders.
I'm depending on you.
You hear me?
And let me tell you something.
Any man...
Any fucking man
who looked like this before
are Peaky Blinder.
A Peaky Blinder still looks like this...
after.
Let's go.
We are here to meet a gentleman
called Haydn Stagg.
[man] A gentleman?
Mr Stagg?
That scoundrel.
Never there when you need him.
Who needs him?
We do.
Where is he?
The last I saw, he was
up to his balls in a lady called Maria.
[all laughing]
[man groans]
[Isiah] No time for tradition
or the rules of the sporting life
because, among the Peaky Blinders,
any man who comes home
from a mission with all his bullets,
he pays a fine.
My name's Haydn Stagg.
I hear there's some men here
from Birmingham looking for me.
I was in the banana warehouse
playing football with the boys.
I'm guessing you gentlemen
aren't here to kick footballs.
No.
We're here about other business.
We like to call it "Black Star" business.
Black Star a pub, is it?
Black Star...
Yeah, Black Star is a pub.
Last pub you ever fucking drink in.
Peaky Blinders take you to the Black Star,
and all your troubles are done.
But the pub you drink in, Mr Stagg,
is called The Dolphin, right?
Every night... [sniffs]
...you're in there.
Not to drink.
You're there divvying up
the day's takings, ain't you?
And there's a woman there.
She sings out, "Opium for sale!"
[guns cock]
Sit down, boys.
[gun cocks]
The rules say the king puts his head
on the block and the game is up.
You're stealing
from the Shelby Company Limited.
from the Peaky Blinders, man.
Therefore...
punishment
is a visit to the Black Star pub.
Hmm?
But out of kindness,
of my heart,
your sentence has been commuted.
Praise the fucking Lord!
And our lovely Ada, eh?
Instead...
Instead, Mr Haydn Stagg,
it's just a beating for you.
Well, before I take this beating...
Arthur Shelby, is it, yeah?
You know, comrade,
beneath your sleeves lies the truth.
The marks on your arm.
Yeah.
The stories about you come up the canal.
You know, where once
you walked fine alone,
now you need a stick.
[Isiah] Let's just fucking do it, Arthur.
[scoffs]
You know, for me, it was the morphine
they gave us in France.
I got a taste for it, Arthur.
1924 before I realised
the fucking war was over.
There's a warehouse
full of it just across the yard there.
Where the boys play football.
And they steal it.
Just roll around laughing.
And it floats in the air.
But I'm strong, comrade.
Arthur, let's just fucking do it.
Liar.
It's me that's due a beating.
But it's me who feels sorry
for you, Mr Shelby,
because you take your beating
every hour of every day.
Your own blood betrays you
because it demands dilution.
Sometimes you want
to cut a doorway in your arm
so your blood can escape
and leave you in blessed peace.
-[Arthur inhales deeply]
-[Haydn] Yeah.
Fuck you, man.
I was once where you are now, Arthur.
[Arthur sobs]
If you're gonna do it, do it.
But look at me as the man you can be.
You've tried Jesus, yeah?
Yeah, he looked you up and down
and he shook his head.
Your loved ones.
Your wife.
Your kids.
Jesus and your wife
and your kids can't help you.
Only you, Arthur Shelby.
Only you.
Don't count the days.
Futile.
You get to a hundred and then you wake up
and it's fucking one again.
[sniffs]
No, don't build mountains.
Walk like it's a flat plain.
Easy step by easy step.
Arthur, just give me the fucking word
and I'll fucking do it!
He's your stick, Arthur.
Give him the order.
[Isiah] Arthur, I'm not gonna
ask you fucking twice!
Isiah, leave him alone.
[Isiah] No. No fucking way.
Leave him alone.
Isiah, I said you can stand down!
Enough, let's go. Come on.
Come on, all of you!
Go on! Go on!
Gypsy graveyard.
You can still read the signs.
No horse will go beyond here,
we'll have to walk.
Tell me whose grave it is.
You'll see.
Who knows what you'll see?
Do you ever go to John's grave?
When things are really bad.
Well what's really bad?
I've done bad things, Esme.
You think now
you're being punished for them?
I would like to make amends.
You want to lift every curse
anyone's ever put on you.
That's a lot of lifting.
-My own curse is in there somewhere.
-I should've done more to protect John.
Think in this holy place, the spirits
are listening to you being kind?
Believe it or not, Esme,
I'm discovering kindness.
I'm learning it from my children.
[chuckles]
-Do you ever think you've lost your mind?
-I lost it long ago.
I only use the crate it came in.
I know why you're here.
I'm in a hurry, Esme.
Think you can make a deal even with death?
Well soon you'll be
in the right place to do it.
The village disappeared. Church fell down.
Only us still use the graveyard.
[decorations rattling]
Do you recall a sapphire?
You gave a sapphire to a woman
called Bethany Barwell.
Ten years ago.
She took the stone back to her camp.
I warned her about it,
but she took it anyway.
[Esme] She gave the sapphire
to her sister, Evadne Barwell.
Evadne put the stone
around the neck of her daughter.
Little girl.
Straight away,
the little girl began to cough.
She died that night.
Seven years old.
I heard they threw
the sapphire in the river.
No one's ever gone to look for it.
I'm guessing it's the girl's mother
who laid the curse.
Only women can lay curses.
Perhaps she waited
till your little girl was seven.
So you'd know how it feels.
-[Tommy] Do you have whiskey?
-[Esme] No.
[Esme] Tommy.
Perhaps the treatment will work
and your daughter will live.
Science.
Science is winning everything these days.
Even against the angels.
I can leave you if you want.
Your horse will know its way back.
But I think there should be
some reward for what I've shown you.
Some consideration.
You can afford it, Mr Shelby, OBE.
I will find her.
I will find this fucking Evadne Barwell.
I will fucking find her.
I'll give her money
to take back this curse.
You only found me
'cause I wanted to be found.
The Barwells
roam from the border to the sea.
I will give her £10,000. More, anything.
You will put out word, Esme.
You will put out word,
I will put out word, I will find her.
And instead of this poor wooden cross...
[Esme] Tommy!
...I will build a monument
to this little girl.
Her mother can decide how big.
It can be as big
as fucking Nelson's Column.
That and £10,000.
I will buy her off.
I will start looking today.
Ruby will be well!
She will be well!
And I will undo
the many wrongs that I have done.
Now that I'm without whiskey,
I can hear the spirits clearly.
They're saying Ruby will be well
if I make amends.
That is the conversation.
If you want my help,
I will help you, Thomas. If you pay me.
Pay me and I'll help you to find her.
-I will pay you.
-But I don't want money.
I don't read the papers,
but I know there was a crash.
Nothing is certain and money loses value.
Instead of money, give me gold.
[panting] Gold. Yes, I will give you gold.
[Esme] In uncertain times,
gold is always certain.
[Tommy] I will give you gold.
And you will help me find this woman
and she will spare my daughter.
[thunder rumbles]
[car approaches]
-[Tommy] Lizzie!
-Where the fuck were you?
Where were you?!
Where the fuck were you?!
She's gone, Tommy. [sobs]
She's gone.
Just now. 5:17.
You weren't fucking near here.
Were you? Were you?
[breathing heavily]
It was before then and she was here,
and then she was gone.
Now she's gone
to where they've put the dead.
They've put her with the dead people.
[Lizzie sobs]
She was asking just now for you.
But went...
5:17.
I told her that you love... [sobs]
I gave her your kiss goodbye.
[sobs softly]