Where do you keep these things? Bank?
We have our own treasury.
Wine cellar.
And a tunnel under the river.
My guess is they've turned
one of their cellars into a strong room.
Did you find someone, Arthur?
Stefan Radischevsky.
- And he speaks Russian?
- Yeah.
He works in the house for four weeks
and keeps his ears open. All right?
I have a bright future too.
Mapped out.
But you wanna try things first.
Michael...
Why does a pen pusher
who sits on his arse all day
want to fire a gun?
There is going to be a vacancy
in Shelby Company, Limited.
No revolvers. All legal.
Get me a meeting with someone
from the Soviet embassy...
He was in the war.
He was in a tunnel collapse.
He won medals...
Take care of him...
Here he is, Mr Shelby.
Thank you, nurse.
Tommy.
I need to speak to you about the priest.
- I know things about him.
- Hmm.
From when I was a...
From when I was a boy.
I will shoot him myself, Tommy.
Just teach me how to shoot.
It's easy, Michael.
Just point and pull the trigger.
He asked for me today, Mary.
Not his mother.
For the first time...
He missed you...
Where is he? Is he in the kitchen?
Yes, he's with the girls and johnny.
Oh.
Did you remember your medicine, sir?
Did you ever read the Bible, Mary?
Sometimes.
Do you ever read it out loud
while standing naked next to my bed?
'Cause when I take the morphine
the doctor gave me, that's what you do.
I'm wide awake,
but you are standing there
naked, plain as day,
reading from the Book of Leviticus.
Do you want to know what happens next?
No.
Neither do I.
That's why I poured the medicine away.
Go and get johnny, Mary.
That's it.
Without the firing pins,
the guns won't work.
And there are no replacements?
They don't make these any more.
These are the end of the line.
Yeah, we had the foreman
take out all the spares.
If we take the pins,
they'll never fire a shot.
And nobody will know
until they unload the bloody things
in Tbilisi.
Or until they are facing our guns
at Kutaisi.
Take them all out and give them to me.
Oh, come on, boys, no fucking about.
And I will tell the Soviet ambassador
that there is no longer a need
to blow up the train.
And I'll tell Tommy
you accept his plan.
You know,
some mornings I wake up,
I think I've died
and this is heaven, Tom.
I mean, the wives and kids
camped out by the valley, huh?
And not being moved on.
Sure, me, meself, I'm surrounded
by maids and food and booze.
See that line, there?
No.
It's the edge of heaven.
The border
between Birmingham and paradise.
And today, my friend,
you are going to step over that line,
back into the world.
You mean, you have something
for me to do, Tom.
Have you ever heard
of Hampton Court Palace, johnny?
No. I can't say I have.
You and three families of the Lees
are going to set up camp
100 yards from the gate of the palace.
You won't be moved on
because I have just bought the land.
You will be joined
by some old friends of mine,
who are going to open a hole
underneath your tents and caravans.
You see this blow to the head
you took, Tom...
And for allowing for the hole to be dug,
you will get £5,000,
which you will split
between the three Lee families.
I take a lot of this money is
to do with not asking questions, Tommy?
Dead right, johnny.
And when the hole is filled in again,
you can go back to paradise.
Mr Shelby,
your brothers are here.
And there is someone who described
himself as "the wandering Jew".
Will you take the Jewish gentleman
to the drawing room
and take my brothers to the kitchen
and give them tea and rum?
Yes, sir.
Good morning, Mr Solomons.
Yeah, it is.
Nice little place
you've got here, Thomas.
What is it?
A foreclosure of the gambling debt
from some poor, young lord
who you pumped full of opium
in one of your casinos,
or is that just tittle tattle?
Drink?
Nah, I don't touch it, mate.
Your housekeeper said
you're not allowed to drink.
Eh?
She said you are suffering from so many
ancient injuries from your sporting life
that your head is like
some sort of smashed vase
what has been stuck back together
by a horse.
Now.
Word in London is that you can be
found wandering
the streets of Birmingham,
stark naked, throwing away money.
You talk to dead people.
Also that you believe
that you are powerful enough
to summon up Jews
of a very particular standing,
up to the gentile wilderness
wherein you live
and order for them to do
your fucking bidding, mate.
Yet, still you came.
Yeah, well, you know...
I was passing, weren't I?
Do you know something, Alfie?
This morning, I tried to read the paper
and I realised
that the only consequence
of my terrible accident
is that I now need glasses.
Right...
All right, well.
I know a man who can make you
a pair of these.
Now, he's a magician, mate.
He's a magician.
So not only will you be able
to read your newspaper
but you will also be able
to see into the future.
Now I know this, right, because he
made this pair here for me.
So you don't have to worry
about telling me what this is all about
because I have already seen it.
You're fucking about with the Russians,
ain't you, you silly boy?
You've got two choices, Michael.
You fuck off to America with Arthur and
join the Apaches, or you marry the girl.
This isn't a joke.
Arthur, are you really going to live
with the Apaches?
- Has she told her father yet?
- No.
He'll fucking shoot you, man.
Are you sure the kid is yours?
I wish I hadn't told you.
Then think of marriage
as a beautiful road...
Flowers all the way down it.
- Is he joking?
- It's hard to tell these days.
Do you, er...
Do you love the woman?
Fucking what?
Well, then go and marry her
like the rest of us.
She doesn't want her family to know.
And she doesn't want to have the baby.
We know a woman.
- Shut up, John.
- Same woman who helped you out, twice.
- They weren't my women.
- Mmm-hmm.
That's why you had them fixed, Arthur.
Charlotte will want the best...
- She is the best.
- "The best."
Used to be a nurse.
Twenty minutes. Done.
And you don't have to go to in
or wait outside.
You go to the Garrison.
Drink whisky. Have a laugh.
Remember, John?
And then this kid walks in, no shoes on,
says, "it's done".
Second time we was in there.
Same kid, this time he is wearing
shiny new shoes.
- And he shouts, "It's done, Arthur."
- And what?
She bought new shoes
with the money I gave her.
It was for a good cause.
Arthur?
If you are going to get on
like this with the Apaches,
they'd fucking scalp you, boy.
Tommy said when that bell rings
we've to all go to the big room.
Come on. Tommy has a plan.
Arthur.
- Arthur.
- Arthur, come here.
Shalom.
Arthur, shalom.
- Alfie.
- Shalom...
Come here. Come on. Listen
I owe you a little something, don't I?
I do. Come on.
Sit down.
Come on, sit down here.
There you go.
Right.
Listen.
Arthur.
I want you to know, right,
that whatever happened
between us, yeah? Back then...
That was business.
It was just business. All right?
And I also want you to know
that I have made my apologies
via my own God
for abusing a very holy day
to get you clinked up and battered,
which I did.
And, now, I would also like to extend
my personal apologies unto you.
All right?
I hear that you have allowed Jesus
to come into your life.
Eh...
Oh, you heard then.
Yeah. That is beautiful.
That is wonderful.
That is lovely, isn't it?
That is lovely.
But I was wondering,
how does that work for you
on a day-to-day considering
your line of work, mate?
Your apology's accepted.
'Cause I hear
you're a right fucking nuisance with it.
Hello...
Listen, all I am saying is that,
every man, he craves certainty.
He craves the certainty, even if
that certainty of yours, right...
Well, I mean...
It's fucking fanciful mate, innit?
Eh?
I'm Old Testament.
Fucking hell. Look at that. Now, that...
That scares me more...
Yeah.
Congratulations, Tommy.
You now have the finished article
right here, don't you?
See, that man, right? He will murder
and maim for you with God on his side.
Yeah.
You don't want to let him go.
If we're gonna do business
with this fucker,
I demand to know why.
Right...
While I was in the hospital,
I formulated a plan.
And this is how it is going to work.
So the Russians cannot be trusted
to pay us.
We are going to take what is ours.
We need to see
what's in their treasury.
And that is why we need Mr Solomons.
Right, boys, just remember
they are fucking insane...
And dangerous...
And drunk on stuff we've never heard of.
And they're worse than us
for spirits and ghosts.
And, today, they're going to test us.
Fuck them.
The Russians all turned and ran.
The Cossacks didn't run, Arthur.
Mr Shelby. Welcome.
How is my car?
I think I am in love with it.
And I yours.
So we should keep what we love, yes?
Excuse the reception,
whenever we open the treasury,
the Cossacks are on guard...
In Russia,
men On the other side of the law
decorate their body in tattoos.
- Nice.
- Right...
Now, some of these tattoos
are proof of allegiance
to underground organisations,
which are the sworn enemies
of the royal household.
So it is customary
in Russian royal households
to check for such tattoos
before engaging a man in business.
And as we approach the allotted day
these ladies here
would like to make sure
that you are
not assassins or infiltrators, so...
No, we're all good.
So they'd like to check your skin.
They want to check our skin?
Yeah.
Now my body has already been checked,
although, at the time,
I wasn't sure that was the reason.
And now it's your turn.
Well then, boys.
Take your clothes off.
Fuck off.
No. No. No. No. No...
Obey.
Obey, Arthur.
No, I won't be obeying nobody.
Get out of my way.
Arthur. Come here...
Eh?
Come on, Arthur.
Shut up, John.
I will have a maid
gather the buttons and sew them back on.
Hmm.
All right. Fuck it.
There you go, ladies.
Made in fucking Birmingham.
All right, I think
we've seen enough, eh?
Tatiana.
Your face, Arthur, is a fucking picture.
Sometimes assassins hide
their allegiances behind their balls.
You pass the test, soldier.
With flying colours.
You see?
He wants to be a good man.
But there, now.
There.
Inside every man there is a devil...
The real diamonds, eh?
It is traditional to seal
the successful examination
with vodka and music...
Holy fuck, Tom. What was that?
Well done, boys. Eh?
Well done, Arthur.
Now you know what you have to do next.
All right?
One last job.
Make contact and play nice.
Give me five minutes.
I brought Michael because, as
chief accountant, he has to be witness.
Ada, can I use your phone?
Michael.
Business first.
Michael, stop looking at your watch.
Ada, whilst you are reading this,
can I go and use your phone?
Who's the lucky girl, Michael?
Her name is Charlotte
and Michael cannot breathe
if he does not talk to her
every two hours
Ada, please...
Phone's in the hall.
Dial nought for the line.
Thank you.
And keep it quick, I pay the bill.
I will.
Not for long.
Think about it, Pol.
Together, we can take control.
With two of us in the company,
we can straighten things out.
What about the politics?
You and me, fighting together
and winning, that is politics.
That is a new kind of politics.
It's just this way, I get paid
and Karl gets a nice Christmas.
Good.
Welcome to the bourgeoisie.
My name is Smith.
My girlfriend is pregnant.
And, er...
We'd like you to help us.
We need to fix a date...
Welcome to Shelby Company, Limited.
Shelby Company, Limited.
Limited and unarmed.
Michael, would you like to welcome Ada,
our new head of property
and acquisitions.
Congratulations.
Where do I sign?
Ada, have you got, erm, whisky?
Yeah, Tommy.
I've already told him.
He's becoming too like his cousin.
I thought that was the idea.
Yeah, Tommy but with a bit more
fucking charm and class.
Yeah.
That'll help.
Yep.
Where am I sleeping, Ada?
- Michael...
- In the room next to Karl's...
Michael...
Good night!
Oh, heartbroken, poor love.
So how shall we celebrate?
Well, with Michael in bed, I thought
I might, erm, go for a little drive.
Drive?
Where are you going to drive?
Polly?
Things have begun to develop
with the man
who is painting my portrait.
Polly?
It's when you stand there in the dress,
you just find yourself talking
about every little thing.
And have you...
- No.
- Hmm?
Not yet.
But he called me two nights ago
to say that the portrait was finished
and I said I'd go there in the morning.
But he said no.
He wanted me there tonight.
Ada, you don't breathe
a fucking word of this to the boys...
- Okay, but is he nice to you?
- No, no. I mean it, Ada.
Is he rich?
His friends write the papers, Ada.
Tommy would try and close him down.
So go.
He's like a tiny bird pecking at you.
And I think he's given up on me.
So bloody go.
Why should the boys have all the fun?
More vodka.
Wait there.
You're doing good, Stefan.
It's a fucking madhouse.
Yeah, I know.
The prince wants me to suck his cock.
And how much do you need to say yes?
That's on top of the day rate
for the arse slaps.
When am I out of here?
Soon.
So what you got?
The strong room is not guarded at night,
but they said they will kill
the three brothers in the "uglya dvor".
Coal yard.
The duke was talking about using a sword
but the woman, she was talking about
using machine guns.
It's a fucking madhouse, John.
We're doing up your pub in Nechells.
It looks a treat.
Keep your fucking head up,
Peaky boy, eh?
Fucking madhouse, man.
We are almost there.
This way.
This treasury was built
200 years ago
to protect the king's jewels
in case of French invasion.
We are now underneath
the River Thames.
Your jeweller.
I don't think they trust me, Tommy.
Mr Solomons is the only jeweller
I trust in London.
Yes. "Trust". Yes.
Might have to add that
on the old invoice.
Thank you. Thank you.
As we agreed, your jeweller
will now select items
to a total value of £70,000.
When you have selected
your chosen items,
they will be put into a box and stored.
When you have fulfilled
your part of the deal,
the box will be delivered to you.
May I just start, right, by saying
that I may choose to stay here
and just starve to death
and choke on sapphires
and never go back
to the fucking world again.
Yeah, well, there is a good reason
for that, you know, little man.
Because my shop, all right,
is just above a rum house.
- So...
- You speak Russian?
I do, yeah. I do.
'Cause of me mum.
Yeah, my mother.
You people, all right?
You hunted my mum
with dogs through the snow.
Yeah.
But today, right,
is for forgiveness, innit?
For selection.
So... Now... Hello!
Right, I think it is fair to say,
yeah, £1,500?
Fifteen hundred.
Mmm, yeah,
I will give you £1,800.
I know the current
market value. Eighteen it is.
That's very gracious of you.
Right then. How about...
Let's have a look at this.
This is a nice little bit
you got there, innit?
Oh, but that was a gift
from Tsar Nicholas.
I ain't asking you though, am I?
I ain't asking you.
All right. I come here to do business,
offer my professional services.
If you keep interrupting me,
I won't be able to focus.
Do you understand?
Mr Romanov, let me remind you
we were told to come here
and choose what we like
and now we have chosen.
Tsar Nicholas gave you that.
I will give you four.
Five, with the royal provenance.
Done.
All right, Rumplestiltskin,
let's go over here
and have a look what's in these boxes.
Two...
That is much nicer, 10.
And that there,
that was definitely a five.
- You keeping schtum?
- Yes, I am.
Yeah, another five.
- Seven!
- Six...
Let's call it six, eh?
Beauty. Look at that.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- That is splendid.
- Splendid, yes.
- Beautiful. Is it not?
- It is.
- It is a work of art.
- You recognise this work, do you?
- Immediately.
I'm guessing, right, that all the bad
ideas around here, they're you.
Right, they are you, aren't they, hmm?
How do you mean?
Yeah. Er, Tommy, see this, right?
It's got paste in it.
That's paste.
Let me tell you something, son.
Somebody comes into my shop
with some paste like this...
Usually, what I make them do, right...
Is fucking swallow it.
Eh? What game are you playing?
- Eh?
- Mr Solomons...
Shall we, er...
- Shall we clean it up?
- Be careful.
Eh?
Hmm?
Yeah.
Yeah. Right, what have we got?
Thirty seven thousand, six hundred.
Mmm.
Oh, well...
Do you have any eggs? Excuse me.
I am simply asking...
Fabergé is not part of the deal.
We would not offer you Fabergé eggs...
My jeweller here,
he advises me to insist on Fabergé.
It's a deal-breaker, Tommy.
Oh.
I brought that from Crimea myself.
Fucking hell...
With the provenance of that being laid
by such a delicate beauty,
that does indeed bring us
the entire selection to £70,000.
Here.
Good man.
And now, Mr Shelby,
you will join your brothers
and Mr Solomons will take his leave.
I demand absolute honesty.
- Oh, sorry, can I?
- I insist.
There.
A woman of style and substance.
I am a student of silence.
Is this a good silence or a bad silence?
It's good.
- It's very good.
- No. It's still wet.
I know it isn't saying much
in the grand scheme of things
but this is the best work
I've ever done.
I'll miss Sundays.
There will be more Sundays.
Sorry.
Sorry, can you not do that, please?
- Can you just not do that, please?
- I am sorry. I am sorry. I am sorry.
- It's all right. It's...
- I am sorry.
Vodka!
I sewed your buttons back on.
I wanted to see if I did a good job.
Yeah, you did.
You did a good job.
Sir?
No, I didn't.
My aunt
only employs the best whores.
How did you feel when I held him?
You were jealous.
You wanted to kill me.
Or him. No?
Why do you play games with people
when there is no benefit to you?
In Russia, because we were bored.
In England, because
we don't know how to stop.
At least they are silly games
and orgasms.
So let's fuck.
- Here?
- No.
Oh... In a darker place.
You still love her, don't you?
You want her?
Why would you fucking say that?
- Why would you fucking say it?
- Tommy...
- You love her.
- What are you fucking saying?
You want her? You want her?
Who the fuck are you, eh?
Huh?
What are you fucking saying?
You want her? Tonight?
Watch...
In the palace in Tbilisi,
there was a priest.
And he would put his hands here.
And with that strangulation,
there was also ecstasy.
It's called Khlysty.
A Siberian prayer.
You're almost hungover.
- You are almost dead.
- But in that moment...
Women who had lost men
in the war would lay down
and they would fuck the ghost.
You want her?
You want her, don't you?
You want her!
Now, you should drink this.
- It's holy water.
- Get the fuck away from me.
There.
I opened up another treasury for you.
You should call this painting...
Fuck Them All.
I will.
The parish...
The king.
The copper.
Yeah, the copper in particular.
Do you want to hear the
wildest story of them all?
Yes.
I killed a policeman.
In cold blood.
With a gun.
Really?
She did it.
I tell you what.
I tell you what, I swear at one point...
At one point, I looked down
at the top of her head
and I thought she was going to
pull me cock off in her hand
and fucking throw it out of the window.
Oh, she sucked me dry, I swear to God.
Like fucking spud water at the end...
We've had worse nights...
You're quiet, Arthur, eh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Fuck off.
- How was your night, brother?
- You got all your buttons back, eh?
- Yeah, all right.
Yeah, what's God going to
say about it, Arthur, eh?
Fuck off, both of ya.
He tells Linda everything.
Every single thing.
Yeah, well, we'll see...
We're going to miss you when
you're gone now, Arthur.
Just drive the fucking car.
Private Letso reporting
for duty, Sergeant Major.
At ease, Private.
Good to see you.
Seven left. Out of 50.
Should I get them tea?
Get 'em beer.
They used to run on it
like cars on petrol.
Give them the black country stuff.
It's in the barrel with the tack.
They're going to fucking clean me out.
Whatever they take,
they'll put back.
Good men.
John, Arthur.
You remember these boys.
Well, if it ain't the Tipton
Fucking Clay Kickers, eh?
- Clay Kickers.
- Come here, you.
- How are ya? Good to see ya.
- How are ya?
- Nice.
- Good to see ya.
And this is William Letso.
From the South African
Native Labour Corps.
Sent to Flanders from the
Bloemfontein diamond mines.
And the best tunneller I ever met.
So, there's three cellars
underneath the house.
Wine, kitchen and septic.
There's a tunnel here that runs
from the house underneath the river
to an underground strong room.
Now, this used to be
the palace treasury.
The tunnel runs directly west
and it's separated from
the house by three iron doors
with locks we can't open.
We need our tunnel to run from here
and hit the strong room, direct.
Primrose Hill 23. Ada Thorne.
Ada?
Is Michael still there?
Right, would you tell him
that I have taken the car?
He can take the train.
And try and find out why
he's been so bloody sour lately.
You shouldn't go looking through
other people's private things.
He's my son.
The bullet was mine.
I never got a chance to fire it.
And the gypsy rules
say it must be passed on...
It's not about rules, Pol.
It's about he asked me.
It's about he told me
why he wanted to do it.
Now, if I tell you,
I can't take the knowledge back.
Better off without it.
So this is when
he was with the parish...
Better off without it, Pol.
This is when he was with the Fathers.
This is when he was in
the care of the Holy Fathers.
Michael wants it
so you don't know...
- That priest...
- That priest
who was there when he was taken in.
And who is still walking
the fucking Earth.
Fuck...
He asked me, Pol...
And I said yes.
And I said,
"You put a bullet
in that fucker's brains."
"By order of the Peaky Blinders."
No.
Not my son.
He'll still be as
dead if Arthur does it.
And part of him will always stay dead.
- I swear to God...
- In whose house it took place...
If my son pulls the trigger,
I will bring this whole fucking
organisation down around your ears.