[siren wailing]
["The Mercy Seat" playing]
♪ I began to warm and chill ♪
♪ To objects and their fields ♪ ♪ A ragged cup, a twisted mop ♪
♪ The face of Jesus in my soup ♪
♪ Those sinister dinner deals ♪
♪ The meal trolley's wicked wheels ♪
♪ And the mercy seat is waiting ♪
♪ And I think my head is burning ♪
♪ And in a way I'm yearning ♪
♪ To be done with all this
Weighing up of truth ♪
♪ An eye for an eye
And a tooth for a tooth ♪
♪ And anyway I told the truth ♪
♪ And I'm not afraid to die ♪
♪ And the mercy seat is burning ♪
♪ And I think my head is glowing ♪
♪ And in a way I'm hoping ♪
♪ To be done with all this
Weighing up of truth ♪
♪ An eye for an eye
And a tooth for a tooth ♪
♪ And anyway I told the truth ♪
♪ And I'm afraid I told a lie ♪
[Polly screaming] Please,
can we get some help here? Please!
It's all right Michael.
It's all right Michael, I'm here.
Don't leave us now, just keep
prepared around, keep breathing.
[indistinct chatter]
No, no, I don't want fucking
kids in here, I want soldiers.
I don't want fucking kids
who joined just for the sport.
Go on, go.
I want men who've served in here.
-All right, Poll.
-[Polly sobbing]
[nurse] Mrs. Gray, please.
[Polly sobbing] Don't go, don't go...
[doctor] He's in good hands.
[Tommy] Polly? Pol? Pol?
Go fuck those bastards responsible!
All right, let them do their job,
all right?
Let them do their job, I'll get soldiers.
I'll be back. I'll be back.
[door opens]
[Tommy] Is it him?
[Arthur] Yeah.
On his own doorstep.
His own fucking doorstep.
[Tommy] Right, get out. And you, out.
[Arthur screaming] What the fuck?
[door closes behind]
[Arthur] Poor John.
Fucking gone.
In the bleak midwinter.
We promised, Arthur. [Arthur] I can't.
In Hull we promised.
-[Arthur] Can't look at him.
-Come here brother.
Come here. Come on, come here.
[Arthur] Oh, my!
Now say it.
Say it, brother.
In the bleak midwinter.
[door opens]
[Esme shouting] You cunt.
Look what have you done.
What have you done?
Look at what you've done.
Come here, come here.
[Tommy sighs]
Leave me with him.
You've spoken to him, now it's my turn.
Arthur?
No peace for either of you, ever.
Our stuff will stay with me.
Taking the children on the road...
to be with decent people.
They'll never know
the cursed side of this family.
We're done with them, John.
[footsteps leaving]
[Tommy sighs]
[man knocking at door]
Tommy, they're gathered.
[footsteps leaving]
[footsteps approaching]
John is dead.
Esme's gone on the road with the Lees.
She's taken the kids.
Michael is badly wounded,
they say it's 60/40 in his favor.
There's no number, there's no percentages.
So the hand, the hand
beneath him stops him falling.
Spoke to someone...
my son will live.
Michael and John were shot
because we killed someone...
Vincenzo Changretta.
[Tommy] His son Luca
has come to take revenge.
Men from New York
and Sicily here in Birmingham.
These men will not leave our city
until our whole family is dead.
That's how it works, an eye for an eye.
-It's called vendetta.
-[Arthur] Yeah, well...
The bullet's been written...
It says Luca.
When the time comes... and it will come...
Me as the oldest brother...
will put this bullet
into his fucking head.
There's been some bad blood between us.
[Polly scoffing]
[Arthur] Polly, please?
Until this business is
settled we stay together.
We stay here...
Small Heath, Bordesley,
Hay Mills down to Greet.
We know every face,
every man is a soldier in this army.
These men are professionals
and they're good at what they do,
so we're gonna need more than we have.
I sent a message to Aberama Gold.
No. No, Tom.
I'll get you 50 Lee boys. Good men, Tom.
I don't need good men Johnny,
for this I need bad men.
[Dogs] Tommy, his
people are fucking savages.
You know, heathens, Tom.
[Dogs] They don't
even let them in the fair,
so they come and steel our horses.
You know, stealing from their own, Tom.
So this is the plan, Thomas?
This is the plan?