Tommy?
[Tommy] Morning, Mrs. Ross.
Have a seat.
Thank you for seeing me, Mr. Shelby.
I know how busy you are.
How can I help you?
Well, you see tomorrow
would have been my son’s...
Twenty-first birthday.
Had he lived.
And I’m having a bit of a thing. Just...
Sandwiches and beer
and looking at old photos.
And as a gesture,
I thought I would invite your brother.
Arthur.
[Tommy] A gesture of what Mrs. Ross?
Not exactly forgiving us.
But something like that.
And also it’s a way of saying thank you
to the Shelby family for helping
me and my children get by
since the death of my Edward.
[Tommy] That’s very kind of you.
That’s very kind. I will let Arthur know.
It will be at my house at midday.
He should come at midday.
Your house midday tomorrow, all right?
One of us will be there.
It ought to be Arthur.
Goodbye, Mrs. Ross.
[footsteps receding]
["Snake Oil" playing]
♪ Yay ♪
♪ You keep it slow ♪
♪ Yay-yay ♪
♪ You keep it low ♪
♪ You cast a spell that keeps me wired ♪
♪ Keeps me red, keeps me on fire ♪
♪ So why do you take me down
Down to nothing ♪
♪ Always out cold
Never been higher ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[Tommy] All right.
At midday today,
Arthur will be here. 47 Artillery Square. Like a goat, sign up for
the fucking saga, eh, Arthur?
Yeah, right.
Dear Lord, forgive me.
But vengeance is forthcoming...
And long overdue. [Tommy] Right.
There are two ways into Artillery Square.
One here, on the towpath.
and here, Navigation Street.
Finn, take a rifle.
You’ll be here, Finn.
Covering the towpath.
Most likely they will
come down Navigation Street.
Johnny and Isiah will set up here
as hawkers selling salted pork.
When you get the signal from me,
they can open fire.
From you, right?
Yeah, I’ll be here
in the window overlooking.
You still know what end
the bullets come out of, Tom?
-[all chuckle]
-He knows.
These men are coming for my brother.
We’re leaving him to be unarmed
and unprotected.
So this is my fucking business.
Arthur, let's go.
[Arthur] Look alive, soldier.
[door opens]
Just put them on the table.
[dog barking in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[lighter clicks]
[vendor] Buy yourselves...
Big and raw, ribs, cheek and tongue...
Ribs, tongue, and cheek! Ah!
[vendor continues chattering]
[knock on door]
Mr. Shelby.
I’m glad you could come.
[Arthur] Er...
Thank you for the invitation.
So...
I don't allow firearms in the house.
It’s a good thing I’m not carrying
a firearm then ain’t it, Mrs. Ross?
Do you mind if I check?
No.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Would you like some tea
while we wait, Mr. Shelby?
What are we waiting for?
The other guests.
[teapot clattering]
[vendor speaking indistinctly]
[whistles]
[guns clicking]
[car door shuts]
-[opens faucet]
-[water flowing]
So where are these other guests?
[closes faucet]
They will be here very soon.
But in the meantime,
there are some things I want to say.
Before they get here.
By all means.
I’ve heard stories that you have...
Welcomed Jesus into your life?
I have indeed.
At the beseeching of your wife,
who they say is a good woman.
She is my shining light.
Though her mother by all accounts was not.
Do you think your repentance
will mean you are forgiven of your sins?
We both know that...
Forgiveness...
Is out of my hands.
I mean for murdering my son.
That was a sporting accident.
Because I have not yet found it
in my heart to forgive you.
I don't think I ever will.
Then...
Why have you invited me here today?
Hmm?
[Mrs. Ross] Off you go now.
Why am I here, Mrs. Ross?
Why did you invite me here today?
[man 1] Too late to back out now.
[man 2] Here you go, mate.
Last day of freedom, mate.
[man 3] He scrubs up well, doesn't he?
[man laughs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Tommy] Now, Johnny, fire!
Move!
[gunshots]
It’s a fucking decoy!
Bring the car around, now!
What are you doing?
[both grunting]
[gunshot]
Oh, shit.
Arthur!
Arthur,
they’re not here for you.
It must be Michael.
-You fucking bitch!
-[clattering]
You set me up, eh?
You set me up...
Or no?
[whimpers]
Arthur, you need to
get to the hospital now.
-[grunts]
-[whimpers loudly]
[growls]
If your faith is real...
I’ve got all the kids.
[glass shatters]
If you’re here in one hour,
I swear to God...
I will cover you in tar
and fucking feathers.
C’mon, Finn, let’s go.
[crying]
[grunting]
[door shuts and locks]
Uh, uh, uh.
Where I’m from,
a hat on the bed...
Unlucky.
My family...
is near Pinkstone.
Maybe...
Maybe that’s what happened.
Last time my men
were sent for you, you got lucky.
Now...
Your luck’s run out.
[softly] It's over.
[breathing heavily]
[gun clicks]
[gun clicking]
And tell your mother...
We have a deal.
[footsteps receding]
[cocks gun]
Come here.
Michael? What happened, eh? What happened?
They heard you, they heard you coming.
The gun misfired.
They ran away.
Johnny!
You came just in time.
You all right? You all right?
I’m fine. Fine.
[Michael breathing heavily]
[door opens]
[Tommy] Oi!
Get out.
[indistinct chatter]
It's 1-8-3-3-3.
Charlie?
Listen, Molly Gold
will be calling in four minutes.
Tell them the Italians are around south. A Rolls Royce. Maybe two. Black.
Tell them to expect
a full complement of men.
We inflicted no casualties.
I said we inflicted no fucking casualties.
[exhales]
-[Luca speaking Italian]
-[driver speaking Italian]
There seems to be an
obstruction, Mr. Changretta...
There's been an accident.
Well, why don't you
move it out of the way?
[policeman] What?
I said why don't you clear it
so that we can get past?
What’s that accent?
We’re Americans.
We’re here on business.
Well, you’re gonna have to wait.
Jesus Christ.
We waited for you
fucking Yanks until 1918.
It will be clear in 20 minutes, all right?
Yeah, all right.
Thank you officer. Big fucking help.
[speaking Italian]
1918, what the fuck is he talking about?
[in English] Talking about the war.
Everything here is about the war.
[sighs]
C’mon, let’s go move it ourselves.
Fucking idiots.
What’s this? Whose wagon is that?
[policeman] They’re gypsies.
Tribe of fucking gypsies.
We can move it, all right?
I said it will be clear in 20 minutes.
Let’s go.
We’ll find another way out of here.
Go. Get us the fuck out of here.
[driver grunting]
Come on, fucking move.
Frankie, fucking move.
[gunfire]
Ahhh!
[car engine starts]
Put the guns down! Put the guns down!
[groans]
[Michael] He spared me.
He said, "Tell your mum
that we have a deal."
What deal?
It will just be me and you
going to Australia, Michael.
-Think about that.
-What deal, Mum?
What deal did you make
with Luca Changretta?
A deal to spare your life.
In return for what?
Men don't have the strategic intelligence
to conduct a war between families.
Men are less good at
keeping secrets out of their lives.
You agreed to give up Tommy?
To save my life?
You never forgave him, did you?
We’re out of our league.
No.
-We don't do that to our own.
-Think.
If it wasn't for me you’d be smoke
blowing out of a mortuary chimney.
Think about that.
Uh, two.
We killed two.
You also shot a copper.
Shot him in the arm with purpose.
There’s a copper on the floor,
the Stratford Constabulary
will swarm all over it.
The copper’s alive.
Got a description of the Italians.
The Italians will be forced underground.
We’re gypsies.
We’re already underground.
You yourself inflicted
no casualties this end so...
You know,
Mr. Shelby,
maybe you’ve been pushing
pieces of paper around too long.
Luca Changretta got away.
You let him get away.
When our paths cross
I won’t be so careless.
And when will your paths cross?
Soon.
[mellow guitar music playing]
If her majesty smells like paraffin,
it’s because my old lamp
is smoking for want of fuel.
Times are hard
in case you haven’t noticed.
I hope your insistence that I take
a boat rather than a cab from the station
wasn't purely for your own amusement.
No. For the avoidance of death and kidnap.
By boat, you get to see
the nicer parts of the city.
He got us here, now.
You'll be all right. This way.
Good morning, Lady Carleton.
I’m not a lady.
[door opens]
Too right you’re not.
[Tommy] Shoeing, stabling, feed,
two hours a day in the gallops.
Did you think of a name?
Yes. Dangerous.
"Dangerous", eh?
Oh, a horse called Dangerous won the
Epsom Derby in 1833, so I stole the name.
-I thought you’d approve.
-[lighter clicks]
You should visit her.
If I leave Small Heath, I'll be shot dead.
Anyway, I'm busy.
Well, the good news is
your horse is the
fastest filly that I have ever ridden.
These are her registration papers.
Ready for your signature.
So, is this why you came here?
All this way in person?
For my fucking signature?
You’ve lost your wife...
And now your brother, too.
I thought it would make you different.
But it doesn't seem to change you. Nothing seems to change you.
[door opens]
The end of year accounts
for the Gray Shelby Institute, Mr. Shelby.
I beg your pardon, madam.
Already signed off on those, Lizzie. What do you think of his shirt?
He’s having them made in London.
I’m not sure about them.
All right, Lizzie, thank you.
But, you know sometimes,
he sees something glamorous and expensive,
he just can’t resist it.
He’s so weak.
Actually,
speaking of the Gray Shelby Foundation,
I’d like to make a donation.
[clears throat]
I'll leave it blank.
You can decide how much, Mr. Shelby.
Then perhaps,
Lizzie?
You can pop to the bank
and pay it in for me?
That be all, Lizzie, thank you.
Drink?
No, thank you.
Did you pack an overnight bag?
No.
Pity.
Why?
Well, because 25 minutes ago,
the Birmingham branch
of the train drivers union
called a wildcat strike
in support of the coal miners.
No trains to London until tomorrow.
It wasn't in any of the papers.
It’s why they call it a wildcat.
No one knows.
Apart from you, of course.
Your city.
So where would I stay in your city?
I’ll be free at four.
I could meet you then.
Meet and do what?
I’ll pour you some gin...
And I’ll make myself...
From my father’s recipe.
"Distilled for the eradication
of seemingly incurable sadness".
I’m going to have that on the label.
I’ll book myself a room.
Already done. The Midland. Suite.
Stay there myself sometimes.
Sometimes it's where you stay.
But not tonight it would seem.
Well, since I’m stuck here
maybe I should try your gin.
4 o’clock then.
Where?
I'll find you.
What the fuck was that about, Lizzie? Eh?
Have a guess.
You know, I can’t even guess anymore.
I’ll be back at 4:00.
Why is she still here?
Something to do with
the coal miners, apparently.
[door opens]
[footsteps receding]
Oh, today’s your lucky day, sir.
I’ll give you 3 to 1 on Raging Robbers.
Come on, gents. Get your bets on.
[continues chattering]
[phone ringing]
Small Heath 5-5-2.
[Luca] Mrs. Gray.
I wanted to illustrate to you
that at any time
we can reach your son.
And we will kill your son...
If you do not deliver Tommy Shelby
as you promised. Huh?
You just tell us where and when
and we’ll do the rest.
[gasps]
Where is he?
Fucking.
Fucking what?
Fucking her.
Ten thousand pounds?
She left it blank
so I filled it in for her.
What’s Tommy’s diary looking like
for the rest of the week?
Oh, fuck Tommy and his cock and his gin.
And his stuck up whore.
I saved this.
Read my leaves, Pol?
You haven’t done my leaves in ages.
Haven’t done anyone’s leaves for ages.
Okay.
Pour.
Swirl the tea cup.
Think about the man you love.
Fuck him.
Think about your white wedding gown.
[exhales]
Now pour the tea back into the pot.
Okay?
I’ll read your tea leaves,
if you go and get Tommy’s diary.
[door opens]
See if Tommy’s got
a free afternoon in the next seven days?
Friday.
Now read my future
and make it fucking good.
Make sure he keeps it free.
Just read my leaves, Pol.
Already have.
[blows air]
Plain as day.
What are you doing?
Stop drinking whiskey. Switch to stout.
Why?
Make sure Tommy keeps that Friday free.
Tell him I have an appointment for him.
And then go and see a doctor
about that baby in your tea leaves.
[rock music playing]
[groans]
Next.
You’re not in the
fucking fairground now, son.
Get down and skip me 200
for taking the piss out of a fine fighter.
-He’s got a head on him that boy.
-[Aberama] And a fist.
So, what do you say, Mr. May?
He works hard, his game.
I need to work on his defense.
Right now his left hand
is just good for wanking.
You don't have to earn your money,
we’re paying you anyway, is he ready?
Is he even registered?
I’ve put him down as a welterweight.
Midlands division.
Amateur turning pro.
Just need your counter signature.
Like I’m going to say no to you boys.
Just tell us.
Is he ready?
[Mr. May] In 30 years,
I’ve never seen a war boy so ready.
[Bonnie exhales]
And that’s 200, Mr. May.
So, who am I fighting first, Mr. Shelby?
When you step in the ring, Bonnie,
who do you see across the canvas, eh?
I see myself.
Forty years old having done fuck all
except tramping the lines.
See my life wasted.
I won’t let it happen.
Me? I’m going to be a champion.
[speaking Romani]
When this business is done...
You’ll be champion of the world Gypsy boy.
[in English] First heard in Camden Town.
Boy’s name is Goliath.
[peppy music playing]
Said he’s at a meeting.
Yes. I was wondering
do you have any boots that I can borrow?
Why do you need boots?
Well, no one here will speak to me.
So, I thought I would
take a walk by the canal.
Is he really making gin?
He’s going mad
cooped up here is what he is.
Like a wasp in a beer glass.
Um...
You’ll look a bit funny in these I think.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Curly.
If you’re going to take a walk along
the canal, you’ll also need this.
Are you serious?
Italians north. Italians south.
He makes gin to take his mind off
being stuck inside a prison.
[gun clicking]
If you had any sense, Mrs. Carleton,
you would get out of here now.
Curly can sail you to Snowhill Station
hidden in the coal sacks.
I said I would wait.
The man you are waiting for doesn't exist.
[Curly stammers]
While you’re waiting
for the man who doesn't exist,
would you like to try some of his gin?
[music continues]
[Devlin] The strike has blocked
the Coventry Road.
Made all the men get off the buses.
Where were the police? They were busy.
Apparently there was a report of
armed men in the Small Heath area.
And there was a murder
at the Summer Lane Hospital.
And something happening
on the Stratford Road.
The strike has
threatened the men's families.
They said come the revolution,
their names would be on the list.
Like in Russia.
And the buses turned round?
Yes. They turned round.
Mr. Shelby.
Factories are shut. Mines are shut.
Coal's running out.
Did you ever consider the possibility
that the Communists might win?
And you and me,
traitors to our class,
will be put up against a wall and shot?
As a businessman,
I consider all possibilities.
But Mr. Devlin,
I’m not a traitor to my class.
Small Heath 5-5-1.
I’m just an extreme example
of what a working man can achieve.
Hello, Ada.
Yeah, it’s me.
I need your help.
[May singing]
[Tommy] Four o’clock.
[May] Is it?
What do you think?
Oh, nice. A little sweet.
I've heard not sweet enough.
Come and see.
[door opens]
[May] My God, Tommy.
What is this, a hobby?
No. Don't really have time for hobbies.
This is more of, uh...
More of a place where I try things out.
I decided if I’m going to be
stuck here in Small Heath,
might as well do something useful.
Less of a hobby,
more of a venture.
Since the start of
prohibition I’ve been sending
single malt, scotch whiskey
to Boston and Halifax, Nova Scotia
hidden in crates of car parts.
[chuckles]
But my supply lines
from Scotland have been unreliable.
There have been a lot of thefts.
And in this modern age,
American women drink
as much booze as the men.
And women apparently prefer gin.
[pours drink]
So with the help
of a friend of mine in Camden Town,
I set up my own source of supply.
Junipers, potatoes,
sugar and water,
all turned into U.S. dollars.
When we’re up and running,
we’ll produce over 200 gallons a week.
But before then...
I need to get my recipe right.
So tell me the truth?
-The truth?
-Mmm-hmm.
You’re unlike any man I have ever met.
And the gin?
Too sweet.
You said you booked a room?
No, I booked a suite.
Thank you.
If you book a taxi, I’ll go. You’re a businessman, Tommy, a good one.
-If only you could...
-If only I could what?
"If only you could change."
Go on, say it.
If only you could change the bad.
And the good is laying off
a thousand men, which I do
like a good businessman.
And I do it like that.
[snaps fingers]
And people go hungry.
And the bad,
the bad is fucking winning the horses
and a gun
and some fucking self-respect.
You fucking people.
You bite like your horse.
I don't trust taxis anymore.
Come with me.
[Arthur] There you go, brother.
Home sweet home.
Place for you to bring women back,
bring your mates,
play games, gamble, cards and
you keep an eye on our back yard.
[glass clatters]
Artillery Square.
Place is full of Communists.
The strikers.
Having a Shelby round here
will keep them in order.
Light the fucking fire.
Take some of the shit off the walls.
Curly will be over later
with some poison for the rats.
-[Finn] Arthur?
-Huh?
This morning...
I wouldn’t have
been able to pull that trigger.
I know I wouldn't.
They would have just walked past.
I’m not John.
-I know I’m not.
-All right.
You’re my brother.
I know you're not.
All right? In the end,
it’s God who pulls
that fucking trigger anyway.
We don't get to decide
who lives and who dies, Finn.
Not us.
You just have to...
Flick a switch...
In your head.
Charlie said it wasn't safe
to walk by the canal.
He's right.
[May] Italians north and south, he said.
[Tommy] No.
It’s mostly chancers, local kids,
trying to get famous.
Sweeney's boys.
Sheffield boys, Manchester, Glasgow.
They all know we’re on the ropes.
And that's not including the mafia.
Yep. Here’s your carriage.
You can catch the 7:15 train.
I thought there was a strike?
Who gave you that idea?
My God!
I know. The bad I can’t help.
I wanted you to stay.
And normally I get my own way.
Losing occasionally makes me worse.
Thank you, Curly.
She looks a picture in my boots,
doesn't she, Tom?
Walk her to the train, Curly.
Yeah.
[woman] Not a minute on the day.
Not a penny of the pay.
This talk of national austerity,
this talk of tightening our belts
must be met with resolute certainty.
We will not accept any goods and pay.
We will not accept working
longer hours for the same wage.
Shoulder to shoulder with the coal miners,
dock workers,
railway men and steel workers.
We will stand united
through the storm
to show they come into our city.
[workers cheering]
Goodnight. See you soon. Take care.
Jessie Eden?
Yes?
I’d like to buy you a drink.
No. I'm afraid the pubs around here don't
allow unaccompanied female drinkers.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
I know you from somewhere.
I’m Ada Thorn, formerly Shelby.
I have a settlement proposition
that my brother's too arrogant
and proud to offer you in person.
[indistinct chatter]
[chattering stops]
Sorry, ladies, we don't...
Don't what?
It’s all right. I’m sorry, I didn't...
"What are you drinking ladies?"
That’s what you’re supposed to say.
Yes. Sorry, uh, what are you drinking?
Beer. Pint.
And a whiskey on ice.
I’m afraid we don't have ice.
Next time make sure you have ice.
This pub’s come
to our attention for its lack of ice.
[men chattering]
[Ada] There is more than one way
to achieve equality.
Before you begin to congratulate yourself,
I’m not impressed with your
power to terrify people.
Hmm.
Whereas, I am impressed by your ability
to stand up in front
of an audience and speak.
I was never able to do it.
I’ve heard people talk about you.
You used to advocate armed revolution.
Shelby Company Limited is prepared to
offer parity for male and female workers
across all the factories in our ownership
and withdraw the pay cut for men.
In return for what?
In return for something very unusual
but very typical of my brother.
What does he want?
To sit down with you and talk.
If he withdraws his pay cut
we've no need to talk.
He wants to talk about
socialism and revolution.
Dear God, are you serious?
My brother’s a book maker,
book makers hedge their bets.
Sometimes long shots come in.
And because we emptied his buses today,
he thinks we are amongst
the runners and riders?
Beneath it all,
my brother’s a very rational man.
Beneath all what?
You mean beneath the beatings,
the cuttings, the shootings,
-the murders.
-Yeah, beneath all that.
Tell your brother that
when we take power all means of
production will be owned by the workers.
Essential industries will
be taken under state control.
Birmingham Town Hall
is a rather beautiful building
and we plan to preserve it.
What else does he need to know?
It's going to happen.
Aren’t you a bit sorry
you jumped ship too soon?
He wants to take you for dinner.
I really have nothing to wear.
You’d need to wear boots,
he’s suggesting dinner
in a scrap metal yard.
Said you would appreciate the sentiment.
If you don't show up,
the offer of parity is withdrawn.
This is not how
you conduct union business.
Well, we must all make personal sacrifices
for the good of the good old cause, right?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Alfie grunts]
Fucking hell it smells of
pig round here, don’t it?
Definitely not kosher.
Come to Small Heath
and you will go to hell
for fucking breathing.
Where is everyone?
[Alfie] Stretch your legs, Treacle.
Fuck me, it looks like
he’s grown since we’ve left London.
Like a mushroom, ain't he?
He grows in the dark.
Need a piss.
Do you? Yeah, well,
this place is a shit hole, yeah.
So, why don't you knock yourself out.
Where is everyone?
Ishmael, please,
will you hit the call of prayer?
[car honking]
Well, hit it.
Thank you. Thank you.
[car honking]
Morning, Alfie.
Yeah, it is. It is.
How come everyone is in fucking bed?
[Tommy] So this must be Goliath?
Right.
Let me introduce you to David.
This way, boys.
[Alfie] Assuming that David's out of bed.
[door opens]
Oh, the problem right between
rum and gin is that gin,
it leads to the melancholy.
Whereas rum incites violence
and also allows you to be
liberated from self-doubt.
Now I hear you’re probably more in need
of the old rum at the moment
rather than gin, mate.
-[bird wings fluttering]
-[bird squawks]
Oh, dear. Sorry,
you’ve got fucking starlings, mate.
-That shit will rot your pipework.
-[gun cocking]
These bastards only
understand one language.
It's all right, Alfie. No need.
It’s all right,
I’m going to get a kestrel.
I hear that you’ve got Italians, mate,
have you got a kestrel for them and all?
Yes. I’ll have a kestrel for them as well.
Well, everything is confirmed, innit?
No weakness behind the eyes.
Don't blink too much.
You smell of smoke and coal and horses.
Huh?
You are back where you belong, Tommy.
I know you don't touch it,
but you have a good nose.
Right, well, you’ve got to
ask yourself seriously though,
did I even want to piss and shit indoors
or was I actually born to
defecate in fields and the outhouses?
It’s a serious issue though, Tommy. Because, your people,
well, your class and my religion is quite
similar actually because you just cannot
wash it out, right, because
it come out of your mother’s tits.
Mmm.
No, the Americans want it sweeter.
What have you heard, Alfie?
I heard a cop got shot. Who shot him?
My kestrel.
Right, oh, upping the stakes, very good.
What of the Sicilians?
They’re still using Sabeeni
for vehicles and places to stay.
Oh. And reinforcements?
Ah, they’re Sicilians, aren’t they?
They don't trust nobody and fucked a goat
on the morning of their first pubic hair.
They’ve got traditions.
How many are here?
Eleven.
Enough to drop a man who
wrapped his balls in an OBE,
until they fell off.
Well, the real question is, Alfie,
which side are you playing for, eh?
[chuckles]
Fucking hell.
What kind of world is it to
bring up children where your own
mate can ask you that question, eh?
Well, the truth is, Tommy,
you’re going to be fucking dead soon
and then your starlings,
they will peck out
your blue eyes, won’t they?
And the jackdaws
will steal your gold and your medals
and pretty soon it will as if you
had never even fucking happened, mate.
Tommy, there are men approaching.
Yeah, let them pass.
All right, you tell Darby Sabeeni from me
that if the Italians win,
they are not planning on leaving.
And after me it will be him and then you.
Then the Titanic.
And the fucking mafia, Alfie.
They’ve come here,
can’t believe our coppers are unarmed.
They’re going to steal their liquor
and it’s against the law.
They’ve come here and
they like what they see.
They’re coming and they’re here to stay.
Mr. Shelby,
I’ve come to talk personal fight.
Your kestrel, huh?
Tommy, when a pikey
walks in with hair like that,
you’ve got to ask yourself,
"Have I made a mistake?"
-Who the fuck are you?
-Who the fuck am I?
Who the fuck is this?
I, my friend,
I am the uncle,
the protector and the promoter
of that fucking thing right there,
whose shadow nothing good
nor godly will ever fucking grow.
That there,
right, is the southern counties
welterweight champion.
He is of mixed religion
therefore he is godless.
He was adopted by Satan himself
before he was returned
out of fear of his awkwardness.
But he’s impossible to marry off
due to his lethal dimensions.
His mother, terrified,
just fucking abandoned him.
And there he is stood before you,
like the first of some
brand new fucking species.
Any man that you put before him, right,
would be like entering
a fucking threshing machine, mate.
Now, will you offer your son?
Name the day, Mr. Shelby.
[mellow music playing]
So, are you finished
for the weekend, Tommy?
Yeah. Your mother wants me
to go up to the foundation. Prize giving.
Just you? Just me.
Why?
No reason. All right.
No reason.
Bye, Michael.
Tommy? Yeah?
Have a good weekend.
["Stagger Lee" playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
♪ It was back in '32
When times were hard ♪
♪ He had a Colt .45 and a deck of cards ♪
♪ Stagger Lee ♪
♪ He wore rat-drawn shoes
And an old stetson hat ♪
♪ Had a '28 Ford
He had payments on that ♪
♪ Stagger Lee ♪
[car engine starts]
[cocks gun]
[music playing]
♪ On a gathering storm comes ♪
♪ A tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat with ♪