♪ Oh ♪
♪ Show ♪
♪ Tell me I'm the only one ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Show ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
Happy or sad, Tommy?
♪ Show ♪
♪ Tell me you're the one I can call ♪
♪ Even if you choke ♪
Mr Shelby.
My bullets ache
to get inside your tinker head.
♪ Up to our knees in Fenian blood ♪
♪ Surrender or you'll die ♪
♪ We are the Brigton Derry Billy Boys ♪
You know, it's a pity.
I was looking forward to killing you.
You're at the back of a long queue.
My white flag is a flag of truce.
Yours is more a flag of surrender.
Whatever you say, Mr McCavern.
Colour is the same,
the outcome is the same.
I believe we have friends in common.
We should postpone our war.
Your brother left me a hand grenade.
He sends his apologies.
You left me landmines.
For which I, too, apologise.
Then peace it is.
Your message said you wanted to
seal our truce with some business.
Since we're men of similar interests
and distribution networks,
I thought we might use
our temporary settlement
for our mutual benefit.
You stand in a yard full of scrap metal
and stolen goods
and you talk like a politician.
No. Nothing here is stolen, Mr McCavern.
Charlie simply finds things
before they're lost.
The nature of the deal
is explained in my proposal.
I've booked you a suite
at the Midland Hotel.
If you need anything in this city,
just mention my name.
So you want to impress me, Mr Shelby?
Isiah.
Also in the envelope is a cheque...
for £500. For your wife.
She can use it to buy a black dress,
rent a black horse with black feathers,
to pull a black carriage
with your body in it,
should you break the terms
of the white flag.
Now, please, enjoy the city
it's my honor to represent.
This week, I managed to get
to the people, York and Lincoln City.
I mean, they're the teams that will lose.
I got to the...
All right. Go on, go on. Take your time.
-Hmm?
I got to the goalkeepers.
They all said five pounds is enough. I...
I've written to the, um, people
at Tranmere Rovers
because the phone you put
into my house has stopped working.
-So I'm gonna need another one of those.
- Okay.
Once we've got that fixed, eh,
then we'll have all the names and numbers
of the first division referees.
-The first?
-Yeah!
Shit. Ah, shit.
Shit, shit, shit...
Billy. Come on. Come on, listen.
Listen to me.
Come on, now.
-No need for that. Hmm?
-Hmm. Yeah.
We need you to find out what they like.
You know, what gets them going.
'Cause a lot of them are comfortable.
A fiver's nothing to them.
We need you to find out
what they really like, Billy.
Yes.
See, 'cause we can offer them that.
Yeah, Shelby Company Limited.
We can offer them
all the lovely things people like.
Hmm?
We can also offer 'em protection
from the things they don't like.
You ever touch my family...
ever...
York...
-Hmm. Lincoln.
- Lincoln.
Hmm.
Tranmere Rovers.
Hmm?
Bye, Finn.
Goodbye, brother.
Shit.
It's all right, Mrs Conners,
you can carry on. It's just me brother.
So, tell me how it happened.
Uh, they were
sleeping downstairs,
and then my husband came home,
drunk from the Marquis
even though he'd just lost his job.
We don't have any money.
Anyway... he came to bed.
But downstairs, they must've
heard a noise. They woke up.
They started, uh, calling out.
They woke my husband up...
and when he's drunk,
you don't wake him up.
What happened then, Mrs Conners?
He, uh...
He...
He went downstairs.
He killed them.
Strangled them, all three of them.
And you've, um...
you've brought
their bodies here today with you?
Proof, Mr Shelby.
Their singing
was the only pretty thing in my life.
I don't care my husband beats me...
but not this.
Mrs Conners, we have your address.
We will speak to your husband.
My brother here
will go to the Bull Ring Market today
and buy you three new goldfinches
and have them delivered to your door.
With the same colours
and, you know, feathers.
The new ones
I will call Thomas, Arthur and Finn.
That'll make him pause
even when he's drunk.
Good day, Mr Shelby.
-You take care, Mrs Conners.
-Bye.
I don't know
how you do this, Tom.
I really don't.
You learn things, Arthur.
That woman has only two rooms downstairs.
Her husband has lost his job
and he beats her.
And yet the thing that brings her
to see her Member of Parliament
is songbirds.
Now, that's politics, Arthur.
It's not for me.
Anyway, look. Our list of losers.
How much
have we made on the football?
Ten grand this week.
Finn showing promise, Tom.
Maybe we should put him on the track.
Just a thought.
-Finn?
-Yeah?
Your lunchtime delivery.
Bring her in.
Tommy.
The next fellow wants to see both of ye.
-Do you know his face?
-No. He's Chinese.
Chinese, in our pub?
Tom.
All right.
Slowly, Micky. Let him in.
Three little birds, eh?
Tommy, Finn and Arthur.
Mr Thomas.
Mr Arthur.
My name is Brilliant Chang.
Brilliant Chang is dead.
Perhaps.
Sometimes, I wonder...
is this heaven?
Doesn't smell like heaven.
So I would say I have survived.
What happened to Maggie?
You don't like me?
I like everything.
I like fucking everything.
You should answer the phone, Mr Shelby.
Micky, bring that phone here, now.
-Hello?
- Arthur! Arthur!
I sent a woman with a gun
to your youngest brother's office.
It's all right, Finn.
Wait, wait.
What the fuck is going on?
Do you wanna die again, Chang? Hmm?
Good.
The guns are pointed.
Now we are all concentrating.
The moment is now pure.
Purity is not necessary.
Displays are not necessary.
They said, "Tommy Shelby.
That door will need some kicking down."
When you walked through that door,
it was open.
You don't need to do anything
to get my attention.
Now, what exactly do you want?
Do you have a match, Mr Shelby?
Anything happens to my brother, Chang...
you die.
If you die here today,
we'll bury you face-down with no hands.
You'll go straight to hell.
I don't care about rituals.
I am a rationalist, Mr Shelby.
Well, tell your friend on the phone
to put her gun down
and we can all have a talk.
Hold your fire, brother.
Hold your fire.
I'm all right.
She fired into the ceiling.
Finn's all right.
Finn's okay.
Give me the order. Hmm?
Give me the order, Tommy.
-Yes or no?
-At ease.
I said, at ease.
May I take something
from my pocket, Mr Shelby?
It is the purest opium
that has ever arrived in Europe.
No salt, no flour...
no lies.
Pure truth.
Came off a ship called the Capital...
out of Shanghai.
Docked at Poplar a week ago.
Stevedores were held at gunpoint.
Chinese unloaded the cargo
by the light of lanterns.
A foreman at the dock estimated there was
seven tons of the stuff.
I made a note at the time.
I spoke to that particular foreman,
and I worked out that
seven tons of pure opium crystals
would be worth...
approximately £1,190,000
on international markets.
The big crash, hmm?
Wall Street.
Now we all
keep our ears open for opportunities.
-What the fuck is going on?
- What are you doing?
-Bastard.
Finn, we are conducting
a piece of business.
She had a gun to my fucking head!
But your trousers are dry.
You didn't piss yourself.
He didn't piss himself, Arthur.
Well done, Finn.
You had a dispute with a lady
and you didn't piss yourself.
And Arthur here tells me
we should put you on the tracks.
It'll be a good day for you
after all, Finn.
-Give me that.
-Hey.
Always have your whores
searched at the door.
If I see that bitch on
the street, I'll fucking cut her, yeah?
Yeah, all right. Come on.
This is a gift, Mr Shelby.
Gesture of goodwill.
I'll throw it in the canal.
Canals are the idea.
Right, Chang?
♪ I'm the man, I'm the man, I'm the man ♪
♪ I'm the man, the evil man
Yeah, I'm the man ♪
♪ I'm the man, the one you hate
Don't you understand? ♪
♪ The evil man ♪
♪ I'm the man, I'm the man
I'm the man, yeah ♪
I'm sorry for calling the meeting here,
but the location is part of the deal.
What fucking deal?
How does it feel
to be barefoot in the mud again, Pol?
Makes me feel young.
What fucking deal?
Four boats,
four days, up the Grand Union
from Poplar to here.
Half the cargo is coal...
and underneath the coal...
pure opium crystal.
Opium?
I vote against it.
They can't use trucks
because the Chinese drivers
get stopped by the police.
They need to get it out of London
because all the warehouses
are being searched by Customs.
The seven tons is bound for San Francisco,
but the outward ship doesn't sail
for seven days from Liverpool.
They need somewhere safe to store it.
All we have to do is take it up the canal
and keep it here for a week.
We don't fuck with the Chinese
though, Tom. Dad always said it.
Ask yourself, would he turn down £250,000
to drive four boats up the canal
with no prospect of inspection?
My vote's against it, Tom.
Hmm? Mmm-mmm.
Polly... £250,000.
That's half of what
Michael lost in Chicago.
I will ask him
to take charge of this business.
Michael's position
will be reinstated in the company?
His period of quarantine will be over.
Think about it, brother.
Four boats sailing up the cut,
smelling of woodsmoke and bacon.
Which one of Charlie's Gypsy
didicoy friends do you trust, Tom, eh?
With a cargo worth a million pounds?
I've already made provision.
I'm needed at a meeting.
Let's vote.
Those in favour?
Mmm.
Motion carried.
Arthur, tell Charlie we need four boats,
four tons of coal before it gets dark.
They sail south tonight.
And don't forget to go to the Bull Ring
and get them three songbirds, Arthur.
Yes, Tommy.
Fuck!
What have you heard, Pol?
The man you cut went to the police.
But we dealt with it.
Was she with him?
If she was,
it would be your fault, Arthur.
But they say his face is so badly cut,
he's hard to look at.
So I would say not.
I would also say
it is time to give up on Linda.
Find someone else
who might be able to put your fires out.
But I can't, though, Pol.
I fucking can't!
And that's it.
That's it.
Whisky?
Thank you, no.
For reasons I can't divulge,
I need to keep Jimmy McCavern alive.
But I've already got
a time and a place for the killing.
You see...
a little alleyway by a shipyard canteen.
A girl called Karen who hates him,
who will give him up.
I have the sound of cranes
and winches to cover the gunshot.
I've got a Bentley to get me away.
The war with the Billy Boys is postponed.
We've made peace.
We're gonna do business together.
When that business is done,
he's all yours.
You can avenge the death of your son
in any way you see fit.
You mean when you say.
When you check
that little stopwatch you've got
that controls the turning of the Earth.
Yeah.
And then you will marry
and you will settle.
Marry? Marry who, Mr Shelby?
Just let me understand you.
Do you mean
that Polly is part of this deal?
Yeah.
Well, Holy Lord God.
Tommy Shelby OBE,
does your vanity have no limits?
I believe it's called
the ego these days.
I read books.
You sit in your throne
and you instruct Polly Gray,
who is of far richer blood than you,
as to when she can
and when she can't marry.
Oh, no, she instructs herself.
She has her own strategies.
And we are of the same blood.
She will marry you,
but only if you agree to postpone
any attack on McCavern
until this business is done.
So, she is some young Gypsy bride
that's yours to give away.
Young she is,
when she's barefoot on the cobbles.
What about a dowry, then, Mr Shelby?
If it's gonna be done in the old way,
well, you know,
you throw in a few coloured ponies or...
I'm having an event at me house.
You are invited.
Polly will be there.
There will be candles
and violins and dancing.
Polly wants you
to propose in the proper way,
and then she will give you
her terms of acceptance.
Inviting you for this purpose
was Polly's idea.
-You can't read?
-I don't read.
-It's Swan Lake.
-Ballet?
Yeah. Apparently, it's about love.
Polly says that for now,
love must defeat revenge.
"As a result of the greed and the excess
of a small number of bankers,
financiers and other feckless gamblers..."
Hear, hear.
"...this comprehensive document,
pleading for government intervention
in all areas of economic life,
represents not just socialism,
but a new breed...
of national socialism."
"And I believe... I believe
that the leaders of my own party
have been very foolish to reject it."
♪ Albert shows, no reprieve ♪
♪ And for each man and woman hung ♪
♪ The last hangman's morality sung ♪
How on earth did you get a ballet company
to come to your bloody house?
It's an independent dance company
dedicated to bringing ballet
to the people.
We share a philosophy.
I'm a patron.
I also gave them a lot of money.
Hmm.
And this date is your wife's birthday.
Yeah.
The party is for her.
And she likes ballet, your wife?
Why wouldn't she?
It's just... Well, you see,
I did some research into her.
Into her past.
If you want to buy her a gift...
she likes diamonds.
Now that we're going to be
conquering the world together,
we need to have no secrets.
We should know each other's weaknesses.
Your wife has led an interesting life.
It may even be possible
that as a younger man in Birmingham,
I came across her.
My friends and I would sometimes go
to nightclubs in the south of town.
Well, if you recognize her,
maybe you can talk about old times, eh?
Maybe,
if we have met before, your wife and I
could even renew our acquaintance.
I am invited to stay the night, yes?
I, too, have done some research,
Sir Oswald.
Yeah, I researched your wife
and your wife's younger sister,
and your wife's stepmother, Lady Curzon.
All of whom you are fucking.
If such things were to take place
on a narrow boat,
the church would get involved.
But...
it's not happening on a narrow boat.
No.
It's taking place in your apartment,
in your country house,
sometimes even in your office here
in the House of Commons.
So, no secrets. And yes.
Yes, you are invited to stay the night
with whichever member of your family
finds favour.
Now, if you don't mind,
I was about to leave.
I need to lock up me office.
Actually, I will come alone.
In society, you are judged
by your hospitality.
I will expect adventure.
Such rogues
we are, aren't we?
Sing like songbirds in the House.
And then afterwards,
relieve ourselves in the bodies
of whomever we choose.
Two men for whom forbidding is forbidden.
Should be quite a party.
You have to listen
to the voices that you hear.
Do what they tell you to do.
You don't even have to rub the lamp
any more to summon the genie.
It wasn't the blue stone, Tommy.
It was you.
Who is it?
It's Tommy's car outside. It's him.
I'll get it.
What's happened?
Nothing's happened. I'm all right.
-Come in.
Do you want a drink?
-No.
-No?
No. I have some information
for the intelligence officer.
Our conversations with Mosley.
He's planning to put forward
proposals on building works.
He, um...
He wants the communists
to consider his new party as fraternal,
which means his activities are now a part
of your official remit. Yeah?
Mr Shelby, it's 2:00 a.m.
You can make your report any time.
-Why don't you stay tonight?
-No.
I'll leave you two to...
Yes.
Good night.
Uh, I stood on a bridge tonight, Ada.
And I looked down...
and Grace was there.
But she was still alive.
Tom, have you still
been taking laudanum?
And the fucking name of the barge
was the January.
Our dad's boat.
The boat I was born on.
We've never gotten off it.
We've never gotten off it
and we never fucking will.
Dr Brooke said that you never arrived
-for your appointment, Tom.
-No.
There is nothing in his books
of any use to a man like me.
They talk about guilt. Eh?
Guilt. What fucking guilt?
-The black barge.
-No. No, that's not it.
That's not it.
He had it right.
Mosley had it right. He said,
"Forbidding is forbidden to us."
We can do anything.
Nothing can stop us.
But there is a part of me
that is unfamiliar to myself...
and I keep finding meself there.
And only the January can get me away.
At least try the doctors again, Tom.
Well, then at least throw away your opium.
It's that that causes the visions.
Just throw it away.
While it's there, it's a temptation.
-Hmm?
How much have you got left?
Seven tons.
-Seven tons?
-Yep.
I'd hate for it to run out, Ada.
Hey, do me a favour.
When that kid of yours arrives...
keep it away from me.
A fucking ballet?
He wants to impress somebody.
And I'm invited?
You and Gina.
Why?
Because he wants to give you the chance
to come back properly.
-Coal haulage?
-Yeah.
Tommy wants you to reopen those books
and become managing director.
So I've come back from Detroit
to become a coal man.
The first delivery is bound
for San Francisco.
But if it works,
Tommy thinks he can find
distribution for it here.
And this, um...
this coal.
-Is it snow white?
-No.
Golden brown.
Fuck.
This is your opportunity, Michael.
There is more money in this
than there is in all the other parts
of our business put together.
Tommy knows what opium does to people.
Tommy knows what whiskey does to people.
He got an OBE for selling it.
I'll speak to Gina.
You'll what?
I'll consult my wife.
Your father ran this business for a bit.
1901.
And he shipped coal, real coal. Just coal.
And his fingernails and his eyelids
and his ears were black with it.
And the merchants
would offer them one price
and then only pay half,
because they could.
And that was wrong, Michael.
Run your hands through it,
get it under your skin,
and then see if Gina
will let you lay a finger on her.
I think golden brown is more to her taste.
Especially when you tell her
how much money you're going to earn.
Now we're in business together,
I should ask,
which foot do you
kick the ball with, Mr Shelby?
I have no religion.
Some nights I wish I had.
He's kin?
Yep.
And the simple fellow?
He's a lot less simple
than you might at first think.
Do you trust them?
Right. So I take a boatload.
Well...
Ten sacks to start with,
so you can test the market.
Then we'll deal in boatloads.
Cash payment on loading.
Ten thousand pound.
Well, for that amount,
it will have to be a cheque.
Don't take cheques.
It'll be a cheque.
I will take a cheque if it's guaranteed
by our mutual friend
in London, Mr Mosley.
Well, who'd ever have thought
I'd be doing business
with fucking Gypsy Catholic scum?
Yeah, who'd have thought, eh, Charlie?
Who would have thought it?
Ah, but you're okay.
Yeah, I'm only okay
until I'm not okay.
And then I'm really not.
Delivery in seven days.
Cheque guaranteed.
Won't your Chinese friends
expect the seven tons that leaves London
to still be seven tons
when it reaches Liverpool?
You leave that to me, Mr McCavern.
Oh, you mean you're bold enough
to skim the Chinese?
You have some kind of death wish,
Mr Shelby?
An evening with a tribe of Gypsies.
When you've unpacked,
there should be a girl laid on for you.
Mr Shelby is a socialist
and believes in
equality of service for all classes.
According to the invitation...
there will be an interval at 9:00.
Say that you're feeling tired
and we'll leave.
Well... if you see a duke,
introduce me.
My God, at last.
-Something that you like about England.
Gina,
I've been made an offer...
to come back into the company.
Michael,
we agreed the baby will be born
in New York. Remember?
The job is haulage.
Supply. Transport.
Opium.
-Tommy has made contact--
-Tommy.
Tommy has made contact
with Chinese suppliers
who have plantations in the Afghan hills.
Pure grade.
We'll take delivery
and ship it all over Europe.
You mean heroin?
Yes.
And how much would you make?
Conservative estimate,
three shipments a year
from Shanghai, seven tons each.
Stand to make approximately
a million pounds. Per annum.
The company will make three.
We could go to New York
whenever we wanted.
On our own fucking plane.
-But we always have to come back, right?
-Yes.
For a million pounds a year, we do.
What happens if you get caught?
Tommy has friends.
If a ship gets stopped,
it'll be the Chinese who hang.
Think about it, Gina.
When we move into our house,
our room for entertaining
will be twice this size.
Will it, now?
Magazines say that
it's all straight lines and simplicity
in the 1930s.
Deco is dead.
We'll be able
to afford dukes and duchesses.
And maybe...
maybe a princess or two.
And the painting on the wall
will be of you.
If Tommy Shelby will be gone,
then it will be Michael Gray
arranging the ballet.
Where will Tommy be?
Where he wants to go to most.
Ah.
There.
A lord.
Actually, I think Mr Mosley's a baronet.
Where the fuck is Tommy, anyway?
Tommy.
My house. My wife.
Let them wait.
Sir Oswald.
Do I not get announced?
Mr Shelby asked me to tell you that
he's busy with the catering preparations
and will be joining you shortly.
In the meantime,
and while you are waiting,
we have opium, cocaine and brandy.
I don't use opium. Or cocaine.
And brandy is for after dinner,
not before.
I also have a list of options
for the end of the evening.
You will notice
that the maids wear name tags.
We hired them specially.
For those guests staying the night,
all things are available...
except the ballerinas.
And who, might I ask, are you?
I am a queen amongst the Romanies.
And I, too, am unavailable.
Lizzie... there's something
I didn't tell you about this evening.
Something about our guest.
Mosley.
It's possible that you've met him before.
Before when?
Before you became who you are.
Would you even remember him?
Will he remember you?
All I remember is
I drank too much champagne.
And I wasn't taking cash.
Lizzie.
It's a pile of bodies...
floating by.
Let 'em go, Lizzie.
Let 'em go.
So, that's why you brought me in here.
To lay your claim.
Yeah.
Well, it's a start, I suppose.
He lays a fucking hand on you,
he will be meat for Johnny Dogs.
You were indisposed
when I arrived.
In society, you greet a guest.
You don't leave them hanging...
looking around like a fucking dog.
Before we join the others,
I have some business.
I need a signature.
By the way, your brandy
before dinner thing amuses me,
but none of the maids are of interest.
And I despise the use of drugs.
Your strategies are very transparent.
I'm involved in a transaction
with Jimmy McCavern,
your acquaintance from the north.
I have no idea who you mean.
I don't trust him.
He wants to pay by cheque.
I need your signature
as a guarantor on the transaction,
should his cheque fail to be honoured.
The sum is £10,000.
And what is it he is buying from you?
Gin distillery. He's buying me old one.
I'm buying a new one.
Hmm.
So, not only is the truce holding,
but you two are actually doing business.
Yeah. But I still don't trust his cheques.
If I sign a cheque guarantee for this man,
it is proof of a connection
between me and him.
Something you could later use against me.
Why would I
want to move against you?
You're curious about my weaknesses.
And you have learned it's not cocaine...
not maids.
But now you will learn my weakness...
is a tendency to trust people.
Do you have a pen?
Mr Shelby.
I know you had no classical education,
but I've just realised
you are the perfect balance
between the gods Dionysus and Apollo.
Irrational frenzy
controlled by reason and self-reflection.
Do you know
the work of Friedrich Nietzsche?
-No.
-Freud?
Yes.
Ah.
There.
Your guarantee of trust.
Now, perhaps you could introduce me
to your wonderful wife.
So, did you know?
What?
Oh, that tonight's special guest
might have fucked you
when you were a nightclub hostess?
Yeah.
Lizzie, if we were to
strike from our guest list
-every man in Birmingham who you--
-Fuck.
-Yes or no?
-Fucking yes. Shit.
Sir Oswald, this is my wife, Elizabeth.
Lizzie, Sir Oswald Mosley.
Since we all appear to know,
and since knowledge is permission,
I'm sure, Mr Shelby,
in the spirit of our honest relationship,
you won't mind me saying,
it was a bottle of champagne
and an evening well spent.
Actually, it was an evening wasted.
For the champagne and brandy
you bought me.
As I recall, it was the booze that
put you to sleep a little prematurely.
Ladies and gentlemen...
the dance is about to begin.
Mr Mosley,
a toast, if I may.
To the end of our deal.
And the beginning of something more.
Happy birthday, Lizzie.
This way.
Polly Gray, Gypsy queen...
will you marry me,
a poor commoner who loves you?
Let's fuck
before the swan dies.
I heard there was a family occasion.
Look, I'm sorry, Linda.
That animal inside me,
it comes out and I can't stop it.
Fuck, Linda.
Without you, I...
Come inside, please.
His name was Frederick.
All we ever did was talk, Arthur.
He just listened.
And now he has no face.
He's as ugly on the outside
as you are on the inside.
May you Peaky Blinders all rot...
in fucking hell.
Arthur.
♪ On a gathering storm
Comes a tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat
With a red right hand ♪
♪ A shadow is cast wherever he stands ♪