ESME: A daughter lost.
A son found. He is yours.
- Evadne Barwell?
- (RAPID GUNFIRE)
(SCREAMING)
NELSON: Since you have proven
your commitment,
Boston is now officially open
for the importation
of your merchandise.
Jack says just a few more weeks
and you'll be free.
Stories about you
come up the canal.
Once you walked fine alone,
- now you need a stick.
- (THUD)
TOMMY:
You stay clean for two weeks,
I'll write Linda
another letter.
HOLFORD: Have you recently
suffered seizures?
It is tuberculoma.
I am afraid it is inoperable.
Mr Shelby.
I only gave opium
to your brother
because he give me big trouble.
He attacked my wife.
(TICKING)
I'd like a pot of green tea,
please.
(CLEARS THROAT)
It's taken me ten years
to build this business.
Business will be safe,
if you do what I say.
How much opium do you have
in your cellar?
Five pounds.
Bring it to me.
Four minutes,
against the clock.
As a Member of Parliament...
..for this constituency...
...it is my duty
to take responsibility
for the welfare...
- Mr Shelby!
- ...of my constituents.
The clock is still ticking.
The consumption of opium
is very prejudicial to health.
Women give it to their children
so they can leave them untended
while they work
in the factories.
Men lose their jobs
when they become addicted.
From now on, you will sell
only cigarettes, cake and tea.
If I hear that you're selling
opium again, time will indeed
run out very quickly for you.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand, I will stop.
Mr Shelby,
the clock is still ticking.
(TRANSLATION FROM MANDARIN)
Please tell...
...your suppliers
and your customers...
...that from now on...
...there will be no more opium
in Small Heath or in Bordesley.
Thank you for the tea.
- (GASPS)
- (SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
- You can let them through now.
- Yes, sir, Mr Shelby.
You tell the pub
and cafe owners
in Montague Street...
...if there's any further trade
in powder,
there will be no more
Montague Street.
I'll have it demolished
and replaced by apartments,
by order of the Birmingham
Urban District Council.
Sorry I'm late,
they closed Montague Street.
There's a gas explosion or...
Right, well, it would be nice
if just one thing
could happen in Birmingham
that wasn't our fault.
I've gathered you all here
today because there is news,
and it's of interest
to the whole family.
First of all,
I'd like to welcome
Finn's new wife, Mary,
- to the family.
- (GRUNTS)
Right, well, I'm very glad
that I dragged myself
out of bed for this.
There is...
...one more item of business.
- Johnny.
- Tom.
Come on, come on.
Hurry up.
Everyone...
...this here is Erasmus.
Nobody calls me that.
They call him Duke.
(EXHALES) 20 years ago,
at Appleby Horse Fair...
...I met a girl.
We shared the shade
of a hazel tree.
Nine months later,
this lad was born.
This is my son.
His mother died on the road.
Up until now,
never tried to find him.
But I'm trying to look at life
in a different way.
A child is a precious thing.
So I'm bringing him...
Into the fucking family
with a snap of his fingers.
No, I am bringing him
into the fold.
He'll have to earn membership
of the family.
For the moment, welcome, son.
You have a seat. Go on.
Sit down here.
There are some mistakes
I've made...
...that I can never address...
...and some I can.
Some wounds I can try to heal.
And new wounds you can open up.
Anyway...
...that's the business
of the day.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- Is it too early for whiskey?
There you go.
Shelby breakfast for you, son.
I don't drink.
And I'm not a Shelby,
all right? I'm a Duke.
(CHUCKLES) You're a fucking
Shelby, all right.
Don't worry about that.
Mm, I think we'll need Curly
and a strong rope
to break this one in, Tom.
Arthur, open up the shop,
put the kid here
on the blackboard,
writing up the odds.
I can't write.
Put the kid on the blackboard,
wiping off the chalk.
Go on, son.
Come on, then.
Lizzie...
...come on.
My father was
the Duke of the Saxon Shore.
My mother was a Romany queen.
Who told you that, your mum?
I don't allow people to talk
about my mother.
Good for you.
So let's get this right, then.
You can't read,
you can't fucking write.
Nothing wrong with that.
What can you do, eh?
I can tell the time.
Tell the time.
Here, he can tell the time.
Ain't that clever?!
It's a lot more
than what you can fucking do.
What did you just say to me?
What time is it, Mr Shelby?
That's what I can do.
You little bastard.
(CHUCKLES) Here, keep it.
Stop you from being late
in the future.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
Is there forgiveness
in your heart
for Arthur Shelby?
No.
But there may be forgiveness
from God.
And you will do God's work?
God is interested in you
as well, Tommy.
And God will be with you
on your journey,
every step of the way.
He may not need to take
many steps.
So, tell me this, Linda...
...is God interested in me...
...or in my money?
I believe you run a foundation,
and that your foundation has
many missions across the world,
but in these times
of financial crisis,
funding is hard to come by,
so perhaps...
...your God's plan
is a practical one.
Perhaps, He would like me
to make a donation
to your foundation
and, in return,
He would like you
to help my brother on his road
to redemption.
Now, I know that in a place
of worship such as this,
you would never ask how much.
So I will tell you plainly.
I will write your foundation
a cheque for £10,000...
Praise the Lord.
...if you agree to look kindly
on Arthur and to help him.
I need to look after everyone
in the family.
Do we have a deal?
Your money will be spent
to do good around the world...
...and a mission will be named
after you.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
But I'm only agreeing
to help him...
...not sleep with him.
No.
No, I imagine the negotiation
for that particular favour
would take a considerable
amount of time...
...and I have an appointment.
God bless.
(SHIP'S HORN BLARES)
Apologies for
the initial misunderstanding.
My brother dealt with it.
For the care you took.
Even though
I succumbed to temptation?
Part of the reason my brother
is back dealing with it
is down to you.
You spoke to him.
As a comrade.
The beating
is still owed to you.
Do you still do that kind
of work yourself,
Thomas Shelby, MP?
Mr Stagg, you see,
I can use men like you.
I have friends
that are in need of guns.
Soon, there will be a shipment
of Thompson sub-machine guns
coming here from Boston.
And I need you to unload
and store those weapons.
There will also be
ammunition...
...like this.
You have a good look.
And I need you
to take better care
of the guns and ammunition
than you did of the powder.
You understand?
Previously,
all of my import and export
went through Belfast docks.
Now we're dealing
with Boston...
...I'm considering shifting
my supply line to Liverpool.
You'll be a very rich man.
Don't you ever say thank you?
Thank you.
Is that why you do it,
Mr Shelby?
Is that why you keep
all this going?
To have people say thank you?
You could close all this down.
You could leave the sport
behind.
You could live like
an ordinary mortal man.
On your gravestone -
"an ordinary mortal man".
But, instead,
you still go round collecting
"please" and "thank you"
and "sorry"
and "forgive me, Mr Shelby".
That what it's all for?
You want to know?
You want to know
why I've carried on...
(EXHALES)...all these years?
It's so I can do this.
And then...
...do this.
Feel it?
I feel it.
Junk doesn't even come close.
Soon, Mr Stagg...
...when my last bit of business
is done...
...I will indeed...
...be an ordinary mortal man.
You have a good day.
Arthur, we've got a problem
with a referee.
He's not taking the money.
He's fucking religious
or something.
Jesus Christ.
With Tommy away, you're in
charge of gambling, Arthur,
what shall we do?
"And this they said to him,
"that they may have some charge
to bring against him."
Arthur, this referee,
he's threatening
to go to the police...
"Jesus...
"...bent down,
"and with one finger,
he wrote on the ground..."
Arthur... brother...
...people are laughing at you.
So I just phoned
our holy referee again.
He basically told me
to fuck off.
Not even basically, actually.
He literally just told me to...
- ...to fuck off.
- ARTHUR: Is that right?
So, do you know?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Do you know what he wrote
on the ground?
- Hmm?
- No.
- Do you know?
- You don't know, do you?
- No, I don't.
Billy, do you know
what he wrote on the ground?
- I...
- Hmm?
Do you know what Jesus wrote
on the ground?
He bent down,
and with one finger,
he wrote on the fucking ground.
Do you know?
Do you know what he wrote?
- Come on, Billy.
- No.
Arthur, what should we do?
Go and get me the referee.
Bring me the fucking referee.
I know she's here with us.
Always.
But still,
it's just you and me.
I thought it'd be good
if we were
in a different place.
I hate that house now.
I wish I could blow it up.
There was a time when we'd say
nothing afterwards
because we didn't have
to say anything.
Now we've got nothing left
to say.
There's business.
What business?
The American.
He's coming to Birmingham.
He's stopping over
on his way to Liverpool.
He's staying with us
tomorrow night.
Frances knows.
She's been making up a menu.
And then...
...we have to make a move.
Do you want to know
what that move is, Lizzie?
No.
I know enough.
Your book of regrets.
23, 24...
...52, 55.
The combination to the safe.
Regrets.
And I'm on there.
I'm on the list.
On the very top of the list.
Yep.
Yes, you are.
I regret marrying you, Lizzie.
Cos I've put you through
so much.
Put you through all of this.
Ruby.
Everything that is to come.
When you married me,
you married a man
and you married a curse.
You have shared my fate.
That is my regret.
But know this, Lizzie.
In this moment,
in this room...
...I love you.
You sound like
you're ticking a fucking box,
and I don't know
what's inside the box!
Never have you let me in...
...even though I know
the combination to the safe.
(EXHALES)
So this is him, is it?
The one who likes
to be fucking difficult, eh?
When I leave this place,
I'm going straight
to the police.
- You are?
- This man pointed a gun at me.
- Who, him there?
- Yeah.
Well, let's phone the police,
eh?
- Don't worry.
- (FINN CLEARS THROAT)
We'll have this sorted out
for you.
Hello?
Yes, get me the police.
Reports of a man
with a revolver on Watery Lane.
There you go.
And you ask for Inspector Moss.
Chief Superintendent Moss.
He's in charge of Watery Lane
and Bordesley Green.
That's right.
And you see this?
That's his betting credit
with us.
He makes a lot of money
from football matches...
...because we give him
the results before the match.
On Saturday afternoon,
you take this whistle,
and you blow.
You give a penalty
to Birmingham City
in the final minute.
The goalkeeper will let
the penalty go by him,
and Birmingham City will win
1-0.
All you got to do is...
(CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(SNORTS)
No.
I won't do it.
If the police won't listen,
I'll go to the newspapers.
I'm not afraid.
I was in France.
Phone Tommy, Arthur.
You shut up.
I'm not phoning fucking Tommy.
I am dealing with this, OK?
- I'm leaving.
- You're going fucking nowhere.
It's time one of us stood up
to you people.
It's not right
what's been happening.
I will not take money to cheat.
Fucking hell.
In France, I ran at the wire...
...and I was not afraid.
I am not afraid.
I won't do a bad thing.
I've seen too many bad things.
A beating will make
no difference.
I know that, cos I can see it
in your fucking eyes.
(SIGHS) Fuck him.
"In the bleak midwinter..."
Holy Mary, mother of God.
- Agh!
- Right, Billy Boy.
You've been in the family
long enough.
- No...
- Yeah.
It's time for you
- to get bloodied.
- Arthur, you can't.
BILLY: Arthur, please...
You've been with us
long enough.
Fuck, Arthur. Jesus Christ.
I can't be that man,
Arthur, please!
Either two men die today,
Billy... or one.
You fucking decide.
- Hate him, Billy. Hate him.
- (WHIMPERS) Please...
Try. You don't know him, Billy.
He's fucking laughing at you,
look.
Come on, hate him.
Look him in the eyes, man.
Look him in the eyes.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Look him in the eyes.
(CRIES) I'm sorry... sorry.
- (GASPS)
- (GARROTTE TIGHTENS)
(BILLY SCREAMS)
(BLOOD GURGLES)
Enough. Enough, enough, enough.
(BILLY SOBS)
It's all right. Billy, Billy,
come on, come on.
- (ARTHUR SHUSHES)
- (BILLY WHIMPERS)
It's all right. It's all right.
Look at you. Look...
Look at you, look.
Huh?
You're bloodied now, Billy.
You're bloodied now.
You're not going to heaven
no more.
They won't let you in.
Isiah,
you take him to the foundry.
You ask for Mr Patches,
all right?
You tell him we got some fuel
for the furnace.
(FOOTSTEPS IN DISTANCE)
(MELODIC WHISTLING)
(WHISTLING CONTINUES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
Who the fuck are you?
(RATTLES)
(ZIPPING)
(SCREAMS)
- I hear...
- Please.
...you're the informant
inside the Shelby organisation.
And who the fuck I am...
...is the man you now work for.
Please, please.
I have something
I need you to do,
and I want to impress
upon you...
- ...to impress...
- (GROANS)
...upon you the seriousness
of my intent.
Cos, you see, I used to do
this kind of thing
for a living.
And sometimes
I kind of miss it.
Just like Mr Shelby,
I miss the...
...the wave of electricity
you get under your scalp.
I miss the taste like metal
on the tip of your tongue.
I'm about to give you
an instruction.
You do as I say,
you stay a man.
Fail, and I will send people
to serve your balls to you
on a china plate.
I'll do what you say.
A decision's been taken.
My associates are going
to take care of Tommy Shelby,
and you are going to give us up
his brother, Arthur.
- Do you understand?
- (WIRE TIGHTENS)
Yes! Yes! Fucking yes! Please!
(PANTS RAPIDLY)
Only information leading
to the murder of Arthur Shelby
will save you
from an Italian death.
Cos it was the Italians
that taught me that
above God, above children,
above his wife
and above his mother...
...most of all,
a man loves his balls.
(WHIMPERS)
(PANTS RAPIDLY)
(SOBS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(KEYS JANGLE)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(EXHALES)
Hello, Arthur.
I think we should pray.
That's how we begin this.
You'd like to pray?
The prayer I've chosen
is the Act of Contrition,
Version 2.
So, you're Catholic now, Linda?
You're Catholic.
Quakers don't pray.
Bow your head, Arthur,
and close your eyes.
And recite the prayer.
You know it well
from when you were boy.
Oh, my mind's all dried up
with junk, though,
and shot full of fuck...
...shot full of holes.
Linda, please.
It's in there somewhere,
Arthur. It's like a song.
Yeah.
Somewhere.
Together, we'll find it.
Digging for the words
will help clean your soul.
I'll begin it.
Forgive me my sins, O, Lord,
forgive me my sins.
The sins of my youth.
The sins of my youth,
the sins of my age,
the sins of my soul.
The sins of my body.
The sins I know,
the sins I know not.
The sins I have concealed
for so long.
For so fu...
For so long.
Caught him stealing a car,
and he's got a stack of cash
from the betting shop.
Steal from who you want.
But don't steal from me.
Here you are.
Get a train
to wherever the fuck
you want to go. Get out.
- I don't ride trains.
- That a fact?
Well, Curly has
a two-wheeled wagon.
What am I, a tinker?
I need four wheels.
And a horse for the hills.
Which hills?
All of them.
All the hills of England.
(CHUCKLES)
Why do you want to leave?
I didn't take to that work
in the betting shop.
Well, you heard him, Charlie.
Get my dad's old four-wheeled
wagon and two strong ponies.
Right.
Curly! Get here.
Before you go,
do you want to know the truth
about yourself?
No. Who does?
Right, well,
I'm going to tell you.
That spring at Appleby Fair,
your mother stole
my watch and chain.
You're from a long line
of thieves.
The watch had the words
"Saxon Shore" carved in it.
Stole it meself from a drunk
when I was a kid.
I imagine she told you
your dad was the Duke
of the Saxon Shore. Well...
...I'm the Duke,
It was my watch.
I'm your father.
That's the truth.
When her dad found out,
he shot me in the chest
with a squirrel gun.
A scar and a stolen watch
and a story she made up.
That's all you need to know
about yourself
before you get on the road.
Esme tells me
the spirits favour you.
That the spirit is in you.
She tried to sell me like one
of those horses, didn't she?
How much did she pay for me?
I've no use for gold any more.
But if you are a horse,
you're in the right place.
Curly!
Curly, hurry up!
This boy has hills to climb.
I remember that watch.
Oh, yeah?
She used to wear it
over her heart.
We buried it with her.
Tom.
The old wagon's right
front wheel is fucked, Tom.
It's standing in the wet.
Put a new wheel on, Curly.
Yeah.
Fix wagons here.
Good families
come from the New Forest
to get their wagons fixed
and fresh horses
before the fairs.
Yeah. Yeah, I like it here.
I like it better than
that betting shop.
Why?
People.
People piss me off.
There are a lot of people
in that betting shop.
So far, here... What?
I've only counted two.
Mm-hm.
Charlie and Curly.
The rest is dogs and horses.
Curly's half horse himself.
Dogs are OK.
Horses are better than people,
mind you.
There's work here
for a man who knows horses.
Unknown.
I want to remain
completely unknown.
Well, you'd be
in the right place
for that as well.
No-one knows anyone here.
Hey, mister!
Save that wheel a minute.
Where would I stay?
Stables,
with the other stallions.
Now that Finn is married off,
plenty of girls round here.
Fathers are mostly unarmed.
I have a future for you, Duke.
You already have a son.
My business has two sides.
Light and dark.
I'll need someone for each.
And I'm dark, am I?
I've realised we don't get
to choose which one we are.
Dark knows dark.
And my affairs,
both light and dark...
...will need settling soon.
Curly!
Find a shovel for the Duke
of the Saxon Shore here.
Get him shovelling shit.
(SNORTS)
And put some petrol
in the boat.
I'm off to meet a lady
in Solihull.
Take a look at her.
Now imagine ten people
living on side.
Step on. Have a look inside.
I've had a response
from the Guinness Trust
about building
charitable housing
at two sites
along the canal network
between London,
Birmingham and Liverpool.
This lock here would be
the one of the sites.
I have the permission.
Just need the finance.
I know that you and your
husband, Bryan Guinness,
are estranged,
but I understand
you still have influence
in the Guinness family.
Your support might help them
make their decision.
Will you help me?
I've booked a suite in a hotel
a mile from here.
My chauffeur
will take us there.
You look quite the thing
dressed like that,
dressed like a working man.
They'll probably show you
to the coalhouse
to make your delivery.
Yep, they probably will.
Oswald has fucked your wife,
so my suggestion is
about balance and proportion.
It would be only fair.
Can I assume...
...I have your support?
This isn't about
charitable housing -
this is about changing
the world.
It's about a different kind
of trust.
Absolute trust.
We have important work
ahead of us.
It's much harder to lie
with your body
than with your words.
This, I have learnt.
Mostly,
I do whatever I want to do.
Sometimes,
I do things for the cause.
In this case, it's both.
Come.
In the interests
of absolute clarity,
that is simply
the English aristocracy's way
of shaking hands.
So...
...welcome.
POLLY: If you do this thing...
...the possibility of war,
you have to consider.
MICHAEL: It was the ambitions
and strategies of one man
that caused this.
POLLY: There will be a war
in this family,
and one of you will die.
We need to leave early
to catch the first train
to Liverpool, yes?
Yep.
So we eat early, finish early.
You changed the combination
of the safe.
Why?
Have you got new secrets?
With the new business
at hand...
...there are some things...
...that I cannot share.
What things?
What are those tablets?
Doctor gave them me.
Painkillers?
- Yeah.
- What pain?
Any pain that comes, Lizzie.
When you're ready, I want you
to tell me everything
that's going on.
It's like the clock's
stopped ticking
and I'm waiting
for the bomb to explode.
We're in that quiet minute.
Tommy?
That's where we live now.
When I know everything...
...I will tell you everything.
NELSON: Oh, no,
Gina's running wild, you see.
Harrods, dope, amphetamines,
lords and ladies,
you know, the whole
English aristocracy thing.
Fuck wine - whiskey.
Shelby, you having whiskey?
- I'll stay on wine.
- Fuck wine, more whiskey.
I'm celebrating.
Celebration, you know.
Getting off
this fucking island.
You see,
the thing with England,
the currency here,
it's not money.
Nah, you got bored of money
a long time ago.
Cos, you know,
anyone can have money,
you can fucking...
...you can fucking find money
in the mud.
You can forge money.
Mr Shelby, you can steal money,
am I right?
The currency here...
...it's blood.
And Mr Shelby knows that
better than all of them.
Blood here is like wine,
like the vintage wine
in that bottle.
It's the... It's the label,
it's the terroir,
it's the grape
that makes the wine.
Who fucking cares
about the glass around it?
And you, my friend,
you're an American.
You fucking... (BANGS TABLE)
...smash the glass,
you spill the blood
and you spend their currency
to get what you want.
Am I right?
When you come to America,
I will show you things.
You're going to America?
To Canada, Lizzie, to collect
payment for the shipment.
I need to do it myself.
And who will be going with you?
Michael will be there
to watch his back.
Another journey, Tommy?
$5 million, Mrs Shelby.
It's worth a little cruise,
don't you think?
You know whiskey does talk...
...Mr Nelson,
and sometimes whiskey is...
...very eloquent.
But $5 million, Mr Nelson...
...that is a legacy.
And when I come back,
I will know everything.
I see myself so clearly
in you, Thomas Shelby.
You are a man with a bright
and glittering future.
(DOOR OPENS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
FRANCES: Mr Shelby, there's
a car coming up the drive.
A Rolls-Royce.
Were you expecting more guests?
No.
Excuse me.
We were on our way
to my constituency in Smethwick
and I heard our American friend
was in Birmingham
and that he was coming here,
so we came
to say one last farewell.
Champagne.
We have much to celebrate.
It isn't that I wasn't sure
Mr Shelby would give you
an excellent send-off,
I just felt, since telegrams
and wires and letters
can so easily be intercepted,
we might confirm
all that we've achieved
during your visit
over champagne.
It is remarkable
how quickly our relationships
have developed.
So many triangles in this room.
Everyone except from Mr Nelson
is the point of a triangle.
How am I part of a triangle?
Mr Nelson,
you have all that you came for?
I have confirmation
that the future of Europe
is in the hands
of men like yourselves.
And that urgent conversations
between Washington, Rome,
and of course Berlin
can now begin.
A two-week visit that may have
changed the course of history.
We all got what we wanted.
Yes.
And I got what I have wanted
from the moment
I set eyes on it.
Elizabeth,
you are a very lucky woman...
...to have each day
what I have only sampled once.
(SCOFFS)
Forgive us, Mr Nelson,
that was a necessary bit
of housekeeping.
Thomas...
...we do so hate
to be indiscreet, but...
...we have told you
many times,
if you are to seek power
in these days
of shiny magazines
and society photographs,
sooner or later,
you will have to find a spouse
who's more suitable.
A woman with Lizzie's past
and personal history
really isn't suitable.
She doesn't deserve you,
Mr Shelby.
You know, the thing is,
Mosley...
...you're right.
You're right,
she doesn't deserve me.
She doesn't deserve what I am.
She doesn't deserve
what I will become.
What will you become?
Truth is, I belong here,
at this table,
with fuckers like you.
She doesn't.
For all I try to hide it...
(CHUCKLES)
...I'm just one of you.
Could there be a sadder ending,
eh?
I'm here on behalf
of your wife, Gina,
and Jack Nelson.
Mr Nelson's prepared
to get you out of here.
But first he needs an answer
to a question.
If the answer is yes...
...you'll be released.
If the answer is no...
...you'll stay.
I have consulted my mother.
Your mother's dead.
Nevertheless,
I have consulted her.
And yes.
When I'm released,
it is my intention
to kill Tommy Shelby.