Help.
Help!
My husband will kill me!
Please save me! My husband will kill me.
Please.
TWO MONTHS AGO
Breaking news!
First on Visphotak News!
In Haryana, the Hathinikund Barrage
on the Yamuna River
has collapsed due to heavy rains.
As a result, many crocodiles have entered
the low-lying areas of Agra,
along with the floodwaters.
Help me get down. My legs hurt. Come here.
-Hold me.
-This is Sharad Pathak,
bringing exclusively on Visphotak News!
Crocodiles have swarmed Agra!
Madam.
It's time for your insulin injection.
You're here?
So many tomatoes?
I got them for cheap, that's why--
-Looking nice, aren't I?
-I bought some for you.
Please manage this once.
I promise, after two days--
I'll help you out.
I filled in for you yesterday.
What?
She canceled the five-hour
bridal makeup appointment?
I could've serviced five clients
in that time!
Sorry, they fell.
No problem.
She booked Seema instead?
Rani's bridal makeup
lasts for a whole month!
Seema's brides start looking ghastly
even before the ceremony ends!
Next time she comes,
no way will I give her a discount!
She didn't even return
my lipstick last time!
In her hurry,
Rani has left her Molly and Polly behind.
Should I go and give them to her?
Sure.
One minute.
Let's go.
Rani ji!
Take me to Belanganj.
Rani ji! Your heads…
Rani ji!
Wait up.
Not fair.
I'll have to work overtime now.
Yes, but…
Rani ji!
Rani ji. Wait!
That's it. Please pull over.
Here you go.
Rani ji.
You forgot to take these.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Did you come all the way
to give these to me?
No.
I was coming here anyway…
QADER SHROUD STORE
For my patient.
You seem to care a lot
about your patients.
Yes.
Thank you.
-Rani ji.
-Yes?
-I…
-Rani, come here quick!
Yes.
I'll be back in two minutes.
-No problem.
-Two minutes. Okay?
Rani, I messed up!
Mrs. Sahay had asked for Dirty Blonde,
but I applied Slutty Red by mistake!
Let me see.
I told you not to start without me!
Hi, Mrs. Sahay.
-Rani?
-No! Don't take these off.
It'll brighten the color.
How are you?
-A cup of tea.
-Sure.
I'll add another layer.
Okay.
I hope you're not in a hurry.
Dirty Blonde is the best color.
It takes a little longer.
Wash it off in ten minutes.
Rani ji…
I was thinking…
Excuse me?
Will you come for a movie with me?
What?
Friday?
Six o'clock?
-Right.
-Okay.
Once there lived a damsel
And her crazy lover
It was a magical time and age
After they met one day
They started meeting everyday
Then they fell in love
It was a catastrophe
Where did you lose yourself
While listening to this story?
People are surprised
Because they are unfamiliar
With the path that love takes
I used to be familiar with those paths
Once there lived a damsel
And her crazy lover
It was a magical time and age
Once there lived a damsel
And her crazy lover
Rishu and I had done
some crazy things for love.
Rishu is now Ravi.
Now, here we are,
standing on opposite banks
of this river of love.
Between us stands
the Uttar Pradesh police.
And we're still trying to figure out
a way to be united forever.
If love doesn't push you
to the brink of insanity,
it's not true love.
Only the meek seek refuge
in passionless relationships.
Jaipur!
Watch your step! Over here, mister!
Guddu ji, here's the 25,000
that you asked for.
Good.
Your job will be done.
You'll be in Thailand in two months.
Two months?
Yes, it'll take two months.
I'll let you know the exact date.
You'll see that velocity
remains constant--
What's going on?
Pay attention here.
Yes, sir.
So the velocity of--
Note this down.
When will you give it, Ravi?
But I've already paid my rent.
When will you answer my questions?
What was that song…
All I need is a lover
For my passion
Poonam, after my wife--
Ravi, you've lost your wife,
not your life.
Anyway, I'm not talking
about the emotional kind of love.
I just…
want to have some fun.
Sorry.
I'm not feeling well today.
No problem.
You'll recover soon.
I'll be back then.
All I need is a lover
For my passion
Yes?
Uncle and Auntie are away
at the Agra Masala Convention.
Masala Convention?
Stop acting like an innocent rabbit.
My point is, there's no one at home.
So will you come over?
It seems difficult today.
Fine!
Come over with sweets on Rakshabandhan!
When will we get out of this place, Rishu?
How much longer?
Everything is set.
The agent has our passports ready.
It's just a matter of one month
and we'll be in Thailand making mad love.
Just make sure you're not ravished
by your admirers by then.
And what about your medical
compounder admirer?
It's not lust. The poor guy is in love.
He's a good man.
But your character is questionable.
Dinesh Pandit writes,
"Judge a lover not by his behavior,
but only by the depth of his feelings."
I want tickets for the 6:00 p.m. show.
How many?
All of them.
Rani…
Sorry! Careful!
Let me.
Move aside.
Streets of Agra turn deadly!
A crocodile was spotted outside
Aslam's tailoring shop.
I'm doing a root touchup now.
Keep it on for 30 minutes
and then wash it off.
Okay.
Abhimanyu?
At this hour?
More tomatoes?
They were being sold cheaply
outside the Royal Cinema.
Thought I'd bring you some.
Shit!
I'm sorry.
Abhimanyu, I'm so sorry!
It's okay, Rani ji.
I'm sure something important came up.
Wait. So sorry…
-Take this--
-Can we try again next Friday?
I'll be waiting.
Again?
Waiting is easy because I can do it alone.
It's the meeting I dread
because you'll also need to be there.
Right.
Don't laugh.
I'm feeling bad for him.
Rani ji, you've killed
so many of your lovers.
Even the bodies of some weren't found.
Don't be over-smart--
Thief!
Run!
Stop!
Oh no!
Yes?
Does Rani Kashyap live here?
I was told she lives here.
Yes, she does.
She's a good woman.
Poor thing is a widow.
She has no one.
She rents a room in my house.
We've found her purse.
I'll call her.
Rani!
Yes?
Coming.
So you've finally found
the purse-snatcher.
We meet again, Rani ji.
Destiny.
Even God must be waiting for justice.
Hasn't Dinesh Pandit
written something similar
in the novel Wrath of Kasauli?
I've read it.
It has a fantastic climax.
Hero pretended to be dead.
He cut off his hand
and kept it on the dead body
to save his lover.
Thank you.
I heard…
someone is looking for you.
Who?
The past.
Your past.
He has read Wrath of Kasauli, Rishu.
He said the climax was good
and that someone was looking for us.
He knows everything.
He has no evidence. Just a story.
He's just trying to scare you.
Told you to leave. Why are you back?
Were you missing me?
We met just this morning.
Did you forget already?
We spent so much time talking
this morning.
Just two Indians sitting
and exchanging stories.
The number you have called
is out of network coverage area.
To Husanpura.
Why have you parked here?
It stinks here.
My customers are complaining.
Please move the vehicle.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I already gave you the trash.
Leave!
I'm leaving.
"When our hearts will beat as one,
all the battles will be won."
Wait a minute! Wait…
These lines…
Are you a fan of Dinesh Pandit?
These lines?
Some crazy man wrote these
and paid me to stand here for an hour.
Is it something bad?
BATTLE OF THE HEARTS
"Even though I tried to stop myself
from talking to you,
I couldn't stay firm, my helplessness won.
Archana knew where her lover
would be waiting."
Mister, may I please make a call?
Sure.
-Rishu?
-Rani.
Rishu, are you okay?
I am fine.
Listen, I just met the agent,
we'll leave next week.
Rishu, the police are after me.
They're following me everywhere I go.
Listen to me, Rani.
It's your fear that's standing
between our freedom and getting jailed.
Inspector Kishore has no evidence.
If you get scared,
he'll find what he's looking for.
The police might call you in
for questioning.
Be brave.
Rishu.
Hello?
Rishu?
Hello.
Okay.
POLICE STATION, AGRA
Hurry up, you scoundrel!
Get in the car.
Naitik Verma.
Is he a lover?
Or a friend?
Why?
Because you speak to him for hours.
I thought he's my friend.
He said his name is Rahul.
One day, a woman called me
and said he's her husband.
Our friendship ended.
In this day and age, Inspector,
can we really claim to know anyone?
I'm sure you know
an acquaintance isn't always a friend.
I won't fall
for your stories anymore, madam.
Pandit writes…
There you go, quoting Pandit again.
I had to.
Because 30 years ago,
in a police station similar to this,
he was insulted and fired from his job.
Ever since, he has been taking revenge
through his stories.
The police are defeated at the end
of every story he writes.
Salute, sir.
Maybe not through his actions,
but through his writing,
he did take revenge.
Rumour has it, even after passing away,
Dinesh Pandit's novels
are still being published.
My name is Mrityunjay Paswan.
I don't think you've recognized me.
We're related.
Looks like you have a poor memory.
In detail,
I'm Rishu's mom's sister's husband's
sister's husband's…
brother.
That means…
I'm Neel's uncle.
To you, Neel was Rishu's distant cousin.
But he was very dear to me.
My dear nephew.
By the way…
I had danced a lot at your wedding
and enjoyed myself.
Inspector Kishore is my friend.
He asked me to lead this case.
So…
I will be asking the questions now.
Because it's personal.
So tell me,
this friend of yours, Naitik ji…
Rahul ji…
why does he call
a travel agent every week?
He probably likes to travel.
How would I know?
And what are you doing here
all alone in Agra?
Rani ji, isn't it strange?
It has been some time
since Rishu passed away.
You've broken ties with your family
and you haven't even remarried.
Is it a crime if a widow doesn't remarry?
Will you lodge an FIR
or arrest me straightaway?
-What are you trying to say?
-I'm saying that
Rishu is right here in Agra with you!
Otherwise, you couldn't have stayed here
without any friends or relatives!
Sorry.
I also mean to say…
I've known Rishu since he was in diapers.
He is far more cunning than he seems.
I'm a modern independent woman.
I'm capable of living alone.
Rani ji, in the department,
I'm known by many names.
But my favorite one is "Woodpecker".
Woodpecker.
Do you know why?
Because until a woodpecker manages
to peck a hole in a tree,
it doesn't stop.
Even the law doesn't interfere
in my cases.
Okay.
You may leave.
Rani ji.
When you meet Rishu, tell him
that Uncle Montu is here now.
The team that was following her.
Did they find anything?
Not yet.
But our force is spread out
all over Agra, sir.
Which are the places
the madam visits regularly?
Just her home and the beauty parlor,
all within a radius of two kilometers.
Then keep your force
within these two kilometers.
We'll find Rishu within a week.
Okay, sir.
Have you seen him?
POLICE STATION, BELANGANJ
Have you seen this man?
-Seen him?
-Sir…
Look properly.
You must have seen him somewhere.
-Seen him? Ask him.
-No, sir.
Don't know?
Done.
Please hear me out!
I'm innocent, sir.
-I have kids at home! I did nothing!
-Move.
That's ridiculous!
Your child told me,
"Mom doesn't help me with my studies.
She's always on her phone
watching her shows."
I'll talk to you later.
Have you seen this man?
I'll be back in two minutes.
Would you like some tea?
-No.
-Yes.
Three teaspoons of sugar.
Sure.
Have you heard about blood sugar?
Yes! So I only asked for three teaspoons.
Ravi?
The police are here.
They asked me if I'd seen this man.
I haven't, right?
I'll tell them.
Sorry, sir. I haven't seen him.
Aren't you getting the tea, madam?
Aren't you ashamed
of asking a handicapped girl
to make tea for you?
Get lost!
Get a warrant if you want tea next time.
Out!
Rani.
Rishu, no! Everyone is home.
-Listen to me--
-No, you listen.
There's a new officer at the station!
Uncle Montu. I know.
-I'll tell you inside.
-Montu?
Hold on.
Everything is over, Rani.
Everything.
Why?
He has arrested the travel agent.
All our money and effort
have gone down the drain.
The police even reached
the coaching center today.
Poonam is also suspicious of me.
I don't know what to do.
-Let's run away.
-What?
-Let us run away now.
-Rani.
I have known Uncle Montu since childhood.
If we run away,
he will get a kick out of it.
Then he will chase us down and kill us.
Uncle Montu? Neel?
What kind of…
These relatives of yours!
We don't have any option, Rani!
I'll surrender
and tell the police that you had nothing
to do with Neel's death.
Have you lost your mind?
Have you lost your mind completely?
Did we flee from Jwalapur and come here
only to surrender?
You've chopped your hand off
for us, Rishu!
Try to understand, Rani.
-Please.
-What brings you here?
Hold on.
Is Rani ji here?
Rani!
Rani.
I'll go to another city.
The police will soon track me down
and arrest me.
-Far from here.
-Quiet.
You're afraid Uncle Montu thinks
we're still together?
I have a better idea.
You trust me, don't you?
I thought you would keep me waiting
once again
and I'd have to go to your house
to meet you.
You won't have to wait any longer.
Will you marry me?
Excuse me?
Marriage straightaway?
What about love?
I don't have the courage to love again.
I waited for you for hours,
but you never noticed me.
Then why choose me?
A patient lover, who spends time on you,
is worthy of spending an entire life with…
And who knows
love…
might happen after marriage.
Or it might not.
Wow, Rani ji…
You offered me my dream world and then
destroyed it, in the same instant.
This is what love is, Abhimanyu.
It can revive us and also ruin us.
If I'd known love was this cruel,
I wouldn't have fallen in love.
But it's too late now.
"We shall meet, says the soothsayer.
As I recite your name like a prayer."
Don't do it, Rani.
I don't think this is a good plan.
If Rani and Rishu aren't together,
Uncle Montu will stop hounding us.
End of story.
Reminds me of something Pandit wrote.
"I'll agree to everything you say.
Just don't let a third person come
between us."
And look! A third person is here already!
We're going the wrong way in life, Rani.
But I hope it's the right way for love…
The wedding is in three days.
Will you come?
This deep bond between us
Always brings a smile when we meet!
I am so besotted by you
That my eyes fill with tears of joy
I will bear this pain for you
With a smile on my face
I am so besotted by you
That my eyes fill with tears of joy
Joy and sorrow are sides of the same coin
I hope these smiles don't lead to tears
I will bear this pain for you
With a smile on my face
What do you think?
Will Romeo come
to his Juliet's wedding?
I know Rishu very well.
This love will lead to his downfall.
And I'll be waiting, anyway, to nab him.
Joy and sorrow are sides of the same coin
I hope these smiles don t lead to tears
I feel smothered
Let me catch my breath, with a smile
Who can I bare my secrets to?
Close friends are hard to find
I will bear this pain for you
With a smile on my face
I am so besotted by you
That my eyes fill with tears of joy
Joy and sorrow are sides of the same coin
I hope these smiles don t lead to tears
I will bear this pain for you
With a smile on my face
Do you drink rum?
Excuse me?
Sometimes.
Do you have whisky?
When I used to watch you from afar,
I had so much to tell you.
But now that you're here,
I am tongue tied…
I'm under pressure to say something
to make you smile.
Do you know of Dinesh Pandit?
Before he met me,
Rishu didn't know of him either.
There you go, bringing up Rishu.
He is always here…
Fine.
Let the three of us play a game
of Snakes and Ladders.
Love happens between two people, Rani ji.
If there are three, they only end up
playing Snakes and Ladders.
Tell me something.
Didn't you feel bad
when I proposed a marriage of convenience?
Didn't you feel bad?
I mean, you must have wished
for something for yourself.
Love, a lover, affection, et cetera.
I was seven when I lost my parents.
The only family I had left
was my uncle, aunt, and their children.
They passed away when I was 20.
And all I was left with was
this house,
these windows, this roof,
and these walls.
I did have a job
that I had no interest in.
I was so lost
I even tried to end my life.
Then one day, you walked into the clinic…
in a sky-blue dupatta
and a pink kameez.
I had never seen such colors.
My world changed in that moment.
The colors were so vibrant
that the clinic, my house,
my neighborhood…
Everything turned pink.
The entire city!
Even the Taj Mahal I see from the rooftop.
That too…
I'm willing to play
Snakes and Ladders all my life
if that's what you want.
Let's go.
Your eyes and mine
Locked in a gaze
Your dreams and mine
Are so alike
I know not, nor do you
But this is the wonder of the divine
I wish I could express
What's going on within my heart
Is it love or an illusion
Wonders everyone
I wish I could express
What's going on within my heart
Who's there, Rani ji?
Pizza.
But I haven't ordered one.
My treat.
There.
You lose again!
Champion, my foot.
I'm focusing on winning
the real game, Rani ji.
The one called life.
With you.
I'll jump off the roof if you ask me to.
For you.
But I don't have the permission to love.
Says Surekha, in Dinesh Pandit's book.
Show me.
Read it carefully.
You might come across a page
where Surekha gets permission to love.
You stay up waiting for that page.
Meanwhile, I will go to bed.
Good night.
Yes.
I have a PhD in waiting after all.
Ravi…
I got a little carried away.
You see,
when I see cops, my heart goes…
thump-thump…
Why do you keep fighting it, Ravi?
You don't have a hand
and I don't have a leg.
We could make a good match.
Perfect.
Do you know how I lost my leg?
I jumped off the second floor
for my last boyfriend.
"I gave him my heart and mine he got…
But he butchered it
without a second thought."
Ever since we've gotten married,
all we do is play Snakes and Ladders.
The board game!
And here you are, kissing Poonam!
She's blackmailing me
and follows me around. What do I do?
And I pushed her away
before anything happened. You saw it!
I told you to stay away from…
From that horny woman!
You must have led her on!
Seriously?
Seriously, is that how much you trust me?
Didn't I trust you
when you said you'd marry Abhimanyu?
Correct.
It's all my fault.
Making a plan was my fault.
Making poor Abhimanyu
a scapegoat was my fault.
Uncle Montu was my fault too, isn't it?
Rani, I said I'll surrender,
but you didn't agree.
He will keep hounding us.
To hell with you and your Uncle Montu!
At first, we weren't in love.
When love happened, the timing was wrong.
When the timing was right,
we couldn't reunite
because we'd become illegal!
Finally, when things worked out
and we were about to leave,
your Uncle Montu lands up!
Rishu, our timing will never be right.
Our love is doomed.
Last time we thought our love was doomed,
I cut off my hand!
But I didn't let go of your hand!
This time around,
I'll cut off someone's head if I need to.
Your love has already made me a criminal.
What's the matter, Rani ji?
You've started without me.
Are you crying?
Is everything okay?
What?
L-S-D. LSD
Are you on drugs, Rani ji?
Love, Sex, Ditching. LSD.
It's spreading in Agra city.
This LSD has gone rampant everywhere.
Look,
I want love.
Poonam wants sex.
And Abhimanyu is getting betrayed.
It's so unfair on him.
I shouldn't have married him.
I am wrong.
Uncle Montu is wrong.
Uncle Montu is troubling me so much.
Take me away, please.
Take me away from here, Rishu!
Take me away…
Call Rishu.
I don't want to preach.
Both of you should leave Agra
as soon as possible.
I'll help you.
Passport, police, I'll manage everything.
How?
I'm a medical compounder.
Judges, cops…
Everyone drops their pants for me.
Because everyone falls sick.
And it's me who gives them injections…
I'll manage everything
But why are you doing this, Abhimanyu?
My parents, my childhood, my youth…
I couldn't save any of them.
Let me at least save the person I love.
So what if it isn't with me,
Rani ji will be happy with someone else.
But if I manage to get a place
in her heart, I can hope…
if you get tired of Rishu some day…
you'll consider me.
It'll take her several lifetimes
to get tired of me.
But I've heard you're very patient.
Don't get too cocky, Rishu.
The one you love is with you now
while I have been wronged.
Fate is a wicked thing.
Without it favoring you,
even a love spanning
lifetimes may never unite.
And if it does, even two strangers
who meet on a train
can become companions
in the journey of life.
Lines of fate are etched
on our hands, my friend.
And I've chopped off my own hand for love.
SAHANI CLINIC
Wait.
So you'll leave for Thailand in two days.
You can stay here until then.
This is your bed.
The bathroom is over there.
No one will come here today
as it's Sunday.
I'll come in through the back door too.
I'll lock this door from the outside.
Thank you.
Can I come with you?
It's risky.
Abhimanyu…
Sorry.
I mean it.
If you really mean it,
will you watch a movie with me
one last time?
Okay.
Let me go deliver lunch to your husband.
And then I'll take my wife for a movie.
Poonam?
How did you know I was here?
I followed you.
You were planning to resign and disappear?
I followed you to the--
Give me a month, Poonam.
I'll come and meet you after that.
And if you don't, then…
Poonam, I said…
Peas pulao.
It's your favorite, Rani ji said.
Yes. Come inside.
Flowers…
Did a woman come here?
Yes. Poonam was here.
Who is Poonam?
She was my landlady.
Why was she here?
Well, Abhimanyu…
She follows me around.
She even blackmails me.
-Blackmail?
-Yes.
Why? Does she want money?
She must want something.
Me.
-You?
-Yes.
Good heavens!
What's her full name?
Why do you want to know?
I might send her a friend request.
Don't worry, she won't tell anyone.
She says she loves me.
Love!
Poonam wants you.
And you want Rani ji.
I want Rani ji too.
While Rani ji wants you.
So many of us are spending
our youth chasing someone.
Why don't you simplify this
and take a U-turn towards Poonam?
And then Rani ji and I will be together.
No more chasing.
I am kidding.
Don't take this seriously.
Enjoy your meal. I'll leave now.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
What's wrong?
Someone else was here as well.
Not really.
Does Rani ji know you're a liar?
The movie plan was better, no?
There are crocodiles in this area.
Maybe they're under
the railway bridge, no?
The cops have taped that area.
So I guess this place is safe.
Isn't it?
Rani ji, do you think the tapes
will stop the crocodiles?
The river is their home.
If someone enters your home
and your life after telling lies,…
of course they won't sit quietly.
I've told Lallan so many times
to take his shoes off outside.
This soil is from the jungles of Rajgir.
The place I got that snake from.
The one whose bite killed
my entire family.
Lallan must have told you about it.
You know, Rani ji,
my uncle betrayed my dad
and stole his business.
That's why I killed his entire family.
I can't stand betrayal.
I have a soft heart.
I loved you with all my heart.
But even you…
I kept the snake hungry for four days.
So when the hungry and angry snake bites,
it would bite deeper.
And death is certain.
If you control a man or an animal by their
habits and tendencies…
you can make them do whatever you want.
Abhimanyu!
Abhimanyu.
Abhimanyu,
Don't you dare hurt Rani!
Tell me one last truth, Rani ji.
Did you, even for once,
think we could be together?
Yes.
I did.
At another time
and place maybe.
If Rishu wasn't in my life,
we could have been together.
Okay then.
You, me and my pink Taj Mahal
is enough for me.
Life is good. The person I love
is in love with someone else.
But it's okay, Rani ji.
This is expected.
If there isn't a trail
of Rani ji's dead lovers lying around,
I doubt if anyone is truly in love
in this city.
You know what, Rani ji?
We have another thing in common.
Dinesh Pandit's stories.
You played out the story
of Wrath in Kasauli in your life.
And I…
The Revenge of the Cobra.
Both our lives are heavily
influenced by Pandit's writings.
You've met your match.
We'll have to wait and see
who's Pandit's bigger fan?
The day you walked into the clinic,
I spotted Pandit's book
in your beautiful hands.
Then your sky-blue dupatta.
Then your pink kameez…
Then your eyes…
By the time I saw your lips,
I was already in love.
Help.
Help!
My husband will kill me!
Please save me! My husband will kill me.
Please.
Sir, I've been telling them
my husband will kill me.
Abhimanyu is very dangerous.
He has murdered his entire family, sir,
after reading Dinesh Pandit's novels.
Sir, he's a psycho!
He will kill me!
Looks like you're stuck between
the devil and the deep blue sea.
Sir, are you even listening to me?
If you don't arrest him now, then…
Then what?
Then he'll kill…
You're safe in here, chatting with me.
Who else would he kill?
Rishu.
Who?
Hello, Elder Brother.
I told you
I would nab Neel's murderer
and throw him at your feet.
I'll call you back in a while.
Great.
I must say…
Romeo is fire.
Madam's spark, even better.
Oh! They're dynamite together!
Amazing.
Go and find madam's…
husbands!
Okay, sir.
What, sir?
Go!
Chiraunji…
DINESH PANDIT
Interesting.
Pandit makes an entry as well.
Okay, sir.
Hello?
Sir, there has been a development.
Remember your lover's face?
Come take a last look.
Come on!
The second patrol party
will reach in ten minutes. Over.
To whom do these belong, Rani ji?
SAHANI CLINIC
Abhimanyu.
Rani Kashyap…
we have reasonable suspicion on you
for the double murder of Poonam Prajapati
and Abhimanyu Bharadwaj.
I didn't kill them.
Damn, I'll have to question her again.
Where is Rishu Saxena?
Come on.
I can't find one husband,
but she lands a bunch of them!
And she's killing them off one by one.
Meena ji.
According to the law,
how long can we keep her in custody?
We have to produce her in front
of the Magistrate within 24 hours.
Meena ji,
you were leaving for court with Rani ji
when you twisted your ankle.
When you sat in the car,
you had a flat tire.
It was quite late by the time
you reached the court.
And the court had closed by then.
The next day is a Sunday.
So when will you take her to court next?
On Monday, sir.
-Then Monday it is.
-Sir.
Wait.
Take Mr. Disciplinarian with you.
Make sure to use him freely.
Sir.
You're always talking big, aren't you?
But today,
all you'll do is scream.
Pandit writes,
"You can drown us, burn us,
or bury us a mile…
but in the face of oppression,
bestow upon us lovers the strength
to bear it all with a smile."
Know this and also tell Uncle Montu.
If Rishu finds out
you've dared to touch me,
a man who cut off his hand for me
won't hesitate to--
Gosh. Such passion.
Divine lovers.
-You. Come here.
-Yes, sir?
Sir.
Spread the word among the media
that madam is being beaten up
at the police station.
Brutally beaten up.
But make sure
there are no marks on her face.
Sir, it's not right
to beat her up in custody.
If the media finds out,
they will raise a hue and cry.
That's exactly what we want.
Agra Police are crossing
all boundaries and limits.
We have the confirmed news.
To cover up their incompetence,
double-murder accused Rani Kashyap
who was under suspicion previously,
is being brutally beaten up
even before she's produced in court.
Who will take responsibility
if something untoward happens?
Chiraunji!y
-Chiraunji!
-I, Rishabh Saxena,
am ready to surrender to the police.
But on one condition.
Rani has to be present
at the time of my surrender.
She should come walking towards me, alone,
so that I'm assured that she's okay.
Only then will I surrender
in three days, at 8:00 p.m.
on the railway bridge.
Salute, sir.
Conduct a recce of the entire area.
Yes, sir.
And ask
these Forest Department people to leave.
Sir, there are crocodiles
under the bridge, so…
I don't want anyone apart from cops
in this area.
Okay.
Sir.
We'll stop the train scheduled to cross
the railway bridge at 8:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Our men will be present in two groups.
The moment we spot Rishu on the bridge,
we will surround him.
Isn't everything seeming a tad too easy?
I don't think we should give
in to Rishu's conditions
and let Rani go to the bridge alone.
We will find a way to outsmart Rishu.
When Rani goes to meet him on the bridge,
our team will close in on him.
There will be cops on the bridge and…
certain death underneath it.
The lovers will struggle
for a little while
before getting separated forever.
Amazing!
Move.
Meena!
Team B on standby.
Wait for my command.
Rani.
Rishu!
Rishu, you won't surrender.
You won't! We'll escape.
Move in. I repeat, move in.
-Seal the bridge.
-Okay, sir.
Rani…
Where is he going?
Who is he?
Sir, come in.
Someone is breaking the cordon.
Who's that fool?
He's breaking the formation!
The warrior from Mahabharata
who is known for breaking formations.
Sir, the DNA report is here.
The sample doesn't match the body.
No one will take action.
I repeat, no one will take action.
Keep everyone ready,
but no one will go forward.
Sir, everyone should stay where they are.
Otherwise, I won't hesitate to shoot.
Abhimanyu!
You won't be able to escape.
You're surrounded.
Put your gun down and talk to us.
I'm not here to talk to you, sir.
I'm here to present a case
for myself and everyone
who gets left behind
and betrayed.
Everyone who has been
cheated and deceived in love.
No one loses in love.
Love sets you free.
I'm not here to listen to your poetry.
I truly loved you, Rani ji.
I have told you all about myself.
I even showed you the pink Taj Mahal
from my terrace.
I laid bare my heart to you.
You could've told me the truth.
I never forced you to do anything.
To make things worse…
you went and told the cops about me.
I told you, Rani ji,
I can't stand betrayal!
Rishu.
Rani…
Rani, no.
Rani!
Hold my hand, Rani.
Agra Police's woes don't seem to end.
This incident took place
during Rishu Saxena's surrender,
in which Rishu and Rani
disappeared into
the crocodile-infested Yamuna River!
There's also news of another unidentified
man falling into the river.
What remains to be seen is
if this case of drowning
will drown the UP Police's
reputation as well.
Sir, does that mean their story is over?
Their story has just begun.
Start the search operation.
Yes, sir.
A NEW TURN
IN THE RISHU SAXENA SURRENDER CASE
SNAKE BITE KILLS AN ENTIRE FAMILY
In what she says
And what you see
Far from these, you will find
The hidden truth
Pieces of truth
Fragments of lies
Have merged together
To form a broken image
To pick and choose
To reweave each thread, anew
Once you see through the web of lies
You will gain clarity
And the truth will set you free
Abhimanyu, Rishu, Rani…
Their house, office, clinic, salon,
and all surrounding areas…
I want all mobile and laptop recordings
and CCTV footage of every place.
Okay, sir.
What can and cannot be
Lie in the realm of darkness
While the dim light reveals
Countless stories
Why does the mind strive
To clear these webs?
Once you see through the web of lies
You will gain clarity
The truth will set you free
Kishore…
Want to hear a story?
POLICE STATION, AGRA
This…
Indigestion is a dangerous thing, sir.
We don't take it seriously
and keep having digestives to ease it.
But sometimes…
it could be the symptom
of a serious illness.
Like cancer.
This case is just like indigestion, sir.
While we're looking for answers,
what appears isn't what is.
What is your point?
Sir, with Rani's,
Rishu's, and Abhimanyu's death,
who stood to gain the most?
Rani…
Rishu…
And Abhimanyu.
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
had these three been alive,
they would have been in jail.
Rani was already in jail.
So would Rishu for murdering Neel.
And Abhimanyu, as well,
for murdering his family.
SNAKE BITE KILLS AN ENTIRE FAMILY
Abhimanyu was being blackmailed
by a man called Lallan.
This snake charmer had helped Abhimanyu
to murder his family.
On the day of the double murder,
Lallan had gone to meet
Abhimanyu at his clinic.
We found that footage
from an ATM in front of the clinic.
Dead.
The other dead body was that of Poonam.
Poonam had gone
to meet Rishu at the clinic that day.
She knew his secret.
She died as well.
Perfect victims.
Compounder Abhimanyu,
an ace Biology student,
knew exactly how to burn a body
and where to place objects
so that they can be identified instantly.
The story gets even more interesting, sir.
We found some more footage
from Bobby Garage.
According to this footage,
Rani and Abhimanyu
returned home at 7:00 p.m.
Fifteen minutes later,
we see someone else entering
Abhimanyu's house.
Rishu.
The three of them probably
came up with a plan.
Because at 10:00 p.m.,
a helpless-looking Rani ji
is seen running in the rain.
Help!
Please save me! My husband will kill me.
Sir, what's interesting is that…
after Rani,
two more people left Abhimanyu's house.
Rishu and Abhimanyu.
Sir, that's why I'm saying…
that night,
they did come up with a plan.
So you're saying their plan
was to jump into the river
in front of everyone?
But there were crocodiles in the river.
They would die immediately.
What kind of a plan is this?
That's the twist, sir.
The question still remains…
Why did Rishu choose
the railway bridge location?
There's no plot twist!
That's the whole case.
Montu…
Sir.
I know this case is personal for you,
but let this one go.
We are under pressure from the media.
Close this case.
Because the deeper you probe,
the deeper the problems
for our department will be.
Sir.
We can't close this case again.
Please give me some more time, sir.
Darn.
Closing a case file
doesn't mean the case is closed.
However hard one tries to hide it,
the truth will come out one day.
Anyway…
you're the department's woodpecker…
SIX MONTHS LATER
-Rishu!
-Rani ji.
Rishu!
Rani ji…
Good evening.
Correct the spelling.
Is everything okay?
Yes. Everything is fine.
I'm just tired.
Complete this, I'll be back.
Do you want water?
No.
SHARDA PRIMARY SCHOOL, DEVSAR
-Now come and submit your homework.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Very good.
-Ma'am!
-Completed your homework, Meenakshi?
-Yes, ma'am.
CHAKIA, BIHAR
Listen, someone has sent a book for you.
There's a crocodile
on the cover of the book.
DINESH PANDIT, THE CROCODILE'S TRAP
There are only three copies of this book.
This is one of them.
Suraj and Arjun came up with a plan
to escape from the police's trap,
they'd have to dive into
the jaws of the crocodile.
They had purposely chosen
this area infested
with dangerous crocodiles.
They started their preparations
three days before the incident.
NIGHT ONE
Rishu, in Pandit's book, do you know why
Suraj and Arjun kept increasing the amount
of meat they fed to the crocodiles?
So that the crocodiles remained hungry
and felt they'd get more meat…
if they swam further away.
They have to be moved far away
from the railway bridge.
Today, we'll feed them meat
2 km away from here.
NIGHT TWO
NIGHT THREE
Now, 12 km of this area
is free of crocodiles.
Our instincts will tell us
where to come out of the water.
Will Rani ji jump if you ask her to?
Of course.
So much faith in your love?
I have faith in you too, sir.
That is because you love Rani so deeply
and you might kill me anytime.
The question is,
why haven't you until now?
Because I want Rani ji
to come to me herself.
-Now.
-Okay.
Yes.
If you enjoyed the story so far,
you'll enjoy the ending even more.
Come to Tota-Maina Lovers Point
Deosar, Himachal Pradesh,
at 6:00 p.m. on March 20th.
Make sure you walk
for 30 minutes every day.
Thank you, doctor.
"Tota-Maina Lovers Point, 6:00 p.m."
Goodness!
This is very steep.
Be careful.
Pandit writes,
"Color of jealousy is red, so is anger.
And so is blood.
Alas! Red is also the colour of love."
Pandit!
Such a dishonest color, isn't it?
There's only one red in my life.
The color of the rose that you're wearing.
You know, it has turned black now.
Excuse me?
Your rose has turned black.
Come here, Rani ji, we'll talk…
Don't come forward.
I'll jump.
Rani ji…
Rishu was right.
I refused to believe him.
Committing murder is like a game to you.
Lallan, Poonam…
They weren't a part of our plan.
Lallan and Poonam were a risk.
Life gave me the chance
to leave everything behind
and start over with you, so I took it.
For you.
Tell me, haven't I made you happy?
You did.
You made me very happy.
For the sake of those moments,
don't do this, please.
I'm willing to bear the consequences
of my actions.
But please don't jump. Please come here.
Stop this drama, boy.
If she really intended to jump,
she wouldn't have invited me here.
Why have you called me here, Rani ji?
So that you can get your closure, like me.
Both our lives are heavily influenced
by Pandit's writings.
Rishu…
Rani!
-Rani ji…
-Rani.
Rani ji…
-Rani…
-Rani ji…
Rani ji…
If we want to live,
we'll have to die in front of the world.
The Crocodile's Trap.
Dinesh Pandit.
Rani…
No way.
We're not doing this again.
Listen to me, Rani.
I have known Uncle Montu since childhood.
He'll go to the depths of hell,
if required, to find us.
Do you want us to take a shortcut to hell?
We will not do this. No.
And what we've already done?
The Revenge of the Cobra.
Wrath of Kasauli.
Rani ji, we've been fools to mold
our lives on Pandit's books.
There's a difference.
We've learned
how to survive from Pandit's books
while you've learned to kill.
There is a difference.
Over there!
Rishu!
-Rishu!
-Rani ji.
Rishu!
Rani ji…
-Rishu!
-Rani ji.
Rishu!
-Rishu!
Rani ji…
Rani ji.
You killed Rishu!
You killed someone too for love.
Why is it so wrong if I do it?
I did the same thing
that you and Rishu did.
Then how is it that your love is right
and mine is wrong?
You don't even know how to love,
Abhimanyu.
You have never loved me.
-No, Rani ji, I--
-All you did was play Snakes and Ladders!
You…
I made a huge mistake.
Okay.
Let me tell you one more truth…
I never thought I'd be able
to be with anyone else apart from Rishu.
After that incident,
I thought I could be with you.
I felt like we had something.
But this kind of betrayal
is too much even for me to bear.
I made a mistake, Rani.
Your punishment is…
I'll never be yours.
You have won me,
but you'll never win over me.
Rani ji, stop!
-Rani ji!
Rani ji.
Rani ji!
Send search and rescue teams right away.
Abhimanyu ji,
this way, please.
You have a lot of people to account for.
Poonam Prajapati.
Lallan Barua.
Ashok Bharadwaj and family.
Rishabh Saxena
and maybe…
Rani Kashyap.
Get him.
Passengers are requested to board
the aircraft from Gate No. 2. Thank you.
What's wrong, sir?
The body wasn't found?
I can gaze at your face, ample…
As you reside in my heart's temple…
To quote the great Pandit,
"Relationships thrive within
the boundaries of right and wrong.
True love, however,
begins where these boundaries end."
I'm the one who taught them
that if we want to live,
we'll have to die in front of the world.
And I'm the one who paid the price!
It's not yours. You're quoting a line
by a Big Daddy author.
The Crocodile's Trap
by the famous Dinesh Pandit.
Sir, how do you know
he's my father?
Amazing!