POLICE STATION DISTRICT - AGRA
Help!
Help! Help!
My husband’s going to kill me.
Please, please help me.
My husband wants to kill me. Please.
TWO MONTHS EARLIER
Today's breaking news,
only on Visphotak News.
Hathni Kund Barrage on the Yamuna river
in Haryana has been destroyed completely
due to heavy rains.
As a result of this,
a lot of crocodiles have been washed away
with the flowing water,
to low-lying areas such as Agra.
Will you help me get down?
My legs are hurting. Come. Help me.
Auntyji, come on.
It’s time for your shot of insulin.
You're here? With so many tomatoes?
They’re quite cheap today.
So I was thinking…
-She looked so pretty.
-…just buy some.
Sona,
please help me out this one time.
I promise you
the next time you need me…
I’ll be there for you.
I helped you yesterday, didn’t I?
What!
She cancelled
a 5-hour bridal makeup session!
I could’ve dolled up
five clients in that time.
-Sorry, they fell down.
-No problem.
She gave it to Seema?
You know what? When Rani does her thing,
girls look like brides for a whole month.
And Seema’s clients,
by the time they get to the altar,
they start looking as scary as Monjulika.
She’ll come back to me.
I’m not going to give her
a rupee's discount.
She hasn’t even returned
the lipstick she had borrowed.
Oh, no! Rani was so upset that she forgot
her Kamla-Bimla here. Look.
Shall I go give it?
Go ahead.
I'll be right back.
Just a minute.
Let's go.
Raniji! Raniji!
-Belanganj.
-Raniji!
Raniji, you forgot your… Raniji.
Just a second.
No, that’s not the point.
Stick to the bookings.
You need to value other people's time.
Yeah, but…
Raniji
Raniji, wait!
Yeah, just,
just a bit further. Pull over.
SHROUD SHOP - QADER SHROUD STORE
BEWARE OF THIEVES
-30.
-Here.
Raniji.
You forgot these.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you so much.
Um, you ran all the way to give me these?
Oh, no, no.
I had some work here.
SHROUD SHOP, QADER SHROUD STORE
BEWARE OF THIEVES
-Hmm.
-Actually, it’s for a patient.
-Looks like you take good care of them.
-Yeah, yeah.
Thank you!
-Actually, Raniji.
-Yes?
-I, uh--
-Rani!
-Rani, come here quickly.
-Yeah.
I’ll be back in two minutes.
-No problem.
-Just two minutes. Okay? Hmm.
Listen, Rani, I goofed up.
Mrs. Sahay asked for Dirty Blonde,
but I applied Slutty Red by mistake.
It's okay, we'll see.
I’ve told you a thousand times
not to start without me.
-Hi, Mrs. Sahay.
-Arey, Rani?
Ah, keep it on, keep it on.
This enhances the color, you know?
How have you been?
-One chai, please.
-Yes, sir.
-We’re applying an extra layer.
-Okay.
You have time, right?
Dirty Blonde,
the best color in town. Trust me.
-Really?
-Takes a little time to apply.
We'll wash it off in ten minutes.
-Raniji.
-Come on…
-I was thinking that would you--
-What?
Would you like to watch a movie with me?
-Friday?
Ah…
At 6?
-Okay.
♪ Once upon a time,
There was a beauty ♪
♪ And her crazy lover ♪
♪ It was a magical age ♪
♪ A magical ambience ♪
♪ It was a magical world ♪
♪ After they met one day ♪
♪ They started meeting
Every day… ♪
RANI
♪ Then they fell in love ♪
♪ It was a catastrophe ♪
♪ Where did you lose yourself ♪
♪ While listening to this story? ♪
♪ People are surprised
Because they are unfamiliar… ♪
♪ With the path that love takes… ♪
RANI
♪ I used to be familiar ♪
♪ With those paths ♪
♪ Once upon a time, there was a beauty ♪
♪ And her crazy lover… ♪
♪ It was a magical ambience ♪
♪ It was a magical world ♪
♪ There was a beauty ♪
♪ And her crazy lover ♪
For the sake of love,
Rishu and I had gone too far.
Rishu had now become Ravi.
Our love was like a flowing river,
but we were on the opposite banks.
And what stopped us from crossing over?
The Uttar Pradesh Police.
And to this day, we are giving it our all
for that elusive happily ever after.
If love doesn't push you to the brink
of insanity, it's not true love.
Only the meek seek refuge
in a passionless relationship.
Jaipur! Jaipur!
Hurry up, Jaipur!
Enter inside.
Hey, uncle, look here, here.
Gudduji, here, uh, the 25
that you had asked for.
Okay, don’t worry,
I’ll take care of everything.
Within two months,
you’ll be off to Thailand.
-Two months?
-Yes, two months
I’ll let you know the exact date.
So that proves the fact that,
in every condition,
the velocity remains cons--
What’s going on over there?
-Pay attention here.
-Yes, sir.
So the velocity of--
Note this down, I’ll be back.
When are you giving it, Raviji?
Rent? I’ve given it already.
When will you give the answers
to my questions?
What was the song?
♪ All I need is a lover ♪
♪ To love ♪
Poonamji,
after my wife passed--
Raviji, your wife is gone
but not your life, right?
And I’m not talking about love
that lasts a lifetime.
Hmm?
Just… a night or two will do.
I am sorry.
-I’m not feeling well today.
-No problem.
You’ll surely feel better someday.
I’ll come back then.
Hmm!
♪ All I need is a lover ♪
♪ To love ♪
Hello.
Uncle &amp; aunty have gone
to the Agra Masala Convention.
Masala Convention?
Now don’t be a clueless cat, okay?
The point is, there is nobody home.
So are you coming?
Looks a bit difficult today.
Alright then, meet me with a gift
on Raksha Bandhan, okay?
When will we get out of here, Rishu?
-How much longer?
-Plan is in place.
The agent has sourced
new passports as well.
Just one more month to go, then it’ll be
just you and me going wild in Thailand.
Meanwhile, just see to it that
you don’t fall for the love of your fans.
And what about
that compounder lover of yours?
He doesn't desire my body.
He desires my love.
He’s a decent man.
But you're not that decent.
Panditji says,
“Character nor behavior reveals,
to judge a person in love,
realize what their heart feels."
Uff!
-Bhai Sahab!
-Hmm?
-Tickets for the 6 o’clock show.
-How many?
All of them, please.
Rani. Hmm!
Sorry, sorry! Did you get hurt?
-Ah!
-Huh?
Arey, yaar!
Come on.
Hey, come on, move aside.
Tamatar le lo.
15 rupees, half kg.
The city of Taj is under threat.
A crocodile was seen
crawling around Aslam Tailor’s shop.
So, I’m just doing a root touch up.
We’ll keep it for half an hour.
Then we will wash it off.
-Okay?
-As you say, beta.
Arey, Abhimanyu? At this hour?
Again with
so many tomatoes? Huh?
They were really cheap
outside Royal Cinema.
So I thought might as well.
Shit!
I am sorry.
Abhimanyu, I am so sorry!
Don’t worry, Raniji. I'm sure you must’ve
been busy with something important.
I… wait…
-So sorry. Take this--
-Shall we try again next Friday?
I’ll be waiting for you.
Again?
Waiting doesn’t scare me.
Because that can be done alone.
I'm scared of the conversations.
For those I’ll need you as well, right?
Right.
Stop laughing.
I feel really bad for him.
Raniji, you have quite the history
of killing your lovers and admirers.
The police never found their bodies.
Don’t try to act over smart--
Help, help, help!
Oh no!
Catch him!
I said stop!
Stop.
Oh no, oh no.
Yes, sir?
Does a girl
named Rani Kashyap live here?
-Uh…
-Locals gave us this address.
Yes, she lives here.
Uh, she’s a really nice girl.
Poor girl is a widow.
She's got no family.
She lives here as a tenant.
We found her purse.
I’ll call her.
Uh, Rani beta!
Yes?
Coming.
So you managed to find me.
Who stole my purse?
And we’ve crossed paths again, Raniji.
Fate.
It looks like
divine justice is on its way.
Your favorite Dinesh Pandit,
says something along those lines
in that novel, right?
Wrath of Kasauli?
I've read the novel.
The climax was to die for.
Faked his own death and cut off his hand
and placed it near the dead body
to save his damsel in distress.
-Thank you.
-By the way,
I’ve heard someone’s been
looking for you for a long time.
Who?
The ghosts of your past.
That officer has read Wrath of Kasauli.
He said he loved the climax
and someone is on the hunt for us.
He knows what we did.
He only has a fictional story,
no evidence.
He’s trying to scare you.
I told you
to go back, right? Why did you come back?
I was missing you.
We met in the morning.
Did you forget?
I was busy in the morning
laying my traps.
I thought two Indians could share
their happiness and sorrow.
The number
you're trying to call is out of coverage.
Please call again later.
The number
you have called is out of coverage area.
Bhaiya, Husanpura?
-Bhaisaab, what's wrong with you?
-The stench is really bad, bhaiya.
All customers are complaining.
Please move your truck.
I’m leaving, madam. I’m leaving.
You’ve already picked up the garbage,
so just leave.
I told you I'm leaving.
"Strengths of the heart
once intertwined,
love can endure attacks of every kind."
One minute. One minute. One…
This… Are you a fan of Dinesh Pandit?
This?
Some mad fellow wrote this on my truck
and paid me
to simply wait here for an hour or so.
Why? Is there any problem?
DINESH PANDIT
ATTACK ON LOVE
"Though I didn't want
to talk to you,
my will lost and vulnerability took over.
Archana knew the place
where her lover would be waiting for her."
-Uncle, uh, uncle?
-Hmm?
-The phone?
-Time to close.
-Rishu! Rishu!
-Rani!
Rishu, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I am fine.
Okay, listen, I just met the agent
and we’re leaving for Thailand next week.
Rishu, Rishu, Rishu, I think
the police is up to something, Rishu.
They’re following me wherever I go.
Rani, listen.
The only thing standing between
prison and freedom is your fear.
Kishore doesn’t have evidence.
They just want to see you worried,
that’s exactly what they want.
And they might call you
to the police station
to ask a few questions.
Just be strong.
Hmm.
Uh, Rishu? Hello? Rishu! Rishu!
Hello?
Okay.
POLICE STATION DISTRICT - AGRA
Come on!
Come on, chindi chor! Go, sit in the van.
"Naitik Verma?"
New lover? Or a friend?
Why?
Because you talk to him for hours on end.
I thought we could be friends.
He told me his name was Rahul.
Then one day, a woman called me
and said that he’s her husband.
So the friendship ended.
You know, the thing is,
inspector sahab, especially nowadays,
can anyone be a 100% certain
if they know a person?
There's a difference between knowing
and recognizing, but you know that.
Hmm.
But this time you can't spin your stories
in the police station, Raniji.
Panditji says--
You couldn’t resist getting Panditji
into the mix, could you?
I had to.
Because in a police station like this
about 30 years ago,
he was framed,
tarnished and fired from his job.
Since that day, he has been trying
to get his revenge through his books.
Look at any of his stories.
-The police will always be the losers.
-Jai Hind, sahab.
So, the pen really is mightier
than the sword, quite a revenge.
I’ve heard Dinesh Pandit bhaisahab
left the world a long time ago.
But his books are
being published even today.
My name is Mrutyunjay Paswan.
I don’t think you recognize me.
I’m your relative, actually.
I think your memory
seems to be a little weak, hmm?
If I had to tell you exactly who I am…
I’m Rishu’s mom’s sister’s husband’s
sister’s husband’s brother.
Which means…
I’m Neel’s favorite chacha.
For you, Neel might be
Rishu’s distant cousin.
But you need to know something.
Neel meant the world to me.
My favorite, my darling nephew.
You know, I danced like crazy
at your wedding functions.
Showered money.
You know Kishoreji, right?
He’s a close friend of mine.
And he has offered me a chance
to take the lead in this case of yours.
So from now on…
I’ll be asking all the questions.
Because
it’s personal.
Tell me one thing, this friend of yours,
a special friend maybe, Naitikji,
Rahulji…
What makes him
call the travel agent every single week?
-He--
-Hmm?
He likes to travel maybe,
how would I know?
And you?
Why are you roaming
around Agra all by yourself?
Isn't it so strange, Raniji?
It’s been such a long time
since Rishu’s gone.
You broke all ties
and are not talking to your family either.
You didn’t even get married again.
So you mean to say,
it’s a crime for a widow to not remarry?
Are you planning
on reporting me or arresting me?
-What are you trying to imply?
-I’m telling you
that I know Rishu is here with you
in this city, here in Agra.
Otherwise, you living here
without any relative, without any friends
simply doesn’t make sense.
Sorry.
What I’m also trying to say is…
I’ve known Rishu
since the time he was just in his nappies.
He’s like an iceberg.
What you see is harmless.
But we’ll never know
the secret it hides underneath.
I…I’m a modern independent woman
and I…I can manage on my own.
Raniji, people from the department
call me by a number of names.
But my most favorite one
is The Woodpecker.
The Woodpecker.
Do you know why?
It's because a woodpecker keeps pecking
the trunk of a tree continuously
and relentlessly
till he bores a hole in it.
He just doesn’t give up.
The thing is that…
the law doesn’t dare to intervene
between me and all my cases.
Okay.
You may leave.
And Raniji…
if you run into Rishu, do tell him…
…his Montu chacha is back now.
You said that a team
was keeping an eye on her, right?
Any news from them?
No, sir, nothing yet.
The force is searching
the whole city, sir.
Where all does our beautiful madam
take her lovely self in the city?
Uh, sir, home, beauty parlor,
she's usually in a 2-kilometer radius.
Then deploy your force
in the same 2-kilometre radius right away.
We’ll nab Rishu in a week's time.
Okay, sir.
Have you seen this person?
POLICE STATION BELANGANJ
No.
-Seen him?
-No.
-Don't know him.
Look closely.
Must have seen him somewhere.
-Seen him?
-No idea, sir.
Let’s ask him.
-Don't recognize?
-No, sir.
Good to go.
Please, listen to me!
Sir, I haven't done anything.
Listen to me.
I’ve two small kids at home.
I have not done anything wrong, sir.
Aunty, how can you say that?
Your son Sonu told me,
"Mummy doesn’t teach me anything at home.
She’s on her phone,
watching Anupama all day."
I’ll call back in some time.
Have you seen this man anywhere?
I’ll be back in just a moment.
Want some chai?
-No.
-Yes.
Uh, sugar, three teaspoons.
Three teaspoons.
Ever heard about diabetes?
That’s why I said, sir,
only three teaspoons.
Raviji.
The police have come here.
They asked me, "Have you seen him?"
No, right?
I’ll tell them.
Sorry, sir, I haven’t seen him.
Uh, arey, madam,
I thought you’re getting us chai.
It’s not ready yet?
Aren’t you ashamed?
Asking a woman on crutches
to make chai for you?
Get lost from here!
If you want chai, come
with a warrant next time. Get out!
Rani!
-Rani--
-Not today. People are around.
-Listen to me.
-You listen to me.
Who is that new DSP at the police station?
Montu chacha, I know.
Get in, I’ll tell you.
Montu?
One minute.
It's all over, Rani.
-Everything.
-Why?
He has arrested our travel agent, Guddu.
All the money we paid,
everything, it's all ruined.
Today, the cops came
to the coaching center as well.
That Poonam is also suspecting me.
I just don’t know what to do now.
-Let’s run away.
-Huh?
Come on, let's run away.
Rani, I’ve known
Montu chacha since I was a kid.
If we both run away,
he’ll have even more fun.
We’ll run to every nook and cranny,
but he’ll follow us and kill us.
Montu chacha! Neel! What kind of a…
-What kind of a family do you have?
-We are left with no other option.
I’ll surrender myself.
I’ll tell the police
you had nothing to do with Neel’s death.
Have you gone crazy? Hmm?
Have you really lost your mind?
We ran away from Jwalapur
and came here, why?
To surrender ourselves?
Rishu, you had to cut your hand.
-Try to understand what I’m saying.
-Auntyji?
Oh, you're here!
Wait a second.
Is Raniji home?
Rani beta.
Rani!
Rani…
I’ll just go to another city.
In a couple of days, the police will
track me and arrest me then and there.
-You will be--
-Ssh! Shut up!
You’re afraid because Montu chacha thinks
we’re here together, right?
I think I have a better idea.
But you have to trust me.
I thought I’d have
to wait for you tonight as well.
I'll have to come home again
for an appointment.
I guess all good things
come to those who wait.
So will you marry me?
What?
I asked, will you marry me?
Are you serious?
What about love?
I don’t have the heart
to fall in love again.
I wait for you for hours at a stretch,
but you never seem to notice me.
Why me?
If he can wait hours for me,
I think he could hold my hand
and walk a few miles too.
And who knows?
Maybe love finds me after we get married.
Or maybe it won't.
Wow, Raniji…
It took you just a moment
to make me the happiest man in the world
and the loneliest too.
Love has the same effect, Abhimanyuji.
It makes you strong and breaks you too.
If I had known love was this merciless,
I would’ve stayed away.
But now there's no turning back.
"My sins have been
washed away since I fell in love.
Saying your name feels like
I'm chanting Bajrang Bali's name somehow."
Don’t do it, Rani.
This is not the right plan for us.
Neither will Rani and Rishu be together,
nor will Montu chacha come after us.
The chapter ends there.
One of Panditji's lines
came to my mind.
“I’ll accept all your demands.
Just make sure
our fights don’t involve a third person.”
We aren’t even fighting.
Yet there is a third one.
We’re spoiling our lives so badly, Rani.
Do you think our love will last forever?
The wedding is in three days.
Will you come?
♪ This deep bond between us ♪
♪ Always brings a smile when we meet ♪
♪ I am so besotted by you ♪
♪ That my eyes fill with tears of joy ♪
♪ I will bear this pain for you ♪
♪ With a smile on my face ♪
♪ I am so besotted by you ♪
♪ That my eyes fill with tears of joy ♪
♪ Joy and sorrow
Are sides of the same coin ♪
♪ I hope these smiles
Don't lead to tears ♪
♪ I will bear this pain for you ♪
♪ With a smile on my face ♪
So, what do you think,
will Romeo come here
for his Juliet’s wedding?
I know the kind of person Rishu has been.
The only thing
that can destroy him is his love.
After all, we are legally obliged
to screw him. Hmm?
♪ Joy and sorrow
Are sides of the same coin ♪
♪ I hope these smiles
Don't lead to tears ♪
♪ With a smile ♪
♪ I feel smothered ♪
♪ Let me catch my breath ♪
♪ With a smile ♪
♪ Whom can I tell my secrets to?
Close friends are hard to find ♪
♪ I will bear this pain for you ♪
♪ With a smile on my face ♪
♪ I am so besotted by you ♪
♪ That my eyes fill with tears of joy ♪
♪ Joy and sorrow
Are sides of the same coin ♪
♪ I hope these smiles
Don't lead to tears ♪
♪ I will bear this pain for you ♪
♪ With a smile on my face ♪
You… You drink rum?
Sorry? Uh, yeah, sometimes
Hm, uh, you have whiskey?
When I used to look at you
from a distance,
I had a thousand things to say to you.
Now you’re in front of me,
I don’t know what to say or do.
I’m stressing out thinking about
what I can say to make you laugh.
Have you heard of Dinesh Pandit?
Even Rishu didn’t know
about him before he met me.
You had to bring Rishuji into this.
He is always here.
[In that case…
you, me and Rishuji
could play snakes and ladders.
Love plays out between two people, Raniji.
If it’s three, we’re better off
playing snakes and ladders.
Tell me one thing.
Hmm?
Didn’t you feel bad
when I said I’m getting married to you
just for my convenience?
Didn’t it break your heart?
You must have made
some plans for yourself.
Love, lover, romance,
intimacy, passion, etc. etc.
I was seven when my parents passed away.
What remained of my family
was my chacha, chachi and their two kids.
They passed away when I was about 20.
I was the only one left.
The house, these windows,
the roof and the walls.
I had a job,
but that could barely get me out of bed.
When I couldn’t see a light
at the end of the tunnel,
I tried to end my life too.
And that’s the day
I saw you at the clinic.
Sky-blue dupatta
rose-pink kameez.
I had never before seen
such colors in my life.
My whole world changed completely.
Such beautiful colors,
made my clinic, my house,
my neighborhood, all turn rosy pink.
The whole city, in fact the Taj Mahal
I saw from my house, turned pink as well.
If I have to play snakes and ladders
with you for the rest of my life,
I’ll do it with a smile.
Shall we?
♪ Your eyes and mine ♪
♪ Locked in a gaze ♪
♪ Your dreams and mine ♪
♪ Are so alike ♪
♪ I know not, nor do you ♪
♪ But this is the wonder of the divine ♪
♪ I wish I could express ♪
♪ What's going on within my heart ♪
♪ Is it love or an illusion ♪
♪ Wonders everyone ♪
♪ I wish I could express ♪
♪ What's going on within my heart… ♪
Who is it, Raniji?
Pizza.
I didn’t order it.
Wanted to surprise you.
♪ The love I imbibe from your gaze ♪
♪ Drives me out of my senses ♪
♪ My very soul
Is getting intoxicated by you ♪
♪ What fault is it of mine ♪
♪ That I fell in love with your eyes ♪
♪ And was driven out of my mind? ♪
♪ My very soul
Is getting intoxicated by you ♪
♪ What fault is it of mine? ♪
Come on!
Come on, you lost again!
What kind of a champion are you?
Hmm…
I’m only focused
on winning the real game, Raniji.
Game of Life, just with you.
If you tell me to jump from the roof,
I’ll do it. Just for you.
But I don’t have the permission to love.
But that’s what Dinesh Pandit’s character
Surekha said just a second ago.
Show me.
Hmm.
Proceed with caution.
Who knows what the pages
of this book contain?
Surekha might get permission
to fall in love.
You keep waiting for the big twist.
I’m off to sleep now.
Good night.
Yeah, I’m soon going to get
my PhD in waiting anyway.
Raviji.
I got a little carried away.
The thing is that seeing the police
my heart goes dhak dhak
dhak dhak.
It starts pounding really hard.
Why do you play so hard to get, Raviji?
You don’t have a hand
and I practically don't have a leg.
But together we could walk
miles on end. Perfect.
Do you know what happened to my leg?
For my ex-boyfriend, I was
on the second floor, and I jumped off.
"I gave him my heart
thinking he's my own,
but he butchered it
leaving me broken and torn."
From the day we got married until now,
we’re just playing snakes and ladders.
The actual board game.
But your tongue is stuck
way down Poonam’s throat.
She keeps blackmailing me,
harassing me, what do I do?
And I pushed her away.
You saw that too, right?
I told you to stay away,
stay away from that… that wicked bitch.
-Who knows? Maybe you led her on.
-Seriously?
That’s how much you trust me and my love?
Didn’t I trust you when you told me
you were going to marry Abhimanyu?
Correct. It’s all my fault.
I made a plan, so I was wrong.
Abhimanyu is trapped and that’s my fault.
And Montu chacha?
That also must be my fault.
I told you, I was ready to surrender,
but you didn't listen to me.
-He’s not going to leave us alone.
-Go to hell!
And take your Montu chacha with you.
At first, we didn’t love each other.
Then we fell in love
but the timing was off.
When the timing was right, we couldn’t
be together 'cause there were issues.
Finally, when we sorted everything,
we were about to leave,
your Montu chacha comes out of nowhere.
The timing of our love story is bad.
I don’t think this is going to work out.
Last time you thought our relationship
won’t work out, I cut off my hand.
But I didn’t let go of your hand.
This time if I have to cut off my head,
I’ll happily do that as well.
My love for you
has made me a criminal anyway.
Oh! That’s not fair, Raniji.
You’ve already started
drinking without me?
You are crying? Is everything all right?
L…
-What?
-L…
L… S… D.
LSD!
Are you high on drugs?
Love. Sex. Deceit. LSD.
You’ll find it all over Agra.
There is LSD everywhere around us.
Look, all I need is love.
Poonam just wants sex.
And Abhimanyu is a victim of deceit.
He’s trapped for no reason.
He shouldn’t have got married.
It’s all my fault.
It’s Montu chacha’s fault.
Montu… whatever he’s doing,
he shouldn’t be doing it.
I don’t want to be here.
Please take me away
from here, Rishu.
Please take me away.
Please call Rishuji right away.
See, I’m not much of a preacher.
But you need to leave the city soon.
I can help you make arrangements.
Passport, police…
-I’ll take care of everything.
-But how?
I’m a compounder.
Be it the judge or the DIG,
I know all their dirty secrets.
Everyone gets sick.
I’ve given shots to the biggest of shots,
I’ll manage everything.
But, Abhimanyuji…
why are you trying to help us?
Mom, Dad, childhood, teenage years…
Couldn’t save any of it.
But the least I can do is save my love.
So what if
I can’t spend my life with Raniji?
It's her happiness that matters.
If I live in some corner of her heart
because of the things I say and do,
then maybe some day
she'll grow tired of Rishuji
and think about me instead. So…
She’ll need a couple of lifetimes
to get tired of me.
But I’ve heard
that you are an expert at waiting.
Don’t be so egoistic, Rishuji.
Today, the love of your life is with you
and I am the victim of love.
Fate can be really evil sometimes.
If it’s not meant to be,
even eternal lovers would never meet.
And if it's destined,
two strangers
who’ve only just met on a train,
can journey together
till eternity and beyond.
Destiny is etched
on the palm of our hands, my friend.
In the name of love, I didn’t think twice
before cutting my hand off.
SAHNI CLINIC
Just a second.
So you’ll leave for Thailand from here
in a couple of days, alright?
Until then, be my guest.
This is the bed,
the bathroom is over there.
It’s Sunday, so no one's coming.
I’ll be coming through that door itself.
-I’ll lock this one from outside.
-Thank you.
Should I come along?
It’s risky.
-Abhimanyu…
-Hmm?
Sorry.
I mean it.
If you’re sorry,
come with me for one last movie tonight.
Okay then, uh…
I’ll go give your husband his tiffin.
And then I have to take
my lovely wife for a movie.
Poonamji, um…
How did you find out I am here?
I followed you here.
You thought a resignation is enough?
You will need much more--
Give me a month to sort everything.
I’ll come back to you soon.
And if you don’t come back…
then…
I told you, Poonamji…
Matar pulao.
Raniji told me
it's your favorite, so…
Yeah,
keep it on the table.
Jasmine… Wow!
Was a lady in this room?
Yes, uh, Poonam was here.
Who Poonam?
-She was my landlady, actually.
-How did she come here?
Now what do I say, Abhimanyuji.
She keeps following me.
Blackmailing me as well.
-Blackmail?
-Yes.
Why? What does she want? Money?
-She must be after something.
-Me.
-You?
-Yes.
Arey, baap re!
What's her full name?
Why do you want to know?
I was thinking
I’ll send her a friend request.
Don’t worry,
she won't tell anyone about all this.
She loves me. That’s what she says.
Hmm.
Love?
So, the thing is, Poonam likes you,
and you like Raniji,
but then even I like Raniji,
but Raniji likes you.
We’re all wasting our lives chasing
something way beyond our reach.
Just simplify it, professor.
Take a U-turn and go back to Poonam.
Raniji stays with me. End of story.
Arey, I was just kidding around.
Why did you get so serious?
-Enjoy your food, I’ll get going.
-Thank you. Okay.
Something wrong?
Did someone else come, too?
Uh…
No one.
Does Raniji know
you’re such a big fat liar?
I would’ve preferred
the movie plan.
There are crocodiles in this area.
But I guess, they’re mostly
near the railway bridge, right?
And anyway, the police have cordoned off
the area with tapes and stuff.
So the…
the plan must be safe.
No?
You think the police and their flimsy tape
can stop the crocodiles?
-No.
-This river is their home.
If someone tries to invade your home,
your life, that too on the basis of a lie…
nobody will tolerate it.
I’ve told Lallan
so many times,
"Take off your slippers before coming in."
This soil is from the jungles of Rajgir.
The same place
from where I sourced that snake long ago.
The one that bit my whole family
and killed everyone.
Lallan must’ve told you about it, right?
Did you know, Raniji?
My chacha betrayed my father
when they were business partners.
He stole his entire business.
So you know what?
I finished off his entire family.
I cannot stand betrayals,
I’m a bit fragile.
I loved you with devotion
and all the right intentions
with all my heart.
And how did you
treat me?
I did not feed the snake
for four whole days.
So, hungry and angry,
when the snake eventually bites,
the fangs go that much deeper.
Chances of survival next to zero.
If we are able to control a human
or a beast by their nature,
they end up turning into a puppet.
Ah!
Abhimanyu!
Don’t you dare touch Rani!
Okay, come on,
tell me one last thing, Raniji.
Did you ever, for even a single moment,
think that we could be together?
Yes.
I did.
Maybe some other time…
Maybe some other place…
If Rishu wasn’t a part of my life, then…
maybe it could've been us.
Okay then.
You, me
and my rosy pink Taj Mahal, that’s enough.
Life is great,
but the love of my life has another date.
But that’s okay, Raniji.
This color also suits you very well.
I mean, if a couple of your lovers
aren’t six feet under,
can you even really call this place
the City of Love?
Do you know, Raniji?
There is one more thing that connects us.
Panditji’s words.
Your life is an adaptation
of Wrath of Kasauli,
while mine is inspired
by The Revenge of the Cobra.
Both of us used Panditji's pen
to write our destinies, Raniji.
You really seem to have met your match.
All that remains to be seen
is who is the bigger fan of Panditji.
The day I saw you at the clinic,
the first thing that caught my eye was,
in these soft, silky hands,
was Panditji’s book.
Then came the sky-blue dupatta,
the rose-pink kameez,
then these eyes,
and by the time I reached your lips,
I was already in love.
Help! Help! Help!
Help!
Help! My husband’s going to kill me.
Please, please help me.
My husband wants to kill me. Please.
Sir, I'm trying to tell them
since a long time
that my husband wants to kill me.
Trust me, Abhimanyu is
a really dangerous man.
He killed his whole family
using a plot from Panditji's book.
He’s a real psycho.
He’ll going to kill me--
Looks like this phrase
suits you right now,
“birds of a feather flock together.”
Are you even listening to what I’m saying?
-If you don’t catch him, if it’s too--
-So what?
He's out for blood, sir.
You’re safe here,
listening to philosophies of life.
Who is he going to kill?
Rishu.
Who?
Pranaam, Elder Brother.
Didn’t I tell you that
whoever killed our Neel…
I will drag them
and throw them at your feet?
I’ll call you back in some time.
Wow!
I must admit.
The lover is extraordinary,
the madam is such a cutie.
They are a thing of ultimate beauty.
Gajab!
Come on then,
let's go and grab both of madam’s…
husbands.
Okay, sir.
What, sir?
Come on.
Chriraunji!
DINESH PANDIT
Great!
Finally, even Panditji makes his entry.
Hmm…
Okay, sir.
Hmm!
Hello?
Mm-hmm.
Sir, we have new information.
Hmm.
You remember how your lover looks, right?
See him one last time. Come on.
Hurry up!
A patrol party is arriving in ten minutes.
Contact Chandni Chawk
police storeroom. Over.
Whom does this belong to, Raniji?
SAHNI CLINIC -
NAME: ABHIMANYU
Ab… Ab… Abhimanyu.
Rani Kashyap.
We have reasonable suspicion on you
for the double murder of Poonam Prajapati
and Abhimanyu Bharadwaj.
But I didn’t kill them.
And I’ll have to ask her again…
Where is Rishu Saxena?
Come on.
Ah!
I can’t find one husband,
and lovers are queuing up for her.
Snow White and the not so better halves.
Meenaji.
So, as per law, for how many hours
can we hold her up in custody?
Law says within 24 hours, we have
to present her in front of the magistrate.
Meenaji, you were
on your way to the court with Raniji,
but, unfortunately…
you sprained your ankle, you were in pain.
Then you sat in the car,
but the tire was flat. Hmm?
You reached the court,
but it was too late.
The court was adjourned. Then came Sunday.
-So, when will you take her to court now?
-On Monday, sir.
On Monday.
Sir!
And, listen,
don't forget
to take Mr. Discipline with you.
And do make very good use of him.
Hmm?
Sir.
You like to spit a lot of lies, don’t you?
But today, you’ll only spit blood.
Panditji says, “Bury me,
drown me, burn me alive,
but don’t let oppressors break my spirit.
This single belief can help love survive."
There's one more thing I need to share.
Go, tell this to Montu chacha as well.
If Rishu finds out
that you ever laid a hand on me,
then the man who didn’t hesitate
to cut his hand off for me
will cut your throat--
Wow! I love this passion.
Divine lovers!
-Hey, listen.
-Yes, sir.
Sir.
Speak to your media friends and tell them
that Madam is being thrashed in custody.
Thrashed real bad.
But be careful.
-Nothing official or on the record.
-Sir.
Sir, thrashing in custody
doesn’t seem right.
If the media finds out about it,
they’d blow it out of proportion.
That's exactly what I want.
Agra Police
have broken all possible limits,
protocols and boundaries.
We have confirmed news.
Agra police, in an attempt
to cover up their own incompetence,
have arrested
double murder-accused Rani Kashyap,
who was the prime suspect
few months ago in another case.
She is being beaten up inside the lockup
before being presented in court.
If something happens to Rani Kashyap,
who will be held responsible for that?
Chriraunji! Chriraunji!
I, Rishabh Saxena, willingly surrender
to the police for the crimes I committed.
I have one condition.
I want Rani to be present at the time
and at the place of my surrender.
She should be able to walk
on her own two feet
and come to me alone so that I am assured
Rani is safe and sound.
Only then
will I surrender myself to the police,
three days from today at 8 in the evening,
on the railway bridge.
-Jai Hind, sir.
-Hmm.
I want a detailed recce
of the entire area.
-Yes, sir.
-Hmm.
And tell these forest department officials
to get out of here.
There are
crocodiles under the bridge--
Nobody except the police
should be allowed on this spot.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Tomorrow night at 8,
a train will cross the railway bridge.
We’re gonna stop it.
Our force will be divided into two units.
As soon as we see Rishu
on the railway bridge,
we’ll start forming a perimeter.
Doesn't all this seem a bit too easy?
I don’t think it’s a good idea
to give in to Rishu’s demands
and let Rani go on the bridge by herself.
Rishu wants to play the game of chess,
but he’s up against a grand master.
According to his plan,
when Rani will walk alone on the bridge
a small police unit
will surround them from all sides.
They’ll be at our gunpoint from above
and death swims in the water below.
They’ll flap their wings,
they’ll poke their beaks,
but finally…
those lovebirds will end up
exactly where they belong.
Gajab!
Move it.
Meena!
Team B standby.
Wait for my command, alright?
Rishu! Rishu! Rishu!
You can't surrender. I won’t let you.
We’ll run away. We’ll run away.
Move in. I repeat, move in.
-Seal the bridge
-Yes, sir.
Rani…
-Arey, where is he going?
-Who is he?
Someone
is breaking the siege and moving ahead.
Who is this idiot? He’ll spoil our plans.
The one who learned how to break
the chakravyuh in his mother's womb.
We have the DNA report, sir.
Sample does not match with the body.
Nobody move an inch.
I repeat, nobody move an inch.
Get everyone ready.
But wait for my orders.
Sir, ask everyone there to stay put.
It won’t take me more than a second
to blow their brains out.
Abhimanyu, you cannot escape.
You have been surrounded by the police.
Come on, put the gun down,
and we’ll talk, okay?
I haven't come here to chat with you, sir.
I stand here for myself
and all those who are always left behind,
the betrayed ones.
The ones who've been scorched
and burned by love.
Love doesn’t leave anyone behind.
Love gives you wings and sets you free.
I’m not interested in your poetry.
I loved you with all my heart,
didn't I, Raniji?
I told you the tragic story of my life.
I even showed you the beautiful, pink
Taj Mahal that we could see from my roof.
I laid my beating heart
out in front of you.
You could have told me the truth.
I never stopped you.
On top of that, you had the guts
to go ahead and report me to the police.
I warned you
before as well, Raniji,
I simply can't deal with betrayal.
Aah!
Ah!
Rishu!
Rani.
Rani, no.
Drop the gun.
-Ah!
-Rani!
Rani, give me your hand.
Difficult times seem to be
a never-ending story for the Agra Police.
This accident took place
as Rishu Saxena was about to surrender.
And Rishu and Rani
have drowned in the Yamuna river
which is plagued with crocodiles.
As per reports, a third unidentified man
fell into the river as well.
It remains to be seen if this case,
which has become
a festering wound for the UP police,
would rip the system apart.
Sir, this is the end of their chapter?
A new chapter has just begun, my friend.
-Initiate the search operation.
-Yes, sir.
NEW TWIST IN RISHU SAXENA SURRENDER
SNAKE KILLS ENTIRE FAMILY
♪ In what she says ♪
♪ And what you see ♪
♪ Far from these, you will find ♪
♪ The hidden truth ♪
♪ Pieces of truth ♪
♪ Fragments of lies ♪
♪ Have merged together ♪
♪ To form a broken image ♪
♪ To pick and choose ♪
♪ To reweave each thread anew… ♪
FOREST DEPARTMENT
♪ To reweave each thread anew ♪
♪ Once you see through the web of lies ♪
♪ You will gain clarity ♪
♪ And the truth will set you free ♪
♪ And the truth will set you free… ♪
Abhimanyu, Rishu, Rani,
their houses, office, clinic, parlor,
all areas around these properties,
whatever is being captured,
be it on laptops,
or CCTVs, or even phones,
-I want all the footage, understand?
-Okay, sir.
♪ What can and cannot be ♪
♪ Lie in the realm of darkness ♪
♪ While the dim light reveals
Countless stories ♪
♪ Why does the mind strive ♪
♪ To clear these webs? ♪
♪ Once you see through the web of lies ♪
♪ You will gain clarity ♪
♪ The truth will set you free ♪
♪ The truth will set you free… ♪
Kishoreji, would you like me
to tell you a story?
POLICE STATION DISTRICT - AGRA
This indigestion
is a really dangerous thing, sir.
People think it’s a petty little illness,
and we binge on digestives to cure it.
But sometimes…
This could be a symptom of a much larger,
underlying issue like cancer.
This case is just like indigestion, sir.
We look for something,
find something else,
and the reality is totally different.
What are you trying to say?
Sir, if Rani, Rishu
and Abhimanyu are actually dead,
who is the one
benefiting the most from this?
Rani.
Rishu.
And Abhimanyu, right?
What do you mean?
Because the thing is, sir,
if they were alive,
they would have been
behind bars right now.
Rani was in there all along.
Rishu would be sentenced
for the murder of Neel.
And Abhimanyu?
For the murder of his family.
SNAKE KILLS FAMILY
So Abhimanyu was actually
being blackmailed by a man named Lallan.
Lallan is the same snake catcher
who helped Abhimanyu kill
all his family members.
When the double murder happened,
the same morning, Lallan went
to the clinic to meet Abhimanyu.
We got this footage from an ATM
across the street from the clinic.
Dead.
The second dead body was Poonam’s.
Poonam went to the clinic
that day to meet Rishu.
She knew what he had been hiding.
She too was killed.
Perfect victims.
And our dear compounder Abhimanyuji
topped his class in biology.
So he knew how to burn those bodies,
how to fake their identities,
place items in such a way that
they could not be identified easily.
But the plot thickens a lot more, sir.
Thanks to an unnoticed camera
at Bobby's garage,
we found some more footage.
According to the footage,
Rani and Abhimanyu came back home
at around 7 in the evening.
And then, exactly 15 minutes later,
someone was seen entering
Abhimanyu’s house that day.
Rishu.
And maybe that evening
among the three of them,
a plan was discussed.
Because after that,
at 10 in the night,
Raniji, portraying herself
as a damsel in distress,
was seen running in the rain.
Help! Help!
Please, please help me,
my husband wants to kill me.
And the interesting thing is that, sir,
after Rani left the house,
two more people were seen leaving
from Abhimanyu’s house.
Rishu and Abhimanyu.
That's why I’m convinced, sir…
on that night…
a conspiracy was surely hatched.
So you're saying their plan was
to jump from the bridge
into the river
while everyone was watching them?
But there were crocodiles below.
They would’ve died.
What kind of a plan is this?
That is the mystery, sir.
One question still haunts me today,
why did Rishu
specifically choose the railway bridge?
That’s not the mystery.
That’s the whole case.
Montu…
Sir.
I know you were
personally invested in this.
But let it go now.
Media is pressurizing us a lot.
Close this case file without any delay.
Because, the more you try to dig,
the more this department
will be scrutinized.
Sir, sir, we can't close
this case yet again.
Please, all I’m asking is
for is a little more time, sir. Sir!
Arey, yaar!
Closing the case file
doesn’t mean the case is closed.
We both know that.
No matter how deep you bury the truth,
the truth will come back to haunt you.
And don’t forget…
after all, you’re The Woodpecker.
Hmm?
SIX MONTHS LATER
Rishu! Rishu!
Rishu!
-Raniji!
-Rishu!
Raniji! Raniji! Raniji!
Good evening.
No. This isn't how you spell it.
What happened? Everything all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Just a little tired, that’s all.
-Alright, you finish these, I’ll be back.
-Okay, ma'am.
-You want some water?
-No, thanks.
We’re late.
Hope class hasn't started.
SHARDA PRIMARY SCHOOL, DEOSAR
Okay,
so now I want all of you to submit
your homework notebooks here on my desk.
-Okay?
-Okay, ma'am.
-Ma'am.
-Very good.
Ma'am.
-Have you completed your homework?
-Yes, ma'am.
CHAKIA, BIHAR
Listen,
did you order something?
A book was delivered just now.
There's a photo
of a crocodile on the front cover.
THE CROCODILE'S TRAP
DINESH PANDIT
"Only three copies
of this book have been printed.
And you are reading one of them."
"Suraj and Arjun made a decision.
If they had to escape
from the clutches of the police,
they would have to jump
right into the jaws of the crocodiles.
They finally managed to find a place
which was full of
blood-thirsty crocodiles.
And the plan to protect themselves
from these crocodiles
began three days before the incident."
FIRST NIGHT
Rishuji, do you know why
in Panditji’s book
Suraj and Arjun
gradually increased the amount of meat
that they fed to the crocodiles
on a daily basis?
So that they remain a little hungry
and force the crocodiles to think
the farther away they go…
the more meat they can eat.
We need to distract them
from the railway bridge.
That is why we will drop the meat
two kilometers away from here.
SECOND NIGHT
THIRD NIGHT
A 12-kilometre area
all around the bridge is clear.
And the place where we decide to get out
of the water is completely up to us.
Tomorrow, when you tell Raniji
to jump, will she agree?
Definitely.
Is your trust in your love that deep?
I’m trusting you as well.
I know you love my Rani so much
that you wouldn’t hesitate
for a second to get rid of me.
But the real question is,
why haven’t you done it yet?
It's because I'd rather have Raniji
come willingly into my arms someday.
-Now. Okay? Hmm?
-Yes.
"If you found
the story interesting,
wait until you reach the climax.
Come to Tota-Maina Lovers Point.
Deosar, Himachal Pradesh,
on 20th March, 6 in the evening."
Remember, you need to walk
at least 30 minutes every day, okay?
Thank you, Doctor sahab.
"Tota-Maina
Lovers Point, at 6."
Baap re!
That’s a long way down,
right?
Just be careful.
Panditji says,
“Red signifies jealousy and anger,
blood too is red.
Perhaps it's apt that red signifies love.“
Panditji.
Isn't it a bloody unfaithful color?
But just one thing
brings red into my life now.
The rose adorning your hair.
-The thing is, it’s turned black now.
-What?
Your red rose, it’s turned black now.
Raniji, come here first
and then we’ll talk.
One more step…
and I’ll jump off the cliff.
Raniji…
Rishu was right all along,
I didn’t believe him.
Killing someone
has become a game for you, isn't it?
Lallan, Poonam, huh?
They were never a part of our plan, right?
Raniji, Lallan and Poonam
were risky for us.
Life gave me a golden opportunity
to forget the mistakes of the past
and start a new life with you
and I grabbed it with both hands.
Just for you.
Tell me one thing honestly.
We are… Were you ever happy with me?
I was. I was really happy.
Then, Raniji, because of a few mistakes,
ple… please don’t do this.
I’ll pay the price for all my sins,
but, Raniji, please…
Please don’t jump off,
what are you doing?
-Come back here.
-Arey, just stop this drama.
If she was really going to jump off,
she wouldn’t have sent me an invite.
Tell me, Raniji,
why have you called me here?
So that both of us
end this chase once and for all.
Both of us have used Panditji’s pen
to write the pages of our destiny, Raniji.
Rishu! Ah!
-Rani! Rani!
-Raniji!
-Rani!
Rani!
Raniji!
-Rani!
-Raniji!
Raniji!
Now if we want to live,
the world needs to see us die.
"The Crocodile's Trap."
Dinesh Pandit?
Rani…
That's impossible.
We are not going to repeat this madness.
Rani, please try to understand
what I’m saying.
I’ve known Montu chacha
since I was a kid.
If he finds out we're alive, he'll drag us
from the depths of hell and lock us up.
And your plan is
to take a shortcut straight to hell
by following a ridiculous plan
from this book. No way, Rishu. No.
And the things we’ve already done?
The Revenge of the Cobra,
Wrath of Kasauli.
The three of us lost our senses long ago
when we became Panditji’s disciples.
There is a difference, sir.
Panditji’s books taught us how to live,
but you ended up learning
how to take lives.
That’s the difference.
Yes.
Over there.
Rishu! Rishu! Rishu!
-Rishu!
-Raniji!
Rishu!
-Rishu!
Rishu! Rishu!
-Raniji!
Rishu!
-Rishu!
-Raniji!
Raniji! Raniji! Raniji!
Rishu!
Rishu.
Ri…
Raniji.
Was killing Rishu
the only choice you had?
You killed someone as well
for the sake of love.
What did I do that is so wrong?
I did the same thing
you and Rishu once did.
Is it fair to say
the murder you committed was love
and the one I committed was wrong?
You don’t even know the meaning of love.
You never really loved me, you know that?
-No, please--
-All you did
was play a game
of snakes and ladders with our lives.
You…
I made a huge mistake.
Okay.
Let me tell you one more truth, Abhimanyu.
I never thought I could be happy living
my life with anyone else other than Rishu.
But after that incident…
I thought you are the one.
I could feel there was
something special between us.
Something.
I never thought you'd betray me.
And this betrayal is something
even I won’t be able to live with.
I made a mistake, Raniji.
So, now your punishment is…
that you can never have me.
You might have won me over…
but you can never win against me.
-Raniji, no, wait!
-Raniji.
Raniji!
Raniji! Raniji!
Send the search
and rescue team right away.
Abhimanyuji, let's go.
There is a lot of red
accounted for in your ledger.
Poonam Prajapati, Lallan Barua,
Ashok Bharadwaj and family,
Rishabh Saxena.
And maybe…
Rani Kashyap, too.
Take him away.
…are requested to board
the aircraft from gate number two.
Sir, we searched everywhere
but could not find the body.
What happened, sir?
Couldn’t find the body?
"Compared to the glow
on your face,
everything else just seems dull.
You’ve now become an idol
in my heart’s sacred temple."
♪ Once upon a time,
There was a beauty ♪
♪ And her crazy lover ♪
♪ It was a magical age ♪
♪ A magical ambience ♪
♪ It was a magical world ♪
♪ Once upon a time, there was a beauty ♪
♪ There was a beauty ♪
♪ And her crazy lover ♪
♪ It was a magical age ♪
♪ A magical ambience
It was a magical world…♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
Panditji says,
"Relations are maintained
within the boundaries of right and wrong.
But true love can blossom
only beyond these constructs."
I was the one who taught them that.
To live peacefully
one needs to die in the eyes of the world,
but they used it on me.
It wasn’t you, it was your father.
The Crocodile's Trap,
Dinesh Pandit.
Arey, sir,
how did you figure out…
that Panditji is my father?
Gajab!