A tree which is not be seen in the entire   landmass.
Grows in our Seshachalam  forest
Cargo worth billions gets smuggled to overseas from here
This is gold. Gold which grows on land.
Red Sandalwood
Where did you hide cargo? Speak out.
My boss wouldn’t spare me if I blurted it out.
Who is your boss.
Do you like me.
Looks like you’ve been anxious because I didn’t see you.
Anxious.
It's easy to blabber sitting on the banks,
Subtitle By Alam_Brothers1
You’d know the depth only once you step into the water.
This world had given you  a gun.
It's given me an axe.
Everyone has his own battles.
Pushpa
Pushparaj...
Thaggedhe Le
Pushpa isn’t flower,
It's fire!
When is the party,Pushpa?