Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
This story begins in Japan
where the sun rises first on the earth
This is a rich Japanese wedding...
It’s a custom here for groom to gift something to bride
This is not about Japanese wedding or their customs
Do you see that violin? It is about this.
It's costs is eight lakhs...
The reason is, it is made of seldom available wood
You will not find this wood anywhere around here.
But, it must be smuggled from China by sea.
Shanghai port, China.
That wood was transported by this ship.
It came from Chennai travelling thousands of miles.
They were loaded onto ships by these lorries
The place in the world where we can find red sandalwood...
Seshachalam forest, Rayalaseema.
Surprisingly this plant doesn't grow
anywhere else than here on the earth.
That is the reason why it costs so much.
This is the gold growing on earth,
it's name is red sandalwood
This red sandalwood is being smuggled abroad from here.
Truthfully this story is not about Redsandal wood
It's about a labourer who became
a part of smuggling syndicate
Are you wondering what is a labourer?
Don't take him lite
A guy like you and me would be everywhere,
but a guy like him is rare like the red sandalwood.
You are escaping right in front of police...
Who are you?
Get down.. get down...
get down.
We have met after long time.
How you doing?
Hope you are doing good.
That’s ok.
Why trouble between us.
I will give you Ten thousand.
Will you leave me?
Ten Thousand.
Bribe? Are you trying to bribe
Tamilnadu Police Is It?
Sir, he's trying to bribe us ten thousand, sir.
Twenty Thousand!
Thirty thousand!
Forty thousand!
Fifty thousand!
One Lakh!
I meant is one lakh per head
What I’m saying is one lakh per head.
Brother... Are you Tamil?
What is your name?
Pushpa!
Hardcore Telugu
Everyone’s story starts with his birth.
But my story has begin after I met him.
Don’t stay there gossiping
while you go and have tea.
Come fast. We have lots of work. OK?
Who is he? Is he your Son in law...
sitting as if he owns the place.
My Name is Kesava... this is the first time I've met Pushpa
Who is that guy? Sitting cross legged?
Hey... what is this?
How can you sit cross legged,
when owner is asking..?
Don’t you have manners?
What?
This leg is mine and this leg is mine...
and i kept my leg on my leg.
Did I put my leg on the owner or what?
Does he want me to work or give him respect?
You must change your behaviour
if you want to work here.
You cant behave as you want
Is it so?
It’s not possible to change my behavior
so how about changing the owner
Give me my wages
I will leave.
This is enough for what I have done.
Give this to your owner and ask him to go
and buy manners in the market if available.
Hold this!
This fellow will either rule the world or go to dogs.
Hey... Where are you going?
I’m also changing the owner.
- I want to see what he becomes.
- Where are you going?
Hey Parvatamma.
How many days will you escape like this?
I gave you money during last Ganga fair.
Forget the principle,
till now you haven’t even paid the interest.
Didn’t I tell you Reddappa that I will pay back next month?
You are postponing every month saying next month.
How many times should I come to your house?
Shameless people... Shameless people.
Reddappa. Don’t shout.
The whole Village is listening.
I am shouting so that everyone can listen.
At least then they will feel ashamed and repay.
She is a widow. Is that the way to talk to her.
widow? So what?
She has a son as grown as a buffalo at home.. right.
Isn’t he a man? Doesn’t he have hands and legs?
No Reddappa, My boy has joined for work in the mill.
He will pay whatever he earns month after month to you.
What will he repay?
Everyone in the village know that
your son has left the work long time back.
What is this son?
Is Reddappa telling the truth?
Have you really left work at the mill?
How will we survive without work.
I am asking you.
Listen Parvatamma. Forget this.
I will come tomorrow morning.
I want you to repay every penny,
If not, this time I will not shout
standing in front of your house...
will do it from your roof top I will shout in front of everyone.
Drink... Neither son is listening nor the buffalo.
Principle Three thousand and
Interest Three thousand six hundred.
Total Six thousand six hundred.
The account is settled. bye.
Glad that your account is settled.
How about mine?
Your Account? What account?
Entire village got to know that we have took a loan from you.
Now, Shouldn’t all of them know that we have repaid?
Isn’t it simple?
Hello Gurappa, Venkatadri Pushpa has repaid his loan.
Ok I take leave now
Yesterday there were so many people at the Ration Shop.
Who will tell all of them?
What do you say now?
Gurappa get me the list of Who all were there yesterday?
A total of 106 people were there.
Pakala Ravi
Chalapathi
Munemma!
hey.. Stop.
Do you expecting me to inform all of them now?
I won’t.
Kondal Rayudu!
Listen Kondalrayudu... Pushpa has repaid his entire loan.
- Has he repaid?
- Yes. He has repaid the entire loan
Bainapalli Subbalakshmi, Batyala Alivelu...
Pushpa has repaid his entire loan.
Pushpa... Inform Venkata Subbamma also.
She is leaving for Dubai in the evening.
- Hundred rupees work...
- Thousand rupees work.
I have to go... I will pay money evening.
Come fast.. Thousand rupees work.
What is this hundred-rupees work?
And what is thousand rupees work?
This is legal, so Hundred rupees only.
That is illegal. More money and more risk...
Thousand rupees work... Thousand rupees work.
Come fast.. Thousand rupees work.
Hundred rupees work... Hundred rupees work.
Hey... why are you going that side? If we go that side,
there is no surety that we will come back home by evening.
I don’t have much work in the evening anyway.
So I’m going.
Stop... Stop... vehicle stop.
Get on to the vehicle... come on...
Hey... please let our parents know
if I am not coming back.
Hey, get down quickly.
Move on... move on...
Move!
Move... move...
To hell with this rain!
Get going.
Hey, come fast.
Quickly... we need to cross over the hill till the evening.
- Bro, Is this your first time?
- Yeah bro.
What's your name?
Will they pay us after the work is done?
Where are you all going?
We put in so much effort to flick this,
and you want to hand over it to the police just like that?
I have an idea.
Come here, I will tell you.
Taskforce DSP Govindappa!
He's nightmare for Red sandal smugglers
After he took charge,
coolies realised that life more important than money
If anyone has to cut the trees or smuggle the goods out of
the forest it can be only after he takes a nap.
Ey.. What are you people doing here?
We came to graze the sheep... sheep
Where are the sheep then?
Sheep have gone into the forest to graze...
How many sheep are you grazing?
How many sheep do we have?
around two hundred I guess.
We will have two hundred sir.
What work does Shepherds have with the axe?
They came to graze the sheep
and I came to kill the tiger if it comes...
Hey... Is this the way to speak to DSP sir?
Don’t you have manners??
of course, we have respect, that’s why we hid the logs.
Otherwise, we would have moved them out
of the forest in front of you.
Then you would have really lost respect?
Hey what are you staring at?
Tiger is caught. Wrap it!
Don’t act smart? Where are goods?
Where are goods?
I thought you are man who came to catch the goods
Didn't know you came to catch whatever come in your way.
Hello Sir.
You have just 6 bullets.
I have sixty axes around me.
We will OUTNUMBER you.
Sir, Look at their faces.
They are all looking like rouges.
Not now.
We will come back again.
He is giving good advice.
If you listen to him, it will do good for all of us.
I plead you sir... please come back sir.
They are strong only when they are in the forest...
Where can they go, sir.
Let's go sir...
we will nab them when they come out.
Look like they will take out the hidden stock in front of us.
We will lose our respect it that happens, Lets go sir.
Leaf lives on Sunlight to grow
The Goat eats away leaves to be alive
And a tiger hunts goat to survive
Isn’t it the power of Hunger?
The tiger perishes in death
the death dissolves in time
And the time surrenders before Kali
This is a great hunger
The hunted knows it should run faster
And the hunter knows he should outrun his prey
If the hunted wins, it will live another day
And the hunter knows, it should win to survive
Life for one
May mean death for another
Goat has to find a place to hide
if it doesn’t want to be the next lunch of the tiger
A Worm is a bait to catch fish
Grains are used to trap the bird
A piece of Meat can lure the dog into danger Survival is the hook for human beings
In the festival to please a god
Chicken and sheep gets killed
The knife gets smeared with blood
And even a goddess can’t escape from a bait
This is the fate of the world
If you are not alert, the bait will catch you
You can only survive if you have a hunger to gobble the bait
A hungry man can’t see right or wrong
Only the fittest will survive here
Goat has to find a place to hide
if it doesn’t want to be the next lunch of the tiger
Somireddy-21 kilogram
Okay bro.
It is the same wage that I paid last time also
Go...
Jayachandrudu-28 KG
Take what I paid for and leave.
Brother. I will be with you.
What?
I will be with you brother.
What do I have with me, except this beedi.
Who are you?
Missing finger.
My real name is Kesava.
Since I don’t have one finger,
everyone calls me missing finger.
What is the matter?
Brother, do you remember Muni Madhav
from that timber depot?
He said that you will become a great man.
Is that so?
I somehow want to earn lot of money
and go back to my village.
I think I can earn fast if I’m with you.
what? so you want me to become
a great man for your sake.. uh?
I thought of myself.
But you will become big.
How much do you want to earn?
Ten Lakhs
That's it?
Ok, go fetch my wages of Thousand rupees
Okay Brother.
Hey missing finger, Didn’t you collect your money already?
Why did you come again?
Not for me. I came for Pushpa’s wages.
I have loaded his log just now.
Pushpa? Who is he?
There.. that guy sitting cross legged under
the tree, and smoking a beedi.
He is a coolie him self.
And you are his coolie is it?
He could be sitting under a tree today,
The day he gets an opportunity he will rule the country.
Remember that.
- Get lost you coolie fellow.
- Hey police.
Hey useless fellows...
You have twenty guns and forty bullets around you.
We will OUTNUMBER you.
No one will survive even if one person moves.
Stay where you are.
Hey, throw
Come on... throw.
Hey, they coming closer... throw it.
Run.. run... run...
If you are caught by police
no one will come to save you.
I've pinned all my hopes on you.
Police are attacking from all sides
Run away from here.
Stop it... Stop
Where is the Lorry?
What sir?
Why do you always catch my collar and not the goods?
Lets go to the station and talk...
It's hot here.
I won’t move my leg.
You go.
Where is the lorry? speak!
Speak, speak out!
Water...
He made the Lorry disappear right in front of our eyes.
Searched everywhere.
But couldn't find the lorry
Not for me Sir.
Give it to him.
He is so tired of beating me.
Poor guy.
Drink Sir.
Where did you hide the goods tell now...?
My boss won’t spare me if I tell you.
Boss?
Who is that?
Who else? It’s me only.
No one is born in Chittoor district,
who can tell me...
not yet.
you call yourself Boss.
And you are laughing?
Laughing...
You have no respect for Police...
laugh...
- Are you the boss?
- Sir!
I know how to stop his laugh Sir.
What is your name boy?
We need to file the case, right?
What’s your name?
Pushpa!
What’s your full name?
Pushpa...
Pushparaju...
Then what’s your Surname?
Surname? Don’t know?
One that is written in front of the name.
I’m asking what is it?
Don’t know?
What are you thinking?
We all have it.
Don’t you have one?
Surname?
Why are you not talking?
Tell
Silence!
Boy... What is your name?
Pushparaju
What is your Surname?
Molleti...
- Molleti...
- Molleti Pushparaju
What is your father’s name?
Molleti Venkata ramana...
What is this?
Will you just write whatever anyone says?
Won’t you verify the details?
Just because my father visited their house
few times, will our surname become theirs?
Can’t you differentiate kids born out of wedlock
and the ones born to a mistress?
Surname belongs to the ones born legally...
not to hybrid fellows.
Rey... Come here.
What is your name?
Molleti Pushparaju!
Just because my father slept with your mother,
you can’t inherit our surname.
You don’t have a surname.
Your name is just Pushparaju.
Pushparaju.
Now say, what is your name?
Pushparaju!
Say loudly so that everyone can hear.
What is this brother?
They have beaten you so badly
Won’t they beat if you hide the Lorry?
Am feeling hungry.
Let’s talk while eating
What is this? Look at all those injuries.
Hey, be quiet.
Go man...
Brother, what is there to eat.
Subbanna...
Jakkareddy, Jollyreddy brothers are coming
These are red sandal smugglers...
Brothers of Konda Reddy.
Konda Reddy brothers are three.
Third one is Jaali Reddy
Unless he feels the feminine air,
he will not be able to breath.
If his eyes falls on any girl,
he make sure that se will loss her virginity.
It doesn't matter whom the girl marries,
she has to spent her first night with Jaali reddy.
Brother...
Obulu is very lucky that
Jalli Brother has gifted 5000 rupees to his marriage.
Second one Jakka Reddy...
Amongst the three he's the one with brains.
He takes care of the whole business.
He is big support to Kondareddy.
He is Kondareddy, the eldest brother.
he is a factionist
In the riots at Siddhavatam,
he chased six of them and slayed them.
Believes in only Revenge over life
so threw a bomb at them.
After that he takes care of the
whole business with his single hand.
If the police caught us, I thought no body will come to save us.
but now I see the owners themselves have turned up.
Now I understood what Pushpa has planned.
Hope all is well...
I am fine but...
Heard that you didn’t tell them whose goods
they are, even after police torturing you badly.
Looks like you have a lot of spunk.
Bro...
Their salary is less than 5 thousand per month.
What will I get if I tell them?
A broken beedi .. but you are different...
Are you asking money to tell where it is...
Coolie fellow...
Jaali?
How much do you want?
You can’t give me what I want.
just, give me five lakhs
Five lakhs!
Who will give him 5 lakhs?
If we give him some nice thrashing,
he will reveal everything...
What is that laugh?
This guy was laughing like this the whole night
40 Laathis broke, but the laugh didn’t go away...
finally we got fed up and stopped.
My thrashing will be different.
Jaali, first let him tell the stock whereabouts
You stay silent.
Okay!
I will pay the money you want.
Tell me where the goods are
You won’t understand if I say, let me show you...
See.. my hands are cuffed...
How can I show like this..?
He is asking us get him a bail...
Did you get it?
Looks like your brother is smarter than you...
anyways pay for what I ate and call a lawyer.
Hey Jaali
Are you telling us, just because we are not doing anything.
Do you know who are you speaking to?
Konda Reddy Brothers.
I will kill you and burry you.
Then who will tell you where the goods are?
Konda Reddy?
What is this? Why did he bring us here?
can see only fields around.
Rey, looks like these coolie fellows sat in a car
for the first time.. go open the door
Brother, door is struck.
It’s not opening...
What’s the hurry?
- That's how you door opens?
- This way!
Where is the lorry, Bro?
I see nothing but a well here.
What is this? Why did you destroy the Lorry
so badly, it is of no use now.
Bro, give us the money, our money
Hey, give them the money.
Here is 5 lakhs...
go and enjoy with your brother.
have fun...
Never seen so much money bro...
Can repay all debts and
bring the buffalo back home.
Whoever had said it, said it right.
‘if I am with you, I can make 10 lakhs just like that brother.
Hey Where are you coming?
I don’t have the habit of sticking to the women once I use her.
Take this hundred and come in an Auto Rickshaw
Come bro. We have an auto here.
Hey Driver... will you drop us at Rangampet..?
What will be the price of that vehicle?
You mean, that Car... bro?
Ya...
It should be around 5 lakhs bro
Does that car cost 5 lakhs!
Isn’t it too expensive.
Yes Brother.
Go and buy that car.
Bro...
What are you talking bro?
We came here in a car when we didn’t have a penny on us.
Would it look good to go in an Auto
when we have so much money?
Go and get that car
Brother, please understand. If we buy the car,
all the money will be spending on the car.
We won’t have anything left with us.
Then we will have to go and work for daily wages again.
And will we go for daily wage work in a car or what?
Hey, I came here in car,
and I will leave only in a car from here.
Till then I won’t move from here.
Listen to me Bro...
Hey... I will not budge an inch in this matter.
Hey, who is that honking?
Do you think your mother owns this road?
Roll down the window.
I want to see who the hell you are...
It’s me. Your son from the hell...
Oh, is that you... Pushpa
What are those injuries on your body?
You are seeing the small, small injuries on my body,
but can’t see the big car in front of you.
What kind of work are you doing..?
Whose car is this?
It is Parvathamma’s...
Which Parvathamma?
Pushpa’s mother.
That’s me.
Then, It’s your car.
But, I can’t understand how you bought this car.
Seeing your difficulty in fetching water,
Brother bought this car for you.
- Who the hell are you?
- Keshava Aunty.
Pushpa, why did you bring me here?
Whose car is this Maa?
Hey wait!
Uncle?
Daddy.. Uncle has bought the car
The one who buys a car becomes car owner... not your uncle.
Come in
Did you see that car, Mohan?
Where did he get so much money to buy?
What else can you expect from a ragpicker?
Obviously through stealth.
Hey looks like Mangalam Seenu Brother
has come. Go and see.
Brother, Namasthe...
Namasthe, Namasthe
Bro, just by spending five lakhs,
I am not only got a car, am also getting respect with it.
why are you staring like that, man?
Jakkareddy bro called us. So we came in our car.
Sit Bro... Now we are qualified to sit here.
don’t want, again have to stand up
when Konda Reddy comes.
I can’t give so much respect to him.
True, bro.
How many loads?
Around 12 loads, Brother
How could you guys go and surrender
3 crores worth of stock to DSP Govindappa?
Don’t we have anyone who can transport
the load by hoodwinking Govindappa?
He is catching us in whichever way we go.
It is not possible to send a load when he is around.
It’s crazy why you are over-praising Govindappa here.
Like a restless lady who throws in the towel with her neighbor.
Leave it - its all beyond your ability.
Who the hell is he?
He is a coolie fellow.
What the hell, Just because you came in a car
you think you earned a right to speak in this meeting.
Get out...
Brother, he is the same guy whom we got out on bail, Pushpa.
I only asked him to come along.
Are you the one who hid our load
and collected five lakhs from us?
Five lakhs are not for hiding the load Sir.
It’s for protecting you and your brothers from going to jail.
As if you don’t know...
it is not a big deal to get beaten by Police.
Speak if you have guts to transport the load without getting caught.
You need an idea for transporting the load.
Not guts...
Yes brother.
what our people are doing is...
Covering the load with Tomatoes and Watermelons.
They move the fruits, they see the load...
Forget Govindappa, Our load can be found
even by a useless Gurkha also.
We have to send the load but no one should know.
I have an idea. Should I tell?
You want to tell us how to transport the load.
Everyone See, who has come to give us ideas.
Coolie fellow.
say what you think. Say.. say...
Is this a pickle to share with the entire world?
Ideas brother...
how can I say it Infront of everyone...?
How dare you?
you are asking, us only to go out.
wait Jaali.
Hey!..I better like what you say...
if not this kondareddy will deal with you differently.
All of you go out.
Hey stop...
check him...
what sir.. Looks like you are suspecting me.
After your thrashing, I have stopped all old businesses
and started milk business now.
Yes Sir, We have taken contract with Kalahasthi Khova Shop
Yes Sir, there is milk only here sir.
we mixed water in the milk,
now don’t tell me you are going to arrest us for that also.
Let him go.
Give some Kalahasthi Khova to Sir.
We will go and come sir...
Where was he hiding all these days?
Give him... Give him all the load and
you be around to supervise.
I can do the complete the work all alone.
Just tell me what you will pay me.
your rate only Pushpa.
We will pay you what we paid last time...
5 lakhs per load. Is it Ok?
Five lakhs is not okay.
Give me 4 percent.
4 percent would mean 4 lakhs.
You will lose one lakh.
You can keep that one lakh to yourself,
just pay my 4 percent.
What is this bro?
He was willing to pay 5 lakhs...
One lakh is our loss.
If we had taken five lakhs, we would have been their servants.
By taking 4 percent, won’t we become his partners.?
Now, Kondareddy and we are Partners...
Partner Pushpa here.
You are very smart brother.
Hey, why is everyone looking at the sky like that?
Looking for the sparrows.
What?
For Sparrows
But... Why?
Bro... see that girl sitting there,
wearing a red saree?
That girl...
She says she won’t sell milk unless she hears a Sparrow.
With such a big work in hand,
what is this sparrow nonsense man?
Who is that mad girl?
It’s my daughter.
She doesn’t listen to anyone. Even mine.
I named her after my mother,
and she is just like her in everything
Hey, Srivalli... let's fill the milk into the tank.
You turn away both your eyes when I look at you
And cover your glances with your eyelids
You stare at even an invisible god without blinking an eye
But you are ignoring me when i’m in front of your eyes
Your looks have become as pricey as gold Srivalli
Your word has become as rare as a ruby
Your smile has become as precious as nine gems
What Sir? Why are you pawing with Lathis?
Its only milk, Sir!
What Sir? Can't we do business?
We are a reformed lot now.
Me, who used to lead in everything
Is following you wherever you go now
Me, who never bent my head before anyone
Has bent my head to look at your anklet
After having lived such a great life,
Am now making rounds of your house
And thought it's enough
even if you look at me for an instant
- Did She see?
- No bro...
Did you see properly?
I have seen brother.
She didn’t even see once.
I think you are very happy, right?
for what, bro?
because she didn’t see.
Why will I be happy bro?
No.. you are feeling happy, eating that peanut candy happily
and saying, she hasn’t looked even once.. I noticed it.
No bro, I’m feeling bad inside.
ok. She didn’t see.
What would you have lost if you had said, she saw once...
at lest I would have felt happy Isn’t it..?
I didn’t get that idea bro. Sorry bro...
You won’t get that idea.
Why will you get any idea that makes me happy?
Your looks have become as pricey as gold Srivalli
Your word has become as rare as a ruby
Your smile has become as precious as nine gems
All Your friends are average looking
May be... That's why you look beautiful
And when one becomes 18
It's not just you, any girl would look cute
When red sandal wears a saree
Even a stone would look like a princess
And, when a seven stone earring is worn
Any girl would look beautiful
Bro...
Now loading is done. Shall we go?
Shall we go?
Yes, Bro.
Is that all? Should we go?
What else? Loading is done.
So, Let’s go. That’s it
Do you find all this funny?
Why bro?
You know it and you are still asking
I seriously don’t know brother.
I don’t know
You know I didn’t come for the load,
but came here for that girl.
You know it and you are still saying
that we should leave.
- Ok.. lets leave then.. come...
- brother.. brother...
you can stay here as long as you want...
I will also stay with you.
I will stay... I will stay and you too stay with me,
and tell me if she is looking at me.
Did she see?
Yes, Brother
She is looking at you only while washing the vessels.
Is it true..?
You are lying to make me happy, isn’t it?
Yes Brother
How can you agree so fast man?
You could have let me feel happy for
some more time...
I think it is better I go and
beg her to look at me instead of dealing with you
Bro, don’t do that brother
I will go and beg her, to look at me
Please don’t do that brother.
I know, there is no use talking to you...
but for the last time,
tell me if she is looking at me or not
I don’t know what to say brother.
I told you to tell me that she is looking at me...
Your looks have become as pricey as gold Srivalli
Your word has become as rare as a ruby
Your smile has become as precious as nine gems
Hello Sir!
What happened sir? It’s the usual milk.
Why are you checking today sir?
What is this? I can hear milk sound on the top
and the sound of the wood below.
Are you hiding any load underneath?
Catch him... Catch him
Sir, Sir Leave me Sir. It’s mistake sir...
Sir Leave me Sir. It’s mistake sir.
Sir, please leave us sir...
we are just labour sir.
This is all because of Pushpa sir...
We did as Pushpa said.
Please leave us sir.
There is one condition if I want to leave you.
All these days you did as Pushpa said.
Now you must do as I say.
What?
Fifteen for Hundred...
Fifteen for Hundred... Fifteen for...
Hello Brother. Please stop.
- How much do you have?
- We need six tickets
We have Two hundred and seventy...
We want 6 tickets.
270?
For the kind of money you have,
you can only wish to watch. Not watch. Please leave
What should we do? How can we see the movie?
Hey girls, you are the girls from the milk center. Am I right?
Yes we are, So what?
Just wanted to check if you could got the tickets
Come girls...
How can we buy a ticket,
when they sell Fifteen rupees ticket for One hundred rupees?
It is the price one has to pay for big brothers movie...
how much are you short?
We are short by four hundred
Is that so, I will give you that money
if you do a work for me
What is that? What should we do?
- You have a friend named Srivalli, right?
- Yes, of course
Ask her to look at our Pushpa once
Hey .. hey.. Srivalli...
Come here.
What?
That guy.. Pushpa. can you look at him once?
Who is Pushpa?
The guy who keeps sitting at your milk center.
Do you remember?
He sits cross legged with a dark guy next to him
Hey girl, his name is Keshava and it’s me
- Ask her she will see him or not...
- You stop man.
- He looks good girl. Please look at him once.
- Is he so good looking?
So, if we have to watch chirajeevi,
then I have to look at him.. Ok.. Ok
I will.. I will
- Okay.. okay. She will.
- Yes
Ok. Take this
Who is she?
Who brother?
- You meat that girl in brown color saree??
- Yes
I will find out
- Hey girl. One more thing...
- What?
You said you will look at him just now.
Why don’t you smile at him too?
What is this smile business? I wont smile
- If you don’t smile...
- No... No. She will smile It’s only a smile.. right.?
You buy tickets.
Where do we met?
Ask him to come the Temple tomorrow
Smile... ask her not to forget the smile
Bro, the priest said that the girl will look
at you if perform Abhishekam.
That’s why I brought you
I don’t believe in all these
Bro, look here.
Srivalli is coming. Our prayers worked
So, what if she comes?
She doesn’t look at me. Come... Let’s go
Where do you want to go? Stay back brother.
Hey, getting late ask him to see her.
He is there, look at him once.
She doesn’t look at me. It’s a waste
Let's go.
(Girls whispering)
I am looking but he is not looking at me.
Stop bro. I had paid thousand rupees
What?
To the priest. Our money will go waste...
Look at him...
This is the last time. If she doesn’t look at me,
I won’t look at her ever again in my life...
Ok Bro. This is my last word. Fast & Final
Look at him... see him.
You wait!
Srivalli is looking at me
Smile at him
Smile!
- Is she looking at you?
- yes
Keep smiling...
- Girl, are you smiling?
- I’m smiling.
Hey.. She is smiling at me too
Did she smile or not?
She is smiled at me
That’s the power of Thousand rupees
you also smile back...
Yes, I too smiled
It’s enough for these faces. Let’s go now
They paid thousand rupees only. Let’s go
Now I understood.
She didn’t see me when I was looking at her.
And I didn’t see her when she was looking at me.
When she caught me looking at her,
while she was looking at me.. she burst out laughing
Oh! Is it?
I know that she loves me
That’s why I was behind her.
Come. Let’s go and speak to her once
Where do you want to go? Don’t forget who you are...
You can’t bend before her
We should take first step in these situations.
Don’t go brother You don’t know.
You wait, man.
Hey Srivalli... Srivalli.
Why were you smiling at me?
do you like me?
When did I like you?
Then why were you smiling at me?
Wont I smile when I am paid...
- Money?
- Yes
What money?
It seems you were feeling sad, because I was not looking at you
was I feeling Sad?
Yes, that’s why your friend Keshava gave me
the money to smile.. so I did...
Did you smile for that?
Whatever it is, We got to see Chiranjeevi movie.
It was very nice.
After having soft drinks and Samosa
we are still left with two hundred rupees.
Let me know where you would tomorrow.
I will come and smile at you for that...
Is this what thousand rupees prayer means?
Tell me where I can find you tomorrow...
All my pride and ego has gone to dust...
Hey Keshava. You have destroyed me.
Hey Keshava. Where are you?
Oh no! he's coming...
I did all this for your happiness
Isn’t it disgusting to ask that girl to smile at me
by paying her for money?
You ruined all the feeling of happiness,
that a girl loved me...
How can we stoop so low, to pay a girl and ask her to smile at me...
Am I like that? Am I like that Jaali Reddy?
No.. no.
You have totally damaged my dignity.
Anyways, How much did you pay?
Thousand
Thousand... for a smile.
Ok. Anyways since I have already become bad...
I will pay five thousand ask her to give me a kiss me
- What are you saying bro?
- I will pay her five thousand. Ask her if she will kiss me
I never thought you can behave like this bro
I’m not like this bro. I’m a very good person
but you have started this
and now you should take this to the end...
what do you mean by end?
I don't know what is the end?
Till end. That’s all
Bro...
Go and do 5000 rupees worship.
ONE thousand tonnes of Syndicate goods!
Approximately two hundred crores!
and halting here instead of enroute Chennai...
That Mangalam Seenu, rotating syndicate goods
That's why we are not able to track the locations.
It is possible that the goods will be coming to Kondareddy godowns.
If you tip us off the moment he lands new stuff,
do you know the reward?
Fifty Lakh Rupees.
- How are you Draccha?
- I’m good Uncle
Srinu? What brings you here?
Excellent location Konda Reddy.
Godown is also nice.
Even Draccha liked it.
He is Mangalam Seenu.
The boss of the smuggling syndicate!
There may be the likes of Kondareddy snoring
at corners to sweat small stuff...
he is the only one man who can navigate
the goods all through the 15 checkpoints to the Chennai Port.
That’s why he is the one who calls the shots.
Nobody can go against him and get away with it.
I see that you are shifting all the load into my godown.
What is the issue?
- You know Gowrreddy right...
- Who? Our Gowrreddy??
I dismissed him from job as
he was messing up the with goods.
How could you do that man?
What if he informs the police?
He knows addresses of all your godowns very well.
That’s why I brought all the stock to your godown kondareddy.
We still have some time to take it to Chennai.
Please safeguard the stocks. I hope it’s safe
What are you talking dear? Did we bring the
stock directly here without trusting Kondareddy uncle?
But the problem is that stock is safeguarded by that Jaali Reddy.
And you know that womanizer Jaali reddy is
surrounded always by girls.
If we trust and leave our stock with here,
it is like digging our own graves.
You said it right. If Govindappa comes behind a girl,
the entire stock will go for a toss.
Syndicate has trusted me and kept the stock with me
You said it right dear...
No need to worry. Now we have a sharp guy called Pushpa.
He is taking care of everything.
After he came, Police are not able to catch even
a stem, forget a log.. there he comes.. see
You are saying he is new. Can we trust him?
I will tell in detail about him some other time Seenu
He doesn’t look like the one to be discussed another time.
Anyways, I have to go for a wedding.
I take your leave
Pushpa, Srinanna’s stock will be with us
for two days. Take care of it...
Sure, Brother
Brother, we are getting late. Come fast...
What did you do with Gowrreddy?
Are you ignoring him or what?
Don’t look at sky always uncle, look at the earth also sometimes.
We get trees from the there only...
wont you put manure to it...
Brother, Look there once.
No...
He is like my younger brother.
I can’t see him die.
Why does this Mogalesh do incomplete work always?
Get me the gun...
Give me.
Why do we need this garbage in our backyard?
Throw it in the forest
Okay Brother
Go and do that work.
Bro...
- What is this?
- Cardamom bro.. for a good smell
I have.
Why delay? Where are the girls?
They are coming brother.
They are waiting... Go
Go... go.
Go and kiss him.
I’m scared dear. What if he bites me?
Why are you scared? He looks so handsome.
What is that meeting they are having there?
I don’t know brother
Why delay girl? He is waiting since morning.
Send her fast
What is your problem to give a small kiss?
If you can’t.. I will go and give him. Tell me
You wait, As If we can’t do that.
Bro Should I come and give you the kiss?
Who is that? Calling me brother and offering me a kiss.
Where did you find them?
Stop those discussions and send her fast
I am feeling scared
Shut up and come.
She is coming bro.. she is Coming
He is asking for a small kiss.
Go and give him a kiss, go...
Keshava, close the door
No, keep it open
What are you doing here dirty fellow?
I’m noticing you since long.
Why are you shouting? Stop those antics...
I will slap you hard idiot
Do it fast Pushpa and let’s go. Girls, turn away.
- Okay dear, as you wish!
- No touching!
What is this?
What you are chewing?
Cardamom...
do you want?
Not there. I will kiss you here
- Here?
- Yes
Why should we pay so much for a kiss here?
Hey Keshava
Ok ok. Don’t make it an issue...
Okay.
Ok give me...
Talk something.
What is there to talk? You took money to kiss me.
Right.. so kiss me...
Why are you crying girl? why?
I thought it is easy when my friends told me.
But my heart isn’t agreeing.
First kiss...
How will I understand if you murmur? Say it clearly
I always wanted to give first kiss to my husband...
To your husband?
If you wanted it to give to someone else,
why did you take money from me?
And why are you crying now?
Stop crying... Stop it
why are you crying now?
What happened dear? My god
What did you do brother?
I didn’t do anything brother. I didn’t even touch her
What did you do? Why is the poor girl crying so much?
Ask Srivalli.
Hey Srivalli. Did I do anything to you?
We trusted and sent our friend and is that what you do to her?
Stop your nuisance for a minute
I didn’t do anything brother.
You all go away... In hurry he would have bite her.
(Indistinct Voices)
What happened, bro?
She is making ruckus here.
Leave it bro. She said she will kiss her husband only right
It’s my kiss man. I paid for it.
If I have to marry her and become her husband, I will.
I should only get that kiss...
I won’t compromise on this
Hey what is this? The entire stock is still here.
Didn’t I tell you that we must cross
the check post with this by the night?
Jalanna was partying the whole night.
He has stopped the lorries as they might disturb the party.
Have your brains gone dead?
Who is Jaali to stop the stock?
Don't know, Brother.
Police are observing us like Jackals for this
address since night,
and you know how risky it is...
Where are the keys?
That is Jalanna’s room.
He will kill if we give you the keys
What will he do?
Pushpa, What are you doing?
Don't scare, come sister...
Hey Keshav,
please ask our guys to drop her in the village safely.
Okay.
Go...
Selva, take her and leave her in the village.
I will be here.
Okay.
- You go.
- Come...
Hey, do it fast.
Pushpa has sent the girl home
We are loading all the stock in the lorries.
Why did you send the girl?
First tell me why you didn’t you send the stock.
Have you converted the godown into your guest house?
Who are you to ask me? This is my godown
you are just a coolie fellow.
How dare you call me coolie?
This is Pushpa.
Partner Pushpa. 4 Percent share.
Give it now
Speak to him brother
Pushpa, Kondareddy brother wants to speak to you
Don’t you use what you have above neck
instead of what you have below the waist?
Bro, please tell
Police have come to know our godown address
What are you saying brother?
Hope all the stock is cleared from the godown
No brother. Your brother Jaali has
stopped all lorries from entering the godown
My god! Thousand tons stock. It is worth 200 crores.
We will be done forever if we are caught.
Mangalam Srinu has trusted us and handed over the stock.
Do something...
You have trusted me and handed over to me...
consider Pushpa is dead, if even one log is caught.
How scared he is, the slave!
Jalareddy, you’ll get it now!
Pushpa doesn’t budge an inch, always gives it back!
How do we tackle this?
Okay bro.
Rey... Pick the stock and throw it in the stream.
What are you looking at? Police are coming.
Get up and move
Brother, listen to me once.
Entire stock is being thrown into water here.
That's all Mangalam Srinu's Stock.
We can put it on Pushpa if Govindappa catches it.
Not good for you to be there now.
Leave from there immediately
Pushpa is caught now.
Srinu will not leave him.
I am sure his time is over now...
Police are here.
Brother... Log
Come fast.
Quickly.
Come on, quick rotate...
Sir, They have put towers in the forest too.
They would have known the information by now
- Rey... Is stock there?
- Sir, nothing is there here. Total license wood
If Pushpa is there stock will not be there.
If stock is there Pushpa won’t be there.
If you want to see both together,
none of you will be there.
- We should all be thankful to Govindappa Sir!
- Yes Bro.
Our range has grown because of this sir only...
If he had caught the stock that day,
I wouldn’t have become a partner today...
Don’t say like that brother? Sir may get angry
What sir? Are you getting angry??
Alas... I don’t even have shirt for you to hold my collar.
I have given it to a girl just now.
Not just you sir, we also do good deeds
Rey... You are not understanding what you are doing...
You are more cruel than animals... Yak
What is crueler than this world sir?
This world has given a gun to your hand
and an axe to my hand.
Everyone has his own war to fight.
I have won this war also sir
I will take care of whatever comes.
Yes, You have won.
But do you know what kind of war you are fighting?
You will lose as much as you are winning today.
You will know as you age...
Losers will always talk about principles.
When does the party start?
Heard about Mangalam Srinu party,
but first time I am seeing it.
Not only smugglers but police,
politicians all have come to party.
When one saw so much money
Pushpa has become hero instantly.
Mangalam Srinu himself personally introduced him to MP
They kill me with their looks if I wear a saree
They scan me with their eyes if I wear a skirt
Forget saree and gown, let me divulge a secret
What is there in the dress when It’s your hold that matters
Will you say yes Dear.
Or will you say No
One becomes upside down if I’m fair
One creates uproar if I’m dark
Forget fair and dark, let me reveal the true color
Color and figure won’t matter once you enter the field
Will you say yes Dear.
Or will you say No
One jumps with joy If I’m tall
One shouts and wails if I’m short
Forget tall and short, let me tell you a truth
You will be satiated with what you get
Will you say yes Dear.
Or will you say No
One feels happy If I'm stout
One feel bliss If I'm slender
Forget stout and slender
It is the man's wicked nature who caught me alone.
Will you say yes Dear.
Will you say No
One person poses like a respected man...
I have a very good heart says one person
There is no good or bad, everyone belongs to the same race
when the lights are off...
Will you say yes Dear.
Will you say Yes
Or will you say No
Will you say yes Dear.
Mangalam Sreenu has arranged a super party
He will get 2 crores from us and give only 25 lakhs to them
Then, not only party, he can do anything.
Figure, liquor...
- Brother, I want to speak to you urgently.
- What is that?
That Mangalam srinu is cheating us bro.
Mangalam srinu is fooling us.
How much does he give us per ton?
Twenty-five lakhs right.
He is selling for Two crores outside...
How do you know?
I have heard from the Murugan's people
when they were talking to each other
Of late I was also getting doubt on him...
He is buying lands in lot of places.
What do you say now?
Nothing to say. Let’s go and ask
We are loosing so much bro.
We are all working hard and he is sitting and
enjoying all the fruits. Ask him Brother
What? you want to go and ask Mangalam Srinu, is it?
Yes Do you know what he is?
Hey Stop... You stop.
You can go and ask but there are lot of other things
between me and Srinu.
We will get into trouble if anything goes wrong.
- What is this?
- Dry mutton curry.
Go and get snacks.
Do one thing man.
You go and ask him that people are talking like this outside.
You are also partner right.
If he agrees 50% share...
else, you didn’t ask me anything.
There is no relationship between us.
What do you say?
No Brother.
If anyone has to ask him, it is you brother.
It won’t look good if I ask
That’s why...
Hey Muniratnam did you see Pushpa’s range.
He is having lunch with Kondareddy...
and he also doing business with him
You said it right.
He used to come to work for
a wage of hundred, hundred and fifty.
Now he has become very big
Where will you get a better match
for your daughter than him.
Why don’t you get her married to our guy?
How did you say such a big thing
so easily in a serious discussion?
How can I give my daughter
without knowing his caste and gotra?
Hello... Do you know who he is?
He is younger son of Molleti Venkata Ramana
Is that so? Then he is our own.
Good match
Munirathnam, The groom family is here.
Please come in.
Namaste!
See, How Muniratnam face is glowing
Our lives are such that we feel happy
if Molleti Venkataramana says hi to us.
A match with such family means...
Its all god grace
Here!
What are you looking at?
Move...
come in please.
Sit... please sit down.
Hey, you go.
What did you guys tell him?
He is talking strangely
What did you say?
That’s what Bro. I told him that you are
third son of Molleti Venkataramana.
Did you say like that?
I’m somehow getting scared
What’s wrong? Did he not tell what the truth is..?
Not like that my son
Be silent Mom.
Bro. Srivalli is coming.
Bring the girl.
(Chants)
The girl is looking beautiful.
Girl, I had told you earlier only.
It was just a small kiss.
You should have given it to him.
See it has come up to marriage.
Now you have to keep kissing him for life.
That too for free.
This is all because of that Keshava
I'll hit you...!
Pushparaj, the youngest son of
Rangampet resident Molleti Venkata Ramana
and the resident of Yarravaripalem village...
We have seen the people
who sell fruits in the name of the tree.
We came here knowing that someone is selling fruits
without even know which tree has given those fruits
They are Venkataramana’s sons.
Greetings Sir.
It is said that relationship means it has
to have 7 generations both sides
Why is it that you are not looking
at even to one generation?
Do you know to whom you are giving
your daughter for marriage?
What are saying sir?
He said he is third son of Molleti Venkata Ramana.
Isn’t he your younger brother?
Will someone become king just because
he has Raju in his name?
and my brother if he takes my father’s name?
He is anyways shameless to say it.
She is a lady shouldn’t she have any shame?
Son, you sit quietly.
Swear on me that you won’t get up
Have you seen what is in that?
Did you see any surname?
No Sir, its only written as Pushpa raju
That’s the story.
He is surviving by using our surname
So what if he doesn’t have surname,
what is it that Pushpa doesn’t have..?
He has a house and earns handful.
Isn’t it enough to take care of your girl?
What do you say Muniratnam?
You said it rightly
what will he take care?
Do you think wedding is just exchanging vows?
We get a girl married to change her surname.
I won’t send her to such house.
Get up dear.
You wait... listen to me.
You sit my dear. Sit.
Hey Son, you both are brothers and you share the same blood...
when such good occasions are happening,
one should overlook and move on.
I agree with you
I agree that my father had an affair with his mother.
But what is the guarantee that he is born to my father?
My father didn’t tell me.
What man?
Did your mother at least tell you to
whom you are born? What?
How dare you?
(Commotion)
- Pushpa!
- Bro, Mother...
Bro, Mother...
Mom!
Keshava, get the vehicle.
Throw her out!
Please leave me... Please
I plead you...
Leave me alone.
Mom!
Please... let me see his face once.
Father!
When your father asked me whether I want love
or respect, then I thought love was enough.
I thought his respect is mine too.
But I never thought you will face
so many insults because of this.
Had I known it, I would have taken
some poison when you were in my womb.
Mom!
Please forgive me, my son.
What is this maa? What are you talking?
What happened now?
You have injuries on your head
that’s why you are talking like this.. Sleep now.
Grandma... Please maker her sleep.
Don’t cry my dear.
Drink some porridge.
Mom...
- Get some tea. Do you have money?
- I have bro.
Bro...
I was just five-year-old then.
I didn’t even know how to fight.
These guys have created all kinds of troubles
and took away whatever we had.
My father had given me a gold chain for my birthday.
In that chain there used to be photo of me and my father.
That was the only thing I had as a memory in those things.
They took away that as well.
I won’t keep silent if they try to take away what I have to get.
Whether it is 10 paise or 10 rupees.
I won’t spare anyone.
I won’t spare anyone, even if its Srinivasa on
the hill or Mangalam Srinu down the hill.
I will collect everything with interest.
This is Pushpa
Pushparaj here.
I won’t compromise.
Beat him here... not there
I have already beaten him there bro.
Beat him on his knee?
On his knee’s bro?
That hand... Mouth...
Beat him on the mouth.
Idiot shouldn’t open his mouth again.
Bro... He is scared
That’s why I asked you to beat.
How dare he comes directly to me
and ask me to increase the rate?
It seems, Twenty-five is not enough for him...
he wants fifty lakhs per ton.
Fifty... Do you want Fifty lakhs?
If I don’t give, you want to deal
with Chennai Murugan directly?
Why can’t you beat him yourself?
You are sitting happily and ordering him?
Bro... Stop now.
Drink this and take a breath.
Haven’t you got tired beating him since morning?
Unnecessary fuss all the time
She talks like that only.
You carry on...
Hello MP Sir.
Come Pushpa. Sit.
Yes. Tell me MP Sir
Hey Srinu. Heard that you kidnapped Nagesh.
His brother came and is regretting
for the mistake that happened.
Leave him for this time.
I will speak to you
So sad... I just killed him MP Sir.
Brother...
You should have called me five minutes ago.
I’m just washing the knife after cutting his neck
and your call came...
I had called your PA also in the morning Sir.
He also didn’t say anything.
Hello MP Sir, please tell me in advance
if there is something like this next time.
It’s a matter of a person’s life. Isn’t it?
I don’t want any differences
between you and me unnecessarily.
That's it sir... I take leave.
- How are you Pushpa?
- I’m fine, Sister.
That is the matter.
Hey Nagesh.
I have given a word to the big man on the other side.
I will go wrong if I leave you.
Hey, Cut him into pieces.
Okay.
You guys have spoilt the entire floor...
Hey Venkatesu... make it clean.
What Pushpa? What made you come to me?
How is Kondareddy?
He is fine Brother.
Brother, I have mixed the color.
What is this? Is this black?
Yes, black sir.
Last time also you had said it was black
but had turned brown.
It was so awkward in front of everyone
It just happened like that last time brother.
This time it will be black for sure.
I don’t have confidence in you.
Put on him and show.
apply on him.
See Pushpa, how he died struggling.
Else, he wanted Fifty lakhs per ton.
All you have to do is to cross two check posts
and deliver stocks to me.
I must cross fifteen check posts
to transport the stock to Chennai.
Can you imagine how difficult it is?
I agree brother, It is a very difficult job indeed.
Even I faced difficulty near fifteenth check post.
That SI Manikandan you know right.
He asked me for one lakh rupees.
That fellow.
Somehow, we made sure the
stock reached Chennai safely brother.
Have delivered the stock to Chennai?
Who told you to do that?
The twenty-five lakhs you give is not enough.
If you give one crore per ton,
I will sell to you only.
Crore?
What is it bro?
If I say no...
Whom did he say he will sell brother?
Chennai Murugan.
I will sell it to him only.
Why should I go to a new person?
Hey, do you understand what you are asking?
We just cut his neck for asking fifty lakhs only.
And here you are asking for one crore.
Don’t you see what just happened..?
I understand man.
I came here to ask fifty lakhs only.
But after seeing him, I understood
how high the risk is...
that’s why I am asking for a crore...
Am I right brother?
Brother, tell me whether you can one crore per ton.
Otherwise, I will sell to Chennai Murugesan only.
All of you think about it and call me.
Okay?
I take leave brother.
Oh! What is this bro?
This is black for sure.
Don’t worry and get it applied.
Brother, why did you leave him like that?
You are coming and asking me,
half an hour after he left?
I was in shock that he was speaking like that
even after seeing what death looks like.
Do you think I was in a dream sequence
with your sister?
I was also in a shock.
We have left him unnecessarily bro.
We should have killed him.
What do you say Singireddy?
Yes, Brother
Brother, Can I make a call?
Brother... Murugan.
Greetings Bro.
This is syndicate member Pushpa speaking.
This time we don’t want to sell stock to Mangalam Srinu.
Thinking of selling it to you directly.
Ok... Ok Brother.
Stock has already reached Chennai Sir.
I will come to Chennai tomorrow and discuss rate with you.
Ok. Write down my pager number brother.
Eight Three... Eight four...
You fool!
I didn't left because you spared me
I left because I decided to leave.
What?
You thought Pushpa means flower...
It's Fire!
Fire!
Who are you?
What do you want?
We have come to meet Murugan.
Is it?
Hey... who are they?
Pushpa, Syndicate member.
Came from Tirupati to discuss business.
Hey, say Pager No. 8384.
He will recognize us with that
Why are you shouting in my ear?
Hey, Murugan Sir is busy and
he said he can’t meet anyone.
You heard it right!
Murugan Sir won’t meet anyone. Leave now
Let him say that after seeing this piece.
What is this?
This is Bro’s visiting card.
He will understand if he looks at it
Its 07:45 PM
It's tea time for Murugan sir.
Quickly go and give a tea to Murugan sir.
Hey, Tea won’t go anywhere.
Murugan himself will come to tea
What is this man?
A grade stock.
I had seen it long back when I started the business.
I’m seeing it again now.
This is gold.
How many hills we have to climb up
to see lord Venkateswara...
Likewise that many hills you need
to climb down to find this kind of stuff
This is A grade Stuff.
The smuggler who buys never knows where we can get it
The one who the cuts the tree knows the exact place
Open the door.
Two tons... five trucks
We have ten tons of stock
Super man!
Will speak to Mangalam Srinu
and fix the rate. You leave.
Brother, We have decided not to sell
the stock to Mangalam Srinu.
That is why we came directly to sell it to you.
That’s why we brought it this far.
Do you want stock or not?
Hey, close the door.
- Start the vehicles...
- Bro.. bro...
Mangalam Srinu is very dangerous.
Can you do business defying him?
Can you buy the stock defying him?
Any who came here defying Mangalam Srinu
and they are all dead.
Brother, many would have come to you.
I called from Srinanna’s place only and
told you that I am coming to you
I’m different bro.
Who are you? Are you a crack?
Do you know to whom you are talking to?
I am Kondareddy’s partner.
Kondareddy himself sent me here to talk to you.
Are you Kondareddy’s man?
You should have told me that earlier.
Call him.
Let me speak once.
That, only after negotiating the price...
Tell me what is the rate?
Hello!
Brother Kondareeddy
Hey Pushpa. Didn’t see you for the last 2 days.
Where did you go?
I came to Chennai?
Chennai? Why??
I came here to meet Murugan.
To meet Murugan?
Hey Jakka.
He says he went to meet Murugan
Whose permission did you take to go to Murugan?
I asked you to go and meet Mangalam Srinu, right?
What bro? Doesn’t Kondareddy know
that we came here?
Just because we gave 4% share,
you want to act as you wish?
One and half crore...
One and half crore per ton.
I just negotiated the deal with Murugan.
As usual, do you want me to sell to
Mangalam Srinu for twenty-five lakhs
or take risk and sell it to Murugan for one and half crore...
Understood bro.
I will tell Muragan brother that
you can’t do business defying Mangalam Srinu.
I will tell him that we don’t have the guts.
I held back for all these days not because
I don’t have guts.
I stopped because I was bound by Syndicate’s decision.
When we know that Mangalam Srinu is
cheating us, who cares for the syndicate?
Finalize the deal.
Brother...
50% share to me and 50% to you from the profits.
You remember we agreed on this the other day.
How dare you information to police
about us.. you idiot?
What is the point of talking to him brother,
when he was informing everything about us to Police.
I don’t have anything to do with it.. brother.
He did everything.
You knew, that he was doing all this.
I know, brother.
Why didn’t you not inform us?
He lured me with money.
I got greedy in the hope to perform my daughter’s marriage.
Daughter?
Who is that?
Does he have a grown up daughter..?
same one brother, the one you saw when she came
to see ‘Choodalani undi’ Movie.. that one...
Is she, his daughter?
Isn’t she beautiful? I saw her from far.
She looks just ok bro
Then ask her to come once.
We shall talk to her
Lay him down here.
Rey, You guys go and get his parents
My...
Where is my father?
What happened to him.
I’m asking you.
What happened to my father?
Tell me.
Rey Busappa, you said she is just ok.
But she is looking superb like a film heroine.
Your father is alive.
But go home and have a bath with lux soap.
wear this saree with jasmine flowers
and come here in the night.
Then, You can take your father home in the morning.
Get ready like a bride for Jalanna and come.
What? Can’t you adjust for one night
for the sake of your father’s life?
Go... Go.
Hey!
Bro!
Go out and have some beer and biryani.
Come back in the morning.
Ok bro.
Rey, we can do this in the morning.
Let’s go. Rey. Let’s go
(Song)
How come you came here dear?
Have you lost your way?
Jalreddy is saying that he will kill my father
Why Jalreddy?
Even I would kill him.
How could your father
show loyalty to the Police?
He said he will spare him,
if I sleep with him tonight.
You came all decked up right.
Go there.
Why did you come here?
If I go there tonight, my father might
return home in the morning...
but I will not be able to come to your house ever.
Why do you want to come to the house of
a guy who doesn’t have surname?
You must have felt happy on the day the relation broke.
You must have felt very happy
that you have gotten rid of me,
and you don’t need to see my face ever again.
Is this what you understood?
You are like this, from the beginning.
When did you ever understood the heart
of a girl that you can understand today.
When my friends told me that you are feeling sad,
because I was not looking at you,
I felt very happy that this boy likes me so much.
I liked you as soon as I saw you.
When you gave me money and asked for a kiss...
I thought this is your way of expressing love.
When I said that I want to give first kiss to my husband,
I gave an indication to you to marry me.
You didn't understand even that.
My father doesn’t even start the lorry without my nod.
Do you think you could come to my house
for marriage proposal without my wish?
Do you know how bad I felt seeing
you anxious when mother-in-law got hurt?
You could have understood that,
had you seen into my eyes once.
You left even without looking at me.
Do you mean to say, that I should
change my heart after hearing whatever you said...
and go fight with jaali and save your father?
It is not going to happen.
Leave now
I know that you won’t do anything like that.
Your money and business are important to you, Isn’t it?
Why will you fight for a stranger like me?
Anyways, I didn’t come for that.
Then why did you come?
I always wanted to share my first kiss and my first night
with someone whom I consider my husband.
Please sleep with me once.
You will never see me again.
I will go.
And after that I don’t care what happens to my life.
What is this dear?
Do you love me so much?
You think I will allow anyone to lay his hand
on you after what you said.
Whoever it is...
will not allow
What Pushpa?
You only brought the girl to make her sleep with me.
Are you doing all this for just 4 percent?
I won't leave her.
Are you firing?
Dear, Come here.
Are you firing bullets on to the girl?
I am going to kill you, idiot.
How dare you lay a hand on girls?
Muniratnam!
Muniratnam, get up!
Look Srivalli, your father is fine.
I made him sit in the car.
What is this man?
You have hit Jalreddy so badly.
O Jalanna. I feel pity looking at you.
What maccha?
You made him incapable for anything.
If Kondareddy gets to know if this, he will kill you bro.
Hey, who will tell?
This fellow only should say if at all...
What man? What will you tell your brother?
Will you go cry before him and
tell him shamelessly that Pushpa beat you.
Ey Jaali, Go and complain.
I don’t care.
Dear, come let’s go.
We will get it resolved either this way or that way.
I’m ready for whatever happens.
Pushpa, I’m not an idiot to go
and complain to my brothers.
This is between you and me...
and I will deal about this with you directly.
I won’t leave you.
This.. This ..This...
This is what is called as being a man.
What you did with women
all these days is not like a man.
Now you have proven that you are a man.
Now stand on your word.
Kesava, he has masculinity in him.
I think he will stand on his word.
What dear? What do you think?
I too believe the same
He will stand on his word right
How will he stand,
when you have already broken everything.
Muniratnam, Come... come.
Pushpa, I will park the car at home and come.
Srivalli, I will take leave.
Pushpa!
Come and have dinner.
No need Aunty.
My mom is waiting for me... I have to go.
Pushpa, wait a minute.
You come.
My mom asked me to give this to you.
Okay.
You go.
Why are you staring at me?
Go.
What girl?
When you call me Dear... Dear,
I feel like I have become your wife
Darling... My Darling
When I call you Darling... Darling,
you suit well as my Husband
Darling... My Darling
When I walk behind you
It feels like going uphill
to Venkanna Temple, Darling
When I sit next to you
It feels like I got Lord Parameshwara.
When I look at the path as you leave
It is as if the lake has dried up.
Darling... My Darling
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
When you tie lungi above the thighs...
My breath gets stopped Darling
When you are chewing a Jarda Pan
My body gets painted Red... Darling
When I hear your yells and roars...
It thrills me like hell...
When you sit cross legged, it mesmerizes me.
When you take out two buttons and show your chest
Won’t it overflow like a milk Pot
My Darling... my Darling
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
When I wear a new saree and you don’t complement
Wouldn’t that saree value become zero, Darling...
When I wear flowers in my hair
And if you don’t smell them
Wouldn’t the flower mound fall down.
When my saree frill slips down
When my saree frill slips down,
and you won’t look at me
The naughty wind would sympathize with me, Darling
If my beauty doesn’t become yours,
my life as girl would become poor
Darling... my Darling
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
My Darling... Come here Darling
Darling with Golden Heart...
Darling with Pride. Darling with Emotions
Bro, Operation to the spine it seems.
Doctor is saying only after that
he can say if he can walk or not
He won’t say who hit him.
And you people don’t know.
Is that right?
Yes Brother.
Bro... Bro... Bro
Whom did he sleep with last night?
Muniratnam daughter came... Bro
Muniratnam daughter came in the night and
went back in the morning with her father.
Then, who hit him?
Bro, looks like Kondareddy wants to kill the guy
who thrashed Jalreddy,
once he gets to know who did it.. ignoring that,
you are looking at Pager and money.
Only six months? For the trashing I gave him,
He should not get up for one year.
I think I haven’t given him enough...
Bro, Jalreddy still has some masculinity left in him.
That is why he didn’t name you.
What If Kondareddy gets to know this...
I lost my count...
How will Kondareddy get to know?
What Pushpa?
Has the stock reached Murugan?
Reached Bro. He sent the message too.
Just reached it seems
Ok. we should go to Tirupati tomorrow
and get the money.
- That Hawala slip is with you, only right?
- It is safe with me.
Be ready in the morning
what is that injury on your hand?
This... Our
That... Got scratched when coming in car.
Be careful man. Ok...
- What Subbareddy?
- Bro...
- Did you get the jeep tyres changed?
- got it Changed bro
What should I do?
- Bro. Do you think he heard?
- No, He didn’t.
No Bro. I have a doubt that he must have heard...
I will do one thing.
I will go out and close the door and wait there...
You speak something.
I will see if can hear it or not
Bro... Speak.. Speak
bro, I could not hear anything
I didn’t speak anything
- What man... What is this?
- Mosquitos Bro
- What?
- Mosquitos
Be careful man. Too many mosquitos here.
What if we get Dengue Fever?
I’m going to Tirupati on work...
Do you want anything?
Don’t you know what I want?
Your hands look good.
Should I bring you gold ring?
What? Don’t you like gold ring?
What do you want?
You are staring at me with eyes wide open.
What happened?
What are you doing?
Going to Tirupati on work
What are you doing now?
Looking at you
Where is your hand?
- what?
- Where is your hand?
Oh. Did my hand touch you? Sorry dear
You didn't remove
It is still there.
I was talking on the phone.. here, I removed it...
I didn’t realise it because I was busy talking on phone
You didn’t know, is it?
You didn’t know?
- You didn’t know, is it?
- Hey... Why are you hitting me, dear?
Don’t talk... I'll not come again
- What happened?
- Don't talk.
I’m leaving now.
I came here to see your face before
going for money collection.
- Do you know how excitedly I came?
- What?
Did I come to get hit by you? I will go.
- Stop Darling...
- I'll go...
This is all waste business.
Stop Darling I will leave
What Darling?
You only did it and now you are only getting angry.
Why did you hit me? See... Again,
you are getting angry
Hold it darling
No, you will again abuse me
Hold it, Darling
No, Thanks Hold it, Darling
Thanks.
I will stay, you go dear... go dear...
Srivalli... Srivalli
Ok Darling... I leave now
Hey. What are you doing dear?
They will find it.
See, if your friend asks, tell her that we were just talking.
Don’t tell her all these things.
It will spoil my reputation.
Ok, Darling. I know
It’s time for work.
what dear? Looks like a lot happened inside
Nothing.
Hey Srivalli.
Ask Pushpa to have tiffin and go.
He had tiffin aunty. He had it just now.
Can’t you see it?
Srivalli!
Careful darling
Darling!
Someone is coming.
Pushpa come... please come.
Shetji, are you fine?
- How are you?
- Fine sir.
How are you?
I am fine.
You go... I'll come.
Pushpa... look, new models have arrived.
Pushpa, go to new godown.
If you wear a striking dress and
if we give frightening looks... it scares (Song Humming)
aa... you get scared. If we come walking with grace
and you stop us for fun... scare... scares..scares
How did you hear what I was singing to myself?
Why can’t I hear?
You think we can’t hear whatever you guys speak inside?
Leave that. When you and Pushpa were talking of beating
Jalreddy, me and Kondareddy sir heard from outside.
What did you say? Move aside.
Max Pager Services
Sister, have to send a message urgently.
Please tell me the number?
Get him up.
What man? Did you forget who we are?
Just because we gave you four percent share
and a seat next to us,
do you think we will remain silent
if you lay your hands on our brother?
I will kill you, idiot.
Hey. He has a 5 crore hawala slip in his pocket.
Search for it.
- Why are you laughing?
- Hit the idiot. Hit him
My brother is talking and you are laughing at him.
Else what bro?
I thought you are killing me because of your brother...
right now I got that you are killing me because of money.
Now business is good, after killing me
you can takeover all the my share also.
Hey... to me nothing is bigger than my brother.
It’s a nice joke bro.
Maybe this is the last joke I will hear.
What are you searching man?
I keep it in the fold of my hand sleeve right.
We got the note.
Kondareddy bro, you have become very commercial.
Hey Subbareddy. Is it the same note?
Yes Brother. It is the same note.
On which date do we get our money?
New title for you. Commercial Kondareddy.
Tag line-No Masculinity
Hey, take him and throw him in the pit
I know brother, that these kind of businesses
will definitely see death some day.
If by mistake, Lord Venkateswara supports me and saves me,
I will become a very big man for sure.
I will sit on the top.
Yes. I can visualize my future.
Why delay?
Shoot him up.
Hey, I will kill this Jakkareddy.
You guys go and kill that Pushpa.
Cut the rope.
Quickly.
Come on cut the rope.
Pushpa, come fast.
Pushpa!
Catch him.
Kill him.
Hold on guys...
He is getting scared.. he is scared...
Bro, we found jakkareddy.
what are you waiting for? Kill him
I will cut his neck bro...
then what about that coolie?
You mean, that Pushpa?
Our men would have killed him by now bro...
What Jakkareddy?
What are you looking at me like that.
Is it because I came back?
You and I may have million things between us...
but when an outsider comes, you are my partner.
That’s it.
You think I will sit and watch?
What man... why are you coming on to me like that.
If my brother-in-law comes to know of it
he won’t leave you...
If you something harm to me,
my brother-in-law won’t leave you.
Why are you taking out the gun? Will you kill me?
My brother-in-law won’t keep quite if you do anything to me.
He will kill all of you.
True Pushpa, It will become a big mess if you touch him.
He is getting scared. He is getting scared.
Even I want to kill him Pushpa.
But no... Leave him.
Let this end with my brother
He is getting scared... Scared.
That’s all. Everyone should fear my brother-in-law.
See... here my brother-in-law himself is calling.
I will go. I will go away.
Hey Kesava... Start the vehicle.
Talk...
Talk to him... you are finished now.
What man Mogileesu?
Yeah, Srinu bro...
Pushpa!
Bro, they caught Mogileesu.
Look Pushpa. Listen to what I am saying...
Let us do business together...
that too at the rate you asked for.
We will discuss about the rest later.
Don’t do anything to my brother-in-law.
Okay?
Areyrey... I just killed him bro.
You should have called me five minutes ego.
Life will not come back once it is gone. Right, bro.
Brother in law...
Why are you silent, bro?
wondering what that sound is?
You alone know that I am not scared of anyone.
Now the entire market will know with this sound.
Bro... Just keep it in your mind
I didn’t come here to mess with anyone
I came here to rule.
I won’t compromise.
Get in Pushpa!
Bro... That Mangalam Srinu is coming.
He is coming here to die today.
Hey... Give me the gun
Hey Jakka .. you hang on,
I asked Mangalam Srinu to come.
If you guys fight here, the entire department will be here,
and I will get everyone killed in an encounter.
So Let's settle the matter here...
I will leave if my brother-in-law’s body is given.
You can go... but, sit first.
We were like brothers right.
Then What is this?
You should ask them all that.
It is they who have started all this.
What is it about starting?
It will not end till you are killed.
Hey Jakka. You stop...
Bro, first ask them why they sold stock to Murugan...
Yes Bro. They sold the stock to Murugan
without Srinanna’s knowledge
Jakka, shouldn’t everyone stick to the syndicate?
Why are you guys doing this?
- How much is this?
- Three crores
How much? How much did you sell a ton for?
One and half crore.
What is this?
Is this true?
I will give all these calculations later
but what is this man? You not only killed by brother-in-law,
you are also complaining against me
Hey, I didn’t kill your brother-in-law.
I killed the person who killed Kondareddy Bro.
Do you think I will sit silently and watch
when someone attacks Jakkareddy bro with a knife?
I shot him.
You hold on man
Even I won’t leave.. I will also kill.
What bro? Looks like both brothers-in-law’s are alike...
Do you think we are scared?
What, you will kill? that too in front me.
Why are you giving the gun?
What is this? Why are you silent?
Bro .. I called him when he was about to kill
my brother-in-law. Still he killed him.
Maybe you also called five minutes late like me.
But anyways, both sides have lost right?
Hey, put that gun away and first explain the calculations.
Till now you said, 25 lakhs per ton.. right?
Then how did he get a crore and half now?
We also asked him the same Sir?
Had he answered this, we wouldn’t have gone to Murugan
and things wouldn’t have come to this
This big man has screwed all of us so badly
What bro Srinu? Why are you silent?
Why don’t you answer when MLA sir is asking you?
What is this? Should I explain accounts now?
Have you guys forgotten what all I did so far?
True Bro. Why are you asking
Srinanna accounts now?
How many people did he manage...?
How many check-posts he managed?
Won’t you take all that into account?
Hello Sir. We are coming there only.
You are paying off the police.
We are also paying off the police.
All of you are giving commissions.
Above that, we are also giving commissions
we are also giving commissions to people
in Forest, revenue, ID... how will it work out?
We, together should pay them once only.
Then see how much will we save?
Twenty-five percent.
Which we were wasting.
Just by bypassing Seenanna and going directly
to Murugan, he paid us one and half crore.
If we all unite and fix a rate,
he will pay two crores at least.
What? two crores??
Bro, the story doesn’t stop here...
There is Chatterjee in Calcutta,
and who is that in Mumbai? Ya.. Singh,
then Agarwal in Delhi.
I kept more people like them, in line.
Bro, we have the kind of stock
that is not available anywhere in the world.
We have it here in Tirupati in our Andhra Pradesh.
The kind that no one on this earth has.
With that kind of stock we have,
why should we go and ask them.
We should demand and create competition
amongst the buyers in the market,
Then they will buy our stock standing in Queue.
We may get three crores per ton also.
If we go by that, our MP sir may get
at least 20 crores as commission.
Yes, Pushpa said it correctly,
If we hand over the syndicate to a person like this,
our business will be good
It’s easy to speak sitting on the shore.
You will know the depth when you get into the water.
Pushpa Come man.
Sit down and tell the whole thing to MP sir...
Give me one chance, Sir.
I will make sure that we see the
kind of profits that we have never seen.
What are you thinking Sir?
Are you thinking, where is my confidence is coming from?
None of the stock I have transported so far was ever caught.
That is my capital.
Trust me, Sir.
All of you are going with him just because he sold two tons for more.
Two people are also dead in the last two months
since he has entered the business,
just think, how many more dead bodies
will we see In the coming days.
What bro? do you want to believe everything this
youngster said and put the business in his hands?
- Bro, I am not totally convinced.
- If we trust him, we all will go bankrupt.
Yes bro, Even I’m getting doubts
Everything he did is right in front of our eyes,
can’t you all see it?
Pushpa will manage the syndicate from now onwards.
Everyone should sell their stock to Pushpa only.
We will have an oath taking ceremony in Kanipakam tomorrow.
Take this cash and go.
MP Sir, If they give me my brother-in-law’s body,
I will go home
Bro, From the time you came in,
you are sitting on his body only.
We will send his body safely home if you get up.
Hey Selva, help Seenanna in the preparations.
Okay Keshava.
Guys come...
That side is mine... This side is mine...
The piece of sky above my head is also mine
That wrong is mine... This right is mine.
The fire that burns the right and wrong is also me
The one who can defeat me is not yet born on the earth
Even If he is born, it would be me again
There is only one who can grow beyond me
And that’s me, myself in the future
If I twirl, it’s my mustache
And I hold Axe in my hand...
Whatever I do is the war
And I never negotiate
Hey Son... This is my bastion
Will throw you in the lake
And I return with a fish
Will stick you to a pole
And I hoist like a flag
Will bury you in the soil and make you disappear
I will be found again as an expensive ore
Hey Son... This is my bastion
Open it.
What is this Draccha?
It is six months since my brother died.
And you are sleeping like a log since then.
How can you?
What should I do?
That Pushpa has grown too big,
and that MP is also in his side.
We can’t do anything till the government changes...
We can’t do anything...
Then you should have waited till the
government changed to send my brother to him.
Did I send him to get killed? I Sent him to kill...
What should I do if he died because of his incapability?
If so, you also couldn’t kill him...
Then, why are you still alive?
What is this Draksha?
Why are you still alive?
Hey you idiotic Husband...
Come back if you are alive
We will together take revenge...
or else I will go alone and kill him
Who are you? Who are you?
I’m the iron I’m the iron
I will become a knife if I’m put under fire
Who are you? Who are you?
I’m the soil I’m the soil
I will become a brick if you crush me
Who are you? Who are you?
I’m the rock... I’m the rock.
Under these circumstances,
Pushpa's marriage muhurat has been fixed.
Despite lot of happenings,
his mother's hope never gave up hope.
To give the marriage card she went to the big house.
It seems that Puspa is getting married on the 11th
This is not going to happen.
I will become the god for sure If you hurt me.
Hey Son... This is my bastion
With regret, Govindappa resigns and leaves,
claiming responsibility for Bhujanga's murder
Even though Jalreddy wants take revenge badly,
he was not in a state to get up.
Burning with vengeance, Dakshayani was left helpless...
when everyone thought that no one can touch Pushpa.
The new person arrived.
And the whole story changed
SP... Bhanwar Singh Shekhawat
There is nothing to say about him...
you are going to witness him.
It is strong
- Is it Sheelavathi or what?
- Yes sir...
Come!
Kupparaju, Sheelavathi is strong
You get good quality here, Sir
That’s why I got asleep,
it came and It will come.
That’s why I’m falling asleep... I will sleep.
- Did you give this to me?
- yes sir
- What is your name?
- Mallesh sir.
- What?
What is your name?
De... De...
Devaraju Sir...
Sir... Sir... Sir... SP sir...
Heard, that you arrested 12 cannabis smugglers.
How? Sir...
10 people, not 12...
two fled...
They did not run away...
they were killed.
Shut up!
Sir... sir... did you kill them?
Sir... he says they were exactly 12 people...
we also have the same information. Where are the other two?
Sir... sir... they were killed sir... killed sir...
Didn’t I say that two of them have fled? He is a smuggler...
He doesn’t know the math. I will teach him now
Sir... what they are saying, is true?
Sir Media is asking
The new SP has come. I’m going to give him the card.
I will meet you once on the way.
Why do you want to meet?
I just want to talk
Just talk?
Will you sit silently once you come?
A lot will happen after that
I just want to talk to you and leave.
I will just talk and leave
What? You will see and go is it,
as if I don’t know what you will do.
You will tempt me and leave.
I will go sleepless after that.
Dear, why are you objecting when I say that
I will meet you and once and leave?
Hey... Where are you going?
I have a small work
Hey... You should not go out of home
once we make you a bridegroom.
Not good for the home.
You tell him, dear
What... what is this old woman’s torture?
Dear... Listen to what I’m telling you...
I don’t know why but my mind is suspecting harm.
You talk.
This is the first holy occasion
happening in my life, my dear son...
Pushpa, listen to me.
Pushpa.
Come...
This is the First-time meeting
with the newly appointed SP.
Sir...
I brought coffee
Keep it there
Had to bend to see him.
He is only Pushpa Sir.
I told you about.
He looks after the entire red sandal syndicate.
He came to see you, Sir.
Hello SP... What is your name?
Ban... var sing Skiva... skyavathaa
whatever it is...
I am getting married on 11th.
Somehow you...
should manage and come.
This is this month’s commission...
One crore rupees.
One short!
One short
Sir?
No Sir, it is all correct.
One short
Guys, come on...
Shall I tell what is the difference
between thief and Police.
He wore a white shirt... I too wore a white shirt,
and both look similar... but there is a difference.
This one has a half-inch sticker. Look...
It is there sir.
That is a brand.
you know what brand is right
Yes Sir.
In Telugu, you call it (Surname) Illi Peru
No sir.
Illu Peru
No Sir
Inti peru (surname)...
Yes sir.
It is like a surname...
It means a stamp that tells who manufactured this...
who gave birth.
That stamp
This one has the stamp,
That’s why it has value.
That one doesn’t have hence it doesn’t have value.
The count is right sir.
There is One short.
If we have a value, we will know the
value of the other person.
Tell us your value sir...
we will pay.
- Mr. Kuppu Raju...
- Sir!
Handcuff him.
If I arrest you now and charge you with PD act,
do you know how many years you will you be jailed?
Three years Sir.
Three years...
Your wedding on the 11th, right?
If you go to jail now, when will you get married?
After three years...
It means when you will get married...
I will decide.
If your marriage happen...
When will your wife become pregnant...
After one month...
a man
Pushpa is a man...
If you go to jail then if she becomes pregnant.
Are you laughing, right?
What? tightening fists?
Getting angry?
open it... open it
You don’t have that much luxury with police...
Open your hands... Open your fist...
Open your fist
Shh!
Did you get what was short?
Hey, you guys hold on.
Pushpa’s count never wrong.
Tell me what is short for you sir...
What?
What is short for you please tell me sir?
Sir...
That was short.
I told you one short; one short right. ‘Sir’, was short.
shouldn’t say... “You should attend the wedding”.
You should say “attend the wedding Sir”.
- Mr. Kuppuraju...
- Sir...
Uncuff him.
Now the count is correct.
Bag... bag... bag...
from now on, along with the cash, sir also should come.
How much sir should take and
how much you will get will be decided by sir.
Shekhawat sir will decide.
Pushpa!
This is my gift for your wedding.
Buy clothes... branded ones.
I gave you a gift.
Won’t you give me a party, Pushpa?
Don’t know why?
Pushpa used to do whatever
Shekakavat said from then onwards.
He used to follow his orders religiously.
Never seen Pushpa bend before anyone till then.
This is the first time he was doing so.
We used to wonder why he is behaving like that.
That day, a little before Pushpa’s wedding muhurtham,
Priest called for the bridegroom.
When we went in to call him,
Pushpa was not there.
Even his motorcycle was also not there.
Wow!! What is this Sir?
What is this Sir?
Never thought you have a funny side too, Sir.
Singing like a Romeo...
But that day you scared me with a mask of a tiger.
Had to scare Pushpa.
Only then you came know how to behave with me.
See now we are drinking together happily.
Where is Pushpa?
Where did he go?
Auspicious time is nearing...
Not able to connect. Calling him
Call him again.
What Pushpa? Today is your wedding, right?
And you are here only. Is it ok?
Sir!
The wedding can happen.
The bride will be there even if I go half an hour late.
But you Shekhawat Sir, gave me time to meet you.
What is more important than that?
When you referred to the wedding,
I remembered one thing.
You said, you will decide when my wife should get pregnant,
and at what time she should get pregnant.
Why did you say that Sir?
I felt very bad.
Tell me why did you say that Sir?
Why are you spoiling the party mood?
Why all that now.
It’s ok sir.
You must have said that to hurt me.
That’s it, right sir? Leave it.
But...
I didn’t like the way you insulted my mother Sir
What did I say about your mother Pushpa?
You know that I don’t have a surname right, Sir?
In spite of that, you insulted me
by saying who manufactured me...
who gave birth.
Stamp, Stamp... this... that. Right Sir?
What is this Pushpa?
Why are you spoiling the party mood?
Why all that now?
When someone speaks about my surname,
it is like insulting my birth.
And if someone insults my birth...
it is like insulting my mother.
Since birth every Idiot has insulted me with this, Sir.
Pushpa.
You are drunk and speaking nonsense.
You are tipsy?
Yes Sir, I had more.
In your gun one thing is more.
What is it?
Like you, I don’t know how to put
in suspense saying One is more...
There one extra bullet in that sir.
In this?
Yes!
Give me!
One, two, three, four.
There are six Sir...
Did you notice it? One is more
That is Service revolver Pushpa.
It will have Six bullets only.
That day when I tightened my fists hearing your words,
you aimed this gun at me right, Sir.
The bullet that had to go into this remained in this only.
That one is more
Do you know what this is Sir?
This is my father’s blood which is flowing in my body.
My father gave me this even before
my brothers could snatch the surname from me.
No one can separate this from me.
This...
This is my brand, Sir...
Hey, Shekhawat sir... Idiot
What? did you think I am of a brand
that will get scared of bullet?
This brand has grown with its own attitude.
Do you know why Pushpa was silent
that day when you said all that?
My mother didn’t have a wedding in her life.
This is the first wedding happening in our house.
I stopped myself till this hour,
thinking my mother will feel bad if anything happens.
Now I won’t hold myself back.
Greetings!
Jakka, Sit down.
Keshava, Where is Pushpa?
you are not understanding what you are doing
What is there to understand?
I'll strip you.
Take it off.
Pushpa, do you know with whom you are confronting?
Bhanwar Singh.
Bhanwar Singh Shekhawat
Is it?
Then remove your pants also
Why this?
Pushpa stripped Shekhawat sir’s clothes
and made him stand stark naked...
imagine how great feels...
Take it off.
Did you understand now? Everyone will feel
the same way when you strip them.
Either it is Shekhawat Sir or Pushpa.
You don’t have clothes on your body.
I don’t have clothes on my body.
But there is one difference, do you know it?
Pushpa started his life like this.
Do you know what was his range when he was a coolie?
This was his range
The range that was then is the same now.
See, If I go on the road like this also,
they will call me Pushpa.
If you go on the road like this without a police uniform...
even your dog won’t recognize you.
Brand is not in the clothes you wear.
It is in your living
Hey Shekhawat Sir...
please keep this in your mind
The load that has to go will go and the
money 'has to come will keep coming
You won’t get a rupee.
You will have just the uniform on your body
but you won’t have work to do.
You will only have ‘Sir’.
I will remove everything else
See you.
(Sanskrit Sloka)
Sorry, Sir... Your dog is not recognising you.
Hey, keep quiet.
What, dear?
What is this attire?
Why did you come like this?
What happened?
Someone thought Pushpa means flower.
I showed him that Pushpa means fire.
Ok. It’s all over, right?
Just started
What happened sir?
Pushpa!
Whoever comes...
Will not budge.