People are assholes, I swear.
Christian and the rest are shitty cowards.
You get me, right?
I don't think burning uniforms
is so crazy. What about it?
And me being stark naked is a lie.
It's cheap gossip.
But sure, now everyone's looking at me
as if I were crazy.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Do you know who that is?
One of the new guys.
My God, I'd fuck his brains out.
A lot of muscle, but not much brain.
I don't care if he's got no brains.
Have you seen him?
He's a Greek god.
-Come on.
-Girl...
Come on, let's go.
RAISING VOICES
I made this T-shirt
to remind myself of how stupid I was.
A way to punish myself.
POSTING
I got myself into this.
#TOTALLYFUCKEDUPBUTSTILLSMILING
It was my fault.
Shut the fuck up.
You're all so lame.
Shut the fuck up. Shut it.
Turn it off, asshole.
Wait, Nata.
Nata!
I'm always running after you.
What the hell's wrong?
I'm going home.
I'll walk you to the bus.
-No need.
-No, Nata.
It was Valentine's Day, dammit.
Nata!
I expected something nice,
and I got a shitty date.
I should've gone home much sooner,
but I was mortified
about explaining to my mother
that I'm going out with an idiot.
I just never learn.
Instead of a romantic night in a hotel,
he sticks me in a garage with his buddies.
AN UNFORGETTABLE WEEKEND!
Then this guy turned up and...
I swear, at that point,
I didn't give a damn.
That's fucking scary, girl.
I ask myself, what's a boyfriend for
if I can't get home safe?
Maybe you should find someone
who cares how you feel.
I obviously don't come
because we have no privacy.
Don't you see he won't change?
Really.
If you want things done right,
you have to do them yourself.
That's what my mom always says.
Right, I didn't mean that.
Right.
Girls, shall we go back?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
FEBRUARY
LIBRARY
Can I get my phone?
I just want to check my messages, please.
Ten minutes. In the box on the shelf.
YOU'RE A SLUT.
-Alma!
-Hey.
They gave you your phone back.
Yeah, for ten minutes.
And only after I've studied,
and if I ask really nicely.
It's about time.
The Dorayakis aren't on offer anymore,
and I was spending a fortune.
It's not so bad without a phone.
I have more time to study,
even to read.
What do you read?
Well, your letter,
before I go to sleep.
You should be a writer.
It's so beautiful.
I wrote it from the heart.
I know that.
I remembered something.
From the summer
they took you out of school.
We were the saddest pair in the world.
We'd spend the day lying around,
doing nothing, not talking.
But it didn't matter.
What mattered was we were together.
Now everybody knows everything
about everyone,
and they tell everything, and that's...
It's like emotional porn.
"Emotional porn"?
It's from one of my mother's books.
I love you loads, Alma.
And I love you.
I'm fine, okay?
Don't worry.
Okay.
PENELOPE SAYS GOOD NIGHT
"Time to turn the lights off."
"And where's Penelope?"
"Do you see her?"
She's here!
Good girl!
Now off to sleep. It's very late.
-Will you read it to me again?
-Again?
You'll catch a cold.
What are you doing?
There's a leak in the junk room.
Look, Penelope.
"The frying pan is too heavy,
and it hits Penelope in the face."
Bam!
I loved this.
See if anything else is worth keeping,
and we'll toss the rest.
It's my stuff.
It's taking up space,
and you don't even remember what's here.
I spent my afternoons with these toys.
You too.
Alma, I went to the trouble
of packing them up and storing them away.
-What? Wait, I'll help...
-I'll take them.
I don't want your help.
-Hello?
-Hello.
-Hi.
-I brought you this.
-You'd better come in.
-Okay.
-We can have a drink if you like.
Okay.
Have you seen
those YouTube fireplace videos?
I'm embarrassed to think
of someone sitting with some wine,
putting on a fake fire,
and turning out the lights.
Maybe it's a paradigm
of how bad society is doing.
Greta's a Nordic name.
Do you have family in Sweden,
Denmark, or somewhere like that?
-No?
-No.
When I was little, they told me
the story of Hansel and Gretel
and the candy house.
Where did you leave Hansel?
There is no Hansel.
So you're alone in the woods.
I really think there's a need for some
feminist revisionism
of traditional fairy tales.
Because, look...
The witch...
Well,
I think she's just an independent woman...
who's attracted to Gretel
and lures her to her house with candy,
and once inside, she makes her do
everything she wants.
And...
Gretel loves it.
You can do what you like with me.
The Brothers Grimm were German, right?
What?
-Gosh, I'm boring you to death.
-No.
It was me. You mentioned that story,
and I drifted off...
I'm sorry. Besides, it's Friday,
and I'm sure you've got
better things to be doing.
So, shall we meet up next week?
Okay.
-No problem.
-Okay?
Can you go get your brother?
Where is he?
At his friend Eli's house.
Jeez, Mom, it's two blocks,
and he's ten. Can't he come back alone?
Do you know
how many ten-year-olds get run over?
They've shut themselves
in the upstairs room. One second.
-We were in the middle of a game.
-You've been on for hours. Let's go.
Mom, can Álex sleep here this weekend?
No, honey, we're going skiing tomorrow.
-Maybe next weekend, okay?
-Great.
Let's go.
I HAVE A PLAN FOR THIS WEEKEND
YOU'LL GO FREAKING CRAZY
ALBERTO:
GREAT!!!
Come here.
Change sides and catch!
Go!
How's school?
Fine.
I'm getting some good grades,
and Nata and her study group
are helping me with notes.
Will you pass?
Yes.
Yes, I'll pass.
I'll work really hard, and I'll get there.
We can go shopping later if you like.
I'm sure you need something.
I'd love to,
but I can't.
I have a lot to catch up on
and not much time to do it.
Besides, Greta
said she wanted to come
to see me this afternoon.
Can she?
Okay with you?
Sure.
I fixed the leak.
No more water in the junk room.
We can put the boxes
with your stuff back in there.
Cool.
Jeez, it's like... Sometimes I go nuts
and watch him eat for hours.
The noise is fucking gross, Berta.
It's far-out, even for you.
It's the algorithm.
It's like it brings out
the worst in me, you know?
It's like an inner god.
Like the keeper of my secrets,
like an invisible friend
who knows me best.
Yes, and you too.
-Me?
-Yes.
-Look, I'll show you.
-No.
No, I want the link
between the algorithm and me
to be totally private, thanks.
-You're hiding something, Alma.
-What do you mean?
-Come on, I can tell.
-No, Berta, don't go all psycho.
I know you.
Okay.
I'll stop.
Whoa, this is the best!
Let's go.
The keys are in that pot.
Come on.
There's no one here.
-Come on.
-Hey.
Hey, come here.
Goddammit.
-Awesome!
-Wow!
Amazing!
No fucking way. We're doing it right.
Put this on and make dinner
while I fix myself up.
-Go on.
-Okay.
I really need to pee.
Where's the bathroom?
-Down the hall, on the right.
-Okay.
Berta.
Sorry, I couldn't find the bathroom.
Use the one in the hall.
First door on the left.
Okay, I'm really sorry.
It's all right.
-Didn't you get dressed?
-This is it, idiot.
You're fucking awesome, Nata.
Dinner?
-Sure, come on.
-Come on.
-S'il vous plaît.
-Thanks.
Watch the door!
Now we're ready.
Whoa!
Stop.
Not like that.
If you come, I'll kill you.
Did you come?
Of course.
I'm such an asshole.
Why?
How the fuck
did I ever think
your brother wanted to be with me?
Have you seen me?
Anyway, the girls he was talking to...
They weren't that hot.
If he'd been a bit wasted,
I could've denied it all.
Are you done?
Don't ever say anything like that again.
Alma, you're amazing.
And you're the bravest girl I've ever met.
Alma.
Goddammit!
I mean, you're...
You're Alma,
you know?
Sometimes I forget.
Okay.
Well, don't ever forget it.
What?
Are we leaving it like this, or what?
What are you doing?
Fuck!
SLUT
WAKE UP
PUTOALFUCKING
1 NEW MESSAGE
LIKE MY DICK, BITCH?
Fuck it.
What the fuck are you talking about?
-What?
-You're talking about me?
No, we're talking about Christian.
He made out with a girl in junior high.
The next day he acted
like he didn't know her.
What's so funny about that?
Hey, Alma. Take it easy, okay?
You've been a pain in the ass lately.
Are you playing with me, Hernán?
Playing what?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Look, if this is
some shitty revenge, stop it, okay?
Right now, I'm the last person
you should play a joke on.
You have to look much sluttier.
-Slutty like how?
-Push your boobs up.
And open your mouth a bit.
Like that.
That's it.
Don't take those shitty photos
of yourselves.
Listen to her! What the fuck
do you care what we do?
Don't take any fucking notice.
That's all we fucking need.
Miss Morality on her high horse.
GALLERY
DELETE THIS PHOTO? DELETE
Watch out for this topic
because it always comes up in the SATs.
And it's not easy.
A lot of general knowledge, dates, laws...
And I'll finish this line next week.
Right, bye.
How are you?
Fine.
Look, I'm going to steal
Bernardo's exclusive.
You passed the first economics assessment.
-What?
-Well done.
Really?
-Thank you.
-No, thank you.
For what?
When I give up a student for lost,
and then see they're not,
I take it as a gift.
You put that very nicely.
You're doing great.
What the hell's up with her?
Moping around all day...
I don't know.
You do know. Tell me.
I'm telling you I don't know.
Who knows what she's been taking?
Don't talk like that about Alma.
She's my friend.
-She doesn't like me either.
-I don't care. I don't like it.
If she's a slut, then what am I?
After the other night,
you're a fucking crazy criminal.
Shut up. They'll hear us.
And don't talk to me like that.
All right, okay.
Jeez, what a temper.
Greta, have you seen my headphones?
In my room.
By the way, any news of Alma?
For someone who's not into her,
you're very interested.
No, I just feel responsible
for what happened at the party.
Right.
Well...
She's fine. I saw her, and she's fine.
Okay.
Hey, did you take some of my weed?
A little to smoke
with the guys in class, but very little.
Right.
I'm missing more.
Ciao.
The last book you read.
Americanah.
A word you hate.
Urine.
It's awful.
-I'm rolling a joint. Do you mind?
-No.
-Use some of mine if you like.
I don't like to use my customers' weed.
Do you have many?
Professional secret.
Just kidding.
I don't even do this for a living.
I just know people with good weed
and pass it to people I like.
That's it. I don't make anything.
Just smoke for free.
In fact, you're subsidizing this joint.
So you like me.
You know the answer already.
Come on, let's keep going.
Your turn.
How was it your first time?
Dammit!
Look, it's like...
I haven't finished rolling, and already
I'm getting a bit dirty.
-No, here goes.
-Sorry.
I can only think of asking
dirty stuff, okay?
I don't know what to do.
Wake up, Alma! It's my birthday!
Let's go!
Party!
Come here.
Take it easy, kids. Take it outside.
-You're the clown on the cake?
-Who?
What's this?
Okay.
Yes.
It's Pablito's birthday.
Thank you for volunteering.
You're welcome.
I think my mother
would rather have you as a daughter.
All the girls over 40 are into me.
Did I miss something?
Okay.
I have something wild to tell you.
All right.
Look.
I've become the dealer...
for a girl well in her 30s,
and I really like her.
What?
Where did she come from?
I met her in the supermarket.
I've dealt to her a few times.
I've spent three Saturdays at her house.
-Have you made out?
-No.
Not yet.
But I jerk off thinking about her.
Fuck, Greta.
I bet you jerk off
thinking about my mother.
Don't you jerk off
thinking about my mother?
No.
I love you loads.
-I love you sometimes.
-Sure.
I'm getting a drink, okay?
Your kids are really excited
about the vacation you promised them.
No, I'm not sorting out your shit!
Come and tell them to their faces,
if you can!
No, you listen to me!
Own your responsibilities.
Yes, I know you have a girlfriend,
but you also have three kids.
WHAT YOU DOING? I NEED TO GET OUT.
Why do I have to take care of everything?
I'm so fed up with you!
LILY:
COME TO MINE
You know what? Fuck off.
COOL!!!
One, two, and three!
Bring on the candy!
Yay!
Yes!
That's it.
What if... Take him some.
Take him a piece.
Okay.
Hi there.
Anyone want some cake? I made it myself.
I do.
Greta asked me to go for a walk
around the neighborhood. Can I?
The cake is delicious.
She deserves it.
I'll be back at 10:00.
Yes?
Yes.
Thanks for saving me.
It was a great plan.
-Do you want to go back?
-No.
-Let's go back.
-No way.
What do you want to do?
I want to show you something.
Okay.
I was sent this photo
and another two dick pics.
Who the fuck sent you this?
He used a nickname.
PutoAlfucking.
-What a fucking clown.
-Right.
You're sure you don't know who sent it?
Alma, can you tell me now, please?
Okay.
The night of the party,
when you went for the coats...
someone turned up.
What are you doing here?
I was really fucked up.
And I didn't want to see your brother.
Or you.
Please, get me out of here.
I swear I wasn't thinking
of disappearing like that,
but the Molly took over,
everything started spinning, and...
I didn't want my parents
to see me like that.
So I asked him to take me to his place.
I didn't know what I was doing.
And I thought
that maybe fucking Hernán
would make me feel better.
But it wasn't a good idea.
The next day,
I had the world's worst hangover,
and I just wanted to run out of there.
-Where are you going?
-My coat?
You didn't have a coat.
Shit, fuck.
-What's wrong?
-This didn't happen, okay?
Don't you dare tell anyone!
Wait, Alma. Alma!
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
I guess I had to process it,
and I was ashamed.
Come here, please.
Greta...
what if Hernán sent the photos?
Then send him a message.
-Now?
-Yes.
Tell him you want to see him.
Berta, what's bothering you so much?
I don't know.
He talks like it's for the Tate Modern.
It's not like that. It's just a show
at the local cultural center.
-Where's the bathroom?
-At the end of the hall.
Are you drinking that?
He's famous. What are you saying?
-Hey, girls.
-They let you out.
-You see? I'll be right back.
-How are you?
What's up, Gretix?
What did you want to talk about?
I want to show you something.
-Maybe you've seen it, huh?
-Let's see.
Did you take it?
No. No way.
-What's this?
-It's this fucking photo.
And this one.
Is this your dick? Or is this it?
Are you crazy?
I've got nothing to do with that.
I don't do that shit.
-Give me your phone.
-What?
Give her your damn phone, Hernán.
Give it to her. Now.
-Fuck, give it to her!
-Okay.
Here.
I wouldn't do that.
We're friends.
Look, Hernán,
a friend doesn't pull down your panties
and fuck you
when you're wasted
and someone's just broken your heart.
What did you tell her?
The truth.
We fucked because you wanted to.
I didn't force you.
In fact...
if anyone took advantage, you did of me.
-You left me there like a piece of shit.
-What? Bullshit, Hernán.
Don't you get it, Greta?
You're the one who doesn't get it.
Okay?
You couldn't wait to fuck her
and made the most
of her being wasted to do it.
Alma.
You're disgusting, man.
A real friend would've left me
at my front door.
Look, man, I think you should get lost.
-You're kidding me, right?
-No.
-You're shitting me, right?
-Beat it.
Beat it.
This is bullshit, man.
This is fucking bullshit.
Alma.
It was okay outside. No damage.
We came in, the couch was slit...
Hey.
You didn't do anything wrong, okay?
Just forget about it.
I'm thinking about the photos.
I don't think it's Hernán.
Who the fuck is sending me this shit?
Oh, you bitch.