["Superwoman" by Ben Sumner
& Glenn Herweijer playing]
MARI, NOT A WHORE OR A SLUT
[gurgling]
♪ In the morning ♪
[crying] Go away!
♪ I'm the best
You others are appalling ♪
♪ I can handle everything with ease
It's a breeze ♪
♪ Slice of cheese
Know what I mean, now wait a minute ♪
♪ Sometimes my head is big
And don't I know it, ha ha ha ♪
♪ Addicted to this bro
Hope I don't blow it ♪
♪ I don't blow it ♪
♪ Every single day I'm running
Making waves ♪
♪ I'm not just a pretty face ♪
♪ I'm a superwoman ♪
♪ Super, super woman ♪
♪ Am I wrong to be strong?
Beat your ass to the song ♪
♪ Flip the script on the chick
Said I can't but I did ♪
♪ Am I wrong to be strong?
Beat your ass to the song ♪
♪ Flip a script on the chick
Said I can't but I did ♪
♪ In the morning ♪
[music fades]
RAISING VOICES
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY MIGUEL SÁEZ CARRAL
[bleeping]
[ominous music plays]
[Berta] I took this photo
the day I decided to slit my wrists.
I couldn't take it anymore.
#I'DPREFERTOBELYINGFLAT
#LEAVINGTHEPAGEOFTHEBOOKOPEN
POSTING
It was better to end it all.
#THISPAINNEVERGOESAWAY
- [clamoring, screaming]
- [phone ringing]
[woman] 1-1-2, what's your emergency?
How can I help?
[man] A young girl's been hit by a car
and she isn't moving at all.
[medic] All right, what's your name?
[chatter on telephone]
Alma.
Very good, Alma.
Listen, I'll take you to the hospital.
We'll be there in a few minutes.
Mm? Just relax.
Everything is going to be fine.
Let's go.
[siren wailing]
One, two, three.
[Nata's mom] Natacha! It's dinner time.
Can you come down and help me, please?
[male TV host] Millions of women
around the world,
summoned by different organizations,
have come out to the streets
to march and commemorate March 8th.
[water running]
Across five continents,
purple signs, scarves and t-shirts...
[Nata's mom] I don't understand
the point of all this.
Yeah, I really don't.
[male TV host] The demonstrations address
misogynist violence and aggression.
[chopping vegetables]
- [breathing heavily]
- [dog barking in distance]
[menacing music plays]
What's wrong?
I think I've been selling weed
to an undercover officer.
[Greta panting]
What?
I... Well, I've been set up and, uh...
Now there's
a super weird-looking car outside,
that I'm sure is watching us.
And they're going to find us all
and arrest us all, David.
Okay, Greta, calm down.
Okay? Where's the car?
On the street.
It's not the Guardia.
The neighbors bought a new car.
- Hey, hey. It's all right.
- No, I just wanna fucking die, I swear.
It's fine, Greta. Okay?
But I need you to focus right now,
and tell me what happened,
from the very beginning, all right?
And be very honest.
It's important, all right?
[Greta sobbing] Uh...
Well, so I... [inaudible]
♪ I, I turn you up, caffeine ♪
♪ Walking with a lean
I got what you need ♪
♪ You need a pick-me-up
No slow down, yeah ♪
♪ French Vanilla drippin' in your cup
I turn you up, caffeine ♪
♪ Shake it on the floor, make it explode ♪
♪ Wanna see that soda pop pop, overflow ♪
♪ Sonnez les matines
Sonnez les matines ♪
♪ French vanilla drippin' in your cup ♪
♪ Dormez-vous? Dormez-vous? ♪
♪ I turn you up
French vanilla drippin' in your cup ♪
♪ Sonnez les matines
Sonnez les matines ♪
♪ I turn you up
French vanilla drippin' in your cup ♪
♪ Dormez-vous? Dormez-vous? ♪
[door closes]
[machine beeping]
[rustling]
Hello, Alma.
How are you feeling today?
Okay.
Your exams all came out very good.
You're extremely lucky.
There are no fractures,
or hemorrhaging of any sort.
But we're keeping you in longer
for observation, 'til tomorrow night.
- Sound good?
- Okay.
Uh, are... are my parents here?
Yes, I spoke with your father already.
No problems from him.
He can come in for a moment, hm?
Let's see.
All right.
I'll take off your C collar.
You no longer need it.
Here's your father, honey.
Just a couple of minutes.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
I didn't even break anything.
Well, I guess being hard-headed
finally came in handy.
[both chuckle softly]
So how did it even happen?
I ran into the street and wasn't looking.
I wanted to get
to the women's march with Mom.
- She knows that I'm fine, right?
- Yes, of course.
She's at the house with Pablito,
and told me to send her love.
I can go home if I want to, right?
- I'm fine.
- Yeah.
I'll give you a piggy-back ride,
like that time you were very sick.
Do you remember?
Get your rest.
I'll be here tomorrow morning,
first thing, okay?
[poignant music plays]
[cellphone vibrates]
ALBERTO:
ARE YOU AWAKE?
ALBERTO: I CAN'T SLEEP.
DAMMIT, THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL
[sniffles]
[indistinct chatter, footsteps]
- [ominous music plays]
- [breathing uneasily]
- [clamoring]
- [metal clanging]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [loud ringing]
- [girl] Can I drink water?
- [nurse] Not right now, honey.
The doctor is going
to come see you shortly.
And she'll tell you if you
can eat or drink something.
- Get some rest, okay?
- Okay.
Berta?
Is that you?
It's Alma.
Why are you here?
Got hit by a car.
You?
Because...
I tried to kill myself.
[Berta's mom] It's likely that we'll stay
for dinner and come back late.
Don't be throwing any parties now.
[Berta chuckles] No, relax.
Besides, I have a project to finish.
[Berta's mom] Okay.
[Berta] What is it? Are you hungry?
Look after them, okay?
[dramatic music plays]
[Berta] Mm.
I prepared 112 pills.
Ironic that it's 112.
Like the emergency number.
It's a miracle you're okay.
[Berta] I didn't manage to take them all.
My mom got home earlier
than she said she would.
I think that, um,
I think she had a hunch
that I might try again.
Wait, you've tried before?
[Berta] Two times.
Holy shit, Berta.
But,
I mean, why?
I can't bear it anymore.
I feel like I don't have the energy to
withstand another fucking crisis.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of the anxiety attacks.
Of the tremors.
The diarrhea, the vomiting.
Stop looking at me like I'm abnormal.
I'm not.
I've been this way
since he began to rape me.
Who?
You know him.
I'm sure he's still
teaching your History class.
What?
[Berta] It all started
with my parents' divorce.
[indistinct shouting]
[Berta] It was a horrible time in my life.
I was majorly fucked up.
[Berta's mom] Listen to me! Fucker!
I hate you!
You fucking son of a bitch!
[door slams]
[door opens]
[Berta] He was the only one who...
Who noticed.
He was nice to me. He...
[teacher] Berta?
[Berta] He told me
that he'd been through the same thing.
And that he knew how I felt.
[Berta laughs]
So, I
clung to him like a lifeline.
- I would...
- Berta!
...look for him in the schoolyard.
He made me feel good.
- He said that... that I was special.
- [indistinct chatter]
I came to think
that he liked me like I liked him.
I told him my secrets.
Private things.
I sent him pictures.
Then one afternoon,
he made me go up to his office.
And... [clears throat]
[breathes shakily]
He made me touch him.
He forced me.
He wiped himself on my uniform.
After school,
I threw it in a trash container.
That way I could pretend
as if nothing ever happened.
Or as if it wouldn't happen again.
But that isn't how it happened.
[tense music plays]
So you haven't told anyone?
Like who?
[poignant music plays]
I was afraid no one
would believe me.
Or they
would think that I was the one
who started it.
[Berta] The abuse stopped. But...
something had broken inside of me.
I fell into a deep, fucked up depression.
Every night,
I'd get as fucked up as I could
on anything I could get my hands on.
And that's when I first attempted
to commit suicide.
Young ladies. Back to your own bed.
[nurse] I'm going to give you something
so you can sleep, okay?
- Everything all right?
- Mm-hmm.
[screams]
[panting]
Are you gonna keep acting
like you didn't know, Alma?
You were there.
[panicked crying]
[panting]
Morning, sweetheart.
- How are you feeling?
- Where's Berta?
They took her up to the ward.
[Christian] You think she told anyone?
I don't know.
[Christian] Fuck.
But after what happened yesterday,
I'd expect anything.
- [Alberto] Hey, babe.
- Hello.
I sent you a bunch of texts last night.
Hm, I fell asleep early.
[Christian] Hey, you're not mad, are you?
We were just messing around.
Course not. I know that. Gonna go pee.
[puffs] Full of shit.
TYPES OF COMPANIES
The origin of the funds can be net,
which are those funds
that are the company's own,
or they can be passive...
[girl] This means that the profits
increase little by little.
Now that they've
returned from their work trip.
We went to this awesome country house.
You'd love it.
[indistinct chatter]
[bell rings]
[Andrea] See you.
[chatter, laughter]
Take care.
So? Nata, how'd you do?
Nata!
Hey!
I was walking home and I...
I saw a Guardia Civil car.
But it went straight.
Listen, after uh...
After... last night,
I think we should call it off.
- What?
- I mean the house thing.
[scoffs]
So I have spent all fucking day preparing
for this moment and you come and screw it.
I don't know why it surprises me.
You're capable of ruining anything.
But you know what?
Whatever.
We're done. We're officially over.
- What? Why? Wait, Nata. No, listen.
- Don't fucking touch me!
You wanted your friends to fuck me.
You're fucking disgusting.
What are you saying? You told me you
wanted to fuck around with multiple guys.
But it was a fantasy, you moron!
I wanted to make you horny.
But if you wanna set something up,
call Christian, let him fuck you
in the ass, since you like that anyway.
- You'll not talk to me like that.
- I'll talk to you however I please.
And don't fuck with me or I'll tell my mom
and you can kiss Canada goodbye.
- [Alberto] Nata.
- And one more thing.
I ended this, okay?
So until the school year ends,
you're gonna put on a sad face
and you're gonna shut your fucking mouth.
Nata, wait.
Forget about taking this bus,
because there's no way we're sharing one.
[door closes]
- [Nata's mom] Natacha, what is this?
- Fuck, Mama! You scared me.
- [Nata] Why aren't you at work?
- Answer my question.
Um...
I borrowed it from a friend. It's, um...
It's my costume for a party.
I'm going as Mariah Carey.
[Nata's mom] Another house
got broken into yesterday.
And the neighbors said
they saw a group of guys run out
with a girl who was wearing
Christmas pajamas just like these!
My God, Nata, was it you?
MER: HEY, I'M WAITING FOR YOU.
ARE YOU COMING?
MER: EVERYTHING OKAY?
MER: IT'S A BIT LATE. RAIN CHECK?
MER: HOPE YOU'RE OKAY
SORRY, MY PHONE DIED IN THE AFTERNOON.
SMALL PROBLEM. NOTHING SERIOUS
[cellphone pings]
MER: SEE YOU SATURDAY?
[puffs]
[elevator voice] Doors opening.
[poignant music plays]
Wanna go out on piggyback? Huh?
It's all right, sweetie.
Everything's okay. Come here.
Darling, I made you some soup. Want any?
Later, thank you.
DON'T LOOK AT US
JOIN US
KIND PEOPLE ARE MY KINDA PEOPLE
Does it hurt?
Yeah?
You're gonna need
a different haircut it seems, huh?
What's wrong?
Huh?
Wanna talk about it?
I ran into...
Into Berta earlier.
At the hospital.
Just a coincidence. She...
She had tried to kill herself.
She just can't handle life, you know?
It's okay.
It's okay, my love.
It's just that I haven't always
been very nice to her, Mom and I...
[sniffling]
You know it's not your fault, okay?
- Honey, are you sure?
- Yeah.
[Vero] Really?
Because there's no going back, okay?
Yes. I don't want to hide the scar.
- [Vero] Wanna be able to see all of it?
- Yeah, all of it.
[Vero chuckles] Well, all right then.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Wait.
- Yes or no?
- Ready. Just careful, okay?
Okay.
[hair clippers buzzing]
[Vero] Here goes.
Jesus.
[both chuckle]
Tsk. You look bomb.
You think?
Yeah, mean it.
How are things at your house?
No one's murdered me
and hid me in the yard,
like some family killers.
That's already way more than I expected.
[Alma] What are you going to do
about your officer friend?
Do you think I should try to go see her?
Um, that's probably the worst idea
you've ever had, seriously.
I think you should delete her number and
stay away from the supermarket
for some time.
[Greta] I don't know, I'll figure it out.
And Nata? Have you heard from her?
I think that she's grounded.
[Nata's mom] Your father and I
are very disappointed, Natacha.
What was the point of spending
all that money on your education?
For the love of God, you're a savage.
So have you decided to turn me in?
I mean, obviously not.
Do you have any idea of the economic
and legal consequences that would bring?
But that doesn't mean you won't get
the punishment you deserve, young lady.
- Okay, I'll be in my room.
- We are not done here!
- Nata, are you a drug addict?
- What?
No. Papa!
The Guardia Civil found joints
in the ashtrays in the house.
- Don't dare lie to me.
- Mama, I said I do not smoke weed.
Who is your dealer?
I've never been high,
I don't know how to roll a joint.
You don't want to cooperate? Very well.
Seems I don't have another option.
The next day, Mama checked me into rehab.
She shit herself.
Soon as we arrive,
a poor toothless junkie says, "Hi" to her.
And she takes off running
as if she's seen Pennywise the clown.
Anyway,
grounded with no allowance.
No partying on the weekends.
Well, doesn't matter anyway,
because I don't have anywhere to go.
You gotta report those guys, Nata.
[sighs]
And what exactly do I report?
The fact that the three of them
tried to rape you.
Ugh, really? I mean,
why won't you let it go?
Nothing happened, so forget it.
Well, sure, those guys
didn't hurt you but... but they wanted to.
What would've happened
if the Guardia hadn't showed up?
[tense music plays]
[buckle clinks]
Nothing, you don't get it.
I can't accuse those guys of anything.
Not to mention
what everyone would think of me.
- What?
- [Nata] That I provoked them,
that I'm a slut,
that I wanted it to happen, for example.
[clears throat] I have read
about serious cases where, in the end, uh,
no one listens to the girl
and they call her a liar.
Nata,
everybody should be aware
of how shitty Alberto and his friends are.
They should be forced
to stand in front of everyone,
and confess what they tried
to do and beg your forgiveness.
Fuck, Nata, they should wear
a fucking sign around their necks
for the rest of their lives, get it?
Are you positive it's not a brain injury
you have? Because you sound unhinged.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I am not okay.
I know.
I'm sorry.
[male voice on TV]
[cellphone pings]
IT'S DAVID. THIS IS MY NEW NUMBER.
HOW ARE YOU?
BETTER, IT WAS JUST A SCARE.
THE CAR WAS GOING SLOWLY.
HOW ARE YOU?
[cellphone buzzes]
[David] Good, good.
Hey, didn't you and I have a date planned?
We can leave it
for another day if you want.
I can't imagine
you're in the mood for anything.
But I'd like to see you.
How about a smoke and a quick trip
around the neighborhood?
We could have a non-date. [chuckles]
What do you think?
[Alma] Hey.
Hey, there.
[Alma chuckles]
Just so we're clear, this isn't our date.
Sure it isn't.
[motorcycle engine roars]
[Alma] She was in shock.
She couldn't believe the mess
she had gotten into, poor thing.
She was really scared.
[David] Yeah.
Same here.
I thought that there'd be a checkpoint
at every intersection I'd drive up to,
and I'd just fucking panic.
Relax.
It's fine, and besides,
I have it all under control.
No, it's not that.
[sniffles]
I've been kinda emotional
after the accident. It's the shock.
Is that weed?
- No.
- Ugh.
Nothing but cigarettes
for our first non-date.
How 'bout on the second one?
We'll see.
You know, being hospitalized
didn't totally suck.
Why?
I was jacked up on a ton of painkillers.
So I was high for the most part.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Should probably get hit
by a car every weekend.
I mean, it'd be cheaper.
May I see the damage?
See? Pretty sure
that I'm gonna have a scar.
Cooler than a tattoo.
[chuckles] Definitely better than yours.
You look really pretty.
Someone's an awesome kisser.
I've had lots of practice, you know?
[David] Mm.
[dramatic music plays]
[Greta] I just have to convince her
that I've stopped dealing, and that's it.
Look, I tell her this is the very last bit
I'm able to sell her.
That way, she'll leave me be.
But I just need at least five more grams.
[both laughing]
Greta, stop it.
Stop, stop. Stop.
Stop.
Mmm...
You don't... feel anything? Or...?
Hm.
I was diagnosed with cancer last year.
The thing is, um...
Well, whatever.
The cancer was in my breast.
Um...
So I had a mastectomy.
I haven't really shown anyone my body yet
because I don't feel
that comfortable, you see?
And now, are you doing fine?
Uh, healthwise, yes.
But I'm not really feeling my best
after everything I've gone through.
[Mer] The day I saw you
at the supermarket,
something happened to me.
I don't know how to explain it.
But after that day,
I went back to the supermarket
because I wanted to,
I don't know, I wanted to see you.
And...
Well, when you were there, I felt
like you were looking for me too.
And so... [soft chuckle] ...I waited.
I was waiting for you there.
♪ Those were the days
I could still touch your face ♪
["Those Were The Days"
by Musou Music playing]
So, um, I've upgraded
to fine processed pastries.
[Mer] And then, with the weed, well,
I don't know. It was like
the perfect excuse to see you again.
Look, I know this is insane.
Shit, I didn't think
this would ever be in my future.
But, well, until very recently,
I didn't even think I'd have a future.
It's a bit pathetic, isn't it?
Not at all.
Mer, am I under investigation?
Wait, what?
I don't understand.
I know you're with the Guardia.
Are you investigating me? You can tell me.
But investigating for what?
For dealing weed?
I work in a different department.
I have nothing to do with narcotics.
Who told you I work with the Guardia?
Uh, no one. Some guys I know
showed me, um, a few pictures
of you going into work.
- Pictures of me?
- Yes.
Okay.
Anyway. Well, I was positive
that you were setting me up
and that you'd been investigating me to...
Um, well, to arrest my brother.
Wait a sec,
you know I'm with the Guardia Civil,
so why'd you come tonight?
I mean, what was all this?
Jesus.
Were you trying to screw me,
then just blackmail me or something?
Yes.
So wait, how old are you really?
Seventeen.
Right.
Well, I promise that neither you
nor your brother will have any problems.
But I think it's best if things end here.
You'd better go home.
[Alma] Oh no, you really don't have to.
[Berta] I insist. It'd make my day
if you took it.
I mean it.
[Berta chuckles]
- Did you want a ride?
- Sure.
["Dreams Abt Optimism"
by Tiffany Day plays]
♪ This summer didn't really
Go as planned ♪
♪ Maybe way too many people
And I caught myself not thinking enough ♪
[Hernán] Alma!
- You've done it again.
- Why is that?
Once again, everyone's talking about you.
- Because of the hair?
- It's sick.
But, no.
There was a rumor about you dying.
So now you're a fucking legend.
Yeah.
- [Mai] Alma! How are you? Good?
- [boy] Hey.
[girl] Wow.
- What do you think?
- Pretty wild, huh?
- [boy] Let's see.
- You've got some ovaries.
[girl] Oh my gosh!
Here, look.
We took notes for you on everything,
so you'll be ready for the exams.
- Mm, thanks. You're the best.
- You got it.
I saw the ambulance. Can I see it?
- Mind if I take a photo?
- Uh, no.
- No, please don't.
- Okay.
[teacher] Alma!
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, everyone.
- [students] Hello.
- How are you? Let's see.
I'm fine. Doing okay now.
Doesn't look bad.
We're really pleased
that you made such a rapid recovery.
Did the trimmer run out of batteries
or what happened?
- Don't listen to this guy.
- Sorry.
You look phenomenal. You actually look
like a Viking warrior queen.
Thank you.
And yeah, it ran out of batteries.
Well, you can count on us
for whatever you need, you know that.
Let's get moving! Get to class,
please, recess is done, all right?
- Me too?
- Especially you.
Oh, my god.
Jackrussell shoots!
Shit, he misses.
Thought you might actually make that one.
Yo, blame it on those bastards
Kevin and Jota.
They're the worst, dude.
♪ You giving me
Giving me dreams bout optimism ♪
♪ I wanna be
Wanna be good now, that's the vision ♪
♪ I'm turning my
Turning my back on old tradition ♪
♪ And he hit it so nice
Yeah I'm feeling so high ♪
♪ I think I could fly ♪
Well, we made it back home.
♪ Yeah, I know I'll be fine
It get better with time ♪
♪ I'm running, I'm running
I stop when he tell me something ♪
♪ Been spending that, spending that Guap
make me feel so lucky ♪
♪ I'm lucky
He sucky ♪
♪ He love when he around me ♪
[message pings]
♪ You jumped in my life
Yeah just like that, yeah so damn quick ♪
DAMN SHITTY SHAVING JOB
YOU DID ON YOURSELF, SLUT
♪ And I guess
I'm so much more secure than I thought ♪
♪ You helped me realize
The shit that I'm not ♪
WHEN I FIND OUT WHO YOU ARE,
I'M CUTTING OFF THAT SHITTY WORM
AND FEEDING IT TO THE BIRDS.
What a cunt.
♪ Turning my back on old tradition ♪
♪ You giving me
Giving me dreams bout optimism ♪
♪ I wanna be
Wanna be good now, that's the vision ♪
♪ I'm turning my
Turning my back on old tradition ♪
NEGATIVE
- [dog barks]
- What's up, Gregory?
What?
Hey, there.
Did Berta tell you too?
Bet that's why you look so sad.
[doorbell rings]
- Good morning, dear.
- Hello.
Come on in.
[cartoon voices on TV]
Berta told me that you saw
each other at the hospital.
- How are you?
- Yeah, fine.
No consequences, except
for the hair trim, of course.
- It suits you. You're very pretty.
- Thank you.
Head on up, Berta's in her bedroom.
Berta, Alma's come to see you!
[knocking on door]
Hey.
How are you?
Pretty good, actually.
I'm on these new pills that are the shit.
Now everything looks so colorful again
and I have this incredible urge to live.
[both chuckle]
That's great.
Why are you here so early in the morning?
Um... I wanted to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Three years ago,
I was there.
I had a stomach bug,
and like always, our toilets were clogged.
OUT OF ORDER
So I went up to the teachers' toilets.
Then I heard his voice.
[teacher] Look me in the eye.
[tense music plays]
[teacher] You'll always look me
in the eyes, right?
You know I like that.
[Alma] He sounded angry.
I couldn't hear what he said to you,
but it didn't sound good.
[teacher grunts]
[teacher talking indistinctly]
[Alma] I replayed it
in my head a million times.
I couldn't find a logical explanation,
so I decided not to tell anyone
and to just pretend it never happened.
- I really am sorry, Berta, honestly.
- Mm.
- Forgive me, please.
- No, no.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
You were only 13 years old
and you were frightened.
- It wasn't your fault.
- But if I'd said something...
Maybe he would have been arrested
and I could've avoided this depression
and the three suicide attempts. Or not.
You know,
I always suspected
that you may have known.
Couldn't be a coincidence
that around that time
you walked in the opposite direction
every time you saw me.
After school,
in between classes, at recess.
- Berta, you should really turn him in.
- No.
Berta, I'll go with you.
I'll back you up, yeah?
No way.
No way, Alma, you've already helped me
more than you can imagine. But...
No.
At least,
say what he did to you to others.
I can't, Alma. I will not do it.
But this isn't just about you.
We have time to avoid this
happening to other girls
In the same position
who could suffer like you did.
I bet that son of a bitch
is looking for a new victim right now.
I can't. I can't do it!
And besides, I've no proof,
so if I chose to accuse him,
it's my word against his.
- But I saw you there.
- No, you saw us both talking.
You don't even know
what happened in that room though.
I trust you.
But Alma, that's the thing!
It doesn't matter.
If it did, I'd have to relive
what happened in there over again.
Relive it all.
Every single day
of that fucking school year.
And it's too much, Alma.
It'd be easier for me to die
than to think about that.
Please, Alma.
Promise me that you
won't tell anyone anything?
[ominous music plays]
[Alma] Psychomorphology studies
the unique physical traits of murderers,
psychopaths, or pedophiles.
HISTORYTEACHER05
According to science, there are signs
that allow us to see traces of evil
in the face of a criminal.
But the truth is,
nature should have marked these people
in a more conspicuous way.
To warn people
about what lies beneath the surface.
Maybe with some bizarre skin pigmentation.
Or a compulsion to scratch
their heads all the time,
Or an inner voice that forces them to
introduce themselves as sexual predators.
I'M A RAPIST
That might stop teenagers who are feeling
lost from entering their hunting grounds.
WITH MY FAVORITE STUDENTS!
Instead, they're out there,
all around us,
invisible,
roaming unnoticed like a shark
swimming near a crowded beach.
So...
I'm just gonna have to paint
your fucking face then.
[serene music plays]
[engine sounds]