[birds chirping]
[woman] Run, run, run, run, run! [laughs]
- I love you, Mommy.
- I love you, baby girl.
[Vero laughing]
[young Alma laughing]
[Pablo laughing]
Wrestling match?
RAISING VOICES
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY MIGUEL SÁEZ CARRAL
[bleeping]
THESE ARE THE SCARS THAT FADED FIRST
[ominous music plays]
# FEAR #SCARS
#ITWASN'TMYFAULT
POSTING
[Vero] These are the marks
that faded first.
#PAINANDDISGUSTANDTERROR
#SCARSTHATDON'TFADE
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct background chatter on TV]
[knocking on door]
Alma? Do you want to watch a movie?
We can make some popcorn if you want.
- [wind howling]
- [curtains blowing]
[ominous music plays]
[sighs]
Alma!
Fuck!
[ominous music continues]
[rain lashing]
[cellphone pings]
MOM: ALMA, COME HOME RIGHT NOW.
DON'T MAKE THINGS WORSE. TURN ROUND NOW!
Hey, get in.
Come on.
[sighs]
So where's this party at?
Huh?
Don't tell me you got dolled up
just to meet people in town.
Where is it? Mind if we tag along?
Alma, sit in the middle,
so I don't have to break
my neck to look at you.
You're so much prettier up close.
So you're friends with Hernán?
Well, we're getting to know each other.
Has he told you anything about us?
No, nothing.
[man 1] Well, that's weird
because he's told us a lot about you.
Like what?
He said that you two dated for a while.
[scoffs] We hooked up one time.
And that's really how long I dated him.
[puffs] Well, you must've been
totally unreal then.
Because, seriously,
he can't shut up about you.
What'd you do to him?
[man 1] What's wrong?
Hernán told us you like to smoke weed.
I just don't wanna get completely stoned.
- Tsk, tsk, tsk.
- No, no, no, no.
It's bad manners
to turn down an invitation.
[ominous music plays]
[man 1] Go on, Jota, but go slow.
[ominous music intensifies]
What you think? It's some good weed?
It's good stuff, yeah.
[man 1] It has an awesome edge to it.
It makes you wanna jump around and dance.
Get naked.
Fuck.
Do you feel like fucking, Alma?
No. It really hasn't done that for me, no.
[man 1 scoffs]
Hey, hey! Where are you taking me?
Gotta make a pit stop at our place.
No, no, no. Drop me off in town first.
You see, we've got
a trunk full of weed. Got it?
Relax.
It'll only take a minute.
[breathes deeply]
[Alma] Why are we stopping here?
[breathing shakily]
Are you afraid, Alma?
[windshield wipers flapping]
Only because my friend
will kill me if I'm late.
Hernán was right.
You've got balls.
Let's go, Jota.
[engine starts]
- [loud horn blows]
- [tires screech]
I'm out!
Hey, Alma! Tell us where the party's at!
Fuck you guys!
No, no, no, no.
Please, please, please, please, please!
Thank you.
[ticket machine beeps]
[cellphone pings]
MOM: PLEASE COME HOME.
LET'S TALK.
[cellphone ringing]
[Greta] Where are you coming from?
This isn't your bus!
What happened?
You all right?
- [cellphone ringing]
- Your mom again.
Um. Two hundred calls, three minutes.
You know, I think she's onto you,
I'm pretty sure.
- Yeah, yeah, I know.
- What do you mean, "I know"?
And... And what do I do? Alma?
You can just... just tell her
that you don't know anything.
[cellphone continues ringing]
Put on your pajamas
and brush your teeth. I'll be right there.
- Wait, I need to get my dinosaurs.
- All right, go. Quickly. Go on, go on!
[sighs]
- How was the movie?
- Awesome, Mom!
The best movie we've ever seen.
Right, Dad?
[chuckles] Yeah, the best.
Hey bud, go on upstairs, go!
- What happened?
- Alma snuck out.
- How?
- Through the window.
What are we gonna do with her, Vero?
Where could she've gone to?
With Greta and Nata?
No, Greta's not with her.
I just talked to her.
And Nata won't answer her phone.
- Don't have any other friends' numbers?
- No, Pablo. Do you?
- [sighs]
- Where are you going?
To the park in town.
- She's probably partying and smoking weed.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
She's challenging us,
and we've got to respond somehow!
Making a scene in front of her friends
is going to make things worse.
Things can't get any worse.
[door closes]
[Alma] I even had to laugh
at their lame ass jokes.
Yeah right, and if you get mad,
then suddenly you're fucking insane.
And if you don't react, you're a whore.
Fucking sons of bitches.
Here.
All right, let's fix your make-up.
Let's go.
The fucking worst part is we're so late.
No big deal.
Anyways, I already messaged my brother.
Next bus will be here
in less than an hour, so...
It's not like
it's the end of the world, okay?
[Alma] Hm.
- [Greta] All done! So hot!
- [Alma] Thanks.
Alma?
- [Greta] Oh, hey, Berta!
- [Alma] Hey.
What you doing here?
[Greta] We were going to go to a party,
but missed the bus. So now we're waiting.
- I see.
- [Greta] Hi.
You want some vodka?
- How'd you get it?
- [Berta] With my cousin's ID.
I stole it from her
at my nana's funeral. [chuckles]
- Well, damn, you do look alike, huh?
- [Berta] Huh, we are related.
You coming?
We need to talk, okay?
I... uh, we're both super late
and we can't miss this bus
or we're not going to make it.
But we've still got loads of time.
We're in! So where are you goin'?
Just down the street. Come on.
Hey, let's go, Gregory!
- Let's go.
- Mm.
[music playing in distance]
I got no fucking clue, dude.
That's what I mean.
You're saying that cause you have someone.
- You really think I think that?
- [indistinct]
[girl 1] Anyway, I'm glad we're all here.
- Today? Yeah? That's awesome.
- That's what you gotta focus on.
[girl 1] Did I tell you,
it's the same chick?
[boy] Wait, how old are you?
- [girl 2] You have to say no.
- [girl 3] I was gonna tell her.
Alma!
[hip hop music playing on speakers]
My bad. I didn't mean to scare you.
You know Alma, right?
- Yeah, everyone knows Alma.
- [Pablo] Was she here?
No.
Do you know where she might be now?
♪ Show no love
'Cause I got no more. No love ♪
Her mother and I
are both pretty concerned.
Well, she hasn't been here.
Thank you all.
[girl 1] Dude, what the fuck?
[boy] I don't know. I thought
that was really fucking weird, honestly.
My mom has a date this evening, all right?
So I'm cheersing to the poor motherfucker
that wants to screw her.
And that he will. [laughing]
And where do you two live now?
In the city, although we're both
sleeping over at Berta's for the night.
Elena and Lily are like my Alma and Greta,
but from primary school.
And just a little more artsy. [laughs]
[Greta] Yeah, you're all artsy
that's for sure.
Yes, and one day
we're all gonna be famous.
You know it.
- But I'll be the very greatest. [laughs]
- [Helena] Right.
Well, you know,
I almost chose art as a Sophomore.
[Lily] Really?
Yes, except I found out that I've got
no talent whatsoever for drawing.
So, yeah.
Um, I'm starving!
My stomach is growling like crazy.
I think I'm going to go for some sort
of super-processed, greasy pastry.
[Helena] I'm hungry too.
- Should we go grab something?
- [Greta] Yeah.
- You coming?
- Yeah.
- [Alma] I'll go with you.
- [Berta] No, no, no. Stay, please.
[Lily] Okay, we'll be right back.
I'll be all alone here watching Gregory.
[Greta] I'll get you something!
[Berta] Want some?
Thanks.
Alma, you're not wearing my necklace.
I forgot it at home.
But um, yeah,
I really love the flying fish, though.
What metal is that?
It's brass. You wearing it
is important to me.
I'll post a photo wearing it.
I don't care about that. I just
wanna make sure that you are wearing it.
[sighs]
Whatever. I just have so many
other great ideas for necklaces.
But I'd need a lot of molds and an oven,
and my mom doesn't care about that stuff.
Well, you're super talented, Berta.
I've got a professor that says that I've
got the personality of a creative person.
And well, at the moment,
I fit the profile of an artsy teenager
to the "T," don't you think?
Parents are divorced,
problems with alcohol, with drugs,
misunderstood, therapy, loneliness...
We had a good time together
in school, right?
Yeah.
[Alma] Hey,
do you like anyone in our class?
[Berta] Mm... no.
- [both laugh]
- Why not?
Well, I mean, I like you.
- But not like in a gay way!
- Yeah, yeah.
I know what I like and I am into penis.
You know, I saw my dad's dick once.
What?
Yeah. He thought no one was in the house
so he was walking around butt-naked.
God!
- It was actually super small.
- Jeez, Berta!
- It was so disappointing!
- Oh, no!
[door opens]
- [Berta's mother] Hello! Berta! I'm home.
- [door closes]
Dude. Wait, wasn't your mom
in the hospital?
Huh?
Well, you've spent the last few days
saying your mom is super ill.
I mean, today
you were crying in math class.
I just didn't have time
to do the homework for science class and...
People were so nice to me when I said it.
And I couldn't take it back and so...
You really are a fucking liar.
You going to tell?
No.
[laughs] No. I love it.
God, Berta, you're the best!
[Berta] Why did we stop hanging out?
Not sure. It's just normal, right?
You switch schools and you just
stop hanging out. It's normal.
Yes. But Greta switched schools like I did
and you still see
each other every weekend.
Why, Alma?
Why did we grow apart?
No idea.
Ah shit, Alma! The bus!
Run, or we'll miss it again! Run!
- [Alma] Bye, Berta.
- Come on!
I'll see you.
[horn beeps]
- [Greta] Hello.
- [Alma] Hi.
- [Greta] Here.
- [ticket machine dings]
[Alma] At least we made it.
Here, this is yours.
[ticket machine beeps]
- [Greta] After you.
- Thanks. [sighs]
[indistinct background chatter]
Yeah, I don't know. What do you think?
Mmm... That maybe she likes you
more than a friend.
No. It's not that.
[engine stops]
[deep sigh]
- [Pablo] I didn't find her.
- [Vero] It might be for the best, Pablo.
I went to the park, but I didn't see her.
Okay, that's enough then.
Her park friends don't know
where she's been either.
She'll return soon. You'll see.
She's not with her guy friends
or girlfriends. Where the hell is she?
[clicks tongue, sighs]
- [girl] Get it!
- [cheering]
- [girl] Let's go!
- [whistle blows]
[Alberto] Hey, what are you doing?
[indistinct shouting]
[player 1] Everybody calm down.
- [player 2] He won't try that again.
- What's wrong with him?
[cellphone vibrating]
[indistinct]
VERO - ALMA'S MOM
INCOMING CALL
Sure. I mean,
I don't really see why she would.
'Cause I mean, we talked about it before...
- Hi?
- [Vero] Hello, Nata.
- Are you with Alma, by any chance?
- [Nata] No.
I thought that you guys had grounded her
and she didn't have permission to leave?
[Vero] Yeah, she was. But she snuck out.
And I really need to speak to her.
Any idea where she is
or who she's out with?
- [Nata] With Greta?
- No, she's not. I already tried her.
I don't know, Vero. She's not here.
And I have no idea where she could be.
I swear, so sorry.
[Vero] Okay. Thank you, Nata.
- [background chatter continues]
- [players shouting]
Motherfuckers!
[beep]
You went to a party without me.
I won't speak to you two
for a month I swear! You're such cunts!
[chatter stops abruptly]
[chatter resumes]
[Nata] You went to a party without me.
I won't speak to you two
for a month I swear! You're such cunts!
I'm sure that if she has a few days,
she'll get over this.
Yeah, I mean we both know
Nata forgives pretty easily.
Honestly? She does.
[cellphone rings]
Oh, run! He's gonna kill me!
- Greta, wait, I'm going to trip! Ah!
- Uh!
[both laugh]
We're sorry!
- Wait, they're here.
- I'm sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- You realize... you're over an hour late.
- It's my fault. I'm sorry.
[exhales]
Fine, here.
One for you and one for you. Put them on.
You can enter through there.
I have to see a few friends.
You two just do your own thing.
Please, don't get into trouble, okay?
- I really don't want any issues.
- Yes, sir.
[techno music plays indoors]
Ah, one last thing.
You look incredible.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Later.
[techno music playing]
- [both scream]
- [Greta] Come. Come on.
Umm...
Before we do anything,
let's go drop our coats.
- Okay!
- And then we fuck around!
Yeah, that's my plan, girl!
[crowd screaming, cheering]
This is so crazy.
Uh, wanna go
and get something to drink already?
Yeah!
["Metronome" by Volodymyr Beichak playing]
- Uhm.
- Oh, hey.
- [both] Two gins...
- With lime, please.
Yes, please.
Hey, girl.
Hey.
Um, we're going to Mokka.
'Cause Buba's brother works there
and we think he can score us some drinks.
Mokka is so fucking far. I'm not going.
Curfew's at 12:00 tonight.
- And can it be later?
- No!
Okay.
What's up with you?
My fingers are blue
and if I don't get inside soon,
I feel like I might freeze to death!
And we didn't even spend
one second together.
- What a fucking great night.
- Well, then, uh...
I can walk you to the bus.
And then I'll go with the guys.
- What's up with you, Nata?
- I'm pissed off, okay?
Fine, but what the fuck
do you think I've done now?
You didn't do anything!
Alma and Greta went out without me
and I found out because of this photo.
- How the hell did they get tickets?
- How would I know?
Alma snuck out and it almost makes me
want to call her mom and tell on her.
Fuck that girl. Just call her.
This was all probably Alma's idea.
I just feel awful for you. It's just that...
She actually believes she's better
than us, you know? And she isn't.
At least, not better than you.
- You're so much hotter. More intelligent...
- Oh, shut up.
It's true though.
You need to think about whether or not
Alma is actually worth your friendship.
[Christian] Hey, lovebirds!
Luca's borrowed his dad's van,
he'll drive us to Mokka.
Go on then.
- You sure?
- Yes.
It'll save you an hour on the bus.
[chuckles] You're the best.
- [soft techno music playing]
- [cheering]
This is perfect. Thanks, dude!
[music and cheering intensify]
- Boo!
- Shit!
Hey, so, is it just me or were you
stalking my brother like a psycho?
[puffs] He's just so hot.
- [Greta] Mhm.
- So, so hot.
You think he might like me a little bit?
Just a teeny bit?
Are you an idiot?!
Turn around! Girl, you are stunning, okay?
- Ah, thanks.
- And tonight I swear you're gonna score.
- Thank you.
- Okay?
And I hope that you understand
how much I hate that it's with my brother.
I don't know, girl. Don't know.
Well, you know what? Hold this.
Right here I've got something
that is definitely gonna... Hm?
- Help you out.
- [gasps]
Where the hell did you get that shit?
Somewhere, huh?
So you want it? Huh?
♪ We all have choices ♪
- You are definitely top five, girl.
- Thank you!
Yeah, well done.
Wow, wait! Oh, my God...
[hard techno plays]
♪ My happy place ♪
♪ On a spiritual level
On a spiritual level ♪
♪ My happy place ♪
[Vero] She's not answering my messages.
She could at least let us know she's fine.
[Pablo] She couldn't care less
about how either one of us feels.
[inaudible]
[Pablo] Have you heard
how she yells at us?
The horrible things she says to you.
The way she looks at us
with hate and scorn.
[inaudible]
Do you realize it's been months
since we had a conversation
that's not about her and her needs.
"Dad, buy me a new phone,
I want clothes and food."
"And I want more money."
"Drive me here, and there.
I want. I want. I want."
She's exhausted me.
She never wants to be with us.
It doesn't matter what you suggest
because Alma always wants
to be somewhere else.
Far away.
As far away as possible.
[door slams]
Don't you think that all of this
contempt, rejection and indifference
is enough to prove to you
that she doesn't love us at all?
No. Of course she does.
This is just a difficult time for her.
I don't like when you talk like that.
It's like you're the one
who doesn't love her at all.
[dog barking in distance]
- [laughter]
- [man 1] Yes, of course. Mi casa, su casa.
[man 2] Seriously, I could get you
financing that profitable...
[man 1] All right, then.
Let's talk, come on.
- Good evening.
- [man 2] That's the idea. [laughs]
Hi, Papa.
Hello, good evening.
- Good evening.
- Hi, honey.
- [Nata's dad] How was the trip to Senegal?
- [man 2] It was good.
[Nata's mom] It was done
with bad taste. It made you want to cry.
So I got rid of all the furniture,
and of course, I staged it beautifully.
Nata, darling!
This is my oldest daughter.
Say hi, Nata.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
- How was the match, good?
- It was great. They won.
Hm. Her boyfriend
is the captain of the soccer team.
Buff! If only I were twenty years younger!
- Momma!
- Oh, my God.
I'm sorry. Sorry, darling,
you're also very pretty.
And she's also a straight A student.
Her father and I are very proud of her.
Goodnight. I'm going to my room.
- [woman 2] Bye, Nata.
- [woman 3] Good night.
[Nata's mother] She's very careful
about what she eats.
It's actually something
I've always insisted on a lot.
Especially with her, because boys are...
GRETITAPOWER
- [techno music playing]
- [cheering]
Friggin' hot!
Hey, you seem super normal!
What? Did the M not hit or what?
It's just that, I only had one pill.
And well, you needed it more than I did.
Are you for real?
You seriously did that for me?
Course.
I swear you're the best friend
in the whole wide world.
You're brilliant. You're gorgeous.
Wonderful. Have I ever told you
that I love you?
I'm just so...
so thankful to be your friend.
Mwuah! Love you.
[music tempo slows down]
It's beautiful. Everyone seems
to love each other so much here.
[Greta chuckles]
- Hi.
- So uh, pretty cool party, right?
Cool. This is incredible!
Thanks for inviting us.
It's nothing.
Oh, some buddies of mine from downtown
are organizing another DJ night.
In a couple of weeks at a club.
I'll try to get you passes.
- Yes, please do.
- [both chuckle]
Hey so, I'm gonna get a drink.
Don't forget that you're a goddess
and he's just a dumb boy who lucked out.
So I actually saw this girl
slip something into your pocket earlier.
- Is that right?
- You know, it's just work thing.
Right.
Why are you asking?
Out of curiosity.
Right.
Well, most of the guys
that I sell to are my friends.
All of my buddies live downtown
and the only clients I have to deal with...
[Alma] Damn, I love his hair.
I mean, of course...
It looks so soft.
I just want to stroke it.
Shit, is this the M talking?
Hope you're not
contemplating getting into that world.
I could bang him right now.
I don't have any condoms,
but I bet he has some in his jacket.
I'd love to get out, but I can't.
Shit, I could drag him to the bathroom.
Go wild.
But you don't need to hear this.
Why isn't he kissing me?
- Sorry, don't know why I keep rambling...
- David, kiss me.
Kiss me!
Come on, kiss me!
Alma, girl, go for it!
You make the first move,
dammit, jump his bones.
Alma, no.
Sorry, but I'm not looking
for anything serious.
Yeah, me neither, dumbass.
I just wanted to fuck, 'kay?
So go fuck off.
- [dog barking]
- Shhh.
[vehicle approaches]
Next one isn't 'til seven.
- Go on, go to bed.
- I won't sleep anyway.
[techno music plays]
Uh! Give me another one!
I think you should slow down a bit.
I think you should worry
about your own life, huh?
You've been serving me all night
and I'm only seventeen.
It's a bit late
to start worrying about me.
[scoffs]
- Hey. You wanna get another drink or shot?
- What?
I said, can I buy you a drink or shot?
[music becomes distorted]
RESTROOMS
Uh, wait for me here, okay?
'Cause I gotta go rescue my friend.
Hey! Okay! Hey.
- What are you doing? You're disgusting!
- What are you doing?
Come on, let's get some air.
Life is a pile of crap, my friend.
Okay, okay, okay.
There you go. That's it.
That's it. All right.
- I really, really, really messed up.
- Uh, no.
I'm so freaking stupid.
You're not! Uh, Alma, everyone
has been turned down at least once.
- Just chill out.
- I'm so fucking stupid.
No, you're not. My brother is stupid.
I'm gonna get our coats. You stay here.
[ominous music plays]
[breathing deeply, trembling]
What are you doing here?
[David] Greta!
Greta!
Where's Alma?
She was literally here
two seconds ago and now she's gone.
Fuck.
Alma!
[birds chirping]
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M CALLING YOU. PICK UP, DAMMIT
WHEN YOU GET BACK, I'M GOING TO KILL YOU
DELETE
We've got to talk to her
as soon as she gets back home.
Right now all I want
is to see her walk through our front door.
[cellphone rings, vibrates]
It's Greta.
- Greta!
- Hello, Vero.
Um... is Alma home?
No. Why?
[Greta] Right, it's just that yesterday,
I lied when you called.
Alma and I went to a party.
- Okay, where is she then?
- Um, I don't know.
I've been looking for her here
for three hours
and I... I can't find her.
- [Vero] But did she leave with someone?
- No idea.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Um, I'm... I'm worried. I...
- Greta, go home.
- Okay.
[pensive guitar music plays]
Where's Alma?
♪ Forgive us now
For what we've done ♪
♪ It started out as a bit of fun ♪
♪ Here, take these before we run away ♪
♪ The keys to the gulag ♪
♪ Oh, children ♪
♪ Lift up your voice ♪
[dog barking]
♪ Rejoice ♪
Pablo.
[music fades]
Alma, my god, just where have you been?
Alma, are you all right?
- What happened? What did you do?
- Where were you?
I was at a party with Greta.
Yes, we know that. We talked to her.
Where were you?
She said that you'd disappeared!
[ominous music plays]
I was dizzy and I got lost.
And, and, and, where were you until now?
I took a bus.
So what? You've been on that bus
since 3:00 in the morning?
- Maybe I fell asleep. I... I don't know.
- [Pablo] But why didn't you pick up?
My battery was dead...
Your battery ran out
the minute you snuck out?
This is absolutely unforgivable!
- We'll have a serious conversation!
- I know and I'm sorry.
- You can't solve this by saying sorry!
- Fine! I admit it! I did screw up! Okay?
Just ground me, whatever you want.
I need to sleep.
Do you have any idea
what could've happened to you?
[heavy breathing]
I need to go to bed.
No! I want you to understand
the consequences of your actions.
You need to think about
what an awful night I've had.
You've no idea what a nightmare it's been
to imagine you could be dead
in a ditch right now, Alma.
Or in someone's car
or the bottom of a pit.
I didn't die, so you can stop crying!
- You're not gonna blow me off so easily!
- Quit yelling at me like some crazy bitch!
Where are you going?
[tense music plays]
- [Pablo grunts]
- [Vero] Pablo!
Pablo, stop, stop, please!
Don't hit her again. Pablo, please.
Apologize to your mother right now
or I'll rip your damn head off!
[crying] Sorry, Mommy. I'm so sorry.
[tense music fades]
[sobbing]
[melancholic music plays]
[sobbing continues]
[sobbing, sniffling]
[pensive music plays]
[engine sounds]