[indistinct chatter]
[tense music plays]
[breathing deeply]
- [girl] You are trash.
- [boy] You're a slut.
[girl] You have shit for brains.
[boy 2] You should be raped for real.
[Alma] Don't go to school.
It's not too late
to avoid screwing up big time.
I mean, school's out in a week
and what happened will be forgotten.
Besides, half the school doesn't know.
It'll go back to normal.
Plus, most people will just forget
your name and your face.
Alma, just don't leave.
[breathes heavily]
Don't do it.
[chattering continues]
RAISING VOICES
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY MIGUEL SÁEZ CARRAL
[bleeping]
[ominous music plays]
"SUCK MY DICK"
#HIGHSCHOOL
#IT'SNOTASAFEPLACE
POSTING
NATA GAVE ME AN STD
[Alma] Suck my dick. Take the whole thing.
ALL GIRLS ARE SLUTS!!!
Dude, this isn't working.
MONDAY
What are you talking about?
It works fine for me.
[cellphone bleeping]
- [girl 1] Dude, look this is wild.
- [girl 2] I don't believe it.
- [girl 1] Give me a marker.
- [girl 2] What for?
- [girl 1] Just give it to me.
- [girl 2] Fine.
- [girl 1] Look, like this?
- [girl 2] No. Too far.
- [girl 1] No, look.
- [girl 2] Okay, enough. Come on.
[girl 1] Come on, quick,
run away. Let's go.
- [footsteps running]
- [door slams]
[ominous music plays]
HI, I'M ALMA
AND I LIKE TO SUCK DICK
Jeez!
Look at her, look at her!
[boy] Alma, don't you know
plastic is bad for the planet?
[boy 2 whoops]
It's better to go "au naturale."
[speedy drumbeat]
[dramatic music plays]
- [thud]
- [grunts]
[Alma] He was touching himself.
Everyone saw it.
He said it was a joke,
something about a reality show on TV.
That's a big lie.
- I'm pretty sure he's lying too.
- See?
I shouldn't have to stand
for this bullshit 'cause I'm not a guy.
- No need to get dramatic.
- I'm not dramatic.
How would you even understand?
Actually, I do understand.
I won't condone what he has done to you,
but I'm afraid
I can't excuse physical assault.
Huh?
[Andrea] Read it carefully
before you begin.
You have 45 minutes.
[door opens]
Sorry to interrupt.
I've come to get my things.
Something wrong, Alma?
I've been suspended for three days.
[Hernán] How are you?
[Alma] How do you think?
I got a three-day suspension
because of that dickhead.
[Hernán] Fuck, that's bullshit, man.
I don't understand what's happening.
I mean, can you explain it?
Shit, man, well clearly
you've ticked someone off.
Check this out.
[Alma] Fuck.
How the hell did they get these photos?
- Did someone hack my phone or what?
- Nah, dude.
It's way easier than that.
Who took that photo?
Nata.
PutoAlfaKing is Alberto's handle.
Now you know then.
Holy shit!
Son of a bitch.
[sighs]
Hey there, skank.
I know it was you
who sent those photos to Alberto.
You're actually the queen
of fucking cunts, for real!
Way to end 12 great years
of a fucking amazing friendship, asshole.
I'm never talking to you again in my life.
But first, I'm gonna to send you
a little goodbye present, okay?
[tense music plays]
[cellphone buzzes]
That's your boyfriend's dick,
in case this time you don't recognize it.
Can you explain to me
what the fuck this is?
It's obvious she was provoked!
Yes, the boy was out of line,
there's no question.
But the reaction your daughter had
was absolutely disproportionate.
I wonder if including a sexual education
course in the curriculum
could do a little more
to keep the kids in line?
We will examine that
in the upcoming school board meeting.
That and the repeated violations
to our code of conduct by your daughter.
[Pablo] Tsk.
[Vero sighs, clears throat]
What a dumbass.
[school bell rings]
♪ Keep your face to the sun
And watch the shadow fall behind ♪
THURSDAY
♪ Fear of winning, fear of losing ♪
[music continues through headphones]
♪ But that's fine
You're gonna shine ♪
[boys chattering indistinctly]
♪ Just take time to heal ♪
♪ Then you'll really blossom
And you'll grow ♪
["Light The Fire"
by Antoine Zamundu continues]
- ♪ You got light... ♪
- [music stops]
I want to see you
after class, in my office.
Understood?
All right.
[heart thumping]
[teacher] All right? Good.
When it comes to calculating it, you need
to make sure you've taken into account
all of the foreseeable
ordinary and extraordinary expenses.
That way, we can manage
the resulting value by simply taking...
[heart continues thumping]
[ominous music plays]
You'll always look me in the eyes, right?
[teacher] Come in.
Are you going to tell me what happened?
He touched his junk and got in my face.
So I kicked him in the balls.
It wasn't a big deal,
he just made himself out to be the victim.
What's the matter?
You have a problem with that kid?
[Alma] Aside from him being an asshole,
no, I barely know him.
Jesus. [inhales]
Well, that was a pretty violent reaction,
you know? [sighs]
I'm just so sick of them picking on me.
There's graffiti in the bathrooms.
They call me a slut.
He'll definitely expel me now,
there's no doubt about that.
[scoffs]
They've already talked to my parents.
And all the effort I've invested
into school won't be worth shit.
[teacher] No.
No, that won't be the case.
Because I'm on the school board.
And I would never
allow something like that.
Do you trust me?
So why won't you be honest then?
The other day, I caught one
of your classmates sharing some photos.
They were photos...
[clears throat]
...that were featuring you.
But you know that already.
Why?
Why did you take those?
I took those one day with my friend.
Just being silly, we were having fun.
Right.
And do you have more silly photos?
Yes.
Wipe your phone.
Delete them.
[inhales, clears throat]
Want one?
I mean...
What are you trying to do?
Hm?
Is it a new way of flirting or is it a...
I don't know...
way to be more popular in school, or what?
- Yeah, it's actually very common.
- Ah, right.
Alma, it's just that...
That bullshit will only crush
your self-esteem and continue to...
attract attention from really bad folks,
you get that?
You're different, Alma.
You don't have to do what is common.
Mmm.
I won't be able to come
to your tutoring sessions next week.
But Andrea will. She'll be with you.
Okay?
You all right?
Yeah.
Okay, you're free to go.
[door opens]
[Berta] Dude, that last photo
you uploaded is fucking great.
Like, we have twice as many likes.
You were right about heating things up.
You know? I have another idea.
Maybe we could take a photo
of, like, his car, you know,
with some dirty tissues
scattered everywhere.
As if he's used them to wipe off stuff.
You know what I mean?
But I thought it all happened
inside the school.
No, yeah, it did.
I mean, but I don't know,
what if there's some girl
that sees his car and recognizes it?
- You know?
- I don't know.
[Berta] What's wrong?
Nothing.
So the... the page isn't working
the way you expected,
so you're frustrated
and don't wanna do this now?
No. No, no it's not that.
[Berta] Are... are you sick of me? [crying]
No. No, Berta, please. Don't cry, okay?
So what's happening then?
Uh, Berta, I just don't know
if we're doing the right thing.
But... but why?
I mean, why do suddenly seem to...
You spoke to him.
I... I went to the meetings.
- [Berta] I asked you not to.
- Nothing happened.
And so because he didn't try
anything with you,
you think everything
I told you so far is bullshit?
[breathing shakily] Did you talk about me?
No.
You've taken his side, Alma.
- Berta, stop. sit down.
- [bell rings]
No! I knew I shouldn't
have told you anything!
Stop the fucking bus!
- Stop it! Stop!
- [Alma] Berta!
- I said stop, dammit!
- Berta, stop!
No, no, don't you ever
fucking talk to me again!
Stop the fucking bus, goddammit!
Let her get off. That's girl's
gone crazy. She'll hurt herself.
- Please stop already.
- Stop this bus!
- [Alma] Come on, Berta. Please stop.
- [Berta screaming, crying]
[Alma] Please!
Berta, wait, fuck, just wait.
Talk to me, okay?
- No, I said leave me alone!
- Wait a minute! I do believe you, okay?
- No!
- Okay, I'm sorry.
You're a fucking liar.
Let go of me, don't touch me!
[Alma] All right, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Berta, listen to me!
I said no!
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
You've ruined my fucking life.
Everything's fucked.
[breathing shakily]
[car horn beeps]
- [screams] No!
- [thud]
[horns beeping]
[sirens blaring]
TRAFFIC POLICE
[poignant music plays]
Will you stay with me for a while?
Of course.
None of this was your fault.
Okay?
Can we just sleep, please?
Dude, look what is this?
- Isn't that our bathroom?
- Whose profile is that?
Their handle says... Coleman Miller.
She says she was raped.
[head teacher] What's going on?
Come on, let me through.
Excuse me, please.
What's wrong?
A student was raped in the bathroom.
Who was it?
We don't know who.
Her handle is "I am Coleman Miller."
[director] Well, we shouldn't...
let's not get caught up in hysteria.
This could be a joke.
You don't joke
about this kind of thing, though.
Even so, we should
handle this with discretion.
[Andrea] It's too late to stop it.
Three hundred students
have shared this post
And they're saying on socials
that a classmate who attends this school
was, unfortunately, abused sexually.
[head teacher] Even worse,
what they're saying is
that this classmate was abused
inside this school.
That proposition changes everything.
[knocking on door]
[head teacher] Not now, Natacha.
Whatever it is will have to wait.
Coleman Miller.
It's Alma.
[head teacher] How do you know?
Because I recognize her t-shirt.
I made it for her.
Alma was raped?
[telephone ringing]
[woman] Operations, Guardia Civil.
How can I help you?
I'll put you through
to the team right away.
[breathing shakily] Fuck. [crying]
Hey, Mom.
I was trying to roll it myself, but...
Give it here.
Thanks.
FEMALE MINOR UNIT
Alma?
I'm Sergeant Mercedes García
from the Federal Judicial Police
of the Guardia Civil's Department
for Female Minors.
Well, then.
How are you, Alma?
I'm just going to ask
some questions, all right?
[tense music plays]
Who is Coleman Miller?
I am.
I am Coleman Miller.
Are you the person that appears
in the photos on this profile?
Yes.
[Mer] I'm going to read the caption
from your first post.
It says, "This is me before I was raped."
Did you write that?
Yes.
Alma, you okay?
Just a bit tired.
[Mer] I understand.
I know it's hard.
But to be able to open an investigation,
I need you to talk to me.
Yeah, yeah, I know. It's just that I...
Alma, did you make up that story?
No.
Well then, tell me what's going on.
Only you know the whole truth.
Shhh.
Alma, you made a promise.
You said you wouldn't tell anyone.
It started two months ago,
when I was hit by a car.
And I ran into my friend Berta
at the hospital.
She told me that she...
was raped by a teacher
for nearly an entire school year.
[ominous music plays]
STATEMENT FROM THE MINOR B.O.U.
[doorbell rings]
[Mer] Hi, good morning. Is Alma there?
- [Vero] Yes.
- [Mer] I need to talk to her.
- [Vero] Come in.
- [gate beeps]
[Mer] I've talked to Berta's parents
and did some digging.
[Mer] Did you know your friend
suffered from mental illness
and was receiving treatment?
[Alma] Yeah, she said she was
dealing with a lot of issues
since the abuse started.
Well, the thing is,
we couldn't find any definitive proof
that it was cause and effect.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Well, you see...
Berta was evaluated and diagnosed
with borderline personality disorder
when she was twelve years old.
Long before she reported your teacher.
What do you mean "reported"?
She told me that she'd never told anyone.
But she did.
They opened an investigation.
But in the end, it was determined
that the abuse never even existed.
Because she cleared the charges.
Why'd she lie?
[Mer] I don't know.
But I spent the entire night
reviewing the case,
and unfortunately, if there's no proof
or a solid accusation on record,
there's nothing we can do.
The case is closed.
Alma,
are you all right?
[Alma] This is a fake account.
No one raped this girl.
She goes to my school
and her name is Alma.
Don't believe anything she tells you.
She's a liar.
[Berta] I told you not to tell anyone.
García, there's a girl outside
who wants to talk to you.
- No time, can you take it?
- It's about Coleman Miller.
Hi there,
I'm Sergeant Mercedes García.
How can I help you?
I wanted to, um, talk about this account.
"We'd like to inform you
that the school board has decided
to suspend your daughter
until further notice,
effective immediately,
due to the violation of article 19B
of the policies set
in the official Student Code of Conduct."
What a clusterfuck, Alma.
[Alma] Yup.
Well, at least your friend
the officer was cool about it
and hasn't been on me
about me starting a fake account.
About a fake rape, I guess.
Berta was just going through a lot.
And she said
some really weird stuff, Alma.
Yeah, but she'd speak these things
with such truth in her voice.
Every detail, everything.
[sighs] I don't know, dude.
Clearly I sound insane.
What are you gonna do now?
Your brother asked me to go
with him to the end of the world.
And I said no. But...
I should probably reconsider, right?
Especially after all of this.
You seen it?
Seen what?
Look.
There's probably a thousand accounts
saying that they want me dead.
What is this?
Um, well, I mean,
just delete those comments
or delete the damn account,
and that's that.
Oh, my god.
[sighs]
Ah, well, then there's these, huh?
The funny ones.
Apparently, I feed their creativity.
I'm their muse.
[Greta] People seriously suck.
I really screwed up.
I've royally fucked up.
And I accused the only teacher
who wanted to help, of being a rapist.
Well then, tomorrow,
you go to school and you speak to him.
You offer an apology.
He'll understand, for sure.
["Nos Vamos A Comer El Mundo"
by Juancho Marqués playing]
[school bell ringing]
["Nos Vamos A Comer El Mundo" continues]
[music turns ominous]
[breathing heavily]
You okay?
[water dripping]
Run away, do you understand?
Run.
I'm going to tell everyone what you do.
- I don't know what you mean.
- [scoffs]
Yes, yes you do know.
[door slams]
Why you standing there?
Help us lay the table, go on.
Um...
I need to speak to the two of you.
What's going on?
Berta wasn't lying.
One of my teachers abused her.
He's abusing another girl now, I know it.
- Alma,
- Mom, please just listen to me, okay?
- We have to tell the Guardia Civil.
- No, Mom, that won't do any good, besides...
I'm not exactly a credible source
to them right now.
Could you convince that girl
to report the teacher?
But she's terrified.
I won't do that to her.
Anyway, he'd just deny it all.
So what do you wanna do?
♪ Dem-dem-dem-dem dem-dem
Dem-dem-dem-dem ♪
♪ Uh, I'm in my prime, Optimus ♪
♪ Sagittarius, so you know
I'm an optimist ♪
♪ Man, keep it all real, I'm a prophetess
Okay ♪
♪ So at least you took an L
Off your bucket list ♪
♪ It's time to make hits
And it's time to diss ♪
♪ How you still dissin'
Still can't find some hits? ♪
♪ Was it worth it, dummy?
I ain't mind a bit ♪
♪ Still on that show
Gettin' no chips, time to dip ♪
♪ Barbie beach house, Barbie Benz ♪
♪ Barbie white picket, Barbie fence ♪
♪ All tea, all shade, bitch, all offense ♪
♪ If you ever try
To confiscate Barbie's Ken ♪
♪ I'ma put you in the box
Where my dollies been ♪
♪ Chop it up
And the next stop garbage bin ♪
♪ 'Cause you hoes
Too old to be gossipin' ♪
♪ I'm just tryna find out
When the new Porsche come in ♪
[young Alma] Wrestling match?
Tooth and nail, til the very end, okay?
Okay.
[grunting, laughing]
[Pablo] Oh, no! Alma!
Hey, hey, let me see.
Are you okay?
Dad, I'm not crying.
- And I won't give up, ever!
- Oh, no?
You sure?
- Yes.
- Let's go then. [roars]
[young Alma laughing]
[poignant music plays]
- [quiet knocking]
- [coughs]
Technically, I'm not smoking
inside the house. Hm?
One day you might wanna go outside
and collect all your cigarette butts. Hm?
One day.
Can't fall asleep?
Um, hey, Dad,
I understand the problems
that might arise from doing this.
But I have to do it.
- I must do it.
- [Pablo] I know.
It's the right thing to do.
And I hope you know
that I'm very proud to be your father.
You were always a very brave girl.
"Tooth and nail, 'til the very end."
I'd forgotten.
I didn't realize at the time, but I did...
I regret the way
that I've been treating you all this time.
The things I've said and...
I'm sorry that I hit you.
- I didn't make it very easy on you either.
- Don't say that. It's not true.
Alma, please forgive me.
You know I'll have
to repeat my senior year.
It's not a big deal.
We'll find you another school.
Or not.
Take the path that fulfills you.
I will always be at your side.
And if what you want
is to ride away on some train,
just say the word
and I'll be there to send you off.
Without question.
- Choo choo.
- [both chuckle]
[girl] You are trash.
[boy] You're a slut.
[girl] You have shit for brains.
[Alma] Don't go to school.
[boy] You should be raped for real.
[Alma] It's not too late to avoid
screwing up big time. [voice echoes]
Alma, stay home. Don't do it. [echoes]
[poignant music plays]
[Alma] Uh, drop me off here.
Here is fine.
Should I come?
No, no need, thanks.
I'll be nearby.
But only if you need me, okay?
Thanks, Dad.
- You got this.
- [breathes deeply]
["You Should See Me In A Crown"
by Billie Eilish plays]
♪ Bite my tongue, bide my time ♪
♪ Wearing a warning sign ♪
♪ Wait 'til the world is mine ♪
MARTIN BAUSSEN PRIVATE SCHOOL
♪ Visions I vandalize ♪
♪ Cold in my kingdom size ♪
♪ Fell for these ocean eyes ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ I'm gonna run this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
One by one by one ♪
♪ One by one by ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ Your silence is my favorite sound ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
One by one by one ♪
♪ One by one by one ♪
♪ Count my cards, watch them fall... ♪
[bell ringing]
[loud, indistinct chatter]
Hey, you guys, hey, come here and look.
Alma's causing issues again!
[windows open]
[tense music plays]
[girl] Hey you guys, look, It's Alma.
[clamoring]
- [girl 2] What's she doing? Is she crazy?
- [girl 3] What the hell?
- [girl 4] Let me see.
- [girl 5] What?
BEWARE! A RAPIST IS HIDING IN THERE!
[Mai] I don't understand why she does it.
Jesus, Mai. She's crazy.
She's for sure gonna get expelled
for this, dude. [chuckles]
Fuck that girl.
[indistinct chatter]
- [head teacher] Should I call her parents?
- No.
I'm calling the Guardia Civil.
BEWARE! A RAPIST IS HIDING IN THERE!
It's Alma.
What happened yesterday, remember?
I know.
[door bangs]
[triumphant music plays]
It's okay. He's never gonna be able
to hurt you again, I promise.
[music turns ominous]
[cellphone ringing]
POSTING
[cellphones ping]
What's the matter?
[Alma] This is the face of a rapist.
He's one of the teachers
at the school I go to.
That fucking bitch.
[Alma] I'm sure that right now
he's abusing another girl.
He's a sexual predator.
Alma!
Hey.
I'm shaking.
Just relax. I'm right here, okay?
[pounding drumbeat]
- Get her out of here.
- I called the Guardia...
- I said, get her out, fuck!
- There's more of them now.
Ah, shit.
Get back to your classes.
And you, take that down immediately
and step off the school premises, now.
I'm not moving from here.
We've called the Guardia Civil.
Your actions will have consequences.
I really hope so.
Get back to class.
I said, get back to class.
Go on, back to your classrooms,
everybody please go on.
Stay where you are.
All of you, back to class.
What a bunch of whores
and absolute dumbasses.
Well fuck, she's got some ovaries on her.
[Alberto] Come on, Nata,
everyone knows Alma's a fucking liar.
[Alberto and Christian laughing]
I don't think so.
Alma would never lie about that.
And you know, I should have turned you in.
- What are you saying? Shut up.
- I don't feel like it.
Alma's right. You should be forced
to wear signs around your necks
that say what pieces of shit you are.
Want us to tell everyone
about your fantasies?
Well no, not really.
Let's place that subject to the side,
where it belongs next to our relationship.
- What are you saying exactly?
- I'm saying I'm dumping you.
It's over, in the same spot where
everything began for us. How's that sound?
Wha... Come on, Nata.
I know that you love me.
There's no fucking reason
for us to break up.
- No?
- No.
Sending photos of your penis to my best
friend doesn't seem like reason enough?
I think you're aware that sending
that type of pornography is illegal.
- Are you crazy? What are you even saying?
- Crazy as fuck!
So crazy that I'll have to tell the school
board and they're gonna have to expel you.
Hey, Nata, don't screw me over, please.
So long, Alberto.
Get out of my way, idiot.
Nata!
Oh!
And one more thing.
Once they know,
they'll have to call the Guardia Civil,
so forget about fucking Canada!
They'd never let in a little pig like you.
[indistinct chatter]
[director] I told you
to get back to class. All of you.
Get back inside right now. Just stop!
I'm asking you to please go back
to your classrooms. Please!
There will be serious consequences
for all of you.
All of you!
Get back to class. Now!
Go back to class.
I will not say it again. Please!
[sirens wailing]
[man] Move aside, please.
Let me through, kids.
Would you please move.
Guys, please.
You got here really quickly.
Yeah, we were already on route when we
received your call. We gotta speak to you.
[students heckling]
[boy] Get out! Bastard!
[angry heckling]
[girl] You're disgusting.
You have some nerve. Rapist!
[boy] They're gonna see you dead. Pig!
That was some scene you made.
Why was her arrested?
A student from another school saw your
profile and felt compelled to speak up.
And filed a claim.
I won't rule out
that there could be more victims.
You should still
probably talk to that girl.
Thanks a lot.
- What's your name?
- My name is Bambi.
Mind if we speak for a moment?
Come with me.
- [engine starts]
- [students heckling]
- Get out!
- Get the fuck out of here!
This is me. My name is Alma.
998,702 LIKES
Hey there, guys. Uh, I've got news
that's kind of incredible.
I got hired as a community manager
for DJ Bárbara Lago.
So I'm going on tour with her
for three months all over Europe.
I can't believe it's real.
Wish me luck, guys.
My brother is at the ass end
of the world, now you're leaving.
And I'm left here.
You are abandoning me.
Has he texted you?
Well, the thing is
even though he won't admit it,
yeah, you definitely broke his heart.
At least I was honest about it.
It was only a fuck, right?
Mm-hmm?
Hey, I'm really gonna miss you.
Miss you too.
But you know, it's only three months.
Yeah? And you are gonna be
so busy with college and other stuff.
And besides, I'll text you
and call you all the time
and it'll be like I never left.
[Greta] Yeah.
But, I mean, if I have a weird day
and I just wanna make out with you,
I won't be able to
and that will make me sad.
And I might drop dead.
Um...
You have an incredible talent
for manipulation, Greta Hernández.
All right!
I know that gave you butterflies
in your stomach.
In the vag, actually.
Crazy lesbian on the loose! She's insane!
- [Greta chuckles]
- [knocking]
- Wow, what a large bag.
- Yeah? Well, It's three whole months, Dad.
Are you sure this
is what you really want to do?
I don't know, but I wanna give it a shot.
[Vero] If you have any trouble,
you come right back.
[Alma] Mom, relax,
nothing's gonna happen, okay?
Yeah, I know. You're so fearless.
But call me every day, all right?
You're so dramatic, I will.
All right, let's go! Come on!
[Alma] Come on.
Get out of my house already.
IF YOU OR ANYONE YOU KNOW
HAS SUFFERED SEXUAL VIOLENCE,
YOU CAN GET INFORMATION
AND RESOURCES TO GET HELP
AT WANNATALKABOUTIT.COM
[serene music plays]
[engine sounds]