MARTIN BAUSSEN PRIVATE SCHOOL
Hey, come see this.
Alma is causing trouble again.
Is she crazy?
-Fuck, that's wild.
-She's gone too far.
Has she no shame?
-And I bet it's a lie.
-I don't get why she does it.
Fuck, Mai, she's crazy.
She'll get expelled for this.
Screw her.
-Should I call her parents?
-No.
It's unacceptable.
I'm calling the police.
BEWARE! A RAPIST IS HIDING IN THERE!
RAISING VOICES
THIS IS ME BEFORE I WAS...
#SURVIVOR
#RAISINGVOICES
POSTING
#NEVERFORGET
This is me
before I was raped.
The first wife defined him as an idiot.
The second...
JANUARY 2018
FOUR MONTHS EARLIER
Alberto, here.
...accused him of being a pervert.
The third fainted on the wedding night
on seeing the size of his member.
Hang on.
And when she came to,
she got out of there.
The fourth
forced him to use a cushion with a hole
to have intercourse.
So, here's my question.
Who can tell me the nickname
of this magnificent specimen?
No one?
"The Desired."
Hang on, guys.
For tomorrow, read up on his reign,
and find out why The Desired
was deeply detested by his wives
and by his people too. Okay? Right, bye.
Alma.
What did you think of the class?
Fascinating.
Have you ever wondered what they'll say
about you when you're gone?
Halfway through that last year,
I'd have said
that all that would be left of me
would be a few anecdotes
that people would tell
at high school reunions.
Like that time
I flattened a bully with one punch.
Or the time I got caught making out
with a guy in the bathroom.
Or the most famous of all,
when I burned my uniform
at the end of junior high.
I'd actually been the star
of some good times,
though none so extraordinary
that people would remember
my name or my face years later.
But what happened later
was very different.
FEMALE MINOR UNIT
Police central operations unit.
How can I help you?
I'll put you through to the team.
What happened at the end of that year
changed everything.
No one will ever forget that.
Bro, Canada is fucking dope.
The universities there
have great campuses.
I'm totally sure.
I'm going to do business studies there.
What are you going to do?
I want to convince my parents
to let me go to the same university.
Long-distance doesn't work.
What'll she do?
I don't know. But I doubt very much
that bitch will graduate.
Watch it, she's my friend.
It's the damned truth.
I wonder when she'll mess up again.
It's sick.
-See you later.
-Okay.
-What's up, Hernán?
-What's up?
-What are you up to this weekend?
-The usual, I guess. And you?
I'm meeting the guys in the park. Drop by.
Okay.
It's my last one. Shall we light up?
No.
Things are hard enough already
without complicating them even more.
Right.
Yesterday I did a mix.
I stayed up really late.
-Really?
-I don't know.
-See what you think.
-Let's hear it.
Ready.
I know I've already lost you
Hey,
it's pretty good, huh?
-I like it.
-You like it?
Yeah, it's cool.
-Shall I send it to you?
-Yes, please.
Cool.
You'll be one of the few things
I'll miss about school.
Don't get mushy on me.
See you later, Alma.
You got that straight, wise guy? Get lost.
Alma.
Hello.
Was that a joint you threw away there?
No, it was a cigarette.
Really, you can check.
You were a bit distracted in class today.
You know you can count on us
if you have any problems, right?
Yeah. I didn't sleep very well.
Allergy problems.
Thanks all the same.
Cooper!
Cooper, come here!
What's up with you? Such a cutie.
SCREW YOU ALL
GRETA:
SEE YOU LATER AT THE MALL?
YEP
Shit.
Cooper, got any papers?
Great.
Totó! So you had them all the time, huh?
Police central operations unit.
How can I help you?
I'll put you through.
Hello.
-I was trying to roll a cigarette, but...
-Give it here.
Now give me that.
Alma.
-Don't worry, I'll be here.
-Okay.
Will long hairs come out of there?
Yeah, it's normal. It's called "puberty."
If I don't have any yet,
can I still go to school on my own?
Why don't you want us to go with you?
They let Hugo go alone.
Damn Hugo.
Go change.
I'll see if there's mail.
Shouldn't you be studying?
I didn't sleep well with my allergies.
Tidy up your room, please.
I found some really cool sneakers
in an online store.
Can I have the card?
They're new. I'm not buying more sneakers.
But these are on sale.
Right, and these are new.
You could listen to me for once, right?
Just to change the dynamic.
You only order me around.
Clean up this mess.
You see?
Like I said.
Hold tight, okay?
Don't cut yourself.
Gee!
Look, I have a super cauliflower.
It looks like a mushroom cloud.
-I'll show it to Mom.
-Okay.
In you go.
-Can I get my allowance?
-Did you study?
Yes.
-Did you clean up your room?
-Yes.
Should I check?
-I'm going to miss the bus.
-You're always missing the bus.
Right.
-Be back by 12:00.
-What?
My friends get home much later.
I don't care
how your friends' parents raise them.
While you live with us,
those are the rules.
Dammit, Alma, about time.
Aren't you my favorite person?
Did I ever tell you
how cute you are, how hot you are,
what a good friend you are,
how good that jacket looks?
How do you do it? You're always...
You're sweet-talking me.
Where have you come from?
-From the park.
-Dammit, Alma.
I'm sorry.
So, what did I miss?
A new chapter of Wake Up
and Drop That Asshole Once and For All.
Dammit.
If I ever make a fool of myself like this,
I give you permission
to slap me all you like.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Even the day you pooed in kindergarten,
you played it cool.
-Right.
-You even held up your hand.
You're the best friend in the world.
Wow.
Some tits!
It's disgusting.
It's obscene.
They shouldn't be left like that.
Something's going on in there.
No, they should put something on them.
Panties or whatever.
The other day I had a dream.
I was naked in the street,
on all fours,
with a girl leading me on a leash.
As if I was a dog.
I woke up dripping wet.
You have to stop watching
that "femmedo" porn.
-"Femdom."
-"Fromedom."
-It's rotting your brain.
-Hey.
-Dammit.
-You were the one who wanted to come.
-Go to hell.
-What? You go to hell.
-Shut the fuck up.
-You shut up.
What's wrong with you? You're going
to scream in my face right here?
-You have no idea who I am.
-Really?
No.
Well, I'd say I know you well.
Fuck you.
No, Nata!
-Leave me alone.
-Nata, please listen to me.
-What a nightmare.
-Hang on.
Nata, will you listen to me, dammit?
-You're hurting me!
-Just a second.
You're fucking hurting me!
Asshole.
I just want to ask you
some questions, okay?
Who is ColemanMiller?
I am.
I'm ColemanMiller.
Are you the person
in the photos on that profile?
Yes.
I'm going to read your first post.
"This is me before I was raped."
Did you write it?
Goddammit!
-Did he hurt you?
-No, it's okay.
I'm fucking sick of him
and his shitty matches.
Nata, he's a fucking narcissist.
I'll fuck a guy tomorrow and post a photo.
What's wrong?
You won't do that.
We've seen loads of your fights,
and it's always the same.
You get over it the next day
and go back to him.
Well, I've said it.
Maybe this time is different.
I don't know, you deserve better.
But hey, if you forgive him,
I'll love you the same.
So cute.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, Susanita's weed has hit me a bit.
Don't sweat it. Try this.
It gets you wasted
with a touch of acid. You'll see.
Well?
It's good, right?
-Right.
-I'll go get some air.
Off you go.
Alma?
Hi.
It's Berta.
-Jeez.
-Is something wrong?
No. Berta.
Sorry, that kid reminds me of...
Boo from Monsters, Inc.?
Remember we saw that movie
at one of my birthday parties?
Never mind. How are you?
Great. The usual.
Your eyes are red,
like you've been crying.
No, I'm fine.
How are you? It's been a while.
Sure, I hang out more
downtown now, you know?
Yeah, arts high school is amazing.
I guess being surrounded by artists,
I'm developing my own creativity.
Do you like it?
-I made it.
-It's cool.
In the school workshop.
We're experimenting with brass,
and with silver too.
I can make you one if you like.
-No.
-No, take this one.
-There's really no need.
-There is.
I want you to have it.
I mean it.
It's bad for me to say it,
being the designer,
but it's gorgeous.
-Hello, Alma. It's been ages.
-How are you?
Honey, we have to go.
My mom's right, it's been ages.
That's not good. Should I call you?
Smile. I don't like seeing you like this.
-Bye, Alma.
-Ciao.
We need to talk.
Jeez.
Was that Berta?
I wouldn't know her.
She told me she wants to talk.
About what?
I can't take it anymore.
We argue, he keeps yelling at me.
We used to have moments on our own,
but for months now,
we have his damn posse hanging around,
and it's shitty.
We need to talk.
Alma, are you okay?
Just a bit tired.
I understand.
I know it's hard,
but to open an investigation,
I need you to talk to me.
I know that. It's just...
It's yours for 200.
Your dad has lots of money.
Shut up. Give me the goddamn bag.
Lunch!
Coming.
Pasta is my favorite food.
Mine too.
How was your exam the other day?
Good.
You need to improve your grades
or it'll be hard to pass.
You always say the same,
but I've never repeated, right?
-What time did you go to bed last night?
-Dunno.
You were still awake at 3:00.
I heard you on the phone.
Greta called. It wasn't that late.
You got up at 12:00.
-It's Saturday, Dad.
-So?
You could've studied, just a bit.
I'm studying, okay? Really. I promise.
I'll pass everything in June.
-It's delicious, Mom.
-Passing is not enough.
You should try harder
if you want a good average.
We've talked about how important
this time is for your future.
-What'll you do?
-I don't know.
It's January. What are you waiting for?
For June?
-What will we do then?
-I don't know!
I'd love to know.
It'd be a lot easier, but I don't!
I'm sorry.
However much you hassle me,
I won't know, okay?
I won't eat lunch with you again.
Shit.
Goddammit.
-Can I stay over?
-Let me talk to Greta's mom.
No. Mom, come on. I'm 17 years old.
It's embarrassing to ask permission
to stay the night.
Fine, but I want you here tomorrow
first thing to study. Okay?
Okay. Ciao.
Dammit.
Alma...
-Your mom is cool.
-She's all yours.
-I can't stand her.
-You're dumb.
Seriously, she always sides with Dad,
even though she knows he's wrong.
I feel like hitting her sometimes.
Well,
it's not easy being a mom.
Nata.
Rolling over!
Asshole.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi.
Nata!
-Hi, how are you?
-Come on, hurry.
-Come on.
-Take it out now!
-Right, okay. Are you ready?
-I can't wait.
-Ready?
-Yes.
Just a second.
Ta-da!
Where the hell did you get that?
A shoebox under my mom's bed.
-Your mom's?
-Yeah.
-You'll end up boarding if she finds out.
-She has no clue.
Her Padel tennis buddies
will have given it to her.
Hey, she really likes big dicks, huh?
-Yep.
-Check this out.
-God!
Eighteen centimeters of pure masculinity.
-It's all mine.
-Nata, someone has used that.
No, no way.
It looks real, right?
-I don't know.
-Right?
I don't know.
I haven't tried as many as you.
Olé!
Hey, watch it!
Run!
Giddyap!
-Sorry!
-Get up! You're so hot.
Let's take some dirty pics.
Get down and dirty.
-Dammit.
-What's wrong?
Every couple has arguments. It's normal.
The main thing is we love each other.
Dammit.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Hi, babe.
Hi, sweetheart. How are you?
Why aren't you wearing pants?
Come on, downstairs.
Let's go see David.
We'll do a...
-Hi.
So quiet.
Hello.
-What are you up to?
-Dying of boredom.
Right.
Hey, can I have some?
We'll smoke in the garden.
Papers.
-Thanks.
-Not at all.
What's that drawing?
I'll be outside.
It's not a drawing. It's a text in Tamil.
One of the three languages in Sri Lanka.
It means "bon voyage."
Are you sure?
Maybe you were scammed.
Maybe it says,
"I'm a fool who thinks he's cool
and has no fucking clue about Tamil."
Yeah, could be.
I have a tattoo too.
-Will you show me?
-No.
No, it's not a good idea.
You know? I don't want to intimidate you.
I've got it in a secret place,
and it's much cooler than yours.
What did I miss?
Well?
-I got my panties wet.
-Right.
I think for just one second,
I'd bet my tit on it,
he was flirting with me.
Really?
My brother is so damn lucky.
Can I not flirt a bit too?
-Nothing.
-No? Dammit.
No, but you know,
you do it better every time.
Right. Well, I'll just keep trying.
ALBERTO:
SEND ME A DIRTY PIC
Alma, did you make this story up?
No.
So, tell me what happened.
You're the only one who knows the truth.
I'm going to class.
Hernán.
-Hey!
-What's up?
You didn't come to the park Friday.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I had to study.
I wanted to ask you
about the guys in that pimped car.
-Kevin and Jota, right?
-What about them?
You tell me. The other day
it looked like you had problems.
No way. They're buddies.
Man...
We've known each other since grade school.
You know you can trust me, right?
I know.
It's nothing sketchy.
But it's great you worry about me.
Hush up.
Next weekend
there's a techno party at Industry.
We could go together.
I don't know. I'll see.
I'm sure you've heard talk
about "post-truth."
It's in fashion now.
It was the word of the year in 2016.
Would anyone like to give
an example to clarify it...?
The results of the makeup exams
are not good.
She failed six exams
in the second evaluation.
It'll be hard for her to pass.
Even if she does,
we doubt she'll be able to sit her SATs.
Alma's attitude is not good.
She's not difficult, but
she's distracted.
We were wondering
if you have any trouble at home.
What kind of trouble?
The crisis has affected kids
more than expected.
A bad financial situation can affect them.
We have no financial worries.
And between you?
Everything okay?
Yes, it's all fine.
We just want to understand
what's going on.
She doesn't have to top the class,
but until now, her grades were good.
She'd take part in class.
Even if only to complain,
but she took part.
Could she be fooling with drugs?
-What?
-No.
The other day, we saw her smoking.
We think it wasn't tobacco.
Maybe you should talk to her.
Thanks. Ciao.
-Catch.
-So?
All right. David.
He knows the record company executive
who's organizing the party.
-Okay.
-He gave him two VIP passes.
One for you and another for me.
For me?
Yeah, "for Alma,"
literally.
But will David be there or not?
Sure, he's the party's
official dealer or something.
Great.
-Mad...
-You can scream.
-I know you want to fuck him.
-Great! We're partying with David!
She's had it.
GRETA: DO YOU HAVE CLOTHES??? NO TRACKSUIT
OR I WON'T GIVE YOU YOUR INVITE
GRETA: AND PUT ON CUTE PANTIES,
MY BROTHER WILL THANK YOU
OR I CAN GO WITHOUT PANTIES
GRETA:
HAHAHAHAHA
Where were you?
-In the library with Greta.
-We need to talk.
Mom, I'm wiped out.
Alma, we had a meeting with your tutor.
What the hell's wrong with you?
You've been fooling us for months.
What are you really doing
when you say you're studying?
Nothing. I can't concentrate.
I'm not into what we do in class.
Are you taking drugs?
What? No.
Nothing? No joints, no pills, no cocaine?
Cocaine?
You know how long
I'd have to save for a gram of coke?
You know how much it costs?
Everybody knows.
Okay, sometimes I have a puff
because my friends smoke.
I don't, I swear.
When was the last time?
I don't know.
Maybe the New Year's Eve party.
No way.
The test only detects drugs
you've taken in the last eight days.
You haven't smoked
since New Year's Eve. Right?
It must be wrong.
You can't even see the red line.
-You're grounded.
-Dammit.
And you're going to graduate.
TUESDAY
WEDNESDAY
THURSDAY
FRIDAY
GRETA: WHAT ABOUT THE PARTY?
SHALL WE CANCEL?
NO WAY!!!
No!
Stop!
No, son of a bitch.
Shit!
GRETA:
WHERE ARE YOU?
ABOUT TO CATCH THE BUS
GRETA: WE HAVE TO BE ON TIME
OR MY BROTHER'LL KILL US
OK
Did you miss the bus, Alma?
I'm waiting.
You'll freeze to death.
We'll take you.
We're going through town anyway.
Come on.
Get in.
MOM: ALMA, COME HOME RIGHT NOW.
DON'T MAKE THINGS WORSE... TURN AROUND NOW!!
IF YOU OR ANYONE YOU KNOW
HAS EXPERIENCED SEXUAL VIOLENCE
YOU CAN FIND INFORMATION AND RESOURCES
TO GET HELP AT WANNATALKABOUTIT.COM