[children chattering, shouting]
[Vero] Alma, I'll pick you up later. Okay?
["Ukelelesong" by Ayoho playing]
[straining]
["Ukelelesong" by Ayoho continues]
RAISING VOICES
[bleeping]
[Nata] The world kept turning
and it didn't care what I was feeling.
I decided not to tell anyone anything.
To put on a smile.
After all, I had brought this on myself.
[menacing music plays]
#IFIDON'TFORGETI'LLDIE
#RAISINGVOICES
- [crowd cheering]
- [hard techno music playing]
You know, you're a dumbass!
Just one sec.
[David] Greta!
Greta!
Where's Alma?
She was literally here
two seconds ago and now she's gone.
Fuck.
[shouts] Alma!
Alma!
I don't know. This is weird as hell.
- Well, maybe she's gone to her house.
- No.
No way she would do that. No.
She was pretty wasted.
[dial tone]
[voice recording]
The number you are trying to reach is...
- [sighs]
- [message bleeps]
ALMA. CALL
[Greta] Let's go.
Alma!
WHERE ARE YOU?
HIYA...
ARE YOU OKAY, ALMA???
ANSWER ME!!!
Alma!
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
Greta...
Just call her parents.
She probably went home, anyway.
And if not,
be honest with them.
[sighs]
[Greta] Hello, Vero, um...
[shakily] Is Alma home?
[Vero] No. Why?
[Greta] Right, it's just that yesterday,
I lied when you called.
Alma and I went to a party.
- [Vero] Okay, where is she then?
- [Greta] Uh, um, I, I don't know.
I've been looking for her here
for three hours. And I... I can't find her.
[breathing deeply]
I don't know what to do.
ALMA IS HERE. SHE'S FINE
VERO:
CAN I TALK TO HER?
[messages pinging]
VERO:
SHE'S GROUNDED
CAN I COME SEE HER?
PLEASE, VERO
NO
[ominous music plays]
- [dog barks in distance]
- [door opens]
♪ Never had to work for love ♪
♪ Don't need you to show me how ♪
♪ Don't want to be fallin' in ♪
FEBRUARY
♪ When I'm fallin' out ♪
♪ Didn't think I'd give for love ♪
[laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Every time I hold back ♪
♪ Now there's lust in my head ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I'm tryna find who I am ♪
♪ There's choosers, there's takers ♪
♪ I don't want to feel this way
When I... ♪
♪ Need someone ♪
♪ I don't want to need no one ♪
♪ I'm not tryna let you in ♪
♪ Even if I've found the one... ♪
[laughter]
I don't know what's wrong with her.
Hey, look.
The legendary party girl has arrived.
[jubilant music playing on cellphone]
Just a little bit embarrassing for you.
[chuckles]
[music and cheering]
- Where did you get this?
- [Alberto] It's going around.
Damn, girl.
Quite the track record you got.
[Alberto] We heard you got lost
afterwards. What happened?
You screw the DJ, the whole band, or what?
[teacher] Good morning!
Everybody take your seat.
You're a bomb-ass fucking friend, huh?
About the same as you guys.
[teacher] Get your books out, please.
[Alberto] Oh,
it's your favorite book, right?
- [teacher] Page 47. Come on now.
- Kill me, dude, this class sucks.
- [teacher] Quiet!
- Seriously.
[teacher] "If in a tear I could tell you
how much this situation hurts me"
"The emptiness you are leaving
this poor heart"
"The things that once
had a lot of value..."
[bell rings]
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music plays]
[knocking on door]
[Nata] Alma!
Alma!
Open up. I know you're in there.
- You should have told me.
- We only had two passes, Nata.
[Nata] I don't give a damn
about your fucking party.
I mean, my parents
wouldn't have let me go anyway.
Then why are you so upset?
It's because you left me out.
The two of you.
But you're worse 'cause we see each other
daily and you said nothing.
- I decided at the last moment, okay?
- What a shitty excuse.
I'm having a real bad day
so drop it already, Nata.
[water running]
[Nata] Tell me something.
What am I to you?
Well, you're my friend.
That word has lost its worth
a little this morning.
For sure.
Because I think you use me so you
don't feel so alone and shitty in here,
and the minute we leave, you ignore me.
Hm. You're one to talk.
Your whole day is devoted to Alberto.
Stop fucking around, Alma.
I found out about the party,
because your mom called asking where you
were and I didn't even have to lie to her.
I mean, how sad is that?
Sorry.
It's like I'm always the third wheel
in Greta, you and I's friendship.
Fucking sucks, honestly.
[chuckles]
[Nata] What, you wanna get caught
smoking in here?
I know you and Greta
have known each other for a million years,
but what bothers me is that it's always...
[poignant music plays]
[Alma] I'm sorry.
Really.
You've no idea.
I wish you'd been there.
[cheering, laughter on cellphone]
- ASS ON THE FLOOR, BRO!
- SHE DRANK THE TOWN DRY!
["Un Baiser sur la joue"
by Vincent Perrot playing]
[message bleeps]
YOU HAVE NO FUCKING IDEA
CANNED GOODS
VEGETABLES
[ping]
- [doorbell chimes]
- [clattering]
- [woman] Fine choice.
- What?
Fine choice.
Yeah. See...
this is all I've got,
because I'm budgeting.
Well in that case, these are better.
A product that is 100 percent artificial.
[groans]
Not sure. I've tried them before,
and I'm not super fond of those.
But they're kind of perfect
if you're living on a budget, huh?
Hm? A flavorful bomb of sugar
and saturated fats to your arteries.
'Kay.
You've sold me. I think I'll give them
a second chance, then.
I'm also a big fan
of giving things a second chance.
Look, another product
that's a hundred percent artificial.
[cashier] That'll be six eighty.
I'll see you around.
Ciao.
- [doorbell chimes]
- [door opens, closes]
This one. Thanks so much.
[moaning]
Agh!
[scoffs]
[sighs]
- Did you hurt yourself?
- [Alma] I'm fine, just a pimple.
Let me see.
I know we're being harsh
with the grounding, Alma,
but you left us no other choice.
I already apologized.
What were you expecting?
That we wouldn't catch you?
That we wouldn't care you ran away?
Well, I don't know, okay?
I didn't think about it.
I just wanted to have fun at the party...
Well, we have to think
about the consequences of our actions.
Maybe we'll make a deal.
What type of deal?
- You take a drug test every week.
- [scoffs]
If it's negative and you focus
on your studies and help out at home,
you can get your phone back
and your money,
and we'll allow you
to go out on the weekends again.
Got it?
And has Dad accepted these terms?
I don't care if he accepts them.
It's a deal.
We only have these left.
- [both chuckle]
- Sure, fine.
[dog barks, pants]
Come, Cooper.
- Go on, run.
- [Cooper barking]
[Alma] I found your message.
How are you holdin' up?
[Alma] Well, I'm grounded until I turn 30.
[Greta] You scared the life out of me.
Where the hell were you?
[ominous music plays]
[Greta] Alma?
[Cooper barking]
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. Um...
I think I might still be hungover,
or maybe the Molly's still getting to me.
I don't know.
What happened to you?
I left for one second
and... and you were just gone.
Mm, I guess,
I... I felt like walking and got lost?
I looked all over the damn place
and couldn't find you.
Where'd you go, Alma?
I don't know, just around.
I, um,
hopped on a bus
and fell asleep until the last stop.
So then I had to take
a different bus home, that's it.
Why didn't you call me?
Ran out of battery.
[pen clicking]
[knocking on door]
Hey.
[Greta] 'Sup?
So, have you spoken to Alma?
Yeah, uh, she's doing fine.
Grounded for eternity, but fine.
Um, did she tell you what happened?
She says she started walking and got lost.
And then she just hopped onto a bus
and fell asleep for a while.
- What?
- There's just no way I believe that.
I mean, it sounds like total nonsense.
Yeah, but why would she lie to you?
Hmm.
- Don't know.
- Meh, don't sweat it.
Okay.
[suspenseful music plays]
[keyboard clacking]
[music, cheering]
[cheering, shouting]
DID YOU SEE THIS GIRL AFTER 4:00 A.M.?
HI THERE!
DO YOU HAVE MORE PHOTOS OF THIS MOMENT?
[ominous music plays]
[footsteps approaching]
- [David] From last night.
- Oh, thanks, son.
[father] You shouldn't've taken
your sister and Alma to that party.
I know, I'm sorry.
[Greta] It wasn't his fault.
It was my idea.
I thought that you were both mature enough
to comprehend the risk
this family's taking.
[David] We know, Mom.
[mother] Your sister was meant
to stay out of this.
Yeah, uh, thing is,
I've never really been out of it.
Not for a single day
or moment in the last four years.
Greta,
we don't like the idea of having
a pot farm in the cellar, either.
We agreed to it
so we wouldn't lose the house.
But there are many nights when it feels
like the worst decision we've ever made.
All we want is to protect you.
[gulps] Yeah, yeah. I know.
Just saying, I've been suffering
the consequences too.
- [father] Sure.
- Yeah.
[father] It's been hard for everyone.
But things may change very, very soon.
I have an interview lined up.
- What?
- Yes.
We weren't going to say anything,
but, well, I have a hunch this time.
Apparently, they need someone
with a profile in sales, like mine.
It's written for me.
And that's what
you were looking for, right?
It's what I wanted,
and the salary's pretty decent.
[inhales] So...
- Amazing!
- [laughs]
[Greta] It's so great. So, so great!
Everything will be normal again.
Hm. Of course it will, Dad.
[Greta chuckles]
[David] Good.
[melancholic music playing]
[Alma] But they can't
make you switch schools.
[Greta] My parents can't afford it, Alma.
[Alma] Well, I don't know,
I'll go with you.
I mean it. I'm not leaving you alone.
You would do that for me?
And for me.
I refuse to live without you.
[sighs]
They won't allow that, your parents.
- I don't wanna be all alone, Greta.
- [Greta] Don't be silly.
I... I swear you won't.
Wherever you go, I'll go too.
And wherever I go, you'll come with me.
No matter what.
I love you.
More than life.
[Pablo] They're not accurate tests.
[Vero] Honestly, I didn't think
it'd be a problem.
[Pablo] And you didn't check with me
before talking to her.
That's just great.
[Vero] Let's not get into how
each one of us handles things.
I don't know what happened.
I already apologized to you.
Yes, Pablo. But it's not me
you need to apologize to.
No, you're wrong.
It's got nothing to do with ego.
Ah, shit, it terrifies me
to think about what could happen
if we don't properly handle it.
Aren't you scared?
You realize locking her in
will make her want to break out again.
And then we'll lose her permanently.
She's gonna let us down again.
Well, she could do it a million times
if at the end of it she trusts me.
[ominous music plays]
[breathing heavily]
[teacher]...summoning and
presentation of the Courts.
- [bell rings]
- [teacher] All right, thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Nata] Alma.
Alma! You wanna smoke with me?
Alma.
How are the exam resits going?
- Um, I'm studying.
- Good.
You still have time to pass the course.
I know you're perfectly capable
of doing it.
- Well, I'm not so sure.
- Well, you have a lot to catch up on.
And it won't be easy.
You have to get serious.
I will.
Okay.
[Nata] So, we're going for dinner
at this super romantic restaurant.
Like the ones
with those giant wine glasses, you know?
Mm-hmm.
And then we're going to a hotel
with a hot tub in the suite.
You're not paying attention.
Uh, no, no. I am. Yeah, yeah.
[Nata] Hm?
You said you're going to a hotel,
and fuck in the hot tub like rabbits.
You're such a dumbass.
And that's supposed to be... a bear?
Bear?
It was meant to be a bird, but, hey...
[Nata] What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I don't know why,
you've been acting weird since the party.
Look, you can tell me.
I mean, we're friends.
I swear I won't tell anyone.
- You've spoken to Greta?
- No.
But I'm sure she's also noticed.
- See ya.
- [Alma] I threw myself at David.
He turned me down.
[Nata] What an asshole.
[Alma] No, it was my fault.
I don't know what the fuck
I was thinking but...
I've never been so embarrassed in my life.
[Nata] Right.
And, then you took off?
Well, after that, I got completely trashed
and then I... went out for a walk.
Later, I couldn't find my way back.
And is that all?
[woman] You have to be very sure.
It's not easy for a woman to report
an assault or even talk about it
with the people closest to her.
And to top it all off,
my dad hit me and now I...
I'm grounded and can't use my phone
until I pass some bullshit exams.
I can't do this.
Come here.
[woman] You have to understand them.
You have to put yourself in their place.
A woman might feel ashamed.
She might be afraid that no one
will believe her. Or she'll be blamed.
She might even blame herself.
[Nata] I can give you my notes
if you want.
And I can also ask my study group friends
about you joining us.
Thanks.
[Nata] That's what friends are for.
[shutter clicks]
COVERED UP, THE WAY YOU LIKE THEM
I MISS YOU, SISTER
SALES
["Until Today" by Donal Black
& Alexander Rudd playing on speakers]
[doorbell chimes]
- [man] Hey!
- [cashier] Hello.
ON SALE
CHOCOLATE SNACKS
[doorbell chimes]
- [cashier] Hello.
- Hi.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
[Greta] I've climbed to the top tier
of processed pastries.
Fantastic. [chuckles]
Gotta treat yourself once in a while.
- Waiting for someone?
- Do you come here often?
[both chuckle]
Um, no. I... I'm just taking the bus.
Well, I can give you a lift,
if you'd like. I have my car with me.
Um, I'm Mercedes.
Mer.
Greta.
[chuckles softly]
You smoke weed, really?
I'm sorry.
Shouldn't've asked,
it's none of my business.
No, it's fine. Relax.
I smoke a bit on the weekends, mostly.
Although, I've been smoking
a bit more lately.
Well,
I smoke too, every now and then.
Oh.
Listen, what if I wanted to buy some?
Lately, I don't like the product
I've been buying.
I mean... I mean, yeah.
I actually know someone super legit.
And um, could you
maybe bring me some to try?
Sure. It's... It's a little pricier
than the usual stuff, but it's worth it.
Okay.
How about this Saturday?
Hmm-hm. Mm.
Sure, perfect, sure.
["Trakatá" by Ptazeta,
Farina & Juacko playing]
FEBRUARY 14
VALENTINE'S DAY, BITCHES!
LET'S PIMP OURSELVES UP
I LOVE YOU, BABY.
READY! ALL THIS FOR YOU @ALBRTMFKR
Wow.
- You look beautiful.
- [Nata chuckles] Yeah.
I got you somethin'.
Aw.
Um, don't freak out, okay?
What happened?
The hotel I wanted to take you to
has tripled its prices tonight.
I can't afford it.
- I'm so sorry.
- Okay, and so?
And so, I found a solution.
Christian'll let us, uh,
use a room in his parents' house.
You're joking.
No, no, we'll have a big bed.
We can be there as long as we want.
We'll be all right. You'll see.
It's got its own sound system.
[Alberto chuckles nervously] Hm?
NO, NO WAY
NO IDEA
- DOESN'T RING A BELL
- NOPE
[messages bleeping]
- I DIDN'T SEE HER
- NO
- NOPE
- DON'T BE SO NOSY, GIRL
THERE WAS A GIRL LIKE HER AT MY STOP
I SAW SOMEONE LIKE HER ON A BUS
SHE WAS FAST ASLEEP
IS THIS HER?
MAYBE SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE FOUND
[exhales]
[knocking on door]
You have a visitor.
- Hiya!
- What are you doing here?
Nothing really. I just heard that you
were grounded, so I got provisions.
- Ah, thanks.
- [chuckles]
So, how's it goin'?
Well, bad. Trying not to kill myself.
You're not wearing
the necklace today, either.
Shit, Berta. You're being really dramatic.
I can give it back...
No. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. It's just... I'm very intense.
This always happens to me.
Uh, you wanna... smoke?
I shouldn't give you what I wanted to.
So what was it?
- A pet tracking device or what?
- [both chuckle]
You see? You really are
super clever, dude.
You're the best.
Wait, okay. My therapist told me
I shouldn't question my decisions.
So...
Here you go.
[Alma chuckles]
From when we both watched Monsters Inc.,
on my birthday.
Jeez, you printed it out and everything.
Not too creepy, right?
Well, I mean, luckily everyone
in art school is crazy like me.
Well, my school's the same way.
But they're more like robot-psychopaths.
Yeah, at my school
they're more like bipolar, schizos...
- Hmm.
- It's too much, uh...
Too passionate about their own thing.
Totally my energy.
So, you see a therapist?
[breathes deeply] Mm, yes.
Since, um...
Well, ever since... since the day I lost it.
You remember that, right?
[ominous music playing]
[crying]
[Alma] Berta?
Are you there?
[screams] Go away! Leave me alone!
[sobbing]
- But, are you okay?
- [Berta] I told you to go! [sobbing]
[melancholic music playing]
[Berta] I'm sure that I...
That I went too far
with you at some point.
I was a fucking mess.
Sorry.
Well, we all go
a bit crazy sometimes, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, but I don't know, for me it...
It was
like I went batshit.
And
the worst part is my parents
went even crazier than I did,
with their divorce, and, well,
I didn't have anyone to turn to.
Sorry.
I wasn't aware
that things had gotten so bad.
[chuckles] It's totally fine.
You know how it goes,
what doesn't kill you makes you fatter.
Shit.
You're the best, Berta.
Mm, I know.
- Oh.
- [both chuckle]
[males chanting, clapping]
Babe, take it easy.
[Alberto breathing heavily]
[chanting continues]
- [pounding]
- [Alberto grunting]
Slow down.
[grunts]
[bed creaking]
[males shouting, laughing]
[breathes deeply]
Whose room is this?
It's the housekeeper's.
That was really great.
- It was. Hm.
- Uh-huh.
The guys said they were gonna order pizzas
and then go out for a drink.
But since Christian's parents
are coming back later,
maybe it's better if we stay here longer?
I'll see you out there.
[door opens, closes]
You guys all seriously suck.
Shut the fuck up.
- Shut up, dickhead!
- Come here, bro!
Fuck, dude. Come on, man! [laughing]
[indistinct]
- Enjoy your Valentine's Day, everyone.
- Am I good or what? Dude, who's playing?
Wait, Nata!
- [Mer] It's really good, no?
- I told you.
- Mm. Much better than mine is.
- [chuckles]
- Sign me up as a client.
- Sure, I'd love that.
Well, um,
guess I'll see you next time, then.
- Mm.
- Do you want a lift somewhere?
No. It's fine. And besides,
I don't have plans 'til much later on.
Does your generation
celebrate Valentine's Day?
And exactly which generation
do you think that is?
Gen Z?
Z?
In your mind I'm that young?
Sorry.
[slow, contemporary pop music playing]
Um, do you guys celebrate Valentine's?
Yeah, 'course.
Well, I mean, we invented it.
'Bout the same time
we discovered electricity and penicillin.
May I have your number?
Yeah.
[phone beeping]
There. We're connected.
Thanks.
[Mer] We can meet at my house
next time, if you want.
Hm, your house. Yeah.
Better to do this somewhere private,
now we're a bit exposed.
Right. Uh... Well, uh, wanna call me?
- Mm. Okay.
- Great.
Well, see you.
Ciao.
[cellphone pings]
RAQUELILLA_AF
FOUR NEW MESSAGES
[ominous music plays]
[door opens]
DO NOT RAPE, SIR
[suspenseful music playing]
NO MEANS NO
[calm, pensive music plays]
[Greta] To my first and best friend.
Today, I remembered the summer
that we spent crying
because I had to switch schools.
[dog barking]
I felt like my arm had been chopped off
and I had to learn to live without it.
And I know that sounds very over the top
and crazy, but, well, it's true.
The worst part of being separated
was knowing that
if something bad happened to you...
[Alma whistles] Come on, Cooper.
[Greta] ...I wouldn't be there with you.
And I'd much rather be the one
getting hurt than seeing it happen to you.
That's the truth.
You're like a sister to me,
and even if you don't know it, I'm always
watching you out of the corner of one eye
because I need to know that you're okay.
I know that you're a total boss
and you don't need anyone to protect you.
Except deep down, everyone needs someone
who will support us and listen to us.
Even bosses.
Alma, you are the best person I know
and you deserve to be happy always.
But, if you're not,
if something bad has happened
to you and you want to tell me,
I'm here.
You're not alone.
But if you don't want to tell me,
it doesn't matter,
I'm going to love you just the same.
I guess there are things
that are hard to tell,
even to your first and best friend.
I love you more than life.
[sobbing]
Mom.
Uh, can I have my phone?
Are you all right?
Yeah, it's just allergies.
I just wanted to message Greta.
[Alma sniffles]
Here.
Thanks.
COVERED UP, THE WAY YOU LIKE THEM
SALES
[suspenseful music plays]
PUTOALFUCKING
YOU'RE A SLUT
[suspenseful music builds, turns ominous]
[music fades]
[dog barking in distance]
[serene, haunting music plays]
[engine sounds]