Let's go. Come on, let's go.
RAISING VOICES
HOW TO HUNT DOWN A PREDATOR
#ASSAULT
#THISISN'TOVER
POSTING
How to hunt down a sexual predator.
APRIL
At 5:00 a.m., Galán attacks the city
with a group of soldiers,
and in under three hours,
Jaca is under his control,
and they head for the next city.
Whoever can name the city,
I'll raise you half a point in the exam.
Huesca.
Exactly.
The insurgents head for Huesca,
starving, with a handful of old trucks
and freezing cold, because...
I don't know if you've ever been
in Huesca in December.
It's goddamn freezing.
So it wasn't easy for them.
In fact, that morning at dawn,
government troops
stopped the insurrection,
arrested Galán and his right hand...
García Hernández.
Can you imagine what happened to them?
-They killed them.
-That's right. A firing squad.
So, in the end, it was all for nothing.
Well,
I don't know if we can be so categorical.
I don't know.
What do you think?
It led to something.
A few months later, the king had to leave.
Someone's done their homework.
In short, history is what it is
because things happened.
I mean, it all serves a purpose.
Right?
One person can achieve many things.
And history is full of examples.
WHO WERE THE GIRLS
WHO REPORTED THEIR RAPISTS?
THE ONES YOU TOLD ME ABOUT AT MY HOUSE
GRETA: DAISY COLEMAN...
AND THE OTHER... WAIT, I'LL LOOK
GRETA: CHANEL MILLER IS THE OTHER ONE.
WHY???
FOR A SCHOOL ASSIGNMENT.
GOTTA GO. UP TO MY EYES
THANKS!
BIOGRAPHY
One night, when she was 14,
Daisy Coleman went to a party
organized by a schoolmate.
She was raped there.
Daisy reported her attacker,
but in a matter of days,
she went from victim to whore.
They threatened her on social media
and spread details of her private life.
They set fire to her home.
She had to leave her hometown.
Daisy fought all her life
against rape culture,
against a depression
she couldn't overcome.
She committed suicide at 23.
HOW TO HUNT DOWN
A SEXUAL PREDATOR
I'm sure that pig is abusing other girls.
And he'll go on.
No, Alma, I said no.
I want to die just thinking about it.
Don't worry, I wasn't thinking about that.
I can do it for you.
What?
I can set up a fake profile on Instagram
of a junior high school student
abused by her history teacher.
What for?
Some girl may identify with your story.
And with a bit of luck,
someone will recognize and report him.
I know it's a long shot,
but we have to try, right?
And the photos?
Of me.
Right, like that.
It'll be me,
but unrecognizable, obviously.
-This one, right?
-Yeah.
What name do we put?
Iam_colemanmiller.
The names of two rape survivors
who reported it,
but they were ignored.
Why are you getting mixed up in this?
Because I owe you.
And I don't want any girl
to feel the way I made you feel.
Alone.
How long
have you been thinking about this?
I'll post something.
This is me
before I was raped.
Perfect.
Nata, concentrate.
You'll regret it later.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'VE GOT
UNTIL YOU LOSE IT
WHEN LOVE IS GONE, ONLY TEARS REMAIN
NATA: WHAT ARE YOU UP TO???
NOTHING, GIRL... BLACK HOLE... SHIT...
NATA: ME TOO... SEE YOU IN BABEL???
YOU'RE NOT GROUNDED ANYMORE???
NATA: NOT AS MUCH...
COME ON, PRETTY PLEASE!
I'll call you later, okay?
Maybe I won't pick up.
You know I get lost easily.
And you know I'll always find you.
Ciao.
Be careful, okay?
You too.
-What's up?
-How are you?
-That was David, right?
-Yes.
You're so lucky, bitch.
-What are you doing here?
-Celebrating. It's payday.
We've sold it all, guys.
Look at this cool scar. I want one.
Throw yourself under the bus,
see if you get one.
-You idiot!
-Come on.
Do you want a bit of magic?
No.
My parents are being a drag
about the tests,
and I don't want to screw up.
-What happened with your thing?
-Not much. Personal use.
Small fine and out.
Exactly.
-Know anything about Kevin and Jota?
-Sure do, girl.
We know you needn't worry
about them anymore.
Someone anonymous called the cops
when they had a huge shipment at home.
Sure, "someone anonymous."
And with their priors,
they weren't let out.
So, no bail, no nothing.
-Fuck them.
-In the slammer.
Fuck them. They're assholes.
-Yeah, they were.
-I'm going in. It's chilly.
-Okay, sorry. Catch you later.
-Go on.
-See you.
-Hey, pass it.
-I rolled it.
-It's my turn.
Look at her! Look at that smile.
Now she has a boyfriend.
No, David isn't my boyfriend.
-Really?
-We've been out three times, that's it.
But have you fucked him yet?
No, we've just kissed and that.
She's waiting
for the northern lights...
and violins in the background.
-You two are hilarious.
-Totally.
Dammit, for once I get it on
instead of you two.
-Don't push it.
-Fuck you.
By the way,
I saw Alberto and his buddies
messing around
because they'd won some shit.
Yes, I saw it too.
-Where?
-Excuse me?
On Instagram.
-Dammit, Nata.
-You still follow him on Instagram?
-Get off my case.
-Unbelievable.
Shut up. I bet you still follow
that old bat.
No. No way.
She doesn't know what Instagram is.
Jeez, you're hilarious too, huh?
Yeah.
Alberto's history, okay?
I believe you, sister.
Hi, Mom.
Honey, what are you doing home so soon?
-Is something wrong?
-No.
You had a fight with Alberto.
Alberto and I broke up.
-I broke it off.
-I thought so.
You seemed down lately,
and not about being grounded.
What did he do? Tell me.
-Mom, don't be a drag.
-What? Tell me about the drama.
Go on, come here.
You can tell me anything.
I won't judge you.
-He got mixed up with another girl, right?
-No, Mom, that's not it.
We just haven't been right for some time.
Nata, honey, men are a bit simple.
Sometimes it's better
to ignore some nonsense
to keep the whole package.
-Nata, will you listen to me, dammit?
-Hey!
I don't know what you're getting at.
You seem so glum lately.
If it's another girl,
use it in your favor.
You can get things you didn't have before.
Alberto looks like the kind of boy
who'd give you those things.
Do you understand me?
A girl shouldn't give up
what took her so much to get
because of her partner's mistake.
Mistakes are forgotten.
Even cheating.
Did Dad cheat on you?
What? No.
-It's as if you were talking about Dad.
-Nata.
Why would I talk about Dad?
What I'm trying to say is
that as a woman,
you'll have to give in to certain things.
Life's like that, and men are like that.
And it's much smarter
to chalk it up and forget
than throw it all overboard.
Listen to me.
Learn it.
POSTING
The world kept spinning
and didn't care how I felt.
I decided not to tell anyone,
to wear a smile.
After all, I'd asked for it.
I took this photo
the day I decided to slit my wrists.
I couldn't take it anymore.
It was better to end it all.
#THISPAINNEVERGOESAWAY
Hey.
We have almost 4,000 followers.
It's not enough.
We need more.
Take it easy.
It sickens me to see him so chill.
We need more hardcore posts.
Talking about this isn't easy.
I know what I'm talking about.
Let's keep going, see what happens.
And just with the posts,
we're helping lots of people.
Have you read the comments?
I'm glad you convinced me to do it,
Coleman Miller.
You should thank me for not reporting you.
-But Nata, you told me...
-Look.
If you blame me again
for what happened, I'm leaving.
No, I'm sorry.
-You were a pig.
-I know.
I've been apologizing since it happened.
How do I know you won't do it again?
Because I really mean it.
I haven't slept since we broke up.
Right.
Because of your guilty conscience.
Because you're the love of my life.
And don't piss me off,
or I'll tell my mother and bye-bye Canada.
Nata, wait.
ENTER CANADA WITH CRIMINAL RECORD...
ENTRY TO CANADA IS NOT PERMITTED
WITH A CRIMINAL RECORD
What do I have to do
to get a second chance?
Work hard at it.
I want everyone to see
that you're dying to be with me again
and you'd do anything to get me back.
I'll do it.
And I want a proper date,
not the shit we had on Valentine's Day.
You'll have that too.
If you do it right, maybe
I'll give you another chance.
I've missed you.
He was fouling a lot.
I was on the ground all the time.
-Really?
-We were mad.
So, in the end, we scored.
-Sure.
-Did you see it?
When are you coming to watch me again?
I'll dedicate a goal to you.
If you need anything,
I'm right behind, okay?
-Are you back with Alberto?
-No, don't start.
-It's incredible you even talk to him.
-Good morning.
Can we sit down, please?
You're quiet today and so well-behaved.
Let's open our books to page 155.
I don't get it.
It's crazy getting back with him
after what he did.
Keep it down.
It wasn't so bad, okay? It's okay.
-Nothing happened.
-Bullshit, Nata.
He and his buddies nearly raped you.
They weren't going to rape me.
It was a gang bang, okay?
Some girls like it.
Do you?
-No, I don't. That's why we didn't do it.
-No, it's why they didn't.
Don't you realize
that you had no fucking power?
Look, not everything
is black and white, okay?
We've talked about it.
He's apologized tons of times.
And it's my decision.
I won't throw it all away
over some nonsense.
"Some nonsense"?
You know who you sound like?
Your mother.
You're turning into a fucking carbon copy.
It's pathetic seeing you play house
at 17 years old.
And with that guy, a loser and a clown,
who'll only ruin your life.
Who the fuck are you to judge me?
You know, I've never heard you say
you love him.
Fuck you, Alma. You're a real know-it-all
who's always lecturing others,
and you know what?
You're the worst of all.
Okay.
Come in.
-Are we meeting up today?
-Today?
I want to take you to a place
with spectacular sushi.
Really?
I'd love to,
but I can't.
I've got a ton of exams to correct here.
Can't you correct them tomorrow?
Or give B's...
-No.
-...to everyone?
I can't.
I can't today.
Okay.
-It's okay.
-Another time.
Sure.
Shut the door.
Ciao.
STUDENT FILE, ÁLVARO GALLEGO
NATACHA SOLÍS ANDRADE
ALMA VAREZ MARÍN
SENIOR YEAR
STUDENT ACADEMIC RECORD
Hi.
I saw you arguing with Nata.
Great, we're a trending topic.
If it's any consolation,
I think Alberto's an asshole.
Nata should be able to see it.
Why does everyone see
that she's fucking up except her?
Nobody knows they're fucking up
while they're fucking up.
I suppose.
Alma, you were right.
I was a bad friend.
I shouldn't have slept with you.
You were out of it.
No, you shouldn't have.
Right.
If I could turn back time,
I wouldn't do it again.
I swear.
I'm really sorry.
It's all right, Hernán.
I'm not just saying it.
I'm going to a therapy group.
They're helping me understand a lot.
Cool.
Negative.
I've been negative for two months, Mom.
Are you going to do the tests
until I'm 30?
-What was it?
-Negative!
Your daughter's asking
how long we'll be doing the tests.
Until 30 sounds good to me.
I don't care.
You're the ones spending a fortune.
The box of 50 is very cheap.
Go on, no more tests.
Yes!
High five!
DAVID: ARE YOU AWAKE?
YEP. WHERE ARE YOU?
DAVID: IN A CLUB. RECORD LAUNCH
ANY MODELS BUGGING YOU?
DAVID: HUNDREDS, BUT NONE I LIKE
AS MUCH AS YOU
DAVID: I HAVE A SURPRISE, HAHA
REALLY? WHAT?
DAVID: IF I TELL YOU
IT WON'T BE A SURPRISE
SURPRISES TURN ME ON
DAVID: WILL TELL YOU LATER
DAVID: GET DRESSED UP
AND I'LL PICK YOU UP IN A BIT
Hey.
What do you want?
I can't eat all this alone.
Will you help me?
I just want to talk, please.
This is shit. It should be banned.
I knew you couldn't resist it.
Playing dirty?
Again?
Listen, Mer. I want us
to keep seeing each other.
Greta...
Look, Mer. I promise
I won't try to kiss you at any time.
I just want to go somewhere
and chat or have a smoke. That's it.
Besides, I turn 18 in three months.
I can wait.
But wait for what, Greta?
I'm 20 years older than you.
Well, okay.
Okay. If you want, just say the word,
and I'm outta here.
But if for whatever reason,
because I'm
really witty,
smart,
you miss me,
you can tell me, because I'm not going
to act the idiot around here.
What?
What's that smile? Yes? No?
You know, I'm Gen Z.
You have to spell it out for me.
Sometimes.
Only sometimes.
Sure, I've missed you.
In fact, just before you came,
I was about to paint my big toe
and screw it up.
Shall I do it?
-Thanks.
-You look gorgeous.
-What?
-I brought you something.
-Really?
-Yes.
A surprise.
So you know I'm serious.
Do you like it?
A lot.
So,
are we getting back together or...
Well,
hold up a bit.
It's a good start,
but you have to work harder.
Right.
-I owed you a party.
-This is amazing.
Let's go.
-Get me a beer. I'll be right back, okay?
-Okay.
Two beers, please.
Thanks.
How are you?
Here I am.
Who was that?
The boss of all this.
A record company executive
and a former customer.
Jeez, it's Bárbara Lago!
I love that woman.
I know. Greta told me.
You can change it if you like.
No. No way.
I really like it.
It's perfect.
So, what's not right?
I'm a bit cut up about Alma.
We were friends for a long time.
I don't get
how you can still be her friend.
She can't stand you either.
She thinks you're a psychopath.
That bitch needs to be taught a lesson.
Come with me.
I'll wait until you're 18.
Two months ago, I'd have hidden
in your suitcase and gone with you.
But now I don't think it's what I want.
Why?
That trip is your dream.
I have to make my own trip.
Are you angry?
No.
No. It's just that...
I didn't expect
an emotional pullback like this.
What I told you in the café was true.
Go on that trip.
And let me fuck you until you go, okay?
Come here.
I'm going to let you take home the exams
so you can look at your mistakes.
You're welcome.
Wow, no way!
THE HISTORY OF SPAIN - 7
GO! YOU'RE DOING GREAT!
I'm going to tell you something important.
Excuse me, guys.
Congratulations.
You did well in the exam.
Thanks.
And thanks for the encouragement.
I need it.
You don't sit with Natacha anymore.
She switched me for her boyfriend.
What happened there?
They split up,
I said some nasty things about Alberto,
now they're together, and I'm the bad guy.
Right, a classic. I've lost
a lot of friendships that way too.
But if I were her, I'd have no doubt
who I'd choose.
We had a staff meeting yesterday.
We were talking about you.
-My ears were burning.
-Right.
We think you can pass the year.
Even sit the SATs.
I think you'll have to put up with me
for another year.
How are your finals going?
Not great. I can't concentrate.
Everything all right at home?
With your friends? Any problems?
No.
No, I'm the problem. I'm just a bit lost.
I don't understand you.
You're very smart.
What happened?
Everyone's so sure, and I'm not.
I'm not like the others.
Just as well you're not.
No?
I mean, you're special.
-You say that because you know I'm down.
-Not at all.
Maybe you're right.
You have low self-esteem,
you're not interested in your studies...
The two could be related.
Right.
I could help you.
How?
We could meet up
once or twice a week after class,
in the classroom, in my office...
Look me in the eye.
What do you think?
Think about it.
Okay?
What did you say?
That I'd think about it.
It's a trap, Alma.
He started like that with me.
The same thing will happen to you.
Do you want that?!
No, obviously not.
But if he tries anything on...
If he does, what?!
What'll you do when he jumps on you?
There'll be nobody there!
The school will be empty!
You're a fool
if you think you can stop him!
-Dammit!
-I won't let him touch me.
-I won't let him do anything.
-You don't get it!
It doesn't work like that!
This isn't a fucking game, Alma!
-Berta.
-Get out!
-What's wrong? Are you okay?
-Yes.
You'd better go.
Don't worry, she'll be fine.
-Fuck!
-Berta.
Go away!
-Take it easy.
-No!
-Breathe with me. Berta!
Will we follow all the rules?
Yes!
And what's the main thing we have to do?
Have fun!
Come on, Frankie!
Mom, my history teacher suggested
I do some orientation classes.
When would that be?
In the afternoon, once or twice a week.
That's nice of him.
Try it. Maybe it'll do you good.
Right?
What?
-I'm going to make a sandwich.
-Okay.
Here already?
Great.
Teenagers don't let themselves
be helped much.
Sure, I've tried drugs, psychics,
and the horoscope.
And still the same, right?
I'll put it on silent.
I didn't know what I wanted either.
I had no idea.
Not studying. I was sure about that.
-Let's go.
-Nothing appeals to me.
Right.
I think of something I might like,
and I think it's going to be
really boring or really hard.
Alma, you can do anything you want.
I'm not just saying it,
or I wouldn't be here.
I don't know why you bother with me.
I just told you.
You'll be able to do whatever you want.
I don't think it's fair you fall apart.
And...
-How did you know what you wanted to do?
-Me?
The same as you.
A teacher helped me.
I like to do the same for my students.
Only the ones worth the effort, of course.
Sorry.
Sorry. I got tied up, and it got late.
I asked Andrea to join us
in these orientation sessions.
She thinks you have
a lot of potential. Right, Andrea?
Of course.
What do you think?
Good.
Let's see.
I'll share this with you.
Let's see what you think...
about this one here.
-After this one, right?
-Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Let's see.
-Are we doing a test?
-Yes, it's a multiple-choice test, okay?
So...