We're going to do lots of things together.
You'll see.
I swear I'll do everything I can
to make you happy.
I can't shake it off that easily!
Stop your crazy yelling!
Pablo!
Pablo! Please stop!
Don't hit her again, please.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Did you see yourself?
You fucking scare me!
She looked as if she hated me, Sole.
You should have seen her.
She used to tell me things.
Now she wants nothing to do with me.
I'm losing her.
RAISING VOICES
I screamed as loud as I could,
but no one took any notice.
#SHUTYOURFUCKINGMOUTH
#CRAZYLIAR
And later, it was much worse.
#CRAZYLIAR #RAISING VOICES
MARCH 3, 2018
Where is it?
Here it is.
What are you doing?
We're meeting Sole to make some banners.
Want to come?
Dunno.
Come on, get out of here for a bit,
and it's Saturday.
Right?
There'll be a lot of women
who can't go on strike...
-Like we'd arranged.
-Almost finished.
Does it look okay?
Okay, and down here, "Feminism."
-In capitals?
-Yes.
Maybe something a bit wittier.
What do you think?
I had one. Wait, what was it?
"Manolito, tonight
you're having dinner solo."
That's a good one. Write it down.
"Manolito." It's brilliant.
It's going to be a historic protest.
Are you coming?
I don't know. Maybe.
You know, you and I were together
at another protest,
against the war in Iraq, in 2003.
I don't remember.
Sure, you were in a stroller.
You were very little.
It was amazing.
Do you know what two million people
shouting at once is like?
For the same cause.
I must have a photo somewhere.
Shall we watch a movie later?
Nata just wrote to see
if I can go to her place.
Can I go?
Sure.
She's cool, man.
Who is she?
-This guy's cousin.
-What? She's not my cousin.
You! What about it?
Did you see that? Right, man.
-Is she your cousin?
-No.
She is his cousin.
-Nata, does your TV have Bluetooth?
-Yeah, grab the remote.
There she is.
Guys, look at that.
Good God.
My God, what sluts, man.
-Where are the girls like this?
-Goddammit.
Here, you psycho. You guys are blind.
You're asking for it, right?
What have they got that we don't have?
First, the desire for dick.
There's more desire
around here than dicks.
Speaking for yourself, Nata?
Excuse me, kid, I'm super sexual.
Well...
You know it's not real, right?
Almita, what's the problem?
The problem is that guys like you
think these things happen.
That girl's not enjoying herself.
No girl likes this fucking shit.
You know what else we don't like?
Getting dick pics we didn't ask for.
Like this one.
Someone sent it to me who gets horny
showing pics of his shitty dick.
-Ring a bell?
-Let's see.
-I have more.
What a big dick.
Let's see.
Ask her. She's seen the most dicks here.
Not as many as you,
or you.
I mean, the locker rooms,
ten guys taking a shower after the games.
Or are you shy
and shower in your clothes, Christian?
I'm not into dicks.
Who knows whose it is?
They're all just as ugly.
-Especially this one.
-Not all of them.
I'm outta here.
-Check out this video.
-Let me see.
MER: ARE YOU COMING TO MY PLACE
WITH SOMETHING?
IS 5 OKAY WITH YOU?
Isn't it crazy that a carrot
comes out of here?
Sure, really crazy.
How long do they take?
A few months, I think.
It'll be up by summer.
That's a long time!
Right.
You took nine months,
and you came out as a chubby baby.
Hi, gorgeous.
Alma, listen. I need some weed urgently.
Do you know anyone who could sell me some?
I don't know. David?
Not an option.
What are you doing?
If you take another gram,
I swear I'll get rid of the plantation.
Fuck the house, the mortgage, all of it.
Okay.
Can you ask the guys from the park?
No.
Hey, it's not all mine.
Sure. Go on, get in the car.
What a son of a bitch.
The park guys
aren't available.
You don't know anyone else?
Pretty please.
Yes?
Okay.
He's hiding something under his clothes.
It could be a bomb.
Look who's here.
-They all died.
-Stop!
-Come in.
-Not another step.
They died.
Kevin, look who's here.
Stop right there.
What's up, Alma?
They died.
Stop!
It's been a while.
Last time I saw you, you took off.
Right, I was late.
What brings you here?
My friend, Greta, would like some weed.
Greta.
Great.
Sit down.
Would you like a beer?
We're in a hurry.
You're a bit nervous, Alma.
You're not wearing a wire, right?
Pull up your T-shirt.
Take it easy.
Things are a bit tense
because of the cops.
Right.
Five grams. Are you selling or not?
Yeah.
-We're leaving.
-Hang on.
Hang on.
You can't leave without trying it out.
No, thanks. I have things to do.
I can't get high.
You won't have beer,
you won't sit down,
you won't take off your coats...
I don't sell to people who disrespect me.
Give it back.
Give it here.
Hey, this is bullshit weed.
Give me back my money,
and we're going elsewhere.
There are lots of dealers around here.
I'm kidding you.
The truth is, it's pretty good.
Do you grow it yourselves?
I have a friend who likes to smoke,
and I'm seeing her tonight.
She could get some every day.
Maybe not every day, but every week.
This chick?
I like Greta.
I don't want you to go back alone.
Don't worry, they're idiots.
It's just an act.
No.
They're sketchy.
You're sketchy.
I mean it.
-Okay.
-Don't go back there alone.
Okay.
Come on, don't worry.
-Ciao.
Hiya. What are you up to?
I've called you tons of times,
but you won't pick up.
I don't know what's wrong. Where are you?
Show some sign of life, goddammit.
I like those little statues there.
My ex bought them on a trip.
Were you together long?
Yes, a long time.
But things happened,
and I realized it wasn't what I wanted.
Honestly, almost nothing in my life
was what I wanted.
And it's important
to allow ourselves to do what we want.
You're right. Look...
To doing what we want.
Exactly. When you least expect it,
it all goes to shit.
Right.
Actually, sometimes life is a bit...
It's really fucked.
Drama queen.
Look,
both my parents lost their jobs
in the crisis.
We were doing fucking great, and suddenly...
Damn, I'm sorry.
What do they do now?
Not much.
My...
My father does some courses.
My mom looks for European subsidies
for councils or something.
Brothers and sisters?
David.
He was studying biology, and now...
I don't know what he does, to be honest.
-I love the color of your nails.
-Right?
Very cool.
Jeez! I'll do yours! I've got it.
-Look.
-You've got nail polish here?
Of course. You never know
whose nails you'll have to do.
-Really.
-I like this color for you.
-But I don't know if it suits me.
-Why not? It's beautiful.
Come on.
Your toenails, less obvious. Here.
All right.
Though I may screw it up a bit.
Let's see.
Come on, please.
-Sorry.
-What a disaster, girl!
Damn, I haven't laughed like this in ages.
The other one.
Well...
I'll see if I have some remover.
Okay.
Listen, I need to talk to you.
Forget it.
Alma, please!
-Who did you tell?
-Nobody.
-What about those other friends?
-Who?
The ones who sell weed. Kevin and Jota.
They're not my friends.
And I didn't tell them anything.
Why?
Because I got sent another dick pic.
I can't imagine them doing that.
They're not very bright, you know?
Okay.
Hey, Alma,
I don't know what Greta's said to you,
but I didn't force you.
You wanted us to do it.
How did you find me at the party?
I saw you leave with Greta.
Greta had gone for the coats
when you appeared.
Why didn't we wait for her?
Come on, don't shit me.
You asked me to get you out of there.
I did you a favor.
Thanks so much, Hernán.
You didn't do me a fucking favor!
It was shit. All of it.
-It shouldn't have happened.
-Okay, but we both fucked up.
No, man, you fucked up.
Okay?
Look, I want to forget all this.
Just pretend you don't know me, okay?
Bye, Hernán.
What's really crazy is how many times
she cheated on the guy...
All right, ready!
Sit down.
Pay attention.
Whoever's going to strike on the 8th,
I need a letter from your parents, okay?
Andrea, are you going on strike?
Yes, I will be joining the strike.
I'll leave school work
for those who come to class.
I don't really get this strike.
It doesn't make sense.
I don't know what you want.
Equality, idiot.
If you don't specify what you want,
it's no use.
-Goddammit.
-There's something interesting here.
Can we ask for something to improve
without specifying how?
-Are we sure of what we want?
-The same as them.
-Why are you against us?
-Forget it. They're dykes.
Christian, let's cut out
the sexist slurs, okay?
What are we against?
The heteropatriarchy.
Don't you know?
Parents are the heteropatriarchy.
The heteropatriarchy lets you get away
with that crap without shame,
or fear.
You're real assholes.
-Such a pain.
-Shut the fuck up.
Let's open our books to page 57.
Hey, stop!
Alma! Tell us more
about the heteropatriarchy, won't you?
Stop! We just want you
to explain it better.
-Teach us, please.
-Why don't the three of you go to hell?
You can't keep your mouth shut, right?
What are you doing, asshole?
Fucking clowns!
What the hell, you idiot?
We're sick of you.
You think you're better than us,
you fucking squirt.
So until school ends
and you're finally out of our sight,
shut it.
Or what?
You don't want to know.
Wouldn't a bigger sign be better?
To see it better.
It looks a bit small.
I don't know.
-I'm going to the library.
-Hold on a second.
Sure you don't want me to take you?
The way things are, I'm worried.
Any news about the break-in?
The police say
they've had several similar cases.
They think they're from the juvenile home.
Savages, Nata.
They wrecked the house.
Fuck!
They broke plates, glassware,
slashed the sofas...
played with her underwear.
I can't think of anything
more unpleasant for a woman.
You know what I mean.
ALBERTO: I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU COME
LIKE THE OTHER DAY.
ALBERTO: I LOVE IT
WHEN YOU'RE SUCH A SLUT.
YOUR SLUT.
I could report them.
Alma, really. Don't be so intense.
Seriously? It's a crime. It's harassment.
But they didn't hit you, right?
Is it not enough they followed me,
threatened me,
and threw me against the fence?
Does it take blood
for them to listen to us?
I'm going for a coffee.
Thanks.
-Hi there.
-Hi.
Coffee with milk and a glass of water.
Thanks.
Alma?
What are you doing here?
I'm at the library.
-How do you want the milk?
-Hot.
I'm sitting there. Do you want to join me?
My idea is to start here,
in north Vietnam.
From there, over to Cambodia.
Then Cambodia to Thailand,
and end up in Bali.
Stay where I like, leave when I get bored...
Go with the flow.
Cool.
And
when do you leave?
When my parents find permanent jobs, and...
and I can give up the weed.
Before you go, you should find out
what that tattoo means.
Yes, I will.
Listen.
I wanted to talk about
what happened on the night of the party.
I'm really sorry. I was very drunk.
I'll always remember it as one
of the most pathetic nights of my life.
But maybe in a few years,
we'll laugh about it
because nothing happened.
So let's forget it, okay?
Right.
The problem is that I can't forget it.
I can't get it out of my head.
I like you a lot, Alma.
I really like you.
And...
I've told you my plan,
and I'm scared
you'll make me change my mind.
Well,
you have to go.
Otherwise, you'll regret it
your whole life.
But first,
I'd like to fuck you,
because doing it with my best friend's
big brother gets me hot.
I should get back. I have a chapter
on the Generation of '98 waiting for me.
Hey.
We...
We could meet on the weekend.
Do you want to?
I'll check my diary.
-Okay.
-That's a yes.
Yes!
-Tell me again.
-No.
-Forget it. I've told you loads of times.
-Yeah, but I want to hear all about it.
The cups were blue.
Turquoise.
Do you think it's a good idea?
Sure.
You're going to fulfill a sexual fantasy
with a guy who's really cute,
and nice.
Plus, I know him,
and he'll treat you right.
Otherwise, he'll have to deal with me,
you know?
And...
You and I are okay, right?
I mean, if it changes anything
between us, I'll forget it.
No, it's all good.
I don't want you to hurt him
or him to hurt you.
Try not to get too hooked,
and it's all good.
Me? No way.
It's just a fuck.
He doesn't want anything serious,
and neither do I.
But if it doesn't work,
you can keep trying
with other members of the family.
I'm going.
Ciao, babe.
Stay for dinner?
I'd love to, but no.
Come on, Alma. It's late.
Hey, seriously, what do I wear?
I don't know,
something that's easy to take off.
You're an asshole.
Hi there.
Need help?
You look happy, huh?
Well, it's...
I had something pending
that seems to be going ahead.
Really?
Can't you give me more details?
For now, it's a bit soon,
but I'll keep you informed.
Set the table. Go on.
Okay.
Mom.
Do you remember the night I ran off?
Yes.
Well,
I slept with a guy.
And it was shitty.
Why was it shitty?
Did something happen?
No.
Yes.
I don't know.
I'd drunk a lot, and...
I was mad because a guy had blown me off.
Maybe I wanted revenge
by sleeping with another guy.
I don't know.
Right.
Alcohol, sex, and frustration don't mix.
I regretted it as soon as I got into bed.
Why didn't you stop it?
I don't know.
I didn't know how.
I was embarrassed about what he'd think.
I thought it was easier.
Alma.
Don't be shy the next time.
Say, "I don't want to go on with this."
If anyone feels bad or disappointed,
it's their problem.
Do you understand?
It's their problem.
YOU ARE HERE
FIGHT LIKE A GIRL
Is it obvious
that I ran out of space in the end?
No way. It's perfect.
-Really?
-Yes.
I like it.
It's clever.
You've got a talent for slogans.
You used to say that when I'd get upset.
Cities worldwide are preparing
for what will be a historic day.
Millions of women are called
to mobilize against discrimination...
Exciting, isn't it?
Yes, very.
Look what they gave me.
Manolito, tonight
you're having dinner solo!
Cool.
-Try it.
-Let's see.
We're sick to damn death
of your sexist waste of breath!
And for pure pleasure, we have a painter,
a court painter, who in his final years
won't work for the court.
He'll work when he wants to
and because he wants to.
I'M COMING JUST THINKING ABOUT IT!
So here is when Goya
no longer needs to use irony
or double meanings.
He has no need to paint
to be a renowned painter,
to demonstrate that he didn't like Godoy,
but loved the Countess of Chinchon.
He's just painting to paint.
And as a painter, we'll see techniques,
and we'll see with those techniques...
THEY WANT US AS ENEMIES
THEY'LL HAVE US AS SISTERS
MER
1 NEW MESSAGE
YOU DIDN'T TAKE IT OFF!
THEY BRING GOOD MEMORIES.
WILL YOU FINISH THEM?
-I'm off.
-Where are you going?
To Greta's.
She was going to come with us,
but she's ill.
The bus leaves at 7:00.
-I'll be there, I promise.
-Okay.
-Ciao.
-Bye.
-Don't be late.
-I won't.
We'll probably stay for dinner
and be back late.
-No parties.
-No, don't worry.
-Besides, I have some work to finish.
-Well...
Kids, sit still and put on your belts.
-See anything?
-No.
-Let's go.
-Come on, up.
Come on.
Up you go.
You'll go crazy.
Go for it.
Let's go.
Light the fireplace
and find something to drink.
-I'll see what I can find.
-Okay.
Hungry, boy?
You're so good, you know?
Take care of them, okay?
We want five more grams.
-Sit down. Want a beer?
-No, we're in a hurry.
Right now I've got nothing on me.
-Let me call Kevin.
-No way we're waiting for Kevin.
No way you're leaving
until Kevin gets here, okay?
Fuck.
What's he doing?
Nacho?
Bro, what are you doing?
He looks scared, buddy.
From the party the other day.
What the fuck are they doing here?
Merry Christmas.
Here.
They're Danish. The fridge is off,
but they're cold anyway.
-Tell them to go right now.
-Why? Relax. One for the road.
No. They leave now!
Either they go or I will.
The other day you were more fun.
Alberto, you're an idiot.
I told you it was a bad idea.
No, we turned up too early.
-What the fuck is going on?
-Shut up! This isn't about you.
CIVIL GUARD
JUDICIAL POLICE
She's your friend, right?
What the fuck is that?
You know what, Greta? I trust no one.
So I followed you.
I saw you go
to your buddy's house, the cop.
Your buddy is a fucking narcotics cop!
That's impossible.
So it's a fucking hoax
that we set up, right?
It makes no... It doesn't make sense.
Look, hon.
I asked around.
Turns out you're David's kid sister,
who happens to move a ton of weed.
Did he send you here?
No.
-He wouldn't do that.
-Don't lie!
He wouldn't do that.
I think your big brother
sent you here so we'd be buddies,
and when we had a big shipment,
he'd call the cops and we'd get stung.
Crazy.
Wait, what if it was a trap?
What if she wanted to get close
so you'd talk about these guys?
Do you have a lot of clients?
Or about David?
Brothers and sisters?
Fuck, that's fucking gross!
-Look, let's go.
-Not until we clear this up.
Think about it, Kevin.
What if the cop followed us here?
What if she's outside now waiting for us?
How much of a stash have you got in here?
That's right. Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have told them.
Forgive me?
You look gorgeous in those pajamas.
Fucking hell.
-What the hell are you doing there?
-Fuck, it was looking so good.
-I told you to go.
-Wipe that shit right now.
Nata,
you could be a porn star.
Christian, stop. This wasn't the plan.
-What?
-Alberto, are you an idiot?
She's going to love it.
What?
Yeah.
He wants to too.
Alberto?
Nata.
Nata, look at me.
Do you want us to bring you
a bottle of white wine? You like that.
Want a joint? It's this weed
that gets girls horny.
Come on, Nata.
We're not savages, goddammit.
We just want you to enjoy yourself.
Fuck. The police!
-Shit.
-Let's go.
Alberto, snap out of it.
Please, Nata. I'm so sorry, okay?
Get your things. We have to go.
Hey, I'm sorry.
We have to go. Nata, get your things!
Nata, move!
Let's go!
Move!
Let's go, Nata.
Come on, Nata! Let's go!
You have to tell your brother.
You need to tell him now.
Shit!
Greta, the bus!
Come on, Greta!
No!
Please, sir, open up!
Hang on.
Greta, everything's all right, okay?
It's okay, all right? Don't worry.
Get on.
There.
I love you.
Shit!
Pick up.
MOM - INCOMING CALL
MOM - MISSED CALL
Do you want to wait for her?
No, she's not coming.
WE WANT TO BE FREE
AMBULANCE