Today we sing together ...
... Life and premature death
of 'one great legend.
Relax, enjoy your calorie
popcorn and other snacks ...
... We will tell you it amazing
story of a hero ...
... Still on his own story
to start.
Charlie hit the slow lazy butcher.
Guys, we start at 'the beginning:
The curtain rises.
There is "one threat in the air.
In her room to the princess
itself from 't live rob:
Better food for the worms
than to live without love.
She reaches for the cup of poison.
Meanwhile the evil preys Malvolio
on the throne ...
... While her father
seriously ill.
Yes, I am seriously ill.
Hear Who's there?
I got it, the long-awaited hero ...
... That his sensitive tar lady junk
from evil.
Let her go
or taste the bitter sting of my revenge.
The sting of my ...
Doctor Marx
I get no response.
Is not this discussed?
Acting is reacting.
Victor, you're so stiff.
Mr. Timms? You did it well.
Maybe too good.
What? My one-dimensional character?
Absurd.
I know who I am.
I am the protagonist, the hero.
Each story has one required.
And who more appropriate to get
let by praising his comrades?
The stage awaits. The public
longs for adventure.
Who am I?
I can be whoever I want.
The captain who returns
After a long journey ...
... For its mechanical arm to pick.
Whether the villainous anthropologist
against pythons fighting in Congo.
Occasionally, Chongo.
And if you want romance ...
... I am the best lover in the world.
Hola.
I noticed that you noticed
you struck me.
The females find me
too attractive.
But you like it not to touch.
Stop. No, really.
Well, here we go. What are you doing?
That tickles. Are they real?
Of course. Conflict. You were right.
I was one-dimensional.
Suddenly I see to light: the hero
can not exist in 'n vacuum.
An abrupt event is needed ...
... To the hero in the story to swing.
Mr. Timms?
Oye.
Exactly. You.
Not so shy. Come on.
Nothing wrong.
Exactly. Closer.
Nice.
I do not bite.
Can you help me?
Are you okay?
I have to go across.
Across ...
Well you have just crossed the road?
Hence the ...
Why did you do that?
-That's my mission. He's waiting for me.
Who?
The Spirit of the West,  amigo.
He drives a coach alabaster,
gold protected by guards.
What are you talking about?
Lighting. We can not do without.
That delusion of your
has destroyed my life.
I had a large network of cultured
friends. I was very popular.
Friends? I see no friends.
-Well, the ...
You're a lonely lizard.
Help me up. I'll help you
to find what you want.
Really?
Hup-. I must return to my mission.
Did you like this then before?
-Yes, often.
Come on. Good. Pull my finger.
The Spirit is waiting for me.
That will not work.
-I have to go across.
Why do not you wait
until there is no traffic?
Not that simple.
It's a metaphor.
Another one.
I knew it.
Help,  amigo
The metaphor has ruptured my spleen.
The road to knowledge is full of pitfalls.
Yes. I seek only
towards the water.
If you want to find water,
you must look for Dirt.
Dirt.
Fate is your good mood.
Tomorrow is Wednesday.
Then comes the water.
At noon, the villagers
together for 's ritual.
A village? With real people and stuff?
Where?
-On one day trips. Follow your shadow.
Do you want me walking in the desert?
That is the side-on.
According to you there is a village.
A real village, not a metaphorical village.
Go ahead. It's okay.
Well, I'm going.
I now turn off the road.
I walk into the desert.
Alone.
-Everyone follows his own path.
See you on the other side.
welcome, amigo
in this bone-dry land
Grim Reaper's his shadow
in this burning sand
his courage is praised
In this wonderful song
but mark my words
because he does not live long
his sun-bleached bones
burns to his intestines grit
Look, that bird eagerly picks
el señor  in his crotch
Here in the Mojave have animals
millions of years had the time ...
... To adapt
the circumstances.
But the lizard ...
That is it.
87 years ago, the founders ...
Do not move.
-I 'm not.
I do not move.
-Try not to notice.
Unnoticed? Why?
Not fall.
What do you mean?
Too late.
I fall-if not more.
Hey, easy. What are you doing?
Tranquilo.
Stand still.
Try not to notice.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm not into.
-Do that somewhere else.
Lead me down.
-Come first-served.
It is art.
-Find your own shelter.
This is fine.
-Here she comes. Run,  mojitos.
Do not move, you said.
-That was before. Now you run.
Adios, amigo.
Hey, beak.
Grumpy.
Do not. I'm afraid of heights.
My glands swell up.
Please, no ...
Madre de Dios.
You. I kill you.
Stupid lizard. Get it.
I squeeze your huevos   nice.
-Bird.
Wait. Come back.
It was just a joke.
Are not we friends?
-I do not know you.
Find your own place.
-We are family.
Come first served basis.
-Then you can kiss my sister.
Dirty, dirty ...
Where are your friends now,  amigo
Help.
Get your slimy branches
of my boots.
I got a bullet for you,
stranger. Get up.
Or do you head back
puzzle together?
No, ma'am.
Who are you?
-Who am I?
I ask the questions. Our village dries out.
But someone dumps water in the desert.
And I want to know what your role in it.
Role?
-What are you doing?
I'm glad you asked. Two one-act plays,
a mystery and a musical.
The melody goes like this:
It is' n Western.
I have an aunt in Morocco
and coming, hip, hi
You come not from around, huh?
It's not finished yet.
What's yours?
Boontje.
-Funny name.
My dad was fond of beans.
Fortunately, not asparagus.
Why?
-I love puttanesca.
As a child you're not happy if you're so hot.
-He was a great man.
Though he was fond of legumes.
-Spicy.
You eat on its axis.
Do you have his remains with you?
-Z 's axis. He smoked like.
They never found him.
Fixed-express.
What do you mean?
-Nothing.
He never went to the mine shaft.
He drank all 's not months.
Your insinuation that he took his parental duty
failed,'s a insult to ...
Miss Bean?
... And if those guys from Andromeda 5
bring him back ...
... Do not I sell my ranch.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
What I do?
-You hugging me.
You were petrified.
Wind down.
You said nothing.
-A defense.
That many lizards.
-That you make up.
Want dying here or you want a ride?
-No, no. Yes, please.
It's Wednesday.
Then it all happens.
Who are you?
-I have many names:
Stage name, pen name, avatar.
I got a pseudonym had ...
How to find the stranger,
looking for companionship ...
... The woman who,
like the ancient Greek Sirens ...
... Attracted to his certain doom.
... And I am one of the few men
with 's maiden name.
Here we are.
Exactly. Well ...
Very kind of you and if there ever ...
-Hortsik.
All right.
Goodbye, Boontje.
WELCOME IN DIRT
Leaving you, Jim?
-We did our best.
The tent is sold.
Without water, nothing grows.
What is that?
Why did they do?
You look-out crazy.
You look crazy out there.
-What a crazy shirt.
Crazy dress.
Mad-Eye.
Funny face.
You're a stranger.
Who love it here not long in coming.
Your beans, Boontje.
-And I need food, Willie.
You owe me for three quarts.
No more credit.
For 12 hours I have.
It is because Mr. Merrimack, from
the bank. He does not take out loans.
You know that guy over there?
Oh, yes. Try not to notice.
Can I have a glass of water?
He wants a glass of water.
Give him a double.
-Give him the spittoon.
Cactussap. We do.
Hey, fruitdruifje. You're
pretty far from home, huh?
Who are you?
Who am I?
I can be who I want.
MADE IN DURANGO
What is it? Do you miss the mangoes
of your mommy?
That's right, yes.
But not so bad
if your dad's cooking.
And where did you come from?
I? I come from the West.
Beyond the Horizon.
Beyond the sunset.
The Far West.
That's right,  hombres.
All before breakfast we make
someone off the appetite.
Salt and pepper
and smothered in clarified butter.
And then we eat him.
Do you eat him?
-I said.
I have seen things which a man
incontinent of hitting.
Just you go three days
in 'n cadaver sitting.
That changes you. Absolutely.
There are a couple more aces in this game.
Just my style.
No, my nagging, furry friend.
I'm not from this neighborhood.
I'm home where troubles are on the brink
and where I can make fuss.
I am actually a piece of fuss.
The name is ...
... Rango.
Do you have the Jenkins brothers diverted?
With a bullet.
Yolk not get them.
All seven?
That's right.
All seven.
What have you done exactly that,
Mr. Rango?
I'm glad you asked me.
And I like to tell.
But attention, please.
For now, the ...
... Complicated.
Your account has been lifted:
and two sips' n sip.
Stay away, Mordecai.
So much of your scholarship.
I have no choice, Boontje.
In these difficult times we can
no credit anymore.
This is a bank.
Here you store the water.
Boontje. You're like a cousin to me
since your father ...
... Not drunk in the shaft
dropped.
I protected from you and others
certain facts.
But it is getting worse ...
-Mr Merrimack?
Are you okay?
Bean, I want to show you something.
Is that all there is?
-And this is the stock.
On Wednesday there will be no more
a deposit.
If I get no water, I reach for my ranch
lost. Is this all there is?
That is not to me. Listen.
Someone dumps water in the desert.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Water in the desert? Was that
during one of your special moments?
We can all dream,
but this is reality.
Why do you think so many people
the tent sale?
What should I do?
We can work with the Mayor
talk. It helps in time of crisis.
The mayor?
-Maybe he is our only hope.
The ball bounced through the shovel
to number three, the roof fell in ...
... With the ethanol in flames flew ...
... And only show a charred body
and show a high-pitched noise remained.
That was six.
What has happened with number seven?
Number seven? Donders
who died of an infection.
Seven men.
-A ball.
A tour of the whole place.
Dance for me, soepkip.
Put a chicken dance.
Dance.
-Si, baila, baila.
Are you deaf? If your loan
not pays off, the country is not yours.
So it is with real estate.
Quid pro-quo.
When I see your face here again,
I cut it off ...
... And I wipe it off my crotch.
-Beware of the bill.
And do not return.
What are you crouching?
Bad Bill, I must tell you something.
What is this?
-You know who that is? That is Rango.
Yes, he is not afraid of you.
For anyone not.
He has the Jenkins brothers killed.
-With a bullet.
All seven.
Oh yeah?
Come here ...
Just wait. Here.
I suppose that's just go for you.
So. That's better.
Time out, hold on.
Listen. I give you another chance
to reconsider.
If you do not want to think ...
... I think about it myself
for me to imagine.
Exactly what I meant.
Listen. Everything is different,
Rango now in town.
New rules: I want my shoes?
and cleaned my coffee hot.
And whatever you do: look at me.
Stay out of my sight.
Rango.
-What does he do?
Who is not afraid.
He reads the lesson that bird.
Pull over if I can find.
I do not want in your
body fluids on my boots.
But violence is not necessary ...
... As long as we work together,
as a team.
So come out and form a glance,
I will take a break.
What is he doing now?
-A big message, I think.
Never mind.
Come take a look.
Look.
He is the hawk-chase.
Give it swallows the bait.
Did you know?
-He finished it.
What do you think, Doc?
-This hawk is dead.
Which may be in the soup.
And with a bullet.
-Just as he said.
A hero.
This four-not between shelves.
Time he met the mayor.
-You will meet the mayor.
Three cheers for Rango.
And as late as the alien is
by praising his new friends ...
... And he sinks deeper
the guacamole from his self-deception.
When is he coming?
-Quick,  compadre.  fast.
My country is not for sale.
I came to save my country, not sell.
-We will arrange something.
If you just talk to us.
Bean, where are you going?
The mayor can see you now.
Water, Mr. Rango. Water.
Without water
there's only dust and decay.
But with water ...
... There is life.
Look. So like they live.
They follow it everywhere.
The iron law of the desert:
Who is in charge of the water
over all the boss.
This is from my private stock.
Rainwater from the great flood.
Not that of Noah,
am I so old it does not.
Power has its advantages.
-That's right, boy.
But it also includes
responsibilities.
I was already mayor
Dirt existed before.
I am a sentimental turtle ...
... But I see a future
for this village. With you there, I hope.
On Dirt.
-Exactly.
You see them, Mr. Rango?
All my friends and neighbors?
Life here is hard. Very hard.
You know how they talking every day
still insist?
They believe it is better.
They believe that water will come.
They believe against all odds
that it will be better tomorrow than today.
People need to believe in something.
And now they believe in you.
Help yourself, Mr. Rango.
Your destiny awaits.
People need to believe in something.
This is not right.
Only the mayor
is not affected by the drought.
Do you have no suspicion?
And that water in the desert?
I have seen them.
Hits the lot is not. I examine it.
If you think there is
of a conspiracy ...
... Talk to the new sheriff.
Excuse me, Mr. Rango.
I bang that ugly sneer on your head.
-I want ...
You want 's comment.
-I do not come for fun.
There's a bullet into.
-I know of the party.
Hence new garb.
-I want a complaint ...
You too?
-Do a search ...
If you would do your best,
you were quite handsome.
To school, eat your vegetables
and read Shakespeare.
Who is Shakespeare?
Sheriff-Rango. If you're really hot.
I try to save my ranch, while
Here you doing with that hand clap lellebel.
Sad child, eh? Such a crowd.
Why does she do that?
It's a survival tactic.
-The button is broken.
Difficult.
It is not rash.
It's a birthmark.
I've done it again, eh?
-What?
Has anyone told you
what happened with the previous sheriff?
May I ask you ...
Sorry, may I ask ... The previous sheriff.
Where is everyone going?
Fine folk dance.
I still need to practice.
Is this normal here?
-Every Wednesday. Dry and secure.
You have slain bird.
-Yes. That's right, yes.
Dead bird. Hose.
Snake?
Rattlesnake-January, he means.
Who was afraid of that hawk.
Maybe he is now.
Can I have your boots when you're dead?
I'm not afraid of Rattlesnake January
-It also said Amos.
Amos?
Do you have gold fillings?
Citizens of Dirt.
Welcome to the big day
for your redemption. Hallelujah.
Disciples, like the holy tap ready.
We have a newcomer
among us, friends.
I do not need to imagine.
So thorough was his first appearance.
Mr. Rango, you come forward?
Give.
-From me.
The time has come, friends.
The moment was predicted.
The sacred moment.
The moment of our destiny.
The moment of our salvation.
This is the moment of hydration.
His guilt.
On-the stake.
He's a devil.
-I get his boots.
Friends, temper your frustrations.
We are hard times ahead.
We must sacrifice.
But if I can help, my door is ...
Wait. This whole thing
stinks three hours in the wind.
First, the bank dry
and now that tap.
Is the bank dry?
In its
the bank has no water.
I want my cash.
We can not give away anything.
-Lift crane my current bill.
No civil disobedience
in my village.
Glad you're here.
The case got out of hand.
Yeah, come on.
A look at the source
of discontent.
Listen, everybody. I've been thinking.
And I've discovered something:
You have 's water problems.
Pay attention. I put something out.
Suppose this guy here 'n sip of water
takes. Small sip, nothing wrong.
And you. Parched
like a rabbit in the desert in July.
So you take it fast 'n sip or two.
Remain vigilant.
What happens then, do you think?
Then everyone takes a sip.
Then the water would soon run out.
Where are we?
Then we thirsty. Very thirsty.
Then we meet
like a set of creatures to attack.
Look. We have
six days before water ...
We have five days ...
As long as we have water,
we have a village.
Sheriff Rango's right.
Until we have water, there is hope.
Believe me:
From now I spend all my time ...
... Aan 't protect
of our precious resources.
Rango and no one pulls a tango.
Good evening, ladies.
Let me see thee no more.
-Wait, Gordy.
Go back and stand up for your rights.
The people here are surprisingly friendly.
What? Not you again.
Mistake.
This is the bank.
-I said, Jedidiah.
Wait.
-It is the sheriff.
Hands where I can see.
Just what I thought, looking for gold
approved without tools.
Gold panning?
Shovel, pickaxe, aspirin,
puzzle books ...
Now one license.
Ezekiel, Jedidiah.
Donders, what's going on?
I have had polyps
smarter than you.
This is not the bank.
-Pappy, the sheriff is here.
He helps us.
-With 's license to look for gold.
Right. Just doing my duty.
To watch the lonely sheriff 's eagle
and outwits the villains.
Does he look like he sounds?
Suppose we find the main vein,
because we are after prospectors ...
... Where we can 't gold
then deposit?
The best financial institution
this side of the Missouri.
Monitored around the clock
by the undersigned.
Thank you.
The bank was robbed.
My goodness, the bank is robbed.
What is it?
-The water is gone.
What did he say?
-The bank is robbed.
Doctor Marx, I am on fire.
Embrace me.
the bank is robbed
The city is dry
the people trodden
the need is high
He has not fulfilled his duty
all the water, it is his fault
Backward. This is now 'one crime scene.
Turn off the area,
looking prints, fibers and DNA.
Take urine samples and get coffee.
And those two are not interchangeable.
Gold Search license.
-Here. That is evidence.
What now?
-We have water.
We're all going to.
-We know what to do.
Right. We all know
what to do.
Namely?
Form an opossum.
Form a posse.
We do this in an orderly manner.
Is there someone here
who can handle a firearm?
Good.
What do we do now, Sheriff?
Now we ride.
Where are we going?
As my deputy
you go looking for the crooks.
Using your eyes seeing red skin.
Which way did they go?
Want to show a bison chat?
You're good.
I'm counting on you, Spoons.
There's some tobacco in your beard.
Always good to show a doctor purchasing.
Reptiles support each other, eh?
I am an amphibian.
-Nobody is perfect.
Are you sure that you see there?
You have a little thing in your eye.
That is conjunctivitis.
It's in the family.
Fortunately it is not contagious.
Tito  Momen,   a posse
s not like a ...
Never mind.
No, little girl. Someone needs
watch over the village while I'm gone.
Can I have one in his pin shooting?
-We're still here.
Sheriff, you bring back the water. Right?
-There you can count on.
Which way we go?
-There are tunnels everywhere.
The village abound.
How they bank
Found it?
At the lesson continued, gentlemen.
Sheriff, here.
Look.
Whether you are the face of God sees.
-Amen.
Every Wednesday he water.
Golden-years.
But why now?
Whatever the reason is,
someone has mastered the water.
What do you think, sheriff?
The thieves came from this direction.
We traced the line to go to the start point
and to keep the rabble.
What did he say?
-Take the lead.
Follow the lead, he said.
Whatever you do ...
Do not look down.
What is this here?
A-aquifer.
What is an aquifer?
-Well, for aqua.
Now he is otherwise empty.
That is a lot.
That was it.
Here, it stops.
Something or someone is messing around
with our water supply.
That leadership has to do.
We searched the bank robbers, right?
That's a very different approach.
Keep your door or I put you somewhere.
Quiet, brutes.
So I can not think.
I got it.
Make the torches.
Good idea.
Slim-conceived, dude.
Climbing.
-Get your foot out of my face.
Not bad, huh?
-Your brain is becoming overheated.
If you're on a roll ...
Hot.
All they needed
had some water.
One dried cactus. Bad sign.
Look.
I saw it first.
Water.
Enter.
He's empty.
-I knew that.
Where did you find?
Sheriff, you gotta see.
Mr. Merrimack, from the bank.
What is he doing here?
-Reverse.
Let me there.
-He was shot in his back.
This man is not shot.
He drowned.
Drowned?
-In the desert?
What an ending.
Whose tracks are those?
Interesting. The ground is still wet.
-We should bury him.
Birds also need to eat.
-Circle of life.
What does the damn Indians?
You see the ghosts, I see.
I'm in the moult. That means
I'm ready to mate.
I'll remember.
Prickly pear.
The ancient prickly pear. This
you bring your food to taste.
Also a natural laxative.
I got a trace.
Three men, to go to the west.
One blind, one with an enlargement
prostate, driving in the amazonezit.
What did he say?
They drive-in amazonezit.
We whisper.
-Thermostat Problems.
Who would need a little research?
Embarrassing.
What exactly are we doing?
Now we ride.
That means we now ride.
At this time.
I think of marshmallows at camp
with my dad. I ate them all night.
Before breakfast
I had to regurgitate them.
I've been my whole dalmatian
vomited.
That's nothing. I have a whole tribe of pygmies.
Who looked at me so strangely.
-I remember. Those were very nice.
I once 'n human spine
in my stool.
Let yourself explore.
Can I use the beans, bean?
Sheriff?
Mr. Rango, tell me
the Spirit of the West.
Tell me.
-Is it true what they say?
Yes, the Spirit of the West.
The eternally unattainable ideal.
He drives a coach alabaster,
gold protected by guards.
He appears to those
that 's quest over with.
And reached the other side.
The other side of what?
-It is a metaphor.
My eye.
-That it heals.
Sheriff, what are you doing
Rattlesnake in January?
What? Where?
Your paths
has already been crossed.
Oh yes. January My brother, you mean.
Your brother?
-I said.
But he's a snake
and you're a lizard.
Mommy regularly.
Has he ever bitten you?
-Sure. Look.
It's okay to feel here.
-Interesting. A navel.
I'm immune to its poison.
It gives my coffee 'n  bite.
Is it true that he is afraid of hawks?
-That is its natural enemy.
Of that snake to my feathers
upright.
I do not sleep.
-No worries.
We find the water
and get home a hero reception.
Before we go to sleep, I
we hold hands ...
... For the Spirit of 'the West
thanks.
Good idea.
I'm not always correct
you've been to.
But tonight, thank you
Sheriff Rango you gave us.
We lead a hard life.
Sometimes I do not know how to save.
Rango but gives me hope
that we succeed.
You have sent us a hero.
Glad to be back on someone
be believed.
Thank you, Spirit of the West. Amen.
Just testing.
It's a cold night.
Do you ever
they look at you?
That is the Spanish Bayonet. We call
him the Wandering Cactus.
Walking?
According to legend, he seeks water.
As a girl I held them in the eye
to see if they moved.
I thought she was me
would lead to an oasis.
A place where enough water was
for everyone.
Night long I kept an eye on them.
But I never saw them move.
But you still look.
Who would not like an oasis?
We find the water is.
I promise you.
What a lonely sound.
Have you ever been lonely?
-Sometimes.
I believe nothing. You're a charmer.
Everybody likes you.
I found quite difficult to make friends.
We sit there isolated on the ranch.
As if you show a box is.
I never met many people.
Anything I can imagine.
Is there someone special in your life?
-I used to.
She could not keep her head.
Now I walk too much danger.
Life is lonely on the prairie.
At a gallop over the plain and all.
Bean?
I vil you alive.
-It was my fault.
Temper.
Difficult-family. Intervention is necessary.
What is that?
It is the water.
I have a plan.
And we all have a role.
What do I do?
-The most important task.
You stay here and if something goes wrong,
you give us the sign.
What size is that dress?
He has it.
He has the water.
-You did.
Well ...
-Why are not you as smart?
I gotta tell you something.
-Quiet. There comes one.
Value gentlemen. I wish you,
you and you have a good day.
This is Madame LuPone's junk
touring  thespiënnes.
What is that?
-Thespiënnes.
It is illegal in seven states.
The curtain rises: the princess
wants from her life on rob:
I yearn for love.
A sentinel surveillance
the castle gate.
Hear Who's there?
Predictable.
-Quiet. My favorite piece.
Under trumpet
her father arrives.
Touched by Cupid.
Please, my beautiful daughter,
and insert ...
Text?
-Put your hands up.
What was that?
Certainly, participatory theater.
You're surrounded.
So the whole family: hands up.
My whole family?
barley with snot and kale
intestine stew, pus bowl
Grandma's bone in polecat blood
cheese toes and clubfoot
We have a full house.
So that is a
old-fashioned showdown.
This is not our whole force.
What does that mean?
-That is the sign.
The sign. Something went wrong.
Should something happen now?
Ideas are welcome.
Run.
Jump on the wagon.
Are we going to throw down, guys?
Delicious, if they flee.
-Maybelle, but screaming.
We escaped.
The public-lived it.
Yes. Bunch of inbreeding.
Bats Invasion.
Then you can drive.
Tonight we're having soup.
-Come on, eropaf.
Not on the water shoot.
Jedidiah. Time for the Alabama-squeezebox.
-All right, Dad.
I sense some hostility.
-From below.
Throw your lasso to that pig.
Let's escape.
Valve-closed and shooting.
Where's the sheriff?
One-appointment.
Boseefus, they let their lust.
What was that? Check it out.
What is it? A problem?
You might say.
Headache.
Was that all?
It was not unpleasant.
Suit.
Here, hold on.
Get off me.
Jump.
It is impossible.
This can not. It is empty.
There is no water.
No water?
-Where we fought for?
You have the means of our existence
squandered.
In that Sunday dress is the sheriff.
Of the gold-seeking authorization?
The what?
-Irrelevant. Astray.
I love you for 'one bank robbery ...
... And the murder of John
Merrimack Joe or Fluffy.
We have not killed anybody.
The safe was empty.
The bank had been robbed.
How do you then that bottle?
-Found in the desert.
Why did you bring him over here?
Wait. So the bottle was empty
when you found him?
Right.
-I believe in nothing.
We hang them up.
Who dumps water in the desert?
That's not for the first time.
It's a puzzle. A  sodejudoku.
What's going on?
-I do not know.
I go to the hole
this enigma.
You go with me.
They're coming.
There they are.
They are the thieves.
Where's the water?
There was no water.
Where is he going?
To the Mayor.
There he established happy with it, eh?
-Nice hit, boss.
Interesting.
Apologies for the shoes, Mr. Rango.
This game requires a certain predetermined etiquette.
And I'm a stickler-precise.
Nice. I have some questions
and I have my own etiquette.
Why would you dump water
in the desert?
However naive bank robbers
their word for it.
If they are suspended
is your job done.
Bravo.
-Good work.
Suppose that the bank had already robbed?
Who will?
-I was hoping you could tell me.
That sounds almost like an accusation.
-Take it as you want.
Something that you said keeps
rattling in my frontal lobe.
What then?
Who is in charge of the water
over all the boss.
Come on, Mr. Rango.
You close to me divine powers.
Why I am the boss
the water?
You clearly have this game in the fingers.
-I play it for many years.
I had been here before
The highway was.
I saw progress and I have
a few things from her classes.
Check it out
from 's broader perspective.
Understand the movements
of history.
Look, kid.
You can almost see how the time goes by.
What you build there?
-The future, Mr. Rango. The future.
Soon it all fades
to show a myth:
The Wild West town, the sheriff,
the gunslinger.
There is no place for it.
Now we are civilized.
Correct, civilized.
That is the future. Join us,
or stay longer in the past.
Mr. Merrimack was sometimes
longer in the past?
Beware, Mr. Rango. You forget
but you're a lizard.
You forget apparently
that I represent the law.
Our new sheriff has come to believe themselves
in his hero.
Rattlesnake come late January.
January is the angel of death.
Wherever he goes, fall thaw.
Do it.
Sit still. You have to look presentable
when it pops its clogs.
ha llegado la muerte
death is coming
Dónde estan between huevos
our hero goes about it now?
The mayor has been the land
bought in the valley. Except for your country.
Why? Without water
country is useless.
Unless he has power over the water.
If the bladder of a monkey.
Once the land is his,
there will be water.
How does he do that?
Sheriff, we have a problem.
Wait, Boontje. It is not necessary.
Hang him upside down to see blue.
-Hang on.
Calm. Let me talk.
They paid the price.
-Calm down, everyone. Come on.
Here with them, then we emasculate them.
You too, Spoons?
They've stolen water.
Everything we had.
Here, nobody hung.
-It is his fault.
You would the water back.
Without water there is no hope.
-Nothing more to believe.
See that sign there?
As long as 'Sheriff' state,
the laws are respected.
In a lawless situation ...
Think about it.
It begins slowly,
like a fungus.
An insult. Allegations.
And soon we eat our children ...
... And get cats and dogs
together the craziest mutants.
Looking for something to believe
Spoons?
Believe in me.
Believe in that sign there.
As long as it hangs there,
We have hope.
Hello, brother.
Thirsty?
That was long ago, brother.
How are you?
-Oh, you know ...
You have all the brothers Jenkins
deflected, I hear.
With a bullet, eh?
Is not that right?
The good people here
believe those stories of yours, huh?
They think
you're a tough killer.
These people trust you.
They think
that you are going to save their village.
They think you are going to save their souls.
But we know better.
Right?
Let your friends to see
how brave you are.
Let me see your true nature.
Pull out your revolver and shoot me dead.
You do not need all.
Just one, huh?
Come on, hero.
Pull the trigger on it.
Do you have the look of a killer, boy?
I see nothing.
It was bragging, right? You
The Jenkins brothers are not diverted.
You will not even get out to the West.
Or does it?
Come on.
Harder. Your friends here
have not heard.
You've just lied to them.
You're a crook and a coward.
Is not that right?
Harder.
Listen well, dirty liar.
This is my village.
If I see you again,
I send your soul straight to hell.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am nobody.
Golden guards.
The alabaster coach.
The Spirit of the West.
Excuse me ...
Mr. Ghost ... Sir?
That's a good one. Sometimes you
dig deep to find what you want.
So you did it.
Is this heaven?
If so, we ate
a biscuit with Kim Novak.
Absolutely.
What are you doing here?
-I am looking. Like you.
I do not even remember what I seek.
I do not remember who I am.
They called the man without a name.
Now they have
a name for everything.
No matter how you call.
No words but deeds.
My actions make everything worse.
I'm a crook.
My friends believed in me,
but they have a hero is needed.
Then be a hero.
-No, you do not understand.
I would not be here.
That's right.
You come from far
looking for something that is not here.
Do not you understand?
It's not about you.
It's about them.
But return is impossible.
-You have no choice.
Nobody can run away
from his own story.
So you did it.
Yes,  amigo.
The other side of the road.
Did you just now?
We see what we have to see.
Is not it beautiful?
Yes, indeed.
Come on, buddy. I want to show you something.
Years ago there was  agua
in this whole valley.
Now there remains only one question:
Where did it go?
They follow the water.
They follow the water. Come on.
That is nonsense.
Without water, the land useless.
What you build there?
The future, Mr. Rango.
Join us,
or stay longer in the past.
I was here
Before the highway came.
I saw progress and I have
a few things from her classes.
Who is in charge of the water
over all the boss.
Come on, Mr. Rango.
You close to my divine powers.
Why I am the boss
the water?
EMERGENCY VALVE
What now,  amigo
Nobody can run away
from his own story.
I go back.
But why?
Because I'm like this.
You dare do, Sheriff. What do you want?
Pappy and the boys
innocent are hung.
But I have a plan.
I know how difficult this is for you,
Boontje. But is it right decision.
Decisions, decisions.
It is not necessary
to suffer any longer.
The family ranch is now a wasteland.
Sign the deed. Then you are freed
the burden of your father.
My father was not affected.
Keep your blood money. I love my country.
In all hell fire.
Do what he says ...
... If I press those beautiful brown eyes
out of your skull.
Wait. You do not ...
-Let me do my job.
You have brought me there.
Now we 't limit.
Ticks rotakte, woman.
-Go to hell.
Where do I come, you think?
Look at me.
I want to die.
I dare you.
This day is
still a lot more interesting.
Put her down.
Or else, kid? Let me finish?
That's the bottom line, yes.
Keep your dirty paws home.
Closed-right gear.
All right, Sheriff.
Let's see something.
Now,  amigos.
Draw.
That was a bad idea.
Thirst, brother?
Here it comes.
It's a miracle.
-Beware.
Look.
-What is that?
That is our salvation, Dad.
We escape, boys.
We break out.
I shoot so many holes in your
that your bowels leak lead.
Then it is good
I still have troops.
That's no hawk.
Those are just bats.
Stick to the plan.
Let him shoot the gun empty.
A bullet is enough.
-That you dare not.
Try it.
Mr. Rango. Are you forgetting something?
Give me your weapon, sheriff.
Nu, Mr Range.
Hold on. No worries, I have a plan.
Help. Open the door.
Good. Plan B.
Clearer talk.
All my problems solved.
Except one.
There is no place
for gunfighters, January
We are now businessmen.
With new-hats.
Where I come from,
we call this improvisation.
You're back.
What was that?
Do not panic. You have plan B swallowed.
Time to panic.
You and the sheriff are the same:
you guys are legends.
Soon no one believes
that you existed.
One last shot
the last bandit to kill.
Is that just beautiful.
If we work together ...
... We stuck 's good solution
for this situation.
You must consult with him.
A bullet.
Respect from one legend
for another.
What did you say?
Soon no one believes
that you existed.
The water is back.
As you promised.
You're a hero.
If you're a hero, then ...
-Not spoil it.
I do not know what you do,
but I'll take one dive.
That 's the end of the journey
of the lizard.
Van't simple beginning
to the legend that we now sing.
And even though he once dead,
who knows by 's accident at home ...
... As in 65% of all unnatural
deaths ...
... Yet the inhabitants of the name
continue to remember their savior ...
Nani Resdi