(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Rango!
♪ Rango
♪ Rango ♪
We are gathered here today
to immortalize in song
the life and untimely
death of a great legend.
Rango...
So sit back, relax,
low-calorie popcorn
and assorted confections
and enjoy your
while we tell you the
strange and bewildering
tale of a hero
who has yet to
enter his own story.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(VOCALIZING)
Crunchy, creamy, cookie,
candy, cupcake.
from the top.
Okay, everybody,
let's take it
The stage is set,
the night moist
with apprehension.
Alone in her chamber,
the princess prepares
to take her own life.
"It is far better
to nourish worms
RANGO: (AS PRINCESS)
"than to live
without love."
(AS HIMSELF)
She reaches for
the poisoned chalice.
Meanwhile,
the wicked Malvolio
to the throne
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
plots his ascension
while her aging father
lies gravely ill.
(AS PRINCESS' FATHER)
"Yes, I am gravely ill."
"Hark, who goes there?"
'Tis I, the much-
anticipated hero,
returning to rescue
his emotionally
unstable maiden!
Unhand her,
you jailers of virtue,
or taste the bitter sting
of my vengeance!
The sting of my...
Dr. Marx?
Dr. Marx,
I'm not getting
anything from you.
(SIGHING IN EXASPERATION)
People, we've
talked about this.
Acting is reacting.
Victor, you were wooden!
There, I said it.
Mr. Timms?
You were good.
Perhaps a little too good.
What's that, Victor?
My character's undefined?
That's absurd.
I know who I am.
I'm the guy,
the protagonist, the hero.
Every story needs a hero.
I mean, who else
is better qualified
to bask in the adulation
of his numerous companions?
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALING DEEPLY)
RANGO:
The stage is waiting.
The audience thirsts
for adventure.
Who am I?
I could be anyone.
(MIMICKING SAILOR)
I could be the sea cap'n
returning from
a mighty voyage
to reclaim his
mechanical arm!
Ow! Ow!
(WITH ENGLISH ACCENT)
Or I could be the
rogue anthropologist,
battling pythons
down in the Congo!
Down, Chongo, down!
(WITH SPANISH ACCENT)
And if you desire romance,
I will become
the greatest lover
the world has ever known!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I couldn't help but notice
you noticing me noticing you.
You know, the womens find me
uncomfortably good looking.
But you seem
remarkably at ease.
Oh, stop it.
No, really.
Well, if you must.
(GIGGLES)
What are you doing?
That tickles.
Are those real?
(GASPS) That's it!
Conflict.
Victor, you were right.
I have been undefined.
People,
I've had an epiphany.
The hero cannot
exist in a vacuum!
What our story needs is
an ironic, unexpected event
that will propel
the hero into conflict!
(CAR HONKING)
(GASPING)
(HONKING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(AVE MARIA
PLAYING)
(SPEEDING AWAY)
Mr. Timms?
Ooh...
(CREAKING)
ROADKILL:
Oye!
That's right! You!
(GASPING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Don't be shy. Come on.
It's okay.
That's it,
a little closer.
Good.
I won't bite you.
(GROANING)
I need a little help here.
Are you okay?
I must get
to the other side.
The other side?
You mean, just now,
that was you
crossing the road?
That's why the...
(MIMICKING ACCIDENT)
Why'd you do that?
This is my quest.
He waits for me.
What? Who?
The Spirit of the West,
amigo. The one.
They say he rides
an alabaster carriage
with golden guardians
to protect him.
What are you
talking about?
Enlightenment.
We are nothing without it.
Your delusional quest
just ruined my life!
Nothing?
I had an incredibly complex
social network going!
Highly sophisticated
friends!
I was very popular!
Friends? I don't
see no friends.
(STAMMERING)
You are a very
lonely lizard.
Now help me up and I will help
you find what you seek.
You will?
Quickly. I must get
back to my quest.
You mean you've
done this before?
Oh, yes. Many times.
Come, come.
That's it, pull my finger.
The Spirit is
waiting for me.
Okay, okay.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Okay. That's not
going to work.
I must get
to the other side.
Why don't you
just wait until there
are no cars coming?
It's not so easy
as it looks.
What?
Is a metaphor.
(SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Whoa!
There's another one!
I knew it.
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
You need a little
help, amigo?
I think the metaphor
broke my spleen.
The path to knowledge
is fraught with consequence.
I'm just looking
for the path to water.
If you want to find water,
you must first find Dirt.
Dirt.
(LAUGHS)
Destiny,
she is kind to you.
Tomorrow is Wednesday.
The water comes.
At noon,
the townspeople gather
for a mysterious ritual.
Oh! A town?
You mean, with real people
and everything? Where?
A day's journey.
Follow your shadow.
You want me
to just walk out
into the desert?
Mmm-hmm.
That's the way.
Okay. So you're saying
there's a town, a real town,
not a metaphor town.
Go on. It's okay.
Okay.
Well, then, I'm going.
I am leaving
the road now!
I'm walking
into the desert!
Alone!
We all have our
journeys to make!
I will see you
on the other side.
(MARIACHI BAND SINGING)
♪ Welcome, amigo
♪ To the land without end
♪ The desert and death
♪ Are the closest of friends
♪ We sing of his courage
♪ In magnificent song
♪ But pay close attention
♪ He won't be here long
♪ As the birds pluck his eyes
The sun bleaches his bones
♪ See his entrails
get scattered
♪ Watch him lose his cojones ♪
Here in the
Mojave Desert,
animals have had
millions of years
to adapt to the
harsh environment.
But the lizard?
He is going to die.
"Four score and
seven years ago,
our fathers..."
ROCK-EYE: Don't move.
What?
Don't move!
Not moving.
(SHUSHING)
(WHISPERING) Not moving.
Try to blend in.
Blend in?
What do you mean?
Blend in.
What are you saying?
(EXCLAIMING)
(HAWK SCREAMING)
Too late.
No, no. It's not too late!
I'm blending!
I'm a blender!
Hey, calm down!
What are you doing?
(EXCLAIMING)
(SCREAMING)
ROCK-EYE:
Stop moving!
Try not to look
conspicuous.
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
I'm blending.
Go blend somewhere else.
Don't distract me.
No room at the inn.
It's an art, not a science.
Find your own hiding place.
No, this is good.
(HAWK SCREAMING)
Here she comes!
You better run, Mojito!
What? I thought you
said, "Don't move."
That was before.
Now, you run.
(SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SCREECHING)
(TWIG SNAPPING)
(GULPING)
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHISTLING)
(HUMMING)
Oh, hey. Proboscis.
Testy.
(SCREECHING)
(EXCLAIMING) Ow!
Please, no, please.
I have vertigo!
My glands are swelling!
Please, no.
(SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMING IN SPANISH)
You! I'll kill you!
You stupid lizard!
Get out of there.
I'm going to strangle
your  huevos!
Big bird! Big bird!
No, wait! Come back!
I was just kidding!
Come on, we're friends, right?
I don't know you!
Lizards, frogs...
Find your own hiding place!
We're practically related!
No room at the inn!
Come on, move over!
You're not my friend!
I'll let you
kiss my sister!
(LAUGHING)
You son of a...
(HAWK SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(RATTLING)
Where are your
friends now,  amigo?
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(COUGHING)
(WATER HISSING)
(SPITTING)
Get your slimy-webbed
phalanges off my boots!
Sorry.
I got a bead on you, stranger.
So you get up real slow
lessen you want
to spend the better part
of the afternoon
putting your face
back together!
No, ma'am, I don't.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm asking
the questions here!
Our town is drying up.
We're in the middle
of a drought.
Now someone's dumping water
in the desert!
It's a puzzle of
undeterminable size
and dimension,
but I intend to find out
what role you playing
in all this.
Role?
What are you involved in?
Well, I'm glad you asked.
I've got two one-acts,
a mystery and a musical
I've been gestating.
I got the words,
I'm just working on the melody
right now. It's like a...
(HUMMING)
I think it's gonna
be a western.
♪ A monkey got a cracker
His mother was a slapper
♪ She'll be coming
'round the mountain
in the rain ♪
You ain't from around
here, are you?
I'm still working on it.
So, what's your name?
Beans.
That's a funny kind of name.
What can I say? My daddy
plumb loved baked beans.
Well, you're lucky
he didn't plumb
love asparagus.
What are you saying?
I mean, I enjoy
a hearty puttanesca myself,
but I'm not sure
that a child would
appreciate the moniker.
My daddy was a great man,
even if he did exhibit
a proclivity for legumes.
Spicy.
You're eating his ashes!
(EXCLAIMING)
You carry his remains?
He loved to smoke.
They never found the body.
No, his ashes.
Well, I'm sure
he had his reasons.
What are you implying?
Nothing.
My daddy was never near
that mine shaft.
He'd been sober
for over a month!
And for you to insinuate
that he would abandon
his parental responsibilities
at a delicate time
in my personal development
is an affront to my sense...
Miss Beans?
Miss Beans? Hello?
(WHISTLES) Hello?
(BOAR GRUNTING)
(SNIFFING)
And until the people
of Andromeda Five
return him safe and sound,
I will not sell my ranch!
What...
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
You're cuddling me.
You were frozen.
I was not.
Yes, you were.
You stopped talking.
It's a defense
mechanism.
Actually, lots of
lizards have it.
You're making that up.
So, you gonna die out here,
or you want a ride into town?
No, no, no. Yeah.
No. Yes, please.
Thank you. Sorry.
Today's Wednesday.
Wednesday's when
we all get to it.
So who are you, really?
Well, I'm a man
of many epithets.
There's my stage name,
my pen name, my avatar.
I had a pseudonym once,
but I had it legally changed.
And so the stranger,
seeking companionship,
finds the woman,
much like the sirens
of ancient times
luring him to
his certain demise.
...nom de plume,
I have a CB handle.
I'm actually one
of the few men
with a maiden name.
Whoa! Well, here we are.
Hmm?
Oh. Oh...
Right.
Well, I sure do
appreciate this,
Miss Beans,
and if there's ever
anything that I...
Get on up!
Okay, then!
See you, Beans.
(PANTING)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
You heading out, Jim?
Well, we gave it
our best shot.
We had to sell out.
Can't grow no crops
without no water.
Bye, now!
Ow!
(LAUGHING)
LUCKY: What is it?
What was that for?
You're funny looking.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're funny
looking, too.
That's a funny-looking shirt.
That's a funny-looking dress.
You got funny-looking eyes!
You got a funny-
looking face!
You're a stranger.
Strangers don't
last long here.
Here's your beans, Beans.
I'm gonna need
some more feed,
too, Willie.
Now, Beans, you owe me
three quarts already.
I can't give you more credit.
But I'll have what
I owe you at noon.
You don't understand.
It's Mr. Merrimack
down at the bank.
He cut off all credit.
Hey, Beans! Beans!
You know that
there fella?
Hey, Beans! Miss Beans!
Nope.
RANGO: Hey, Beans!
Hey.
Right. Blend in.
Yeah, blend in.
(SPITTING)
(GASPING)
(MUFFLED PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(PIANO MUSIC STOPS)
(SPOONS CLACKING)
(CREAKING)
(SNORING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
I'd like a glass
of water.
(ALL LAUGHING)
He wants a glass of water!
Make it a double!
Give him the spittoon!
Cactus juice.
That's what we got.
(EXCLAIMING)
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
(GULPS)
(GASPING)
Hey, there, fruit cup.
You're a long ways
from home, ain't ya?
Who exactly are you?
RANGO:
Who am I?
I could be anyone.
What's the matter?
You missing your
mommy's mangos?
As a matter of fact, I am.
But not as much as
your daddy's cooking!
(ALL GASPING)
Exactly where did you
say you were from?
Me? I'm from the West.
Out there,
beyond the horizon.
Past the sunset.
The Far West.
(ALL MUTTERING)
Yeah, that's right,
hombres.
The place I come from,
we kill a man
before breakfast
just to work up
an appetite.
Then we salt him,
and we pepper him.
Then we braise him
in clarified butter.
And then we eat him.
You eat him?
That's what I said!
(ALL GASPING)
Hell, I seen things
make a grown man
lose control of his
glandular functions!
You spend three days
in a horse carcass,
living off your own juices.
It'll change a man.
Oh, yeah.
Had a few extra aces
in this deck, gents.
Just the way I like it.
So, no, my hirsute
little rodent friend,
I am not from
around these parts.
You might say
I'm from everywhere
there's trouble brewing
and hell waiting
to be raised.
You might say
I'm what hell's
already raised up.
Name's
Rango.
Are you the fella
that killed them
Jenkins brothers?
Uh-huh.
Killed them
with one bullet.
Don't get no deader.
All seven of them?
That's right.
(CLEARING THROAT)
All seven of them.
Exactly how you
do that, Mr. Rango?
(CLEARING THROAT)
You know, I'm glad
you asked me that.
And I will be happy
to tell you how.
But you're all gonna
have to listen up!
Because this
is where it gets
complicated.
That'll close out
your account, Mrs. Oats,
two gulps and a swig.
Hands off, Mordecai!
That's what's left of
your college education!
I don't rightly have
no other choice, Beans.
Times being so hard,
we just can't give
no more credit.
But this here is a bank.
This is where
you keep the water.
(LAUGHING)
Beans, you've been
like a niece to me
ever since your daddy
did not fall drunk
down a mine shaft.
I've tried to protect you and
others from certain realities.
But that... Well...
(MUTTERING)
Mr. Merrimack?
Realities are bearing down.
Mr. Merrimack!
Are you all right?
Beans, I need to
show you something.
That's all that's left?
And this here
is the reserve!
I don't know if
you've noticed,
making deposits on
a Wednesday no more!
but folks just ain't
Mr. Merrimack,
if I don't get some water,
I'm gonna lose my ranch
and you're telling me
that's all that's left
in the whole town?
Now that just don't make
no sense. Now, listen.
Someone is dumping
water in the desert.
I seen it with my own eyes.
(SNORTING)
Water in the desert?
Was this during
one of your special times?
(SCOFFS) No.
Well, we can all dream,
but this is the reality.
Why do you think
so many people
are selling out?
They just can't make it.
Well, what am I
supposed to do?
Well, I suppose
we could talk to the Mayor.
I hear he's been
helping people out
in this time of crisis.
The Mayor?
He may be our only hope.
Bullet hits a shovel,
ricochets back
towards number three,
and that's when
the roof caved in,
igniting the thermos
of pure grain alcohol
instantly vaporizing
his bodily form,
leaving nothing but
a charcoal statue
and a high-pitched squeal.
(MIMICKING SQUEAL)
ALL: Oh!
Hold on, there.
That's only six.
What happened
to number seven?
Number seven?
Hell, he died of infection.
(ALL CHEERING)
Seven men!
One bullet!
Drinks all around!
(GUN FIRES)
Dance for me, Sod Buster!
Yes, dance like a chicken!
That's right! Dance!
You got corn in
your ears, mate?
You don't pay the mortgage,
you don't own the land!
That's basic real
estate law, my friend.
Quid pro quo!
If I see your face
in this town again,
I'm gonna slice it off
and use it to wipe
my unmentionables.
Mind the beak.
And don't come back!
What are you all
gawping at?
(SNIFFS)
Hey, Bad Bill,
there's something
I got to tell you!
Oy. What is this?
You know who that is, Bill?
That there's Rango!
Yeah, he ain't
afraid of you!
He ain't afraid
of none of you.
Killed them
Jenkins brothers.
Done it with
one bullet, Bill.
All seven of them!
Is that right?
(COUGHING)
(ALL GASPING)
(BURPING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Let me get that
before you...
No. Oh, I know. Here.
Oh!
Just take care
of that for you.
There. All better.
(GULPS)
(CRACKING)
(CREAKING)
(BULLETS CLATTERING)
Whoa! Whoa.
T.O. T.O. Just a second.
All right, now listen!
I'm going to
give you fellas
one last chance
to reconsider!
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
And if you don't
want to reconsider
I might consider
reconsidering myself.
Huh?
Now that's what
I'm talking about. Yeah.
All right, now listen up!
Things are going to be
different around here
now that Rango's in town.
I want my shoes
shined every morning,
Got some new rules!
my coffee hot,
Danish on the side.
Whatever you do,
don't look me in the eye.
Stay out of my
peripheral vision!
It's Rango.
What's he up to?
He ain't afraid
of nobody.
He's telling
that bird what's for!
And when you see me
coming, stand aside.
I take large steps
and I don't want
none of you hayseeds
getting your bodily fluids
on my boots!
Of course, there is
no need for violence,
as long as
we stick together,
work as a team.
So I want you all
to come outside now
and line up single file
while I take
a brief intermission!
What's he doing now?
I think
it's a number two.
(GASPING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Never mind.
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
(HAWK SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Take a look-see
over here!
Well, look at him now!
He's chasing
after that hawk!
Give him hell, Rango!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(RUMBLING)
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
(MOANING SOFTLY)
Oh, no!
(PANTING)
(HAWK SCREECHING)
(TOWNSPEOPLE MUTTERING)
Did you see that?
He killed that thing!
What do you think, Doc?
This hawk is dead!
(ALL GASPING)
Shoot, I say
we cook that right up.
He did it
with one bullet!
Just like he said!
It's about time we had
a hero around here.
One who ain't
in a pine box.
I think it's time
he met the Mayor.
You hear that, Rango?
You're going to
meet the Mayor!
Let's hear it for Rango!
(ALL CHEERING)
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
And so the
stranger basks
in the adulation
of his new friends,
sinking deeper
into the guacamole
of his own deception.
When is he going to die?
Soon,  compadre. Soon.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(RANGO HUMMING)
(MIMICKING BALL)
BEANS: My land
is not for sale!
I came here
to save my land,
not sell it!
MERRIMACK: I'm sure
there's something reasonable
we can work out if
you just talk to him!
(EXCLAIMING)
Beans! Where are
you going? Beans?
The Mayor will see you now.
Water, Mr. Rango, water.
Without it,
there's nothing
but dust and decay.
But with water
there's life.
Look at them,
so desperate to live,
they'll follow it anywhere.
That's the immutable
law of the desert.
Control the water
and you control everything.
This is from
my private stock.
Vintage rainwater
from the Great Deluge.
(CHUCKLES)
Good heavens,
I'm not that old.
Not Noah's deluge.
(LAUGHING DESPERATELY)
I guess power
has its privileges.
You make a good point, son.
But with privilege
comes responsibility.
Uh...
Hell, I was mayor here
before there was a Dirt!
And I may be just
a sentimental old turtle
but I think there's
a future for this town.
And I hope
you'll be part of it.
(SHATTERING)
To Dirt!
To Dirt.
You see them, Mr. Rango?
All my friends
and neighbors?
It's a hard life here.
Very hard.
Do you know how
they make it through
each and every day?
They believe.
They believe
it's going to be better.
They believe that
the water will come.
They believe
against all odds
and all evidence
that tomorrow will
be better than today.
People have
to believe in something.
Right now,
they believe in you.
Pick it up, Mr. Rango.
Your destiny awaits.
People have to believe
in something.
BEANS: It just
don't make no sense.
This whole town
is drying up,
and the Mayor is
the only one who don't
seem to be affected.
Doesn't that make you
just a wee bit suspicious?
And what about that water
I saw out in the desert?
All right! No need
to incite anxiety.
I'll inquire
about the Mayor.
But if you really
feel there's some
conspiracy occurring,
I suggest you take it up
with the new sheriff.
Mmm-hmm.
RANGO: This is going
to be good. Hey!
Watch that needle there.
Not too tight.
I want to leave room
for some pucker!
That's good.
Oh, easy there, tiger.
A little up and back?
I don't think so.
Have you got French
cuffs with that?
Excuse me, Sheriff Rango.
I want to talk to you.
Hey, Beans,
what do you think
of the new duds?
I got a 10-gallon hat
marked down from 15.
That's nice.
Have you met Angelique?
Hello, Beans.
Hello, Angelique.
Tart.
Floozy.
Trollop.
Excuse me, Mr. Rango.
I will blow that ugly
right off your face!
I was just thinking that...
Oh, you want the old
John Hancock, do you?
Well, here. Hold this.
Sheriff Rango, this
isn't a social call.
There's a bullet in there.
I know about the
shindig this afternoon.
I ordered myself
some right fancy duds.
Sheriff, I'd like to file a...
Mr. Rango!
Oh, you, too? No problem.
Here, let me just...
I need you to investigate...
You know, Beans,
I bet you clean up real nice,
you put a little
effort into it.
What?
Now, remember, son,
stay in school,
eat your veggies,
burn everything
but Shakespeare.
Who's Shakespeare?
(SHOUTING) Sheriff Rango,
if that is your real name.
I am trying to save
my daddy's ranch,
which is on the verge
of an agricultural meltdown
while you're
playing patty-cake
with this here trollop!
Sad, really.
Such a drab little thing.
Why does she do that?
It's a survival reflex.
Her switch is just broken.
Well, that's
an inconvenience.
It is not a rash!
It is a birthmark!
I did it again, didn't I?
Did what?
(SIGHING) Let me
ask you something.
Did anybody here
mention what happened
to our last sheriff?
(HAMMERING)
(GULPS)
(CLINKING)
(CLOCK CHIMING)
Pardon, but may I ask you...
Excuse me, may I ask you...
The last sheriff... Pardon me.
Where is everybody going?
What exactly
happened to the...
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ All day
♪ I've faced the barren waste
♪ Without the taste of water
♪ Cool water
♪ Old Dan and I
♪ With throats burned dry
♪ And souls that cry
♪ For water
Oh! I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
♪ Cool
♪ Clear water ♪
(CLEARING THROAT)
This is a heck of a hoedown
you got going.
Still working
out those steps.
So, is this considered
normal civic behavior?
Mmm-hmm.
Every Wednesday,
just like clockwork.
You kill bird.
Yeah. Matter of fact,
I did.
Bird dead. Snake come.
Snake?
He means
Rattlesnake Jake,
Mr. Rango.
He never comes to town
'cause he's scared
of that hawk.
But he might come now.
Can I have your boots
when you're dead?
No!
And I ain't got no problem
with this Rattlesnake Jake.
That's just
what Amos said.
Amos?
PRISCILLA: You got
any gold fillings?
My fellow Dirtonians.
I welcome you to our
great day of deliverance.
Hallelujah.
ALL: Hallelujah!
Acolytes, prepare
the holy spigot!
We have a newcomer
amongst us today,
my friends.
A man I think needs
little introduction to you
so bold has been his entry
into our fair society.
Mr. Rango, would
you step forward?
(STRUGGLING)
The time has come,
my friends.
The time that
was foretold!
ALL: Hallelujah!
The sacred time!
The time of destiny!
ALL: Hallelujah!
The time of deliverance!
It is the time of hydration!
(ALL GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
It's his fault!
It's the newcomer!
Burn him!
MAN: He's a witch!
I get his boots!
My friends, my friends!
Temper your frustrations.
Times will be tough
from now on.
Sacrifices will
have to be made.
But if I can help
in any way,
please know that
my door is always...
Hold it, hold it!
stinks three ways
to Sunday.
Now, this whole thing
First the bank's run dry
and now this here spigot?
MAN: The bank's run dry?
What's she
talking about?
She said there's
no water in the bank!
ALL: Huh?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(ALL SHOUTING)
This is all we have!
We can't give it all out!
That was my
rehydration account!
(GUN FIRES)
None of that
civil disobedience
in my town,
thank you very much.
Oh. Oh!
Thank goodness
you're here, Sheriff.
Things were getting
out of hand.
Come right in.
Let me have a
gander at the source
of the societal
discontentment here.
(SHUDDERING)
Mercy.
(CLEARING THROAT)
All right, listen up!
I've been thinking
and I believe
I've figured
something out.
You folks have
a water problem!
(ALL MUTTERING)
Now just pay
attention, everybody.
I'm trying to make
a point here.
Let's say this fella
here were to take
a drink of water.
Just one little drink.
No harm, no foul, right?
And you!
You're just as dried up
and parched as
a jackrabbit in July.
So you belly on up
and take you a double shot!
Stay with me.
What do you think
happens then?
Why we'd all be drinking!
And before you know it,
there wouldn't be
any more water.
And then where would we be?
We'd be thirsty.
Real thirsty.
We'd turn on each other
like a bunch of animals!
Now look here.
We have got six
days of water.
We have got five days...
(ALL MUTTERING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
As long as we've got water,
we've got ourselves a town.
Sheriff Rango is right.
As long as
we have this water,
we have some hope.
And you can all
take it from me.
My 100%
full-time employment
from this moment on
our precious
natural resource.
will be to protect
Ain't no one gonna
tango with the Rango.
Evening, ladies.
BOTH: Evening, Sheriff.
MAN: And don't
you come back!
Hold on there, Gordy.
You get back in there
and you assert yourself,
and I think you'll find
the people of this here town
to be
surprisingly hospitable.
Thank you, Sheriff.
MAN: What?
Not you again!
(GORDY EXCLAIMS)
I stand corrected.
This ain't the bank.
I told you, Jedidiah!
Hold it right there!
Who's that?
It's the Sheriff!
Get them hands up
where I can see them!
Just as I suspected.
Prospecting without
the authorized equipment.
Don't move a muscle.
Prospecting?
(CLATTERING)
Now, you got your shovel,
pickaxe, Benadryl, loofah,
assorted snacks,
some puzzle books
and you're gonna
need a permit.
Loofah.
PAPPY: Ezekiel, Jedidiah!
What the Sam Hill's
going on up there?
I've had polyps
removed smarter
than the two of you!
(SNIFFING)
Hell's fire,
this ain't the bank!
Pappy, the Sheriff
is standing right here,
helping us out.
Gonna give us
a permit for
prospecting.
That's right, sir.
Just doing my duty.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
The lonely constable
on his rounds,
keeping an eagle eye out
for mayhem and malfeasance.
Does he look
like he sounds?
Uh-huh.
Well, Sheriff,
if we was to hit
the mother lode,
being prospectors and such,
where would
we deposit said annuity?
Here in the town of Dirt,
we happen to have
the finest
financial institution
this side
of the Missouri.
noon and night
by yours truly.
Protected morning,
Much obliged.
(ROOSTER CROWING)
The bank's been robbed!
Good Lord,
the bank's been robbed!
What's going on?
It's gone!
The water's all gone!
What'd he say?
He said the bank's
been robbed!
Dr. Marx! I'm on fire!
Embrace me!
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ The bank's been robbed,
the town is dry
♪ "We'll die of thirst,"
the people cry
♪ He promised
to protect the vault
♪ The water's gone,
it's all his fault ♪
RANGO: All right, folks,
stand back, clear the area.
This is a crime scene now.
Secure the perimeter,
dust for prints,
check for fibers,
scan for DNA.
I want a urine sample
from everyone.
And get me a latte.
And don't mix up the two.
What's this?
"Prospecting Permit."
I'll take that.
Material evidence.
What are we gonna
do now, Sheriff?
We need that water.
We're all going to die!
My friends, we all know
what we have to do now.
That's right.
We all know what
we have to do now.
And that would be?
(MUTTERING) Form a posse.
Form a possum!
(MUTTERING) A posse.
Now, we're gonna be doing this
in an orderly fashion.
First off,
does anybody here
know how to use
a firearm of any kind?
All right, then.
What do we do now, Sheriff?
Now we ride!
Where are we going?
What?
RANGO: Now, as my deputy,
you'll be in charge
of all tracking and
finding of villains,
utilizing your
well-developed Injun-uity,
no offense taken.
So which way do
you think they went?
You want to sniff the air
or commune with
a buffalo or something?
Oh, you're good.
I'm depending
on you, Spoons.
You got a little tobaccy
in the beard there.
Always good to have
a medical man along, Doc.
Reptiles got to
stick together, right,
my brother?
I'm an amphibian.
Ain't no shame in that.
Whoa!
You sure you're fit for
duty there, soldier?
Well, you got
a little something
in your eye there.
Oh, that?
That there's conjunctivitis,
sir. It's hereditary.
Oh. Well, I'm glad to hear
it's not contagious.
Now, just wait
a cotton-picking minute!
A posse ain't
no place for a...
Never mind.
Hold on there,
little sister.
to look after the town
while I'm gone.
Someone's gonna have
Can I gut-shoot someone?
Let's put a pin in that.
Sheriff, you're going
to bring that water back,
aren't you?
Count on it, little sister.
Which way
do we go, Sheriff?
There's tunnels
everywhere.
Whole town's
perforated with them.
How'd them fellers
find the bank, anyway?
Gentlemen, if we can
just stay on task here.
AMBROSE: Sheriff!
Over here!
Would you look at that?
Like seeing
the face of God.
Amen, brother.
I remember
when it used to flow
every Wednesday.
Those were
the halcyon days.
Must be a reason
she quit on us.
Whatever the reason,
something is controlling
this here water.
What do you say, Sheriff?
Clearly, the robbers came
from this direction.
I say we track
this pipe back
to its hydraulic origin
and apprehend
the culprits
behind this
aquatic conundrum.
What'd he say?
I think he said
follow the pipe.
He said follow the pipe.
Whatever you do,
do not look down.
Whoa!
What is this place?
It's an aquifer.
Oh.
What's an aquifer?
Well, it's for aqua.
Well, it's empty now.
That's a big one.
It's the end of the line.
Don't go no further.
Someone or something
is messing with our hydration
has got something
to do with it.
and that pipe
I thought
we was following
bank robbers!
We're experiencing
a paradigm shift.
I'm gonna shift
the features on your face
if you don't shut up!
Go ahead and try!
(BOTH SHOUTING)
Quiet, you savages!
Stop your rattling.
You're affecting
my cogitation.
(SILENCE)
Whoa! I got it.
Snuff out them torches.
BUFORD: Sure enough.
Smart thinking
there, feller.
WAFFLES: Start climbing.
FURGUS: Get your
foot out of my face!
Not bad, huh, Beans?
You keep thinking like that,
your hat's gonna
catch on fire.
Well, you know, you get
on a roll, you just...
(EXCLAIMING)
Hot, hot! Burn.
Poor things.
All they wanted
was a little water.
Cactus dying of thirst.
It don't bode well.
Hey, look what I found!
BUFORD: What you got there?
I saw that first!
Hey, that's mine!
Give me that!
It's empty anyway.
I knew that.
Where'd you find that?
Sheriff! You're going
to want to see this!
It's Mr. Merrimack
from the bank.
AMBROSE:
What's he doing here?
Everybody stand back.
All right, let me see.
Looks like them
varmints shot him
in the back.
No, this man wasn't shot.
He was drowned!
Drowned?
In the middle
of the desert?
What a way to go.
Well, now, whose
boot prints are those?
That's interesting.
The ground's still wet.
I suppose
we should bury him.
I don't know.
Birds got to eat, too.
Circle of life!
Hey! What's that
dad-gum Indian doing?
I see you're consulting
with the spirits.
No, I'm molting.
Means I'm ready to mate.
Oh.
I'll keep that in mind.
Cactus fruit.
Ah, yes.
The ancient cactus fruit.
I believe your people
use it as seasoning
when preparing
your native dishes.
Also natural laxative.
(COUGHING)
(SHUSHING)
Pick up trail.
Three men heading west.
One blind, one with
(SNIFFING)
enlarged prostate,
riding sidesaddle.
What did he say?
They're riding
sidesaddle.
We're whispering.
What'd he say?
Someone's
got a bad valve.
All right, which
one of you fellers
needs a check-up?
Awkward.
Uh...
What exactly are
we going to do now?
Now we ride!
(SILENCE)
(LOUDLY) That means
we're riding now!
This moment.
(PLAYING MARIACHI MUSIC)
(COUGHS)
WAFFLES: Marshmallows
remind me of going
camping with my daddy.
I could eat them
all night long.
Of course he did
make me cough them back
up again for breakfast.
(BURPS)
This one time,
I coughed up an
entire Dalmatian.
I coughed up a whole
tribe of pygmies.
That ain't nothing.
They started looking
at me weird.
I remember them.
They was quite friendly.
I found a human spinal column
in my fecal matter once.
You might want
to get that looked at.
Pass the beans, Beans.
Sheriff?
No, thanks.
Mr. Rango? Can you
tell us about the
Spirit of the West?
(ALL AGREEING)
Yeah, tell us about that.
WAFFLES: Is it true
what they say?
Yes, the Spirit
of the West!
The eternally
unattainable ideal.
They say he rides in
an alabaster carriage
with golden guardians
to protect him.
But he only appears
to those who have
undertaken an epic quest!
And have made it
to the other side.
The other side of what?
It's a metaphor.
WAFFLES: Ow! My eye!
That's gonna heal right up.
Sheriff? What are
you going to do about
Rattlesnake Jake?
(RATTLING)
What? Where?
Sorry about that.
Word is you come against
him once or twice.
(CLEARING THROAT) Yeah.
Jake. You mean my brother.
Your brother?
That's what I said!
But he's a snake
and you're a lizard.
Well, Momma had
an active social life.
Did he ever bite you?
Sure enough did.
Look at that baby.
Go ahead, you can touch it.
That's interesting.
That there's
a belly button.
Luckily, I'm immune
to his venom.
Put some in my coffee
just to give it a little tang.
he's only scared
of them hawks?
Is it true
Them's what we call
his natural predator.
(FAINT COYOTE HOWL)
(ALL GASP)
All this talk of that
serpentine devil is
putting my quills on edge!
I ain't sleeping
tonight. No, sir.
RANGO: Don't you all
worry about a thing.
Come tomorrow,
we'll locate that water
and return to
a hero's welcome.
Friends, before
we bunk down
I'd like us all
to join hands
for a moment,
say a few words
to the Spirit of the West.
ELGIN: That's a good idea.
Ain't always spoken
rightly to you,
Spirit of the West.
But tonight
I want to thank you
for bringing Sheriff
Rango into our lives.
It's a hard life we got.
Sometimes I don't know
how we're gonna make it.
But somehow, Sheriff Rango
makes me think we will.
We needed a brave man
and you sent us one.
Nice to have someone
to believe in again.
Thank you, Spirit
of the West. Amen.
Amen.
(CHUCKLES)
Just checking.
It's a little
cold tonight.
Thank you.
You ever feel like
those things are
looking at you?
That's a Spanish dagger.
But around here,
we just call them
the Walking Cactus.
Walking?
There's an old legend
they actually walk
across the desert
to find water.
When I was a little girl,
I'd stay up late
watching them,
to see if they'd move.
I thought if
I could follow them,
they'd lead me to
someplace wonderful.
Someplace with enough
water for everyone.
Night after night,
I watched them.
I never saw them move.
RANGO: But you're
still watching.
Who doesn't want to find
someplace wonderful?
We'll find the water,
Beans. I promise you.
(COYOTE HOWLING)
That's such
a lonely sound.
You ever get lonely?
Sometimes.
I can't imagine it.
You're such a charmer and
everyone likes you so much.
I never made friends
easy like that.
No?
No, we're pretty isolated
out there on the ranch,
sort of like
being sealed up
in a little box.
Don't really see
a lot of folks.
I wouldn't know
what that's like.
There someone special
in your life, Rango?
Oh, there used to be.
But she couldn't
keep her head.
Besides, my life's
too dangerous for
that kind of thing.
You know,
it's an awful
solitary existence
out there on the prairie.
Riding the ranges
and the suchlike.
Beans?
I'm gonna skin
you alive, boy!
I'm gonna whup you
like a red-headed stepchild!
Choleric varmints,
ain't they?
Dysfunctional family.
Need intervention.
What's that coming?
RANGO: It's the water.
(ALL MURMURING)
I have a plan,
and each and every one
of you has a part to play.
What do I do?
Spoons, you got
the most important
job of all.
You stay up here on the ridge,
and if anything goes wrong,
you give the signal.
(VOCALIZING)
Hey, Beans.
What size dress
you wearing?
He got it!
Hallelujah!
He found the water!
You did it, son.
Well, actually...
Why can't you be all brainy
like your brother?
Pappy, about that water.
There's something
I gots to tell you.
Hush up, now.
Somebody's coming.
(FAIR MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOPING)
Good sirs,
gracious good afternoon
to thee and thee and thee.
May I present
Madame Lupone's
Terpsichorean Troupe
of Traveling Thespians!
What is that?
I think they's thespians.
Thespians?
That's illegal
in seven states!
The stage is set.
The princess prepares
to take her own life.
I yearn for love.
Meanwhile, the lone
sentry stands watch
at the castle gate.
Hark! Who goes there?
This plot is
highly predictable.
Quiet! This is
my favorite part.
Arriving to great fanfare
'twas her aged father,
(FANFARE)
strucketh by Cupid.
Prithee, unhand
my fair daughter
and reach for the...
Line?
"Reach for the sky!"
What was that?
Must be that
immersive theater.
We got you surrounded!
You and your
entire family
get your hands up
where I can see them.
(CHUCKLES)
My entire family?
(RUMBLING)
♪ Grits and spit
and collard greens
♪ Waffle chitlins,
monkey brains
♪ Refried bones
and booger blood
♪ Pickled eggs
and flaps of mud ♪
(GASPS)
It's a full house.
Looks like we're
gonna have ourselves
a good old-fashioned standoff.
I'll have you know,
you're not looking at
our entire contingent.
(SPOONS CAWING)
What's that
supposed to be?
That's the signal.
That's the signal!
Something must
have gone wrong!
(GRUNTING)
So something's
supposed to happen?
I am open
to suggestions.
(PANTING)
(SQUEALING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Run!
Get on the wagon!
Should we have ourselves
some sport, chill'ens?
(LAUGHS) I likes it
when they run.
Maybelle,
give the holler!
(HOWLING)
(ALL HOWLING)
Looks like we made it!
That audience was
quite responsive.
Yeah, well, I think
that chromosome pool
is about dried up.
(LAUGHING)
(WHOOPING)
We got bats!
Here! You drive.
(PLAYING
RIDE OF THE VALKYRIES)
Looks like there's
gonna be soup tonight!
Come on,
let's get some!
What in tarnation?
Don't shoot the water!
Jedidiah! It's time for
the Alabama squeeze box!
Okay, Pa!
I am sensing hostility.
Incoming!
Hello!
Goodbye!
Lasso that swine!
(WHOOPING)
Huh?
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
I suggest we take
evasive action!
I suggest you
shut up and shoot!
What happened
to the Sheriff?
He had a previous
engagement!
Boseefus, give them
some gumbo now!
(THUMP)
What was that?
Go check it out!
What is it?
Is there a problem?
You could call it that.
(THE BLUE DANUBE
PLAYING)
Whee!
Huh?
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Headache.
Is that all you got?
(SCREAMING)
That wasn't
altogether unpleasant!
Eat lead!
Here, hold these.
(EXCLAIMS)
Get your hands off me!
Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry.
BOTH: Whoa!
Jump!
It's impossible.
It can't be.
It's empty.
There's no water!
No water?
Then what the hell
we been fighting for?
Sir, you have defiled
and desecrated
the very sustenance
of our livelihood!
I think that there fella
in the purty dress
is the Sheriff.
That's the same
fellow what give us
a prospecting permit?
A what?
Irrelevant! Obfuscation.
You and your kin
are under arrest
for bank robbery
of our beloved
financial advisor
and the murder
Johannes Merrimack
the Third, AKA, Fluffy Joe.
Sheriff, we didn't
kill nobody.
We done tunneled into
that vault, but there
weren't nothing in it.
Somebody done
robbed that bank
before we robbed it.
Then where'd you
get this here jug?
That's what I been trying
to tell you, Pappy.
I found it in the desert.
Then why in tarnation
did you bring it here?
this here jug was empty
when you found it?
Hold on! You're saying
Uh-huh. That's right.
I don't believe
a word of it.
Let's hang them, Sheriff!
String them up!
Who'd dump water
in the desert?
Wouldn't be
the first time.
It's a puzzle!
It's like a big
old mammogram!
What's going on, Sheriff?
I don't know.
But I'm going to strip
away this mystery
and expose
its private parts.
You and your kin
are coming with me.
(CLINKING)
(CLOCK CHIMING)
CLETUS: They're coming!
Here they come!
Looks like they
got them robbers.
Where's the water?
There weren't no water.
(ALL MUTTERING)
(STAMMERING)
Where is he going?
He's going
to see the Mayor.
He's got to be
pleased with that.
CHORIZO:
That's a good one, boss!
(SIGHING)
That's interesting.
I do apologize for
the shoes, Mr. Rango,
but there's a certain
protocol to this game,
you understand.
I'm a bit of a stickler
for protocol.
Well, that's good,
'cause you got a few
questions to answer
and I've got my
own protocol.
But why would anyone dump
water in the blooming desert?
It does seem a bit naive,
taking the word of
admitted bank robbers.
Besides, once they hang,
your job is done.
Bravo!
Job well done.
But what if somebody
did rob the bank
before they got there?
And who would do
that, Mr. Rango?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
That sounds marginally
near to an accusation.
Take it any way you like.
Ow!
RANGO:
Something you said
keeps rattling around
in my frontal lobe.
MAYOR: What's that?
"Control the water
and you control everything."
(CHUCKLING)
Come now, Mr. Rango.
You attribute
divine power to me.
How on earth
could I possibly
control the water?
You've obviously
mastered this game.
Well, I've been
playing it for
many years, sir.
I was here before
the highway split
this great valley.
I watched the
march of progress,
and I learned
a thing or two.
Perhaps it's time
you started to take
the long view,
begin to appreciate
the broad sweep of history.
Look out there, son.
You can almost
see time passing.
What are you
building out here?
The future, Mr. Rango,
the future.
One day soon,
all this is going
to fade into myth,
the frontier town,
the lawman, the gunslinger.
There's just no place
for them anymore.
We're civilized now.
That's right, civilized.
That's what
the future holds.
You can either
be part of it,
or you can
be left behind.
Is that what happened
to Mr. Merrimack?
Did he get left behind?
Careful, Mr. Rango.
You seem to forget
you're just one
little lizard.
You seem to forget
I'm the law
around these parts.
Our new sheriff
has been playing
the hero for so long,
he's actually starting
to believe it.
Call in Rattlesnake Jake.
But Jake's
the Grim Reaper.
He never leaves
without taking
a blooming soul.
Do it!
Now be still.
You gotta look presentable
to meet your maker.
(SINGING
LA MUERTE A LLEGADO)
♪ Death has arrived
♪ How will the
hero survive? ♪
The Mayor has bought up
all the land in the valley,
except for your ranch,
Miss Beans.
That just don't
make no sense.
Without water,
that land is useless.
Unless he controls
the water.
Like a monkey's bladder!
Then he could bring it
back once he's
bought up all the land.
But how does
he control the water?
Sheriff,
we got a problem.
(SHOUTING ANGRILY)
Hold on, Beans.
That won't be necessary.
Hang him till
his head turns blue!
Give us them robbers!
Hold on!
Calm down, everyone!
Let me talk!
Nail them to the courthouse!
RANGO: Now, calm down.
Get them out here
so we can cut off
their giblets!
You, too, Spoons?
They done taken that water.
They taken everything we got!
No one's stringing anyone up.
Not while I'm sheriff.
But this is all his fault!
You said you's gonna
bring the water back.
It's just, we got no hope
without that water.
We got nothing
left to believe in.
You see that sign up there?
As long as that sign
says "Sheriff,"
you can believe that there's
law and order in this town.
But without law and order,
ruminate on that. Oh, yeah.
Starts out slow,
like a fungus.
Somebody says a cross word.
Accusations start flying.
Neighbor turns on neighbor.
Pretty soon, we're
eating our children!
And then dogs and cats
are getting together
to create all sorts of
unnatural mutant aberrations!
So, you want something
to believe in, Spoons?
Believe in me.
Believe in that there sign.
For as long
as it hangs there,
we got hope.
(GUN FIRING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GASPING)
Hello, brother.
Thirsty?
(GULPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Long time, brother.
How you been keeping?
Well, you know...
I hear you been telling
about how you killed
all them Jenkins brothers.
With one bullet,
wasn't it?
Isn't that right?
All these good folks here
believe your little stories,
don't they?
Why, they believe
you're just a stone killer,
don't they?
Seems these
folks trust you.
you're gonna save
their little town.
They think
you're gonna save
their little souls!
But we know better,
don't we?
So why don't you
show your friends here
what you're made of?
Show them
who you really are.
Why don't you
just pull your gun
and shoot me?
But, of course,
you won't need all these.
Just one, right?
Go ahead, hero.
Pull the trigger.
You got killer
in your eyes, son?
I don't see it.
You didn't do
any of them things
you said, did you?
You didn't kill them
Jenkins brothers.
You ain't even
from the West!
Are you?
Say it!
No.
Oh, speak up.
I don't think your friends
here heard you.
No.
All you've done is lie
to these good people.
You ain't nothing but
a fake and a coward.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
Louder!
Listen close,
you pathetic fraud.
This is my town now.
If I ever see you again,
I will take your soul
straight down to hell!
Who are you?
RANGO:
Who am I?
I'm nobody.
(GRUNTS) Ow!
(GASPS)
Golden guardians.
The alabaster carriage.
(GASPS)
The Spirit of the West.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Excuse me?
Mister Spirit, sir?
Ah. There's a beaut.
to dig deep to find
what you're looking for.
Sometimes you got
So you made it.
Is this heaven?
If it were,
we'd be eating Pop-Tarts
with Kim Novak.
Yeah.
No kidding.
What are you
doing out here?
Searching, same as you.
(SIGHING) I don't even know
what I'm looking for anymore.
I don't even
know who I am.
They used to call you
the Man with No Name.
These days they got a name
for just about everything.
Doesn't matter
what they call you.
It's the deeds
make the man.
Yeah, but my deeds
just made things worse.
I'm a fraud.
I'm a phony!
My friends believed in me,
but they need
some kind of hero.
Then be a hero.
No. No, no,
you don't understand.
I'm not even
supposed to be here.
That's right.
You came a long way
to find something
that isn't out here.
Don't you see?
It's not about you.
It's about them.
But I can't go back.
Don't know that
you got a choice, son.
No man can walk out
on his own story.
ROADKILL:
So you made it.
That's right,  amigo.
The other side of the road.
Did you just see that?
We each see
what we need to see.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
It is.
Come, my friend.
I want to show
you something.
Many years ago,
this entire valley
was covered in  agua.
Now only one
question remains.
Where did it go?
They follow the water.
They follow the water!
Come on!
(SPRINKLERS WHIRRING)
BEANS:
That just don't
make no sense.
Without water,
that land is useless.
What are you
building out here?
The future, Mr. Rango.
You can either
be part of it,
or you can
be left behind.
I was here before
the highway split
this great valley.
I watched the
march of progress,
and I learned
a thing or two.
Control the water
and you control everything.
Come now, Mr. Rango.
You attribute
divine power to me.
How on earth
could I possibly
control the water?
What now,  amigo?
No man can walk out
on his own story.
I'm going back.
But why?
Because that's who I am.
You got a lot of nerve
showing up here, lawman.
What is it you want?
Your pappy and them
boys are about to hang
for something
they didn't do.
But I've got a plan.
(CLINKING)
MAYOR:
I appreciate how difficult
this is for you, Beans.
But you're making
a practical decision.
Decisions, decisions.
There's no need
for any more suffering.
(GULPING)
Your family's ranch
is nothing but
a wasteland now.
Sign the deed
and relieve yourself
of your father's burden.
My daddy was
not a burden!
Keep your blood money
and I'll keep my land!
(HISSING)
Do what he says or,
by all the fires
of the black pit,
I'll squeeze them
pretty brown eyes
out of your skull!
Now, hold on, Jake.
There's no need to...
Let me do my job!
You brought me in.
Now we're gonna
play this thing
out to the end!
Sign the damn
paper, woman!
Go to hell!
Where do you think
I come from?
Look into my eyes.
I want to see you die.
(GRUNTING)
RANGO: Jake!
I'm calling you out!
Jake!
This day just got
a little more interesting.
(HISSING)
(GASPING)
Put her down.
Or what, little man?
You going to kill me?
That's just about
the size of it.
Get your filthy
paws off me!
Shut your gob!
All right, Sheriff,
make your move.
(CHUCKLING EVILLY)
(SIGHING)
(CLINKING)
(EXHALES)
(CHIMING)
(SPURS JINGLING)
(RATTLING)
(GASPS)
Now,  amigos!
ALL: Heave! Heave!
(COCKS GUN)
Ow!
That was a bad idea.
(CREAKING)
Thirsty, brother?
Huh?
Here it comes!
No. No!
(EXCLAIMING)
It's a miracle!
Look out!
Lookee there!
What is that?
It's our salvation, Pa!
It's a jailbreak, boys!
We're busting out!
(WHOOPING)
I'm gonna blow
so many holes in you,
your guts'll be
leaking lead!
Well, then it's a good thing
I brought some backup.
(EXCLAIMING)
What?
Ain't no hawk.
Ain't nothing but bats!
Stick to the plan, boys!
Let's bleed that devil dry!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
It only takes one bullet.
You ain't got the nerve.
Try me.
MAYOR: Oh, Mr. Rango.
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Hand me your gun, Sheriff.
Now, Mr. Rango.
(CHUCKLING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Beans! Hold on.
Don't worry, I got a plan.
Help!
Open the door!
Okay, plan B.
(MUFFLED)
Beans, you're mumbling.
All my problems taken
care of except for one.
It's a new West, Jake.
There's no room
for gunslingers anymore.
We're businessmen now.
Yeah, we got new hats.
Where I come from,
we call this
improvisation.
(PANTING)
You came back.
(COUGHING)
What was that?
No need to panic,
but I think you just
swallowed plan B.
What?
Okay, panic time.
You and the Sheriff are
more alike than you think.
You're nothing
but legends.
Pretty soon, no one will
believe you even existed.
One last bullet
to kill one last outlaw.
How fitting.
(CLICKS)
(CLINKS)
Sheriff, I'm sure
if we work together,
we can reach a mutually
beneficial solution
to our current situation.
You better take
it up with him.
One bullet.
I tip my hat to you,
one legend to another.
What was that you said?
"Pretty soon, no one will
believe you even existed."
No, Jake! No!
(MAYOR SCREAMING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Rango!
You brought the water back,
just like you promised.
You really are a hero.
Well, the thing about
heroes is, whenever you...
Don't spoil it.
Right.
Well, I don't know
about you all,
but I could sure
go for a dip.
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
And so the lizard
completes his journey
from humble beginnings to
the legend we sing of today.
And although he
is certain to die,
perhaps from
a household accident,
which account for 65%
of all unnatural deaths,
the people of the village
will always remember
the name of the one
who saved them.
ALL: Rango!
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ From out of the dust
came a man true and bold
♪ Champion of the Fandango
♪ By night he drank whiskey,
by day killed bad men
♪ And the townspeople
knew him as Rango
♪ Coming down the mountainside
the people hailed his name
♪ And of his legend
they sang, oh!
♪ With iron in his heart
and steel in his claw
♪ He pumped their heads
all full of lead, Rango!
♪ Rango!
♪ Rango
♪ A ladies' man indeed from
his head down to his knees
♪ Rango was doing the tango
♪ When in came Bad Bill
from his hideout in the hills
♪ With a notion to kill Rango
♪ Rango!
♪ Rango
♪ Now Rango, he is gone
♪ But his legend
still lives on
♪ In the brothels and saloons
♪ Of Durango
♪ He lived as he died
♪ With a six-gun at his side
♪ And all the ladies cried
♪ For Rango
♪ Rango!
♪ Rango
♪ Rango ♪