- That was Park Wonseok, right?
- You mean in the video?
Does that mean he was killed
and that he didn't kill himself?
- Right.
- Who did that?
I could've sworn I saw
somebody kicking him out of the window.
I don't feel safe in this school anymore.
Seok Jaebum?
What are you doing here?
Uh, I...
Actually, I...
Seok Jaebum, was it you?
Are you the one who left the note for me?
Note?
Oh, right. You're here
because you received a note too, right?
Uh...
Agh, we should have caught him!
That was probably the guy
who left the note, don't you think?
Definitely. Seriously, who is that guy?
Do you think he would've shown himself
to me if you hadn't been there?
Ah, sorry, that might've been the case.
Sorry, I ruined it for you.
Oh, no, no, it's fine.
I was in the athletic field,
ditching class,
when I saw you heading
into the shooting range alone.
That reminded me
of the auditorium incident
when you got attacked,
so I followed you in.
I guess I should thank you.
Do you think
that's the same guy
from the auditorium incident?
Maybe it's someone else?
Why do you say that?
Huh?
Oh, it's just...
It's just a hunch that I'm having.
SOUNDS FROM YOUR HEART
Ok Chanmi.
I'd like to apologize.
I should've investigated this
as a homicide case from the beginning.
I'm sorry it took us so long
to come around.
You need to find the cell phone.
My older brother's cell phone.
We'll look into it.
In the meantime, do you know of anyone
who might've been on bad terms
with your older brother?
No.
You transferred to this school
on purpose all the way from Busan.
Is there anything
you've managed to piece together so far?
Are you...
asking me if I know
who the perpetrator is?
Now? Three months after he was killed?
Now, after all the evidence
has disappeared and the murderer's
had plenty of time
to hide whatever's remaining?
I understand you're feeling frustrated
as a family member of the victim.
But your attitude is not going to help
this investigation. Wouldn't you agree?
I mean, what I'm asking is...
Chanmi.
You said you noticed someone
coming towards your brother
when you were on that video call
with him, correct?
Yes, I did.
Hey, hold on a second.
We stopped talking
because someone came towards my brother.
It seemed like the phone fell
to the ground.
Huh? What the...
Then someone picked up the phone.
I couldn't see their face.
It's exactly the same
as what I told you three months ago.
Do you remember your brother's expression
when that person approached him?
Did he seem happy to see them,
or did he not seem to like them?
I didn't really notice anything
in particular.
I called you in here today
mainly because I wanted to apologize.
Um, if you think of anything that
might be useful for the investigation,
feel free to reach out anytime.
If there's nothing else,
you're free to go.
May I also ask you a question?
The video of my brother falling,
the one that everyone saw
in the auditorium...
Why do you think they chose
to release it now and in this way?
If they had submitted that video
to the police from the beginning,
this case would have been investigated
as a homicide, right?
That's a mystery to us too.
You know that we can't share
any technical details with you, right?
Where was that video taken?
Chanmi,
I want to make this very clear to you.
We will investigate this case
as the police.
Please don't think about investigating
this case on your own.
What's up with you?
Ditching class and all.
We could just talk in the classroom.
Why did you text me to come out?
Osung.
Answer me truthfully.
What's going on?
Did you send Chanmi another note?
No.
You didn't?
I already got what I needed from her
in the auditorium that last time.
What else would I need from her?
I didn't send her another note.
Really?
Why do you ask?
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
If you didn't do it, it's fine.
Why are you paying
so much attention to her?
Chanmi's my shooting coach after all.
Hello, Mr. Jo.
Oh! Our dear Ajung!
You're finally back at school.
-How have you been?
-Oh, good, good.
Ajung, how is everything going
with your debut?
-It's going pretty well, thanks to you.
-If you become a superstar one day...
...don't forget about me.
Oh, of course!
How could I ever forget about you, Mr. Jo?
Good, good. You should head to class.
I'll be on my way then.
Hey, Ajung.
You already know which class
you'll be joining, right?
Yes, I do.
-Head on up then.
-Yes.
Aw.
She's finally back at school. My oh my.
Oh.
What did Mr. Jo say to you?
"Ajung, don't forget about me
if you become a superstar one day."
Pft, what the heck?
What the...
Hey, Ajung!
Are you vomiting for real?
Ah...
Hey, are you vomiting for real?
Wow, this is crazy.
I can't believe you're so disgusted by him
that you're actually vomiting.
I was in the same class
as Wonseok last year.
Do you know who might've been
on bad terms with him?
I'm not sure.
Several students told us
that it might've been you.
That's not true.
I wasn't on bad terms with him.
Didn't you guys get into a bloody fight
first semester of last year?
Everyone seemed to know
since it was a big fight.
Yes, we did fight once.
But just because we had a fight
doesn't mean I killed him.
Why did you two fight?
It was early in the first semester
of junior year.
Park Wonseok came to me
and challenged me to fight him.
So I did.
You're the one
who first reported his death.
Why were you in the science lab building
while everyone else was gathered
at the recording studio in the auditorium?
I told the police
all about that last time.
I'm sorry.
I transferred here
after the incident occurred.
There's a stray cat that I feed every day.
And that day, I was opening a can
of cat food for her behind that building
when I heard something fall...
Oh, right. That cat.
So after hearing the thud,
you went over there,
and Park Wonseok was already lying there.
Yes.
Was there anyone else nearby?
I don't think so.
I didn't see anyone.
Who do you think
was Park Wonseok's best friend?
I believe it was Gi Osung.
Oh, come have a seat.
So, were there any human rights violation
or anything of the sort
during the police investigation?
No, not at all.
Good.
Stay focused on your studies
even though things
are chaotic here at school.
Yes, Mr. Gu.
Oh, also, why haven't you come by
for academic counseling?
Everyone else has already stopped by!
Oh, I...
Hey. Where do you think
you'll be a year from now?
A college campus,
or a remedial boarding school?
Back in the day, we studied all night
and didn't even go home.
Where will I be...
a year from now?
NEUNGHWA LIVING FACILITIES
How are your studies going?
Mom, whenever I come see you,
why don't you have anything else
to ask me about other than my studies?
Of course. You're a high school senior.
Mom, when do you think
you were the happiest?
Hmm, let's see, when was I the happiest...
Maybe it was when you started kindergarten
and your older brother
started elementary school.
What did you like best about that time?
The two of you.
Whenever I looked at the two of you...
...it always pulled at my heartstrings.
Because my kids were starting
new chapters in their lives.
Starting kindergarten
and starting elementary school.
Is raising a child all about
seeing them grow up,
seeing what they end up doing,
and seeing that process repeat
over and over?
Exactly.
My son, you're so smart.
Mom.
Come on,
why are you being like that again?
It's nothing.
Sooheon.
As your mom...
...I'm frustrated and heartbroken
that we've ended up like this, but...
as long as you're doing okay, Sooheon,
I'll be fine with it.
No matter what,
I just want you to be happy.
Do you understand what I mean,
my son?
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm going to be happy.
I'm sorry.
Mom, why are you crying?
Stop with the tears now, huh?
I'm fine.
REVENGE OF OTHERS
Sooheon!
Sooheon! Hey!
MMA, KICKBOXING, JIUJITSU,
MUY THAI, LOSING WEIGHT
Here.
Oh.
I just occurred to me
that I should thank you somehow.
You let me stay on the rooftop
even though
it might be inconvenient for you.
Anyway, for a lot of things, okay?
Drink this. Drink it up.
-Oh, should I open it for you?
-Chanmi.
-What is it you want to say?
-Huh?
It's about my brother.
I received a message
from my brother's adopted family.
They said I can come by
to pick up his things if I want to.
They haven't given you
any of his stuff until now?
I think they're feeling much better now
that they know his death wasn't a suicide.
What do you mean?
I don't really understand it either.
So... what I wanted to ask you was...
Do you think you could come with me
when I go over there
to pick up his things?
I just don't feel like
I can go there alone.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Thanks.
No problem.
You want to go now?
Yeah, now.
We were very surprised to learn
that someone had killed him.
We're even being investigated.
Well, at least now
we know he didn't commit
the grave sin of committing suicide.
So, Wonseok's soul
will be saved after all.
Amen.
By the way,
how did you know from the beginning
that he didn't commit suicide?
They're twins.
Don't twins have some sort of
spiritual connection or something?
Anyways, I'm just relieved
that it wasn't a suicide.
Is this his stuff?
We already took care of his clothes,
shoes, books, et cetera.
So this is the only thing that's left.
But it's locked,
so we have no idea what's inside.
It made us feel uneasy.
Not being able to get rid of it.
Now that it's in the hands
of his younger sister, it's all good.
I'll be off then.
You guys were the ones who killed Wonseok.
What? You're relieved
that it wasn't a suicide?
How could anyone stand to live
with a family like this?
He must've already been dead inside.
How could you
even call yourselves parents?
-Your child died!
-My god.
-How dare you, you little punk!
-Just stop, Sooheon. Let's go.
Shouldn't you be eager to find out
who killed your own child?
Shouldn't you want to see the face
of the person who killed your own child?
Even his younger sister is going through
all kinds of trouble to find the murderer!
Seriously, how can
you call yourselves parents?
Huh?!
Sooheon!
Let's just leave.
Please.
Do you know the passcode?
Should I bring some tools?
If it's not the passcode
that I think it is,
then let's break it open.
In that case, I'll bring the tools anyway.
My brother and I...
were abandoned on April Fool's Day.
During the Cherry Blossom Festival
at Jinhae.
We had always hoped that
what had happened to us
was just an April Fool's Day joke.
So the password my brother and I
always used was...
0401.
Since this passcode is only 3 digits...
It worked!
Wow.
He won this when he was in middle school.
We took this when we were
at the orphanage.
And this is the pistol I gave him.
These I bought every time I saw a star.
I gave these to him for his birthday.
It was his dream to study
in a military academy
and become a general one day.
Huh?
And this is...
evidence that he had secretly
been drinking alone?
But why whiskey?
I heard it's easier to buy
a bottle of whiskey
than it is to buy a bottle of soju.
You can always pretend
you're buying it as a gift.
Oh...
Sooheon.
Have you ever drunk before?
I know you probably won't believe me,
but no.
Believe it or not,
I've never had it before either.
Do you...
want to drink this together?
Cheers!
-Here, let me pour you another round.
-Again?
Ah, my brother was a real punk.
A high schooler secretly drinking whiskey.
He must've been going through a lot.
If people drank
every time things got tough for them,
every teenager in Korea
would be an alcoholic.
He must've been struggling.
You don't have to comfort me.
I already know he was a terrible person
and had a bad reputation as well.
I liked Wonseok though.
He was loyal
and manly.
Stop.
I don't need you to make me feel better.
It just makes me wonder...
Is that about all
that's left of someone after death?
What do you think
you'll be doing a year from now?
If nothing special happens to me,
I think I'll be a soldier by then.
A soldier? Just like Wonseok wanted?
Yeah.
I heard that being a parent is all about
seeing your child grow up,
then seeing what they end up doing,
and seeing what they do after that.
I'm gonna go to the restroom real quick.
You should get to school earlier.
And don't drink anymore.
It sucks to see someone cry
when they're drunk.
What's with you? That's the first thing
you say when you see me?
It seems Hong Ajung is back at school.
Can you tell her I want to see her?
I heard you and Park Wonseok were close.
And that you were
in some shooting club together.
But you do realize
your story lacks credibility, right?
What do you mean?
He told you I was his girlfriend?
When you were living all the way in Busan?
Yeah, um...
That's not true.
I wasn't his girlfriend.
What?
What do you mean?
How could I be his girlfriend
when we've never even kissed?
We were never together.
I have a real boyfriend.
That's why I'm telling you
that your story lacks credibility.
Wonseok lied his ass off to you.
Hold on.
Then, what's this?
Wow, he must've really tried his best
to fool you even showing you this.
I asked him for a favor one day.
I said, "Will you be my fake boyfriend?"
When I asked him, he said, "Okay!"
Well, I needed a fake boyfriend back then.
As you already know,
I was going to join a talent agency.
So in any case, Wonseok pretended to be
my boyfriend at school too.
LAST SUMMER
I went to Daebu Island with my girlfriend.
Wow, I can see hearts in your eyes.
You're so in love.
-Hey, hey!
-What else did you do with Hong Ajung?
-It's nothing. Ah, it's nothing.
-What? Show me.
Hey, why are you trying
to keep it to yourself?
-Show me, huh? Show me.
-No, it's nothing. You're making it shake!
-It's not shaking. Just show me! Come on.
-Uh, next time, next time.
Hey, stop, okay?
You...
Didn't you and Wonseok go
to Daebu Island together
and have grilled clams?
I would die if I ate shellfish.
My allergies are so fucking severe
it would kill me.
Jeez, I don't think
I can keep listening to this bullshit.
Was he in a relationship with himself?
Was he a pervert or what?
Hey.
Was that everything
you wanted to know about Wonseok?
Are we done here?
-You're incredible.
-What?
Didn't you already
have two servings of school lunch?
Did you give up on becoming an idol star
and switch to being a mukbang streamer?
Don't you usually prefer
butter and cheese?
You didn't use to like kimchi before...
I'm surprised too.
The mysteries of the human body.
I'm pregnant.
I'm twelve weeks pregnant.
You're crazy.
That wasn't funny at all.
Let's go.
Excuse me, how much is the total?
It's 21,000 Won.
Hey, are you really puking?
Are you being serious?
I'm serious.
Oh, my god!
Ah.
PREGNANCY JOURNAL
I took this at eight weeks.
I'm going for a check-up tomorrow,
and I'll have an ultrasound
since it's been 12 weeks.
-Are you really going to have the baby?
-Of course I will.
I have no other choice.
What about your life?
Does your mom know about this?
By the way, who's the father?
This is my life,
and nothing about that will change.
My mom knows about it too.
Who's the father?
I can't tell you that right now.
You're driving me crazy.
Are you going to keep coming to school?
Well, I came back to school
because it's safer after
the first 12 weeks have passed, but...
I don't think I'll be able to graduate,
don't you think?
I was thinking I'd drop out
after the summer break this year.
I see you're a planner.
What about the father?
Does he also want this baby?
Can he take responsibility for it?
We're going to take care of it together.
I have a close relationship
with the baby's father.
You're ridiculous.
Is there anything we can do to help?
This is my first time
with something like this.
You see? This is why I like Sooheon.
He's got the basics down.
He's really a decent human being.
Sooheon, I'll let you know
when I need help.
Please just keep this a secret.
Soyeon.
You can prepare a wig, some heavy makeup,
and an outfit tomorrow
so that you can pass as my older sister.
You're coming to the clinic
with me tomorrow.
Hold on.
Sejin.
How many hours did you practice yesterday?
Oh, yesterday I practiced
for about six hours.
Do you think that's enough?
You won't be able to get into a college
in the US if you don't give it your all.
Here. Don't stop here and slur your bow
to make it sound smooth.
Okay.
Let's try again.
HOW ARE THINGS GOING WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
SIX MONTHS AGO
STOP BEING SO NOSY.
THIS IS THE ONLY THING
THAT BRINGS ME JOY THESE DAYS
STOP BEING SO NOSY?
PLEASE HAVE MERCY ON ME.
COME ON, SEND ME A PHOTO.
CHANKYU
THE CAFÉ WE OFTEN VISIT.
OH THAT LOOKS DELICIOUS
DON'T YOU HAVE PICTURES
WITH YOUR FACES IN THEM???
THIS IS HOW
WE ALWAYS TAKE PICTURES.
May I take your order?
Oh, can I have a grapefruit ade?
Oh, also...
By any chance,
do you recognize this person?
Ah, I don't think so.
I recently inherited this café
from my older sister.
Oh.
That's Park Wonseok.
Oh, Sejin, do you know that person?
Welcome.
May I take your order?
Ah, I was in the same class
as Wonseok in sophomore year.
Our school's so far from here.
How did you end up
getting a part-time job here?
I take violin lessons over there.
I'm trying to get into a conservatory.
Um, I dropped out of Yongtan High
after finishing my junior year last year.
Oh, you dropped out.
I'm heading for the US next month
because I'm preparing to apply
to colleges in the US.
I see.
By the way,
what brings you all the way here?
-It's pretty far from school.
-Oh...
Well, Wonseok and I were in the same club,
so we would message each other often.
I remembered him telling me
that he used to come to this café often.
Seems like you and Wonseok
must have been close.
Especially if you made it a point
to come here yourself.
I also...
still think of Wonseok often.
He used to sit over there.
Since I'm still working here part-time,
I can't help but think of him.
You must have been
really close to Wonseok.
We were close.
He saved my life.
He was really a good person.
He was...
a good person?
Yeah.
Thanks to him,
I was able to stay in school.
TWO YEARS AGO, SPRING, SOPHOMORE YEAR
Hey, Sejin!
Bullseye.
Hey, is it true
you have two fathers at home?
Is that right? Or was it two mothers?
Huh?
If you have two male parents,
who's the father and who's the mother?
-Is the one with the beard the dad?
-Crazy bastard.
Shit.
Does something smell gay to you?
Oh, did the gayness rub off on you? Huh?
Oh, it looks like
you have egg on you. Here.
Well...
It's a long story, but...
I was adopted when I was five.
I don't even know
what my biological parents look like.
When I was a junior in 8th grade,
my parents divorced,
and my father came out
as gay.
Um, I do refer to him
as my younger dad, but in any case,
I live with two dads.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Oh, my Sejin.
You really worked up a sweat, huh?
It's time to take a shower.
Oh, I heard that gay people
wash themselves with milk. Is that true?
Here.
-Hey.
-Shit. Damn.
Ugh, something feels off, doesn't it?
Sejin, should we take our clothes off
so we can wash up properly?
Don't touch me, you fucker.
You fucking bastard,
you have a death wish...
-What are you doing, motherfucker?
-Hey!
Stop fucking around and get lost.
What the fuck is he saying?
Oh, are you guys a couple?
You motherfucker!
Well, shit! Hey!
Who do you think you are? Huh?
Okay, let's see what you got.
You little...
Fuck.
Let's go.
Okay.
The truth is...
there's something I haven't told you.
When I was eight years old,
I was adopted from an orphanage,
just like you.
I also have a twin sister.
She's the younger one.
She's still at the orphanage in Busan.
Oh, I see.
This is my sister, Ok Chanmi.
I'm really jealous
you have a younger sister.
-You're jealous?
-Yeah.
Really.
I think it'd be really cool.
Then let's all hang out together one day.
Sure, sounds good.
MOK JEONGHYEON OBSTETRICS & GYNECOLOGY
Come to think of it,
I think your boobs have gotten bigger.
Shut up.
Ms. Hong.
Please head to the doctor's office.
MOK JEONGHYEON OBSTETRICS & GYNECOLOGY
Excuse me.
-It's our turn.
-It won't take long.
DOCTOR'S OFFICE 1
MOK JEONGHYEON
How have you been?
How have you been feeling?
HEAD DOCTOR MOK JEONGHYEON
Why are you so surprised?
How can you be here?
I don't want to drag this on
for very long.
I heard you sued my parents while I was
in the juvenile detention center.
Drop the lawsuit.
Get out.
Get out right now.
I will, once I have your answer.
Will you drop the lawsuit?
Get out! Get out right now!
Get out before I call the police!
Get out! Get out!
Get out, you demon!
What the heck?
I'm sorry. Please hold on for a minute.
That's definitely Ju Hyeokgeon.
Huh? Do you know him?
I went to middle school with him.
His name is Ju Hyeokgeon.
There was a huge incident.
Doctor Mok! Please lean back.
Doctor! Doctor!
Jeez, do I have
to make another appointment?
What a mess.
That kid goes into the doctor's office
for a brief moment,
and then the doctor faints,
like what the...
Right.
The victim's mother was a doctor.
Oh, that's right!
The victim's mother was a doctor!
What?
The victim?
ORDER HERE
WE MAKE PEOPLE HAPPY
So, that guy back there
killed the doctor's daughter?
I think it was the second semester
of 8th grade.
Wow, I can't believe
it's already been over two years.
Wow, shit.
Then why is he walking the streets
like nothing happened
when he should be rotting in prison?
A minor never goes to prison.
A minor?
Damn.
The victim was stabbed to death.
Brutally.
So you mean...
the doctor's daughter
was murdered like that
when she was in middle school?
I think he was put on probation
or something,
even after he committed murder,
because he was a minor.
He was in a juvenile detention center
for a while and that was it for him.
So did you say
you're a friend of Sooheon's?
Oh, yes.
I'm the director at this gym.
Hello.
So, you'd like to register
for the beginner class?
Yes.
In that case, there's a promotion
that'll give you
a discount for six months.
That's a great deal for a student
on a budget.
Why don't we fill out a registration card
for the time being?
He can't register, director.
Why not?
He's a senior, so he's gotta study.
If you want to learn,
come after you've graduated.
I'll be right out after a quick shower.
Do you want to wait outside?
Sure.
Ugh, that idiot.
He's ruining things again, seriously.
What did I even like about him
to start training him
in the first place? God.
GOGO STADIUM
MMA, KICKBOXING, JIUJITSU,
MUY THAI, LOSING WEIGHT
Fuck.
Look at him.
Mister.
Are you a minor by any chance?
-I'm an adult.
-Okay.
-What?
-Mister.
Can you do me a favor
and buy me some cigarettes?
You insolent punks.
Get lost, jackass.
Why are you talking to me like that?
-Mister, come here, come here.
-Let's go, let's go.
-Hey.
-It won't take long, come on.
Let me go!
Hey!
Hey, that's Ji Sooheon.
-Leave.
-What's he doing here?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-Right?
-Damn, these bastards.
Man.
I could've handled them myself.
What are you doing here?
Woo!
Are you having fun?
Wow! So nice!
Hey, that was awesome!
You know, you're a great driver!
When did you start driving?
As you already know,
I can't really remember, but...
I heard I started driving here
since sophomore year.
My dad probably hooked me up
or something like that.
My body seems to remember how to drive.
Want to give it a try?
Me?
I don't even have a license,
and I've never driven before.
You drive a motorcycle, don't you?
But this is different, isn't it?
I'll ask if they can clear the track.
If you're the only one driving,
it should be just fine, right?
Okay, slowly lift your foot off.
That's right, good, good.
That's right.
Step on the middle one there.
There you go, left, right.
-Just slightly.
-Yeah.
Not too much pressure, easy.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
I think I'll be fine if I try again.
Yeah, d... don't step
on the break like that.
-Sorry.
-Oh, okay.
-Okay, should we go again?
-Okay, slowly...
You got it, right?
Don't hit the brakes so suddenly.
-Okay.
-Yeah? Now, step on the accelerator.
Good, good, good, good.
You're doing great. Let's go.
There you go!
Good, that's it.
Wow, keep going on like this!
Keep on, keep on, keep on!
That's great!
Hey, what was that?
That was awesome!
You're such a good driver.
Didn't I tell you you'd be a good driver?
It always feels nice
after a good ride like that.
Ah, yeah.
By the way, this car's really fast.
Thanks to you,
I really blew all my stress.
Let's come back again.
SHOPPING MALL ENTRANCE
JI SOOHEON
SOOHEON, COME UP TO THE ROOFTOP...
You didn't have to
drive me all the way up here.
-Are you working part-time here?
-Yeah.
You should come bowling sometime.
You know I got you covered.
You really helped me relieve some stress.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, not at all, it was nothing.
Let's go again when we have the chance.
-I'd love to.
-Okay, then. Take care.
Soyeon.
Did something good happen to you?
-You look excited.
-Well, yeah.
-You're not here to bowl, are you?
-Nope.
Oh, um, come up to the rooftop
after your shift.
We need to talk business.
Business?
There's another kid out there
that needs to be taught a lesson.
THE HITCHHIKER'S GUIDE TO THE GALAXY
YONGTAN HIGH SCHOOL LIBRARY
Mother.
Oh, Jaebum, you haven't had dinner, right?
I heard you went to the race track.
Mother.
Did anyone come inside my room
while I was taking a shower?
No.
No one went in there.
There's no one in this house
who would go inside your room.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing. I'll be there soon.
Hurry up, your father will be here soon.
Okay.
I never leave my key here.
Who is that?
A juvenile?
-A juvenile delinquent?
-Yeah.
He's a piece of shit.
6 HOURS AGO
How do you know my daughter Eunjin?
Dr. Mok, did Ju Hyeokgeon come
and visit you yesterday?
Who are you?
I've also experienced injustice in my life
just like you.
It was my younger sister.
Juvenile delinquents deserve
to be punished
to the fullest extent of their crimes.
No one who committed a planned,
brutal murder like that
should ever be forgiven.
TWO YEARS AND THREE MONTHS AGO
What?
Didn't I tell you not to come here?
Get lost.
Fucking bitch.
You fucking bitch!
You think you're all that, huh?
You arrogant bitch!
Didn't I say I'd kill you?
You thought I wouldn't do it? Fuck you!
Fuck!
He stabbed my Eunjin 20 times
just because she refused
to be his girlfriend.
Because she rejected him
in front of the other students.
Eunjin! Eunjin!
Then, as he threw
the knife on the floor, he said...
Ma'am,
report me to the police if you will.
I'm a minor anyway.
What?
That he wouldn't be punished
because he was a minor.
If you take care of this job,
that'll cover six months
of your mom's bills.
So I have to
make that bastard
kneel and apologize in front
of the mother who lost her daughter?
Let's figure out his route,
then decide when and where we'll do it.
Okay.
Ah, well...
This conversation was much shorter
than I thought it would be.
If you have something to tell me,
don't use your cell phone.
Leave me a note or tell me in person.
Don't forget.
I won't.
-Let's go.
-Oh, wait!
Also, this is something
I wanted to mention, but...
don't you think you were too harsh
on Sa Junggyeong last time?
Yeah.
I wasn't really thinking about it,
but somehow I ended up
going harder than I meant to.
I'll be more careful.
Oh, actually,
I'm fine with you punishing them harder.
It's just that if the situation escalates,
we'll have to deal with the police.
Sorry.
I'll be more careful.
I didn't mean like that.
When I lose my focus,
I prefer coffee to an energy drink.
How about you?
You should rest
when you're starting to lose focus, Osung.
The coffee's delicious.
-Huh?
-Hey!
Hey.
-Did you get home okay?
-Of course. What about you?
-Yeah.
-Ji Sooheon.
Do you want a cup of coffee?
Thank you for offering,
but I don't drink coffee.
Hey, Sooheon,
I have something to tell you.
-Hey, Osung, I'm going to head inside.
-What did you want to tell me?
What's this?
2022 PRO BASKETBALL LEAGUE
CHAMPIONS SERIES
Champions series
for pro basketball league?
-Champions series?
-It's in the first row.
Right behind the bench.
Wow, this is amazing.
Are you free tonight?
Me?
Can I really have this precious ticket?
Of course it's for you.
Am I dreaming?
It's tonight. Can you go?
Of course I'm going! Wow, damn.
Is this a VIP ticket?
I got it from someone I know.
I thought you might like basketball.
I'm a huge fan. How did you know?
I saw you playing.
- Don't forget your homework.
- Okay.
Hey, Osung.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Do you know who this guy is?
-Why?
-Hey, did you take notes?
- Yeah.
- I didn't take any.
Is this the one? That's so much text.
Why?
That's Park Wonseok.
Park Wonseok?
This guy is Park Wonseok?
LITERATURE
-Ah, welcome.
-How are you doing?
How can I help you today?
Please replace these wheels
with black ones.
-Okay, so, all of them?
-Yes.
Okay, got it.
-Hyeokgeon! Come here.
-Yes?
Go get us some coffee.
-Why don't we head inside?
-Sure.
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'll have two iced americanos, please.
Ah.
It looks like your father
has another customer.
Yes.
Your father must be happy
to have such a good son
who helps him with his business.
Hold on.
There.
Thank you.
Bye.
He's handsome.
Looks like he's the son
of the body shop owner.
Yeah.
I heard he left to study abroad
and then came back
because he struggled to adjust
or something like that.
I see.
It seems like he's chosen to work
with his father.
That's a great choice, really.
If you're going to study,
you've got to excel.
If you're just mediocre,
it won't make much of a difference.
You're right.
It's good to learn practical skills.
He's spending all his time
at the body shop, learning the trade.
He practices even after work
going home late at night.
He's a diligent kid.
MMA, KICKBOXING, JIUJITSU,
MUY THAI, LOSING WEIGHT
GOGO STADIUM
MMA CHAMPIONSHIP
Soyeon.
Did anything happen at school
while I was gone?
Wow, you didn't go...
I have Ju Hyeokgeon's route.
I think we can do it today.
Today?
Can we do it another day?
Why? Do you have another commitment?
I...
It's just... I have something today.
That bastard Ju Hyeokgeon is going
to be alone at a body shop tonight.
Tomorrow, he'll move to a dorm
to start at a mechanic school.
Today's our last chance.
What kind of appointment is it?
Can you just postpone it?
I'll postpone it.
Let's do it tonight.
I'll go ahead and prepare.
Ah, let me take your cellphone.
I'll wait somewhere far away
from the body shop.
Wait, let me just send
a text message really quickly.
- IT'S ME SOOHEON...
- (
I WON'T BE ABLE TO GO
TO THE GAME TONIGHT.
IT'S AN URGENT MATTER. I'M SO SORRY :(
This is the body shop
where Ju Hyeokgeon will be at.
He'll be there alone
after the business closes for the day.
And here's a transit pass you can use.
The person you dialed cannot be reached...
JI SOOHEON
Dad, is that you?
Who's there?
Ju Hyeokgeon. Nod if you're listening.
You know what with these tools,
I can modify your body like a car.
Do you catch my drift?
Nip a bit here, tuck a bit there.
Break this.
Cut that off. Isn't that right?
You brutally murdered Shim Eunjin,
a female classmate,
two years and three months ago.
You should end up just like her,
don't you think?
Maybe I can just stab you twenty times.
Wouldn't that be fair?
Spare me!
Spare you?
Please, spare my life.
I would if you were a minor.
But you aren't one anymore.
Spare my life.
Spare me. Forgive me.
These are words you should say
to Shim Eunjin's mother.
You got me?
This is your last warning.
Apologize to her
from the bottom of your heart.
Whether she forgives you or not,
you apologize to her.
As proof of your promise,
I'm going to take a few of your fingers.
Please! Spare me!
Please, please! Forgive me!
Did everything go okay last night?
Everything went well.
Okay.
Ah!
That bastard
will visit the hospital today
to apologize.
Bastards like that really deserve
to die though.
Good work.
DO NOT CROSS-POLICE LINE
UNDER INVESTIGATION
-What's going on?
-Sir, you're here.
Where? Where is it?
Over there.
What is this mess?
This way.