(waves crashing)
(birds chirping)
Ugh, you surprised me!
CHANMI (on phone): How about
this ocean view in the dead of winter?
Is this healing
at all for your rotten soul?
(chuckles)
The beach? At this time of year?
I'm so jealous.
WONSEOK (on phone): Don't you have
a match today or something?
Hey, think before you speak, will ya?
The opening ceremony
has to take place tomorrow
in order for the game to start.
Watch it! You can't disrespect me
like that. I'm older than you.
How about you win a gold medal this time
so you can hang it
around your older brother's neck?
Wonseok.
(laughs lightly)
Yeah?
Is this your death wish?
You were only born 10 minutes before me
and you think you'll be my older brother
for the rest of your life?
I mean, of course.
Nothing will ever change the fact
that I'm your older brother.
(laughs)
Fine!
(clears throat)
My older brother.
My older bro, older bro,
older bro, older bro!
-There. Are you satisfied?
-(soft chuckle)
Tomorrow I start winter vacation,
so I'll come down to Busan on Sunday.
I have something I need to tell you.
Something you need to tell me? What is it?
Uh...
(laughs lightly)
I'll tell you when we meet.
What is it? Tell me!
Are you really going to leave me hanging?
-Just give me a little clue.
-Oh...
What is it? Huh? What is it?
What is it?
Hey, hold on a second.
DATA STRUCTURE ZONE
Huh? What's that?
(waves crashing)
-(humming)
-(Wonseok groans)
(grunts)
Huh? What the...
(suspenseful music)
CALL ENDED
OK CHANKYU
(light ominous music)
REVENGE OF OTHERS
(singing)
♪ Let's go catch the stars, let's go ♪
♪ Following light far far away ♪
♪ Through darkness
Magic carpet ride Fly high! ♪
♪ To Paradise, ooh whoa ♪
♪ Beautiful stars rise, it's time♪
♪ Let's Catch the Stars! ♪
♪ A single drop of dawn light ♪
♪ Starlight bright necklace ♪
STUDENTS (groaning): What? What?
ANNOUNCE (on speaker):
For the first series, load.
(gun clanking)
(lively music)
2021 17TH PRESIDENTIAL SECURITY
SERVICE CUP NATIONAL PISTOL CHAMPIONSHIP
ANNOUNCER (on speaker): Attention.
(lively music continues)
(beeps)
(gunshot)
(gunshots)
ANNOUNCER (on speaker): Stop, Unload.
CASTER: Ok Chanmi
of Busan Su Yeong High School
is leading the game with five hits.
Lee Yunseon from Haegil High
is in 2nd place.
One-hit difference between them.
ANNOUNCER (in English):
For the next series, load.
Attention.
CHANMI (in Korean):
When I was a little girl...
My twin brother and I were abandoned
in Jinhae
where the cherry blossom festival is held.
Whenever I heard news about abandoned dogs
at tourist attractions
during the vacation season...
-It reminded me of my story.
-ANNOUNCER (in English) : Stop, Unload.
(in Korean)
The bronze medal has been decided.
The bronze medal goes to
Ok Chanmi of Busan Su Yeong High School.
(applause and cheering)
CHANMI: At least, I had my brother
when we were abandoned.
We were extremely close
as siblings.
HOST: Bronze medal winner,
Busan Suyeong High's Ok Chanmi.
(cheering)
HOST: Silver medal winner,
Choongbook Athlete High's Ha Sungmin.
CHANMI: I won 3rd place in the 25-meter
Pistol Championship.
I could've won
but I made a ridiculous mistake.
While shooting
I remembered the last call I had
with my twin brother.
HOST: Athletes, please stand. And bow.
Congratulations.
Okay, okay. One, two, three.
SU YEONG HIGH SCHOOL SHOOTING TEAM
Huh?
AHRIM: Chanmi, what are you doing?
I swear I had three bags,
but I'm missing one.
What's that you have on your shoulder?
Oh, god, how did that get there?
I think you're definitely
in the early stages of dementia.
(laughs)
(exclaims with excitement)
TASA SU YEONG HIGH SCHOOL SHOOTING TEAM
(hisses)
-Welcome.
-I caught this fresh today.
Enjoy your meal.
-Thank you.
-Let's have a drink!
I hope you sell out!
-WOMAN: It's so cheap.
-MAN: I know.
So fresh!
OK CHANKYU
AUTOMATED VOICE:
The number you're trying to reach...
What the heck?
It's been off for the past three days.
(exclaims with excitement)
-STUDENT 1: Definitely the beach.
-STUDENT 2: Yep.
(sighs)
STUDENT 3: I'm really scared.
(rattles)
(light music)
(cheering)
(light music continues)
KING KONG BOWLING
CUSTOMER 1: Nice!
Here you go.
Please let me know if they don't fit.
-Hope you have a wonderful time.
-CUSTOMER 2: Thank you.
Sir, can I leave at 4 o'clock today?
It's Saturday.
How could I possibly let you go at 4?
I already asked you a week ago
and you said you were okay with it.
You should have arranged
for someone to fill in for you.
Ugh, Gyeongseok suddenly decided
not to show up today. What the hell.
Hey, someone spilled a drink
in lane no. 3. Hurry up now.
-CUSTOMER 3: Oh, excuse me.
-That's okay. Did it spill on you?
-Oh, yes, yes, yes.
-CUSTOMER 4: It's okay though.
-Be careful.
-Sorry.
Thank you.
SOOHEON: Hey, Coach, this is urgent.
Can you please cover for me
at the bowling alley?
Like now.
COACH: SORRY, I CAN'T
(sighs)
Hey, Sooheon! Stuck pin in number five!
(grunts)
Okay.
(sighs)
(bowling pin rattles)
DEOKJUN: Oh, hey, Sooheon.
What? Why is everyone...
Coach, I thought you said
you couldn't come.
Well, you owe me one
since I'm doing you a favor.
-Right?
-(both laugh)
But coach,
I thought you said you were busy?
Coach?
How could you call our landlord?
I have to pay my debt to Sooheon.
Actually, he's my dance teacher.
(chuckles)
Ah, I see, I see.
Sergeant Park,
you didn't even read my text.
-I'm here now, aren't I? Man.
-(laughs)
But isn't this place
overcrowded with people?
I don't really know,
but the three of you should figure it out.
-Sorry. Thank you and sorry!
-Hey, hey!
-Hey, hey, wait!
-Sooheon!
Oh, he's just going to leave?
-(laughs)
-(sighs)
(light music)
-Hmm?
-(laughs lightly)
-Hi, how are you?
-Sooheon, you're here. How are you?
This is for you.
I thought I told you
not to bring me anything.
Is everything okay with my mom?
Of course. She's doing well.
I'm sorry to bring this up,
but your account balance
is starting to add up quite a bit.
I'm so sorry.
I'll make a deposit as soon as possible.
I'm sorry.
The management is even
talking about discharging your mom, so...
I'm sorry.
I'll wire the money as soon as I can.
-I'll go get your mother then.
-(laughs lightly)
My boy!
Mom!
You came.
-How have you been?
-Good.
(laughs lightly)
-Mom, you look pretty today.
-(scoffs)
-You look handsome too.
-(soft chuckle)
-I've always been handsome, Mom.
-(laughs lightly)
Are you doing well in school?
Of course. I'm doing well in school.
Mom, do you sleep well at night?
Mm-hmm.
You don't have to visit me
so often anymore. Focus on your studies.
(inhales deeply)
I can't focus on my studies
unless I see that you're doing okay.
(laughs lightly)
Do you think you can get
into a good university next year?
Next year?
(inhales deeply)
Of course, of course.
I'll attend a good university next year.
Don't worry, Mom.
(both chuckle lightly)
(inhales deeply)
(long beep)
(car horn beeping)
-WOMAN 1: Babe! Call the ambulance!
-MAN 1: What should we do? Oh, my god!
Don't touch him! Don't touch him!
Hurry up and call the ambulance!
-MAN 2: Are you okay?
-WOMAN 2: Are you okay? What should I do?
-MAN 3: What happened?
-WOMAN 2: Hey, are you okay?
WOMAN 1: Hey, hey!
HANSUNG ORPHANAGE
-CHANMI: Come in.
-(Yoonji laughs)
Ta-da!
(laughs)
It's so pretty!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
(quietly) Ah
-Chanmi, Thank you so much.
Girls, I'm giving one to each of you
so that you don't fight.
-Okay.
-It's late, so hurry and get to bed.
-Good night.
-Yep. Good night.
(breathes deeply)
(sighs)
(Wonseok groans)
What's this?
(children shouting in distance)
Ah...
Shoulder, shoulder, shoulder,
put your hands on...
On each other's shoulders. There you go.
-(laughs lightly)
-I'm gonna take the picture, now smile.
-One, two, three.
-(camera shutter clicks)
Oh, and tilt your head a little...
There you go, nice.
-(laughs)
-Smile, oh wow, so pretty today!
-One, two, three.
-(camera shutter clicks)
Now, can you smile a little wider?
Yes, yes, now put your heads together.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Smile a little wider. One, two, three!
(sighs)
Chanmi, Chankyu.
Shoulders, put your arms
around each other, right, smile.
Here goes the last shot.
Can you smile a bit wider?
One, two, three.
(laughs)
Good.
(sighs in relief)
Should we say bye now?
Hey, Chankyu.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye, Chanmi.
Why do you have so little energy?
Aren't you supposed to be a guy?
Didn't we agree not to be sad?
(sobs)
I'm not sad.
(laughs lightly)
I'll see you in the army when we grow up.
Yeah, see you in the army.
Chankyu, let's go now.
(dramatic music)
Thank you.
Jiwon.
(sobbing)
Let's go, Wonseok.
(sobbing continues)
(breathes carefully)
-Hey Chanmi.
-Yes?
Can you pick one for me?
Ah...
CHANMI: Umm...
-I think this one's the best.
-Oh, this one?
What do you girls think?
-I like it.
-Me too.
All right, then I'll put this
in a frame that is pretty as Chanmi.
-Thank you.
-Oh yeah!
(all laugh)
They are an interesting bunch,
aren't they?
Chanmi, isn't it crazy how much
they're just like you and your brother?
Asking for the same photo and everything?
Do you guys share
a twin connection or something?
(laughs)
Oh, Jiwon,
I'm planning to go to Seoul tomorrow.
Are you going to meet Chankyu there
for your break?
-Yes.
-Okay then.
(laughs lightly)
YONGTAN HIGH SCHOOL
Oh, excuse me.
Do you happen to know Ok Chankyu?
He's a junior here.
Ok Chankyu?
Do we have someone
by that name in our grade?
Ok Chankyu?
(breathes cluelessly)
I'm not sure.
Oh, okay.
Oh, oh, wait, hold on.
I meant Park Wonseok.
Do you know Park Wonseok?
Park Wonseok? You must know him, right?
Why do you ask?
It's just that I can't seem to reach him.
I was thinking
that if he had any close friends,
I could contact him through them.
I'm not a stalker or anything.
I really can't get ahold of him.
Park Wonseok
is dead.
What?
(dramatic music)
Why is Chankyu
de... dead?
(coughs)
(retches)
(telephone ringing)
Hello? This is Hanseong Orphanage.
Oh, Ok Chankyu?
Yes, of course. I know him well.
Chankyu used to live with us here.
Why do you ask?
What?
What, what did you just say?
Chankyu is...
dead?
BORN APR. 12, 2004
PARK WONSEOK
DIED DEC. 23, 2021
PASTOR: "Our Father, who art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive
those who trespass against us.
-Lead us not into temptation
-(sobs)
-(sniffles)
-But deliver us from evil
For thine is the kingdom, and the power,
and the glory, forever and ever, amen.
Amen."
(sniffles)
Yes.
(dramatic music)
(sobbing)
(sobbing continues)
SOONA: Thank you.
(Chanmi breathes heavily)
(sobs)
Are you his twin?
Yes?
(sighs)
Why are you only
just reaching out to me now?
(cries)
Why did my brother die?
Why did he commit suicide?
Young lady,
are you picking a fight with us?
Honey.
-(sniffles)
-Oh, Lord.
(sighs)
I had no idea you and Wonseok
were in touch.
While I was organizing Wonseok's things,
I saw the photo
that was taken of you guys in Busan.
So I called the nursery.
Yeah, Wonseok has never told us
that he kept in touch
with his twin sister, not even once.
(sighs)
That wasn't the only thing he was hiding.
He was seduced by the devil.
so he lived in sin.
Weren't you his parents?
How could you say about your dead son?
Don't you feel remorseful?
Do you not have any guilt?
If you have a bone to pick,
it should be directed at Wonseok.
-(sighs)
-Young lady.
Young lady.
Suicide
cannot be forgiven.
It's the worst sin.
We can't even pray to the saints
out of embarrassment!
(sniffles)
Are you even grieving at all?
How dare you!
(shaking)
(scoffs)
You ungrateful little...
-(clicks tongue)
-Let's go.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
Give me my brother's phone.
What?
-Give me the phone my brother was using.
-I don't have it.
-Ma'am!
-(grunts)
Give me the cellphone, give it to me!
(sobs)
Give me the cellphone now!
Hey, young lady!
How would we have the cell phone
if even the cops couldn't find it?
This brat has the nerve to show
no gratitude and cause a scene.
(sobbing)
Please, ma'am!
(breathes with incredulity)
Give me his cellphone, please.
-Father!
-I said give me the phone!
The cops couldn't even find it
at the scene!
(sighs)
(sniffles)
SPECIAL VICTIMS UNIT 1
END SCHOOL VIOLENCE NOW
(sighs)
Uh, excuse me.
This case has been closed.
Two days
before you were transferred, ma'am.
I know. I'm just watching it.
Ah, so I guess being transferred
to the Special Victims Unit
after having been
in the Gang Intelligence Unit
has you bored already. Yeah, I guess so.
Aren't you going out for lunch?
Ms. Jin.
Do vegetarians really hate meat?
I want to eat it, but I'm resisting.
I totally get people who love meat.
Ah, I see.
In that case, I'll go out for a kill
and come right back.
(sighs)
(breathes curiously)
Who is she?
Oh. She insisted on meeting
the case manager.
She said she is the younger sister
of the student involved
in the Yongtan High School suicide case.
Yongtan High School? Younger sister?
Yes, that's right.
(inhales deeply)
Shall we take a seat here and talk?
I'm the case manager. What's the matter?
It wasn't...
a suicide.
He didn't commit suicide.
He would never.
He would never commit suicide.
What? What's this?
Hey, Park Wonseok was an only child
who attended Yongtan High School
and committed suicide.
What do you mean
you're his younger sister? Who are you?
I'm his twin.
He was adopted
by his family when we were 8 years old.
My name is Ok Chanmi.
I'm currently living
in Hansung Orphanage in Busan.
His name was Ok Chankyu
before he was adopted.
If it wasn't a suicide,
are you saying
that someone killed your brother?
On that day,
we had a normal video call
and even had plans to meet.
It's common for someone's
final conversation to go that way.
Detective,
my brother...
He's not the type to decide
something like that by himself
and not say anything to me.
Definitely not.
He's not that type of person.
Suicide cases are often impulsive
rather than planned.
No.
My brother is not that type of person.
(inhales deeply)
Ah...
What is it?
Hey, hold on a second.
Someone else was there that day.
Then soon after,
the video chat suddenly ended.
It's that person who ended the call.
Anyone can come in and out of a classroom.
Just because the call ended
doesn't mean someone killed your brother.
Young lady, even his parents accepted
the results of the police investigation
and the case was determined
to be a suicide.
Then where is my brother's cell phone?
That other person took it.
The person that was there. They took it.
I can understand you're frustrated
by this situation.
Detective.
I know
my brother.
(sobbing)
He's not the type of person
who would commit suicide.
We have to catch the suspect.
What are the police doing about this?
You sit there and you say you know
what people are like,
and that you know how it all turned out.
Don't be like that.
A dead person can't do anything
about this...
Go find the murderer.
You need to find the murderer!
(machine beeping)
NEUROSURGEON JEON INSEON
(breathes deeply)
(knocking)
(door opens)
Hello.
INSEON: Have a seat.
How are you feeling?
Are you in any pain
or feeling any discomfort anywhere?
No, I'm fine.
Why did I faint?
Please come back in a week
with your guardian.
I don't have anyone who can come with me.
My mother is in a nursing home right now.
You said you're a senior
in high school, right?
Your teacher can come with you.
Okay.
(gulps)
(dramatic music)
Ok Chankyu.
There's no way you would have jumped
from this high up.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
(shaking breath)
Hello.
CUSTOMER: Hi.
Just a second.
-Enjoy your meal.
-Thank you.
(gasps)
WOOSUNG HOSPITAL
DEAR JI SOOHEON,
THIS IS WOOSUNG HOSPITAL
NEUROLOGICAL CENTER
WE ARE CONTACTING YOU
BECAUSE YOU DID NOT ATTEND
YOUR SCHEDULED APPOINTMENT.
PLEASE GIVE US A CALL.
(breathes tired)
I don't feel anything wrong though.
(sighs)
SHOOTING TEAM MEMBERS ONLY
SHOOTING RANGE
Huh?
It's not like I'm late.
Why isn't anyone here?
Good morning.
Chanmi, weren't you supposed
to go to Changwon?
Where?
The shooting team headed there at eight.
They already left on the bus.
-They said they were going to practice.
-I see...
-Have a good day.
-Oh, yes. You too.
(indistinct chatter)
(sighs)
Ahrim.
Don't feel bad for leaving me.
You have nothing to feel sorry about.
Why the hell did you suddenly say
you're moving to Seoul?
Hey, if you transfer now...
It'll be hard to get the score
in the group competition,
which will make it even harder
to get into college or get a job.
I get it.
I'm a traitor, right?
Why are you transferring as a senior,
you crazy fool?
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you doing this?
Come on. Get a grip!
BUSAN STATION
DEPARTURE TIME DESTINATION TRAIN TYPE
09:06 SEOUL KTX
(light music)
CHANMI: I'm transferring
to a school in Seoul
because I need to find
my brother's killer.
(breathes carefully)
(grunts)
(groans)
(gasps)
(grunts)
(shouts)
(groans)
(bell dings)
-MAN 1: What is going on?
-MAN 2: Why are you getting so worked up?
-Get him off, get him off!
-MAN 3: Stop, stop, stop!
-(Sooheon breathes roughly)
-MAN 4: Stop it! Stop it!
MAN 5: Stop it. Hey, why are you getting
so worked up? Huh?
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
I'm sorry.
(breathes deeply)
(scoffs)
-Sooheon.
-Yes?
Why are you hitting him so hard
when he has a competition
the day after tomorrow?
I'm sorry.
-(breathes heavily)
-Hey, Sooheon, let's have a serious talk.
You should become one of my players.
-I'll make you a champion.
-Oh. No, it's okay. I'm good.
I just want to focus on my studies.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You suck at studying,
but you're always rejecting me anyway.
-So arrogant.
-(laughs)
Come on, dammit. Just give it
some thought while you're showering, okay?
What? You think I'm only asking
'cause I have nothing better to do?
Damn.
MAN 6: Hit harder!
-There you go.
-MAN 7: Faster!
USED
NANO SCOOTER ELECTRIC SCOOTER ₩500,000
-Have you thought about it?
-(gasps)
Oh, hey, coach.
(sighs)
Do you really think the thief is going to
put a stolen scooter
on the second-hand market?
-It seems like he did?
-What?
See, this is mine. Look at this dent
and the scratch. They're the same as mine.
Wow, how ballsy. He actually put it up
for sale in this neighborhood.
(scoffs)
Co... Coach...
Can I borrow your bike?
Oh, uh, um, okay.
I sold the bike I was riding in Busan
for 300.000 won.
Could you give me a discount?
No negotiating.
I have a lot of buyers right now.
POST OFFICE
Here.
You can keep the chain. Safe driving.
Thank you.
(motorbike engine rumbles)
(sighs)
(sniffles)
Hello.
Hello, is this the dorm?
I called you earlier today.
It's going to take me around 20 minutes.
Yes, I know.
(sighs)
What?
-Sounds good, I will see you there.
-Is this the thief?
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, hey, stop right there.
Where do you think you're going?
Get off.
-What? Are you crazy?
-(scoffs)
Are you crazy? Get out of my way!
-I'll call the cops.
-Wow, this is my scooter.
Go ahead and open the storage box.
There's a skull sticker on it.
I just bought this with cash,
so now it's mine.
It's a stolen object so it's stolen goods.
You're a middleman for stolen goods.
-I mean, a middle woman.
-(scoffs)
That's some bullshit.
Hey, I just bought this with my money,
so it's mine.
If you feel like it's unfair,
go catch the thief.
If you bring me the money,
I'll give this back to you.
Words are not going to work with you.
Hey, let's call the cops then.
(car horn honking)
Please move your motorcycle!
Dammit.
Stay right here.
(clicks tongue)
(sighs)
Why is it not working?
Crap.
(engine revs)
CHUNGMA DORM
So you'll be staying from today.
Is this your only luggage?
The rest is being sent from Busan.
You're from Busan?
Yes, I'm transferring.
Transferring?
I thought you were a college student.
-I don't accept high school students.
-Oh...
Um... I'm a transfer,
college transfer student.
(sheepish laugh)
Yes.
I am a high school student.
I promise I'll be super quiet.
No one will know I'm here.
I won't make a peep
and all I'll do is sleep.
-Pretty please? I beg you.
-(sighs)
CHUNGMA DORM
(exhale)
Hey, what do you guys think you're doing?
(scoffs)
Selling the stolen item
and then stealing the same sold item?
Very creative, you conniving bastards.
Dammit!
(panting)
(grunts)
(grunting)
(groans)
You son of a bitch!
-Wait, wait!
-(shouts)
(groans)
Hey. Give me back the money
you made from selling my scooter.
(sneering)
I don't have it.
(groans)
I said I don't have it!
-Now.
-Okay, okay. I'll give it to you.
Ugh.
(groans)
(groans in pain)
(engine revs)
(Sooheon grunts)
(both sigh)
(gasps)
(both pant)
(groans in pain)
(sighs)
Have you ever heard
of the term "lifesaver"?
I'm the saver and you're the life.
Let's just call it even.
I bought the scooter with my own money
and you just got your life saved.
(sighs)
-Thank you for saving me from that but...
-You got the better end of the deal.
Hey, wipe that water off. It's cold.
(scoffs)
(sighs)
(light music)
YONGTAN HIGH SCHOOL
WELCOME FRESHMEN YONGTAN HIGH SCHOOL
FULLY-LOADED
CHUNGMA DORM
CHANMI: It's my first time
going to my brother's school.
(sighs)
I'm going to attend the same school
as his murderer.
(engine revs)
(light music)
(Chanmi groans)
(coughs)
(groaning continues)
(grunts)
(sighs)
You again?
Hey, don't you...
you just knocked over someone.
Uh...
Are you hurt?
(groans)
(grunts)
Would I get up if I were hurt?
JI SOOHEON
(sighs)
(sniffs)
Wow...
It smells terrible. What should I do?
I'm not hurt, so you should go.
Don't be surprised
if you see me at school.
It's my first day as a transfer.
(sniffles)
I said you can go.
(light music)
(sighs)
Pour.
Man, it's not coming off.
(sighs)
-Hey.
-Huh?
What?
LEFT TURN YIELD ON GREEN
JI SOOHEON
(light music)
(engine revs)
CAR HANDWASH YONGTAN CAR SERVICE
Why are you parking next to...
Hey, what are you doing?
This isn't a parking lot.
Excuse me? But...
He... I mean... he also parked here...
Oh!
-You're Sooheon's girlfriend, right?
-What?
You two must be very close,
wearing each other's jackets.
-Ah...
-Okay!
No, I mean...
(sighs)
(upbeat music)
-NARIN: I wonder what's for lunch today.
-Yeah.
Hey, look at that.
What's that? She's wearing a male uniform.
I think she's new. She's crazy.
-Hey, look! It's Ji Sooheon's name tag.
-(Narin gasps)
Isn't this big news?
What's gonna happen to Kook Jihyun?
(scoffs)
I know, right?
Excuse me, do you know
how can I get to the shooting range?
Huh?
You can go this way.
Or you can go that way.
What? Some brat's
wearing Sooheon's uniform?
I think she just transferred.
She transferred during senior year?
That's not the problem right now.
The problem is
that she's wearing Ji Sooheon's uniform.
What's that brat's name?
It was Sooheon's name tag,
so I couldn't tell what her name was.
I mean...
if she just transferred,
how can she already be...
so close to Sooheon?
Chanmi.
It was tough to get you on the team
so make sure you work hard
and devote yourself to school
-and athletics until you graduate.
-Yes, coach.
-Captain?
-Yes.
-Make sure you help her adjust.
-(laughs lightly)
-Take her to the office first.
-Yes.
Let's go.
PROCEED WITHOUT HESITATION
TOWARD THE WORLD, YONGTAN HIGH...
Chanmi, are you good at shooting?
Oh, yes, somewhat...
Aw, come on.
You must be good if you're an athlete.
(inhales deeply)
When I was in the army,
I was an artilleryman.
Ever heard of K9?
155mm Self-propelled artillery.
Boom!
(laughs)
Well, I guess that wasn't so funny.
(breathes silently)
(indistinct chatter)
Be quiet, quiet.
-(inhales deeply)
-Hey, that's her.
(whispering)
That's her! That's her!
All rise. Bow.
-Good morning.
-ALL: Good morning.
Let me introduce our transfer student.
As you can see,
Chanmi is a transfer student.
-Let's be good to her.
-Yes, sir.
-Chanmi, say hello.
-Ah...
I'm Ok Chanmi.
I am on the shooting team...
and I'm from Busan.
I don't know much about Seoul life
but I hope you'll be patient with me.
I look forward to getting to know you.
(applause)
Okay, Chanmi,
take a seat at the empty seat.
Good news.
Over the break, our very own Kook Jihyun
won the national essay contest.
A round of applause.
(applauds and exclaims)
Hey, Sooheon.
What happened to your uniform?
Did you sell it?
Do you like shaking things up in class?
I expect you to be on your best behavior
since you're a senior.
-What happened to your uniform?
-Uh, well...
-Here is Sooheon's uniform.
-Oh?
(all groan)
-STUDENT: What?
-NAKJUN: Why...
What the... why is... what is...
(all cheer)
-It's not true.
-STUDENT 2: They're dating!
What are you talking about?
Let's go!
What's going on?
(sighs)
JATAEK: Quiet, quiet, quiet!
Settle down now.
PRINCIPAL: Hello, welcome.
Hello, Principal.
Welcome, Jaebum.
I'm glad to see you again.
Ah.
-Hello.
Now, let's head in.
I'm Jaebum's teacher.
Jaebum said he's going to be
a senior again.
Since he made such a hard decision,
we'll do our best to assist him.
I had hoped he'd go straight to a college
in the United States
but this is what the doctors ordered,
so what else could we do?
Before the accident,
they said that going back to school
can bring back his memory.
So I guess we'll just have to trust them.
Jaebum also agreed.
-Osung will have to help him.
-Yes.
I've been close with Jaebum
for a long time, so no need to worry.
I'll help Jaebum with school,
and look after him
so that he doesn't have any difficulties.
(soft chuckle)
All right, Osung, I'll be counting on you.
Jaebum, if there's anything
Osung couldn't help you with
just let me know, okay?
(Principal laughs)
(sighing)
Oh, um...
I was supposed to graduate last year,
but I'm back as a senior.
Just think of me as one of your peers.
No need to treat me like an elder.
I would appreciate it if you just
treated me as a friendly classmate.
Nice to meet you all.
(applause, cheer)
All right. Shall we take attendance?
-Kang Younghun.
-Here.
-Gi Osung.
Okay, Kim Seojun.
-Kim Seojun?
-Here.
-Kim Eunyoung.
-Uh, Park Eunhye.
-Here.
Okay, Park Jimin.
I can see that you're here.
Jiwon is here.
-Bang Jinwon.
-Here.
Good.
(indistinct chatter)
CHANMI: Chankyu couldn't make it
to his senior year.
If he were alive,
he would still be walking down
this hallway with the name Park Wonseok.
(light music)
-Didn't mean to scare you.
-Didn't mean to get scared.
Let's go.
So you're not going to go to college?
I'm going to take
a marine officer test in the fall.
Oh, a soldier, I see.
If you get in, I guess that's
one less person to compete
against in terms of getting into college.
Hey, by any chance...
Yeah?
Did you know Park Wonseok?
Did you already hear
about Wonseok's death?
It must have been so shocking
for the people who were close to Wonseok.
If anyone were close to Wonseok,
it would be Hong Ajung.
She was his girlfriend.
Wow, she looks like a celebrity.
She's so pretty.
You happy?
What's her name?
Hong Ajung.
She's in my class this year,
but she didn't attend the first day
of school.
Can I have her number?
Phone number? You don't even know her.
Ah...
I heard she's a trainee
at an entertainment agency, right?
-I just want to ask her some questions.
-Yeah?
Okay, then.
I'll send you Hong Ajung's number.
Ah, sorry.
Where are you going?
The class is about start.
Shooting practice starts
during the 5th period.
-I'm off.
-Okay, then.
-Sooheon, where are you going?
-I got permission to leave early.
CAREER EXPLORATION CAMP
SEARCH
HONG AJUNG
Hello?
Why do people call then not say anything?
CALL
HONG AJUNG
What's wrong with this person?
What the...
Why does he have Hong Ajung's cellphone?
(light music)
(breathes quickly)
(breathes relieved)
WOOSUNG HOSPITAL
The hospital?
Huh?
(breathes seriously)
INSEON: Mr. Ji.
Good afternoon.
You're finally here after I told you
I'll be calling your school
if you refuse to visit me.
(sighs)
Is it okay for us to talk here
rather than in the treatment room?
Okay, then. Take a seat.
Were you in any pain
while you were away from the hospital?
(inhales deeply)
I've been fine.
Though I did feel
a little bit of pain once.
You didn't come to the hospital
because you didn't want to hear
about your results, right?
(inhales deeply)
Mr. Ji.
(sighs)
Since you said you don't have a guardian,
I have no other option
but to tell you directly.
(inhales deeply)
Mr. Ji, the reason
why you suddenly fainted is
because you have a brain tumor.
(breathes nervously)
Brain...
tumor?
Yes, and it's a very dangerous one.
(gasps)
So...
do I need surgery?
You can't have surgery.
The location of the tumor
makes the surgery very dangerous.
So...
(shaking)
...what's going to happen to me?
We can't do anything right now.
We just have to hope
the tumor doesn't grow.
Will I...
die early?
-(sighs deeply)
-Doctor.
Please tell me the truth.
How much longer do I have to live?
Six months.
Or up to a year.
It is possible that you can live longer
with this condition.
(sighs)
(somber music)
(engine revs)
(somber music continues)
(engine rumbles)
-Hey, Chanmi.
-Yes?
Is something up with Sooheon these days?
I haven't seen him around.
Uh...
I...
I have no idea.
-I'm going to go now.
-Oh, okay.
(light music)
(sighs)
(sniffles)
DANGER DO NOT ENTER
SCIENCE ROOM TEMPORARILY CLOSED
WONSEOK: Of course.
Nothing will ever change the fact
that I'm your older brother.
CHANMI: Fine!
(clears throat)
My older brother.
Older brother.
Older bro, older bro,
older bro, older bro!
-There. Are you satisfied?
-(scoffs)
Tomorrow I start winter vacation,
so I'll come down to Busan on Sunday.
I have something I need to tell you.
Something you need to tell me?
What is it?
Uh... I'll tell you when we meet.
Are you really going to leave me hanging?
Just give me a little clue.
-Oh, come on.
-Huh?
Hey, hold on a second.
(grunts)
Oh.
Did I scare you?
I didn't mean to.
Sorry.
Oh. No, it's okay. I'm good.
What are you doing here anyway?
You know, just...
-What about you?
-Oh.
I was reminded of this place
all of a sudden so I stopped by.
You know, before the break...
There was a kid
that committed suicide here.
He jumped off.
I was in the same class as him.
What...
do you mean you were reminded
of this place?
I thought of him today.
I wasn't close to him.
Park Wonseok.
But I saw him fall off
and I called the cops.
(closing theme music)