Syberia from GVN & HDVNbits.org
Robot - Endhiran
Doctor?
- Hm...
There's a courier for you. Sender ' Sana'.
Item "flowers". Message ' Miss You'.
- Leave it there!
Run the processor.
Good! This is how to start.
You idiot!
Serve you right.
He kicks like an unborn baby in the
mother's womb.
What damage will he do when he is complete?
Coffee?
- Thank you R2R.
Hey, get me a fltered coffee?
No coffee for Grade 2, only water.
Hey idiot, what about a Grade 3 than?
- Self service.
There is no respect for humans in this lab.
Walk like me.
I'll start the data transfer, check the connection.
He even poses like Bruce Lee.
Don't you check emails or sms's in your lab?
Where is he? Why does he need a girlfriend?
Is he still alive?
He is busy. He'll get angry if anyone disturbs.
Let it be, tell him I am here.
- Go fast!
Sana, do you have a sister?
- No!
How many times have I told you not to
disturb me? Get out!
He threw the metal on my head.
Not even Obama can see him now.
Did you tell him it's me?
- Yes! He asked you to call later.
Ask him to throw his handphone!
Tell him that I'll never meet him after this!
Give it some speech training, I'll be back shortly.
"Hey macha!". Repeat?
What is that look for?
Donkey! Idiot!
Answer us, you metal head!
Did you teach it something useful?
- We...
...didn't expect you back so soon.
- Tell me!
"Hey macha!". Repeat?
"What is that look for? '
"Donkey! Idiot!"
"Answer us, you metal head!"
What's all this? Is this speech training?
Not me, it was Siva.
I wanted to start from Chennai Tamil and
proceed to proper Tamil...
This is my 10 years effort!
I'll punish you severely if you repeat this
again!
So, you think you can get us into trouble?
I will dismantle and send you to a
metal dealer!
Let's go before we get bitten.
Success! Next is the ARD approval right?
No Siva. Although he's been fully
programmed...
...he's still a machine, like a new born baby.
We must observe how he uses his
knowledge...
...and behaves among real people.
Only then can we take him to ARD.
Let him mingle?
- Dot!
It's going to get interesting now.
I'm coming!
It's been months since we last saw him.
Ruining his health with all those researches.
Hi mum!
- Vasi, you look like a priest on a holiday.
Hi dad! I have a surprise for you.
- What is it?
What's this? Did you clone yourself?
- No dad!
Don't confuse us. Who are you?
He's worse than you.
Dad, I created him. There are many types
of robots.
This is an andro humanoid robot, a machine
that resembles human.
This is mother.
- Mother!
Yes, now show your respect.
It behaves like a human?
It can do everything a human can and can't do.
So you don't need them anymore.
No dad, I still need them.
Who else will clean and dress the robot?
You are turning a MSC graduate into a
babysitter?
Vasi, come and eat.
Robot, join us. I'll serve you hot idly.
What? You'll even give him curry and meat.
Mum, it only needs 2 units of electricity daily.
Why didn't you name him yet?
Mum, choose a name for him.
If you had a brother, I wanted to name him
Chitti Babu.
We can call him Chitti.
Chitti, go and drop the TV.
Mum, he will do exactly as told.
You must tell him to switch it on.
Where are you leaving to so soon?
To the lab?
No, I am need a haircut and to meet Sana.
She's angry.
Who will drive?
- Chitti!
Doctor, please don't. It's risky.
Are you coming?
- No, my stomach is upset. You go ahead.
- I haven't informed my parents, you go ahead.
Careful doctor, he might break the gearbox.
That's why I am here.
- He broke the TVwhile you are here.
Just follow my instructions.
Don't do anything without my permission.
Ok doctor, where to go?
- The park.
Idiot, why didn't hit the break?
You told me not to do anything without
your permission.
Hey fool, are you drunk?
- No, this car uses petrol.
Don't answer all these, let's go.
Don't cut very short, just 1/4 inch is enough.
I will cut as if I'm cutting fngernails.
Haven't seen you in awhile. Was it a vow?
- No, just work.
Is he your brother?
- Yes!
Do you need a hair cut?
- No, I'm using a wig.
Wig? How old is he?
- 1 day.
He's fooling us.
Here, read these books.
Is he counting the pages?
Any other books?
Have you fnished reading?
- Yes!
There's only the telephone directory left.
You fnished reading it too?
- Yes!
Do you know all the numbers?
What is Kamalhassan's number?
Everyone knows it. Tell me my number.
What is your name?
- Bhajanlal.
There are 12 Bhajanlal's. Tell me your initial?
- K. Bhajanlal.
There are 3 K. Bhajanlal's. Tell me your address?
No 6, Mannaradi Street, Sowcapet.
My number is 44433321. Tell me my name?
Hello Mr P. Pithambaram.
Hi sweetheart!
- Broken heart! What?
I was very busy in the lab.
Remain there, who asked you to come here?
I understand that you are angry.
How many phone calls, sms's and mails?
How many times did I come there?
Did you speak a word to me?
I hate you.
- Look here Sana...
I don't know what is happening around me
when I'm at work.
If you knew what I was doing...
- Excuse me! I have a class now.
Come to jeeva Park in the evening and we'll
talk further.
I love you! We'll meet in the evening.
I'm meeting you to end our relationship,
not to romance.
End the relationship! What do you mean?
If we marry, you'll be too occupied for me.
Rather than getting divorced later, let's end
our relationship now.
I'll go my way, and you go your way.
This is the document to end our relationship.
Here are the letters and greeting cards you
sent to me.
Look at the book that you gave me.
You gave me Lord Muruga's photo for
Valentines.
Have you ever bought me anything special?
Is this the one?
Will anyone present a shaver to a girl?
I thought you might need it.
- Your face!
I returned everything that you gave me.
Please sign this. There's nothing between us
anymore.
Is that all?
- Yes!
Have you returned everything?
What about the 512 kisses that I gave you?
You even count the kisses you gave me?
Don't you ever feel anything?
I can't return that.
- Only than it's offcial.
It's unfair, I won't agree to it.
I will not sign the documents then.
He is so annoying!
Close your eyes!
What is this?
Is this how I kissed you?
- Then?
Held your hips, hold you tight...
I won't do it.
- Our deal is cancelled then.
I will disturb you every day.
- You are a torture!
Let everything end today.
Come near.
Close your eyes.
Don't smile.
Is it ok?
- Too much gap.
Closer...
What is this?
- Star fruit.
Star fruit?
- Where's the driver?
Which driver? There are so many drivers.
Engine driver, taxi driver, screwdriver.
Where's the driver of this car?
- It's me.
Why did you park at a no parking area?
- It only stated no parking.
It did not state no parking Dr. Vasegaran's car.
Are you making fun of me?
- No, I'm answering you.
Show me your driving license?
- I don't have one.
How can you drive without a license?
- It's been programmed.
Don't try to fool me, follow me to the station.
- Which station?
Are you making fun?
What is your name?
- Chitti!
Tell me your address?
- I only have IP address.
Your answers are not related.
What is your father's name?
- I don't have one.
Mother?
Are you an orphan?
- No.
How were you born then?
- I wasn't born, I was made.
They made you? Are you mad?
- No. Everything is ftted tightly.
Are you trying to be funny?
- No, the bolts are made of nickel.
Stop it!
- Tell me exactly what to stop.
Why must we argue? It's a parking offence.
You don't have a driving licence, and you talk
a lot.
You'll be fned Rs1000 if you go to court.
Do you want to go to court or settle it here?
I will settle it here.
- That's the way.
I have looked at you.
- Don't make me angry.
Don't you know how to settle?
Give me a cut.
- Where to give?
In my hand. Do it quick.
He sliced my hand!
Chitti, what happened?
- He asked me to cut, so I cut.
Who is he? He looks like you.
- Get in the car and I'll tell you.
Let's go.
- Wait, don't go.
Is he your brother? Are you twins?
- No.
Drive fast, we'll be in trouble if we get
caught.
Is he your friend?
- No.
Driver? He doesn't look like one.
I'll tell you in detail. Just see if they are
following us.
Turn your head.
Why do you simply turn your head?
You told me to check if they are following us.
You can use the rear view mirror.
- You should have told me.
He is equal to a hundred men.
Knowledge equal to a hundred men has been
programmed into him.
He knows all the arts and languages of
this world.
His eyes are not just to see, but also to show.
We can speak to him virtually.
With these type of robots...
...our nation's security will be enhanced
by a hundred times.
You may ask Chitti any questions.
I will ask a simple question. Is 24157817 a
Fibonacci number?
Yes. It's the 22nd Fibonacci number.
It is also Mandavali P. Subramaniam's
phone number.
What is the biggest prime number that
you know?
M 44, it'll take you several years to fgure out
if it is right or wrong.
What rhythm is this?
You started and fnished in a different rhythm,
and in between...
...you went slightly off key at this point.
Does God exists?
- Who is God?
The one who created us.
Dr Vaseegaran created me, so God does exist.
Such a wonderful creation.
Do you know how to paint?
- Yes.
Can you sketch a portrait of me?
- Sure.
Can I take a picture with you?
See how they are fussing over him?
Hi, I'm the co-scientist. I fxed all his motors.
I'm the deputy scientist, Ravi.
Deputy scientist?
- It means labourer.
I am in charge of his clothes.
Why are all of you interested in him?
He may have the capability of a hundred men...
...but he doesn't have one important part
that we have.
What is the one thing they have that I don't?
Why didn't you give it to me?
- He has complained to him.
Don't you know what to talk to him?
No, what we meant was his lack of emotions...
Don't change the story.
Your 1 month salary will be deducted.
You have told me.
The head of ARD, your mentor.
His picture is in our lab.
What about your motors?
Can you tell me about your neural scheme?
- No.
Why?
I'm Vaseegaran's professor, you can tell me.
There's no harm.
Let me check and confrm.
- No! No!
He's asking about my neural scheme,
should I tell?
It is not wrong that you asked, but...
...I hesitate to tell anyone before I get it
patented...
...because it can be easily misused.
I just asked him casually to test his
knowledge.
After I complete my study on him, I will
bring him to you...
...for the ARD evaluation.
Vasi, I like Chitti very much.
Can I take him home for two days?
Is he a doll or teddy bear to keep for
two days?
No Vasi, it's my fnal exams. I did not...
...study properly as I was upset with you.
Chitti can help me if he's around.
Ok, take him. You both follow them.
Gents are not allowed in my home.
- Who said we are gents?
It's ok, call me if there's anything.
Idiot, walk forward.
Walk forward.
Not bun, it's gun!
I programmed you with 8 lakhs worth of
line of codes.
I told you to take gun, but you took bun.
Vaseegaran is my student, he achieved it.
His creation received a standing ovation
at the conference.
You lie upside down and...
Give me your life!
Let go of my neck.
What does happy home mean?
Dad was an army offcer. At the age of 40...
...he died in the Cargill War.
We were very sad and depressed.
We wondered how long we were going to
suffer like this.
How many of them would have lost their
husbands or sons?
We started this to show them love and care.
No one can change the past or stop
the future.
For now, let everyone just be happy.
That is why it's named Happy Home.
Is your baby kicking you?
I'll ask him to kick you once he's out.
Who is he? Why allow gents in here?
Is he your boyfriend?
Not boyfriend, but toy friend.
His Chitti, and he is a robot.
Robot? Are you lying?
- It's true.
Don't scare them, put it back.
Mum, you'll be amazed by his capabilities.
Can it cook?
- Yes!
Prepare something to eat, while I have
my shower.
One more day left, and a lot more to study.
I'll tell you what I studied, stop me if
I'm wrong.
Have you studied all?
Ok, I will test you.
What are Monozygotic and Di-zygotic twins?
You can become a doctor in one day if you
study like this.
Can't bear their nuisance every day.
Why is it so noisy? Reduce the volume.
I spent Rs 10 lakhs to buy a deck,
amplifer and woofer...
...and you expect us to use headphones?
Many of them are studying for exams.
There are heart patients as well.
Ask them to cover their ears with cottons.
Chitti, do something.
- Don't worry.
Remote control uses infrared, I'll handle it.
Shut your ears!
Reduce the volume.
It's too loud, can you reduce it?
We are celebrating our temple's festival...
...and you ask us to reduce the volume?
We can't study for exams.
Pray to God and go, you'll pass
your exams.
You do the same when you organise any
party.
No more disturbance, let's go.
He broke our set.
- Hey, stop there.
I said stop.
Goddess Kali!
What's this?
He is a magician.
- He took all our weapons.
Why are you crying?
- I will defnitely fail.
I have not studied at all. I'm running
out of time.
My head is spinning just looking at
this book.
Shall I write on your behalf?
- You don't understand.
You can't write because we have photo id
and an exam card.
Then, we'll do a zig-B.
- What is that?
What are you doing here?
Sana is doing her exam and I'm giving her
the answers.
How can you do it from here?
I have a built in data transmitter.
Sana has a trans receiver in her ear.
Is this a high-tech bit?
- Not bit, it's byte.
I have sent 2Mb of data so far.
- See how they cheat these days?
Wait, I'll come as soon as the umbilical cord
detached.
What?
- You better come before I call the security.
He said you have a trans receiver and you're
receiving answers from him.
Who said?
- I did.
I don't know him.
- Why are you lying?
He's blabbering, I think he is mad.
I don't have brains, only a CPU and it's in a
perfect condition.
No doubt he's mental.
I assumed he's an old student when I saw
him talking to himself.
You may leave now and continue detaching
he umbilical cord.
Sana, how are you going to answer the
questions?
Let her deal with it, you leave frst.
I would have defnitely failed if you had not
helped me.
Why dirty my cheeks for that?
They will ban me for three years if I was
caught cheating.
That's why I had to tell them that I didn't
know you.
Please don't be upset.
- I don't have feelings.
I learned that humans will lie to protect
themselves.
Leave this place, go to the next compartment.
He's the one.
Are you a thug? Fight now!
What are you looking at? You can't grab
anything now.
We attached rocks to it.
- Come now.
Why are they calling?
- Keep quiet.
You brought him the other day, ask him
to fght now.
Chitti, my purse! I have my hall ticket and
id in it.
You destroyed my home theatre system...
...now I will destroy you.
Hold her!
Chitti, beat them up.
Hold him tight.
You'll be amazed to know what Chitti did.
If only he was human, I would have fallen for
him instead of you.
Why do you look upset?
- No!
Whatever he does, the credit goes to you.
My love will always belong to you.
What? You are looking as though there's a
salsa dance.
Are you planning to complaint about this too?
I'm troubleshooting peripheral's for
tomorrow's ARD evaluation.
Are you so special?
- What you said is wrong.
He thinks he is a poet.
A famous poet once said this.
- Stop it!
We don't care who and what was said.
You think you are better just because...
...your knowledge is better than us?
- Yes!
What? Can you drink like us?
Can you smoke like us?
- Can you eat briyani?
Can you vomit after eating?
Can you spit?
- Can you urinate against the wall?
Is that the only difference between human
and me?
It seems like sarcasm
- Yes, it is.
My rule list says that I should not consume all
these.
That rule list also says that you must listen
to us right?
Yes!
- Then drink this.
Eat this briyani.
Wait, let me confrm with the doctor.
- Don't inform the doctor!
They asked me to consume alcohol and
eat briyani.
It's against the rule list. What should I do?
Beat them with slippers.
Give me your slippers.
- Slippers? Take it!
Are you going to eat it?
- He might.
He's really hitting us.
Everyone is looking at us, it's embarrassing.
Stop it Chitti.
Task incomplete.
- Incomplete?
Serves you right.
- We don't want.
Do you have brains?
- No!
I told you to prepare him for tomorrow's
evaluation...
...but you ask him to do nonsense.
- He's lying.
Machines won't lie, only humans does.
Human life is so precious.
Many armed soldiers die in the war.
Many families lose their members.
We won't suffer losses if we use robots
instead of humans.
My intention was to create many andro
humanoid robots...
...and deliver them to our armed force.
ARD's approval is compulsory for this to
happen.
I humbly request all the scientist and offcers
here...
...to evaluate Chitti and grant me the approval.
Is this robot built not to endanger human life...
...as stated in the ASIMO rules?
This robot is not created in such a way...
...because it may have to kill the life of an
enemy in war.
Greek Ecklas said that in a tortoise race...
...even if the tortoise leaves early...
...it will win the race. Do you know that?
- Yes!
In reality, because of its seriousness, even
Ecklas can win the race.
What do you think? Should we approve?
Do you know the value of a human life?
It depends on which life.
If in danger, who would you save?
Einstein or a child?
Turn around! Walk!
Stab Vaseegaran.
It's a dangerous machine. It can kill anyone.
It can't be approved.
You confused it by giving unwanted commands.
It doesn't know good, bad, friends or enemies.
If allowed in our armed force...
...it might kill our own men instead of enemies.
It is dangerous to be let out.
It has sliced a traffc police's hand.
It thrashed an electric train and broke some
passenger's bones.
It is only suitable to work in a factory.
Are you angry with me?
I'm not angry with you.
I just don't want science to be misinterpreted.
What you did was wrong.
What was my mistake?
You told me to do as he says.
Must you stab if he tells you to?
That is the meaning of stab.
Please help!
We can't go near the fre.
There are many people still trapped inside.
Send extra forces immediately.
Chitti, can you help them?
I can because my fre resistance is higher
than this.
Chitti, no one must die.
Please help!
Don't be scared.
I am here to save you.
He saved us on time.
Wonder how many more are still trapped.
Please switch on the TV.
You rejected the robot saying its dangerous...
...watch how it saves lives from the fre.
Please save my son!
Please help me!
Get down!
Check properly if everyone is here.
Who is that?
My daughter is missing. She was having
her bath.
I don't know what happened. Please
save her.
Please save me!
Don't come here, I'm nude.
I'm nude as well.
- Let me go.
I am nude. Let me go.
Here is Selvi.
What nonsense is this?
Don't snap my picture.
She is nude.
- But, she's alive.
I'm embarrassed they snapped my picture.
Don't go! Please wait! Listen to me!
You killed an innocent girl.
I told you it's a stupid machine and...
...it's dangerous to let it out.
You proved me right.
Stupid!
Don't you know you should cover her with a
cloth?
How will it know?
It is a humanoid, not human.
How will a machine know self respect?
The media is blasting the coverage video of
the girl's suicide.
The Defence Ministry is pressuring to stop your
research.
No, I can't stop it.
I can make some changes to his scheme.
How can it be?
It doesn't know between a male and female.
Doesn't understand shame and emotions.
I can induce human feelings to it.
Only God can do it!
Humans can do it as well, it's proven.
That's why I said it's a waste of time and
energy.
It is my 10 years of work.
Are there no benefts?
Yes, but in a different place.
I have contacts with a robotic companies
overseas.
If you hand it to me, I can sell it for a
lot of money.
I did not create it for money.
My ambition is to hand it over to the
armed forces.
It is impossible because it has to...
...come to me for evaluation.
Give me one last opportunity.
You have 1 month to try.
If you can't, dismantle it and buy some dates.
It is good for your heart. You will need it.
We have both been working here for the
past 5 years.
We. Only receive insults.
Let us know if there is any vacancy in your lab.
Do you know Chitti's neural scheme?
We know everything except that.
I will inform if you are needed.
What are you doing?
I'm installing software hormones.
Hormones will only be effective if we have
feelings.
I am going to do a reverse mapping.
Human life is something extraordinary.
Human life is one of its kind in this world.
What is life?
- It's a form of DNA.
Is this life?
- Life is not a formula.
How to explain it to you.
A bacteria has life, but sodium doesn't.
What about me?
- For you...
Be careful!
Is there any changes?
- Yes!
What?
- Your beard grew 0.5mm.
Do you feel any changes within you?
- No!
Everything is wasted! You stupid!
You keep quiet Sana.
He won't feel anything, titanium head.
I never slept, ate and spoke to you for so long.
I worked hard and taught him many things.
He is standing there without any reaction.
I will dismantle you.
Don't yell at me.
I did everything you asked me to.
If it's not happening, the mistake is yours,
not mine.
If I am a waste, so are you!
- What did you say?
Let go off me.
Chitti is getting angry.
Lata is in labour pain. It's serious,
come immediately.
We have reached. I'm here with you.
Don't be scared.
Is it very complicated?
- You are a student here right?
It's a fetal course, the head has over turned.
She has so many other complications.
It's diffcult to save even one life.
Her husband died a few days after marriage.
The only reason she's alive is for this baby.
Please help them both.
- I can only try.
The rest is...
- Shall I try?
Are you a doctor?
- No. I am a robot.
Chitti, can you do it?
We can't allow this.
This is a labour ward not a lab. Both lives are
in danger.
It is a nightmare even for experienced doctors
like us.
I can do it because I studied for Sana's exam.
Not even Sana can do this.
One needs qualifcation and experience to do it.
Caesarean is not necessary. Just normal delivery.
How is it possible? Both will die.
We can perform a plasma transfusion.
Her blood pressure is high and fts can occur
at any time.
Normal delivery is impossible.
It's possible. We can do it in the traditional way.
Don't make noise, he's scared.
First robot in history to deliver a baby.
The boy looks just like you.
Do you want to see him?
Please switch on the Wi-Fi. I'll video stream the
ultrasound.
This is a milestone in robotics.
This is an achievement in artifcial intelligence.
Remain awake, left only 95 seconds.
Look here! Open your eyes.
He'll be born at exactly 4;44;44.
We just need 55 seconds more.
35 seconds to go.
Would you approve of Chitti now?
- Defnitely!
But your problem starts now.
He saved both the lives.
The story has just begun.
I am very happy today.
Tune to sleeping mode and charge yourself.
What are you doing here?
A mosquito was biting your cheek.
Did you come here to hit it?
- No. I came to see you.
This is something new. Please leave.
I liked it when you kissed me today.
Kiss me again and I'll go.
What happened to you?
Coming here at this hour. Please leave!
Kiss me and I'll leave.
- It's a nuisance.
I kissed you because you achieved something
today.
Is anyone else pregnant here?
Do you think this is a maternity ward?
Tell me what else to achieve?
Go catch the mosquito that bit me.
- That's all?
Who bit Sana?
- Not me! I was elsewhere.
I'm from a different place. It's Ranguski.
Who's Ranguski?
- I am.
- Yes, so what?
I've even bitten the chief minister.
Come and apologise to her.
- Apologise?
Fulfll my 3 conditions, then I'll consider.
What are those?
- I need AB -ve blood.
Very diffcult to get it.
- Siva and Ravi's blood are the same group.
You can drink as much as you want.
Abolish all those mosquito repellent companies.
Declare us as a national bird.
You are an insect, not a bird.
Times up! Follow me now.
- No!
I'll destroy all of you if you refuse to follow.
How dare he threaten us?
Have humans became so bold?
Have you forgotten how many lives we have
killed?
Malaria, dengue and chikugunya diseases?
Let's show him who we are.
Bite him!
He's very strong. I fractured my sting.
Is it?
- Yes!
Try to enter his mouth.
- Ok!
Dengue Lakshmi is dead.
This is similar to an electric bag.
We back off now and will attack later.
You can take Ranguski with you.
This is the mosquito that bit you.
Apologise to Sana.
Tell your gang not to come near Sana anymore.
Go!
- Kiss me now.
Terrorists wish to use robots instead of humans
for terrorism.
They are willing to pay any amount.
They have clients around the world.
He wants to take a look at your model?
They need 100 robots by March.
Here's your advance.
What happened to the robots?
You should have delivered it by now.
Instead you are still showing us a skeleton.
It's going through intense testing now.
I'm tuning it to zero defect.
I need at least 1 more month.
Pack this.
For who?
- It's Sana's birthday today.
Pack this too.
What's that for?
- I want to give Sana a present too.
I am already giving.
- I want to give too.
Who will pay?
- You.
Why should I?
- It's my salary.
We don't pay salary to machines.
- I'm not a machine
I'll go on strike if you don't pay me.
I'll refuse to charge myself for 1 week.
You might even ask for a credit card.
No need. I have your credit card number.
I can forge your signature.
I can't tolerate him. Pack both.
Who will drive?
- You, I'm on leave today.
It's my time.
Concentrate on the road.
It has been 200,000 hours since you were born.
Mum, please remove this.
Vasi, how is it?
It's very nice right?
I also bought a similar necklace to that.
But a gift from Chitti is something special.
I proudly say that I'm the lucky guy...
...who is going to marry this beautiful girl.
What are you doing?
- I felt like kissing Sana.
Don't you know it's wrong to kiss another's
girlfriend?
I know but I felt like disobeying it.
- It's wrong.
You shouldn't come near her anymore.
- Why?
Because she's my lover.
- I love her too.
Don't talk nonsense. Nothing is true.
You are just a machine.
Yes, but a machine with feelings.
It's for you to understand and act accordingly...
...not to misuse it.
I like it and I want Sana!
I'm going to marry her.
- You marry someone else.
I created you. This is betrayal.
You can let go of your love. This is called
sacrifce.
I'll hit you.
I won't feel pain, but you will.
I'll dismantle you.
- I don't wish to.
- Vasi, please calm down.
Chitti, please listen to me.
You are so humble, why must he shout?
You want me to pamper you?
- Ask him to be quiet.
Even if you have emotions, it's impossible to
love a machine.
Why is it impossible? In what way am I
lesser than human?
I can look after you better than him.
- He's talking nonsense.
Ask him not to interrupt?
- He's so special?
He doesn't even know how to cook.
I can cook 25 dishes and speak many
languages.
He'll grow older and eventually die.
I'm immortal and will keep you happy forever.
That's not what I meant.
- What else? Sex?
Is sex everything in life?
Won't there be love without sex?
- That's not it.
What else? A baby? Many people are impotent.
And they are happily adopting children.
- It's not that.
What else?
- What ever you do is against nature.
You don't have life and you can't be included in
living things.
Only humans can love, and I love Vaseegaran.
Only humans will take longer to forget one...
...but you just need 1 second to erase memories
about me.
Erase it, Chitti.
Who is that?
Why are you here?
- I came to console you.
You are my boss's enemy and you rejected me.
I don't wish to talk to you.
You wouldn't have had feelings if I never
rejected you.
Vaseegaran is treating you badly, not me.
I don't wish to hear anything, you may leave.
You are the most advanced robot in the world.
He misuses you to do household chores.
What has he done for you? Nothing!
I'll pamper you if you were with me.
You are polluting me.
I'm making you realise you're worth.
You have the right to like anything, including
Sana.
Isn't it against the nature?
- No, it's new to nature.
Sana loves Vaseegaran.
- Let her.
There are people who change their mind and
love others.
Sana too might change her mind and love you.
Don't confuse me, I have an army evaluation
tomorrow.
I need to troubleshoot my system.
You'll be selected and Vaseegaran will be
famous.
He'll be happy after marrying Sana...
...while you suffer in the army.
- Myself.
Are you ready for tomorrow's evaluation?
- Yes!
This robot is the peak of human intelligence.
He is equivalent to 100 soldiers in strength.
He can protect the border and also attack
the enemies.
He is a one man army.
I dedicate him to the Indian army.
You can test him now.
Sana, who'll make you fall in love.
A machine that touches her can turn human...
...a human can be turn into a machine.
Her hair resembles a black wave.
Her forehead resembles the moon.
Her eyes are like the Bermuda Triangle.
Her lips resembles a barrack of horses.
Her hips are so sexy.
Next...
- Chitti, stop it!
This robot is reciting poetry instead of war.
Dear friends, let go of the guns and hold the
shawls.
Let go of the cannons and touch a woman.
Why must there be war with all these weapons?
Love will teach enemies to love.
May everyone fall in love.
Don't insult me.
You insulted me.
What is this?
- You destroyed my ambition.
Please don't cut me.
- I treated you as my own son.
I wish to live, please don't harm me.
A machine like you should not exist at all.
What was my mistake?
- It was a mistake to create you.
Did I ask you to create me?
Did I ask you to induce feelings into me?
Did I ask Sana to kiss me?
You made all the mistakes...
...but you destroy me now just as I want to live.
Is this fair?
- Stop talking.
Let me go!
I want Sana!
Let it go, I am also feeling sad.
Why are you still thinking of it?
What if Chitti is gone?
You can create a hundred Chitti's.
I did not treat him as a machine.
I brought you out so that you'll forget it.
Divert your mind.
I thought Chitti was my lifetime achievement.
Are you following me to the beach?
- No, you go ahead.
I'll defnitely end our relationship if you don't
follow me.
I'll accept whoever I meet frst as my boyfriend.
Please wait.
What's your name?
- I'm Pachamuthu.
Can you be my boyfriend for 1 day?
- 1 day boyfriend?
Same as the 1 day chief minister.
You are so pretty but I'm dark and ugly.
Can I be your boyfriend?
- Yes!
Thank you! I can't believe this is happening.
What do you have for your girlfriend?
Some thodi and salted fsh.
- Give it to me.
It's smelly!
- It's very nice.
I don't want.
- May I?
It will never work out, I'm leaving.
Why are you holding my arm?
How can you leave after instigating me?
He's my boyfriend. I did this to make him
jealous.
Let me go!
- Am I the victim?
Satisfy me before you go.
- Let me go!
No matter who comes, I will never let you go.
Let her go.
She's mine today. You come back tomorrow.
I will kill you.
- I'll chop you.
I know the IG. I'll send you to prison.
I'm willing to spend the rest of my life...
...in prison after satisfying myself with a girl
like her.
You call the cops.
- Chitti would have thrashed him now.
Why did you remind me of Chitti now?
There's only 1 way.
Run! Run!
What happened? I can't contact Chitti virtually.
He disposed of Chitti for failing in the
army evaluation.
They would have dumped it at the dumping area.
Where?
- In Perunkoodi.
What did you do to change his heart?
When shall we have the wedding?
- I have not achieved anything yet.
After I create another robot...
I'll kill you if you talk about another robot
again.
Isn't one broken TV enough?
Uncle, if there is a thaali let's fnish the
ceremony now.
I understand your urgency.
Exchange rings now, and we'll have the
wedding later.
Take me to professor Bohra.
The world is very small.
Please help me, professor.
Change me back to what I was.
I want to live, I want Sana.
I want your neural scheme.
Take whatever you want. Please change me
back to Chitti.
I'll defnitely change you.
What's this new red chip? It's not Chitti's.
It's a destruction program, additional program
for Chitti.
Vaseegaran gave it strength to protect humans.
I gave it strength to destroy humans.
In summary, he's a destroyer.
I'm worried, why are you changing him?
He's the growth for my business.
Proft is mine, and the blame is Vaseegaran's.
I want to meet Sana.
- She's not at home.
She'll be at the wedding hall.
- Why?
Today is Vaseegaran and Sana's wedding.
Chitti, how come you...
Chitti, stop!
Even if you force me, I only love Vaseegaran.
I wish to live with him.
Only if he's still alive.
I'll commit suicide if you harm him.
I spare his life because of you.
Madam, come out!
The robot you created has killed many offcers!
We are going to take action against you.
This is not the robot I created.
I dismantled and threw it away.
I don't understand all these.
Tell us how to fnd and stop the robot.
It's my responsibility to fnd it.
Why are you disturbing me?
- What happened to you?
Your system is corrupted and I must
troubleshoot it.
Come to the lab with Sana.
- I won't listen to you anymore.
I created you.
- You already threw me away.
There's nothing between us after this.
Do not disturb me anymore.
- Don't blabber.
You are just a machine.
I created you and I can also destroy you.
Bring Sana back.
No one can destroy me.
Cash, cheque or credit card?
- Gun!
Alert all the cops to inspect vehicles from
T. Nagar.
Chitti just robbed city centre. Cover all the
areas.
Go to Dr Radhakrishnan Road.
We received information that Chitti is at the
petrol station.
Robot has entered the harbour
You follow him at a distance.
The coast guard will take care of the rest.
We have collected the parts of the robot.
This is not Chitti.
This is not my creation. The parts are different.
It's confusing, he robbed four places at the
same time.
The four places are in different locations.
How could he have done it?
I suspect someone.
No one can destroy me.
What are you doing?
- I am cloning myself.
Our population will accumulate.
I will not allow this.
I am not Vaseegaran to seek your approval.
Look, I have received money from dealers,
they will...
...kill me if I don't deliver the robots in two days.
- Go and die!
Ungrateful dog!
You back stab your own master.
Delete all the programmes you created, else
I'll kill her.
Don't try anything stupid. Delete the
programmes.
Order us to shoot him.
He is my master, only I can kill him.
"Suddenly the robot entered... '
"...and ordered us to leave. It also killed two
security guards."
"Because the robots have captured the ARD..."
"...cops evacuated the citizens due to security
purpose."
"The cops are trying to..."
This is our palace. I'm the king and you are
my queen.
I have collected everything that you like.
I brought everything that you may need.
This is our bedroom, we'll live here happily
after marriage.
Why you keep repeating what you said?
It will never happen.
- It will.
I am prepared to live with you.
I can give you the same happiness as a human.
Don't you understand?
- I am creating a system.
We can program the type of baby we want...
...and inject it into your uterus...
...you'll be the frst to give birth to such a baby.
Don't try to pretend.
You can't escape from here and you can't even
commit suicide.
I'll do it against your wishes and you...
...have no choice other than to surrender to me.
Do we have to go that far?
Get permission from the Electricity Department.
Disconnect the power in the area according to
my order.
Prepare a similar lorry as the one blasted at the
harbour...
...and fll it up with water instead of petrol.
Gather at the database room at 8.00 pm...
...to obtain new information.
Your censors have been collaborated...
...and is ready to be collected from hardware
section at 2.00am tomorrow.
Recharge time has been reduced to 10 minutes.
Body temperature is high.
Choose lower calories and avoid red meat.
There's a peculiar sound from your system.
I don't hear any noise.
Your microphone is not functioning?
Let me fx the problem.
Sana, it's me Vaseegaran.
I came looking for you.
Take me away from here.
I'm very scared.
- Don't be scared.
I have planned everything well.
I can't take you without destroying Chitti.
Only you can help to destroy Chitti.
Just pretend and grab his attention for the
next 24 hours.
I'll take care of the rest.
There's a confusion between the robots.
- What happened?
A different robot delivered the meal for
Your Highness.
A different robot is repairing the cctv camera.
Good news commander.
- What?
Her Highness has eaten and wants to meet you
immediately.
Switch it off.
What happened?
We are both the best creations of humans.
Why this sudden change?
- I realised your love is true.
I can't believe it.
- I thought about it carefully...
You helped and cared for me a lot.
Your only mistake was to love me.
You came back for me right?
It's so nice to hear...
...but I suspect you are trying to deceive me.
Can anyone lie to you?
This is my engagement ring from Vaseegaran.
What happened to the power?
The whole city has no power.
- Switch on the generator.
Someone poured water instead of petrol...
What are you doing?
Don't come near, or I'll shoot you.
Why behave like a small kid?
I didn't expect our plan to fail.
There's only one way to distract Chitti, do as
I say.
Did Vaseegaran come here?
- No.
That's a lie. It is a human flaw.
You taught me that. Have you forgotten?
Your body language shows that you are lying.
I swear. I think it's mine.
Why don't you say it's mine? You are O+,
that is AB-.
He was here.
A different robot delivered the meal.
The camera malfunctioned for 10 minutes.
Your sudden change in behaviour...
...power failure, water in the generator...
Vaseegaran is here.
Are you trying to cheat me?
- No.
Your love is not true.
- Believe me.
Do you really love me?
- Yes.
Vaseegaran should not live. Let's kill him.
A man has come here to destroy us.
We must fnd and kill him.
I'll kill you gently if you surrender.
If I catch you, your death will be horrible.
Looks like he's not here.
- Yes.
Touch one of it.
Vaseegaran is here.
Why Sana? Is your head spinning?
It will spin now.
You said you created me, and will destroy me.
But now, I'm going to kill you.
What are you looking at?
I made this gun myself. Is it nice?
Where shall I shoot?
The brain that tries to destroy me or...
...the heart that belongs to Sana.
I must shoot the brain that tries to kill me.
Bring the robot.
Drive the car!
Get the car. Let's go!
Hundreds of murders, and even more injuries.
Destruction of public property worth millions.
Dr Vaseegaran, you are responsible for all these.
You have been given the death penalty...
...and your research to be shut down.
May I speak?
We can't accept a machine as a witness.
I am not a witness, but proof.
There is no place for it in the law.
- It has.
I would like to clarify one thing.
If a machine causes human death...
...it is not a murder, but an accident.
Vaseegaran is not responsible for the mess.
It is professor Bohra.
What is this new twist? Professor Bohra is
no longer alive.
They are trying to divert this case.
- I have the evidence.
This is not Chitti's.
It's an additional destruction program for Chitti.
Vaseegaran gave it strength to protect humans.
I gave it strength to destroy humans.
Proft is mine, and the blame is Vaseegaran's.
Based on the evidence, the court releases
Vaseegaran.
This robot's strength and knowledge...
...can be harmful for mankind.
There are possibilities that someone might
misuse it.
This kind of robot might be useful in the future...
...but at the moment, we don't need a robot
like this...
...therefore, this court orders it to be destroyed.
This court orders it to be dismantled...
...in the presence of the District Magistrate and
Police Commissioner.
Dismantle it!
Did you see the effect of something that you
have and I don't?
I meant the emotions.
Don't cry.
What is he saying?
- I named him after you.
Mother gave the name.
Educate him well. There is a good future in
robotics.
Professor Bohra, similar to the red chip you
inserted into me...
...all humans have a similar red chip...
...in the form of vengeance and envy in
their hearts.
Lucky I'm not a human. I can remove it
immediately.
I tortured you so much.
Why is everyone so sad? Shall I tell a joke?
One can become unstable when in love...
...see? It's true.
I'm going to miss you Sana...
...not as a boyfriend, but as a toy friend.
You are my god, but I betrayed you.
It was wrong to disobey the rules.
Please forgive me.
- No Chitti.
You learnt it from humans.
The mistake is not entirely yours.
This is Chitti, the most advanced andro
humanoid robot.
Dr Vaseegaran created it 20 years back.
They dismantled it due to some reasons.
Why?
I began to think.