Man: That's it.
(Man coughing)
(Thunder rumbling)
The tide's against us.
Aye, but we have the wind.
She'll blow us straight to the gates.
Matthos: You're coming home.
Davos: King's landing hasn't been home
for 20 years.
I spent most of my life
dodging the royal fleet.
And now I'm sailing right at them.
This is the royal fleet.
And you're not a smuggler anymore,
you're the high captain.
Of course, there are...
Several royal fleets at the moment.
Not after tonight.
When the sun rises,
Stannis will sit on the iron throne
and you will be his hand.
- Gods be good.
- God.
Father, there is only one
and he watches over us.
- But not over them?
- Over all of us.
The people of king's landing did not
choose the false king, Joffrey Baratheon.
They will be glad to
see his head on a spike.
Well, first, we have to put it there.
Our ships outnumber theirs 10-to-1.
Our army outnumber theirs 5-to-1.
Those walls have never been breached,
and the men guarding the walls,
when they see you,
they don't see a liberator,
they see a stranger come
to set their city on fire.
I have faith in the lord of light.
I have faith in our cause.
And I have faith in my captain.
(Thunder rumbling)
Are you afraid, my lion?
If the city falls, Stannis will
burn every Lannister he can find.
Of course I'm afraid.
I won't let them hurt you.
I'm a Lannister.
I don't have a choice in all this.
But it's not your war.
It is now.
You can't fuck your way out of everything.
I have so far.
Do you remember what you said
when you met me in your tent?
That I should make love to you
like it was your last day on this earth.
Pycelle: As you know, your grace,
it is not only the sworn duty of a maester
to carry out the wishes
of the house he serves,
but also to offer guidance
and counsel in times of war.
Your words are always wise and measured.
- If you could...
- If anything,
a maester's duties become more urgent
in times of war and turmoil.
I remember back in the days of king...
You brought me something?
Yes.
Essence of nightshade
is as dangerous as it is efficacious.
A single drop in a cup of wine
suffices to soothe ragged nerves.
Three drops will bring on
a deep and dreamless sleep.
Ten drops, however...
I know what ten drops will bring.
Your grace, if I may ask...
You may not.
You must have a lot of work to do.
I'm sure many brave men
will need your wisdom soon.
Yes. A siege is very...
Be careful on the stairs, grand maester.
There are so many.
Your grace.
Men: (Singing) And so he spoke
that lord of castamere
but now the rains weep o'er his halls
with no one there to hear
yes, now the rains weep o'er his halls
and not a soul to hear
- good boys!
- Lannisters!
Where'd you learn the Lannister song?
- Drunk lannisters.
- (All laughing)
You've got a pretty voice.
Thank you very much.
And I like your nose.
How many times you break it?
Well, now let's see.
First time, I was five.
- My mam smacked me with an iron poker.
- Oh.
It wasn't me she was aiming at.
She was trying for my little brother.
Now he was a real pest.
Second time, I was nine.
Got in a scrap with a few older boys.
They won.
Third time...
Eh, you don't want to know
about the third time.
Poornose.
Don't feel sorry for him.
He'll be halfway up your arse
before the night's through.
(Laughing)
Welcome, friends.
This round's on me.
I don't think he likes me.
You think you're a hard man?
(Chuckles)
I know it.
(Men laughing)
It's warm in here.
We've got beautiful women
and good brown ale.
Plenty for everyone.
And all you want
is to put one of us in the cold ground
with no women to keep us company.
Oh, there's women in the ground.
I put some there myself.
So have you.
You like fucking and drinking
and singing.
But killing,
killing's the thing you love.
You're just like me.
Only smaller.
And quicker.
Eh? (Chuckles)
Your lord imp's going to miss you.
I expect he will someday.
(Bells tolling)
Man: Here we are.
(All chatting)
One more drink before the war?
Shall we?
I've always hated the bells.
They ring for horror.
A dead king, a city under siege.
- A wedding.
- Exactly.
Podrick, is that it?
"Is that it?" Nice touch.
As if you don't know the name
of every boy in town.
I'm not entirely sure
what you're suggesting.
I'm entirely sure you're entirely sure
what I'm suggesting.
Do you trust him?
Oddly enough, I do.
Good.
The map you asked for.
There must be 20 miles of tunnels
beneath the city.
Closer to 50.
The targaryens built this city
to withstand a siege
and to provide escape if necessary.
I'm not escaping.
Strange as it sounds,
I'm the captain of the ship,
and if the ship goes down, I go with her.
That is good to hear.
Though I'm sure many captains say the same
while their ship is afloat.
You look well suited for battle, my lord.
Well, I'm not.
For all our sakes, I hope you are wrong.
My little birds tell me
that Stannis Baratheon has taken up
with a red priestess from asshai.
What of it?
You don't believe in
the old powers, my lord?
Blood spells, curses, shape-shifting.
What do you think?
I think you believe in what you see
and in what those you trust have seen.
You probably don't entirely trust me.
Mmm, don't take it personally.
I don't entirely trust myself.
And yet I have seen things
and heard things,
things you have not,
things I wish I had not.
I don't believe I've ever told you
how I was cut.
No, I don't believe you have.
One day, I will.
The dark arts have
provided lord Stannis with his armies
and paved his path to our door.
For a man in service to such powers
to sit on the iron throne,
I can think of nothing worse.
And tonight,
I believe you are the only man
who can stop him.
(Tolling continues)
They're welcoming the new king.
I've never known bells to mean surrender.
They want to play
music with us? Let's play.
- Drums.
- Drums!
(Men shouting)
Tyrion: Remember, wait till the ships...
Bronn: The ships are in the bay.
- They must be far enough in...
- I know what "in" means.
- Do you know how to use that?
- I chopped wood once.
No, I watched my brother chopping wood.
I saw you kill a man with a shield.
You'll be unstoppable with an ax.
- Don't get killed.
- Nor you, my friend.
- Oh, are we friends now?
- Of course we are.
Just because I pay you for your services
doesn't diminish our friendship.
Enhances it, really.
Oh! "Enhances." Fancy word for a sellsword.
Been spending time with fancy folks.
Lady sansa and Sheila.
- Shae.
- Shae, yes.
Surely my sister has asked you to join the
other highborn ladies in maegor's holdfast.
She has, my lord, but king
Joffrey sent for me to see him off.
Sansa.
Always been a great romantic, my nephew.
Joffrey: Sansa, come here.
I will pray for your safe return, my lord.
- Will you?
- Just as I pray for the king's.
Stay safe, my lady.
And you, my lion.
Your king rides forth to battle.
You should see him off with a kiss.
My new blade.
Hearteater, I've named it.
Kiss it.
You'll kiss it again when I return
and taste my uncle's blood.
Will you slay him yourself?
If Stannis is fool enough to come near me.
So you'll be outside the gates
fighting in the vanguard?
A king doesn't discuss battle plans
with stupid girls.
I'm sorry, your grace.
You're right, I'm stupid.
Of course you'll be in the vanguard.
They say my brother robb always goes
where the fighting is thickest.
And he is only a pretender.
Your brother's turn will come.
Then you can lick his blood
off hearteater, too.
Some of those boys will never come back.
Joffrey will.
- The worst ones always live.
- Shh.
Come, my lady.
(Men shouting)
(Distant drums beating)
Where's our fleet?
On the way.
Why isn't it here now? They're coming.
Hound, tell the hand
that his king has asked him a question.
The king has asked you a question.
Ser lancel, tell the hound to tell the king
that the hand is extremely busy.
The hand of the king would like me
to tell you to tell the king...
If I tell the hound to cut you in half,
he'll do it without a second thought.
That would make me the quarterman.
It just doesn't have the same ring to it.
Cut me in half and I won't be
able to give the signal.
No signal, no plan.
No plan and Stannis Baratheon
sacks this city, takes the iron throne,
puts your pinched little head
atop a gate somewhere.
It might be quite amusing,
except that my head would be up there, too.
I've never much liked my head,
but I don't want to
see it removed just yet.
Where are their ships?
It was wise to attack at night.
We took them by surprise.
Lord varys knows what you had
for breakfast three days ago.
There are no surprises here.
If it's true there is
dissension in their ranks,
maybe their sailors have mutinied.
Maybe.
(Drumming continues)
(Baby crying)
I don't know why she wants me here.
She's always saying how stupid I am.
She hates me.
Maybe she hates you less than
she hates everyone else.
I doubt it.
Maybe she's jealous of you.
Why would she be jealous?
Sansa.
I was wondering where
our little dove had flown.
You look pale, child.
Is your red flower still blooming?
Yes.
Fitting, isn't it?
The men will bleed out there
and you will bleed in here.
Pour lady sansa some wine.
I'm not thirsty, your grace.
So? I didn't offer you water.
What's he doing here?
Ser ilyn?
He's here to defend us.
When the axes smash down those doors,
you may be glad to have him.
But we have guards to defend us.
Guards we have paid.
Should the city fall,
they'll be the first ones out of the doors.
(Door opening)
The lads caught a groom and two maids
trying to sneak away
with a stolen horse and some gold cups.
The battle's first traitors.
Have ser ilyn see to them.
Put their heads on spikes
outside the stables as a warning.
The only way to keep the small folk loyal
is to make certain they fear you
more than they do the enemy.
Remember that if you ever
hope to become a queen.
(Door closing)
You said he was here to protect us.
He is.
Traitors are a danger to us all.
More wine.
- (Distant drums beating)
- (Men shouting)
There they are.
- Archers to their marks.
- Archers, to your marks!
Archers!
Nock your arrows!
Man: Nock arrows!
- Hold fast.
- Man 1: Hold fast!
What are you doing? We need to attack them.
- Hold fast.
- Man 2: Boulders ready!
Man 1: Hold fast!
There's only one ship.
Where are the rest of them?
Archers, stand to!
Man the below!
- Nock.
- Man 3: Nock and set!
Draw!
Hold.
Man 3: Hold.
There's no one on board.
Man 4: More rocks coming up!
Man 3: Hold.
Wildfire.
Steer clear! Steer clear!
Matthos! Get down!
(Men screaming)
(Men wailing)
(Groans)
- Prepare to land.
- Your grace.
Stannis: The dwarf
has played his little trick.
- The wildfire.
- He can only play it once.
We're too far from the gates.
The fire, their archers...
Hundreds will die.
Thousands.
Come with me and take this city!
(Cheering)
Sansa, come here, little dove.
My queen.
What are you doing?
Praying.
You're perfect, aren't you?
What are you praying for?
For the gods to have mercy on us all.
On all of us?
- Yes, your grace.
- Even me?
Of course, your grace.
Even Joffrey?
- Joffrey is my...
- Oh, shut up, you little fool.
Praying to the gods
to have mercy on us all.
The gods have no mercy.
That's why they're gods.
My father told me that
when he caught me praying.
My mother had just died, you see.
I didn't really understand
the concept of death, the finality of it.
I thought that if I prayed very, very hard,
the gods would return my mother to me.
I was four.
Your father doesn't believe in the gods?
He believes in them,
he just doesn't like them very much.
One for her.
Here.
Sit.
Drink.
Not like that. Drink, girl.
I should have been born a man.
I'd rather face a thousand swords
than be shut up inside
with this flock of frightened hens.
They are your guests under your protection.
You asked them here.
It was expected of me,
as it will be of you
if you ever become Joffrey's queen.
If my wretched brother
should somehow prevail,
these hens will return to their cocks
and crow of how my courage inspired them,
lifted their spirits.
And if the city should fall?
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
The red keep should hold for a time,
long enough for me to go to the walls
and yield to lord Stannis in person.
If it were anyone else outside those gates,
I might have hoped for a private audience,
but this is Stannis Baratheon.
I'd have a better chance
of seducing his horse.
Have I shocked you, little dove?
Tears aren't a woman's only weapon.
The best one's between your legs.
Learn how to use it. Drink.
Do you have any notion of what happens
when a city is sacked?
No, you wouldn't, would you?
If the city falls, these fine women
should be in for a bit of a rape.
Half of them will have bastards
in their bellies come the morning.
You'll be glad of your red flower then.
When a man's blood is up,
anything with tits looks good.
A precious thing like you
will look very, very good.
A slice of cake
just waiting to be eaten.
- More pressure!
- (Men grunting)
Man 4: Pull! Pull!
Man 5: That's it, men!
Pull! Pull!
He's a serious man, Stannis Baratheon.
They're coming. They're coming ashore.
Rain fire on them.
Archers!
There are too many.
Hound, form a welcome party
for any Baratheon troop
that manages to touch solid ground.
Pod, run to the king's gate.
Bring any men guarding it here, now.
Yes, my lord.
Let's go. Stannis is sending us fresh meat.
You, too.
Any of these flaming fucking arrows
come near me,
I'll strangle you with your own guts.
(Men grunting)
Pull, pull! Go!
Nock!
Draw!
- Draw!
(Men grunting)
Man 6: Kill the lannisters!
- Loose!
- Draw!
To the mud gate, go now!
First and second squads, to the gate!
To the mud gate!
Hound: Any man dies with a clean sword,
I'll rape his fucking corpse.
(Grunting)
(Groans)
Cersei: When we were young, Jaime and I,
we looked so much alike
even our father couldn't tell us apart.
I could never understand why
they treated us differently.
Jaime was taught to fight
with sword and Lance and mace,
and I was taught to smile
and sing and please.
He was heir to casterly rock,
and I was sold to some
stranger like a horse
to be ridden whenever he desired.
You were Robert's queen.
And you will be Joffrey's. Enjoy.
I don't think I know this one.
Pretty.
That's the worst curtsy I've ever seen.
Here, it's not difficult.
I mastered it when I was four.
Straighten your back and bend.
Better. You learn fast.
How long have you been
in lady sansa's service?
A few weeks, your grace.
When did you leave lorath?
I had a lorathi handmaiden once.
But she was a nobleman's daughter.
You're not.
When did you come to Westeros?
Ten years ago, your grace.
From lorathi commoner to the red keep
in 10 years,
all without learning how to curtsy.
I imagine that's a very interesting story.
What's your name?
Shae, your grace.
Tell us a story, shae.
- When I was 13, I...
- (Door opens)
Your grace!
What news?
The imp has set the river afire.
Hundreds of ships are burning, maybe more.
Stannis' fleet destroyed, but...
But...
But his troops
have landed outside the city walls.
Where is Joffrey?
On the battlements with lord Tyrion.
Bring him back inside at once.
- Your grace...
- What?
The king's presence is good for morale.
Bring him back to his chambers now.
- Not here?
- With the women and children?
Do you want him to be mocked as a coward
for the rest of his life?
- No, but I...
- Now!
When I told you about
ser ilyn earlier, I lied.
Do you want to hear the truth?
You want to know why he's really here?
He's here for us.
Stannis may take the city,
he may take the throne,
but he will not take us alive.
(Grunting)
(Screaming)
Man 7: Help me!
(Groaning)
Man 8: Fall back!
Man 9: Fall back!
Get the ladders up!
(Grunts)
Faster, you bastards! Faster!
Come on, kill the scum!
Someone bring me a drink.
Fuck the water. Bring me wine.
Can I get you some iced milk
and a nice bowl of raspberries, too?
Eat shit, dwarf.
You're on the wrong side of the wall.
I lost half my men.
The Blackwater's on fire.
Dog, I command you to
go back out there and fight.
You're kingsguard, clegane.
You must beat them back or
they're going to take this city.
Your king's city.
Fuck the kingsguard.
Fuck the city.
Fuck the king.
(Men shouting)
Man 10: Loose!
Man 11: Put your backs into it!
All right, get up!
Man 10: Loose!
Clear!
- Fonnard!
- (Men shouting)
Man 10: Loose!
Fonnard ladders!
(Men shouting)
- Man 12: Heave!
- (Men grunting)
- Heave!
Your grace,
the queen has sent me to
bring you back to the red keep.
If you won't defend your own city,
why should they?
What would you have me do?
Lead.
Get down there and lead your people
against the invaders who want to kill them.
What did my mother say exactly?
Did she have urgent business with me?
She did not say, your grace.
Man 10: All men to the battlements!
Ser boros, ser mandon,
stay with my uncle and represent the king
on the field of battle.
Man 10: Archers, hold your line
or I'll kill you myself.
Stand fast!
Get up, you fool.
Man 13: We need more arrows!
Where is the king?
- Why isn't he with us?
- Man 14: Who are we fighting for?
Who leads us?
I'll lead the attack.
I'll lead the attack!
- Yes.
- What are you talking about?
Pod, my helmet.
Ser mandon, you will
bear the king's banner.
Men, form up.
Men...
Men!
- They say I'm half a man.
- (Banging on door)
But what does that make the lot of you?
The only way out is through the gates.
And they're at the gates.
There's another way out.
I'm going to show you.
We'll come out behind them
and fuck them in their arses.
(Pounding continues)
Man 12: Heave!
Heave!
Don't fight for your king
and don't fight for his kingdoms.
Don't fight for honor.
Don't fight for glory.
Don't fight for riches,
because you won't get any.
This is your city Stannis means to sack.
That's your gate he's ramming.
If he gets in, it will be
your houses he burns,
your gold he steals,
your women he will rape.
Man 12: Heave! Heave!
Heave!
Those are brave men knocking at our door.
Let's go kill them.
(Cheering)
Lancel: The battle is lost, your grace.
Stannis' troops are at the gates.
When the gold cloaks saw the king leaving,
they lost all heart.
Where is my son?
I want to escort him back to the battle.
Why do I care what you want?
- Bring me...
- Now listen to me...
(Groans)
Don't be afraid.
The queen has raised the drawbridge.
This is the safest place we can be.
Joffrey's not hurt. He's fighting bravely.
His knights have rallied behind him.
They will save the city.
Shall we sing a hymn?
(Singing) Gentle mother, font of mercy
save our sons from war, we pray
(gasps)
You must go.
Run to your chamber and bar your door.
Stannis won't hurt you. This one will.
- Come with me.
- I need to say goodbye to someone.
The queen said they'd rape everyone.
No one is raping me.
Go. Run.
(Singing continues)
(Door closing)
(Breathing heavily)
(Distant screams)
- The lady is starting to panic.
- (Gasps)
What are you doing here?
Not here for long.
- I'm going.
- Where?
Some place that isn't burning.
North, might be.
Could be.
What about the king?
He can die just fine on his own.
I can take you with me.
Take you to winterfell.
I'll keep you safe.
Do you want to go home?
I'll be safe here.
Stannis won't hurt me.
Look at me.
Stannis is a killer.
The lannisters are killers.
Your father was a killer.
Your brother is a killer.
Your sons will be killers someday.
The world is built by killers.
So you'd better get
used to looking at them.
You won't hurt me.
No, little bird, I won't hurt you.
- Man 12: Heave!
- (Men grunting)
Come on, you bastards!
Get up those ladders!
(Groans)
Attack!
Roll it over!
(Men cheering)
(Chanting) Halfman! Halfman! Halfman!
Oh, fuck me.
(Men shouting)
(Grunting)
(Groans)
Shh!
Be calm, my sweet.
They're still fighting.
No one's going to hurt you.
I'll tell you a story.
You know the one about
the mother lion and her little cub?
- They lived in the woods.
- The kingswood?
Yes, my love.
In the kingswood,
there lived a mother and her cub.
She loved him very much.
But there were other things
that lived in the woods. Evil things.
Like what?
Like stags.
Stags aren't evil.
They only eat grass.
And wolves.
My lord.
Cersei: He could hear them
howling in the night.
The little cub was frightened.
His mother said, "you are a lion, my son.
You mustn't be afraid.
"For one day, all the
beasts will bow to you.
"You will be king.
"All the stags will bow.
All the wolves will bow.
"The bears in the north
and the foxes of the south,
"all the birds in the sky
and the beasts in the sea,
"they will all come to you, little lion,
"to rest a crown upon your head."
And the cub said,
"will I be strong and
fierce like my father?"
"Yes," said his mother.
"You will be strong and fierce
just like your father."
I will keep you safe, my love.
I promise you.
(Door opens)
Back to the boats!
Stand and fight!
Stand and fight, damn you!
Father.
The battle is over. We have won.
Man: (Singing) "And who are you,"
the proud lord said
"that I must bow so low?"
"Only a cat of a different coat
"that's all the truth I know
"in a coat of gold or a coat of red
"a lion still has claws
"and mine are long and sharp, my lord
"as long and sharp as yours"
and so he spoke, and so he spoke
that lord of castamere
but now the rains weep o'er his hall
with no one there to hear
yes, now the rains weep o'er his hall
and not a soul to hear