Boy.
Lovely boy.
-What do you want?
-A man has a thirst.
A man does not drink
for a day and a night.
-A boy could make a friend.
-I have friends.
Get us beer before I skin you.
A man does not choose his companions.
These two, they have no courtesy.
A man must ask forgiveness.
You're called Arry.
This man has the honor to be Jaqen H'ghar.
-Once of the Free City of Lorath.
-Beer, you little shit. Get us beer!
You should've asked nicely.
Come closer and I'll shove
that stick up your bunghole
and fuck you bloody!
A boy has more courage than sense.
Come here!
Yoren said none of us
were to go near those three.
-Come here!
-They don't scare me.
Then you're stupid. They scare me.
What are Gold Cloaks doing
so far from King's Landing?
-What you doing?
-They're looking for me.
You in command here?
-You're a long way from home.
-I asked you a question.
Aye, you did.
But you asked without manners.
And I chose not to answer.
I have a royal warrant
for one of these gutter rats
you're transporting.
Well, the thing is, these gutter
rats belong to the Night's Watch now.
That puts them beyond
the reach of kings and queens.
Does it?
It's a funny thing.
People worry so much about their throats
that they forget about what's down low.
Now, I sharpened this blade
before breakfast.
I could shave a spider's arse
if I wanted to.
Or I could nick this artery in your leg
and once it's nicked,
there's no one around here
that knows how to unnick it.
We'll just keep that.
Good steel is always needed on the Wall.
It seems you have a choice.
You can die here at this crossroads
a long way from home,
or you can go back to your city
and tell your masters
you didn't find what you were looking for.
We're looking for a boy named Gendry.
He carries a bull's head helmet.
Anyone turning him over will earn
the king's reward.
We'll be back with more men.
And I'll be taking your head home
along with that bastard boy.
My lord.
You make me wait a long time.
But your friend keeps me company.
We were just speaking of your bravery
in the victory against
the Stark auxiliary forces.
It was quite a battle.
I heard you suffered
a terrible head wound.
The Northerners
are such fearsome warriors.
And I tell him the story of how we meet.
To find so lovely a creature
working in your father's kitchens,
it almost beggars belief.
Strange things do happen.
-You should taste her fish pie.
-I don't think Lord Varys likes fish pie.
-How can you tell?
-I can always tell.
Men like Lord Varys and I can't let
our disadvantages get the best of us.
We'll make a fisherman of him yet.
I am glad your new friend was able
to accompany you to the capital.
Friends are such
an important part of life.
Unfortunate that your father
didn't want her to come.
But rest easy my lord,
I am very good at keeping secrets
for my good friends.
Your discretion is legendary,
where your friends are concerned.
How unspeakable of me to go on and on
when all you want to do is rest.
I will leave you.
Welcome to King's Landing, my dear.
This city is made brighter
by your presence.
We have a council meeting, my lord.
-I don't like threats.
-Well, who threatened you?
I'm not Ned Stark. I understand the way
this game is played.
-Ned Stark was a man of honor.
-And I am not.
Threaten me again and I will have you
thrown into the sea.
You might be disappointed in the results.
The storms come and go,
the big fish eat the little fish,
and I keep on paddling.
Come, my lord.
We shouldn't keep the queen waiting.
From this time until the end of time,
we are not part of your realm
but a free and independent
kingdom of the North.
He has more spirit than his father,
I'll give him that.
You've perfected the art
of tearing up papers.
We can give him his father's bones back,
at least, as a gesture of good faith.
You'll give the Starks our reply, cousin?
I will, Your Grace.
Did you see my brother
when you were the Starks' guest?
I did. They have not broken his spirit,
Your Grace.
If you speak with him...
tell him he's not been forgotten.
-I will, Your Grace.
-Safe travels, cousin.
You have a deft hand with diplomacy.
If that's everything.
A raven flew in this morning
from Castle Black.
-Trouble with the wildlings.
-That's why they're called wildlings.
Somewhat less wild these days.
Seems they've stopped killing each other
and started following
this "King-Beyond-the Wall."
Another king? How many is that now?
Five. I've lost count.
The Lord Commander asks
that we send more men to man the Wall.
Perhaps he's forgotten that we're fighting
a war. We have no men to spare.
The cold winds are rising
and the dead rise with them.
The Northerners
are a superstitious people.
According to the Commander, one of these
dead men attacked him in his chambers.
Mormont doesn't lie.
-How do you kill a dead man?
-Apparently, you burn him.
One trip to the Wall and you come back
believing in grumkins and snarks.
I don't know what I believe.
But here's a fact for you.
Night's Watch is the only thing
that separates us
from what lies beyond the Wall.
I have every confidence that the brave men
of the Night's Watch will protect us all.
...and I said, if the Gods wanted us
to have dignity,
they wouldn't make us fart when we died.
We fart when we die?
My blessed mother, I was holding her hand
when she left this world.
She farted so hard the whole bed shook.
Seems a bit greedy for one man
to have so many wives.
-Wouldn't two or three be enough for him?
-We were having a serious discussion.
Would you look at that.
Nothing like the sight
of a woman walking away.
I prefer watching them come towards me.
I'm sure that's nice too.
Yeah, well, there was a milkmaid
named Violet on the next farm
over from where I grew up.
And we were wrestling together
from the time we were six years old,
and then we got older and the wrestling...
changed.
You were with her? How many times?
Well, as many times as I could.
I wish I grew up on a farm.
We need more potatoes.
Get another sack from the sledge.
Get the turnips, too.
No. Ghost, no.
No. Ghost away. Shoo. Shoo!
-You all right? Did he frighten you?
-You... you shouldn't touch me.
Right. I'm sorry, I just wanted
to make sure you weren't hurt.
You're very brave.
What are you doing?
This is Gilly.
She's one of Craster's daughters.
-Hello, Gilly. What are you doing?
-Sam said you could help.
I'm sorry, but Sam knows
we’re not supposed to--
She's pregnant.
We have to take her with us when we leave.
-What?
-I know it sounds a bit mad.
No, it doesn’t sound a bit mad,
it's impossible.
-The Lord Commander ordered us--
-We are sworn to protect.
-Sam, we can't take her.
-Please, sir, please.
I can still run if I have to.
It's just not possible.
I'm going to have a baby. If it's a boy...
If it's a boy what?
You want us to risk our lives for you,
and you won't even tell us why.
-Why'd you do that?
-Do what? Ask her a question?
-You were cruel.
-Cruel?
Sam, are you in such a hurry
to lose a hand?
-I didn't touch her.
-No, you just want to steal her.
What do you think
Craster cuts off for that?
I can't steal her.
She's a person not a goat.
We're heading deeper and deeper
into wildling territory.
We can't take a girl with us.
Mormont wouldn't have it,
and even if he would,
what would we do with her?
Who's going to deliver a baby? You?
I could try. What? I've read about it.
A bit.
I'm sorry, Sam. We can't help her.
Khaleesi.
-You don't need to see this.
-He is blood of my blood.
-Who did this?
-Khal Pono, perhaps.
Khal Jhaqo. They don't like the idea
of a woman leading a khalasar.
They will like it far less
when I am done with them.
Is it as you remember, my lord?
It looks smaller.
Everything looks bigger
when you're a child.
I remember my father's cabin
felt like a palace when I was little.
Now look at it.
They'll be waiting for me on the docks.
-Who will?
-Anyone who matters.
This is a big day for them.
They haven't had much
to get excited about since I left.
It's a hard place, the Iron Islands,
always has been. It's cold and it's wet.
-I love the cold and wet.
-They say hard places breed hard men.
And hard men rule the world.
And you'll be king before long.
Try smiling with your lips closed.
Better.
My father doesn't
trust you Iron Islanders.
I don't blame him.
He says that you're all reavers
and rapers,
and that no matter how many women
you have, you'll never be satis--
Quit talking about your father.
He's right about us.
Our wives from the Iron Islands,
they're for breeding.
But that's not enough for us.
That's why we take salt wives.
The women we capture.
Capture me.
Take me with you when you go ashore.
Make me your salt wife.
-Your place is on this ship.
-Not after you leave.
Father will punish me.
He'll call me a whore.
I haven't paid you.
Unbelievable.
Yes, but I'm not going to stand for this.
I barely touched her.
Now, you charge twice as much
as every other brothel.
And this is what I get? Crying?
One moment my friend, a moment.
Please accept my sincerest apologies.
Aremca will take good care of you.
I'm sorry, my lord.
Did he hurt you?
No, my lord.
-It's Mhaegen.
-Who?
She works for you. She's the one...
The gold cloaks, they killed her baby.
Yes. That was poorly handled.
Sometimes those with the most power
have the least grace.
I can't stop thinking about it.
I can't sleep.
That poor little baby.
You know, you remind me of another girl.
A lovely thing I once acquired
from a Lysene pleasure house.
Beautiful, like yourself.
And intelligent, like yourself.
But she wasn't happy.
She cried often. I asked her why...
but we didn't have the kind of rapport
that you and I have.
Yes, it was quite sad.
Girls from the Lysene pleasure houses
are expensive. Extremely expensive.
And this one wasn't making me any money.
I hate bad investments. Really, I... I do.
They haunt me.
And I had no idea how to make her happy.
And no idea how to mitigate my losses.
A very wealthy patron, he offered me
a tremendous amount of money to let him
transform this lovely sad girl
to use her in ways
that would never occur to most men.
And you know what occurs to most men.
I would not say he succeeded
in making her happy...
but my losses were definitely mitigated.
Take tonight off to mourn Mhaegen's child.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And you'll be happy?
That makes me happy.
More wine?
-Damn it, boy!
-Apologies, my lord.
Leave us Podrick. I believe
we know how to pour our own wine.
That your new squire?
I could have found you a proper lad.
Myself, I prefer the improper ones.
-That's a good red. Dornish?
-You know your wines, my lord.
That I do.
-A fine dinner, my lord.
-Call me Tyrion, please.
I'm sure you're getting used
to fine dinners now that you're a lord.
-Maybe I'll hire this cook of yours.
-Wars have been started for less.
I heard there was some trouble
in Littlefinger's brothel the other night.
Nasty business. Had to be done.
Yes, of course.
The City Watch must keep the peace.
Only, I hadn't realized peace
depended on killing babies.
-Orders are orders.
-Quite right.
Especially the queen's orders.
I never said they were
the queen's orders.
No, but who else would want
to murder King Robert's bastards?
-She's always been a jealous woman.
-You know your sister better than I do.
You've heard the awful rumors
about my brother and sister.
I don't listen to filth.
That's good of you,
but you have heard them.
I suppose people who do believe
that filth consider Robert's bastards
to be better claimants to the throne
than Cersei's children.
Joffrey is my king.
The rest doesn't interest me.
I appreciate your loyalty.
Tell me, when your men slaughtered
Ned Stark's men in the throne room,
did you give the order?
I did. And I would again.
The man was a traitor.
He tried to buy my loyalty.
A fool. He had no idea
you were already bought.
Are you drunk?
I will not have my honor
questioned by an imp!
I'm not questioning your honor,
Lord Janos.
I'm denying its existence.
Do you think I'll stand here
and take this from you, dwarf?
Dwarf? You should've stopped at imp.
And yes, you will stand here
and take it from me,
unless you'd like to take it
from my friend here.
I intend to serve as Hand of the King
until my father returns from the war.
And seeing as you betrayed
the last Hand of the King,
well, I just wouldn't feel safe
with you lurking about.
What are you ta--
My friends at court will not allow this.
-The queen herself granted--
-The queen regent.
And you're a fool
to believe she's your friend.
We shall hear
what Joffrey has to say about this.
No, we shan't.
There's a ship leaving
for Eastwatch by the sea tonight.
From there, I'm afraid
it's rather a long walk to Castle Black.
I hope you enjoy the Wall.
I found it surprisingly beautiful,
in a brutal, horribly uncomfortable
sort of way.
The lads will escort you.
The streets aren't safe at night, my lord.
These men are under my command!
I command you to arrest this cut-throat.
His name is Bronn.
And he is the new commander
of the City Watch.
Boys.
I have friends at court! Powerful friends!
The king himself made me a lord!
To the new commander.
If I told you to murder
an infant girl, say,
still at her mother's breast,
would you do it without question?
Without question, no. I'd ask how much.
If they come back, I say we yield.
Gendry's the one they want.
Don't want to get caught
in the middle of a battle.
I ain't afraid of no battles.
If you got within a mile of a battle
you'd fill your pants.
-I've seen lots of battles. I saw--
-Liar.
I saw a man kill another man
just outside a tavern in Flea Bottom.
-Stabbed him right in the neck.
-Two men fighting isn't a battle.
-They had armor on.
-So?
-So, if they got armor on, it's a battle.
-No, it isn't.
What does a dyer's apprentice
know about battles anyway?
Gendry's an armorer's apprentice.
Hot Pie, tell Gendry what makes
a fight into a battle.
-It's when they've got armor on.
-And who told you that?
-A knight.
-How'd you know he was a knight?
Well, because he's got ar... armor on.
You don't have to be a knight
to have armor. Any idiot can buy armor.
-How do you know?
-Because I sold armor.
What do the Gold Cloaks want with you?
-No idea.
-You're a liar.
You know, you shouldn't insult people
that are bigger than you.
Then I wouldn't get to insult anyone.
Well, I don't care what any of them want.
-No good's ever come of their questions.
-No good's ever come.
Who asked questions before?
How can someone so small
be such a huge pain in my arse?
Who asked questions?
The Hand of the King. Hands of the King.
Lord Arryn came first,
a few weeks before he died
and then Lord Stark came
a few weeks before he died.
Lord Stark.
See, asking me questions is bad luck.
You'll probably be dead soon.
-What did they ask about?
-My mom.
-Who's your mom?
-She was just my mom.
Worked in a tavern.
Died when I was little.
And who was your father?
Could've been one of those
gold-hatted bastards for all I know.
What about you anyway?
You thought they were after you.
Why? Did you kill someone
or is it just because you're a girl?
-I'm not a girl.
-Yes, you are.
You think I'm as stupid
as the rest of them?
Stupider. The Night's Watch
doesn't take girls. Everyone knows that.
Yeah, that’s true.
But you're still a girl.
I am not!
Yeah, well, pull your cock out
and take a piss then.
I don't need to take a piss.
Lommy and Hot Pie can't know.
No one can know.
Well, they won't. Not from me.
My name's not Arry.
It's Arya. Of House Stark.
Yoren is taking me home to Winterfell.
Who's your father?
The Hand, the traitor?
He was never a traitor. Joffrey is a liar.
So, you're a highborn then. You're a lady.
No. I mean, yes.
My mother was a lady
and my sister, but--
You were a Lord's daughter
and you lived in a castle,
but all that about cocks
I should never have said.
And I've been pissing
in front of you and everything.
I should be calling you "my lady."
-Do not call me "my lady."
-As my lady commands.
Well, that was unladylike.
What you carrying?
Various oranges. Wine from the Arbor.
And the heir to Pyke and the Iron Islands.
The only living son of Balon Greyjoy.
Me.
I don't like wine. Woman's drink.
I need to get to Pyke.
I'll find you a horse.
I'm heading that way.
I can take you there.
I bet you can.
You been at sea long? Or were there
just no women where you came from?
-None like you.
-You don't know what I'm like.
Maybe you don't know what you're like.
Maybe you need someone to teach you.
Do you know who I am?
You think I offer free rides
to every man in jewelry...
Lord Greyjoy?
Have my things sent up to the castle.
You should give me the reins.
I'm a better rider than you.
Been on horseback
for the past nine years.
Nine years. Do you still know
your way around a ship?
Have these hands ever touched a rope?
Don't you worry about my hands.
The sea is in my blood.
Your blood will be in the sea
if I don't watch where I'm going.
I have a proposal for my father.
One that will make him king again.
And me after him.
You may get to stay in a castle tonight,
if you're lucky.
-Is that an offer from my future king?
-An order from your future king.
You can tell your grandchildren
about this night.
I don't imagine it'll be a story
fit for children.
Father.
Nine years, is it?
They took a frightened boy.
What have they given back?
-A man. Your blood and your heir.
-We shall see.
-Stark had you longer than I did.
-Lord Stark is gone.
And how do you feel about that?
What's done is done.
I've brought you a proposal
from Robb Stark.
Who gave you those clothes?
Was it Ned Stark's pleasure
to make you his daughter?
If my clothes offend you,
I will change them.
You will.
That bauble around your neck,
did you pay the iron price for it,
or the gold? I asked a question.
Did you pull it from the neck
of a corpse you made,
or did you buy it to match
your fine clothes?
Iron or gold?
Gold.
I'll not have my son dressed as a whore.
My fears have come true.
The Starks have made you theirs.
My blood is salt and iron.
Yet the Stark boy sends you to me
like a trained raven,
clutching his message.
-The offer he makes is one I proposed.
-He heeds your counsel.
I've lived with him, hunted with him,
fought at his side.
-He thinks of me as a brother.
-No! Not here. Not in my hearing.
You will not name him brother.
This son of the man who put
your true brothers to the sword,
or have you forgotten your own blood?
I forget nothing. I remember my brothers.
And I remember when my father was a king.
I see. I destroy
Robb Stark's enemies for him
and he will make me
King of the Iron Islands once again.
-I will lead the attack myself.
-You will?
I'm your son.
Your only living heir. Who else?
I told you to wait outside.
-How did you get past the guards?
-Anything with a cock is easy to fool.
My dear.
-Yara?
-So good to see you, brother.
This is a homecoming
I'll tell my grandchildren about.
-She can't lead an attack!
-And why not?
-You're a woman!
-You're the one in skirts.
This isn't Winterfell, boy.
Your sister took over command
of your eldest brother's ship
after your new father killed him.
-What's dead may never die.
The only night she's spent
off these islands
have been spent on the sea.
She's commanded men.
She's killed men.
And she knows who she is.
No man gives me a crown.
I pay the iron price.
I will take my crown.
For that is who I am.
That is who we have always been.
You won't stand a chance
against the Lannisters on your own.
Who said anything about the Lannisters?
You'll have your gold when we take
the treasury at King's Landing.
All these kings fighting
for the throne and this Stannis
has the smallest army.
Why would I bet on the man
with the worst chance?
Because you're a smart gambler.
Stannis has proved himself in war, twice.
His baby brother
has never set foot on a battlefield.
-Neither has the false King Joffrey.
-And yet, they both have larger armies.
Well, Stannis has just begun the fight.
His bannermen will rally to his cause.
There's no man in the Seven Kingdoms
more honorable than Stannis Baratheon
or more worthy of loyalty.
What is the world coming to when smugglers
must vouch for the honor of kings?
-You mind your words, pirate.
-Matthos.
Do you think I'm insulted? I am a pirate.
I'm an excellent pirate.
I don't sail for promises.
Of course you do.
Every time you leave harbor,
you're leaving on a promise.
A promise that somewhere on the seas
somebody's got some gold
and you can take it from them.
That's a promise that always comes true.
As is mine.
You're not a young man, Salladhor.
And correct me if I'm wrong,
but most pirates don't grow old.
Only the clever ones.
You want to spend your last
few years on the sea
stealing from Pentoshi cheesemongers
and Meereenese silk merchants, then go.
They're out there waiting for you.
That's easy.
What I'm offering you is hard.
Come with me and plunder
the greatest city in Westeros.
You'll be the richest man in Lys.
And the most famous.
They'll be singing songs about you
as long as men have voices to sing.
Salladhor Saan is a good name
for songs.
It is.
One thing. I want the queen.
-The queen?
-Cersei. I want her.
I'll sail with your fleet,
all 30 of my ships
and if we don't drown at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay,
I will fuck this blonde queen
and I will fuck her well.
This war isn't about you.
We're not attacking King's Landing
so that you can rape the queen.
I'm not going to rape her.
I'm going to fuck her.
-As if she would just let you.
-You don't know how persuasive I am.
I never tried to fuck you.
Stannis is the rightful king
and the Lord of Light.
The one true God.
I've been all over the world, my boy,
and everywhere I go,
people tell me about the true Gods.
They all think they found the right one.
The one true God
is what's between a woman's legs.
And better yet, a queen's legs.
I never thought you'd have
a true believer for a son.
He's young yet.
I promise you the gold.
I promise you the glory.
I cannot promise you the queen.
-You believe your king can win?
-He's the one true king.
You Westerosi are a funny people.
Man chops off your fingers
and you fall in love with him.
I'll sail with you, Davos Seaworth.
You're the most honest smuggler
I ever met. Make me rich.
Get me to the gates
of King's Landing and I will.
When will the king have us sail?
As soon as his God wills it.
He's my God too, and yours.
Or are you too blind to see?
-Let me teach you how to read.
-You and your mother.
It won't take long.
You already know the letters.
The holy books are more
persuasive than I can be.
I wish I had a God, truly.
Now, I'm not mocking you,
but I've seen men pray
to every God there is.
Pray for wind, pray for rain,
pray for home. None of it works.
But you always came home.
-I wasn't praying.
-No. But I was.
Every night that you were at sea,
I lit a candle and I prayed for you.
You want me to have a God? Fine.
King Stannis is my God. He raised me up
and blessed me with his trust.
He gave you a future I could never
have imagined.
You know how to read.
You'll be a knight someday.
You think a Fire God commanded
all that? It was Stannis. Only Stannis.
-Stannis is my king, but he's only a man.
-Don't tell him that.
Lord Janos Slynt was the Commander
of the City Watch.
-You had no right to exile him.
-I have every right. I am the King's Hand.
You're serving as the King's Hand
till Father gets here.
-I'm Queen Regent.
-Listen to me, Queen Regent.
You're losing the people.
-Do you hear me?
-The people? You think I care.
You might find it difficult to rule
over millions who want you dead.
Half this city will starve
when winter comes,
the other half will plot to overthrow you.
And your gold-plated thugs
just gave them their rallying cry.
The queen slaughters babies.
You don't even have the decency
to deny it.
It wasn't you who gave the order, was it?
Joffrey didn't even tell you.
Did he tell you?
I imagine that would be even worse.
He did what needed to be done.
You want to be Hand of the King?
You want to rule? This is what ruling is.
Lying on a bed of weeds,
ripping them out by the root one by one
before they strangle you in your sleep.
I'm no king but I think there's
more to ruling than that.
I don't care what you think!
You've never taken it seriously.
You haven't, Jaime hasn't.
It's all fallen on me.
As has Jaime, repeatedly,
according to Stannis Baratheon.
You're funny.
You've always been funny.
But none of your jokes
will ever match the first one, will they?
You remember... back when you
ripped my mother open
on your way out of her
and she bled to death.
She was my mother too.
Mother gone.
For the sake of you.
There's no bigger joke
in the world than that.
-Your Grace.
How did you fare with your pirate?
Salladhor Saan will join our fleet.
Thirty ships. His men know how to fight.
In my experience,
pirates prefer fighting unarmed men.
-It does seem the wiser choice.
-There won't be a choice, this time.
Do you trust him?
Salladhor Saan is an old friend.
I've known him thirty years.
I've never trusted him.
Now, once he gets the smell of gold,
he never stops.
Well, if he does his job,
he'll have his share.
Leave us.
At once, Your Grace.
The Lord of Light shines
through you, young warrior.
Come.
What did you say to him?
I told him death by fire
is the purest death.
-Why?
-Because it is true.
-You're troubled, my king.
-Yeah.
These armies are toys
for the Lord of Light.
Tell your lord to burn them then.
I tell him nothing.
I pray for his commands and I obey.
My little brother has 100,000 men
according to the scouts.
Men whose allegiance
rightly belongs to me.
-You must have faith.
-Faith?
In a real war,
the side with the greater number wins.
Nine times out of ten.
-Then we must be the tenth.
-I cannot defeat my brother in the field.
And I can't take King's Landing
without the men he's stolen.
I have seen the path to victory
in the flames.
But first you must give yourself
to the Lord of Light.
I've said the words, damn you!
I burnt the idols.
You must give all of yourself.
I have a wife.
I took a vow.
She's sickly.
Weak.
And shut away in a tower.
She disgusts you.
And she's given you nothing. No sons.
Only stillborns. Only death.
I will give you a son, my king.
A son?