Imagine this,
President of Colombia goes
on TV and tells the whole world
he'll never make a deal with you.
Now a normal person
thinks, "I'm fucked."
But Pablo Escobar, he thinks that's
just your opening offer.
So the man finds a way to respond.
And how did Gaviria take Pablo's offer?
I think it's safe to say
that he didn't really care for it.
But it wasn't just Gaviria
Pablo was talking to.
In his mind, he was also negotiating
with the leader of the free world.
You see, the problem was, George Bush
had his own plans for Escobar.
We will, for the first time,
make available the appropriate resources
of America's armed forces.
And for the drug kingpins,
the death penalty.
And with a commander in chief who
used to be the head of the CIA,
well, you can use your imagination
as to what
"appropriate resources" might mean.
He started by
appointing a new ambassador.
Badass former Navy man, Arthur Crosby...
who specialized in Latin
American affairs and counterterrorism.
Next, he dug into his old CIA Rolodex,
where there was no shortage of guys
who knew how to fight dirty.
And he sent us one of those, too.
Lastly, and what Peña and I like to
call his own personal
"fuck you" to us...
he sent us something he thought
we must need: A boss.
Now just how long that person
would be my boss remained to be seen.
My title might be "ambassador,"
but that's some bullshit
politician's word.
I know what it means
to be on the front lines.
And everybody in this room wants
the same thing, to take down Escobar.
Now as a veteran of numerous
conflicts, I learned one immutable truth:
The only way to
succeed is by working together,
by communicating, by sharing intelligence
and collaborating.
Understood?
Uh, this is Claudia Messina.
She is the new DEA country attaché.
She'll be taking over all DEA
operations in-country. Messina?
Thank you, Ambassador.
The DEA will be opening field offices
in Cali, Cartagena and Barranquilla.
As far as the
Medellín team is concerned,
they will be housed out of CNP headquarters
until further notice.
But only after some
personnel changes have been made.
All right, now as far as
long-term intelligence is concerned,
that's under the purview of the CIA,
the station chief, Bill Stechner.
Bill, you have
anything you'd like to add?
I'm good.
All right, who's here from Centra Spike?
I am, sir. Edward Jacoby.
All right, let's get Centra Spike
back in the air immediately.
I want to know every word
these assholes say
and all information flows through me
and I will disseminate as I see fit.
Yes, sir.
When Escobar sticks
his fucking head out,
we're gonna nail that son of a bitch.
What about him?
Other than the fact that
he wasn't here today.
Well, I suggested that he stay home.
You mentioned making some changes.
What exactly does that mean?
It means I'm making some changes.
Murphy's a good agent. He's
done a lot of good work down here.
Yeah.
Looks like it.
Do you have any idea
the strings that were pulled
to get that guy not to press charges?
Sounds to me like the guy
would've had a dog sniffing up his ass
before he got on the plane.
Maybe Steve did him a favor.
Was that a thank you?
Be straight with me, Agent Peña,
and I'll be straight with you.
I don't need a guy like that
making my life more difficult.
- And making the DEA look bad.
- Ma'am...
Messina. Or boss.
We've been down here a long time.
You've been down here
all of what, two hours?
It may not make the front page, but...
a lot of the intel we have
is because of Steve.
He's a good man. He's going
through some shit right now.
You know, he was at the airport
to stop his wife from leaving the
country with their
kid. He didn't make it.
Add that to watching Escobar
build a five-star prison
and then walking out the back door.
We both deserve to see this through...
boss.
Have you, uh... had
anything to eat in the last 24 hours?
This new boss... Messina...
what do you know about her?
Only what I've heard.
She's out of New York.
Doesn't put up with any shit.
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Am I out?
I don't know.
Well, I ain't ready to go
home yet, Javi. I'll tell ya that.
Damn it! She's fucking...
Take a shower. Sober up.
Talk to you.
Now, Gaviria had made it clear
that the government was
not to negotiate with Escobar.
But Colombia Attorney General
Gustavo de Greiff
didn't give a shit
what the president wanted.
Unlike the US, where the attorney general
is appointed by the president,
in Colombia, the Supreme Court
chooses the attorney general,
whether the president likes it or not.
And in the case of Gustavo de Greiff,
you bet your ass Gaviria didn't.
Uh-huh.
Listen, thanks for talking
to Messina, man.
I mean it. You saved my ass.
One more fuck-up, Murphy...
Oh, I know.
Is it gonna happen again?
I don't know.
DEA politics weren't the only
thing we had to navigate.
The Pinzón plan was in full effect.
He was doubling down on police presence.
Medellín was under martial law
and the base of Carlos Holguín
would look like Fort Apache.
Me and Javi were
officially guests of the CNP.
With all the comforts and amenities
that a guest of the National
Colombian Police could expect.
Which was zero.
And we weren't alone.
The DEA, CIA, Centra Spike
and the army, all under one roof.
It was one-stop shopping
for all things Pablo Escobar.
After Gaviria announced a new $1.4
million reward for Pablo's capture,
Colonel Pinzón activated
a new tip line.
And apparently he thought Javi and
I were just the guys to oversee it.
Forget about the fact
that my Spanish was for shit.
He was sidelining us and there was
nothing we could do about it.
Pablo would even have his
men call in just to fuck with us.
I'm not sure what we expected.
To many people, Escobar was a hero.
It was like asking Chicago
to rat out Michael Jordan.
And those that didn't worship Escobar,
they were simply too scared to call.
But we had a system anyways.
One tip in a particular location
didn't mean shit.
A second call with the same
information still
might not be worth acting on.
But three calls on the same
location from three different sources?
Yeah?
Now, that had to be checked out.
Hey, I said it was a system.
I didn't say it worked.
Fuck me.
Our inability to catch
Escobar was frustrating.
But back in Bogotá, it
was becoming a real liability.
Get ready to get your balls snipped.
So... your wife left.
You're upset, knocked a
few back to numb the pain
and then decide to take it out
on some Wall Street scumbag.
Yeah, something like that.
Isolated incident?
Yeah.
Look, I know I've been in Colombia
for all of about 20 seconds.
Mm.
Before that, you and Peña had
complete autonomy to call your own shots.
It's gonna take you a minute
to get used to the new order.
You don't trust me yet? That's fine.
But if I'm gonna have your back,
I need to know that I can trust you.
Otherwise, I have no problem
sending you back to your wife in Miami.
Am I making myself clear?
Loud and clear.
Excellent.
You're dismissed.
I got "La Quica" and "toilet."
All right, well, now, that I got.
We can't take that to Pinzón.
He'll laugh us out of the office.
Maybe we can get
Centra Spike to do a flyover,
see what they come up with.
Be a lot better than
the fucking tip line.
I'll be right back.
- A toilet?
- It's a long story.
- Give me the CliffsNotes.
- Look, just do me a favor
and ask them to sweep over
that specific area.
We're looking for any chatter from
Escobar's sicarios. Anything at all.
You recognize a voice, you come get me.
Duvall 1-4-4-3-6, we heard
some chatter at 1600 megahertz.
Be advised.
That is definitely Velasco.
No ID on the girl.
What's the deal with the other call?
The quality's too poor
for voice recognition.
All right... these were
taken about two hours ago.
What's here is fincas, fincas.
Everything else is just smaller houses
here, here and here, and the outskirts.
You can probably eliminate the smaller
ones, not Escobar's style.
Which of the fincas have
road access both east and west?
This one here.
It's rough terrain down the back
of the mountain, but it's drivable.
It's gotta be the one.
We'd have a good chance if
we came at him from both sides.
This is good.
Great. What about Pinzón?
We're gonna need vehicles,
we're gonna need men.
Leave Pinzón to me.
What did he say?
He said no.
Oh, she's not gonna last.
She gives up pretty fuckin' easy.
But Messina didn't give up easy.
She called Crosby...
Crosby called Gaviria...
and in less than 15 minutes...
- I understand.
- ...Pinzón was gettin' a kick in the ass.
I guess everybody works for somebody.
Just because we could make Pinzón dance
didn't mean we could call the tune.
We would've gone in stealth.
Surround the fucker, then grab him.
Pinzón didn't do shit that way.
He liked kicking down the front door,
waking up the whole damn neighborhood.
Don't forget that Pablo made a career
of staying ahead of the cops.
A lot of the fincas he used had tunnels
built just for this purpose.
Even though he didn't like using them.
I guess you could say that
he was paranoid, but then again,
if people are actually after you,
that's not paranoid. That's just smart.
Peña! Messina!
He was here.
You know, in all the
years I chased Escobar,
I could count on one hand
the times we almost had him.
And each time, we forgot
the two most important things
we already knew about him:
Close doesn't count.
And Pablo is never more dangerous
than when you almost have him.
With all the cops on the street,
it was easy to forget...
this was still Escobar's town.
He tolerated it all in
the interest of negotiations.
Chasing a man and his family
out of their home
in the middle of the night?
That wasn't a negotiation.
To Escobar...
well, that was an act of war.
Peña!