( theme music playing )
( crickets chirping )
Catelyn:
Are you sure about this?
No.
It's dangerous.
If we take Tywin's
castle from him,
the lords of Westeros
will realize he's
not invincible.
Take his home,
take his gold,
take his power.
Why are you telling me?
You begged me
not to send Theon
to negotiate with his father
and I ignored your advice.
Now Winterfell is burnt
to the ground,
the North is overrun
with ironborn,
and Bran and Rickon
are gone.
So Casterly Rock...
I'm asking your advice.
We have enough men?
If Walder Frey cooperates.
If Walder Frey
cooperates.
If reinforcements arrive
from King's Landing
before we take
the castle...
we'll be caught between
Tywin's army and the sea.
We'll lose the war and die
the way Father died.
Or worse.
Show them how it feels
to lose what they love.
Walder:
My honored guests...
be welcome
within my walls
and at my table.
I extend to you
my hospitality
and protection
in the light of the Seven.
We thank you for your
hospitality, my lord.
I have come to make
my apologies, my lord,
and to beg
your forgiveness.
Don't beg my forgiveness,
Your Grace.
It wasn't me you spurned.
It was my girls.
One of them was supposed
to be queen.
Now none of them are.
This is Arwyen
my daughter.
My daughter Walda,
my daughter Derwa,
my daughter Waldra.
My eldest granddaughters
Ginia and Neila.
Serra and Sarra,
granddaughters, twins.
You could have
had either.
Could have had both
for all I care.
My granddaughter
Marianne.
My granddaughter Freya.
My granddaughter...
Wertha.
Waldra.
Waldina.
- I'm Merry.
- Fine.
And here's my youngest
daughter Shirei,
though she hasn't
bled yet.
Clearly you don't have
the patience for all that.
My ladies.
All men should
keep their word,
kings most of all.
I was pledged
to marry one of you
and I broke that vow.
The fault
is not with you.
Any man would be lucky
to have any one of you.
I did what I did
not to slight you,
but because I loved another.
I know these words
cannot set right
the wrong I have done
to you and your house.
I beg your forgiveness
and pledge to do
all I can to make amends
so the Freys of the Crossing
and the Starks of Winterfell
may once again be friends.
Walder:
Very good.
There she is.
Come closer.
Let me have a look at you.
Still can't see you.
Old eyes.
Love.
That's what the Starks
of Winterfell call it, eh?
( chuckles )
Very honorable.
I call it a pretty face.
Mmm, very pretty.
Prettier than this lot,
that's for sure.
Very shapely as well.
Oh, you try to hide her
under that dress.
If you wanted to hide her,
you shouldn't have brought her
here in the first place.
I can always see
what's going on
beneath a dress.
Been at this a long time.
I bet when you take
that dress off,
everything stays
right where it is.
Doesn't drop an inch.
Your king says he betrayed
me for love.
I say he betrayed me
for firm tits
and a tight fit.
And I can respect that.
When I was your age,
I'd have broken 50 oaths
to get into that
without a second thought.
Well, I've enough room
in the hall for you lot.
We'll set up
tents outside
with food and ale
for the rest of your men.
Thank you, my lord.
Well, let's get ready.
The wine will flow red
and the music
will play loud
and we'll put
this mess behind us.
- ( horse neighs )
- ( weapons clang )
Where?
There.
It's a back gate.
My men use it
when they visit
Yunkai's bed slaves.
Your men,
but not you?
Daario:
I have no interest
in slaves.
A man cannot make love
to property.
This is where
we enter the city.
Very few guards.
They know me.
They let me inside--
We're not gonna sneak
an army through a back gate.
I kill the guards.
I take your two best men
and lead them
through the back streets,
which I know well,
and open the front gates.
Then comes the army.
Once the walls
are breached, the city
will fall in hours.
Or perhaps you'll lead
Grey Worm and me
to the slaughter,
cutting the head
off our army.
The masters of Yunkai
will pay you your fee
and you won't have
to split it three ways
'cause you've already
slaughtered your partners.
You have
a very suspicious mind.
In my experience,
only dishonest people
think this way.
You command the Unsullied.
What do you think?
( Daenerys speaking
Valyrian )
You leave tonight.
Very good.
We'll prepare.
Ser Jorah.
You can use
an extra sword.
You're the Queensguard,
Ser Barristan.
Your place
is by the queen.
If we are truly
her loyal servants,
we'll do whatever
needs to be done
no matter the cost,
no matter our pride.
We're west
of Castle Black,
but the Nightfort's
closest to us.
It was the first
castle on the Wall.
The Watch abandoned
it during the reign
of King Jaehaerys I.
Too big.
Impossible to maintain.
Other than
Castle Black itself,
the Nightfort's
the perfect castle for us.
It's got a secret
sally port,
the Black Gate,
as old as the Wall itself.
No one's used it
in centuries most likely.
It leads through the Wall
right down
into the Nightfort,
if one knows
how to find it,
which, it just
so happens, I do.
How do you know
all that?
I read about it
in a very old book.
You know all that
from staring
at marks on paper?
Yes.
You're like a wizard.
Our father
used to tell us
that no wildling ever looked
upon the Wall and lived.
Here we are.
Alive.
( donkey braying )
Remember what happens
to children who run.
I'm your father
and I'll do the talking.
The roads have gone
right to hell, haven't they?
Cracked three spokes
this morning.
- Need a hand?
- Need about eight hands.
Oh!
Got to get this
salt pork to the Twins
in time for the wedding.
Many thanks.
Don't!
Don't kill him.
Dead rats don't squeak.
You're so dangerous,
aren't you?
Saying scary things
to little girls.
Killing little boys
and old people.
A real hard man you are.
More than anyone
you know.
You're wrong.
I know a killer.
- A real killer.
- That so?
You'd be like
a kitten to him.
He'd kill you
with his little finger.
That him?
- No.
- Good.
Don't kill him.
Please.
Please don't.
You're very kind.
Someday it'll
get you killed.
( groaning )
( grunts )
Where are we?
The Gift, I think.
Brandon the Builder
gave all this land
south of the Wall
to the Night's Watch
for their sustenance
and support.
Maester Luwin
taught me that.
Doesn't seem to be supporting
anyone at the moment.
It's good land
and there's no war up here.
Why leave?
Wildlings.
Sorry.
But they come over
the Wall and raid,
steal, carry off women.
Old Nan said they turn
your skull into a cup
and make you drink
your own blood from it.
That's what Old Nan said.
There's a storm coming.
- I don't see any--
- ( thunder rolling )
It's as good a place
to shelter as any.
We can drink some blood
while we wait.
I don't need much.
( screeching )
Only one old man
and eight good horses.
What's one old man
doing with eight horses?
He breeds them
for the Watch.
How's he keep folks
from stealing them?
The Watch protects him.
Not today they don't.
He's selling horses,
he's got some gold in there.
- Tormund: And proper steel.
- Let's carve him up.
We just take
the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
I keep telling you.
He's an old man.
A spear through the heart's
a better way to die
than coughing up
your last with no one
but your horses to hear.
The Watch might send a few men
looking for a horse thief.
They'll send a lot more
to hunt down murderers.
I hope so.
Killing crows
in their castle is tough.
Killing them out here
in the open,
that's what we do.
Spread out.
Surround the hut
and move in.
- ( sword clangs )
- ( snorts )
( neighing )
Ygritte!
Man:
Clear the barn!
No one's going to believe
you're a hog farmer
if you eat them all.
Best part of the animal.
Don't worry.
They're still there.
I know
they're still there.
You check
every five minutes
like you're afraid
they're gonna move.
I'm not afraid.
Of course you are.
You're almost there
and you're afraid
you won't make it.
The closer you get,
the worse the fear gets.
No point in trying to hide
behind that face.
I know fear
when I see it.
Seen it a lot.
I knew fear
when I saw it in you.
You're afraid of fire.
When Beric's sword
went up in flames,
you looked like
a scared little girl.
And I know why, too.
I heard what
your brother did to you.
Pressed your face
to the fire
like you're a nice
juicy mutton chop.
That give you some ideas?
Might do.
Go ahead, then.
You might get away.
Might even make it
there on your own.
They're just over
the river.
The closest you've
been to family
since Ilyn Payne
snipped your daddy's neck.
Someday I'm gonna put
a sword through your eye
and out the back
of your skull.
( thunder rumbling )
( thunder crashes )
How are we going
to get past the Wall?
My uncle said
it's 700 feet high.
( thunder crashes )
How did you get past it?
Got in a boat and rowed
past the Bay of Seals.
It would take us two months
to get to the Bay of Seals.
Some climb
straight up the ice.
Even Hodor's not strong
enough to climb the Wall
with me on his back.
Hodor.
- 19 castles
guard the Wall.
- ( thunder booms )
- Only three
are still manned.
- Hodor!
One of those abandoned
fortresses will give us
a way through.
My uncle said
the gates were sealed
with ice and stone
when the castles
were deserted.
Well, we'll have
to open them up again.
( hoofbeats, horse neighs )
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Meera: There's a rider
out there.
- Just one?
- ( thunder crashes )
- Meera: There's more.
- Hodor!
( horses neighing )
Shh. Shh.
- It's just thunder,
sweet giant.
- Hodor.
Man:
I yield.
- I yield.
- Wildlings.
( men shouting )
Where's Shaggydog
and Summer?
- Hunting.
- ( horses neighing )
- ( thunder crashes )
- Hodor!
- Shh, quiet, Hodor.
Make him shut up.
If they hear us...
- Hush, Hodor.
No-- no more Hodoring.
- Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
- You need to keep quiet.
- They're gonna hear us.
- ( Hodor shouting )
- Bran: Hodor, be quiet.
( thunder crashes )
- Ah! Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
- Hodor! Hodor!
- Hodor, be quiet!
What did you do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
( horse screaming )
What's that?
That's a horse dying.
Man:
Bring them over here.
Man #2:
That was the last of them.
The rest are dead.
Orell:
I heard shouting up there.
Thunder.
I know the difference
between shouting and thunder.
Maybe it's ghosts.
( laughs )
( eagle screeching )
That won't
help you, grandpa.
Where you riding?
Doesn't matter now,
does it?
No, it doesn't
matter now.
Cut his throat or he'll
tell the crows we're here.
You understand.
Let me stand at least.
Let me go
with a bit of dignity.
Make the crow kill him.
You're one of us now.
Prove it.
The wolves are out there.
I can't do it by choice.
I don't know how.
It happens in my dreams.
You're a warg, Bran.
It's in your blood.
I can't.
You just did with him.
A wolf is nothing
compared to that.
She looks sharp.
( muttering prayer )
Do it.
I told you.
He's still one of them.
Go on, boy.
Go on!
( groans )
He's a crow.
He'll always be a crow.
And here's his crow wife
guarding him.
He'll stab us in the back
first chance he gets.
- Kill him.
- ( Jon shouts )
( screaming )
- He's one of them.
- No!
Do you hear me?
( screams )
You're not gonna die
for one of them.
Do it.
They'll find us
if you don't.
( swords clanging )
( breathing heavily )
( growling )
( Orell shouts )
( gasps )
You were right
the whole time.
( gasps )
( eagle screeches )
( Jon screaming )
Hyah!
Daario:
When you hear a songbird's
whistle, you come.
I'm a great whistler.
The greatest in the land.
- ( guard shouts in Valyrian )
- Daario Naharis.
( whistling )
Daario:
That one was quick.
- There may be others.
- I doubt it.
The Yunkish prefer
to let their slaves do
their fighting for them.
( guards shouting )
That's what you call
a few guards?
( guards shouting )
( men shouting )
Come on!
What do you got, huh?
( cheering )
Lord Edmure...
I hope I'm not
a disappointment to you.
( chuckles )
You're a delight
to me, my lady.
You may now cloak
the bride
and bring her under
your protection.
In the sight of the Seven,
I hereby seal
these two souls,
binding them as one
for eternity.
Look upon each other
and say the words.
Both:
Father, Smith,
Warrior, Mother,
Maiden, Crone,
Stranger...
- I am hers...
- I am his...
- and she is mine...
- and he is mine...
Both:
...from this day
until the end of my days.
- Is that safe?
- They're long gone.
You were right.
I can get inside Summer's
mind whenever I want.
Of course you can.
North of the Wall
there are wildlings
who can control
all sorts of animals.
But you did a lot
more than that.
You got inside
Hodor's mind.
They can't do that
north of the Wall?
No one can do that...
anywhere.
When I was looking
through Summer's eyes,
- I saw Jon.
- Where?
He was with the wildlings.
They tried to kill him,
but he got away.
Osha:
He'll be heading back
to Castle Black, then.
That's where we should go.
For all we know,
Castle Black's already
under attack.
- If this many
wildlings got through--
- I already told you.
I'm not going
north of the Wall.
Everything Jojen
told me is true.
You saw what I did
to Hodor.
I have to find
the three-eyed raven.
Listen to me,
little lord.
Don't worry.
I'm not asking you
to come with me.
It won't be safe
for Rickon.
Me?
I'm coming with you.
No.
You and Osha and Shaggydog
head for the Last Hearth.
The Umbers
are our bannermen.
They'll protect you.
I'm coming with you.
I'm your brother.
I have to protect you.
Right now I have
to protect you.
Robb's at war
and I'm going
beyond the Wall.
If something
happens to us,
you're the heir
to Winterfell.
Would you know how
to find the Last Hearth?
You southerners
build your big castles
and you never move.
You're easy to find.
We're not southerners.
And I don't want
to leave you.
Shh, shh.
Come here, little soldier.
You and me,
we're gonna have
some adventures.
You don't have to do
any of this.
( crying )
Your family
took me in
and was good
to me when they had
no cause to be.
Shh.
We'll be fine,
you and me.
The Umbers
are great warriors.
Even I heard
about them growing up.
They'll teach you
how to swing a sword.
I know how
to swing a sword.
( kisses )
You're leaving now?
It's the middle
of the night.
I learned to walk
in darkness.
Say your good-byes,
little man.
Keep this one safe.
He means
the world to me.
We've been waiting
a long time.
Haven't we?
I don't know,
you tell me.
How long does it take
to sack a city?
It was just as you said.
They did not believe
until it was too late.
Their slave soldiers
threw down their spears
and surrendered.
And Daario Naharis?
( footsteps )
The city is yours,
my queen.
( music playing )
( people laughing,
chatting )
They're good,
aren't they?
They ought to be
because they cost enough.
( laughs )
- Look at the crowd there.
- ( Catelyn laughs )
He complained
about this marriage
the entire ride
from Riverrun,
and now look at him.
Blackfish:
The gods love
to reward a fool.
- Uncle.
- What?
He's my nephew.
I love him.
And he's a damned fool.
( chuckles )
Don't you drink,
Lord Bolton?
Never do, my lady.
Dulls the senses.
That's the point.
Didn't you marry
one of these Frey girls?
Aye.
Lord Walder let me
choose any of his
granddaughters
and promised me
the girl's weight
in silver as a dowry.
So I have
a fat young bride.
( laughs )
I hope she makes you
very happy.
Well, she's made me
very rich.
Pardon, my lord,
my lady.
I need to find
a tree to piss on.
My mother's alone
with Roose Bolton.
I should rescue her.
Your mother is less
in need of rescue
than any woman
I've ever met.
Be kind.
She's finally starting
to like you.
And I like her.
But if she had her way,
I would be back in Volantis
playing my harp and you
would be sitting over there
eating blackberries
out of Roslin Frey's hand.
Perhaps I've made
a terrible mistake.
( scoffs )
Striking your king
is an act of treason.
No, don't.
Don't insult them.
Your Grace.
( pounding on tables )
( pounding stops )
The septon has prayed
his prayers,
some words were said,
and Lord Edmure
has wrapped my daughter
in a cloak.
But they are not yet
man and wife.
A sword needs a sheath.
( guests laughing )
( laughs )
- And a wedding
needs a bedding.
- ( guests cheering )
What does my sire say?
( guests chanting )
To bed! To bed! To bed!
If you think the time
is right, Lord Walder,
by all means,
let us bed them.
( guests cheering )
( music playing )
( chanting )
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Man:
Go on!
Oh!
Careful now, ladies.
Once you set
that monster free,
there's no caging
him again.
( chanting continues )
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Poor girl.
Every bride
suffers the same.
I'm sure you endured
yours with grace.
Oh, Ned forbade it.
He said it wouldn't be right
if he broke a man's jaw
on our wedding night.
( chuckles )
That is a very
strange custom.
I suppose it does
seem strange
from a foreigner's
perspective.
It seems normal
to you?
It's a tradition.
Without the bedding ceremony,
there's no real proof
the lord and lady
consummated their marriage.
But there are other ways
of providing proof.
Boy or girl?
I don't know.
But if it's a boy,
I know what we should
name him.
Oh, do you?
It seems to me the father
should have some say in
his son's naming.
Eddard.
Don't you want to teach
little Ned Stark
how to ride horses?
I do.
( band playing
"Rains of Castamere" )
( wolf whining )
( whines )
Man:
Go on, line 'em up!
( chatter, laughter )
( laughing )
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Got salt pork
for the feast.
The feast is over.
Hound:
Doesn't sound
like it's over.
If I tell you
it's over, it's over.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell out of here.
Got pig's feet, too.
Are you soft
in the head?
Turn this cart around.
( music stops )
Your Grace.
I feel
I've been remiss
in my duties.
I've given you meat
and wine and music,
but I haven't shown you
the hospitality
you deserve.
My king has married
and I owe my new queen
a wedding gift.
Robb!
( gasping )
( grunts )
( screams continue )
( screaming )
( men laughing )
Stark soldier:
You ready to head home
to Winterfell, right?
( men laughing )
Stark soldier:
Feast over yet, is it?
Aye, it's over.
( men screaming )
( wolf howling )
- ( banging )
- ( growling )
( growling )
Guard:
Follow him.
- Aim!
- ( snarling )
( growls )
( wolf whines )
( guard shouting )
( groaning )
( guards shouting )
It's too late.
- ( grunting )
- ( fighting continues )
( chuckles )
The King
in the North arises.
( chuckles )
Lord Walder!
Lord Walder, enough!
Let it end!
Please.
He is my son.
My first son.
Let him go and I swear
that we will forget this.
I swear it by
the old gods and new.
We will take
no vengeance.
You already swore me
one oath right here
in my castle.
You swore by all
the gods your son
would marry my daughter!
Catelyn:
Take me for a hostage,
but let Robb go.
Robb, get up.
Get up and walk out.
Please!
And why would I
let him do that?
On my honor as a Tully,
on my honor as a Stark,
let him go
or I will cut
your wife's throat.
I'll find another.
Mother.
The Lannisters send
their regards.
( knife pierces )
( wails )
( knife clatters )