( White Walkers screeching )
- ( weapons clashing )
- ( men shouting )
- ( squelching )
- Man: Fall back!
( wind howling )
( panting )
( breathing heavily )
Brother?
( snow crunching )
( Ghost snarling )
Did you send the ravens?
Tarly, look at me.
That was your job.
Your only job.
We need to get
back to the Wall.
It's a long march.
We know what's out there,
but we have to make it,
have to warn them
or before winter's done,
everyone you've ever known
will be dead.
( theme music playing )
( wind blowing )
( people talking
indistinctly )
First time you've seen
a giant, Jon Snow?
Well, don't stare too long.
They're shy.
When they stop being shy,
they get angry.
And when they're angry,
I've seen them pound a man
straight into the ground
like a hammer on a nail.
( growling )
- Man: Crow!
- Boy: Crow!
- Girl: Look over there!
- Man #2: Crow!
Girl:
Crow! Look over here!
Look!
Woman:
Ah, look, crow coming!
Boy:
Crow!
Ygritte:
You're wearing
the wrong color.
Mance was a ranger.
In your hearts,
all you crows want
to fly free.
When I'm free,
will I be free to go?
- Crow!
Sure, you will.
- Oh!
- ( laughter )
And I'll be free
to kill you.
Got no respect, this lot.
Got no fathers to slap 'em
when they're foul.
What happened
to their fathers?
Some of them were killed
by crows like you.
Don't look so grim,
Jon Snow.
If Mance Rayder likes you,
you'll live another day.
And if he don't...
I smell a crow.
We killed his friends.
Thought you'd want
to question this one.
What do we want
with a baby crow?
This baby killed
Qhorin Halfhand.
He wants to be
one of us.
That half-handed cunt
killed friends of mine.
Friends twice your size.
My father told me
big men fall just as quick
as little ones
if you put a sword
through their hearts.
Plenty of little men
tried to put their swords
through my heart.
And there's plenty
of little skeletons
buried in the woods.
- What's your name, boy?
- Jon Snow.
Your Grace.
( laughter )
- Your Grace?
- ( laughter )
Did you hear that?
From now on, you'd better
kneel every time I fart.
( laughs )
Stand, boy.
We don't kneel for anyone
beyond the Wall.
So, you're
Ned Stark's bastard.
Thank you for the gift,
Lord of Bones.
You can leave us.
The girl likes you.
You like her back, Snow?
That why you want
to join us?
Bearded warrior:
Don't panic, boy.
This isn't the damned
Night's Watch
where we make you
swear off girls.
This chicken eater
you thought was king
is Tormund Giantsbane.
Can't believe this pup
killed the Halfhand.
He was our enemy
and I'm glad he's dead.
He was my brother once.
Back when he had
a whole hand.
What were you
doing with him?
The Lord Commander sent me
to the Halfhand for seasoning.
Why?
He wants me to lead
one day.
But here you are,
a traitor
kneeling before
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
If I'm a traitor,
then you are, too.
Why do you want
to join us, Jon Snow?
I want to be free.
No, I don't think so.
I think what you want
most of all
is to be a hero.
I'll ask you
one last time--
why do you want
to join us?
We stopped
at Craster's Keep
on the way north.
I saw...
You saw what?
I saw Craster take
his own baby boy
and leave it
in the woods.
I saw what took it.
You're telling me
you saw one of them?
And why would that make you
desert your brothers?
Because when I told
the Lord Commander,
he already knew.
Thousands of years ago,
the First Men
battled the White Walkers
and defeated them.
I want to fight for the side
that fights for the living.
Did I come
to the right place?
We'll need to find you
a new cloak.
( children chattering )
What if you took off
that bit there?
Don't you want to leave
something to the imagination?
Trouble is, I've never
had much imagination.
I want you to take it off.
( tsks )
Mouth.
( door opens, closes )
Podrick:
Ser Bronn.
I didn't hear that.
- Apologies, ser.
- Bronn: Back away.
Keep backing away
till you're outside
this establishment.
- Then back away some more.
- Lord Tyrion sent me.
I will murder you, boy.
He said it was a matter
of life and death.
( knocking )
- Pod?
- Cersei: It's your sister.
The queen.
What are they doing here?
Protecting me, I assume.
Will you let me in?
No, I don't think so.
If I wanted to kill you,
do you think
I'd let a wooden door
stop me?
They stay outside.
I'm not afraid of you,
little brother.
- Why are you here?
- I wanted to see your face.
They said you'd lost
your nose, but it's not
as gruesome as all that.
The man who cut me
lost more than his nose.
I should hope so.
The rebels came
for Joffrey's head,
they lost their own.
Thanks to Father.
Of course, it wasn't a rebel
who tried to kill me.
No? Curious.
Bit of a comedown
from chamber of the Hand.
But then I don't suppose
you need much room.
Grand Maester Pycelle
made the same joke.
You must be proud to be
as funny as a man whose
balls brush his knees.
You're meeting
Father today?
How do you know that?
Because I have hundreds
of spies in my employ.
The Master of Whisperers
owes me a favor or two.
Father told me.
What do you want from him?
What do I want from him?
He's my father.
Do I need
to want something?
I'm sure
he loves me dearly,
as any father loves
his child,
his baby boy.
Yet he hasn't come
to visit once
since arriving
in King's Landing.
I lay here,
my face split in half,
but Father never came.
You're going
to make me cry.
Why do you care
what I want from him?
Because you've slandered me
to Father before.
Slandered?
When?
You told him
I had my guards
beat that servant girl
at Casterly Rock.
You did have
your guards beat her.
A girl of nine,
I believe.
I was nine, too.
She lost an eye,
if I remember correctly.
If I remember correctly,
she never stole
a necklace again.
It's not slander
if it's true.
And what's this truth
you plan on telling him today?
Why are you so nervous
about what I'm going
to say to Father?
Because you're a liar.
I expect you'll tell lies
about me, about Joffrey.
Any lies in particular?
You're a clever man,
but you're not half as clever
as you think you are.
Still makes me
more clever than you.
( door opens )
Oh, look at these two
shining warriors.
Ser Taryn Mant and...
Ser Whosit of Whocares.
Ser Meryn Trant.
Ser Bronn
of the Blackwater.
- You're no knight.
- Pod.
Ser Bronn
of the Blackwater
was anointed
by the king himself.
You're an up-jumped
cutthroat,
nothing more.
That's exactly who I am.
And you're a grub
in fancy armor
who's better
at beating little girls
than fighting men.
Now, I have an appointment
with Lord Tyrion.
You put your hand
on that door,
you lose the hand.
As much as I appreciate
a walk in the sunshine,
your lordship,
I am wondering
why you sent for me.
A number of people
in this city want to kill me.
You're here to protect me.
I've been doing that
for a while now.
Do you grow bored
protecting me?
I grow poor
protecting you.
Poor?
Under my patronage
you've become a knight,
you've served as Commander
of the City Watch.
- Briefly.
- I'm sure you
filled your pockets.
And now my pockets
are empty.
You've given me a taste
for the finer things.
And if you want me
to carry on protecting you,
you'll need to pay more.
- I thought
we were friends.
- We are.
But I'm a sellsword.
I sell my sword.
I don't loan it out
to friends as a favor.
- How much?
- Double.
- Double?
- I'm a knight now.
Knights
are worth double.
I don't even know how much
I'm paying you now.
Which means
you can afford it.
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( waves lapping )
( seabirds calling )
Here. Here!
Help me!
( horn blowing )
Who are you?
I was in the battle
at Blackwater.
I was a captain
and a knight.
Aye, ser,
and serving which king?
The one true king
of Westeros--
Stannis Baratheon.
I thought you were dead.
Everyone thought
you were dead.
And your son?
He may have swam
ashore as you did.
No, the wildfire took him.
I saw it.
I'm so sorry,
my friend.
I, too, have lost a son.
There is nothing worse
in this world.
But, Davos, you were
a good father.
If I was a good father,
he'd still be here.
Stannis lives?
He licks his wounds
at Dragonstone.
Will you take me there?
There is nothing for me
at Dragonstone.
This war is not over.
Not for you, maybe.
But for Salladhor Saan,
the war is over.
We're both sworn
to King Stannis.
I am sworn to no man.
I promised you 30 ships
and you promised me
riches and glory.
I delivered the ships.
Stannis never gives up.
Never.
- Now he will regroup--
- He's a broken man.
His fleet lies at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
They say he sees no one--
not his generals,
not even his wife.
Only the Red Woman
whispering in his ear,
telling him what
she sees in the flames
and burning men alive.
What?
They built a great fire
when Stannis returned.
All those who spoke
against her she called
servants of darkness.
They say she sang
to them as they burned.
I'm a pirate.
You're a smuggler.
Servants of darkness.
I'm thinking
Dragonstone is a good
place for us to avoid.
Take me back there, please.
You cannot turn
Stannis against her.
Maybe not, but I could
carve her heart out.
You could try.
If you fail,
they will burn you.
If you succeed,
they'll burn you.
And you've only
just come back to life.
Stay alive a little
longer, my friend.
You call me friend.
You drank with me
on my wedding day.
And you drank with me
on four of my wedding days,
but I don't ask you
for favors.
I have to stop her.
Please, do this for me.
When you are dead,
I will gather your bones
in a little sack
and let your widow
wear them around her neck.
We should set the siege lines
1,000 yards from Harrenhal.
There won't be a siege.
The Mountain can't
defend a ruin.
I imagine the Mountain
will defend
whatever Tywin Lannister
tells him to defend.
The Lannisters have been
running from us since Oxcross.
I'd love a fight.
The men would love a fight.
I don't think
we're going to get one.
( flies buzzing )
200 Northmen
slaughtered like sheep.
The debt will be
repaid, my friend.
For them
and for your sons.
Will it?
They rot in the ground
while their killer
runs free.
The Kingslayer won't
remain free for long.
My best hunters
are after him.
- Robb: A Mallister?
- Ser Jeremy.
My father's bannerman.
Find her a chamber
that will serve as a cell.
Talisa:
She's your mother.
She freed
Jaime Lannister.
The Lannisters robbed
them of their sons
and she robbed them
of their justice.
( coughing )
Water.
This needs to be
cleaned and closed.
What's your name, friend?
Qyburn.
You're lucky to be alive.
Lucky?
( birds cawing )
( sighs )
The badge
looks good on you.
Almost as good
as it looked on me.
Are you enjoying
your new position?
Am I enjoying it?
I was very happy
as Hand of the King.
( chuckles )
Yes.
I heard how happy you were.
( blows )
You brought a whore
into my bed.
It wasn't your bed
at the time.
I sent you here
to advise the king.
I gave you real power
and authority.
You chose
to spend your days
as you always have,
bedding harlots
and drinking with thieves.
Occasionally I drank
with the harlots.
What do you want, Tyrion?
Why does everyone assume
I want something?
Can't I simply visit
with my beloved father?
My beloved father who
somehow forgot to visit
his wounded son
after he fell
on the battlefield.
Maester Pycelle assured me
your wounds were not fatal.
I organized
the defense of this city
while you held court
in the ruins of Harrenhal.
I led the foray
when the enemies
were at the gate
while your grandson,
the king,
quivered in fear
behind the walls.
I bled in the mud
for our family.
And as my reward,
I was trundled off
to some dark little cell.
But what do I want?
A little bloody gratitude
would be a start.
Jugglers and singers
require applause.
You are a Lannister.
Do you think I demanded
a garland of roses
every time I suffered
a wound on a battlefield?
Hmm?
Now, I have seven kingdoms
to look after
and three of them
are in open rebellion.
So tell me what you want.
I want what is mine
by right.
Jaime is your eldest son,
heir to your lands and titles.
But he is a Kingsguard,
forbidden from marriage
or inheritance.
The day Jaime put on
the white cloak,
he gave up his claim
to Casterly Rock.
I am your son
and lawful heir.
You want Casterly Rock?
It is mine by right.
( sighs )
We'll find you
accommodations
more suited
to your name
and as a reward
for your accomplishments
during the battle
of Blackwater Bay.
And when the time is right,
you will be given a position
fit for your talents
so that you can
serve your family
and protect our legacy.
And if you serve
faithfully,
you will be rewarded
with a suitable wife.
And I would let myself
be consumed by maggots
before mocking
the family name
and making you
heir to Casterly Rock.
- Why?
You ask that?
You, who killed your mother
to come into the world?
You are an ill-made,
spiteful little creature
full of envy, lust,
and low cunning.
Men's laws give you
the right to bear my name
and display my colors
since I cannot prove
that you are not mine.
And to teach me humility,
the gods have condemned me
to watch you waddle about
wearing that proud lion
that was my father's sigil
and his father's before him.
But neither gods nor men
will ever compel me
to let you turn Casterly Rock
into your whorehouse.
Go, now.
Speak no more of your rights
to Casterly Rock.
Go.
Oh, one more thing.
The next whore I catch
in your bed I'll hang.
Sansa: Dorne.
It's going to Dorne.
- Shae: Why Dorne?
- It's carrying silk
and it's supposed to bring
back wine in exchange.
But it's not
coming back.
The captain's tired
of risking his life
so King's Landing
lords and ladies
can get drunk
on better wine
than they deserve.
He's going
to stay in Dorne.
Wait out the winter
where it's beautiful
and warm.
I met some people
in Dorne who weren't
so beautiful and warm.
Don't ruin the game.
I told you,
I don't want to play.
What about that one there?
That one?
It's going to Volantis.
Why?
Because when I got
on a ship in Volantis,
it looked like that one.
That's not how
the game works.
You're not supposed to just
blurt out the right answer.
You've got
to invent a story
about where the ship
is going and why.
Why should I make up a story
when I know the truth?
Because the truth
is always either
terrible or boring.
Lovely day for it.
Watching the ships.
Lord Baelish.
Might I speak
with Lady Sansa
alone for a moment?
I saw your mother
not long ago.
She's very eager
to see you.
And your sister.
Arya's alive?
You said
you'd take me home.
You said King's Landing
was your home.
You are the property
of the crown.
Stealing you
would be treason.
If you were to tell
just one person--
- I won't tell anyone.
- How do I know?
Because I'm a terrible liar.
You said so yourself.
Please, Lord Baelish.
Tell me what to do.
Tell me when.
I'm waiting for word
on an assignment
that will take me far away
from the capital.
When I set sail,
I might be able
to take you with me.
But you'll need
to be ready to leave
on a moment's notice.
You're her handmaiden?
Yes.
And you're his...?
I help manage
his affairs.
- He's an important person.
- So is she.
I grew up in the shadow
of her father's castle.
The day she was born,
they rang the bells
from sunrise till sunset.
We've both done
rather well, you and I.
Yes.
Given where we started.
And where is that?
It's not easy
for girls like us
to dig our way out.
Ros:
Watch out for her.
I always do.
Watch out for her
with him.
( dragon screeching )
( screeches )
( screeching )
They're growing fast.
Not fast enough.
I can't wait that long.
I need an army.
( dragon screeching )
We'll be in Astapor
by nightfall.
Some say the Unsullied
are the greatest soldiers
in the world.
The greatest slave-soldiers
The distinction means
a good deal to some people.
Do those people
have any better ideas
about how to put you
on the Iron Throne?
It's too beautiful
a day to argue.
( man vomiting )
You're right.
Another lovely day
on the high seas.
Daenerys:
Don't mock them.
They're the first Dothraki
who have ever been on a ship.
They followed me
across the poison water.
If they'll do it,
others will.
And with a true
khalasar--
The Dothraki follow strength
above all, khaleesi.
You'll have a true
khalasar when you prove
yourself strong.
And not before.
( seabirds calling )
Your Grace.
I heard you were dead.
Not yet.
I had hoped to speak
to you alone, Your Grace.
We are alone.
Your Grace, you are
the rightful king.
Not only by blood.
You're an honorable man,
a just man.
And there is still
a war to fight.
I am fighting.
By burning
prisoners alive?
How would you punish
the infidels, Ser Davos?
I do not judge people
for the gods they worship.
If I did, I'd have
thrown you in the sea
before you ever set foot
on Dragonstone.
- I'm not your enemy.
- You are my enemy.
Was it me you fought
on Blackwater Bay?
Did I set
your ships ablaze?
I wasn't there
when the wildfire killed
our men by the thousands.
I could have
saved those men.
You would have
taken the city,
Stannis would now sit
upon his rightful throne,
and you would
stand beside him.
But I wasn't there
because you convinced
your king to leave me behind.
Do you hear them screaming?
All those burning men
in the water
crying for their mothers,
for their gods for help?
Until the moment
the Blackwater swallowed them.
( gasps )
Don't despair, Ser Davos.
What I told
your son is true.
Death by fire
is the purest death.
( growls )
This woman is evil!
She's the mother of demons.
Take him to the dungeon
and lock him in a cell.
- Your Grace!
- Come on.
You've chosen
the darkness, Ser Davos.
- She will destroy us all!
- I will pray for you.
Davos:
Your Grace!
( door closes )
( guards shouting )
Guard:
Halt. Down.
Guard #2:
Why have we stopped?
It's Lady Margaery,
Your Grace.
Joffrey:
What is she doing?
Who gave her permission?
Maid: My lady.
We should have
guards, my lady.
Why?
Pardon me.
Stop, my lady.
You'll ruin your dress.
I have others.
Would you like
to speak with her,
Your Grace?
No.
He was a soldier.
He went to fight
on the walls
when the ships came
into Blackwater Bay.
He never came back.
And your mother?
She died
when she had me.
Bad men wanted
to come into this city
and do terrible things,
but your father stopped them.
Whenever you look
at this knight,
I want you to remember
your father.
He wasn't a knight.
He was just a soldier.
And what do knights
swear to do?
Protect the weak
and uphold the good.
Your father did that.
Be proud of him.
Was your father
a soldier, too?
You should be proud, too.
Under King Joffrey's
leadership,
your fathers
saved the city.
They saved us all.
From now on, we're going
to take care of you.
All of you.
( children laughing )
Come to me for whatever
you need to feed them,
clothe them,
or house them.
Directly to me.
( doors open )
- Your Grace.
Please, sit.
Sit.
I do apologize,
my lady.
Small council meetings.
At what point
does it become treason
to waste the king's time?
( laughs )
That's a lovely gown,
my lady.
Yes, it suits you
perfectly.
I imagine you might
be rather cold.
The climate is a bit
more forgiving back in
Highgarden, Your Grace.
Shall I have them bring
you a shawl, my lady?
I am touched by your
concern, Your Grace.
Luckily for us Tyrells,
our blood runs quite warm.
- Doesn't it, Loras?
- Yes.
Loras, isn't the queen's
gown magnificent?
The fabric,
the embroidery,
the metalwork.
I've never seen
anything like it.
You might find a bit
of armor quite useful
once you become queen.
Perhaps before.
Joffrey tells me you
stopped your carriage
at Flea Bottom
on your way back from
the sept this morning.
Yes. I paid a visit
to an orphanage
the High Septon
told me about.
Margaery does a great
deal of work with the poor
back in Highgarden.
The lowest among us are no
different from the highest
if you give them a chance
and approach them
with an open heart.
Cersei:
An open heart is what
you'll get in Flea Bottom
if you're not careful,
my dear.
Not long ago, we were
attacked by a mob there.
We had a full complement
of guards that didn't stop them.
The king barely escaped
with his life.
My mother's always had
a penchant for drama.
Facts become less and less
important to her
as she grows older.
Our lives were never
truly in danger.
You're right, of course.
But you are
your father's son.
We can't all have
a king's bravery.
Hunger turns men
into beasts.
I'm glad House Tyrell
has been able to help
in this regard.
They tell me
100 wagons arrive
daily now from the Reach.
Wheat, barley, apples.
We've had a blessed harvest.
And, of course,
it's our duty to
assist the capital
in time of need.
Well, as Ser Loras said,
Lady Margaery has done
this sort of...
charitable work before.
I'm sure she knows
what she's doing.
I'm sure she does.
( speaking Valyrian )
The Unsullied have stood here
for a day and a night
with no food or water.
( speaking Valyrian )
They will stand
until they drop.
( speaking Valyrian )
Such is their
obedience.
They may suit my needs.
Tell me of their training.
( speaking Valyrian )
They begin their
training at five.
Every day they drill
from dawn to dusk
until they have mastered
the shortsword,
the shield,
and the three spears.
Only one boy in four survives
this rigorous training.
( speaking Valyrian )
Missandei:
Their discipline
and loyalty are absolute.
They fear nothing.
Even the bravest men
fear death.
( speaking Valyrian )
( continues in Valyrian )
Missandei:
My master says
the Unsullied are not men.
Death means nothing
to them.
( speaking Valyrian )
He begs you attend to this
carefully, Your Grace.
( speaking Valyrian )
Tell the good master
there is no need.
( speaking Valyrian )
Missandei:
My master points out
that men don't need nipples.
( speaking Valyrian )
To win his shield,
an Unsullied must go
to the slave marts
with a silver mark,
find a newborn and kill it
before its mother's eyes.
This way, my master says,
we make certain
there is no weakness
left in them.
You take a babe
from its mother's arms,
kill it as she watches,
and pay for her pain
with a silver coin?
( speaking Valyrian )
( continues in Valyrian )
My master would
like you to know
that the silver is paid
to the baby's owner,
not the mother.
How many do you
have to sell?
( Missandei speaking
Valyrian )
8,000.
Master Kraznys asks
that you please hurry.
Many other buyers
are interested.
8,000 dead babies.
The Unsullied
are a means to an end.
Once I own them,
these men--
They're not men.
Not anymore.
Once I own
an army of slaves,
what will I be?
Do you think these slaves
will have better lives
serving Kraznys
and men like him
or serving you?
You'll be fair to them.
You won't mutilate them
to make a point.
You won't order them
to murder babies.
You'll see they're properly
fed and sheltered.
A great injustice
has been done to them.
Closing your eyes
will not undo it.
( grunts )
( chittering )
( hisses )
The warlocks.
I owe you my life, ser.
The honor is mine,
my queen.
You know this man?
I know him
as one of the greatest
fighters the Seven Kingdoms
has ever seen
and as the Lord Commander
of Robert Baratheon's
Kingsguard.
King Robert is dead.
I have been searching
for you, Daenerys Stormborn,
to ask your forgiveness.
I was sworn to protect
your family.
I failed them.
I am Barristan Selmy,
Kingsguard to your father.
Allow me to join
your Queensguard
and I will not
fail you again.
( theme music playing )