Lord,
cast your light upon us.
All: Lord of light, defend us.
Show us the truth.
Strike this man down if he is guilty.
Give strength to his sword if he is true.
Lord of light, give us wisdom,
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
All: For the night is
dark and full of terrors.
(Gasps)
(Both grunting)
Get back.
All: (Chanting) Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
- Guilty.
- Kill him!
(Chanting continues)
(Chanting stops)
Lord, cast your
light upon this man, your servant.
Bring him back from
death and darkness. Restore his flame.
(Grunting)
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
- Lord, cast...
- Arya, don't!
Thoros: Bring him back
from death and darkness...
- (Grunts)
- (Yelps)
No! Let go of me! Let me go!
Looks like their god
likes me more than your butcher's boy.
Burn in hell!
Beric: He will.
But not today.
(Indistinct chattering)
Orell says there are crows
patrolling on the wall.
Tell me what you know.
There are four to a patrol, two
builders to check for structural damage,
two rangers to watch for enemies.
How often do these patrols go out?
It varies.
If I knew where on the wall
we were heading, I could tell you.
You'd like to know that.
(Sighs)
There are 19 castles guarding the wall.
How many are manned?
Three.
You sure of that?
Which three?
Castle black.
Aye, castle black.
Everyone knows castle black.
Which others?
Eastwatch-by-the-sea and the shadow tower.
How many men remain in castle black?
- A thousand.
- Liar.
What happens to your
eagle after I kill you?
Does he drift away
like a kite with his strings cut,
or does he just flop dead to the ground?
He's no crow.
Just 'cause you want him
inside, you don't make him one of us.
I'm not afraid of you.
(Groans)
I like you, boy.
But if you lie to me, I'll pull
your guts out through your throat.
A thousand men.
(Sighs)
We'll find out soon enough.
I don't need you to protect me.
Of course you do.
Who stopped rattleshirt
when he was about to cut your throat?
Who vouched for you with mance?
It seems you owe me a debt.
Give it back.
Well, I stole it.
It's mine. If you want
it, come steal it back.
Yg ritte!
Ygritte! Seven hells.
Is orell right? Are you still a crow?
It's time you proved yourself.
Ygritte.
You swore some vows.
I want you to break 'em.
I want you to see me.
All of me.
We shouldn't.
We should.
(Exhales)
Why are you still dressed?
You know nothing, Jon snow.
(Gasps)
(Moaning)
That thing you did with your mouth...
Is that what lords
do to their ladies in the south?
I don't know.
I just wanted to kiss you there is all.
Hmm.
You seemed to like it.
Aye, I liked it some.
Who taught you that?
There's been no one else. Only you.
A maid. (Chuckles) You were a maid.
I was a man of the night's watch.
How about you? Were you a maid?
What do you think?
Who was he?
Just a boy.
He came trading with his brothers.
He had red hair like
me. Kissed by fire. But...
He was weak. Not like you.
That was the first one.
Then there was this thenn boy.
Spoke no common,
but, gods, he was built like a mammoth...
(Clears throat) Yeah, thanks.
I think I've heard enough.
We'd best get back.
Tormund...
I'm not done with you yet.
How long's it been since you had a bath?
Let's not go back.
Let's stay here a while longer.
I don't ever want to
leave this cave, Jon snow.
Not ever.
Hound: I want my gold.
It says clearly on that
note, you'll be paid when the war is over.
Piss on that! You're nothing but thieves.
We're outlaws. Outlaws
steal. You're lucky we didn't kill you.
Come try it, Archer.
I'll shove those arrows up your ass.
You can't let him go.
He's a murderer. He's guilty.
Not in the eyes of god.
- You can't!
- Enough!
Beric: The judgment isn't ours to make.
Go in peace, sandor clegane.
The lord of light isn't done with you yet.
Man: Riders coming through!
(Horse neighing)
(Indistinct chattering)
Man: The kingslayer.
- Down!
- (Grunts)
On your knees.
Lord Bolton, I give you the kingslayer.
(Groans)
Pick him up, Locke.
(Grunts)
You've lost a hand.
No, my lord, he has it here. (Chuckles)
Take this away.
Send it to his father?
You'll hold your tongue
unless you want to lose it.
Cut her free.
Apologies, my lady.
You're under my protection now.
Thank you, my lord.
Find suitable rooms for our guests.
We'll speak later.
Lord Bolton.
Is there word from the capital?
You haven't heard?
Stannis Baratheon laid siege
to king's landing.
Sailed into Blackwater bay.
Stormed the gates with thousands of men.
And your sister...
How can I put this?
Your sister...
Is alive and well.
Your father's forces prevailed.
Ser Jaime isn't well.
(Groaning)
Take him to beurn.
(Groaning continues)
(Jaime groans)
Will I die?
The corruption has spread.
I fear it must be cutaway.
The safest course
would be to take the whole arm off.
Then you'll die.
You're no maester.
Where's your chain?
The citadel stripped me of it.
They found some of my experiments too bold.
I can leave your upper arm,
make the cut at your elbow.
I don't need my right hand to kill you.
I can take away the rotting flesh
and try and burn
out the corruption with boiling wine.
Mmm. (Clears throat)
With any luck, that will suffice.
You'll need milk of the poppy.
No milk of the poppy.
There will be pain.
I'll scream.
Quite a bit of pain.
I'll scream loudly.
(Groans)
(Breathing heavily)
(Screaming)
Cersei: Lord baelish.
Your grace.
I wonder if I might ask you for a favor.
Of course, your grace.
I believe that house Tyrell don't hold the
crown's best interests at heart.
I see. And have you
shared these suspicions with lord tywin?
My father's a practical man.
He appreciates facts.
Myself, I often find them a hindrance.
And he appreciates
those who aid his family, as you well know.
He's almost as generous
to those who help us
as he is unpleasant
towards those who don't.
You have a good
working relationship with the tyrells.
I thought you might
look into it before you leave the capital.
- I shall do my best.
- Thank you.
And your best will prove better than
when I asked you to locate Arya stark?
I assure you that it will.
Gods, boy, that's enough.
We're not in a tavern.
- Pardon, my lady.
- No need to speak.
Are there any figs? Fetch some.
I always take figs
midafternoon. They help move the bowels.
To what do I owe this summons?
Thank you for seeing me, my lady.
I had hoped we might discuss
a few financial matters.
I climbed all those steps
to discuss financial matters?
It's the royal wedding.
I'm told you had a hand in planning it.
Naturally.
It's shaping up to be
a very involved affair.
The word "extravagant" has been used.
What good is the word "extravagant"
if it can't be used
to describe a royal wedding?
- I understand that.
- Good.
But, as master of coin, it falls upon me
to calculate the cost for the crown.
As of now, it's a huge expense.
And?
And we're at war, lady olenna.
Oh, I'd nearly forgotten.
And maintaining supply lines...
I can't think how it slipped my mind.
What is it, 12,000
infantrymen the Tyrell family has supplied?
1,800 mounted lances. 2,000 in support.
Provisions, so this city
might survive the winter.
A million bushels of wheat.
Half a million bushels each
of barley, oats, and rye.
20,000 head of cattle. 50,000 sheep.
You don't have to lecture me
about wartime expenses.
I'm quite familiar with them.
And we are grateful for your contributions,
which are necessary
for the preservation of the realm.
As is a royal wedding.
The people are hungry
for more than just food.
They crave distractions.
And if we don't provide them,
they'll create their own.
And their distractions are likely to
end with us being torn to pieces.
A royal wedding is much
safer. Wouldn't you say?
I would.
And traditionally paid
for by the royal family.
I was told you were drunk,
impertinent, and thoroughly debauched.
Imagine my disappointment at finding
nothing but a browbeaten bookkeeper.
(Footsteps approaching)
Where did you go for them, volantis?
- My lady...
- Oh, very well.
I won't have it said
that house Tyrell refuses to play its part.
We'll pay for half,
and the celebrations will go on as planned.
- Is that sufficient?
- Quite. Thank you.
Very good, then. That's settled. Good day.
- Give me that.
- (Door opening)
Arya: What are you doing?
Just mending lord beric's armor.
I'm going to stay and Smith
for the brotherhood.
Have you lost your mind?
When the lannisters find this place,
you think they'll spare the smiths?
They'll cave your head in.
They wanted to kill me
long before I joined the brotherhood.
You don't have to.
I want to. They need good men.
Robb needs good men, too.
We're leaving tomorrow.
And then you...
What? Serve him?
I've served men my entire life.
I served master mott at king's landing,
and he sold me to the watch.
I served lord tywin at harrenhal,
wondering every day
if I'd get tortured or killed.
- I'm done serving.
- You just said you were serving lord beric.
He may be their leader, but they chose him.
These men are brothers. They're a family.
I've never had a family.
I can be your family.
You wouldn't be my family.
You'd be "my lady."
(Water dripping)
- (Indistinct yelling)
- (Swords clanking)
Willem.
(Man groaning loudly)
Willem!
(Groans)
Is this a rescue?
Lannister filth! Take him!
Please, I didn't do anything.
I'm just a squire. Please...
(Grunts)
(Thuds)
Bring them in.
(Door opening)
Is that all of them?
It took five of you
to murder two unarmed squires?
Not murder, your grace. Vengeance.
Vengeance?
Those boys didn't kill your sons.
I saw harrion die
on the battlefield, and torrhen...
Was strangled by the kingslayer.
- They were his kin.
- They were boys!
Look at them.
Tell your mother to look at them.
She killed them as much as I.
My mother had nothing to do with
this. This was your treason.
It's treason to free your enemies.
In war, you kill your enemies.
Did your father not teach you that, boy?
- (Groans)
- Leave him.
Leave me to the king.
He wants to give me
a scolding before he sets me free.
That's how he
deals with treason. Our king in the north.
Or should I call him
the king who lost the north?
Escort lord karstark
to the dungeon. Hang the rest.
Mercy! I didn't kill
anyone. I only watched for the guards.
This one was only the watcher.
Hang him last, so he
can watch the others die.
Please! Please, no. They made me do it!
They made me! They made me!
(Inhales)
(Door closes)
Word of this can't leave riverrun.
They were tywin Lannister's nephews.
The lannisters pay their debts.
They never stop talking about it.
Would you make me a liar as well?
It wouldn't be lying.
We will Bury them
and remain silent until the war is done.
I'm not fighting forjustice
if I don't serve justice
to murderers in my ranks,
no matter how highborn.
He has to die.
The karstarks are northmen. They
won't forgive the killing of their lord.
Your mother's right. If you do this,
the karstarks will abandon you.
You tended to their wounds.
You brought them supper. Now they're dead.
And more boys will keep dying
until this war is over.
You need karstark men to end it.
Spare his life. Keep him as a hostage.
A hostage.
Tell the karstarks that as long as they're
loyal, he will not be harmed.
(Thunder rumbling)
The blood of the first men flows through
my veins as much as yours, boy.
I fought the mad king for your father.
I fought Joffrey for you.
We are kin, stark and karstark.
That didn't stop you from betraying
me, and it won't save you now.
I don't want it to save me. I want it
to haunt you to the end of your days.
Kneel, my lord.
Rickard karstark, lord of karhold,
here, in sight of gods and
men, I sentence you to die.
Would you speak a final word?
Kill me and be cursed.
You are no king of mine.
(Grunts)
Arya: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
Ser meryn.
The hound.
What are you going to do with me?
At first light we'll ride for
riverrun. Your brother's there now.
He'll make a contribution to our
cause, and you can go home.
I'm a hostage and you're selling me.
Don't think of it that way.
But it is that way.
It is.
And it isn't.
More is than isn't.
Beric admired your father
a great deal, you know.
He wanted to refuse your ransom altogether.
So, why don't you?
We need the gold.
(Sighs)
Do I frighten you, child?
You're angry with me,
and I don't blame you,
but letting him go was the right thing.
I have more reason to want him hanged.
I thought he killed you.
He did.
But how...
Thoros, how many times
have you brought me back?
It's the lord of light who brings you back.
I'm just the lucky drunk
who says the words.
How many times?
Five, I think.
No, this makes six.
Six.
There was the first time. The mountain.
Show her.
Lance right through the chest.
Beric: Then I was stabbed in the belly.
Then it was an arrow in the back.
And that ax in the side.
Then the lannisters caught me
and executed me for treason.
Was it a hanging or a dagger in the eye?
Both. Fuckers couldn't decide.
And the hound makes six.
Second time I've been killed by a clegane.
Thoros: You'd think you'd learn.
It's not getting any easier, you know.
Beric: I know.
Every time I come back,
I'm a bit less.
Pieces of you get chipped away.
Could you bring back a man without a head?
Not six times. Just once.
I don't think it works that way, child.
He was a good man, ned stark.
He's at rest now, somewhere.
I would never wish my life upon him.
I would.
You're alive.
Selyse: Lord, cast your light upon me.
Protect me in the darkness.
Burn away my sins.
Help me serve you.
Use me as you will. (Gasps)
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
(Door opening)
I have prayed day and night
for you to come to me.
My lady.
I meant to come sooner.
The battle...
I know of your troubles, my king.
The lady melisandre has told me everything.
Yes, of course.
(Sighs)
You mustn't despair.
Your claim is true. You will be victorious.
I believed that once.
You are the one god's champion
and the finest man I've ever known.
Selyse.
I've broken a sacred vow.
I've sinned.
I've wronged you.
I have shamed you.
You're doing god's work.
You don't understand.
The red woman...
The lady melisandre...
I know, Stannis.
The lady melisandre has told me everything.
No act done in service
of the lord of light can ever be a sin.
When she told me,
I wept with joy.
Oh, my sweet boys.
Petyr, tommard, edric.
I thank god every day
for bringing melisandre to us.
She gave you a son.
I gave you
- nothing.
- That's not true.
So, you've come to see her as well?
There is no need.
You must keep away from such distractions.
She's my daughter.
I want to see her.
You are a king.
You don't need my permission.
Girl: (Singing) The sea
I know, I know
oh, oh, oh
the birds have scales
and the fish take wing
I know, I know
oh, oh, oh
Stannis: (Whispers) Shireen.
Father!
You've grown since I last saw you.
Mother said you fought in a battle.
Did you win?
Did the onion knight come back with you?
He did. He fought bravely.
He hasn't come to visit me.
He said he'd bring
me back a present from the capital.
He won't be visiting, child.
Why not? He's my friend.
Look.
He made this for me.
But don't tell mother
I have it. It's a secret.
Mother doesn't like the onion knight.
Ser davos is a traitor.
He's rotting in a
dungeon cell for his crime.
Best forget him.
(Door opening)
(Door closes)
Not so hard. You'll scrub the skin off.
What are you doing here?
I need a bath.
Help me out of these rags.
Now get out.
(Door closes)
There's another tub.
Jaime: This one suits me fine.
(Exhales)
Don't worry. I'm not interested.
(Sighs)
If I faint, pull me out.
I don't intend to be
the first Lannister to die in a bathtub.
Why should I care how you die?
You swore a solemn vow, remember?
You're supposed to
get me to king's landing in one piece.
Not going so well, is it?
No wonder renly died,
with you guarding him.
That was unworthy. Forgive me.
- You protected me better than most...
- Don't you mock me.
I'm apologizing.
I'm sick of fighting. Let's call a truce.
You need trust to have a truce.
I trust you.
There it is. There's the look.
I've seen it for 17
years, on face after face.
You all despise me.
Kingslayer. Oathbreaker.
A man without honor.
You've heard of wildfire?
Of course.
The mad king was obsessed with it.
He loved to watch people burn,
the way their skin blackened and
blistered and melted off their bones.
He burned lords he didn't like.
He burned hands who disobeyed him.
He burned anyone who was against him.
Before long, half the
country was against him.
Aerys saw traitors everywhere,
so he had his pyromancer
place caches of wildfire all over the city,
beneath the sept of baelor
and the slums of flea bottom.
Under houses, stables, taverns.
Even beneath the red keep itself.
Finally, the day of reckoning came.
Robert Baratheon marched on the capital
after his victory at the trident.
But my father arrived first,
with the whole Lannister army at his back,
promising to defend the city
against the rebels.
I knew my father better than that.
He's never been one
to pick the losing side.
I told the mad king as much.
I urged him to surrender peacefully.
But the king didn't listen to me.
He didn't listen to varys,
who tried to warn him.
But he did listen to grand maester pycelle,
that gray, sunken cunt.
"You can trust the lannisters," he said.
"The lannisters have always
been true friends of the crown."
So, we opened the gates,
and my father sacked the city.
Once again, I came to the
king, begging him to surrender.
He told me to bring him my father's head.
Then he turned to his pyromancer.
"Burn them all," he said.
"Burn them in their homes.
Burn them in their beds."
Tell me, if your precious renly
commanded you to kill your own father
and stand by while thousands of men,
women, and children burned alive,
would you have done it?
Would you have kept your oath then?
First, I killed the pyromancer.
And then, when the king turned to ere,
I drove my sword into his back.
"Burn them all,"
he kept saying. "Burn them all."
I don't think he expected to die.
He meant to burn with the rest of us
and rise again,
reborn as a dragon to
turn his enemies to ash.
I slit his throat to
make sure that didn't happen.
That's where ned stark found me.
If this is true...
(Grunts softly)
Why didn't you tell anyone?
Why didn't you tell lord stark?
Stark?
You think the honorable ned stark
wanted to hear my side?
He judged me guilty
the moment he set eyes on me.
(Breathing heavily)
By what right does the wolfjudge the lion?
- By what right?
- Help! Help!
- The kingslayer!
- (Panting)
Jaime. My name is Jaime.
Shireen: (Whispering)
Onion knight. Ser onion knight.
Princess? Gods, what are you doing here?
Shh! You'll wake Bert.
He's the fat one. He's
on guard duty tonight.
He likes to drink wine and sleep a lot.
Go back to your room.
You're not supposed to be here.
- If your father knew...
- He said you were a traitor.
Are you?
I am, child.
I disobeyed my king,
your father, and now I'm paying the price.
I don't care. You're my friend.
You must get bored
down here. I brought you something to read.
It's about aegon and his dragons.
Aegon used to live here. Did you know that?
- And the targaryens built this castle.
- Aye.
So they did.
You can hide the book under your cloak.
It's a good one. I'll bring you more.
Thank you, my lady.
I'm sure it's a fine book,
- but it's wasted on me.
- Take it.
I have more.
My lady, I can't read the words.
You can't?
I'll teach you. I'll come when
Bert's on duty and teach you.
- No. No. No.
- It's easy. It'll be fun.
Go. We can't.
Why not? What will
they do, look us in cells?
(Chuckles)
- I wouldn't know where to start.
- At the beginning.
This word is "aegon."
When you see "a," 'e,"
and "g" together like that,
it sounds like "egg."
And the title of the whole book
is an history of aegon the
conqueror and his conquest of Westeros.
(Unsullied chanting)
- Jorah: It was a bitch of a siege.
- Barristan: Mmm.
You were first through the breach at pyke?
The second.
Thoros of myr went in
alone, waving that flaming sword of his.
(Chuckles) Thoros of myr. Bloody madman.
Robert knighted you after the battle?
Proudest moment of my life.
One knee in the dust,
the king's sword on my shoulder,
listening to the words,
"in the name of the warrior,
I charge you to be brave."
All I could think of
was how badly I had to piss.
(Laughs)
Jorah: In full plate metal for 16 hours.
Never occurred to me
till the fighting was over.
I was very nearly the first man
knighted to piss on the king's boots.
(Laughs)
Robert would have laughed.
He was a good man, a great warrior.
And a terrible king.
I burned away my years
fighting for terrible kings.
- You swore an oath.
- Yes.
And a man of honor keeps his vows,
even if he's serving a drunk or a lunatic.
Just once in my life before it's over,
I want to know
what it's like to serve with pride,
to fight for someone I believe in.
Do you believe in her?
With all my heart.
These are the ones?
Yes, khaleesi. The officers.
(Daenerys speaking valyrian)
You did not choose this life.
But you are free men now.
And free men make their own choices.
Have you selected your own leader
from amongst your ranks?
Remove your helmet.
(In valyrian)
This one has the honor.
What is your name?
Grey worm.
All unsullied boys
are given new names when they are cut.
Grey worm, red flea, black rat.
Names that remind them what they are...
Vermin.
(Both in valyrian)
From this day fonnard,
you will choose your own names.
You will tell your fellow soldiers
to do the same.
Throw away your slave name.
Choose the name your parents gave you,
or any other.
A name that gives you pride.
"Grey worm" gives me pride.
It is a lucky name.
The name this one was born
with was cursed.
That was the name he had when he
was taken as a slave.
But grey worm is the name this one had
the day Daenerys stormborn set him free.
Jorah: King Robert wanted her dead.
Of course he wanted her dead.
She's a Targaryen. The last Targaryen.
I suppose no one on the small
council could speak sense to him.
I didn't sit on the small council.
Doesn't the lord commander
of the kingsguard traditionally...
Traditionally, yes,
but I killed a dozen
of Robert's friends during his rebellion.
He didn't want advice on how to govern
from a man who had fought for the mad king.
Can't say I minded much.
I always hated the politics.
Yeah, I imagine I would, too.
Hours spentjabbering about
backstabbings and betrayals the world over.
Mmm-hmm.
Still, she'll have to
Wade through that muck
if she wants to rule the seven kingdoms.
She'll have good men around her
to advise her, men with experience.
Which men do you have in mind?
Forgive me for what I'm about to say,
but your reputation
in Westeros has suffered over the years.
It suffered for a reason.
I sold men into slavery.
I don't know if your presence by her side
will help our cause when we go home.
Our cause?
Forgive me, ser barristan,
but I was busy defending the khaleesi
against king Robert's assassins
while you were still bowing to the man.
We both want her to rule. Am I wrong?
You onlyjoined us a few days ago.
I can't speak to your intentions.
If we're truly her onal servants,
we will do whatever needs to be done,
no matter the cost, no matter our pride.
You're not lord commander
here. You're just another exile.
And I take my orders from the queen.
(Neighs)
Talisa: Come to bed.
You were right.
The karstarks are gone.
(Clattering)
Almost half our forces.
Tywin Lannister knows what he needs to
do to make us unravel.
Nothing.
Only wait.
Don't let him.
What can I do? Attack king's landing?
There's nothing
he'd like better. He'd crush us in a day.
We could ride north.
Take your land back
from the greyjoys. Wait out the winter.
Winter could last five years.
Once my bannermen are home again,
sitting by the fire,
surrounded by their families,
warm and safe, they'll
never ride south again.
When I gathered my lords
together, we had a purpose, a mission.
Now we're like a band
of bickering children.
Give them a new purpose.
What?
I don't know.
I don't even know where winterfell is.
Here.
And we're here.
King's landing...
What is it?
I can't force them to meet us in the field
and I can't attack them
where they're strongest,
but I can attack them where they're not.
And casterly rock can't run away.
I'm going to take their
home away from them.
Can you do it?
I need men to
replace the karstarks who marched home.
There is only one person in this kingdom
with that kind of army who hasn't
already sided with the lannisters.
(Laughs)
The man whose daughter
I was supposed to marry.
Walder frey.
(Grunting)
He's such a splendid fighter.
Do you have any idea when we might...
I'll plant the seed
as soon as Joffrey and I are married.
It should grow quickly.
Joffrey won't let me leave.
He's got too many reasons to keep me here.
And only one to let you go.
Because it will please me.
Loras: Squire.
Well fought, ser.
That was no fight.
I don't know you.
Ovaer, if it please you.
I should like to
see you spar with a proper partner, ser.
(Moans)
(Panting)
How did you know?
Know what?
That I wanted to.
My lord...
I'll have you know I'm to be married soon,
and even my intended
hasn't the slightest notion.
They rarely do, in my experience.
You have a good deal of experience, do you?
With the husbands.
That didn't take long.
Well, it took long enough.
It seems
our knight of flowers is engaged to be wed.
Is he?
And...
Who's the lucky girl?
Littlefinger: She may
not be the grandest ship in the world
or the fastest,
but she's mine.
I've always wanted a ship.
Now I want a dozen.
Strange, isn't it?
What is?
It doesn't matter what we want,
once we get it, then
we want something else.
Your hair is different.
Is it?
Lady margaery wears it that way.
Many ladies wear it this way.
I have good news. I'll
be leaving the city soon.
You still want me to come with you?
It's not a question of what
I want. It's what you want.
You want to go home, don't you?
Of course. More than anything.
But maybe it would be better to wait.
I've been thinking how dangerous it would
be. Not just for me, but for you.
You've been so kind. I'd feel
terrible if anything happened to you.
I can't tell you how touched I am
by your concern for my welfare.
I hope you know that
I'm your friend, sansa.
Your true friend.
I do, lord baelish.
Petyr.
If you wish to stay,
then of course you will stay.
We'll speak again when I return.
(Exhales)
Tywin: You're late.
What's she doing here?
Our business concerns her, too.
Sit.
You'll be pleased to learn that
after one conversation with olenna Tyrell,
I've saved the crown
hundreds of thousands on this wedding.
Never mind that now.
We have something important to discuss.
I'm master of coin.
Saving money is important.
Stop that. You're making me uncomfortable.
Your sister has learned
that your new friends the tyrells
are plotting to marry
sansa stark to ser loras.
Very well. She's a lovely girl.
Missing some of loras' favorite
bits, but I'm sure they'll make do.
Yourjokes are not appreciated.
It wasn't my best, but...
I bring them into the royal fold,
and this is how they repay me,
by trying to steal
the key to the north out from under me.
Sansa is the key to the north? I seem to
remember she has an older brother.
The karstarks have marched home.
The young wolf has
lost half his army. His days are numbered.
Theon greyjoy murdered both his brothers.
That makes sansa
stark the heir to winterfell,
and I am not about
to hand her over to the tyrells.
Tyrion: The Tyrell army is
helping us to win this war.
Do you really think it's
wise to refuse them?
There's nothing to refuse. This is a plot.
Plots are not public knowledge.
And the tyrells won't carry this one out
until after Joffrey's wedding.
We need to act first
and kill this union in its crib.
And how do we do that?
We find sansa stark a different husband.
Wonderful.
Yes, it is.
You can't mean it.
I can and I do.
Joffrey's made this
poor girl's life miserable
since the day he took her father's head.
Now she's finally
free of him, and you give her to me?
That's cruel, even for you.
Do you intend on mistreating her?
The girl's happiness
is not my concern, nor yours.
She's a child!
She's flowered, I assure
you. She and I have discussed it at length.
There, you see? You will wed her,
bed her, and put a child in her.
Surely you're capable of that.
And if I refuse?
You wanted to be rewarded
for your valor in battle.
Sansa stark is a finer
reward than you could ever dare hope for.
And it is past time you were wed.
I was wed.
Or don't you remember?
Only too well.
You should be thanking the gods for this.
This is more than you deserve.
Tyrion will do as he's bid. As will you.
(Tywin clears throat)
What do you mean?
You'll marry ser loras.
I will not.
The boy is heir to highgarden.
Tyrion will secure the north,
you will secure the reach.
No, I won't do it.
Yes, you will.
You're still fertile.
You need to marry again and breed.
I am queen regent, not some broodmare.
You're my daughter!
You will do as I command,
and you will marry loras Tyrell
and put an end to the disgusting
rumors about you once and for all.
Father, don't make me do it again, please.
Not another word.
My children.
You've disgraced
the Lannister name for far too long.
(Door slams)