Lord, cast your light upon us.
Lord of Light, defend us.
Show us the truth.
Strike this man down if he is guilty.
Give strength to his sword if he is true.
Lord of Light, give us wisdom.
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
Get back!
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
-Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
-Kill him!
Guilty. Guilty. Guilty.
Lord, cast your light upon this man,
your servant.
Bring him back from death and darkness.
His flame has been extinguished.
Restore it.
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
-Lord, cast...
-Arya, don't!
Bring him back from death and darkness...
No! Let go of me! Let me go!
Looks like their God likes me more
than your butcher's boy.
Burn in hell!
He will.
But not today.
Orell says there are crows
patrolling on the Wall.
Tell me what you know.
There are four to a patrol,
two builders to check
for structural damage,
two rangers to watch for enemies.
How often do these patrols go out?
It varies.
If I knew where on the Wall
we were heading, I could tell you.
You'd like to know that.
There are 19 castles guarding the Wall.
How many are manned?
-Three.
-You sure of that?
Which three?
Castle Black.
Aye, Castle Black.
Everyone knows Castle Black. Which others?
Eastwatch-by-the-Sea
and the Shadow Tower.
How many men remain in Castle Black?
-A thousand.
-Liar.
What happens to your eagle
after I kill you?
Does he drift away
like a kite with his strings cut
-or does he just flop dead to the ground?
-He's no crow.
Just because you want him inside you
don't make him one of us.
I'm not afraid of you.
I like you, boy.
But if you lie to me,
I'll pull your guts out
through your throat.
A thousand men.
We'll find out soon enough.
-I don't need you to protect me.
-Of course you do.
Who stopped Rattleshirt
when he was about to cut your throat?
Who vouched for you with Mance?
It seems you owe me a debt.
-Give it back.
-Well, I stole it.
It's mine. If you want it,
come steal it back.
Ygritte!
Ygritte! Seven hells. Ygritte!
Is Orell right?
Are you still a crow?
It's time you proved yourself.
-Ygritte.
-You swore some vows.
I want you to break them.
I want you to see me.
All of me.
We shouldn't.
We should.
Why are you still dressed?
You know nothing, Jon Sn...
That thing you did, with your mouth...
is that what lords do
to their ladies in the South?
I don't know.
I just wanted to kiss you there is all.
-You seemed to like it.
-Aye, I liked it some.
Who taught you that?
There's been no one else. Only you.
-A maid. You were a maid.
-I was a man of the Night's Watch.
-How about you? Were you a maid?
-What do you think?
-Who was he?
-Just a boy.
He came trading with his brothers.
He had red hair like me.
Kissed by fire. But he was weak.
Not like you.
That was the first one.
Then there was this Thenn boy.
Spoke no Common, but gods,
he was built like a mammoth...
Yeah, thanks. I think I've heard enough.
We'd best get back. Tormund...
I'm not done with you yet.
How long's it been since you had a bath?
Let's not go back.
Let's stay here a while longer.
I don't ever want to leave this cave,
Jon Snow.
Not ever.
I want my gold.
It says it clearly right there
on that note you'll be repaid in full
when the war's over.
Piss on that! You're nothing but thieves.
We're outlaws. Outlaws steal.
You're lucky we didn't kill you.
Come try it, archer.
I'll shove those arrows up your ass.
You can't let him go.
He's a murderer. He's guilty.
-Not in the eyes of God.
-You can't!
Enough! The judgment isn't ours to make.
Go in peace, Sandor Clegane.
The Lord of Light isn't done with you yet.
Riders coming through!
The Kingslayer.
Down! On your knees.
Lord Bolton, I give you the King slayer.
Pick him up, Locke.
-You've lost a hand.
-No, my lord, he has it here.
-Take this away.
-Send it to his father?
You'll hold your tongue
unless you want to lose it.
Cut her free. Apologies, my lady.
You're under my protection now.
Thank you, my lord.
Find suitable rooms for our guests.
We'll speak later.
Lord Bolton.
Is there word from the capital?
You haven't heard?
Stannis Baratheon laid siege
to King's Landing.
Sailed into Blackwater Bay.
Stormed the gates with thousands of men.
And your sister...
How can I put this?
Your sister...
is alive and well.
Your father's forces prevailed.
Ser Jaime isn't well. Take him to Qyburn.
-Will I die?
-No.
The corruption has spread.
I fear it must be cut away.
The safest course
would be to take the whole arm off.
Then you'll die.
You're no maester. Where's your chain?
The Citadel stripped me of it.
They found some of my experiments
too bold.
I can leave your upper arm,
make the cut at your elbow.
I don't need my right hand to kill you.
I can take away the rotting flesh
and try and burn out the corruption
with boiling wine.
With any luck, that will suffice.
You'll need milk of the poppy.
-No milk of the poppy.
-There will be pain.
-I'll scream.
-Quite a bit of pain.
I'll scream loudly.
-Lord Baelish.
-Your Grace.
-I wonder if I might ask you for a favor.
-Of course, Your Grace.
I have reason to believe
that House Tyrell do not hold
the Crown's best interests at heart.
I see. And have you shared
these suspicions with Lord Tywin?
My father's a practical man.
He appreciates facts.
Myself, I often find them a hindrance.
And he appreciates those
who aid his family, as you well know.
He's almost as generous
to those who help us
as he is unpleasant
towards those who don't.
You have a good working relationship
with the Tyrells.
I thought you might look into it
before you leave the capital.
-I shall do my best.
-Thank you.
And your best will prove better
than when I asked you
to locate Arya Stark?
I assure you that it will.
Gods, boy, that's enough.
We're not in a tavern.
-Pardon, my lady.
-No need to speak.
Are there any figs? Fetch some.
I always take figs midafternoon.
They help move the bowels.
-To what do I owe this summons?
-Thank you for seeing me, my lady.
I had hoped we might discuss
a few financial matters.
I climbed all those steps
to discuss financial matters?
It's the royal wedding.
I'm told you had a hand in planning it.
Naturally.
It's shaping up to be
a very involved affair.
The word "extravagant" has been used.
What good is the word "extravagant"
if it can't be used to describe
a royal wedding?
-I understand that.
-Good.
But, as Master of Coin, it falls upon me
to calculate the cost for the Crown.
-As of now, it's a huge expense.
-And?
And we're at war, Lady Olenna.
I'd nearly forgotten.
-Yes, and maintaining supply lines--
-I can't think how it slipped my mind.
What is it, 12,000 infantrymen
the Tyrell family has supplied?
Eighteen hundred mounted lances.
Two thousand in support.
Provisions so this city
might survive the winter.
A million bushels of wheat.
Half a million bushels each
of barley, oats, and rye.
Twenty thousand head of cattle.
Fifty thousand sheep.
You don't have to lecture me
about wartime expenses.
I'm quite familiar with them.
And we are so grateful
for your contributions
which are necessary
for the preservation of the realm.
As is a royal wedding.
The people are hungry for more
than just food.
They crave distractions.
And if we don't provide them,
they'll create their own.
And their distractions are likely
to end with us being torn to pieces.
A royal wedding is much safer.
-Wouldn't you say?
-I would.
And traditionally paid for
by the royal family.
I was told you were drunk, impertinent,
and thoroughly debauched.
You can imagine my disappointment
at finding nothing
but a browbeaten bookkeeper.
Where did you go for them, Volantis?
-My lady--
-Very well.
I won't have it said that House Tyrell
refuses to play its part.
We'll pay for half the expenses
and the celebrations will go on
as planned.
-Is that sufficient?
-Quite sufficient. Thank you.
Very good, then. That's settled. Good day.
Give me that.
What are you doing?
-Just mending Lord Beric's armor.
-Why?
I'm going to stay on
and smith for the Brotherhood.
Have you lost your mind?
When the Lannisters find this place,
you think they'll spare the smiths?
They'll cave your head in
with your own helmet.
The Lannisters wanted to kill me
long before I joined the Brotherhood.
You don't have to do this.
I want to. They need good men.
Robb needs good men, too.
We're leaving tomorrow.
-And then you--
-What? Serve him?
I've served men my entire life.
I served Master Mott at King's Landing
and he sold me to the Watch.
I served Lord Tywin at Harrenhal,
wondering every day
if I'd get tortured or killed.
I'm done serving.
You just said you were serving Lord Beric.
He may be their leader,
but they chose him.
These men are brothers. They're a family.
I've never had a family.
I can be your family.
You wouldn't be my family.
You'd be "my lady."
Willem.
Willem!
-Is this a rescue?
-Lannister filth! Take him!
Please, I didn't do anything.
I'm just a squire. Please...
Bring them in.
Is that all of them?
It took five of you to murder
two unarmed squires?
-Not murder, Your Grace. Vengeance.
-Vengeance?
Those boys didn't kill your sons.
I saw Harrion die on the battlefield
and Torrhen--
Was strangled by the Kingslayer.
-They were his kin.
-They were boys!
Look at them.
Tell your mother to look at them.
She killed them as much as I.
My mother had nothing to do with this.
This was your treason.
It's treason to free your enemies.
In war, you kill your enemies.
Did your father not teach you that, boy?
Leave him.
Aye.
Leave me to the king.
He wants to give me a scolding
before he sets me free.
That's how he deals with treason.
Our King in the North.
Or should I call him
the King Who Lost the North?
Escort Lord Karstark to the dungeon.
Hang the rest.
Mercy, sire! I didn't kill anyone.
I only watched for the guards.
This one was only the watcher.
Hang him last
so he can watch the others die.
Please! Please, no. They made me do it!
They made me! They made me!
Word of this can't leave Riverrun.
They were Tywin Lannister's nephews.
The Lannisters pay their debts.
They never stop talking about it.
Would you make me a liar
as well as a murderer?
It wouldn't be lying.
We will bury them and remain silent
until the war is done.
I'm not fighting for justice
if I don't serve justice
to murderers in my ranks,
no matter how highborn.
-He has to die.
-The Karstarks are Northmen.
They won't forgive
the killing of their lord.
Your mother's right.
If you do this,
the Karstarks will abandon you.
You tended to their wounds.
You brought them supper.
Now, they're dead.
And more boys will keep dying
until this war is over.
You need Karstark men to end it.
Spare his life. Keep him as a hostage.
A hostage.
Tell the Karstarks
that as long as they remain loyal,
he will not be harmed.
The blood of the First Men flows
through my veins as much as yours, boy.
I fought the Mad King for your father.
I fought Joffrey for you.
We are kin, Stark and Karstark.
That didn't stop you from betraying me.
And it won't save you now.
I don't want it to save me.
I want it to haunt you
to the end of your days.
Kneel, my lord.
Rickard Karstark, Lord of Karhold,
here in sight of gods and men,
I sentence you to die.
Would you speak a final word?
Kill me and be cursed.
You are no king of mine.
Joffrey. Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
Ser Meryn.
The Hound.
-What are you going to do with me?
-At first light we'll ride for Riverrun.
Your brother's there now.
He'll make a contribution to our cause
and you can go home.
-I'm a hostage and you're selling me.
-Don't think of it that way.
-But it is that way.
-It is.
-And it isn't.
-More is than isn't.
Beric admired your father
a great deal, you know?
He wanted to refuse
your ransom altogether.
-So, why don't you?
-We need the gold.
-Do I frighten you, child?
-No.
You're angry with me.
And I don't blame you.
But letting him go was the right thing.
I have more reason
than most to want him hanged.
-I thought he killed you.
-He did.
But how...
Thoros.
-How many times have you brought me back?
-It's the Lord of Light brings you back.
I'm just the lucky drunk
who says the words.
-How many times?
-Five, I think.
-No, this makes six.
-Six.
There was the first time, the Mountain.
Show her. Lance right through the chest.
Then I was stabbed in the belly.
Then it was an arrow in the back.
And that axe in the side.
Then the Lannisters caught me
and executed me for treason.
-Was it a hanging or a dagger in the eye?
-Both. Fuckers couldn't decide.
And the Hound makes six.
Second time I've been killed by a Clegane.
You'd think you'd learn.
-It's not getting any easier, you know?
-I know.
Every time I come back, I'm a bit less.
Pieces of you get chipped away.
Could you bring back a man without a head?
Not six times. Just once.
I don't think it works that way, child.
He was a good man, Ned Stark.
He's at rest now, somewhere.
I would never wish my life upon him.
I would.
You're alive.
Lord, cast your light upon me.
Protect me in the darkness.
Burn away my sins. Help me serve you.
Use me as you will.
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
I have prayed day
and night for you to come to me.
My lady. I meant to come sooner.
-The battle--
-I know of your troubles, my king.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
Yes, of course.
You mustn't despair. Your claim is true.
You will be victorious.
I believed that once.
You are the One God's champion,
and the finest man I've ever known.
Selyse.
I've broken a sacred vow.
-I've sinned.
-No.
I've wronged you.
-I have shamed you.
-You're doing God's work.
You don't understand.
The Red Woman...
-The Lady Melisandre.
-I know, Stannis.
The Lady Melisandre
has told me everything.
No act done in service
of the Lord of Light can ever be a sin.
When she told me,
I wept with joy.
My sweet boys.
Petyr, Tommard, Edric.
I thank God every day
for bringing Melisandre to us.
She gave you a son.
I gave you...
-nothing.
-That's not true.
So, you've come to see her as well?
There is no need.
You must keep away from such distractions.
She's my daughter.
I want to see her.
You are a king.
You don't need my permission.
Under the sea, I know, I know
The birds have scales
And the fish take wing
I know, I know
-Shireen.
-Father!
-You've grown since I last saw you.
-Mother said you fought in a battle.
Did you win?
No.
Did the Onion Knight come back with you?
-He did. He fought bravely.
-He hasn't come to visit me.
He said he'd bring me back
a present from the capital.
-He won't be visiting, child.
-Why not? He's my friend. Look.
He made this for me.
But don't tell Mother I have it.
It's a secret.
Mother doesn't like the Onion Knight.
Ser Davos is a traitor.
He's rotting in a dungeon cell
for his crime.
Best forget him.
Not so hard. You'll scrub the skin off.
-What are you doing here?
-I need a bath.
Help me out of these rags.
Now, get out.
-There's another tub.
-This one suits me fine.
Don't worry. I'm not interested.
If I faint, pull me out.
I don't intend to be the first
Lannister to die in a bathtub.
-Why should I care how you die?
-You swore a solemn vow, remember?
You're supposed to get me
to King's Landing in one piece.
Not going so well, is it?
No wonder Renly died
with you guarding him.
That was unworthy. Forgive me.
You protected me better than most--
-Don't you mock me.
-I'm apologizing.
-I'm sick of fighting. Let's call a truce.
-You need trust to have a truce.
I trust you.
There it is. There's the look.
I've seen it for 17 years
on face after face.
You all despise me.
Kingslayer. Oathbreaker.
A man without honor.
-You've heard of wildfire?
-Of course.
The Mad King was obsessed with it.
He loved to watch people burn,
the way their skin blackened,
and blistered, and melted off their bones.
He burned lords he didn't like.
He burned Hands who disobeyed him.
He burned anyone who was against him.
Before long,
half the country was against him.
Aerys saw traitors everywhere.
So, he had his pyromancer place caches
of wildfire all over the city.
Beneath the Sept of Baelor
and the slums of Flea Bottom.
Under houses, stables, taverns.
Even beneath the Red Keep itself.
Finally... the day of reckoning came.
Robert Baratheon marched on the capital
after his victory at the Trident.
But my father arrived first
with the whole Lannister army at his back,
promising to defend the city
against the rebels.
I knew my father better than that.
He's never been one
to pick the losing side.
I told the Mad King as much.
I urged him to surrender peacefully.
But the king didn't listen to me.
He didn't listen to Varys
who tried to warn him.
But he did listen
to Grand Maester Pycelle,
that grey, sunken cunt.
"You can trust the Lannisters," he said.
"The Lannisters have always been
true friends of the crown."
So, we opened the gates
and my father sacked the city.
Once again, I came to the king,
begging him to surrender.
He told me to bring him my father's head.
Then he turned to his pyromancer.
"Burn them all," he said.
"Burn them in their homes.
Burn them in their beds."
Tell me, if your precious Renly
commanded you to kill your own father
and stand by while thousands of men,
women, and children burned alive,
would you have done it?
Would you have kept your oath then?
First, I killed the pyromancer.
And then when the king turned to flee,
I drove my sword into his back.
"Burn them all," he kept saying.
"Burn them all."
I don't think he expected to die.
He meant to...
burn with the rest of us and rise again.
Reborn as a dragon
to turn his enemies to ash.
I slit his throat to make sure
that didn't happen.
That's where Ned Stark found me.
If this is true,
why didn't you tell anyone?
-Why didn't you tell Lord Stark?
-Stark?
You think the honorable Ned Stark
wanted to hear my side?
He judged me guilty
the moment he set eyes on me.
By what right does the wolf
judge the lion?
-By what right?
-Help! Help! The Kingslayer!
Jaime. My name's Jaime.
Onion Knight. Ser Onion Knight.
Princess? Gods, what are you doing here?
-You'll wake Bert.
-Bert?
He's the fat one.
He's on guard duty tonight.
He likes to drink wine and sleep a lot.
Go back to your room.
You're not supposed to be here.
-If your father knew--
-He said you're a traitor.
-Are you?
-I am, child.
I disobeyed my king, your father,
and now, I'm paying the price.
I don't care. You're my friend.
You must get bored down here.
I brought you something to read.
It's about Aegon and his dragons.
Aegon used to live here.
Did you know that?
And the Targaryens built this castle.
-So they did.
-You can hide the book under your cloak.
It's a good one. I'll bring you more.
Thank you, my lady.
I'm sure it's a fine book,
-but it's wasted on me.
-Take it. I have more.
-My lady, I can't read the words.
-You can't?
I'll teach you. I'll come
when Bert's on duty and teach you.
-No. No. No.
-It's easy. It'll be fun.
-Go. We can't.
-Why not?
What will they do, lock us in cells?
-I wouldn't know where to start.
-At the beginning.
This word is Aegon.
When you see A, E, and G
together like that, it sounds like egg.
And the title of the whole book
isAn History of Aegon the Conqueror
and His Conquest of Westeros.
It was a bitch of a siege.
You were first through the breach at Pyke?
The second. Thoros of Myr went in alone,
waving that flaming sword of his.
Thoros of Myr. Bloody madman.
Robert knighted you after the battle?
Proudest moment of my life.
One knee in the dust,
the King's sword on my shoulder,
listening to the words.
"In the name of the Warrior,
I charge you to be brave."
All I could think of was
how badly I had to piss.
In full plate metal for 16 hours.
Never occurred to me
till the fighting was over.
I was very nearly the first man
knighted to piss on the king's boots.
Robert would have laughed.
He was a good man, a great warrior.
And a terrible king.
I burned away my years
fighting for terrible kings.
-You swore an oath.
-Yes.
And a man of honor keeps his vows,
even if he's serving a drunk or a lunatic.
Just once in my life before it's over,
I want to know
what it's like to serve with pride,
to fight for someone I believe in.
Do you believe in her?
With all my heart.
-These are the ones?
-Yes, Khaleesi. The officers.
All Unsullied boys are given new names
when they are cut.
Grey Worm, Red Flea, Black Rat.
Names that remind them
what they are. Vermin.
-King Robert wanted her dead.
-Of course, he wanted her dead.
She's a Targaryen. The last Targaryen.
I suppose no one on the small council
could speak sense to him.
-I didn't sit on the small council.
-No?
Doesn't the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard traditionally--
Traditionally, yes, but I killed a dozen
of Robert's friends during his rebellion.
He didn't want advice on how to govern
from a man who had fought
for the Mad King.
Can't say I minded much.
I always hated the politics.
Yeah, I imagine I would too.
Hours spent jabbering about backstabbings
and betrayals the world over.
Still, she'll have to wade
through that muck
if she wants to rule the Seven Kingdoms.
She'll have good men
around her to advise her,
men with experience.
Which men do you have in mind?
Forgive me, Ser Jorah,
for what I'm about to say,
but your reputation in Westeros
has suffered over the years.
It suffered for a reason.
I sold men into slavery.
I don't know if your presence
by her side will help our cause
-when we go home.
-Our cause?
Forgive me, Ser Barristan, but I was busy
defending the Khaleesi
against King Robert's assassins
while you were still bowing to the man.
We both want her to rule. Am I wrong?
You only joined us a few days ago.
I can't speak to your intentions.
If we're truly her loyal servants,
we will do whatever needs to be done,
no matter the cost, no matter our pride.
You're not Lord Commander here.
You're just another exile.
And I take my orders from the queen.
-Come to bed.
-You were right.
The Karstarks are gone.
Almost half our forces.
Tywin Lannister knows what he needs
to do to make us unravel.
Nothing. Only wait.
-Don't let him.
-What can I do?
Attack King's Landing?
There's nothing he'd like better.
He'd crush us in a day.
We could ride north.
Take your land back from the Greyjoys.
-Wait out the winter.
-Winter could last five years.
Once my bannermen are home again,
sitting by the fire,
surrounded by their families,
warm and safe,
they'll never ride south again.
When I gathered my lords together,
we had a purpose, a mission.
Now, we're like
a band of bickering children.
-Give them a new purpose.
-What?
I don't know.
I don't even know where Winterfell is.
Here.
And we're here. King's Landing...
What is it?
I can't force them to meet us in the field
and I can't attack them
where they're strongest,
but I can attack them where they're not.
And Casterly Rock can't run away.
I'm going to take their home
away from them.
Can you do it?
I need men to replace
the Karstarks who marched home.
There is only one person in this kingdom
with that kind of army
who hasn't already sided
with the Lannisters.
The man whose daughter
I was supposed to marry, Walder Frey.
He's such a splendid fighter.
Do you have any idea when we might...
I'll plant the seed
as soon as Joffrey and I are married.
-It should grow quickly.
-Joffrey won't let me leave.
He's got too many reasons to keep me here.
And only one to let you go.
-Because it will please me.
-Squire!
-Well fought, ser.
-That was no fight. I don't know you.
Olyver, if it please you.
I should like to see you spar
with a proper partner, ser.
-How did you know?
-Know what?
-That I wanted to.
-My lord...
I'll have you know I'm to be married soon
and even my intended
hasn't the slightest notion.
They rarely do, in my experience.
You have a good deal of experience,
do you? With the husbands.
-That didn't take long.
-Well, it took long enough.
It seems our Knight of Flowers
is engaged to be wed.
Is he?
And... who's the lucky girl?
She may not be the grandest ship
in the world or the fastest...
but she's mine.
I've always wanted a ship.
Now, I want a dozen.
-Strange, isn't it?
-What is?
It doesn't matter what we want,
once we get it,
then we want something else.
-Your hair is different.
-Is it?
-Lady Margaery wears it that way.
-Many ladies wear it this way.
I have good news.
I'll be leaving the city soon.
-You still want me to come with you?
-It's not a question of what I want.
It's what you want.
You want to go home, don't you?
Of course. More than anything.
But maybe it would be better to wait.
I've been thinking
how dangerous it would be.
Not just for me, but for you.
You've been so kind.
I'd feel terrible
if anything happened to you.
I can't tell you how touched I am
by your concern for my welfare.
I hope you know
that I'm your friend, Sansa.
-Your true friend.
-I do, Lord Baelish.
-Petyr.
If you wish to stay,
then of course, you will stay.
We'll speak again when I return.
You're late.
-What's she doing here?
-Our business concerns her too. Sit.
You'll be pleased to learn
that after one conversation
with Olenna Tyrell,
I've saved the Crown
hundreds of thousands on this wedding.
Never mind that now.
We have something important to discuss.
I'm Master of Coin.
Saving money is important.
Stop that.
You're making me uncomfortable.
Your sister has learned
that your new friends the Tyrells
are plotting to marry Sansa Stark
to Ser Loras.
Very well. She's a lovely girl.
Missing some of Loras' favorite bits,
but I'm sure they'll make do.
-Your jokes are not appreciated.
-It wasn't my best, but I thought--
I bring them into the royal fold
and this is how they repay me,
by trying to steal the key
to the North out from under me.
Sansa is the key to the North?
I seem to remember
she has an older brother.
The Karstarks have marched home.
The young wolf has lost half his army.
His days are numbered.
Theon Greyjoy murdered both his brothers.
That makes Sansa Stark
the heir to Winterfell.
And I am not about to hand her
over to the Tyrells.
The Tyrell army is helping us
to win this war.
Do you really think
it's wise to refuse them?
There's nothing to refuse. This is a plot.
Plots are not public knowledge.
And the Tyrells won't carry this one out
until after Joffrey's wedding.
We need to act first
and kill this union in its crib.
-And how do we do that?
-We find Sansa Stark a different husband.
-Wonderful.
-Yes, it is.
-You can't mean it.
-I can and I do.
Joffrey has made
this poor girl's life miserable
since the day he took her father's head.
Now, she's finally free of him
and you give her to me?
-That's cruel, even for you.
-Do you intend on mistreating her?
The girl's happiness is not my concern.
-Nor should it be yours.
-She's a child!
She's flowered, I assure you,
she and I have discussed it at length.
There, you see? You will wed her,
bed her, and put a child in her.
-Surely, you're capable of that.
-And if I refuse?
You wanted to be rewarded
for your valor in battle.
Sansa Stark is a finer reward
than you could ever dare hope for.
-And it is past time you were wed.
-I was wed.
Or don't you remember?
Only too well.
You should be thanking the gods for this.
This is more than you deserve.
Tyrion will do as he's bid. As will you.
-What do you mean?
-You'll marry Ser Loras.
-I will not.
-The boy is heir to Highgarden.
Tyrion will secure the North,
you will secure the Reach.
-No, I won't do it.
-Yes, you will.
You're still fertile.
You need to marry again and breed.
-I am Queen Regent, not some broodmare.
-You're my daughter!
You will do as I command
and you will marry Loras Tyrell
and put an end to the disgusting rumors
about you once and for all.
Father, don't make me do it again, please.
Not another word.
My children.
You've disgraced the Lannister name
for far too long.
It's always summer, under the sea
I know, I know
The birds have scales
And the fish take wing
I know, I know
The rain is dry, and snow falls up
The stones crack open
The water burns
The shadows come to dance, my lord
The shadows come to play
The shadows come to dance, my love
The shadows come to stay