( theme music playing )
My name
is Grey Worm.
I come from
the Summer "Ills."
Isles.
Summer Isles.
Grey Worm:
( speaking Valyrian )
I am from an island
called Naath.
When they took you?
"When did they take me?"
I was five years old.
You remember your home?
I remember when they
rowed us away from shore.
How white
the beaches were.
How tall the trees.
And I remember
my village burning.
Smoke rising
into the sky.
Do you remember your home?
Unsullied.
Always Unsullied.
Before Unsullied,
nothing.
That's not true.
Perhaps one day
you will return
to the Summer Isles.
I don't want return.
( speaking Valyrian )
Kill the masters.
Daenerys:
How are the lessons coming?
Very well,
Your Grace.
Missandei is teacher
good, my queen.
You'll have
to continue later.
It's time.
( grunting )
( speaking Valyrian )
( speaks Valyrian )
( gasps )
( slaves shouting )
( screaming )
Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa!
( shouting continues )
Daenerys:
Remind me, Ser Jorah,
how many children
did the Great Masters
nail to mileposts?
163, Khaleesi.
Yes, that was it.
( shouts in Valyrian )
Barristan:
Your Grace,
may I have a word?
The city is yours.
All these people,
they're your subjects now.
Sometimes it is better
to answer injustice
with mercy.
I will answer injustice
with justice.
( screaming )
( screaming continues )
( screams echoing )
( panting )
( grunts )
What the hell was that?
That was me
knocking your ass
to the dirt
with your own hand.
You're a rare talent.
When you're fighting
cripples, anyway.
You learned to fight
like a good little boy.
I'll bet that thrust
through the Mad King's back
was pretty as a picture.
You want to fight pretty
or you want to win?
You talk to my brother
this way?
All the time.
He got used to it.
Do you think
he did it?
No.
Oh, he hated
the little twat, sure.
But who didn't?
And poison's
not his style.
Or murder,
for that matter.
You want to know for sure,
why don't you ask him?
You haven't been
to see him yet, eh?
We're done for today.
( seagulls calling )
Your brother ever tell you
how I came into his service?
You stood for him
in his trial by combat
at the Eyrie.
Aye.
But only when
Lady Arryn demanded
the trial take place
that day.
You were his first choice.
He named you
for his champion
because he knew you
would ride day and night
to come fight for him.
You gonna fight
for him now?
To tell you the truth,
this isn't so bad.
Four walls.
A pot to piss in.
I was chained
to a wooden post
covered in my own
shit for months.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
Maybe a bit.
I'm sorry I didn't
come sooner.
It's complicated, yes.
- So how is our sister?
- How do you think?
Her son died in her arms.
Her son?
Don't.
You know what's coming?
My trial for regicide.
Yes, I know.
I know the whole bloody
country thinks I'm guilty.
I know that one
of my three judges
has wished me dead more
times than I can count.
And that judge
is my father.
As for Cersei,
well, she's probably
working on a way
to avoid a trial altogether
by having me killed.
Now that you mention it,
she did ask.
So, should I turn around
and close my eyes?
Depends.
Did you do it?
The Kingslayer brothers.
You like it?
I like it.
You're really asking
if I killed your son?
Are you really asking
if I'd kill my brother?
How can I help you?
Well, you could
set me free.
You know I can't.
Then there's really
nothing else to say.
What do you want me to do?
Kill the guards?
Sneak you out of the city
in the back of a cart?
I'm the Lord Commander
of the Kingsguard.
Sorry, I'd forgotten.
I'd hate for you to do
something inappropriate.
Inappropriate?
You're accused
of killing the king.
Freeing you is treason.
Except I didn't do it.
Which is why
we're having a trial.
A trial.
If the killer threw himself
before the Iron Throne,
confessed to his crimes,
and gave irrefutable
evidence of his guilt,
it wouldn't matter
to Cersei.
She won't rest
until my head's on a spike.
Not just yours.
She's offering a knighthood
to whomever finds Sansa Stark.
Sansa couldn't
have done this.
She had more reason than
anyone in the Seven Kingdoms.
Do you think it's a coincidence
she disappeared the same
night Joffrey died?
No, but...
Sansa's not a killer.
Not yet, anyway.
- ( wood creaking )
- ( men shouting )
( footsteps approaching )
Where are you taking me?
I'm getting married
to your Aunt Lysa.
She's waiting for us
at the Eyrie.
You'll be safe there.
Did you kill Joffrey?
Did I kill Joffrey?
I've been in
the Vale for weeks.
I know it was you.
And who helped me
with this conspiracy?
Well, there was Ser Dontos.
You used him to get
me out of King's Landing,
but you would never trust
him to kill the king.
- Why not?
- Because you're too smart
to trust a drunk.
Then perhaps it was
your husband.
No.
How do you know?
I just do.
You're right.
He wasn't involved
in Joffrey's death.
But you were.
Do you remember that lovely
necklace Dontos gave you?
I don't suppose you noticed
that a stone was missing
after the feast.
The poison.
I don't understand.
The Lannisters gave you
wealth, power.
Joffrey made you
the Lord of Harrenhal.
A man with no motive
is a man no one suspects.
Always keep
your foes confused.
If they don't know who
you are or what you want,
they can't know
what you plan to do next.
I don't believe you.
If they catch you,
they'll put your head
on a spike
just like my father's.
You'd risk that
just to confuse them?
So many men,
they risk so little.
They spend their lives
avoiding danger.
And then they die.
I'd risk everything
to get what I want.
And what do you want?
Everything.
My friendship
with the Lannisters
was productive.
But Joffrey,
a vicious boy with
a crown on his head,
is not a reliable ally.
And who could trust
a friend like that?
Who could trust you?
I don't want
friends like me.
My new friends
are predictable.
Very reasonable people.
As for what
happened to Joffrey,
well, that was something
my new friends wanted
very badly.
Nothing like
a thoughtful gift
to make a new friendship
grow strong.
I can't believe
you're going.
Leaving me alone here
with these people.
The time has come,
my dear.
There's nothing
more tedious than a trial.
Except perhaps
these gardens.
If I have to take one
more leisurely stroll
through these gardens,
I'll fling myself
from the cliffs.
( Margaery laughs )
Have you been
to see Tommen yet?
No.
Have they even agreed
to the match?
No one tells me anything.
I wasn't originally meant
to marry your grandfather
Luthor, you know.
He was engaged
to my sister,
your great-aunt Viola.
I was to be given
to some Targaryen
or other.
Marrying a Targaryen
was all the rage back then.
But the moment
I saw my intended,
with his twitchy
little ferret's face
and ludicrous silver hair,
I knew he wouldn't do.
So the evening
before Luthor was
to propose to my sister,
I got lost on my way back
from my embroidery lesson
and happened
upon his chamber.
( laughs )
- How absentminded of me.
- Mm-hmm.
The following morning,
Luthor never made it
down the stairs
to propose to my sister
'cause the boy couldn't
bloody walk.
And once he could,
the only thing he wanted
was what I'd given him
the night before.
I was good.
I was very, very good.
You are even better.
But you need
to act quickly.
Cersei may be vicious,
but she's not stupid.
She'll turn the boy
against you as soon
as she can.
And by the time
you're married,
it'll be too late.
Luckily for you,
the Queen Regent
is rather distracted
at the moment.
mourning her dear
departed boy.
Accusing her brother
of his murder,
which he didn't commit.
Well, he could have done.
He could have done,
but he didn't.
- You don't know, Grandmother.
- But I do know.
You don't think I'd let you
marry that beast, do you?
What?
I don't understand.
Shh. Don't you worry
yourself about all that.
You just do
what needs to be done.
Jon:
Bring it through!
( swords clanging )
And again.
- ( laughs )
- Very nice. Good.
A lot of wildlings fight
with a weapon in each hand.
First thing you want to do
is disarm them to try
and even the odds.
Let's see what you can do.
Olly, you just watch
for now.
I can fight.
Have you ever
held a sword before?
I was the best archer
in our hamlet.
- ( men laugh )
- I was!
I believe you.
We'll go hunting
for rabbits one day.
Right now,
watch and learn.
You two.
Take it slow,
try and disarm each other.
( shouts )
( groans )
You know how to fight.
You could have gone
easier on him.
He wouldn't have learned
anything that way.
Alliser:
Lord Snow.
What do you think
you're doing?
Grenn and I were
helping them.
Grenn's a ranger.
You're a steward.
Maybe you forgot that
while you were off with
your wildling bitch,
but I didn't.
Someone has
to train them.
And that someone
isn't you.
Go find a chamber pot
to empty.
Go on. Do it.
You traitor's bastard.
Give me an excuse.
Mormont's not here
to protect you now.
Get back to work.
Now!
I said now!
The bastard's well-liked.
You're not.
You think I care
if they like me?
We're at war.
For now.
But you can't be
acting commander forever.
There will be a choosing.
The old maester
will insist on it.
You might reconsider
his request to march
on Craster's.
Let the mutineers
take care of Snow.
Or you might be taking
orders from him
the rest of your life.
A bastard, eh?
Took you for highborn.
My father was highborn.
My mother wasn't.
Name's Locke.
Jon Snow.
You fight well.
What brought you up here?
A sense of duty.
I wanted to do my part
for the safety of the realm.
( laughs )
I was a game warden
in the Stormlands.
Fed a prized partridge
to my hungry kids.
I was stupid enough
to get caught.
Chose the Wall
over losing my hand.
Figured I wouldn't
have to suck up to any
highborn cunts here.
Alliser:
Come on, get on with it.
What are you
waiting for? Summer?
Guess I was wrong.
( knocking )
You sent for me,
Your Grace?
Your Grace.
How formal of you.
How many Kingsguards
are posted outside
Tommen's door?
Ser Boros
is on duty tonight.
- Tomorrow I believe--
- So one?
You have one man
guarding the future king?
I promise you
Tommen's safe.
We're protecting him.
The way you
protected Joffrey?
Why did Catelyn Stark
set you free?
- What?
- I've been wondering
for months.
Ever since
that great cow brought
you back to the capital.
Why did she
set you free?
You know why.
She'd hoped I'd send
her daughters back to her.
She hoped
or did you promise?
I swore by all the gods
that if her daughters
were alive, I'd return
them to her.
So you made a sacred vow
to the enemy.
I wanted to get
back to you.
Should I have told her
to fuck off?
You didn't mean it, then?
You have no loyalty
to Catelyn Stark?
Catelyn Stark's dead.
So if I told you
to leave the capital
right now and find Sansa,
if I told you to find that
murderous little bitch
and bring me her head,
would you do it?
I know you went
to see Tyrion.
That creature
who murdered our son.
I had to see him.
I had to know
for myself.
And?
He didn't do it, Cersei.
You've always pitied him.
Our poor little brother.
Abused by the world.
Despised by his father
and sister.
He'd kill us all
if he could.
I want four men
at Tommen's door
day and night.
That will be all,
Lord Commander.
( sighs )
( door opens )
Ser Pounce?
( door creaks )
( door closes )
How did you get past
the Kingsguard?
Kingsguard.
I don't think you're
supposed to be here.
Mother doesn't allow me
to have visitors at night.
I'm not a visitor,
Your Grace.
Word has it
I'm to be your bride.
Did you know that people
in arranged marriages
often never meet
until their wedding day?
Before we decide to spend
our lives together,
we ought to get
to know one another.
Don't you think?
Yes.
But if my mother
found out--
It can be our secret.
Hmm?
If we're going to be
man and wife,
we'll have a few secrets
from her, I hope.
So, Your Grace...
Yes?
Tell me a secret.
- ( cat meows )
- ( laughs )
Hello. Aren't you
a proper fellow?
That's Ser Pounce.
Very handsome.
Joffrey didn't like him.
He threatened
to skin him alive
and mix his innards
up in my food
so I wouldn't know
I was eating him.
That's very cruel.
You don't strike me
as cruel.
No.
I don't think I am.
That's a relief.
Because you know
what happens when we marry?
We say our vows in front
of the high septon.
And after the ceremony,
there's a feast.
When we marry,
I become yours.
Forever.
It's getting late.
( sighs )
I should go.
May I come and visit
you again?
( laughs )
All right, then.
Remember,
our little secret.
( door closes )
Brienne:
"Ser Jaime Lannister.
Knighted and named
to the Kingsguard
in his 16th year.
At the sack
of King's Landing,
murdered his king
Aerys II.
Pardoned by
Robert Baratheon.
Thereafter known
as the Kingslayer."
It's the duty of
the Lord Commander
to fill those pages.
And there's still room
left on mine.
Valyrian steel.
Mmm.
It's yours.
I can't accept this.
It was reforged
from Ned Stark's sword.
You'll use it to defend
Ned Stark's daughter.
You swore an oath
to return the Stark
girls to their mother.
Lady Stark's dead.
Arya's probably
dead, too,
but there's still a chance
to find Sansa and get her
somewhere safe.
I've got something
else for you.
I hope I got
your measurements right.
I'll find her.
For Lady Catelyn.
And for you.
I almost forgot.
I have one more gift.
I don't need a squire.
Of course you do.
He'll slow me down.
My brother owes him a debt.
He's not safe here.
You're keeping
him from harm.
It's chivalry.
I won't
slow you down, ser--
my lady.
I promise
I'll serve you well.
See? He's a good lad.
You'll get along.
Compliments of Lord Tyrion.
His axe from the Blackwater.
What are you
waiting for, a kiss?
Ready the lady's horse.
They say the best swords
have names.
Any ideas?
Oathkeeper.
Good-bye, Brienne.
Podrick:
Come on, move.
I should never
have taken her away.
- She wasn't safe here.
- She's not safe out there.
I should have known.
You told us there were
wildlings south of the Wall.
If they're raiding
the smaller villages,
Mole's Town could be next.
- Castle Black could be next.
- I should go back for Gilly.
We have orders.
No one's to leave
the castle.
I remember when you
disobeyed orders and rode
south to help Robb.
And I remember
who came after me
and brought me home.
I know how hard
it is, Sam, believe me.
When you told me about Bran
going beyond the Wall,
all I could think about
was getting my strength back
so I could go and find him.
I wish I could have convinced
him to come back with me.
I tried.
Really, I did.
How fast could they travel?
A crippled boy being pulled
on a sledge by a simpleton?
I don't know.
They'd pass
wildling villages.
They could try to find
shelter at one of them.
The wildlings
have joined up with Mance.
Every village
or sheltered place
will be deserted.
Except...
Sam:
Craster's?
You think Bran
might have found--
Snow.
I don't mean
to interrupt.
Thorne wants to see you.
Your foray
to Craster's Keep,
I'll sanction it.
But I won't order
anyone to go with you.
Volunteers only.
Thank you, Ser Alliser.
( men chatting )
Ahem, brothers.
( chatter continues )
( pounds )
I'm going beyond the Wall
to Craster's Keep.
I'm going to capture
the mutineers holed up
there or kill them.
I'm asking for volunteers
to come with me.
There's 60 miles of wilderness
between here and Craster's
and Mance Rayder has an army
bearing down on us,
but we have to do this.
Our survival
may depend on
us getting
to these mutineers
before Mance does.
They know the Wall.
They know our defenses.
If Mance learns what
they know, we're lost.
But if that's not enough,
then consider this.
If the Night's Watch
are truly brothers,
then Lord Commander Mormont
was our father.
He lived and died
for the Watch
and he was betrayed
by his own men.
Stabbed in the back
by cowards.
He deserved far better.
All we can give him now
is justice.
Who will join me?
I can't let a recruit
come north of the Wall.
Then let me say my vows.
If it's a fight you're
heading for, then you
need men who know how.
Thank you, brothers.
( women whimpering )
Woman:
No, don't.
Don't, please.
Woman 2:
Please don't. Ow!
You're hurting me.
Karl Tanner
from Gin Alley
drinking wine
from the skull
of Jeor fucking Mormont.
Any command for us,
Lord Commander?
What's that?
Fuck 'em
till they're dead?
- ( whimpers )
- Did you hear that, boys?
Fuck 'em
till they're dead.
Rast.
Go outside
and feed the beast.
We should kill that thing.
You should shut
your fucking hole,
ugly little cunt.
You look like
a fucking ballsack.
Ugly. Look at your
stupid cunt face.
I could piss in any gutter
and soak five of you.
Know how much
they paid me to kill
a man in King's Landing?
Seven silvers.
They told me a man's name
and that man never saw
daylight again.
None of them cocksuckers
got away from me.
Haven't lost a fight
since I was nine.
Maybe it's time.
What do you think, eh?
Maybe you're the man.
Eh, cunt?
I wouldn't stand a chance.
None of us would.
I was a fucking legend
in Gin Alley.
A fucking legend!
I would take any knight--
any knight, any time.
Fucking cunts in steel plate.
Fucking cowards.
( baby fussing )
- A gift for the gods.
A gift for the gods.
What the fuck is that?
Craster's last child.
A boy.
What am I supposed
to do with him?
What did Craster
do with 'em?
Kill 'em before
they could grow up
and do the same to him?
All right.
Don't need another
mouth to feed.
- Hand him over.
- He didn't kill them.
- He offered them.
- To who?
To the gods.
The white walkers.
Women:
A gift for the gods.
Shut up!
So...
if it worked for him...
( crying )
Let's give the walkers
what they want.
( baby crying )
Rast is headed that way.
( baby fussing )
( crying )
( loud breathing )
( growling )
Pink-eyed fuck.
You thirsty?
( growls )
- ( growls )
- Fuck!
( crows cawing )
( wind howling )
( ice crackling )
( barks )
( baby crying )
Hodor.
Do you hear that?
Is that a baby?
It's coming.
I'm going out there.
No, we need
to stay together.
I'm going.
( whines )
( baby crying )
( wolf howling )
( growls )
- Bran. Bran.
- Hodor. Hodor.
- Hodor.
- Bran, what happened?
Summer, he's hurt.
They've caught him
in a trap.
Who?
I didn't see, but they
have my brother's wolf.
They have Ghost.
Bran:
They're Night's Watch.
Look.
Jon might be here.
If Jon was here,
why would they put
his wolf in a cage?
( woman whimpering )
( men shouting )
They might have been
Night's Watch once,
not anymore.
We're not safe here.
We need to go.
No.
Bran, we need to go now.
I'm not leaving
without Summer.
Can you remember
where the cage was?
The east side
of the keep.
If I'm not back
soon, we'll meet--
Hodor.
( shouting )
( groans )
Hodor.
If I was your size,
I'd be king of
the fucking world.
( men laughing )
Help him up.
This is nice.
Fine leather.
You're no wildling.
Important. Highborn.
Who are you?
( grunts )
You see,
where I come from,
a commoner like me slaps
a little lord like you,
I'd lose my right hand.
But we're a long way
from home, aren't we?
And the two of you,
fancy-looking folks
north of the Wall
creeping through
the woods.
Isn't that a bit odd?
I like your curly hair.
My mom had curls
like that.
Beautiful brown curls.
Why'd you drag a crippled
boy all the way up here?
See you haven't played
this game before.
A highborn hostage,
that's valuable.
But three of them,
that's a lot
of mouths to feed.
- Rast: What the fuck's
wrong with him?
- Come here.
( screams )
No, please.
Please.
Please, let me help him.
- Who are you?
- Please.
- I'm Brandon Stark!
I'm Brandon Stark
of Winterfell.
It's Jon Snow's brother.
It's Meera. It's Meera.
I'm right here.
And I thought this
was gonna be another
boring day.
Meera:
I'm right here.
( wind howling )
( ice crackling )
( baby crying )
( crying stops )
( crackles )
( theme music playing )