( theme music playing )
- ( woman laughing )
- Ramsay: Tansy!
Woman:
Tansy! Tansy!
- Ramsay: Tansy!
- ( dogs barking )
( growling )
( laughing )
Ramsay:
Tansy!
- ( screams )
- There you are.
( barking )
( screaming )
I can't see her, Ramsay.
( panting )
Tansy!
( whimpering )
If you make it out
of the woods, you win!
Run, Tansy, run!
( screams )
( whimpering )
( panting, crying )
- Ramsay: Tansy.
- Woman: Where is she?
- Ramsay: Tansy,
Tansy, Tansy!
- ( barking )
( whimpering )
( screams )
( crying )
Good girls.
Down, girls.
Down.
Well done.
You, too.
- I only wounded her.
- You brought her down.
That's what matters.
A fine shot.
Wasn't it, Reek?
A fine shot, master.
My lady.
Please, my lord.
It hurts.
Oh, sweet.
Don't cry.
It will be over soon.
She thinks
she's pretty.
Let me put one
through her face.
We have to reward
the hounds, love.
They did all
the hard work.
Why? I did
whatever you asked.
But you made Myranda
feel jealous.
- Me jealous of her?
- My lord, please.
You can see that your presence
has become a bit of a problem.
- ( crying )
- ( dogs snarling, barking )
Rip her!
- Rip her!
- ( Tansy screaming )
( tearing )
Not so pretty now.
Tyrion:
Your new hand, it's nicer
than the old one.
Wouldn't you agree, Pod?
Is it solid gold?
Gilded steel.
You're not eating.
Why is no one eating?
My wife wastes away
and my brother
starves himself.
- I'm not hungry.
- You lost a hand,
not a stomach.
Try the boar.
Cersei can't get enough
of it since one killed
Robert for her.
A toast.
To the proud
Lannister children.
The dwarf, the cripple,
and the mother of madness.
- Oh!
- I'll clean it up.
No, I'll do it.
Leave us.
It's only wine.
I can't fight anymore.
What about your left?
I can hold a sword,
but all my instincts
are wrong.
How can I
protect the king
when I can hardly
wipe my own ass?
You're the Lord
Commander now.
Command.
Let others
do the fighting.
When was the last time
Father used a sword?
I'm not Father.
I'm the Kingslayer.
When people find out
I can't slay a pigeon...
Train, then.
Learn to fight with
your other hand.
With whom? You?
Men talk.
Soon as someone
discovers I can't fight,
he'll tell everyone.
You need a proper,
discreet swordsman.
As it happens,
I have just the one.
My brother tells me
you can keep your
mouth shut.
Unusual talent
for a sellsword.
He tells me
you shit gold
just like your father.
Is this place safe?
There's this knight,
Leygood,
- got thunderbolts
on his shield.
- Uh-huh.
Right here is where
I fuck his wife.
She's a screamer,
that one.
If they don't hear her,
they won't hear us.
( whistles )
I've never seen
Valyrian steel before.
She's a beauty.
The problem is,
if you fight with
an edged blade,
I'll have to.
And if I fight with
an edged blade,
I'll have no one
left to pay me.
( blade clatters )
I haven't used a sparring
sword since I was nine.
Ah!
Bold warrior you are,
attacking a man when
his guard's down.
Best time
to attack a man.
Mind yourself.
- If I still
had my right hand...
- Plan on growing it back?
Come on, then.
Man:
Open the gates!
Riders coming in!
( horse whinnies )
Man:
Let's get these
horses seen to!
Father.
Welcome home.
Walda, this is
Ramsay Snow, my bastard.
A pleasure, Mother.
Hello.
Roose:
See that the horses are fed,
watered, and rubbed down.
And take Lady Walda
to her chambers.
This way, my lady.
Where is your prize?
With the hounds.
I'll have a look at him.
I hear you took a hand
from the Kingslayer.
Word travels.
How he screamed.
- You would have loved it.
- ( laughs )
Father.
What did you
do to him?
I trained him.
He was a slow learner,
but he learned.
You flayed him.
Peeled a few bits.
Removed a few others.
This was Balon Greyjoy's
son and heir.
We've been flaying
our enemies for 1,000 years.
The flayed man
is on our banners.
My banners,
not yours.
You're not a Bolton.
You're a Snow.
Tywin Lannister has given
me the North.
But he won't lift a finger
to help me take it.
As long as the ironborn
hold Moat Cailin,
our armies are trapped
south of the Neck.
Theon was
a valuable hostage,
not your plaything.
I wanted to trade him
for Moat Cailin.
I already asked.
Lord Greyjoy refused.
Savages have no--
You sent terms
to Balon Greyjoy
without my consent?
You made me acting
Lord of the Dreadfort.
I acted.
I had to smuggle myself
into my own lands
thanks to the Greyjoys.
I needed Theon.
I needed him whole.
Theon was our enemy.
But Reek,
Reek will never
betray us.
I placed far too much
trust in you.
Reek, how could you
let me stand before
my father unshaven?
- It's disrespectful.
- I'm sorry, my lord.
Give him the razor.
If I'm not a Bolton,
Father, what does it matter?
Go on, Reek.
A nice close shave.
Reek, tell Father
where are Bran
and Rickon Stark?
I don't know,
my lord.
You murdered them
and displayed their corpses
at Winterfell.
Ramsay: Reek,
did you murder
the Stark boys?
No, my lord.
Just two farm boys.
Ramsay:
And crisped them
so no one would know.
Theon:
Yes, my lord.
The Starks have always
ruled the North.
If Bran and Rickon
are alive,
the country will rally
to their side
now that
Robb Stark is gone.
Oh, that's right, Reek.
Robb Stark is dead.
Sorry.
I know he was like
a brother to you.
But my father put a knife
through his heart.
How do you feel
about that?
- You ready for a hunt?
- Always.
Find those boys
and I'll give you 1,000 acres
and a holdfast.
Your pet rat
have any thoughts
on which way they went
after Winterfell?
Jon Snow is at
Castle Black.
Who the fuck
is Jon Snow?
Their bastard brother.
He could be
sheltering them.
He may know
where they are.
Even if he doesn't,
he's half Stark himself.
Could be a threat.
You want to prove
yourself a Bolton?
Gather whatever
men you can and ride
for Moat Cailin.
Bring this creature
of yours.
Maybe he'll be
of some use.
Take the Moat
for the family,
for our family,
and I'll reconsider
your position.
Lord Varys.
Breakfasting
with the king?
I'm afraid foreigners
aren't welcome at such
exclusive affairs.
- Oh, to be foreign.
- Ahem.
Shae has been noticed.
Sansa's maid
saw you with her.
She already told
your sister.
It's only a matter of time
before your father hears.
So I'm guilty
of being seen with
my own wife's handmaiden.
My father will ask you
if there's anything more
and you'll tell him
some clever lie.
No, I will not.
How long do you imagine
your father and sister
would let me live
if they suspected
me of lying?
I have no pet sellsword
to protect me.
No legendary brother
to avenge me.
Only little birds
who whisper in my ear.
Forgive me
if I don't weep for you.
No one weeps
for spiders or whores.
I have friends across
the sea who could help her.
She won't leave.
I've told her this is
a dangerous place
so many times,
she no longer believes it.
Your father has promised
to hang the next whore
he finds you with.
Have you ever known
your father to make
an idle threat?
From House Tyrell
and the people
of the Reach,
Your Grace, it is
my honor to present you
with this wedding cup.
May you
and my daughter Margaery
drink deep
and live long.
A handsome goblet,
my lord.
Or shall I call
you Father?
I shall be honored,
Your Grace.
She's the whore
I told you about.
The dark-haired one.
Have her brought
to the Tower of the Hand
before the wedding.
A book?
"The Lives of Four Kings."
Grand Maester Kaeth's history
of the reigns of
Daeron the Young Dragon,
Baelor the Blessed,
Aegon the Unworthy,
and Daeron the Good.
A book every king
should read.
Now that the war is won,
we should all find
time for wisdom.
Thank you, Uncle.
One of only two Valyrian
steel swords in the capital,
Your Grace, freshly
forged in your honor.
Careful, Your Grace.
Nothing cuts like
Valyrian steel.
So they say.
( panting )
Such a great sword
should have a name.
- What shall I call her?
- Man: Stormbringer.
- Man #2: Terminus.
- Man #3: Widow's Wail.
- Man #4: Wolfsbane.
- Widow's Wail. I like that.
( chuckles )
Every time I use it,
it'll be like cutting off
Ned Stark's head
all over again.
( door opens )
Don't.
You want me on the desk?
- What's wrong, my lion?
- Don't call me that.
What should I call you?
I'm afraid our friendship
can't continue.
Our friendship?
There's a ship waiting in
the harbor bound for Pentos.
What?
You'll have your own
cabin, of course,
and across the Narrow Sea
a house, servants.
What is this?
I'm a married man.
My wife has
suffered a great deal,
as you well know.
I don't want her
to suffer anymore
on my account.
I need to uphold my vows.
She doesn't want you.
- I need to do right by her.
- You don't want her.
By our children.
- What are you afraid of?
- I'm not afraid.
You are. You are afraid of
your father and your sister.
- You're going to run
from them all your life?
- I need you to leave.
I'm not afraid of them.
I'm not going to run.
- Shae.
- We will fight
them together.
It's like you said,
I am yours and you are mine.
You're a whore!
Sansa is fit to bear
my children and you are not.
I can't be in love
with a whore.
I can't have children
How many men
have you been with?
500? 5,000?
How many whores
have you been with?
I have enjoyed my time
with all of them
and I have enjoyed my time
with you most of all.
But now that time
is over.
( Shae crying )
You'll have a comfortable
life in Pentos.
Bronn will escort you
to your ship.
( door closes )
- ( woman screaming )
- Melisandre: Hear us now.
Accept these tokens
of our faith, my lord,
and lead us
from the darkness.
( crying )
Sire, I served you well.
( crowd chanting )
Lord of Light,
show us the way...
Selyse, you're my sister!
Yours are the stars
that guide us.
Tell him!
Melisandre:
Lord of Light, protect us,
for the night is dark
and full of terrors.
( screaming )
Did you see?
Their souls.
It was their souls.
Our lord took them.
Did you see?
Lord Florent was
your brother by law.
He was an infidel.
He worshipped the gods
of his fathers
and their fathers
before him.
They were the gods
of your fathers, too.
I ordered him to tear
down his idols.
He disobeyed.
How many ships did he
bring to your cause?
How many men?
A good deal
more than you.
Did you see,
Ser Davos?
They're with
our lord now.
Their sins
all burned away.
Did you see?
I'm sure they're more
than grateful, my queen.
( sniffs )
Meat's off.
Our larders
are almost empty.
Serve fish, then.
We're on an island.
You hate fish.
I hate a good many things,
but I suffer them all the same.
When Storm's End
was under siege
and I was starving,
Stannis boiled soup
for me from books.
The binding glue
is made from horses.
One morning,
he shot two seagulls
on the beach.
I've never tasted anything
as good as grilled seagull.
- Do you remember?
- Of course I remember.
Have you ever known
true hunger, my lady?
It's all I knew
when I was a child.
Until you found
the Lord of Light?
Until he found me.
I fear for
our daughter's soul.
Every mother should fear
for her child's soul.
- She's a stubborn
little beast.
- She's a child.
You barely know her.
You think she's sweet
because she smiles
when you visit.
She's sullen and stubborn
and sinful.
Why else would
the Lord of Light have
seen fit to mark her face?
She needs the rod.
She's my daughter.
You will not strike her.
As you command.
Perhaps the Lady Melisandre
could speak with her.
( knocks )
Come in.
Were you sleeping,
Princess?
Did you watch the ceremony
on the beach?
I heard it.
And it frightened you?
Ser Axel was my uncle.
He was always
kind to me.
They're in a better
place now, Princess.
The fire cleansed them
of the sins of the world.
But they screamed.
Women scream
when they give birth.
Afterward they are
filled with joy.
Afterward they aren't
ash and bone.
You have so many
questions, don't you?
So did I
when I was a child.
I was much like you.
Only I wasn't a princess.
And you didn't have this.
No.
But I suffered in other ways,
sweet girl, believe me.
What do you know
of the gods?
I read
"The Seven-Pointed Star."
Lies and fables.
Septons speak
of seven gods.
There are but two--
a god of light
and love and joy
and a god of darkness,
evil, and fear.
Eternally at war.
There are no seven heavens
and no seven hells?
There's only one hell,
Princess.
The one we live in now.
( heavy breathing )
( growls )
- Hodor.
- ( breathing heavily )
Why did you wake me?
You've been gone
for hours.
I was hungry.
We're all hungry.
I was just eating.
Summer was eating.
Your body can't live on
the food your wolf consumes.
Spending too much time
in Summer's skin
is dangerous.
You're not
a direwolf, Bran.
Must be glorious, though.
To run, to leap,
to hunt.
To be whole.
I know that's tempting,
but if you're trapped
in Summer for too long,
you'll forget what it was
to be human.
You'd forget us, Bran.
You'd forget your mother
and father.
You'd forget your brothers
and sisters.
You'd forget Winterfell.
You'd forget you.
And if we lose you,
we lose everything.
( wind blowing )
( wolf barks )
Hodor, take me
to the tree.
( caws )
Voice:
Look for me...
( cawing )
Voice:
...beneath the tree.
- Cersei: He saw us.
- ( screaming )
( dragon roaring )
Voice:
North.
( gasps )
I know where
we have to go.
( bells tolling )
Let it be known
that Margaery of House Tyrell
and Joffrey of the Houses
Lannister and Baratheon
are one heart, one flesh,
one soul.
Cursed be he
who would seek
to tear them asunder.
With this kiss,
I pledge my love.
( applause )
We have a new queen.
Better her than you.
- Bit much, wouldn't you say?
- It feels proportionate.
- Proportionate to what?
- The expected extravagance.
People who spend their money
on this sort of nonsense
tend not to have it
for long.
You ought to try
enjoying something
before you die.
You might find
it suits you.
Not now, Mace.
Lord Tywin and I
are speaking.
Anyway, I don't know what
you're complaining about.
I'm paying my share.
Shall we stick golden roses
in half the meat pies
to commemorate
your generosity?
No, your heartfelt
thank-you is its
own reward.
I would imagine
I'd be hearing it
again before long.
Wars are rather expensive.
"The Iron Bank
will have its due."
How they love
to remind everyone.
Almost as much as you
Lannisters with your debts.
I'm not worried about
the Iron Bank.
We both know
you're smarter than that.
Come, Tywin, let us
celebrate young love.
- ( music playing )
- ( people laughing, chatting )
All taken care of.
- You saw her board the ship?
- Aye, she's on it.
You saw the ship
sail away?
No one knows she's there
but you, me, and Varys.
How do you know?
Because if someone follows
me without an invitation,
I'm the last person
they ever follow.
There's someone
following you?
She's gone.
I know you don't
want to believe it,
but she is.
Now, go drink till it
feels like you did
the right thing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Not you.
You look
exquisite, child.
The wind has been
at you, though.
I haven't had
the opportunity
to tell you
how sorry I was to hear
about your brother.
War is war,
but killing a man
at a wedding,
horrid.
What sort of monster
would do such a thing?
As if men need more
reasons to fear marriage.
My lady.
Lord Tyrion, you see?
Not as bad as all that.
Perhaps if
your pauper husband
were to sell his mule
and his last pair of shoes,
he might be able to afford
to bring you to Highgarden
for a visit.
Now that peace has come
and all is right
with the world,
it would do you good
to see some of it.
You must excuse me.
It's time I ate
some of this food
I paid for.
♪ A coat of gold ♪
♪ Or a coat of red ♪
♪ A lion
still has claws ♪
♪ And mine,
my lord... ♪
Very good. Very good.
Off you go.
- ( coins clatter )
- ( crowd laughs )
My love, why don't we
make the announcement?
( taps goblet )
Everyone.
The queen would like
to say a few words.
( applause )
We are so fortunate
to enjoy this marvelous
food and drink.
Not all among us
are so lucky.
To thank the gods
for bringing the recent
war to a just end,
King Joffrey has decreed
that the leftovers
from our feast be given
to the poorest in his city.
- ( applause )
- ( music playing )
You're an example
to us all.
Ser Jaime,
I'm very sorry.
Ser Loras,
it's quite all right.
Your sister looks
very beautiful.
Loras:
As does yours.
So, looking forward
to your wedding?
Yes, very much.
Our fathers are both
rather keen on the prospect.
They certainly are.
Perhaps they should
get married.
( laughs )
If you were
to marry Cersei,
she'd murder you
in your sleep.
If you somehow managed
to put a child in her first,
she'd murder him, too,
long before he drew
his first breath.
Luckily for you,
none of this will happen
because you'll never
marry her.
And neither will you.
Your Grace.
My king.
- My queen.
- Lady Brienne.
So good of you to come.
I'm no lady,
Your Grace.
Did you just bow?
Apologies, Your Grace.
I never did master
the curtsy.
You're the one who put a sword
through Renly Baratheon.
That's not true, my love.
Brienne had nothing
to do with it.
A shame.
I'd knight
the man that put an end
to that deviant's life.
I just wanted
to congratulate you both
and wish you good fortune.
The country has been
at war too long.
I hope your reign
is long and peaceful.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you.
I hope we see
more of you.
Lady Brienne.
You're Lord Selwyn
Tarth's daughter.
That makes you a lady
whether you want
to be or not.
As you say, Your Grace.
I owe you my gratitude.
You returned my brother
safely to King's Landing.
In truth, he rescued me,
Your Grace.
More than once.
Did he?
Haven't heard
that story before.
Not such a fascinating
story, I'm afraid.
I'm sure you have many
fascinating stories.
Sworn to Renly Baratheon.
Sworn to Catelyn Stark.
And now my brother.
Must be exciting to flit
from one camp to the next
serving whichever lord
or lady you fancy.
I don't serve
your brother, Your Grace.
But you love him.
Your Grace.
No, no, come to my chambers
and I will examine
you personally.
- She'll do no such thing.
- Oh, Your Grace.
Yes, well, this young
lady sought my advice--
You should see Qyburn.
He's quite good.
- Your Grace.
- Qyburn? Deplorable man.
Brought shame
on the Citadel with his
repugnant experiments.
More repugnant than
your gnarled fingers
on that girl's thighs?
Your Grace,
I am a man of learning.
My little brother had you
sent to the Black Cells
when you annoyed him.
What do you think
I could do to you
if you annoyed me?
I never meant
to annoy anyone.
But you are.
You annoy me right now.
Every breath you draw
in my presence annoys me.
So here's what I want
you to do.
I want you to leave
my presence.
Leave this wedding
right now.
Go to the kitchens
and instruct them
that all the leftovers
from the feast will be
brought to the kennels.
Your Grace,
Queen Margaery--
The queen is telling you
the leftovers
will feed the dogs
or you will.
A gold dragon to whoever
knocks my fool's hat off.
( crowd laughing )
You're in rather
a good mood.
- I suppose I am.
- I won't ask why.
- Small pleasures.
- Your Grace. Lord Tywin.
Prince Oberyn.
I don't believe you
have met Ellaria.
This is the Lord Hand
Tywin Lannister
and Cersei Lannister
the Queen Regent.
I suppose it is
former Queen Regent now.
Lord Hand
and Lady Cersei,
- Ellaria Sand.
- My lord. My lady.
Charmed.
Can't say I've ever
met a Sand before.
We are everywhere in Dorne.
I have 10,000 brothers
and sisters.
Bastards are born
of passion, aren't they?
We don't despise them
in Dorne.
No?
How tolerant of you.
I expect it is a relief,
Lady Cersei,
giving up your regal
responsibilities.
Wearing the crown for so
many years must have left
your neck a bit crooked.
I suppose you'll never
know, Prince Oberyn.
It's a shame
your older brother couldn't
attend the wedding.
Please give him
our regards.
With any luck,
the gout will abate
with time and he will
be able to walk again.
They call it
the rich man's disease.
A wonder
you don't have it.
Noblemen in my part
of the country
don't enjoy the same lifestyle
as our counterparts in Dorne.
People everywhere
have their differences.
In some places the highborn
frown upon those of low birth.
In other places
the rape and murder
of women and children
is considered distasteful.
What a fortunate
thing for you,
former Queen Regent,
that your daughter
Myrcella has been sent
to live in the latter
sort of place.
( taps goblet )
Everyone, silence!
Clear the floor.
There's been too much
amusement here today.
A royal wedding
is not an amusement.
is history.
The time has come
for all of us
to contemplate
our history.
My lords...
my ladies...
I give you
- King Joffrey...
- ( shouting )
...Renly, Stannis,
Robb Stark,
Balon Greyjoy.
The War of the Five Kings.
( applause, laughter )
I'm the rightful king.
- King in the North!
- Yes!
- Traitor. You're a traitor.
- ( laughing )
For the Seven Kingdoms!
Let the war begin.
- ( laughing )
- ( howls )
Renly, you're no king.
Away, degenerate.
Away. Away.
Ooh, careful.
( squeals )
- Go on.
- I want you to
be my prince.
( laughing )
Stannis!
Who's got the gold
now, Stark?
I am the rightful king.
Challenge me, ruffian.
- Take that.
- I'm drowning.
I'm drowning.
I am the King
in the North!
Not wildfire!
- ( laughing )
- ( crying )
Pay each of them 20 gold
when this is done.
Podrick:
Yes, my lord.
We'll have to find another
way to thank the king.
Charge!
Ready, again.
I am the King
in the North!
- Charge!
- Yes!
- ( crowd cheers )
- Your head!
- ( laughing )
( laughing )
( grunting )
Fine gentlemen.
( applause )
Well fought.
Here you are.
Champion's purse.
Though you're not
the champion yet, are you?
A true champion defeats
all the challengers.
Surely there are
others out there
who still dare
to challenge my reign.
Uncle.
How about you?
I'm sure they have
a spare costume.
( crowd laughs )
One taste of combat was
enough for me, Your Grace.
I would like to keep
what remains of my face.
I think you
should fight him.
This was but
a poor imitation
of your own bravery
on the field of battle.
I speak
as a firsthand witness.
Climb down from
the high table
with your new
Valyrian sword
and show everyone how
a true king wins his throne.
Be careful, though.
This one is clearly
mad with lust.
It would be a tragedy
for the king to lose
his virtue
hours before
his wedding night.
( light laughter )
A fine vintage.
Shame that it spilled.
It did not spill.
My love,
come back to me.
It's time for
my father's toast.
( applause )
Well, how does he expect me
to toast without wine?
Uncle, you can be
my cupbearer
seeing as you're
too cowardly to fight.
Your Grace does me
a great honor.
It's not meant
as an honor.
Bring me my goblet.
What good is an empty cup?
Fill it.
Kneel.
Kneel before your king.
I said...
kneel!
Look, the pie.
( applause )
My queen.
- ( gasps )
- ( applause )
Margaery:
Wonderful.
My hero.
- Can we leave now?
- Let's find out.
Uncle.
Where are you going?
You're my cupbearer,
remember?
I thought I might change
out of these wet clothes,
Your Grace.
No, no, no.
No, you're perfect
the way you are.
Serve me my wine.
Well, hurry up.
This pie is dry.
Mm, good.
Needs washing down.
If it please Your Grace,
Lady Sansa is very tired.
No.
( coughs )
No, you'll wait here...
un--
( coughs )
- ( coughing )
- Your Grace?
( coughing )
It's nothing.
( gasping )
- He's choking!
- Help the poor boy.
( gasping )
- Idiots, help your king.
- Move away!
( choking )
- Joffrey! Joffrey!
- Cersei: Help him!
- Someone help him!
- Joffrey!
( gagging )
- Come with me now.
- Cersei: Joffrey! Joffrey!
If you want to live,
we have to leave.
Don't touch him!
( gurgling )
- Joffrey.
- ( gasping )
Please, Joffrey.
Joffrey, what is it?
Help him!
( gasps )
( crying )
My son.
( crowd sobbing )
Man: He's gone.
Our king is gone.
He did this.
He poisoned my son,
your king.
Take him.
Take him!
( crowd shouting )
( music playing )
♪ In a coat of gold ♪
♪ Or a coat of red ♪
♪ A lion still has claws ♪
♪ And mine are long ♪
♪ And sharp, my lord ♪
♪ As long and sharp
as yours ♪
♪ And so he spoke
and so he spoke ♪
♪ That Lord of Castamere ♪
♪ And now the rains ♪
♪ Weep o'er his hall ♪
♪ With no one
there to hear ♪
♪ Yes, now the rains ♪
♪ Weep o'er his hall ♪
♪ And not a soul
to hear. ♪