( theme music playing )
( snorts )
( horse whinnies )
( grunts )
First Ranger, you have
command of Castle Black.
Lord Commander,
it is my duty to tell you
I believe this mission
to be reckless, foolhardy,
and an insult
to all the brothers
who have died
fighting the wildlings.
As always, thank you
for your honesty.
Safe travels,
Lord Commander.
Thank you, Sam.
Oh, um...
It's dragonglass.
It's what I used
to kill the white walker.
I hope
you don't need them.
Me, too.
Yah.
( Aemon gasping )
( coos )
There he is.
- ( Little Sam giggles )
- ( laughs )
That laugh.
Egg.
Egg laughed like that.
One of the first things
I remember.
His little brother Aegon.
He became king.
And before that,
he was a jolly fellow,
like this one.
( laughs )
Get him south,
Gillyflower.
Before it's too late.
- ( wind whistling )
- ( crying )
( wind howling )
( gasps )
Theon, wait.
Not Theon, my lady.
Reek.
Help me.
You're his wife now.
Theon.
Do what he says.
Do what he says
or he'll hurt you.
He already hurts me
every night.
All day I'm locked
in this room
and every night
he comes...
It can't be any worse.
It can.
It can always be worse.
- What did he do to you?
- Please.
- You betrayed my family!
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You have to help me.
Theon, help me.
He'll see us.
You don't know him.
My family still has
friends in the North.
All I need to do
is give a signal
and they'll rescue me.
Climb to the top
of the broken tower.
Light this candle
and put it in the window.
- Promise me, Theon.
- Reek! My name is Reek.
Your name
is Theon Greyjoy.
Last surviving son
of Balon Greyjoy,
Lord of the Iron Islands.
Do you hear me?
Theon...
promise me.
( door closes,
latch clanks )
( wind howling )
Yes, Reek?
( cooing )
Aemon:
Egg.
Mother's looking
for you.
Egg.
Get some sleep, Sam.
You'll have to speak
for him tomorrow.
You don't know that.
Get some sleep.
I'll watch over him.
Sam:
I'm staying, too.
He's always
been good to me.
I can't leave him now.
Egg!
( labored breathing )
Egg.
I dreamed...
that I was old.
Sam: His name
was Aemon Targaryen.
He came to us
from King's Landing.
A maester of the Citadel,
chained and sworn,
and sworn brother
of the Night's Watch,
ever faithful.
No man was wiser
or gentler or kinder.
At the Wall,
a dozen lord commanders
came and went during
his years of service,
but he was always there
to counsel them.
He was the blood
of the dragon...
but now his fire
has gone out.
And now his watch
is ended.
All:
And now his watch
is ended.
( sniffles )
You're losing
all your friends, Tarly.
My beautiful wife.
When my father told me
we were marrying,
I half expected
a fat, bearded beast.
Do you know how pleased
I was when I saw you?
You've made me
very happy.
Our scouts report
that Stannis Baratheon
rides for Winterfell.
He's a respected
commander.
His troops are loyal
and battle-tested.
He's hired thousands
of foreign sellswords
to bolster his army.
But this storm
is a stroke of luck
for us northerners.
Our people are used
to fighting in the frost.
His army is out there now
suffering in the snow.
One day I'll be
Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North.
You'll be my lady
and Wardeness.
But isn't
your stepmother pregnant?
What of it?
What happens
if she has a boy?
Then I'll have
a baby brother.
But he'll be the heir.
I'm Lord Bolton's
eldest son.
But you're a bastard.
A trueborn will always
have the stronger claim.
I've been naturalized
by a royal decree from--
Tommen Baratheon?
Another bastard.
Bastards can rise
high in the world.
Like your half-brother
Jon Snow.
Born the bastard
of Winterfell,
now the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
You didn't know?
Yes, he's done
very well for himself.
Oh.
I nearly forgot why
I asked you to join me.
Come, my lady.
Ramsay:
Your northern friend.
Reek told me
you wanted to leave.
Why?
Winterfell is your home
and I am your husband.
Tough old bird.
Everyone talks
when I start peeling them.
But this one,
her heart gave out
before I even got
to her face.
We do breed them tough
in the North.
Bring my wife
back to her chamber.
It's far too cold
out here for a lady.
You should hold on
to your candles.
The nights
are so long now.
( chuckles )
( chatter )
- ( chatter continues )
- ( man coughing )
Davos:
40 horses died
in the night.
We'll lose more
come sunset.
We're running
out of food.
We can't open
the supply line
until the snow clears.
What else?
The Stormcrows
rode off last night.
500 men.
Sellswords.
Loyal to nothing
but gold.
We still have
a hard march
to Winterfell
and we won't be marching
anywhere in this weather.
And?
This isn't our time.
We should head
back to Castle Black
when the snow clears.
I retreated from
King's Landing, Ser Davos.
If I retreat again,
I'll become the King Who Ran.
- Your Grace--
- Winter is coming.
Those aren't just
the Stark words.
It's a fact.
If we march
back to Castle Black,
we winter at Castle Black.
And who can say
how many years
this winter will last?
It's better to
wait for the right time
than risk everything.
This is the right time
and I will risk everything.
Because if I don't,
we've lost.
We march to victory
or we march to defeat.
But we go forward.
Only forward.
Your Grace.
I've trusted
in your visions
and your prophecies
for years.
You saw it yourself,
my king,
when you stared
into the flames.
A great battle
in the snow.
- I don't know what I saw.
- You do know.
Trust yourself.
And you?
Do you trust yourself?
I trust in the Lord.
Are you sure?
I have seen myself
walk along the battlements
of Winterfell.
I have seen
the flayed man banners
lowered to the ground.
But sometimes
sacrifices must be made
to ensure victory.
I have shown you
the power of king's blood.
The usurper Robb Stark.
The usurper
Joffrey Baratheon.
We don't have
Robert's bastard here.
No, we have
someone better.
And your blood
runs through her veins.
Have you lost your mind?
Do you doubt me?
Still?
After all
that you've seen.
There must be
another way.
- Leeches or--
- There is only one way.
You must become king
before the Long Night begins.
Only you can lead
the living against the dead.
All your life has led us
to this moment.
- To this decision.
- She's my daughter.
Get out.
( door opens )
There's always
some sort of grub on.
A bit of mutton
would be nice.
- A beauty from
beyond the Wall.
- ( man chuckles )
Where you going, love?
Aren't we better-looking
than the fat man?
No, the question is
is she pretty down south
in the real world
or is she pretty
'cause she's the only
girl here?
Even in White Harbor,
I'd want a kiss.
Come on, love,
give us a kiss.
- Leave me alone.
- Oh, if you were my girl,
I wouldn't leave you alone.
- One little kiss.
- Come on, give him a kiss.
A man gets lonely
guarding the Wall.
There's no need
to be rude.
We just want
a little affection.
Ooh.
( laughs )
Get your hands off her.
Brother Derek,
Brother Brant,
I believe you both
have guard duty tonight.
Sam the Slayer.
You gonna slay me
with that sword?
Brant:
Look at his hand shake.
Gilly, go on.
Get back to your room,
lock the door.
- I'm warning you.
- Come on.
Come on.
( grunts )
Sam!
You lying
sack of shit.
Derek:
Killed a white walker, eh?
- You fat-ass fuck.
- ( groans )
Come on, get up.
- Gilly: No!
- This your hero?
This hog?
Leave him alone!
Stubborn little
wildling bitch,
aren't you?
- ( Gilly screams )
- ( grunts )
- Come on!
- No!
- Sam! Sam! Sam!
- Come on!
( whimpering )
( grunting )
- Gilly: Sam! Sam!
- Derek: Come on.
- Brant: Right.
- ( Gilly crying )
- Derek: I'll deal with this.
- ( fabric ripping )
- Derek: Turn her over.
- Brant: All right.
I said get your hands
off her.
Brant:
You're gonna get
yourself killed.
Your lover Jon Snow's
not here to save you.
I killed a white walker,
I killed a Thenn.
I'll take
my chances with you.
( snarling, growling )
( barks )
- ( door slams )
- Sam!
- I'm all right.
- You're not.
Just a bit woozy.
( wincing )
The next time you see
something like that,
you leave it alone.
I will not.
They would have--
I don't know what
they would have done.
I know they
would have killed you
if Ghost hadn't come.
No. No, no.
They were tiring out.
I had them
in the palm of my hand.
Don't be stupid, Sam.
You're not a fighter.
What kind of man
would I be
if I ran away when I saw
someone hurting you?
Just promise me
whatever happens,
you'll take care
of Little Sam.
But of course I will.
And...
I'll take care
of you, too.
I need more water.
Stay.
Please?
( breathing quickens )
( winces )
Am I hurting you?
Are you sure?
( moans )
Oh, my!
( chains rattling )
- ( whip cracks )
- ( grunts )
Malko: A rare find
for the fighting pits,
my friends.
Not your usual street tough
or drunken pirate.
This one's
a Westerosi knight
from an ancient house
trained in sword and lance.
He fought beside
the stag king Robert
on the far side
of the Narrow Sea.
He was first
through the breach
during the Siege of Spike,
slaughtering 50 men
with his flaming sword.
He killed
the great Khal Drogo
in single combat.
Betrayed by his woman,
he sold himself into slavery
to repay his debts.
- Bidding begins
at 12 gold honors.
- ( crowd mumurs )
13.
Do I have 14?
15?
15 gold honors.
Do I hear 16?
16?
20.
Sold.
Wait! You have
to buy me as well.
Why?
We're a team.
I'm a great fighter, too.
( laughing )
He's funny.
You have to give him that.
( laughing )
( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- ( laughing continues )
( grunting, shouting )
You're right,
he's funny.
Thank you, my lord.
Thank you.
Yes.
My lord, if I may.
I've heard Meereen
has become a free city.
You might run into trouble
if you try to fight slaves
in the fighting pits.
Now, if you were
to fight freed men
who'd be paid a wage--
There's your wages,
funny man.
Should last the rest
of your life.
Malko:
These are warrior hands,
not a serving girl's.
5, going once...
( giggles )
How long before
the King of Meereen
comes to claim my pillow?
Don't be ridiculous.
My marriage to Hizdahr
is political.
I think he's smart enough
to understand that.
I think the Sons
of the Harpy have
stopped killing
because their leader
was made king.
Are you jealous?
You think
I'm petty enough
to speak ill of a man
just because
he represents
competition?
I do.
( laughs )
You're right.
My motivations
are entirely impure.
Doesn't make me wrong.
You told me yourself
I can't fight enemies
within and without.
So when enemies without
come knocking,
I need the city
of Meereen behind me.
I have no choice.
Everyone has a choice.
Even slaves
have a choice--
death or slavery.
So what else
can I do, hmm?
Marry me instead.
Even if I wanted to do
such an inadvisable thing,
I couldn't.
Why not?
You are queen.
You can do what you like.
No, I can't.
Then you are the only person
in Meereen who's not free.
And I know I'm here
to serve my queen and
not give advice,
but can I make
one more suggestion?
Of course.
On the day
of the great games,
gather all
the Great Masters
and Wise Masters
and Worthy Masters
you can find
and slaughter
them all.
I am a queen,
not a butcher.
All rulers are either
butchers or meat.
You there.
Where would I find
the High Septon
or High Sparrow
or whatever bloody
fool name he's got?
It's not as good a name
as Queen of Thorns,
I'll admit.
You should have
the decency
to stand when
you speak to a lady.
You should have the decency
to kneel before the gods.
Don't spar with me,
little fellow.
( groans )
For me,
it's the knees.
- You?
- Hips.
Ah.
A man of the people.
Is that your game?
It's an old game.
Dull and unconvincing.
A man of the people
who does Cersei's
dirty work for her.
The people always
do the dirty work.
Spare me the homilies.
I can smell a fraud
from a mile away.
Useful talent.
I'm here for my grandson
and granddaughter.
Your grandson
and granddaughter
swore sacred vows
and lied.
The Father judges us all.
Sons of high lords,
sons of fishermen.
If you break his laws,
you will be punished.
Don't you
walk away from me.
You don't give commands
here, Lady Olenna.
What is it you want?
Gold?
I'll make you
the richest septon
who ever lived.
( chuckles )
What, then?
I imagine this
is strange for you.
Everyone you meet
has a hidden motive
and you pride yourself
on sniffing it out.
But I'm telling you
a simple truth.
I serve the gods.
The gods demand justice.
How do they communicate
their demands?
By raven or horse?
By the holy text,
"The Seven-Pointed Star."
If you don't have one
in your library,
I'll give you my own.
I've read
"The Seven-Pointed Star."
Then you'll remember
the passages concerning
buggery and perjury.
Your grandchildren
will be punished
in the same manner
as anyone who breaks
the sacred laws.
Half the men,
women, and children
in this foul city
break the sacred laws.
You live among murderers,
thieves, and rapists,
and yet you
punish Loras
for shagging
some perfumed ponce
and Margaery for defending
her brother?
Yes. The gods' laws
must be applied
to all equally.
If it's equality
you want, so be it.
When House Tyrell
stops sending our crops
to the capital,
everyone here will starve.
And I'll make sure
the hungry know
who's to blame.
( chuckles )
Have you ever
sowed the field,
Lady Olenna?
Have you ever
reaped the grain?
Has anyone
in House Tyrell?
A lifetime of wealth
and power
has left you
blind in one eye.
You are the few,
we are the many.
And when the many
stop fearing the few...
( dog barking )
Lady Olenna.
Cersei:
Starving yourself
won't make things
any better for her,
my love.
She's in a prison cell
and there is nothing
I can do.
I am the king!
The queen is in prison
and there is nothing
I can do!
No matter who you are,
no matter how strong
you are, sooner or later,
you'll face circumstances
beyond your control.
Events you couldn't
possibly have anticipated
or prevented
even if you had.
You cannot blame
yourself for fate.
Your father,
your brother,
your grandfather--
I was Queen
of the Seven Kingdoms
and what could I do?
Hold them as they
left this world.
Kissed their heads
after they'd gone.
I'll call in the army.
I'll take back
the sept
and kill every
last one of them.
I'll start a war
if I have to.
You know as well as I do
who the first casualty
of that war would be.
I love her.
I love her...
and I can't help her.
We must be strong
for those we love.
We cannot give in
to despair.
I will speak
with the High Sparrow.
There must be
something he--
Let me talk to him
on your behalf.
The king cannot
sully himself negotiating
with an unwashed fanatic.
You will try
to help her?
I'll do everything
I can to win her freedom
and her brother's.
Your happiness is all
I want in this world.
- I know.
- No, you don't.
You can't possibly.
Not until you have
children of your own.
I would do anything
for you.
Anything to keep
you from harm.
I would burn cities
to the ground.
You are all that matters.
You and your sister.
From the moment you came
into this world.
My boy.
My only boy.
( door opens )
Prince Doran hopes
this satisfies
your concerns
about the princess's
well-being.
You looked different
when I left.
You had more hair.
And more hands.
- How's Trystane?
- He'll be all right.
I'm sorry for that.
It wasn't supposed
to happen that way.
Why is it
happening at all?
Your mother's
worried about you.
Threats have been made.
Dorne's too dangerous
for you.
- I've come to take you home.
- This is my home.
This has been
my home for years.
I didn't want to come here,
but she told me to.
I did what she said.
I did my duty and now
she's forcing me to go back?
It's for your own good.
These are complicated matters.
No, it's not
complicated at all.
It's simple.
I love Trystane,
I'm going to marry him,
and we're staying
right here.
- I don't understand.
- Of course you don't.
You don't know me.
Bronn:
♪ Brothers, O brothers,
my days here are done ♪
♪ The Dornishman's
taken my life ♪
♪ But what does
it matter ♪
♪ For all men must die ♪
♪ And I've tasted
the Dornishman's wife ♪
♪ I have, I've tasted
the Dornishman's wife. ♪
( clapping )
He's got a good voice.
We're lucky
he's a singer.
If he were a fighter,
we might have been
in trouble.
It's against my code
to hurt a woman.
It's amazing
how many men we beat
seem to have this code.
I wouldn't say
you beat me.
How's your arm?
Wonderful.
Wouldn't feel right
to leave Dorne without
a new scar.
( scoffs )
You think you're
leaving Dorne?
No great hurry.
Dornish women
are the most beautiful
women in the world.
Thank you.
I said Dornish women.
I didn't say you.
I'm not the most
beautiful woman
you've ever seen?
Bronn:
I've seen
quite a few women
in all
the Seven Kingdoms.
Name one more beautiful
than I am.
Well, now,
in King's Landing,
there was an absolutely
gorgeous...
There was a what?
In King's Landing,
you were saying?
Was I?
There was a woman
more beautiful than I am.
Was there?
My memory's not
what it was earlier.
How's your arm now?
You seem
concerned with it.
You must really like me.
( laughs )
And how about
your head?
My head?
You don't even want
to know what's
going on in--
( breathing heavily )
Your nose is bleeding.
It's nothing.
It's the dry air.
My dagger was coated
with a special ointment
from Asshai.
They call it
the Long Farewell.
It takes time to work,
but if a single drop
makes contact with the skin,
death.
The only antidote.
Who's the most
beautiful woman
in the world?
( quietly )
You.
Sorry? Who?
Don't drop it.
( gasping )
I think you're
very handsome as well.
- I'm sorry about the locale.
- No, you're not.
It felt like
the safest place.
Not for your
clientele, clearly.
It was an establishment
like no other.
The sheer range
of appetites catered to.
Desires that
didn't even exist
until we invented them.
You've always been
rather impressed with
yourself, haven't you?
The past is the past.
The future is all
that's worth discussing.
The future
of House Tyrell.
Don't pretend to have
any concern for my house,
my grandchildren or me.
I should have known
you'd return to the capital
as soon as things
started to go wrong.
- I promise you--
- I promise you,
Lord Baelish,
that our fates
are joined.
Together we murdered a king.
If my house should fall,
I will have nothing to hide.
And if I should meet
with some accident
here at your broken
little flesh market,
they'll never even find
what's left of you.
So...
do you deny a part
in all this?
Cersei summoned me
to King's Landing.
I dared not refuse her.
And what did she want?
A piece of information
she knew that I had.
Neither silence
nor lies were an option.
But I have
other information
of which she is unaware.
And as you say,
our interests are aligned.
I have a gift for you.
What kind of gift?
The same kind
I gave Cersei.
A handsome young man.
Yezzan:
Many worthy fighters
have died
trying to make it
to the great games.
When most of you
worthless scum join them
in death this afternoon,
it will represent
a significant rise
in your station.
But if you do happen
to triumph here,
you will fight
at the Great Pit
of Daznak itself
in front of the queen.
So whatever happens,
the gods have smiled
upon you today.
This is the day
your lives actually start
to mean something.
You and you.
You.
You two.
You, you, and you.
Up.
- Valar morghulis.
- Men: Valar dohaeris.
Prepare yourselves.
Sitting through
the great games
will be bad enough.
For generations
in the days leading up
to the great games,
it has been customary
for our ruler
to make the rounds
of the lower pits
to pay the fighters there
the honor of her presence.
- ( applause, cheering )
- Move yourselves.
Your Grace.
Your future Grace.
You honor us all.
Stand there.
Stand straight.
That's the fucking queen.
( softly )
We fight and die
for your glory,
O glorious queen.
All:
We fight and die
for your glory,
O glorious queen.
( crowd shouting )
- Man: Fight!
- ( metal clanging )
( men shouting,
grunting )
( applause, cheering )
( screams )
( shouting )
I think I've seen enough.
Your Grace,
it is a tradition
for the queen to stay
until the victor has emerged.
I've sacrificed
more than enough
for your traditions.
What are you doing?
Wait your turn,
you piece of fucking filth.
- ( grunts )
- ( crowd cheering )
( crowd cheering )
( screams )
( grunting )
( applause )
( applause, cheering )
Get him out
of my sight.
Khaleesi, please.
I just need
a moment of your time.
I brought you a gift.
Tyrion:
It's true.
He has.
Who are you?
I am the gift.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Your Grace.
My name
is Tyrion Lannister.
( coughs )
( door closes, locks )
Cersei:
This is horrible.
Unacceptable.
Are they feeding you
enough at least?
I brought you this.
Venison.
It's quite good.
I had it myself for supper
only last night.
We did everything
we could from the moment
they took your brother.
Tommen even went
to the sept himself
to confront
the High Sparrow.
But I fear the Faith
has left reason behind.
I know you did this.
We are making every effort
on your behalf.
I swear to you
by all the seven gods.
Lies come
easily to you.
Everyone knows that.
But innocence,
decency, concern,
you're not very good
at those, I'm afraid.
Perhaps that's why
your son was so eager
to cast you aside
for me.
You're upset.
You're not
thinking clearly.
I'll visit again
when you've had a chance
to calm down.
I don't want
to see you again.
I do hope you change
your mind about that.
I've been told
men often go mad
in the Black Cells
beneath the Red Keep.
Though I suppose
your isolation will end
when your trial begins.
Leave.
Yes.
I'm afraid I must.
My son needs me now
more than ever.
Get out,
you hateful bitch!
( knocks on door )
( door opens )
Sleep well, sister.
- ( sighs )
- ( lock clicks )
Thank you, Boake.
- You saw her?
- Yes.
- And?
- Her accommodations
seem sufficient.
What happens
to her now?
Well, she and her brother
are both being held
under fair suspicion.
A trial will be held
for each of them
to determine if they're
guilty of any acts
that might constitute
a violation of the tenets
of the faith.
Who will stand judge?
Seven septons
as it was in all trials
before the Targaryens.
Will you be
one of them?
I will.
If one
or both of them
were to confess
before the trial...
Then they will be shown
the Mother's mercy.
And what does
the Mother's mercy entail?
It depends upon
the situation.
The acts themselves,
the degree of contrition.
Thank you,
High Septon,
for bringing them
whatever justice
they deserve
in the eyes
of the Seven.
Did you know
this chapel
is one of
the oldest structures
in King's Landing?
I think I may have
heard at one point.
Baelor built his sept
around it.
But men worshipped here
long before him.
Who carved this altar?
- Do you know?
- I'm afraid I don't.
No one does.
There's no name on it
or anywhere else
in the chapel.
No, the people
who built this place
didn't inflict their vanity
on those who came after them
the way Baelor did
with that great gilded
monstrosity up there.
Hmm.
Their faith was clean.
Strip away the gold
and the ornaments,
knock down the statues
and the pillars,
and this is what remains.
Something simple...
and solid and true.
The Tyrells' finery
will be stripped away.
Their lies knocked down.
Their true hearts
laid bare for all to see.
And so it will be
for all of us.
High and low alike.
What will we find
when we strip away
your finery?
A young man came to us
not long ago.
Broken in body
and spirit.
He had so much
to strip away.
So much
weighing him down.
But piece by piece,
he unburdened himself.
Let go of vanity,
pride, sin.
Now his soul is so light,
he will float through
the Seven Heavens
like a bird.
Hmm.
And he has much
to say about you.
( door opens )
( door closes )
Move.
Let me go
immediately.
You will order her
to let me go.
I am the queen!
Have you lost your mind?
Let me go!
Get your filthy hands
off me!
Have you lost your mind?
I am the queen!
Let me go!
Look at me.
Look at my face.
It's the last thing
you'll see before you die.
( music playing )