-Look out!
-Fire! Fire!
Get out of there!
Get out of the fire! Get out of the fire!
A band of 20 men, maybe less.
They were in and out before anyone
spotted them.
Burnt our food stores to the ground,
all our siege weapons destroyed.
-Dozens of tents were--
-Horses?
We're still getting a count,
but hundreds are dead.
Twenty men rode into our camp
without a single guard sounding the alarm?
The northerners know more
about their land than we ever will.
Put last night's guards in chains.
Either they fell asleep or they conspired
with the enemy.
-Find out the truth and then hang them.
-Your Grace.
Unless there's a thaw, we can't press
forward to Winterfell
and we don't have enough food
to get us back to Castle Black.
We're not returning to Castle Black.
Forgive me, Your Grace, I never claimed
to be an expert in military matters,
but if we can't march forward
and we won't march back...
Have the dead horses butchered for meat.
Halt!
There it is!
Open the gates.
It was a failure.
It wasn't.
I went to save them. I failed.
You didn't fail him.
Or him. Or her.
Every one of them is alive because of you
and no one else.
I don't think that fact's lost on them.
You have a good heart, Jon Snow.
It'll get us all killed.
Out of my way.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
Find some healthy horses
and a few knights to guard you.
I'm sending you back to Castle Black.
Tell the Lord Commander
his king commands him
to send food, supplies, fresh horses.
In return, when I take the throne,
I'll make sure the Night's Watch
has all the men it requires.
He can guard all 19 castles on the Wall
if he so wishes.
Your Grace, you named me your Hand.
Yes.
The King's Hand should never abandon
the king, especially in time of war.
You're not abandoning me.
You're obeying a command.
A boy with a scroll could deliver
this message.
And if Jon Snow refuses the boy
with the scroll, what does the boy say?
I didn't name you Hand for your expertise
in military matters.
Ride for Castle Black.
Don't come back empty-handed.
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse
and Princess Shireen could accompany me.
My family stays with me.
At least let me take Shireen.
-A siege is no place for a little girl.
-My family stays with me.
Are you all right?
What's this one now?
The Dance of Dragons, A True Telling
by Grand Maester Munkun.
Now that sounds like a proper story.
Ser Byron Swann wanted to kill
the dragon Vhagar.
He polished his shield for a week
so that it was like a mirror.
And he crouched behind it
and crept forward,
hoping the dragon would only see
its own reflection.
But the dragon saw a dumb man holding
a mirrored shield.
And burnt him to a crisp.
Thus ending the dragon-slaying career
of Ser Byron Swann.
I made you something, Princess.
-Do you like it?
-He's beautiful.
-Thank you.
-You're very welcome.
Will you make me a doe, too?
So that he can have company?
Course I will.
But why am I getting a present?
Because you deserve it.
My son was always on me,
trying to teach me to read.
Gods, I was stubborn about it.
Made it this far without reading.
Seemed to me I could make it to the grave.
Wish I'd listened to him.
This is my own poor way
of saying thank you.
For teaching me to be a grown-up.
I'll be gone for a few days, Princess.
I want to hear all aboutThe Dance
of Dragonswhen I'm back.
You'll read it yourself.
Prince Doran. Forgive us.
We started without you.
Please, sit.
Princess Myrcella.
-Uncle.
-What a lovely dress.
-You don't like it?
-You must be cold.
Not at all. The Dornish climate agrees
with me.
Prince Trystane.
How's your jaw?
-A fleabite.
-What are you doing in Dorne?
Looking after the safety of my niece,
the Princess Myrcella.
And rather than send a raven or speak
to me directly,
you decided to enter my country in secret
-and abduct our guest by force?
-We received a threatening message.
The princess's necklace in the jaws
of a viper.
That necklace was stolen from my room.
Excellent. A last meal
before the beheading?
Oh, I can't behead you.
Many in Dorne want war.
But I've seen war.
I've seen the bodies piled
on the battlefields.
I've seen the orphans starving
in the cities.
I don't want to lead my people
into that hell.
No, you want to break bread
with the Lannisters.
And that is precisely what we are doing.
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
King of the Andals and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms.
King Tommen insists on his sister's return
to the capital?
I'm afraid he does.
I cannot disobey my king's command.
She will return with you
to King's Landing.
And my son Prince Trystane
will accompany you both.
If the alliance between the Iron Throne
and Dorne is to continue,
their engagement must stand.
I accept.
One more thing. My brother was named
to the small council before his death.
Your father understood the importance
of keeping Dorne in the fold.
With Oberyn gone, Trystane will take
his place on the small council.
-You have my word.
-The word of a kingslayer.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
You are mother to four of my nieces,
girls I love very much.
For their sake, I hope you live a long
and happy life.
Speak to me that way again, and you won't.
May I inquire as to the fate
of my man Bronn?
Tell me, Ser Jaime, in King's Landing,
how do they punish a commoner
who strikes a prince?
He said it was just a fleabite.
The fault is mine.
Bronn is merely a soldier
following my orders.
If anyone should be punished, it's me.
Prince Trystane must learn judgment
if he is to rule one day.
I'll let him decide.
I have learned the value of mercy
from my father.
-I'll set your man free.
-You're a good man.
On one condition.
Why do we play? I'm better than you.
I'll always be better than you.
Have I ever missed once?
I don't think I have. I can't recall.
You must love humiliation. Or pain.
Which do you love most, humiliation
or pain?
That one hurt, didn't it?
You going to cry?
Give up, little sister.
-You're going to miss.
-Oh, I never miss.
You will. You're thinking too much.
Now you're nervous. What if she's right?
-Luck.
-Now it's my turn.
You're too slow.
You've always been too slow.
Am I gonna be happy at the end
of this walk?
You'll find out very soon.
Say it one more time, handsome. Who am I?
The most beautiful woman in the world.
-And that's the truth.
-Slut.
Prince Doran, Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
I didn't realize there were knights
of the Blackwater.
Only the one.
I believe you've already met
Prince Trystane.
Prince.
-Sorry about the other day.
-Prince Trystane here is a man of mercy.
He's agreed to grant you your freedom.
I'm glad to hear it.
-Pie looks good.
-There was one condition.
Perhaps some soup instead.
Oysters, clams, and cockles!
-Oysters, clams, and cock--
-How much for your little clam?
Oysters, clams, and cockles!
Come on.
Some oysters, girl!
I'm talking to you.
Is...
-Girl!
-Tie her up!
Are you deaf? Girl!
Girl!
My lord.
Lord Tyrell.
On behalf of the Iron Bank,
may I be the first to welcome you
to the Free City of Braavos.
-I hope your journey was trouble-free.
-A bit of chop the last few days.
Nothing too awful.
Good to see the old chap still guarding
the harbor.
And how goes the harvest in the Reach?
Oh, the vintners say this might be
the best year for red grapes
in half a century.
If we come
to a satisfactory arrangement,
I'll be sure to send a cask
of the Arbor's finest your way.
I'm afraid I don't partake.
Some consider usury distasteful,
dishonorable.
Pure nonsense, of course.
I'm glad we see eye to eye on this matter.
Did you know that at one point
Maegor the Third
tried to outlaw it in the Seven Kingdoms?
Wanted to arrest anyone
caught charging interest
-and cut off both their hands.
-Most unfortunate for the glovers.
If a man charges no interest on a loan,
then he has nothing to gain
and everything to lose,
so why chance it?
Whereas the promise of reward makes
a man willing to gamble.
We are not gamblers here at the Iron Bank,
Lord Tyrell.
You are the world's best gamblers.
And all those bets you won built this.
We should celebrate.
I'm afraid I still have a good deal
of work to do.
Oh, nonsense. Work's over. Do you sing?
-I don't have that gift.
-Oh, it's not a gift.
It's a skill. Anyone can learn it.
So give me a kiss by the Long Canal
And give me two kisses in Salty Town
For we're going to die tomorrow
The bareheaded beggar
The king with his crown
Thought that old shit
would never stop singing.
Wasn't bad, though.
The Tyrells can all rot in hell.
Treasonous cunts.
They were going to make
that boy-fucker Renly king.
This is the place, lads.
The sleekest little minks in Braavos.
-You buying?
-Oh, I'm buying.
But I never was good at sharing.
-Sell your fish somewhere else.
-Let her in, Brusco. I'm hungry.
Come here, sweetness.
They say oysters get the juices flowing.
We'll take half a dozen.
Three coppers.
Here's a silver because the lady
likes you.
Too old.
Brea.
I have just the one. Anara.
Our most expensive girl.
But well worth it, I assure you.
Too old.
-Do you have what I want or not?
-Of course.
Of course.
These fresh?
Come on, the lads are hungry.
Nothing better for your cockstand
than fresh oysters.
-Here. Thank you.
-I'll have one.
Any vinegar?
Who let this girl in? Shoo! Shoo!
Good.
I'll tell you when we're done.
You'll have a fresh one for me tomorrow?
Of course.
I'll have you whipped, girl. Go, go on.
Out, out, go.
Valar morghulis.
And?
-The thin man wasn't hungry today.
-Perhaps that is why a man is thin.
-Tomorrow.
A girl has work to do.
Your rebellion is over.
You can swear your allegiance
to me now
or you can die.
I believe in second chances.
I don't believe in third chances.
You write like a seven-year-old.
Your maester kindly agreed to copy it
over for me.
He didn't try to make you pay?
Maybe he's changed.
The queen will be thrilled to know
you're bringing her daughter home.
She will.
-You love her very much, don't you?
-Of course, she's my niece.
I wasn't talking about her.
You think I disapprove?
Why?
Because people disapprove of that sort
of thing where you are from?
They disapproved of Oberyn and me
where you are from.
Here
no one blinked an eye.
A 100 years ago, no one would have blinked
an eye at you…
if you'd been named Targaryen.
It's always changing, who we're supposed
to love and who we're not.
The only thing that stays the same
is that we want who we want.
I know your daughter had no part
in the terrible thing
that happened to the man I love.
Perhaps even you are innocent of that.
Father.
Aren't you cold?
No. What are you reading?
-TheDance of Dragons.
-What's it about?
It's the story of the fight
between Rhaenyra Targaryen
and her half-brother Aegon for control
over the Seven Kingdoms.
Both of them thought they belonged
on the Iron Throne.
When people started declaring for one
of them or the other,
their fight divided the kingdoms in two.
Brothers fought brothers,
dragons fought dragons.
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
And it was a disaster
for the Targaryens as well.
They never truly recovered.
The Dance of Dragons.
Why is that a dance?
It's just what they call it.
-Doesn't make much sense.
-I think it's poetic.
If you had to choose
between Rhaenyra and Aegon
-who would you have chosen?
-I wouldn't have chosen either.
It's all the choosing sides
that made everything so horrible.
Sometimes a person has to choose.
Sometimes the world forces his hand.
If a man knows what he is...
and remains true to himself...
the choice is no choice at all.
He must fulfill his destiny...
and become who he is meant to be.
However much he may hate it.
It's all right, Father.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
It doesn't matter. I want to help you.
Is there any way I can help?
-Yes, there is.
-Good. I want to.
I'm the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
And I'm your daughter.
Forgive me.
Where's my father?
I want to see my father.
It will all be over soon, Princess.
No. No.
Where's my father?
No, you can't do this.
Father, where are you?
Please, let me see my father.
Don't let her do this.
Please let go!
Let me see my father! Where are you?
Please!
-It's what the Lord wants.
-No.
-Please! Let go! No!
-It's a good thing.
-A great thing.
-Stop. Stop!
-Please!
-Hear us now, my lord.
-You can't do this!
-For you, we offer up this girl...
Please!
...that you may cleanse her
with your fire
and that its light may lead our way.
Please! No, please let me see my father.
If we don't act, we'll all starve here.
All of us.
-But if we make this sacrifice
-Accept this token of our faith, my lord,
and lead us from the darkness.
-Lord of Light, show us the way.
-Mother! Mother, please!
Mother, please! Mother!
-Mother!
-We can't.
There's no other way.
She has king's blood.
-Please don't do this!
-Lord of Light, protect us.
Please! Father, please!
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
Father please! Father!
Father, don't do this! Please!
Mother, no! Please! Please, help!
Don't do this!
Please, Father! Mother, help!
-No.
-No, please! Don't do this!
Don't do this, please, Mother!
Please, Mother! Mother, help!
Mother, help! Help!
Please don't do this, Mother! Please!
Please, Mother! Please!
Please! No! Please! No!
No!
Where have you been?
Just making sure everything is in order.
They're waiting for you.
Clap your hands.
That one, the smaller man. No question,
that's where you should put your money.
-The smaller man it is.
-I'm not putting my money anywhere.
Kings and queens never bet on the games.
Perhaps you should go find someone
who does.
People used to bet against me
when I fought in the pits.
He would have bet against me.
Common novice mistake.
I've spent much of my life in this arena.
And in my experience, large men do triumph
over smaller men far more often than not.
Has your experience ever involved
any actual fighting?
You yourself?
Have you ever tried to kill another man
who was trying to kill you?
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
the crowd saw me,
all skin and bone back then,
then they saw a pile of angry muscles
ready to murder me.
They couldn't get their money out
fast enough.
But the pile of angry muscles
never had any muscles here
or...
here. And the big men were always too slow
to stop my dagger from going
where their muscles weren't.
Yes, whenever I saw a beast like
that one standing across from me
making his beast faces,
I knew I could rest easy.
You don't approve?
There's always been more than enough death
in the world for my taste.
I can do without it in my leisure time.
Fair enough.
Yet it's an unpleasant question,
but what great thing has ever been
accomplished without killing or cruelty?
It's easy to confuse what is
with what ought to be,
especially when what is has worked out
in your favor.
I'm not talking about myself.
I'm talking about the necessary conditions
for greatness.
That is greatness?
That is a vital part of the great city
of Meereen,
which existed long before you or I
and will remain standing long
after we have returned to the dirt.
My father would have liked you.
One day your great city will return
to the dirt as well.
-At your command?
-If need be.
And how many people will die to make
this happen?
If it comes to that, they will have died
for a good reason.
Those men think they're dying
Someone else's reason.
So, your reasons are true
and theirs are false?
They don't know their own minds,
but you do?
Well said. You're an eloquent man.
Doesn't mean you're wrong.
In my experience, eloquent men are right
every bit as often as imbeciles.
-Your Grace--
-Shut your mouth.
-You can end this.
-She cannot.
You can.
Protect your queen!
Go!
Your Grace! Your Grace! Come with me.
I know a way out.
I know a way--
Stay close.
This way.
The other side. Follow me.
Protect your queen!
Drogon!
Valahd.