Man: We're going to braavos!
In the old times,
whenever braavos stood in danger,
the titan would step with fire in his eyes.
He'd Wade into the sea
and smash the enemies.
He's just a statue.
Don't be afraid. He's
announcing our arrival.
I'm not afraid.
The house of black and white.
This is where you'll find the man you seek.
Here I leave you.
Thank you for bringing me.
Any man of braavos
would have done the same.
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
Hello.
Valar morghulis.
Jaqen h'ghar gave me this.
No one here by that name.
Please.
I crossed the narrow sea.
I have nowhere else to go.
You have everywhere else to go.
But wait...
Cersei.
Walder frey.
The mountain.
Meryn trant.
Cersei.
Walder frey.
The mountain.
Meryn trant.
Cersei. Walder frey.
The mountain.
Meryn trant.
Cersei.
Walder frey.
The mountain.
Meryn trant.
Cersei.
Walder frey.
The mountain.
Meryn trant.
Must be good food if it's crowded.
Ale?
Before we left,
a maester gave you a raven scroll.
You are becoming an observant young lady.
My mother used to say,
"dark wings, dark words."
An old saying. Inaccurate in this case.
Excuse me.
Sansa: So, it was good news?
My marriage proposal has been accepted.
I thought you still mourned
the death of my beloved aunt lysa.
Ale?
Sansa: I'll have some.
My lady.
What is it?
Podrick: Sansa stark. Don't look.
You sure?
She's dyed her hair, but it's her.
She's sitting with petyr baelish.
Littlefinger?
A bunch of knights with him.
A bunch? What's a bunch, podrick? Six? 20?
Ten, I think. Too many.
My lady, I don't think this is the right...
- Ready the horses.
- We only have one horse.
Find more.
Littlefinger: Do you like the taste?
I don't see what all the fuss is about.
Why do men love it so much?
It gives some men courage.
Does it give you courage?
Guard: That's far enough.
Lord baelish, lady sansa.
My name is brienne of tarth.
We've met with renly Baratheon.
What did he say about you?
He said
your onalty came free of charge.
Someone appears to have
paid quite a bit for it since then.
Lady sansa,
before your mother's death,
I was her sworn sword.
I gave my word
I would find you and protect you.
I will shield your back
and keep your counsel
and give my life for yours if need be.
I swear it by the old gods and the new.
Please, lady brienne,
no need for such formality.
You were catelyn stark's sworn sword?
- I was.
- Strange.
I knew cat from the time we were children.
She never mentioned you.
It was after renly's murder.
Ah. Yes.
You were accused of killing him.
- I tried to save him.
- But you were accused.
By men who didn't see what happened.
And what did happen?
He was murdered by a shadow.
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
A shadow?
With the face...
Littlefinger: This woman
swore to protect renly.
She failed.
She swore to protect
your mother. She failed.
Why would I want somebody
with your history of failure
guarding lady sansa?
Why should you have any say in her affairs?
Because I am her uncle.
I married her aunt lysa
shortly before my beloved's untimely death.
We're family now, and you are an outsider.
Forgive me, lady brienne,
but experience has made me
wary of outsiders.
Lady sansa, if we can have a word alone...
Please, my lady. If I could explain...
I saw you at Joffrey's wedding
bowing to the king.
Neither of us wanted to be there.
Sometimes we don't have a choice.
And sometimes we do.
You should leave.
We don't want our new friend
wandering the countryside alone.
The roads in these parts aren't safe.
Why don't you stay?
The man asked you to stay...
Hyahl hyahl
guard: After her!
Brienne1yah! Hah! Podrick: Oh!
Podrick: Stop!
Guard 1: Pm take him!
Podrick!
Guard 2: Hold on to her!
Take her!
Guard 3: Keep moving!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
That's a good boy. Come on. Come on.
No, no, no, stop!
I guess that means you're unarmed.
Brienne: Down, podrick! Down!
Podrick.
Yes, my lady?
You can stand now.
Yes, my lady.
Sansa stark?
Wary of strangers, as she should be.
I saw her riding on the east road
with littlefinger.
We'll follow them.
My lady,
if both stark girls refused your service,
maybe you're released from your vow.
I swore to their mother
I would protect those girls.
But if they don't want your protection...
Do you think she's safe with littlefinger?
No, my lady.
Get your horse.
A summons from the queen.
Cersei: There are only
two like it in the world.
The one I'm wearing,
the one I gave to myrcella.
- It's a threat.
- Of course it's a threat.
Our daughter's alone in dorne
surrounded by people who hate our family.
"It's a threat."
No note?
They blame us for the death
of oberyn and his sister
and every other tragedy
that's befallen their cursed country.
I will burn their cities to the ground
if they touch her.
- Softer.
- What?
Not so loud.
Our daughter's in danger
and you're worried I'm speaking too loudly?
The world can't know she's our daughter.
Then don't call her your daughter.
You've never been a father to her.
If I was a father to any of my children,
they'd be stoned in the street.
And what has your caution brought?
Our eldest child murdered
at his own wedding.
Our only daughter shipped off to dorne.
Our baby boy set to marry
that smirking whore from highgarden.
I'm going to make things better.
You've never made anything better.
I'm going to dome
and I'm bringing our daughter home.
You can't just ask prince doran
to give her back.
She's promised to his son.
I'm not going to ask him anything.
You go down there with an army,
it's an act of war.
No army.
Do you know where they're keeping her?
- Oberyn mentioned the water gardens.
- I'll find her.
Is there anything else, your grace?
You're going to dorne?
A one-handed man, alone.
I never said I was going alone.
No sunflowers. I don't like yellow.
Roses are very nice. Definitely roses.
And music. I adore music.
But no flutes. I hate flutes.
We can have a harp if
you like, but no flutes.
Then there's the food.
Food is the most important thing.
Don't you agree?
We're going to need pigeon pies.
That's what they eat in
the capital, don't they?
Don't they?
Don't who?
People eat pigeon pie in the capital.
They certainly do, my dear.
It's a fine place, isn't it?
A fine place.
I never thought I'd end up
settling down in a place like this.
You won't.
Pardon?
We won't get to live at stokeworth.
When mother dies, my sister gets the castle
because she's older.
She hates me.
She calls me mean names,
and sometimes, even still,
she pulls my hair when
mother's not looking.
You know what I think?
I think you're a good person.
And your sister is a mean person.
She is.
I've been all over the world,
and if there's one thing I've learned,
it's that meanness comes around.
People like your sister,
they always get
what's coming to them eventually.
One way or another.
Who's that?
Jaime fucking Lannister.
- Ser Jaime.
- Ser bronn of the Blackwater.
I was very sorry to hear about your father.
Thank you.
This is my betrothed, lollys.
A pleasure.
Run along, love.
Beautiful young bride you've chosen.
When were you planning on getting married?
- Just get on with it.
- On with what?
What you're here for.
There's no way this little visit could
possibly mean anything good for me.
It's very good for you.
- Lollys will be marrying ser Willis bracken.
- Mmm.
We made a deal, your sister and I.
I would have advised against that.
How is this good for me?
'Cause you're going to come with me
and help me with something important.
And when we return,
I'm going to give you a much better girl
and a much better castle.
Return from where?
As far south as south goes.
Trystane: My future queen.
You are beautiful.
The prince does not wish to be disturbed.
Remove yourself from my path or I'll take
that long ax and I'll shove it up your...
Doran: Captain.
Let her pass.
Your brother was murdered,
and you sit here in the water gardens,
staring at the sky and doing nothing.
Oberyn was slain during a trial by combat.
By law, that is not murder.
- Your brother.
- You don't have to remind me.
He was my brother
long before he was anything to you.
What will you do about his death?
I will Bury him. I will mourn for him.
And then?
You would have me go to war?
The whole country would have you go to war.
Then we are lucky
the whole country does not decide.
The sand snakes are with me.
They have the love of their people.
They will avenge their father while
you sit here in your chair doing nothing.
Oberyn is dead,
and this Lannister girl
skips about the water gardens,
eating our food, breathing our air.
How many of your brothers and sisters
do they have to kill?
Let me have her.
Let me send her to
Cersei one finger at a time.
I loved my brother.
And you made him very happy.
For that, you will always
have a place in my heart.
But we do not mutilate little girls
for vengeance.
Not here.
Not while I rule.
And how long will that be?
Daario: The unsullied are too conspicuous.
Anyone can see you coming from a mile off.
Of course you haven't found
any sons of the harpy.
You haven't, have you?
My second sons, on the other hand,
they drink, whore,
fight in the streets,
they blend in.
They overhear things in taverns,
follow people to nice, quiet alleys,
break a few fingers,
overhear a few more things.
Before you know it...
No one here.
We go.
In a hurry? You're afraid?
Unsullied fear nothing.
Right.
That's your problem.
You understood fear once long ago,
but you've forgotten what it means.
Someone who's forgotten fear
has forgotten how to hide.
Fear is useful that way.
Sons of the harpy,
they want to put a collar back on my neck.
On all of our necks.
Please, your grace, you must kill him.
It would send a message.
I think you should exercise restraint,
your grace.
For one thing,
he may have valuable information.
The son of the harpy
has no more valuable information.
How do you know that?
Because I questioned him.
Hizdahr: And the information you did get,
he is young and poor.
He is born free.
Why should he want to bring back slavery?
What did it do for him?
Perhaps the only thing that gave him pride
was knowing that
there was someone lower than he was.
They pay him.
Great families afraid to do a thing.
They pay poor men to do it for them.
- And how do you know this?
- Everyone know this.
I don't know it,
and I'm the head of a great family.
Barristan: We do not know
what this man did or didn't do.
Give him a trial at least. A fair trial.
Show all the citizens of meereen
that you're better than
those who would depose you.
Teach them a better way.
I do not know the place
from where old ser comes.
Things maybe are different there, I hope.
But here in meereen,
before Daenerys stormborn, they own us.
So we learn much about them,
or we do not live long.
They teach me what they are.
Mercy, fair trial, these
mean nothing to them.
All they understand is blood.
Daenerys: Thank you all for your counsel.
Your grace, a word, please, I beg you.
- About what?
- About your father.
- About the mad king.
- The mad king?
You're here to remind
me of my enemies' lies?
Consider me reminded.
Your grace,
I served in his kingsguard.
I was at his side from the first.
Your enemies did not lie.
Go on.
When the people Rose in revolt against him,
your father set their
towns and castles aflame.
He murdered sons in front of their fathers.
He burned men alive with wildfire
and laughed as they screamed.
And his efforts to stamp out dissent
led to rebellion
that killed every Targaryen except two.
I'm not my father.
No, your grace. Thank the gods.
But the mad king gave his enemies
the justice he thought they deserved.
And each time,
it made him feel powerful and right.
Until the very end.
I will not have the son of the harpy
executed without a fair trial.
Your grace.
There's a bug.
Yes, best be careful.
You might accidentally
consume some solid food.
When I agreed to come with you,
did I misrepresent my intentions?
Besides,
what else is there for me to do
inside this fucking box?
You don't like it?
- I want to take a walk.
- You can't.
Cersei has offered a lordship
to the man who brings her your head.
She ought to offer her cunt.
Best part of her for the best part of me.
Well, I suppose a box
is as good a place for me as anywhere.
Are we really going to
spend the entire road to volantis
talking about the futility of everything?
You're right. No point.
The road to volantis?
You said we were going to meereen.
What's in volantis?
The road to meereen.
And what do you hope to find
at the end of the road to meereen?
I told you. A ruler.
We've already got a ruler.
Everywhere has already got a ruler.
Every pile of shit on the side of every
road has someone's banner hanging from it.
You were quite good, you know, at ruling.
During your brief tenure as hand.
I didn't rule. I was a servant.
Still, a man of talent.
Managed to kill a lot of people.
Yes, but you showed great promise
in other areas as well.
She wanted me to leave king's landing.
She begged me.
I wouldn't go.
'Cause I liked it.
Power.
Even as a servant.
People follow leaders.
And they will never follow us.
They find us repulsive.
I find us repulsive.
And we find them repulsive,
which is why we surround ourselves
with large, comfortable boxes
to keep them away.
And yet,
no matter what we do,
people like you and me
are never really satisfied inside the box.
Not for long.
You're right.
- Let's go for a walk.
- No.
How many dwarves are there in the world?
Is Cersei going to kill them all?
Not him.
Are you trying to deceive your queen?
Shall I throw them in a cell, your grace?
That won't be necessary, ser meryn.
I don't want to dissuade the other hunters.
Mistakes will be made.
- Thank you, your grace.
- Take the head.
- Pardon me, your grace.
I would take it, if you don't mind.
It could prove useful for my work.
Very good.
Over there will be fine.
You heard the man. Over there.
You're the hand of the king?
No, unde.
Clearly it would not be appropriate
for a woman to assume that role.
I'm merely advising my son
until he comes of age
and chooses a hand for himself.
Your grace,
I would be willing to serve provisionally
as the king's hand
until he becomes old enough...
You're a good man, lord Tyrell,
but I don't imagine you'll have the time.
In addition to being master of ships,
the king has appointed you master of coin.
Oh, your grace.
He called your experience and wisdom
in financial matters unparalleled.
He said he would be honored to have you
represent the crown's interests in the same.
The honor is all mine, your grace.
Your grace, in the past
on several occasions,
a grand maester has served
as the king's hand.
The king has named beurn
the new master of whisperers.
Your grace, him? This man?
This embarrassment to the citadel?
Your grace, what qualifications
can he possibly have for this post?
The qualification of
loyalty, grand maester.
That's far more than the eunuch ever had.
Far more than many ever have.
I must say, I cannot see...
Uncle kevan, in light of your position
as commander of the Lannister armies,
it would please the king
if you would serve as his master of war.
No man living better deserves the title.
That is kind of you to say.
I would like to hear it
from the king himself.
The king is very busy at this moment.
He should be here
learning what it means to rule.
He is learning.
On this occasion, in his capacity as ruler,
he's asked me to speak on his behalf.
I returned to the capital
to pay my respects to my brother.
And to you. And to serve the king.
I did not return to serve as your puppet.
To watch you stack the small council
with sycophants.
Sending your own brother away
so he wouldn't be...
My brother has left the capital to
lead a sensitive diplomatic mission.
What mission?
That is not your concern as master of war.
I do not recognize your authority
to dictate what is and is not my concern.
You are the queen mother, nothing more.
You would abandon your king
in his time of need?
If he wants to send for me,
I will be waiting for him.
At casterly rock.
Shireen: Come on, you know this one.
It looks like an animal.
Snake.
Snake.s.
- It's an s.
- Right, very good.
Huh!
Did you know that the youngest
lord commander in history, osric stark,
was elected at the age of 10?
I know s.
You'll learn, I promise.
I taught ser davos, and old people
are terrible at learning new things.
Well, you're a wonderful teacher.
Very patient.
I only said that the more time
that you spend practicing,
the faster you'll be able to read.
That's all right. We're doing just fine.
I'm sure you and ostrich stark
have a lot to talk about.
How old were you
when you learned how to read?
- Three.
- Three?
Who taught you, your mother?
No, old maester cressen did.
I had a lot of time to practice.
My mother kept me inside because...
What do you call it in the south,
what happened to your face?
Greyscale.
What do you call it north of the wall?
I don't know.
But two of my sisters had it.
They both died.
How did they cure you?
I don't remember. I was a baby.
Lots of people came and tried, I think.
Whatever they did, it went away.
What happened to your sisters?
My father made them move out of the keep
into the hut outside.
None of us were allowed to go near them.
But we heard them, especially at night.
They started to sound not like themselves.
Did you ever see them?
Only once at the end.
They were covered with it.
Their faces, their arms.
They acted like animals.
My father had to drag them
out to the woods on a rope.
What did he do with them in the woods?
- Mother.
- Leave us.
Your grace.
You need to stay away from that girl.
- Why?
- She's a wildling.
Her name is gilly. She's nice.
I'm teaching her to read.
She's a wildling.
Your father defeated her people.
He executed their king for treason.
They could strike at
him by striking at you.
Gilly wouldn't do that.
You have no idea what people will do.
All your books and you still don't know.
Stannis: I ordered mance rayder
burned at the stake.
You prevented that order
from being carried out.
You showed mercy to mance rayder.
A king's word is law.
Perhaps you should ask ser davos
how much mercy I show to lawbreakers.
Show too much kindness,
people won't fear you.
If they don't fear you,
they don't follow you.
With respect, your grace,
the free folk will never follow you
no matter what you do.
You're the man who burned their king alive.
Who, then?
You?
Only one of their own.
Do you know this wretched girl,
lyanna mormont?
The lord commander's niece.
Lady of bear island and a child of 10.
I asked her to commit her house
to my cause. That's her response.
Jon: "Bear island knows no king
but the king in the north,
"whose name is stark."
That amuses you?
I apologize, your grace.
Northerners can be
a bit like the free folk.
Loyal to their own.
Stannis: I know.
My brother, Robert, went on often and loudly
about how difficult it was to control them.
Even with your father's help.
Tonight, the night's watch
elects a new lord commander.
Ser alliser Thorne is going to win.
- Most likely.
- Unpleasant man.
He thinks you're a traitor.
What's your life going to be like here
at the wall with Thorne in command?
Unpleasant, I expect.
Your bravery made him look weak.
He'll punish you for it.
I don't punish men for bravery.
I reward them.
I don't doubt it, your grace.
But I'm a brother of the night's watch.
I pledged them my life, my honor, my sword.
I don't know what I have left to give you.
You can give me the north.
I can't.
Even if I wanted to, I'm a bastard, a snow.
Kneel before me. Lay your sword at my feet.
Pledge me your service
and you'll rise again as Jon stark,
lord of winterfell.
He'll make you a stark
with the stroke of a pen?
It's the first thing I
ever remember wanting.
I'd daydream that my father
would ask the king
and just like that, I would never be
the bastard of winterfell again.
You deserve this. You do.
I couldn't be happier for you.
I'm going to refuse him.
But you'd be lord of winterfell.
I swore a vow to the night's watch.
If I don't take my own word seriously,
what sort of lord of winterfell would I be?
Alliser: Crowded. You'd think
we were serving venison stew.
Does anyone wish to speak for candidates
before we cast our tokens
for the 998th lord commander
of the night's watch?
Seralliser Thorne is not just a knight,
he's a man of true nobility.
He was acting commander
when the wall came under attack
and led us to victory
against the wildlings.
Black brothers: Hear, hear.
Janos: He's a veteran of 100 battles
and has been a defender of the watch
and the wall almost all of his life.
Black brother: Aye.
He's the only true choice.
Black brother: Yes!
Ser denys mallisterjoined
the watch as a boy
and has served loyally,
longer than any other ranger.
Through 10 winters he served.
As commander of the shadow tower,
he kept the wildlings away.
We could do no better.
Aemon: If there is no one else,
we will begin the voting.
The triangular tokens
count for ser alliser Thorne.
The square tokens for ser denys mallister.
- Each brother will...
- Maester aemon.
Aemon: Samwell tarly. Go on.
Janos: Sam the slayer.
Another wildling lover
just like his friend Jon snow.
How's your lady love, slayer?
Her name is gilly.
Brother slynt knows her quite well.
They cowered together in the larder
during the battle for the wall.
Lies!
A wildling girl, a baby, and lord janos.
I found him there after the battle was over
in a puddle of his own making.
Whilst lord janos was hiding
with the women and children,
Jon snow was leading.
Ser alliser fought bravely, it is true.
And when he was wounded,
it was Jon who saved us.
He took charge of the wall's defense.
He killed the magnar of the thenns.
He went north to deal with mance rayder
knowing it almost certainly
meant his own death.
Before that,
he led the mission to
avenge lord commander mormont.
Mormont himself chose
Jon to be his steward.
He saw something in Jon
and now we've all seen it, too.
He may be young,
but he's the commander we turned to
when the night was darkest.
I can't argue with any of that.
But who does Jon snow want to command?
Night's watch,
or the wildlings?
Everyone knows he loved a wildling girl,
he spoke with mance rayder many times.
What would have happened in that tent
between those two old friends
if Stannis' army hadn't come along?
We all saw him put the king-beyond-the-wall
out of his misery.
Do you want to choose a man
who has fought the wildlings all his life,
or a man who makes love to them?
It is time.
It appears to be a tie, maester.
Jon snow!
Jon snow! Jon snow! Jon snow!
You. You.
What have you got there?
- I said...
- Turn around and go.
Turn around and go.
That's a nice little sword.
Worth 100 pigeons, a sword like that.
Nothing's worth anything to dead men.
Thug: Come on. Quickly, go! Go!
Who are you?
Why were they scared of you?
You lost this.
You said there was no jaqen h'ghar here.
There isn't.
A man is not jaqen h'ghar.
Arya: Well, who are you, then?
No one.
And that is who a girl must become.
She doesn't belong here.
And no matter how many of you traitors
call her "mhysa",
she will never be your mother.
Daenerys: Why?
For you, mhysa.
You wanted the harpy dead,
but your hands were tied.
I set you free, as you did all of us.
He was our prisoner, awaiting trial.
You had no right.
He would rather rip your city apart
than see slaves lifted from the dirt.
There are no more slaves.
There are no more masters.
Then who lives in the pyramids?
Who wears gold masks
and murders your children?
When grey worm came to us,
I was the first to take
up the knife for you.
I remember the look on my father's face
as I struck down his master,
who had traded his infant son for a dog.
My father died in the fighting.
If we allow the sons of the harpy
to return us to chains,
he never lived.
The harpy's life was not yours to take.
Once, the masters were the law-
and now you are the law.
The law is the law.
Take him.
Crowd: Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa!
She should have cut off the traitor's head
in the great pyramid and been done with it.
Which is what I keep
telling her to do to you.
Crowd: Mhysa! Mhysa!
You opened your gates to me
because I promised you freedom and justice.
One cannot exist without the other.
-Brother! Brother!
Mhysa, please!
Forgive me.
A citizen of meereen was awaiting
trial and this man murdered him.
The punishment is death.
-Mercy, mercy
Mhysa.
Mhysa!
I'll stand guard outside your door tonight,
your grace.
We all guard tonight.
Leave me.
Drogon.