( theme music playing )
( water dripping )
( voices whispering )
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
I've been sweeping
this floor for days.
Good.
I didn't come here
to sweep floors.
No?
Why come, then?
You said I could be
your apprentice.
You said you'd teach me
how to be a Faceless Man.
A man teaches a girl.
Valar dohaeris.
All men must serve.
Faceless Men
most of all.
I want to serve.
A girl wants
to serve herself.
Here we serve
the Many-Faced God.
To serve well,
a girl must become
no one.
Which one's
the Many-Faced God?
I see the Stranger.
I see the Drowned God.
I see the weirwood face.
There is only one god.
A girl knows his name.
And all men know his gift.
Where are they
taking him?
- ( bells tolling )
- ( people shouting )
( people shouting )
Queen Margaery!
Man:
- I am his and he is mine.
- I am hers and she is mine.
Both:
From this day
until the end of my days.
( breathing heavily )
Did I hurt you?
No.
You were lovely.
- It all happened so fast.
- Yes. ( chuckles )
I was scared
maybe I hurt you.
- It sounded like--
- No, no, no.
You're very sweet.
The sweetest king
who ever lived.
This is all I want
to do all day,
every day,
for the rest of my life.
( laughs )
Wouldn't that
be glorious?
Shouldn't we rest
a little while?
Just to catch our breath?
There's no rush, is there?
Of course not.
Are you hungry?
Should I have them
bring you some cake
or pomegranate juice?
No, I'm fine.
I just want you
all to myself.
I want to know everything
there is to know
about King Tommen,
First of His Name.
King Tommen.
Still sounds
strange to me.
Does Queen Margaery
sound strange to you?
So strange.
- Husband.
- Wife.
( laughs )
Sometimes it feels odd.
I'm the king,
I've married the most
beautiful woman
in the world,
and it's all because
my brother died.
I understand.
But it's not your fault.
You know that, don't you?
You mustn't
feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
That's what's odd.
Do you like to sail?
I love to sail.
I do, too.
I think we're going
to be very happy,
you and I.
I do, too.
( kisses )
Living in a tower
so high it touches
the clouds.
Of course, my grandmother
couldn't wait to go home.
The capital's not
for everyone, I suppose.
Does your mother
like it here?
I don't think so.
She told me
never to trust anyone
in King's Landing.
It's so wonderful to have
her watching over you.
A lioness
guarding her cub.
Well, but I'm a man now.
You are.
And the king.
But you'll always be
her baby boy.
- I suppose.
- I adore her.
She's always been
so generous with me,
so kind.
And the horrors
she's had to endure--
losing her husband,
her eldest child,
and her father.
It's no wonder
she's so protective
of you.
She'll never let you
out of her sight.
Cersei:
You look
very much in love.
The first days of marriage
are often so blissful.
She's certainly
very pretty, isn't she?
Like a doll.
She smiles quite a lot.
Do you think
she's intelligent?
I can't quite tell.
Not that it matters.
Do you ever miss
Casterly Rock?
There's nothing for me
in Casterly Rock.
That's where
you grew up.
You always told me
that you liked the people
there better.
You said that King's Landing
smelled of horse dung
and sour milk.
( chuckles )
Why are we speaking
of Casterly Rock?
The way that
you talked about it,
I always thought
that you missed it,
that you--
that it was
your real home.
This is my real home now,
where my family lives.
I want you
to be happy, Mother.
I know that.
I know you do.
My sweet boy.
But wouldn't
you be happier
in Casterly Rock?
Margaery:
I said, "Darling,
surely four times is enough."
- ( women giggling )
- "Are you trying to set
a new record?"
He said,
"Well, what is the record?
I'm sure we can break it."
( laughing )
Mother.
Welcome.
Don't you look lovely?
Marriage agrees with you.
Can we bring you
anything to eat or drink?
I wish we had
some wine for you.
It's a bit early
in the day for us.
No, no,
I can't stay.
I just wanted
to let you know
if there's ever anything
I can do for you...
You are very sweet.
Tommen seems
quite taken with
his new queen.
I absolutely adore him.
You raised
a gallant young man.
I'm forever grateful.
Good.
I'm glad to hear
you're happy.
Ecstatic.
I really am.
Exhausted,
to be honest.
But what could I expect?
He is half lion, half stag.
( women laugh )
I'll leave you
to it, then.
Oh, forgive me.
I haven't been
at court for long.
I get so confused.
What's the proper way
to address you now?
Queen Mother
or Dowager Queen?
There's no need
for such formalities.
In any event, judging from
the king's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother will be
a Queen Grandmother soon.
Won't that be
a lovely day?
Can you imagine
the celebrations?
They'll ring the bells
all day and night.
Remember...
anything you need.
( women giggle )
( laughing )
( laughter echoing )
( horse neighs )
( men shouting )
( animals squawking )
( flies buzzing )
( caws )
Roose:
We can't hold the North
with terror alone.
Ramsay: You can't hold
the North if you let these
lesser lords insult us.
Roose: I sent you there
to collect taxes,
not bodies.
Ramsay:
Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.
Said the Warden of the North
would always be a Stark
and he'd be damned if he'd
kiss a traitor's boot.
Roose:
He left you no choice.
I flayed him living
along with his wife
and brother.
Made his son watch.
And?
The new Lord Cerwyn
paid his taxes.
I've something important
to tell you.
Stop eating
and listen.
We don't have enough men
to hold the North
if the other houses
rise up against us.
Do you understand that?
Our pact with
the Lannisters protects--
I had a pact
with Tywin Lannister.
And Tywin Lannister is dead.
The remaining Lannisters
are a thousand miles away
dealing with that fact.
They've never
once in the history
of the Seven Kingdoms
sent their army
this far north.
If you think
they will for us,
you're a fool.
We've become
a great house
by entering into alliances
with other houses
and parlaying
those alliances
into greater power.
The best way to forge
a lasting alliance
isn't by peeling
a man's skin off.
The best way is marriage.
Now that you're a Bolton
by royal decree,
it's high time you married
a suitable bride.
And as it happens,
I've found the perfect
girl to solidify our
hold on the North.
That's Moat Cailin.
Yes, a bit shabby,
isn't it?
You've been here before?
On our way down
to King's Landing
with my father
and Arya.
Where are you taking me?
Home.
The Boltons
have Winterfell.
Your marriage proposal,
it wasn't for you.
No.
Roose Bolton
murdered my brother.
He betrayed my family.
He did.
He serves
the Lannisters.
For now.
- I won't go.
- Winterfell is your home.
- Not anymore.
- Always.
You're a Stark.
Dying your hair
doesn't change that.
You're Sansa Stark,
eldest surviving child
of Ned and Catelyn Stark.
Your place
is in the North.
I can't marry him.
You can't make me.
He is a traitor.
A murderer!
You're not marrying
Roose Bolton.
No, you'll be marrying
his son and heir Ramsay.
One day he'll be
Warden of the North
and you--
- No.
- Sansa.
No, you can't make me.
I will starve myself.
I will die before
I have to go there.
I won't force you
to do anything.
Don't you know by now
how much I care for you?
Say the word and we turn
the horses around,
but listen to me.
Listen.
You've been running
all your life.
Terrible things
happen to your family
and you weep.
You sit alone
in a darkened room
mourning their fates.
You've been a bystander
to tragedy from the day
they executed your father.
Stop being a bystander.
Do you hear me?
Stop running.
There's no justice
in the world.
Not unless we make it.
You loved your family.
Avenge them.
( horse neighs )
Man:
Banners!
How do we
get through there?
We don't.
We go around.
Takes us miles
out of the way.
We'll lose sight
of them.
Brienne:
Doesn't matter.
I know where
they're going.
Aren't you getting
a bit old to be a squire?
How did you end up
squiring for the Imp?
He hates that nickname.
Well, he's not here
to complain about it, is he?
I squired for a knight
named Ser Lorimer
during the War
of the Five Kings.
One night he had
a bit too much to drink
and he was famished,
so he borrowed a ham.
He borrowed it?
He wasn't a thief.
He was drunk and hungry
and he wasn't thinking.
I was drunk, too.
He gave me half the ham.
Next morning,
one of the guards
saw him passed out
under a wagon
with the hambone
still in his hand.
They hanged him
that afternoon.
They tied the noose
for me, too,
but Lord Tywin heard
my family name was Payne,
so he pardoned me
and sent me
to King's Landing
to squire for his son.
As punishment
for both of you.
It didn't seem
that way.
Lord Tyrion was always
very good to me.
Yes, all your lords
have been very kind to you.
All except me.
Sorry you had to squire
for such a nasty person.
I'm not sorry.
You're the best fighter
I've ever seen.
You beat the Hound.
I'm proud to be
your squire.
I'm sorry I'm always
snapping at you.
If you didn't snap at me,
I wouldn't learn anything.
You want to be
a knight, Pod?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll train with a sword
twice a day.
Before we ride in the morning
and after you make camp
in the evening.
- And I'm going to show you
how to ride properly.
- Thank you.
I can't knight you,
but I can teach you
how to fight.
I suppose that's
more important.
You weren't a knight,
but you were a Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon,
weren't you?
I was.
Lord Tyrion said
he was a good man.
He was.
How did you end up
serving Renly?
When I was a girl,
my father held a ball.
I'm his only living child,
so he wanted to make
a good match for me.
He invited dozens
of young lords to Tarth.
I didn't want to go,
but he dragged me
to the ballroom.
And it was wonderful.
None of the boys
noticed how mulish
and tall I was.
They shoved each other
and threatened to duel
when they thought
it was their turn to dance.
They whispered in my ear
how they wanted
to marry me and take me
back to their castles.
My father smiled at me
and I smiled at him.
I had never been so happy.
Till I saw a few
of the boys snickering.
And then they all
started to laugh.
They couldn't keep
the game going any longer.
They were toying with me.
"Brienne the Beauty"
they called me.
Great joke.
And I realized I was
the ugliest girl alive.
A great lumbering beast.
I tried to run away,
but Renly Baratheon
took me in his arms.
"Don't let them
see your tears,"
he told me.
"They're nasty
little shits
and nasty little shits
aren't worth crying over."
He danced with me
and none of the other
boys could say a word.
Renly was the king's
brother after all.
But wasn't he...?
Lord Tyrion
said he was...
Yes, Pod, he liked men.
I'm not an idiot.
He didn't love me.
He didn't want me.
He danced with me
because he was kind
and didn't want
to see me hurt.
He saved me
from being a joke.
From that day
until his last day.
And I couldn't
save him in return.
Nothing's more hateful
than failing to protect
the one you love.
One day I will avenge
King Renly.
But you said a shadow
murdered him.
How do you fight a shadow?
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
I know it was Stannis.
I know it in my heart.
Stannis is a man,
not a shadow.
And a man can be killed.
- Lord Commander.
- Your Grace.
I'd like to speak alone.
Olly is my steward now
as I was
Lord Commander Mormont's.
I want him to attend
my meetings to learn
from men with experience.
One day he might command.
Very well.
Have you considered
my offer?
I have.
And I thank you for it.
You do me great honor.
All my life I wanted
to be Jon Stark.
Say the word
and you will be.
But I have to refuse you.
I'm Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
My place is here.
I'm giving you the chance
to avenge your family,
to take back the castle
where you grew up.
To rule the North.
I wish I could fight
beside you.
Believe me, I do.
But I swore a sacred vow
at the godswood.
I pledged my life
to the Night's Watch.
You're as stubborn
as your father.
And as honorable.
I can imagine
no higher praise.
I didn't mean it
as praise.
Honor got
your father killed.
But if your mind's made up,
I won't try and dissuade you.
May I ask, Your Grace,
how long you plan to stay
at Castle Black?
Are you bored
of us already?
You saved us
from Mance Rayder's army.
We will never forget that.
But it's a question
of survival.
The Night's Watch can't
continue to feed your men
and the wildling
prisoners indefinitely.
Winter is coming.
I know it.
We march on Winterfell
within the fortnight,
before the snows
trap us here.
And the wildlings?
If they'd rather burn
than fight for me,
so be it.
I leave their fate to you.
You could execute them.
That's the safest course.
Or you could see
if this Tormund fellow
is more willing to compromise
than Mance ever was.
I assume the brothers
of the Night's Watch
would rather see
the wildlings dead.
Most of the brothers, yes.
There's little love
for the free folk here.
You're the Lord Commander.
Your decision.
( door opens )
You have many enemies
in Castle Black.
Have you considered
sending Alliser Thorne
elsewhere?
Give him command
of Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
I heard it was best
to keep your enemies close.
Whoever said that
didn't have many enemies.
Davos:
He sees something in you.
Might not be apparent
from his tone,
but it's the truth.
He believes in you.
I'm sorry
I disappointed him.
The king
is a complicated man,
but he wants
to do what's right
for the Seven Kingdoms.
As long
as he's ruling them.
He's the one true king.
He has a blood right
to that throne.
I've sworn to stay
clear of the politics
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Have you now?
How does the Night's
Watch vow go again?
I'll bet you've
got it memorized
since you got here.
Night gathers
and now my watch begins.
No, not that bit.
The bit at the end.
I am the sword
in the darkness,
the watcher
on the walls,
the shield that guards
the realms of men.
- I pledge my life--
- Right, that's enough.
The shield that guards
the realms of men.
That's what
you swore to be.
Now, I'm not
a learned man,
but the best way
to help the most people
might not be sitting
in a frozen castle
at the edge of the world.
It just might mean
wading in the muck,
getting
your boots dirty
and doing what needs
to be done.
And what needs
to be done?
As long as the Boltons
rule the North,
the North will suffer.
Just one man's opinion.
( door closes )
( door opens )
What do you want?
Who are you?
- What?
- You, who walk in here
with a coin
you never earned
whose value
you do not respect.
Who are you?
No one.
Ow! Cunt!
A lie.
A sad little lie.
Who are you?
I told you, I'm no--
Do that again, and--
Who are you?
You're about to find out.
What are you doing?
We were only playing.
The Game of Faces.
- A girl is not ready.
- Clearly not.
I am ready!
For what?
For whatever you want.
To be a Faceless Man.
To be no one.
Jaqen:
Whose sword is that?
It belongs to Arya Stark.
Arya Stark's sword,
Arya Stark's clothes,
Arya Stark's stolen silver.
A man wonders
how is it that no one
came to be surrounded
by Arya Stark's things.
( sighs )
( door closes )
What do we do with them
after we wash them?
Man:
Open gate!
Man #2:
Honor guard, stand to!
Man #3:
Hold up. Easy.
Lady Sansa.
Welcome.
Lord Bolton.
May I introduce my son
Ramsay Bolton?
It's an honor
to meet you, my lady.
I'll bring you
a bowl of hot water.
You must want to wash.
Thank you.
Welcome home,
Lady Stark.
The North remembers.
( men chatting )
Sam?
Maester Aemon?
He apologizes
for not being here.
He's not feeling well.
Take good care of him.
- Brothers.
- ( chatter stops )
As you all know too well,
it's long past time to dig
a new latrine pit.
( men laugh )
First Builder Yarwyck and I
have decided to appoint
a latrine captain
to oversee this crucial task.
( men laugh )
Brian.
Seems like a good job
for a ginger.
( men laugh )
- That's him!
- That's him.
Ser Alliser.
You have more experience
than any other ranger
at Castle Black.
You proved your valor
many times over
while defending the Wall
from the wildling attack.
I name you First Ranger.
Men:
Hear, hear!
( pounding on tables )
Jon:
Lord Janos.
I'm giving you command
of Greyguard.
Greyguard is a ruin.
Yes, the fort
is in a sorry state.
Restore it as best you can.
First Builder Yarwyck
can spare 10 of his--
Slynt: I was charged
with the defense
of King's Landing
when you were soiling
your swaddling clothes.
Keep your ruin.
( men shouting )
- All right, all right!
- ( shouting stops )
Enough of that.
You mistake me, my lord.
That was a command,
not an offer.
Pack your arms and armor,
say your farewells,
and ride for Greyguard.
I will not go meekly off
to freeze and die.
Give it to one
of the fools who cast
a stone for you.
I will not have it.
Did you hear me, boy?
I will not have it!
Are you refusing
to obey my order?
You can stick your order
up your bastard ass.
( men murmuring )
Take Lord Janos outside.
Olly, bring me my sword.
- Dolorous Edd: Get out.
- Slynt: You cannot do this!
Get your hands off me!
Scum, all of you!
If the boy thinks
he can frighten me,
he's mistaken.
Yes, very mistaken.
Disgrace!
I have friends.
Important friends
in the capital.
- You'll see.
- Kneel!
If you have any
last words, my lord,
now's the time.
I was wrong.
You're the Lord Commander.
We all serve you.
I'm sorry.
Not only for this,
for all I've done
and said.
I was wrong.
My lord, please!
Mercy! Mercy!
I'll go! I will!
( sobbing )
Please.
I'm afraid.
( whimpering )
I've always been afraid.
( sobbing )
( women giggling )
You have served
us well, my son.
Thank you, Father.
Which of the Seven
will you worship today?
- The Maiden.
- Always the Maiden.
High Septon:
And the Stranger.
- Two is extra,
you realize?
- Yes, yes.
( snaps fingers )
- ( gasps )
- What are you doing?
This establishment belongs
to Lord Petyr Baelish.
You can't--
( groans )
You have profaned
our faith,
the faith of our fathers
and forefathers.
I am the High Septon
of the--
- You are a sinner.
- ( groans )
And you shall
be punished.
- ( cracks )
- Ah!
( woman laughs )
- Sinner.
- Sparrows: Sinner.
- Sparrows: Sinner. Sinner.
- Man: Repent!
- Sinner. Sinner.
- ( groans )
Sinner. Sinner.
- Man #2: Shame on you.
- Sparrows: Sinner. Sinner.
( doors close )
Your Grace,
Grand Maester,
Lord Tyrell, uh...
It doesn't matter.
As the High Septon
of the Faith of the Seven,
I give voice
to the will of the gods
and am their
foremost servant
in this world.
An insult to me
is an insult to the gods.
An assault
on my person
is an assault
on our very religion.
- You were assaulted?
- I was.
By those fanatics
who call themselves sparrows.
They humiliated me,
they beat me,
they left me
naked and bleeding
on the cobblestones.
I am lucky to be alive.
I heard this assault began
in Littlefinger's brothel.
High Septon,
this is a rather
shocking thing to hear.
High Septon: I tend
to both the highest born
and the lowliest amongst us.
Even prostitutes may earn
the mercy of the Mother.
So you were ministering
to the needs of these
devout prostitutes?
A man's private affairs
ought to stay private.
What do you want from us,
High Septon?
Justice.
I ask that you
protect our faith
by arresting these
criminals and throwing
them in the black cells.
I ask that you execute
their leader,
this so-called
High Sparrow.
He's a threat to everything
we hold sacred.
- If he goes unpunished--
- And where do I find
this man?
This High Sparrow?
I don't think this is
a good idea, Your Grace.
Nonsense, Ser Meryn.
These are deeply
religious people.
Where can I find
the High Sparrow?
Man:
Seven blessings.
- ( people coughing )
- ( flies buzzing )
( baby crying )
- Man: Thank you.
- Man #2: Just a little more.
( baby continues crying )
Woman:
Thank you.
Man #3:
A young man said I'd find
the High Sparrow back here.
- Where is he?
- High Sparrow?
Sounds ridiculous,
doesn't it?
Like Lord Duckling
or King Turtle.
Still, it's meant to.
We're often
stuck with the names
our enemies give to us.
The notion
that we're all equal
in the eyes of the Seven
doesn't sit well
with some,
so they belittle me.
Woman #2:
Seven blessings to you.
Seven blessings
to you, my dear.
It's only a name.
Quite an easy
burden to bear.
Far easier
than hers.
Cersei:
Why no shoes?
Because I gave
them away to someone
who needed them more.
We all do that.
It stops us from forgetting
what we really are.
Is that why you came
to King's Landing?
To remind everyone?
Everyone?
Hard enough job
reminding myself.
Well, I tell them
no one's special
and they think I'm special
for telling them so.
Perhaps they're right.
It would be comforting
to believe that,
wouldn't it?
Have the gods sent
you here to tempt me?
I hope not.
I had assumed
you'd only come here
to arrest me
for that incident
with the High Septon.
An unacceptable way
to treat the chosen
representative
of the gods in this world,
wouldn't you say?
Hypocrisy is a boil.
Lancing a boil
is never pleasant.
Although they could
have been more careful
with the blade.
The High Septon came
to speak to me today.
He doesn't want me
to arrest you.
He wants me
to execute you.
I wouldn't presume
to know your thoughts
on the matter.
My thoughts on the matter
are in line with your own.
The High Septon's
behavior was corrosive,
as was his attitude.
Having a man like that
reside in the sept eats away
at the faith from the inside.
So now he resides
in the Red Keep dungeons
instead.
The faith and the crown
are the two pillars
that hold up this world.
One collapses,
so does the other.
We must do
everything necessary
to protect one another.
( squeaking )
- ( flesh squelches )
- ( rat squeals )
- Your Grace.
- Send a raven
with this message
to Littlefinger
at the Eyrie or wherever
he's slithering about.
At once, Your Grace.
How's your work
coming along?
Very well.
You've made progress?
More than I expected.
- Still a way
to go, but...
- Very good.
I'll leave you
to it, then.
Make sure Littlefinger
is clear on the meaning
of the word "immediately."
( bottles rattle )
Shh.
Easy, friend.
( people shouting )
Ramsay:
She really is lovely.
I hope I can
make her happy.
I hope so, too.
I've become quite fond
of Lady Sansa during
our travels together.
She's suffered enough.
I'll never hurt her.
You have my word.
I've heard very little
about you,
which makes you
quite a rare thing
as lords go.
I haven't been
a lord very long.
I was a bastard.
And you're not
anymore.
Allow me a moment alone
with Lord Baelish.
Yes, Father.
And thank you,
Lord Baelish.
I'm forever
in your debt.
He seems pleased.
Shouldn't he be?
I assure you,
she's still a virgin.
Tyrion never consummated
the marriage.
By the law of the land,
she is no man's wife.
Inspect her if you must.
I'll leave that
to the brothel keeper.
It's her name I need,
not her virtue.
Then I have delivered
everything I promised.
And you're prepared
for the consequences
when the Lannisters hear
I've wed Sansa Stark
to Ramsay?
The Lannister name
doesn't mean what
it once did.
Tywin is dead.
He kept his house in power
through sheer will.
Without him,
Jaime has one hand
and no allies.
Tommen is a soft boy,
not a king to fear.
The queen
will be enraged.
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.
Cersei is Queen Mother,
a title whose importance
wanes with each passing day.
And yet she still
has friends,
men in important places
whom she can ask
for favors.
A message for you
from Cersei Lannister.
A rider arrived
from the Eyrie shortly
before dawn.
Apparently she thinks
you're still in the Vale.
A message for me,
you say?
Strange that the seal
is broken.
I'm sure you understand
my position, Lord Baelish.
If you receive
word in the night
from the Queen Mother,
it does make me question
our new alliance.
The Lannisters made you
one of the great lords
of Westeros,
yet here you
are in the North
undermining them.
Why gamble
with your position?
Every ambitious move
is a gamble.
You gambled
when you drove a dagger
into Robb Stark's heart.
It appears that
your gamble paid off.
You're Warden
of the North.
I had Tywin Lannister's
backing.
Who supports me now?
You?
The Eyrie is mine.
The last time
the lords of the Eyrie
formed an alliance
with the lords of the North,
they brought down
the greatest dynasty
this world has ever known.
I'd like to borrow
one of your birds.
Cersei will expect a reply.
I'd like to read
the reply.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
Volantis is a large city.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
The likelihood
of you being spotted here
increases a hundredfold.
Mm, I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
( sighs )
I'm not sure how many new ways
I can find of saying this.
I will not be of any use
to Daenerys Targaryen
if I lose my mind.
I can't remember
the last face I saw
that wasn't yours.
It's a perfectly
good face.
I am losing my mind.
If anyone recognizes you,
you'll lose more than that.
Look, we are thousands
of miles from Westeros.
What am I?
One more drunk dwarf.
( knocks )
- Driver: Whoa!
- ( horses neigh )
( seagull screeching )
( people shouting )
Woman:
We have to go now.
Come on, hold it.
Hold it.
Are you ready?
Slaves.
Yes, the Volantene masters
are very organized.
Flies for dung shovelers.
Hammers for builders.
Tears for whores.
Lest they forget.
( woman speaking Valyrian )
( crowd repeating )
We should keep moving.
The only red priest
we had in King's Landing
was Thoros of Myr.
This one's
much better-looking.
Stone Men.
Good luck stopping
the spread of greyscale
with prayer.
You'd have better luck
dancing away the plague.
Shh.
We're going to meet
the savior.
You should have told me.
Who doesn't want
to meet the savior?
Come on.
Let's find a brothel.
- ( people shouting )
- ( animals calling )
Man:
Build your house in a day.
( speaking Valyrian )
It's even better luck
to suck a dwarf's cock.
See?
We blend right in.
Just two more travelers
mad with lust.
Thank you.
( sniffing )
What curious hair.
The Mother of Dragons!
( men laugh )
It appears you're not
the only Targaryen supporter.
( man laughs )
We were just heading
east to see you.
I've got a dragon
for you.
How much to make him
spit fire?
Someone who inspires
priests and whores
is worth taking seriously.
What makes you
worth that much?
- I'm magic.
- I'll bet you bloody are.
( laughing )
Well, she's taken.
Where are you going?
I need to speak
to someone with hair.
- Hello.
- You've got no drink.
- You've got no money.
Do I look like
a man without money?
Never trust looks.
Until quite recently,
I was one of the richest
men in the world.
( laughs )
Who needs wealth
when you can make
a woman laugh?
I always pay my debts.
I'm well known for it.
( laughter )
You like her.
They all like her.
They all want
to fuck a queen.
That's because
they've never met a queen.
You're just saying that.
You know how
to spot a liar.
If I could pick
any girl here,
I would pick you.
Why?
Because you have
a skeptical mind.
All right, then.
I'm warning you,
we're going to have
to wash you first.
Come on.
I'm-- I'm sorry,
I can't.
Of course you can.
You're shy.
I'm not.
Have another drink.
Gladly, but this
I can't do.
Believe me, no one
is more shocked
than I am.
I hope it passes.
What will I do
in my spare time?
Go for a piss.
That's a start.
( urinating )
( mug splashes )
No need to worry.
I was just--
Oh, I thought
you were someone else.
Show's almost over.
I'm sure there
are girls inside
who'd be happy to oblige.
You've made
some kind of mistake.
Why don't you tell me
what you think you're
doing and then--
I'm taking you
to the queen.
( theme music playing )