Your grace, I want to say...
You will not speak.
How do I know you are who you say you are?
If only I were otherwise.
If you are Tyrion Lannister,
why shouldn't I kill you
to pay your family back
for what it did to mine?
You want revenge against the lannisters?
I killed my mother, Joanna Lannister,
on the day I was born.
I killed my father, tywin Lannister,
with a bolt to the heart.
I am the greatest
Lannister killer of our time.
So I should welcome you into my service
because you murdered members
of your own family?
Into your service?
We have only just met.
It's too soon to know
if you deserve my service.
If you'd rather return to the
fighting pits, just say the word.
When I was a young man, I heard a story
about a baby born
during the worst storm in living memory.
She had no wealth, no lands, no army,
only a name
and a handful of supporters,
most of whom probably thought
they could use that name
to benefit themselves.
They kept her alive,
moving her from place to place,
often hours ahead
of the men who'd been sent to kill her.
She was eventually sold off to some warlord
on the edge of the world
and that appeared to be that.
Then, a few years later,
the most well-informed person I knew
told me that this girl
without wealth, lands, or armies
had somehow acquired all three
in a very short span of time,
along with three dragons.
He thought she was our best,
last chance to build a better world.
I thought you were worth meeting,
at the very least.
And why are you worth meeting?
Why should I spend
my time listening to you?
Because you cannot build
a better world on your own.
You have no one at your side
who understands the land you want to rule,
the strengths and weaknesses of the houses
that will eitherjoin or oppose you.
I will have a very large army.
And very large dragons.
Killing and politics
aren't always the same thing.
When I served as hand of the king,
I did quite well with the latter,
considering the king in question
preferred torturing animals
to leading his people.
I could do an even betterjob
advising a ruler worth the name.
If that is indeed what you are.
So you want to advise me?
Very well.
What would you have me do with him?
I swore I would kill
him if he ever returned.
I know.
Why should the people trust a queen
who can't keep her promises?
Whomever ser jorah was
when he started informing on you,
he is no longer that man.
I can't remember ever seeing a sane man
as devoted to anything
as he is to serving you.
He claims he would kill for you
and die for you
and nothing I have witnessed
gives me reason to doubt him.
And yet he did betray you.
Did he have an opportunity
to confess his betrayal?
Yes.
Many opportunities.
Tyrion: And did he?
Daenerys: No.
Not until forced to do so.
He worships you.
He is in love with you, I think.
But he did not trust you with the truth.
An unpleasant truth to be sure,
but one of great significance to you.
He did not trust that you
would be wise enough to forgive him.
So I should kill him?
A ruler who kills those devoted to her
is not a ruler who inspires devotion.
And you're going to need
to inspire devotion, a lot of it,
if you're ever going to rule
across the narrow sea.
But you cannot have him by your side
when you do.
Remove ser jorah from the city.
(Door slams)
Confess.
My son...
Let me speak to...
Confess.
I meant it.
My face will be the last thing you see...
(Door opens)
(Sobbing)
(Screams)
My name is lanna. I'm an orphan.
When I was eight, I begged enough money
to buy my first bucket of oysters.
I sold that bucket and made enough money
to buy two more.
(People chattering)
Arya: It took a while,
but I finally saved enough
to buy myself an oyster cart.
Now every morning,
I make my way down to the canals.
I pass the fish mongers and the bakers.
I usually see lhara,
my first customer of the day,
on her way home.
Then I turn left onto moonsinger Lane...
Turn left onto ragman Lane,
where I do most of my trade.
Lanna is very impressive.
Very industrious.
She will make a fine servant
for the many-faced god.
How will she serve him?
She will no longer
turn left onto ragman Lane.
She will turn right and
go to ragman harbor.
What will she do there?
She will see.
- (People chattering)
- Arya: See what?
Jaqen: How can a man tell a girl this?
If he knew what she would see,
there would be no reason to send her.
Oysters, clams and cookies!
(Laughs)
Your oysters fresh?
Best in the city.
You wouldn't lie to an old man, would you?
Mmm.
Very nice. Give me four with vinegar.
It's my 18th voyage.
Returned from all of them
without a scratch on me.
Can't do it.
Captain: Please, I've three children.
Without me...
Here, take it. You have
to. I've three children.
- What will they do?
- Come on.
Captain: They've nothing without me.
Please, you have to!
Please, you don't understand!
Jaqen: The man is a gambler.
He wagers that a sailor's ship
will make it to its destination.
It is a strange wager for the captain.
He only wins if he loses his life.
So why would a captain
make the wager in the first place?
A girl tells a man that she has seen.
If the captain dies,
the thin man pays his
family a lot of money.
But perhaps the gambler loses his bet
and decides he does
not have to pay after all.
A destitute woman and her small child,
what can they do to such a man
if he keeps their money for himself?
To whom can they turn for recourse?
(Whispering prayer)
The many-faced god.
You said you didn't know
what I would see at the docks.
A man had no idea what a girl would see
and what she would not.
A girl named lanna
will return to the docks.
She will watch the gambler.
She will come to know as much about him
as she knows about herself.
And then what?
A gift for the thin man.
She's not ready.
Perhaps she is, perhaps she's not.
And if she's not?
It is all the same to the many-faced god.
(Door u n locks)
(Door locks)
The trial will take place soon.
The high sparrow will be presenting
a substantial case against you.
The charges?
Fornication, treason, incest,
the murder of king Robert.
- All lies.
- Of course.
My concern is that the
faith does not adhere
to the same standards
of proof as the crown.
I hope you'll excuse me for saying it,
but belief is so often the death of reason.
I wish you had said it sooner.
Is there any word from Jaime?
No, I'm afraid not.
Grand maester pycelle
has summoned your uncle kevan
back from casterly rock
to serve as hand of the king.
He now presides over the small council.
Tell him I need to speak to him.
I implored him to visit
you, but he would not.
What about my son, the king?
If you can visit me,
then surely the king...
Your arrest and queen margaery's arrest...
The king has not taken them well.
He remains in his chambers.
His servants often find his food
in the hall, left untouched.
You need to talk to him.
You need to talk to my son
and tell him to come and see me,
come and see his mother.
He... I tried. He wouldn't see me.
He won't see anyone.
I can't stay here.
There is a way.
A way out.
Confess?
To the high sparrow? I won't.
I made him.
I Rose him up from nothing.
I will not kneel before
some barefooted commoner
and beg his forgiveness.
Good bye.
The work continues.
Why, theon?
Not theon. There is no theon.
- Reek.
Why did you tell him, reek?
I was helping you.
You wanted to escape.
There is no escape.
Not ever.
Theon greyjoy tried to escape.
The master knew.
He knows everything.
He hunted him and caught him
and strapped him to a cross
and cutaway piece after piece
until there was no theon left.
Good.
If it weren't for you,
I'd still have a family.
If I could do what ramsay did to you
right here, right now, I would.
I deserved everything.
I deserve to be reek.
I did terrible things.
Turned on robb.
Captured winterfell.
- Killed those boys.
- They weren't "those boys."
They were bran and rickon.
They were your brothers.
You'd known them since they were born.
They weren't. They were only...
Only what?
- I can't.
- Tell me.
I can't, not unless the master says.
- Tell me. They weren't what?
- They weren't...
Tell me why bran and rickon should be gone
while you still breathe the air.
Tell me to my face, theon.
Tell me that they weren't your brothers!
They weren't bran and rickon!
I couldn't find them.
It was two farm boys.
I killed them and burned them
so no one would know.
You didn't...
Do you know where they went,
bran and rickon?
I can't talk to you anymore.
Theon, you have to tell me.
Do you have any idea where...
Not theon! Reek!
(Door slams)
Our scouts tell us
he's got no more than 6,000 men.
More than half of those
are mounted, however.
And how high do Stannis' horses jump?
Our walls have been fully repaired.
The gates have been reinforced.
We have enough food for six months.
We are more prepared for a siege
than they could ever be.
All we have to do is wait for them
to freeze, starve, and mutiny.
You disagree?
Stannis isn't from the
north. You are, father.
I think you're missing an opportunity
to show the people of the north
how house Bolton treats southern invaders.
And what do you recommend?
That we not sit and
wait for Stannis to decide
what sort of fight this is going to be.
That we hit first and hit hard
and leave a feast for the crows.
A smart commander does not
abandon a defensive advantage.
As long as we stay behind these walls,
they can't touch us.
Not to mention that the snow is so deep,
we couldn't get an army through
to engage them even if we wanted to.
I don't need an army.
I need 20 good men.
So, have you decided yet?
Whether I'm worthy of your service?
Have you decided yet
whether you're going to have me killed?
It's probably my safest option.
I could see why you would think so.
It's what your father would have done.
And what would your father have done?
My father, who publically
sentenced me to death?
I'd say his thoughts on having me killed
were abundantly clear.
Is that why you killed him?
Someday, if you decide not to execute me,
I'll tell you all about
why I killed my father.
And on that day, should it ever come,
we'll need more wine than this.
I know what my father was.
What he did.
I know the mad king earned his name.
So, here we sit.
Two terrible children
of two terrible fathers.
I'm terrible?
I've heard stories.
Why did you travel to
the far side of the world
to meet someone terrible?
To see if you were
the right kind of terrible.
Which kind is that?
The kind that prevents your people
from being even more so.
Well, I did reopen the fighting pits.
Under my rule, murder will once again
become entertainment.
Yes, that was wise.
And you agreed to marry someone you loathe
for the greater good.
Very impressive.
My own sister married someone
she loathed as well,
though not by choice,
and certainly not for the greater good,
gods forbid.
She ended up having him killed.
Perhaps it won't come to that.
It's not impossible that varys was right
about you after all.
Varys? King Robert's spymaster?
Yes, he's the one who convinced me
to come find you.
He was my traveling companion, before
ser jorah seized that role for himself.
Jorah sent my secrets to varys.
For 20 years, the spider
oversaw the campaign to find and kill me.
He did what he had to do to survive.
He did a lot of other things as well,
things he didn't have to do.
I suspect he's the main reason
you weren't slaughtered in your crib.
- But you trust him?
- Yes, oddly.
He may be the only
person in the world I trust.
Except my brother.
The brother who killed my father?
That's the one.
Perhaps I will have you killed after all.
Your queenly prerogative.
I had given up on life
until varys convinced me
you might be worth living for.
You chop off my head, well,
my final days were interesting.
I'm not going to kill you.
- Banish me?
- No.
So if I'm not going to be murdered
and I'm not going to be banished...
You're going to advise me.
While you can still speak
in complete sentences.
- Advise you on what?
- How to get what I want.
The iron throne.
Perhaps you should try
wanting something else.
If I wantjokes, I'll get
myself a proper fool.
I'm not entirelyjoking.
There's more to the world than Westeros.
How many hundreds of thousands of lives
have you changed for the better here?
Perhaps this is where you belong,
where you can do the most good.
I fought so that no child
born into slaver's bay
would ever know what it meant
to be bought or sold.
I will continue that fight here and beyond.
But this is not my home.
When you get back to your home,
who supports you?
The common people.
Let's be generous
and assume that's going to happen.
Here in slaver's bay,
you had the support of the common people
and only the common people.
What was that like?
Ruling without the rich?
House Targaryen is gone.
Not a single person who shares your blood
is alive to support you.
The starks are gone as well.
Our two terrible fathers saw to that.
The remaining members of house Lannister
will never back you, not ever.
Stannis Baratheon won't back you, either.
His entire claim to the throne rests on
the illegitimacy of yours.
That leaves the tyrells.
Not impossible.
Not enough.
Lannister, Targaryen,
Baratheon, stark, Tyrell.
They're all just spokes on a wheel.
This one's on top, then that one's on top.
And on and on it spins,
crushing those on the ground.
It's a beautiful dream, stopping the wheel.
You're not the first person
who's ever dreamt it.
I'm not going to stop the wheel.
I'm going to break the wheel.
(Grunting)
(Whistles)
You said whoever wins will fight
at the great pit in front of the queen.
I won.
You struck me.
Have me flogged if it makes you happy.
But I'm the best you've got.
If I win at the great pit,
how much can you sell me for?
You're a free man.
You could have gone anywhere.
Why did you come back?
Let me fight for her and I belong to you.
Woman: Thirsty?
Confess.
I'll get out of here before long.
I can make you a wealthy woman.
A lady of the court.
Confess.
Or I can make sure you die
in the most hideous way imaginable.
And all I do is sit here
imagining hideous ways for you to die.
(Door opens)
- (Door closes)
- (Latch locks)
(Slurping)
Does it hurt?
Good.
How are you?
I'm not the one who got punched
and kicked in the face.
You know what I mean.
I'm good.
Are you scared?
- A little.
- Me, too.
(Knocks on door)
- Who's there?
- Olly.
Come in.
I heard what happened.
Oh, not to worry.
Men brawl from time
to time. It's only natural.
Figured you were hungry.
Oh, you're a good lad.
Wanted to ask you something
if you've got the time.
I need to check on baby Sam.
(Door closes)
Samwell: Now then, how can I help?
- It's about the lord commander.
- Yes?
He's going up to hardhome
to save all them wildlings.
Wildlings killed my mum and dad.
- They killed everyone in my village.
- We've been fighting them for years.
This wasn't a fight.
We were farmers.
They slaughtered us.
So why is he saving them?
Wildlings are people.
Just like us, there are good ones
and bad ones.
The one he's traveling with,
with the red beard,
he led the raid on my village.
- Oh, olly...
- How can he trust him?
I've seen the army of the dead.
I've seen the white walkers.
And they're coming
for us, for all the living.
And when it's time,
we'll need every last man we can find.
But what if we let the wildlings
through the gates
and they cut our throats while we sleep?
Jon's taking a risk, but he has to.
We don't stand a chance othennise.
Sometimes, a man has to make hard choices,
choices that might look wrong to others,
but you know are right in the long run.
You believe that?
With all my heart.
Try not to worry.
I've been worrying about Jon for years.
He always comes back.
(Wind howling)
(Men grunting)
Ranger: Watch your bow!
You trust me, Jon snow?
Does that make me a fool?
We're fools together now.
(Man whistles)
Lord of bones.
Been a long time.
Last time I saw you,
the little crow was your prisoner.
The other way around now. What happened?
War.
You call that a war?
The greatest army the north has ever seen
cut to pieces by some southern king.
We should gather the elders,
find somewhere quiet to talk.
You don't give the orders here.
I'm not giving an order.
Why aren't you in chains?
He's not my prisoner.
What is he?
We're allies.
You fucking traitor.
You fight for the crows now?
I don't fight for the crows.
We're not here to
fight. We're here to talk.
Is that right?
You and the pretty crow
do a lot of talking, tormund?
And when you're done talking,
do you get down on your knees
and suck his cock?
(Grunting)
Gather the elders, and let's talk.
(Man coughs)
My name's Jon snow.
I'm lord commander of the night's watch.
We're not friends.
We've never been friends.
We won't become friends today.
This isn't about friendship.
This is about survival.
This is about putting a 700-foot wall
between you and what's out there.
You built that wall to keep us out.
Since when do the crows give two shits
if we live?
Jon: In normal times we wouldn't,
but these aren't normal times.
The white walkers don't care
if a man's free folk or crow.
We're all the same to them,
meat for their army.
But together, we can beat them.
Beat the white walkers?
Good luck with that. Run from them, maybe.
It's not a trick.
It's a gift, for those who join us.
Dragonglass.
A man of the night's watch
used one of these daggers to kill a Walker.
- You saw this?
- Jon: No.
But I trust the man.
There are old stories about dragonglass.
There are old stories
about ice spiders big as hounds.
And with the things we've seen,
you don't believe them?
Jon: Come with me
and I'll share these weapons.
Come with you where?
Jon: There are good
lands south of the wall.
The night's watch
will let you through the tunnel
and allow your people to farm those lands.
(Murmuring)
I knew mance rayder.
He never wanted a war
with the night's watch.
He wanted a new life
for his people, for you.
We're prepared to give you that new life.
If?
If you swear you'll join us
when the real war begins.
Where is mance?
- He died.
- How?
I put an arrow through his heart.
(Wildlings shouting)
Tormund: Hey.
Hey.
Loboda: I say we send the lord commander
back to castle black.
With no eyes.
Hey, none of you saw mance die.
I did.
The southern king,
who broke our army, Stannis,
wanted to burn him alive to
send us a message.
Jon snow defied that cunt's orders.
His arrow was mercy.
What he did took courage.
And that's what we need today,
the courage to make peace with
men we've been killing for generations.
I lost my father, my uncle, and
two brothers fighting the damn crows.
I'm not asking you to forget your dead.
I'll never forget mine.
I lost 50 brothers the night that mance
attacked the wall.
But I'm asking you
to think about your children now.
They'll never have children of their own
if we don't band together.
The long night is coming,
and the dead come with it.
No clan can stop them.
The free folk can't stop them.
The night's watch can't stop them.
And all the southern kings can't stop them.
Only together...
All of us.
And even then, it may not be enough.
But at least we'll give
the fuckers a fight.
You vouch for this man, tormund?
He's prettier than both my daughters,
but he knows how to fight.
He's young, but he knows how to lead.
He didn't have to come to hardhome.
He came because he needs us.
And we need him.
My ancestors would spit on me
if I broke bread with a crow.
So would mine, but fuck 'em. They're dead.
(Sighs)
I'll never trust a man in black.
But I trust you, tormund.
If you say this is the way,
we're with you.
This is the way.
(Murmuring)
Elder: I'm with tormund.
We stay here, we're dead men.
At least with king crow, there's a chance.
(Giant growls)
Tormund.
Keep that new life you want to give us.
And keep your glass, king crow.
As soon as you get on his ships,
they're gonna slit your throats,
and dump your bodies
to the bottom of the shivering sea.
That's our enemy.
That has always been our enemy.
I fucking hate thenns.
(Chatter)
Man 1: Move it.
Woman: Be careful.
Man 2: Move 'em along, now.
Man 3: We'll catch the tides.
That's it, come on!
How many are with us? Five thousand?
I'm not good at counting.
We're leaving too many behind.
The free folk are stubborn.
You know how long it took mance
to band them together?
Twenty fucking years.
And he knew them better than I ever will.
They're running out of food,
and there's nothing to hunt.
They'll come around.
Jon: Get yourselves ready.
Man 4: Aye!
Johnna is gonna look after you.
She's in charge. You listen to her.
Man 5: Take her.
I want to go with you.
I need to get the old folks on the boats.
I'm right behind you. I promise.
Go on.
Man 6: Another one.
Man 7: Keep moving.
We'll meet you out there.
Man 8: Won't be able to take
that on the boat. It's too big.
Man 9: That's the last one!
Man 8: Three more! Move on!
Man 10: There's more
dragonglass everywhere.
Man 11: I've got some more daggers
over here.
Man 12: Put that dagger in his bag.
(Speaks old tongue)
The fuck you looking at?
(Dogs barking and howling)
- (Wind gusting)
- (Barking continues)
(Thunder rumbling)
(Murmuring)
(Whining)
- Man: Steady!
- (Rumbling)
- (Wind howling)
- (People shouting)
Shut the gate.
Man: Shut the gate!
(Screaming)
Shut the gate!
- Open the gate!
- Letusin!
(All shouting)
(People screaming)
- (Pounding)
- Man: Open the gate!
(Shouting stops)
(Distant screams echoing)
(Screams)
(Roaring)
(People screaming)
Tormund: Ready your arrows!
(Snarling)
- Tormund: Wait!
- Keep in line! Get in line!
Get in line!
(Growls)
- (Thumping)
- (Snarling)
(Growling)
(Yells)
Man 1: Get to the front!
Man 2: Go on, shoot it!
Karsi: Wait!
Jon: Duncan, hold the line!
Lord commander!
Get them to the ship and come back for me!
- But you'll never make...
- Now!
- Let me on!
- Bloody fucking move!
- Let go!
Jon: You should be on one of those boats.
So should you. My little girls got on.
They're gonna let them pass the wall
even if you're not there?
You have my word. I've given orders.
Don't think you're gonna be there
to enforce those orders.
(Thunder rumbles)
If they get through, everyone dies!
Night's watch!
With me! Move!
Move!
(Screams)
Man: No!
- Jon: Tormund, the sleigh!
- Okay!
The dragonglass.
You and me, then!
(Giant growling)
Loboda: Get the glass.
(Yells)
(Grunts)
(Gasping)
(Gasps)
(Rings)
(Grunts)
(Panting)
- (Screams echoing)
- (Groans)
(Panting)
(Screaming)
(People shouting)
Come on!
- The dragonglass.
- Fuck the glass!
We are gonna die here!
(Screeching)
Oh, fuck!
Man: Here they come!
(Wood creaking)
Wun wun, to the sea!
(Roaring)
Man: In the boats! Quickly!
- Faster, faster!
- Run!
Quickly!
- Go! Row!
- Go, come on!
(Wildlings screaming)
Let's go! Now!
(Screaming)
(Screaming continues)
(Water sloshing)