( theme music playing )
( wind howling )
- ( bird screeches )
- ( man shouts )
( horse neighs )
- Man: Look out!
- Man #2: Fire! Fire!
- ( men shouting )
- ( horse whinnies )
( horse neighing )
( screaming )
( coughing )
Davos:
A band of 20 men,
maybe less.
They were in and out
before anyone spotted them.
Burnt our food stores
to the ground,
all our siege weapons
destroyed.
- Dozens of tents were--
- Horses?
We're still getting a count,
but hundreds are dead.
20 men rode into our camp
without a single guard
sounding the alarm?
The northerners know
more about their land
than we ever will.
Put last night's guards
in chains.
Either they fell asleep
or they conspired with
the enemy.
- Find out the truth
and then hang them.
- Your Grace.
Unless there's a thaw,
we can't press forward
to Winterfell
and we don't have
enough food to get us
back to Castle Black.
We're not returning
to Castle Black.
Forgive me, Your Grace,
I never claimed to be an expert
in military matters,
but if we can't march forward
and we won't march back...
Have the dead horses
butchered for meat.
Man:
Halt!
- Man #2: Halt!
- ( men coughing )
- Man #3: There it is!
- ( horse whinnies )
( wildlings murmuring )
Open the gates.
( rumbling )
( baby crying )
Jon:
It was a failure.
It wasn't.
I went to save them.
I failed.
You didn't fail him.
Or him.
Or her.
Every one of them
is alive because of you
and no one else.
I don't think
that fact's lost
on them.
You have a good heart,
Jon Snow.
It'll get us all killed.
Alliser:
Out of my way.
( horse neighs )
( men shouting )
( sighs )
You sent for me,
Your Grace?
Find some healthy
horses and a few knights
to guard you.
I'm sending you back
to Castle Black.
Tell the Lord Commander
his king commands him
to send food, supplies,
fresh horses.
In return,
when I take the throne,
I'll make sure
the Night's Watch has
all the men it requires.
He can guard all 19 castles
on the Wall if he so wishes.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
Yes.
The King's Hand should
never abandon the king,
especially
in time of war.
You're not abandoning me.
You're obeying a command.
A boy with a scroll
could deliver this message.
And if Jon Snow refuses
the boy with the scroll,
what does the boy say?
I didn't name you
Hand for your expertise
in military matters.
Ride for Castle Black.
Don't come back empty-handed.
Your Grace,
perhaps Queen Selyse
and Princess Shireen
could accompany me.
My family stays with me.
At least let me
take Shireen.
A siege is no place
for a little girl.
My family stays with me.
( men coughing )
What's this one now?
"The Dance of Dragons:
A True Telling"
by Grand Maester Munkun.
Now that sounds
like a proper story.
Ser Byron Swann wanted
to kill the dragon Vhagar.
He polished his shield
for a week so that it was
like a mirror.
And he crouched behind it
and crept forward,
hoping the dragon would
only see its own reflection.
But the dragon saw
a dumb man holding
a mirrored shield.
And burnt him
to a crisp.
( laughs )
Thus ending
the dragon-slaying career
of Ser Byron Swann.
( laughs )
I made you something,
Princess.
Do you like it?
He's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Will you make me a doe, too?
So that he can have company?
Of course I will.
But why am I
getting a present?
Because you deserve it.
My son was always on me,
trying to teach me to read.
Gods, I was stubborn
about it.
Made it this far
without reading.
Seemed to me I could
make it to the grave.
Wish I'd listened to him.
This is my own poor way
of saying thank you.
For teaching me
to be a grown-up.
I'll be gone
for a few days,
Princess.
I want to hear all about
"The Dance of Dragons"
when I'm back.
You'll read it yourself.
( birds chirping )
Prince Doran.
Forgive us.
We started without you.
Please, sit.
Princess Myrcella.
Uncle.
What a lovely dress.
- You don't like it?
- You must be cold.
Not at all.
The Dornish climate
agrees with me.
Prince Trystane.
How's your jaw?
A fleabite.
What are you
doing in Dorne?
Looking after
the safety of my niece,
the Princess Myrcella.
And rather than send a raven
or speak to me directly,
you decided to enter
my country in secret
and abduct our guest
by force?
We received
a threatening message.
The princess's necklace
in the jaws of a viper.
That necklace
was stolen from my room.
Oh, excellent.
A last meal before
the beheading?
Oh, I can't behead you.
Many in Dorne want war.
But I've seen war.
I've seen the bodies
piled on the battlefields.
I've seen the orphans
starving in the cities.
I don't want to lead
my people into that hell.
No, you want to break bread
with the Lannisters.
And that is precisely
what we are doing.
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms.
( slams )
King Tommen insists
on his sister's return
to the capital?
I'm afraid he does.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
She will return with you
to King's Landing.
And my son Prince Trystane
will accompany you both.
If the alliance between
the Iron Throne and Dorne
is to continue,
their engagement
must stand.
I accept.
One more thing.
My brother was named
to the small council
before his death.
Your father understood
the importance
of keeping Dorne
in the fold.
With Oberyn gone,
Trystane will take his place
on the small council.
You have my word.
The word
of a kingslayer.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
You are mother
to four of my nieces,
girls I love very much.
For their sake,
I hope you live
a long and happy life.
Speak to me
that way again,
and you won't.
May I inquire
as to the fate
of my man Bronn?
Tell me, Ser Jaime,
in King's Landing,
how do they
punish a commoner
who strikes a prince?
He said it was
just a fleabite.
The fault is mine.
Bronn is merely a soldier
following my orders.
If anyone should
be punished, it's me.
Prince Trystane
must learn judgment
if he is to rule one day.
I'll let him decide.
I have learned
the value of mercy
from my father.
- I'll set your man free.
- You're a good man.
On one condition.
( hands slapping )
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
I'll always
be better than you.
Have I ever missed once?
I don't think I have.
I can't recall.
You must love humiliation.
Or pain.
Which do you love most,
humiliation or pain?
That one hurt,
didn't it?
- ( smacks )
- You going to cry?
Give up, little sister.
- You're going to miss.
- Oh, I never miss.
You will.
You're thinking too much.
Now you're nervous.
What if she's right?
- Luck.
- Now it's my turn.
You're too slow.
You've always been
too slow.
( cell door unlocks )
Am I gonna be happy
at the end of this walk?
You'll find out
very soon.
Say it one more time,
handsome.
Who am I?
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
And that's the truth.
- Slut.
- ( Tyene laughs )
Prince Doran,
Ser Bronn
of the Blackwater.
I didn't realize there were
knights of the Blackwater.
Only the one.
I believe you've already
met Prince Trystane.
Prince.
Sorry about
the other day.
Jaime:
Prince Trystane here
is a man of mercy.
He's agreed to grant
you your freedom.
I'm glad to hear it.
Pie looks good.
There was one condition.
( grunts )
( Bronn groans )
Perhaps some soup
instead.
- ( merchants shouting )
- Arya: Oysters, clams,
and cockles.
Oysters, clams,
and cock--
How much
for your little clam?
( laughs )
Oysters, clams,
and cockles.
Come on.
Some oysters, girl!
I'm talking to you.
Is, uh...
- Girl!
- Man: Tie her up!
Thin Man:
Are you deaf?
Girl!
My lord.
Sailor:
Tycho:
Lord Tyrell.
On behalf
of the Iron Bank,
may I be the first
to welcome you
to the Free City
of Braavos.
I hope your journey
was trouble-free.
A bit of chop
the last few days.
Nothing too awful.
Good to see the old chap
still guarding the harbor.
And how goes
the harvest
in the Reach?
Ah, the vintners say
this might be
the best year
for red grapes
in half a century.
If we come
to a satisfactory
arrangement,
I'll be sure to send
a cask of the Arbor's
finest your way.
I'm afraid
I don't partake.
Oh.
Some consider
usury distasteful,
dishonorable.
Pure nonsense,
of course.
I'm glad we see
eye to eye on
this matter.
Mace:
Did you know that at one
point Maegor the third
tried to outlaw it
in the Seven Kingdoms?
Wanted to arrest anyone
caught charging interest
and cut off
both their hands.
Most unfortunate
for the glovers.
Mace:
If a man charges
no interest on a loan,
then he has nothing to gain
and everything to lose,
so why chance it?
Whereas the promise
of reward
makes a man
willing to gamble.
We are not gamblers
here at the Iron Bank,
Lord Tyrell.
You are the world's
best gamblers.
And all those bets
you won built this.
( coins clink )
( door opens )
Mace:
We should celebrate.
Tycho:
I'm afraid I still have
a good deal of work to do.
Mace:
Oh, nonsense. Work's over.
Do you sing?
- I don't have that gift.
- Oh, it's not a gift.
It's a skill.
Anyone can learn it.
♪ So give me a kiss
by the Long Canal ♪
♪ And give me two kisses
in Salty Town ♪
♪ For we're going
to die tomorrow ♪
♪ The bareheaded beggar,
the king with his crown... ♪
Trant:
Thought that old shit
would never stop singing.
Wasn't bad, though.
The Tyrells can all
rot in hell.
Treasonous cunts.
They were going to make
that boy-fucker Renly king.
This is the place, lads.
The sleekest little minks
in Braavos.
- You buying?
- Oh, I'm buying.
But I never was good
at sharing.
- ( chatter, laughter )
- ( music playing )
Sell your fish
somewhere else.
Oh, let her in, Brusco.
I'm hungry.
Come here, sweetness.
They say oysters
get the juices flowing.
We'll take
half a dozen.
Three coppers.
Here's a silver
because the lady
likes you.
Too old.
Brea.
Madame:
I have just the one.
Anara.
Our most expensive girl.
But well worth it,
I assure you.
Too old.
Do you have
what I want or not?
Of course.
- ( gasps )
- These fresh?
Come on,
the lads are hungry.
Nothing better
for your cockstand
than fresh oysters.
- Guard: Here. Thank you.
- Guard #2: I'll have one.
Any vinegar?
Who let this girl in?
Shoo! Shoo!
( guards chuckle )
Good.
I'll tell you
when we're done.
You'll have a fresh one
for me tomorrow?
Of course.
Madame:
I'll have you
whipped, girl.
Go, go on.
Out, out, go.
( whispering )
Valar morghulis.
And?
The thin man
wasn't hungry today.
Perhaps that is why
a man is thin.
Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
- ( thuds )
A girl has work to do.
Your rebellion is over.
You can swear
your allegiance
to me now...
or you can die.
( crying )
I believe
in second chances.
I don't believe
in third chances.
You write like
a seven-year-old.
Your maester kindly agreed
to copy it over for me.
He didn't try
to make you pay?
Mm-mmm.
Maybe he's changed.
The queen will be thrilled
to know you're bringing
her daughter home.
She will.
You love her very much,
don't you?
Of course,
she's my niece.
I wasn't talking
about her.
You think I disapprove?
Why?
Because people disapprove
of that sort of thing
where you are from?
They disapproved of Oberyn
and me where you are from.
Here no one
blinked an eye.
100 years ago,
no one would have
blinked an eye at you
if you'd been named
Targaryen.
It's always changing,
who we're supposed to love
and who we're not.
The only thing
that stays the same
is that we want
who we want.
I know your
daughter had no part
in the terrible thing
that happened
to the man I love.
Perhaps even you
are innocent of that.
( horse whinnying )
( tent flap rustles )
Father.
Aren't you cold?
No.
What are you
reading?
- "The Dance of Dragons."
- What's it about?
It's the story
of the fight between
Rhaenyra Targaryen
and her half-brother
Aegon for control over
the Seven Kingdoms.
Both of them thought
they belonged on
the Iron Throne.
When people started
declaring for one of them
or the other,
their fight divided
the kingdoms in two.
Brothers fought brothers,
dragons fought dragons.
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
And it was a disaster
for the Targaryens as well.
They never truly recovered.
"The Dance of Dragons."
Why is that a dance?
It's just what
they call it.
Hmm, doesn't make
much sense.
I think it's poetic.
If you had to choose
between Rhaenyra
and Aegon...
who would you
have chosen?
I wouldn't have
chosen either.
It's all the choosing sides
that made everything
so horrible.
Sometimes a person
has to choose.
Sometimes the world
forces his hand.
If a man knows
what he is...
and remains true
to himself...
the choice
is no choice at all.
He must fulfill
his destiny...
and become
who he is meant to be.
However much
he may hate it.
It's all right, Father.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
It doesn't matter.
I want to help you.
Is there any way
I can help?
Yes, there is.
Good. I want to.
I'm the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
And I'm your daughter.
( sighs )
Forgive me.
Where's my father?
I want to see my father.
It will all be over
soon, Princess.
( crying )
No.
Where's my father?
No, you can't do this.
Father, where are you?
Please, let me
see my father.
Father, where are you?
Don't let her do this.
Please let go!
Let me see my father!
Where are you? Please!
- Selyse: It's what
the Lord wants.
- Shireen: No.
- Please! Let go! No!
- It's a good thing.
- A great thing.
- Shireen: Stop. Stop!
- Shireen: Please!
- Melisandre: Hear us now,
my Lord.
- Shireen: You can't do this!
- Melisandre: For you,
we offer up this girl
- Please!
- ...that you may cleanse
her with your fire
and that its light
may lead our way.
Shireen: Please!
No, please let me
see my father.
If we don't act,
we'll all starve here.
- All of us.
- ( Shireen crying )
But if we make
this sacrifice...
Melisandre:
Accept this token
of our faith, my Lord,
and lead us
from the darkness.
- Lord of Light,
show us the way.
- Mother!
Mother, please!
Mother!
- Mother!
- We can't.
- There's no other way.
She has king's blood.
- Please don't do this!
Melisandre:
Lord of Light,
protect us.
- Please! Father, please!
- For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
Father!
Father, don't do this!
Please!
Mother, no! Please!
Please, help!
Don't do this!
Please, Father!
Mother, help!
- No.
- No, please!
Don't do this!
Don't do this,
please, Mother!
Please, Mother!
Mother, help!
Help!
Please don't
do this, Mother!
Please!
Please, Mother!
Please! No!
- ( fire crackling )
- ( Shireen screaming )
( screaming stops )
No!
( applause, cheering )
( applause, cheering
continue )
( drums beating )
( drumming stops )
Where have you been?
Just making sure
everything is in order.
- ( horse neighs )
- ( gate opens )
( cheering )
( cheering stops )
( speaking Valyrian )
( cheering )
They're waiting for you.
Clap your hands.
( cheering )
( both grunting )
- ( groans )
- ( Daario chuckles )
That one,
the smaller man.
No question,
that's where you
should put your money.
The smaller man it is.
I'm not putting
my money anywhere.
Kings and queens
never bet on the games.
Perhaps you should go
find someone who does.
People used
to bet against me when
I fought in the pits.
He would have
bet against me.
Common novice mistake.
I've spent much
of my life in this arena.
And in my experience,
large men do triumph
over smaller men
far more often than not.
Has your experience
ever involved any
actual fighting?
You yourself?
Have you ever
tried to kill another man
who was trying to kill you?
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
the crowd saw me,
all skin and bone
back then,
then they saw
a pile of angry muscles
ready to murder me.
They couldn't get their
money out fast enough.
But the pile of angry muscles
never had any muscles here
or... here.
And the big men
were always too slow
to stop my dagger
from going where their
muscles weren't.
Yes, whenever I saw
a beast like that one
standing across from me
making his beast faces,
I knew I could rest easy.
- ( shouting )
- ( crowd cheering )
You don't approve?
There's always been
more than enough death
in the world for my taste.
I can do without it
in my leisure time.
Fair enough.
Yet it's an unpleasant
question,
but what great thing
has ever been accomplished
without killing or cruelty?
It's easy to confuse what is
with what ought to be,
especially when what is
has worked out in your favor.
I'm not talking
about myself.
I'm talking about
the necessary conditions
for greatness.
That is greatness?
That is a vital part
of the great city
of Meereen,
which existed
long before you or I
and will remain standing
long after we have returned
to the dirt.
My father
would have liked you.
- ( gate opens )
- ( crowd cheering )
( speaking Valyrian )
One day your great city
will return to the dirt
as well.
- At your command?
- If need be.
( crowd cheering )
- ( warrior speaking Valyrian )
- And how many people will die
to make this happen?
If it comes to that,
they will have died
for a good reason.
Those men think they're
dying for a good reason.
Someone else's reason.
So your reasons are true
and theirs are false?
They don't know
their own minds,
but you do?
Well said.
You're an eloquent man.
Doesn't mean you're wrong.
In my experience,
eloquent men are right
every bit as often
as imbeciles.
( Jorah speaking Valyrian )
- Your Grace--
- Shut your mouth.
( crowd cheering )
( both grunting )
- ( groans )
- ( cheering )
( man groans )
( groans )
- ( groans )
- ( cheering )
( applause )
( groans )
- You can end this.
- She cannot.
- You can.
- ( crowd chanting )
( screams )
( crowd cheering )
( shouting in Valyrian )
( booing )
( speaking Valyrian )
- ( grunts )
- ( crowd groans )
( groans )
( crowd booing )
( people shouting )
( people screaming )
Protect your queen!
( crowd screaming )
Go!
Your Grace!
Come with me.
I know a way out.
I know a way--
( groans )
( men shouting
in Valyrian )
( Missandei screams )
Stay close.
( clamoring )
( groans )
( screams )
This way.
The other side.
- Follow me.
- ( people screaming )
Protect your queen!
( men shouting )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
( groans )
( shouts in Valyrian )
- ( dragon roars )
- ( gasps )
( dragon roars )
( men shouting
in Valyrian )
( roars )
( screaming )
( screeches )
Drogon!
( roars )
( roaring )
- ( spear pierces )
- ( roaring )
( roaring )
Valahd.
( roars )
( dragon roars )
( music playing )