[♪♪♪♪♪]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Come in.
[DOOR OPENS]
And?
Nothing?
She won't eat.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
We'll try again at supper.
I think they're watching me.
-Who?
-Her soldiers.
Of course they are.
That's their job.
What have I told you, Martha?
The greater the risk,
the greater the reward.
Go on. They'll be missing you
in the kitchen.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
VARYS:
The Northern armies?
JON:
Just crossed the Trident.
They'll be at the walls
of King's Landing in two days.
How is she?
She hasn't seen anyone
since we returned.
Hasn't left her chambers,
hasn't accepted any food.
She shouldn't be alone.
You're worried for her.
I admire your empathy.
Aren't you worried for her?
I'm worried for all of us.
They say every time
a Targaryen is born,
the gods toss a coin
and the world holds its breath.
We're not much for riddles
where I'm from.
We both know
what she's about to do.
[SIGHS]
That's her decision to make.
She is our queen.
Men decide where power resides,
whether or not they know it.
What do you want?
All I've ever wanted.
The right ruler
on the Iron Throne.
I still don't know
how her coin has landed.
But I'm quite certain
about yours.
I don't want it.
I never have.
[SIGHS]
I have known more kings
and queens than any man living.
I've heard
what they say to crowds,
and seen what they do
in the shadows.
I have furthered their designs,
however horrible.
But what I tell you now
is true:
You will rule wisely and well,
while she--
She...
is my queen.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
Your Grace?
There's something
you need to know.
Someone has betrayed me.
Yes.
Jon Snow.
Varys.
He knows the truth about Jon.
He does.
Because you told him.
You learned from Sansa.
And she learned from Jon,
though I begged him
not to tell her.
As I said...
he betrayed me.
TYRION:
I'm glad Sansa told me.
I am your Hand.
I need to be aware
of any threats you're facing.
And Varys?
Your Master of Whisperers
needs to be aware too.
You spoke to him first.
Without coming to me.
Without asking my permission.
It was a mistake.
Why do you think
Sansa told you?
What do you think
she hoped to gain?
-She trusts me.
-Yes, she trusts you.
She trusted you
to spread secrets
that could destroy
your own queen.
And you did not let her down.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
If I have failed you, my queen,
forgive me.
Our intentions were good.
We wanted what you want.
A better world, all of us.
Varys as much as anyone.
But it doesn't matter now.
No.
It doesn't matter now.
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
It was me.
I hope I deserve this.
Truly, I do.
I hope I'm wrong.
[INHALES AND EXHALES
SHARPLY]
Goodbye, old friend.
Lord Varys.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I, Daenerys of House Targaryen,
First of My Name,
Breaker of Chains
and Mother of Dragons...
sentence you to die.
[GROWLING]
Dracarys.
[ROARS]
[GROWLS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
This was all
she brought with her
when we crossed the Narrow Sea.
Her only possession.
[SPEAKING VALYRIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
What did I say would happen
if you told your sister?
I don't want it,
and that's what I told him.
She betrayed your trust.
She killed Varys
as much as I did.
This was a victory for her.
Now she knows what happens
when people
hear the truth about you.
Far more people in Westeros
love you than love me.
I don't have love here.
I only have fear.
I love you.
And you will always be my queen.
Is that all I am to you?
Your queen?
[JON EXHALES HEAVILY]
[SOFTLY]
All right, then.
Let it be fear.
TYRION:
The people who live there,
they're not your enemies.
They're innocents, like the ones
you liberated in Meereen.
DAENERYS:
In Meereen,
the slaves turned on the masters
and liberated the city
themselves the moment I arrived.
TYRION:
They're afraid.
Anyone who resists Cersei
will see his family butchered.
You can't expect them
to be heroes.
-They're hostages.
-They are.
In a tyrant's grip.
Whose fault is that? Mine?
What does it matter
whose fault it is?
Thousands of children will die
if the city burns.
Your sister knows how to use
her enemies' weaknesses
against them.
That's what she thinks
our mercy is:
weakness.
-I beg you, my queen--
-But she's wrong.
Mercy is our strength.
Our mercy
towards future generations
who will never again
be held hostage by a tyrant.
Ready the Unsullied.
Tonight you sail
for King's Landing
-to join the Northern armies.
-Cersei's followers
will abandon her
if they know the war is lost.
Give them that chance.
-[INHALES SHARPLY]
-If the city surrenders,
they will ring the bells
and raise the gates.
Please, if you hear them ringing
the bells, call off the attack.
DAENERYS:
Wait for me outside the city.
You'll know when it's time.
DAENERYS:
Your brother was stopped
trying to get past our lines.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
It seems he hasn't abandoned
your sister after all.
The next time you fail me...
will be the last time
you fail me.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
GUARD 1:
Let them pass.
[BABY CRYING]
GUARD 2:
Through the gate.
GUARD 3:
Get going.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
DAVOS:
The rearguard
should be here by daybreak.
TYRION:
She wants to attack now.
Daybreak at the earliest.
SOLDIER 1: Careful with that.
SOLDIER 2: My lord.
TYRION:
Davos.
I need to ask you a favor.
You're the greatest smuggler
alive, aren't you?
I'm not gonna like this favor,
am I?
SOLDIER 1:
He's always better
when he's got some food in him.
SOLDIER 2:
Problem is when
he's got drink in him.
See what he did the other week?
SOLDIER 1:
Aye. Fighting as well.
Commander nearly caught him.
Ay up. Where you going?
I'm Arya Stark.
I'm going to kill Queen Cersei.
Think about it.
She kills Cersei,
the war's over.
There won't be a siege.
You might not even die tomorrow.
[CHUCKLES]
I need to go talk to my captain.
Go ahead, talk to him.
SOLDIER 1:
Where's he going?
[SPEAKING VALYRIAN]
[CLEARS THROAT]
We speak the common tongue.
Ah. Good.
I want to be alone
with the prisoner.
Get some rest.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
UNSULLIED:
We have orders
to guard the prisoner.
Ordered by whom?
The queen herself?
-No.
TYRION: Well, in that case,
as Hand of the Queen, I outrank
whomever gave your order.
Probably by quite a lot.
How did they find you?
Did you consider taking it off?
Cersei once called me
"the stupidest Lannister."
And you're going back to her,
to die with her.
You've underestimated her
before.
She's going to die.
Unless you can convince her
to change her course of action.
Difficult to do from here.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
When have I ever been able
to convince Cersei of anything?
Try.
If not for yourself,
if not for her,
then for every one of the
million people in that city,
innocent or otherwise.
To be honest, I never really
cared much for them.
Innocent or otherwise.
You do care for one innocent.
I know you do.
And so does Cersei.
She has a reason now.
The child is the reason
she'll never give an inch.
All the worst things
she's ever done,
she's done for her children.
It's not impossible
that she'll win.
She won't.
Her enemy's forces
have been depleted,
as she said they would be.
Two of the three dragons
are dead.
-She's evened the odds.
-The city will fall tomorrow.
She has the Lannister army,
she has the Golden Company--
I defended the city
last time it was attacked.
I know it better than anyone.
It will fall tomorrow.
Then I suppose I'll die
tomorrow, if not before.
Why?
Escape.
The two of you, together.
Remember where we met,
where they keep
the dragon skulls,
beneath the Red Keep?
Take her down there.
Keep following
the stairways down,
down as far as they'll go.
You'll come out onto a beach
at the foot of the keep.
A dinghy will be waiting
for you.
Sail out of the bay.
If the winds are kind,
you'll make it to Pentos.
Start a new life.
Sail right past the Iron Fleet
and into a new life?
Sounds a lot less likely
than Cersei winning this war--
There won't be an Iron Fleet
for much longer.
Do it.
If you don't,
you'll never see Cersei again.
Swear to me.
You have my word.
If it works,
give the order
to ring all the bells
in King's Landing
and open the gates.
That will be our signal
that the city has surrendered.
I'll try.
I never thought
I'd get to repay the favor.
Remember, ring the bells
and open the gates.
Your queen
will execute you for this.
If Daenerys can make it
to the throne
without wading through
a river of blood,
maybe she'll show mercy
to the person
who made that possible.
Tens of thousands
of innocent lives...
one not particularly
innocent dwarf...
it seems like a fair trade.
If it weren't for you,
I never would've survived
my childhood.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SOFTLY]
You would have.
You were the only one
who didn't treat me
like a monster.
You were all I had.
[CRYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[MEN GRUNT]
SOLDIER 1:
Eyes on the horizon!
SOLDIER 2:
Load the scorpion!
[GRUNTING]
SOLDIER 3:
Archers, close up!
MAN:
Come on!
SOLDIER 4:
Up to the espringal!
SOLDIER 5:
To the back of it!
SOLDIER 6:
Archers, line up!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
WOMAN:
This way! Come on!
SOLDIER 1:
Clear the streets now!
WOMAN: No!
-In, now.
-And you, come on.
SOLDIER 2: Inside, now!
MAN 1:
Quickly.
Yes. Follow down there.
They're here.
Get to the Red Keep.
FATHER: My son!
SOLDIER 1: Get inside!
MAN 2:
Just ahead of you,
I can see it!
SOLDIER 1:
All right, move it!
WOMAN: Come on!
SOLDIER 2: Keep moving!
SOLDIER 3: Keep going!
SOLDIER 3: Quickly!
SOLDIER 2: All the way!
MAN 1: Come on!
MAN 2: Come on!
FATHER:
Hold your mother's hand!
SOLDIER 4:
Make way for the Golden Company!
Close the gate!
If you hear the bells ring,
they've surrendered.
Call off your men.
SOLDIER 1:
Move along now, lads.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
SOLDIER 2: That's it.
SOLDIER 3: Go on, move it.
SOLDIER 3:
Come on, move, move. Faster,
faster. Come on, move it.
-Keep going.
SOLDIER 2: Keep moving.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
-Move.
SOLDIER 2: Stay with him.
MAN: Hold on.
WOMAN: Hold my hand.
ELEANOR:
Get behind there.
SOLDIER 1:
Close the gate!
No more through.
-No.
-No. Mommy.
-Vicky! Please!
-No, please, sir!
MAN 1: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1: Close the gate!
MAN 2: Open it!
MAN 3: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 2: Get back.
-Look, try that one. Go. Go.
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
SOLDIER 3:
The gates are locked now!
WOMAN:
Open!
SOLDIER 3: Get back!
WOMAN: Open the gate!
Soldier! Soldier!
MAN 4: Please open the gate!
-Go back to your homes!
Stay back! It's closed!
Soldier!
SOLDIER 1:
Move away! Stop!
MAN 5:
Let us in!
MAN 1:
We're not leaving!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
Turn!
[ROARS]
SOLDIER 1: Turn it around!
-Turn it around!
Get back! Back!
Fire!
[ROARS]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
SOLDIER 2:
I can see her!
Ready!
Move!
Fire!
-Reload!
SOLDIER 3: Reload!
Faster!
Hurry!
[SCREAMING]
Fire!
[MEN SCREAMING]
[EXPLOSION IN DISTANCE]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[EXPLOSIONS APPROACHING]
[RUMBLING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[UNSULLIED YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
[DOTHRAKI ULULATING]
[GRUNTS]
[MEN GRUNTING AND YELLING]
[UNSULLIED ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[DROGON ROARS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
MAN 1:
Go!
MAN 2:
Run!
[DROGON ROARS]
QYBURN:
Your Grace.
All we need is one good shot.
The scorpions have
all been destroyed, Your Grace.
The Iron Fleet
hold Blackwater Bay.
Euron killed one of her dragons.
He can kill another.
QYBURN:
Your Grace,
the Iron Fleet is burning.
The gates have been breached.
The Golden Company--
Our men will fight harder
than sellswords ever could.
They will defend their queen
to the last man.
QYBURN: Yes, Your Grace.
-The Red Keep has never fallen.
It won't fall today.
[DROGON ROARS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[ALL GRUNTING]
MAN 1:
No, no, no!
[MEN GRUNTING]
JON:
Move, move!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
-[ROARS]
-[SCREAMING]
MAN:
Run.
Run!
Come on!
[DROGON ROARS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[ROARS]
[ROARING]
[SWORDS CLANGING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
SOLDIER 1: Ring the bells!
SOLDIER 2: Ring the bells!
MAN 1:
The bells!
MAN 2: Ring the bells!
WOMAN: Ring the bells!
MAN 2:
Ring the bloody bells!
MAN 3: Ring the bells!
WOMAN: Ring the bells!
WOMAN:
Tell the queen
to ring the bells.
MAN 4:
Ring the bells!
Ring the bell!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
WOMAN:
This way.
SOLDIER:
Ring the bell!
MAN 1:
MAN 2:
Ring them!
[DROGON SNARLING]
-[BREATHING HEAVILY]
WOMAN:
Ring the bells!
MAN 3:
MAN 4: Ring the bells!
MAN 5: Help us!
MAN 6:
In the name of the--
[DROGON ROARING]
MAN 7:
Queen! We're surrounded!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
MAN: Ring the bells!
MAN 2: Now! Come on!
[SNARLING]
MAN:
Hurry up!
WOMAN:
Ring the bells!
[RINGING]
[BELLS RINGING]
[SIGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[ROARING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SCREAMING]
[DROGON ROARING]
-[GRUNTS]
-[GROANS]
[MEN YELLING]
[PANTING]
No!
Get back!
JON:
Stay! Stay!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SCREAMING]
[CRYING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[SCREAMS]
No, no, no, no, no.
Quickly. Quickly.
Stop!
[GRUNTING]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
-Get off me! Get off, bitch!
-No, get off! Help! Help!
No!
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
Go!
[GRUNTS]
[WOMAN BAWLING]
[WOMAN GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
Find somewhere to hide.
[ROARS]
[ROARING]
MAN:
My God!
[PANTING]
EURON:
The Kingslayer.
[SPITS]
JAIME:
We need to get the queen
out of King's Landing.
EURON:
Listen.
That's the sound
of a city dying.
It's over.
-Well, maybe for you.
[SWORD RINGS]
If you kill another king
before you die...
they'll sing about you forever.
You're no king.
Oh, but I am.
And I fucked the queen.
If I win...
I'll bring your head to Cersei
so you can kiss her
one last time.
[GRUNTING]
[DROGON ROARS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[CHOKING]
[COUGHING]
[EURON ROARS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GROANING]
[RUMBLING]
Your Grace, it isn't safe here
any longer.
The Red Keep is the safest place
in the city.
QYBURN:
The Unsullied have breached
the gates of the Red Keep.
Maegor's Holdfast
would be a better place
to wait out the storm.
[CRYING SOFTLY]
[PANTING]
You fought well...
for a cripple.
[WHEEZING]
[GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BOTH YELL]
[YELLS, THEN PANTING]
[EURON YELLS]
Another king for you.
But I got you!
I got you!
[PANTING]
I'm the man
who killed Jaime Lannister.
[SIGHS]
[RUMBLING]
[DROGON ROARS]
Go home, girl.
The fire will get her,
or one of the Dothraki.
Or maybe that dragon
will eat her.
It doesn't matter. She's dead.
And you'll be dead too
if you don't get out of here.
I'm going to kill her.
You think you wanted revenge
a long time?
I've been after it all my life.
It's all I care about.
And look at me. Look at me!
You wanna be like me?
You come with me, you die here.
Sandor.
Thank you.
[RUMBLING]
[DROGON ROARING]
[MEN GRUNTING]
Your Grace.
[SWORD RINGS]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GROWLS SOFTLY]
Hello, big brother.
Ser Gregor, stay by my side.
Ser Gregor, I command you.
Obey your queen, Ser Gregor.
[GRUNTS]
[DROGON ROARING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Yeah, that's you.
That's what you've always been.
[DROGON ROARING]
[PANTING]
[CERSEI GASPS SOFTLY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SOBS]
[CRYING]
[SNIFFLES]
You're hurt.
It doesn't matter.
You're bleeding.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[ARYA GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
OWEN:
Alanna!
Alanna! Have you seen my wife?
Have you seen my wife?
-Let go.
-Have you seen my wife?
[CHILD WAILING]
MAN:
Out of the way!
[ARYA GRUNTS]
[DROGON ROARS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING
AND WAILING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
MAN:
No!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Oh.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
NORA:
Take my hand.
Get up. Get up.
[DROGON ROARING]
NORA: No. No.
-Wait! Wait!
No!
[RUMBLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GAGGING]
[GRUNTING]
Fucking die!
[LAUGHING]
[COUGHS]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[YELLING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[DROGON ROARING]
We need to fall back!
Fall back behind the wall!
-Fall back!
SOLDIER 1: Fall back!
JON:
Get out of the city!
Fall back!
-Fall back!
SOLDIER 1: Fall back!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
-[RUMBLING]
-[GASPS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[COUGHING]
[STONE CRACKING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ARYA PANTING]
You can't stay here.
You have to keep moving.
We can't go out there.
You have to.
Everyone out there is dead.
If you stay here, you'll die.
Follow me.
Follow me!
MAN 1:
Come on, quickly. Come to me.
MAN 2:
Lean him up there.
MAN 1:
Come on, quickly. All of you!
Run!
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
GIRL:
Mama!
Mama! No.
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
[DROGON ROARS]
Get up.
Get up!
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
We have to keep moving.
Take her.
Take her!
-Take her.
-Come on!
Come on!
[SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[RUMBLING]
[PANTING]
This way.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
CERSEI:
I want our baby to live.
Don't let me die, Jaime.
Please don't let me die.
It's all right.
-Please don't let me die.
-It's all right.
I don't want to die.
Just look-- Look at me.
-Look at me.
-Not like this.
Not like this. Not like this.
Look-- Look--
Look me in the eye.
Don't look away. Don't look--
Look at me! Just look at me.
Nothing else matters.
[CRYING]
Only us.
[RUMBLING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]