[♪♪♪♪♪]
DAENERYS:
When I was a child, my brother
would tell me a bedtime story...
about the man
who murdered our father.
Who stabbed him in the back
and cut his throat.
Who sat down on the Iron Throne
and watched
as his blood
poured onto the floor.
He told me
other stories as well.
About all the things
we would do to that man...
once we took back
the Seven Kingdoms
and had him in our grasp.
Your sister pledged
to send her army north.
She did.
I don't see an army.
I see one man, with one hand.
It appears
your sister lied to me.
She lied to me as well.
She never had any intention
of sending her army north.
She has Euron Greyjoy's fleet
and 20,000 fresh troops.
The Golden Company from Essos,
bought and paid for.
Even if we defeat the dead,
she'll have more than enough
to destroy the survivors.
"We"?
I promised to fight
for the living.
I intend to keep that promise.
-Your Grace, I know my brother--
-Like you knew your sister?
He came here alone, knowing
full well how he'd be received.
Why would he do that
if he weren't telling the truth?
Perhaps he trusts his
little brother to defend him,
right up to the moment
he slits my throat.
SANSA:
You're right.
We can't trust him.
He attacked my father
in the streets.
He tried to destroy
my house and my family,
the same as he did yours.
JAIME:
Do you want me to apologize?
I won't.
We were at war.
Everything I did, I did
for my house and my family.
I'd do it all again.
The things we do for love.
DAENERYS:
So why have you abandoned
your house and family now?
JAIME:
Because this goes
beyond loyalty.
This is about survival.
You don't know me well,
Your Grace.
But I know Ser Jaime.
He is a man of honor.
I was his captor once.
But when we were
both taken prisoner
and the men holding us
tried to force themselves on me,
Ser Jaime defended me.
And lost his hand
because of it.
Without him, my lady,
you would not be alive.
He armed me, armored me,
and sent me to find you
and bring you home
because he'd sworn an oath
to your mother.
You vouch for him?
BRIENNE:
I do.
You would fight beside him?
I would.
I trust you with my life.
If you trust him with yours,
we should let him stay.
What does the Warden
of the North say about it?
[SIGHS]
We need every man we can get.
Very well.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Thank you, Your Grace.
Either you knew Cersei was lying
and let me believe otherwise,
or you didn't know at all.
Which makes you
either a traitor or a fool.
-I was a fool.
-Not for the first time.
Cersei still sits on the throne.
If you can't help me
take it back,
I'll find another Hand who can.
[WIND WHISTLING]
I suspect one of you
will be wearing this
before it's all over.
[MEN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Coal's coming through.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[METAL HISSES]
[HAMMER CLANGING]
[HISSING]
Don't you have something better
to do?
You make my weapon yet?
Just as soon as I'm done
making a few thousand of these.
You should make mine first.
And make sure
it's stronger than this.
[BLADE THUMPS]
It's strong enough.
It's going to be safer
down in the crypt, you know.
Are you going to be
down in the crypt?
-No, but--
-But you're a fighter.
I've done my share.
You've fought them?
I did. Some of them.
How many?
A few.
That was enough.
What are they like?
Bad.
Really bad.
"Really bad"?
Even a smith's apprentice
can do better than "really bad."
What do they look like?
What do they smell like?
How do they move?
How hard are they to kill?
Look,
I know you want to fight.
And I know you're not scared
of rapers or murderers or...
This is different. This is...
This is death.
You want to know
what they're like? Death.
That's what they're like.
I know Death.
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
He's got many faces.
I look forward
to seeing this one.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
-My weapon?
-I'll get right on it.
I'm sorry
for what I did to you.
You weren't sorry then.
You were protecting
your family.
I'm not that person anymore.
You still would be,
if you hadn't pushed me
out of that window.
And I would still be
Brandon Stark.
-You're not?
BRAN: No.
I'm something else now.
[RAVEN CAWS]
You're not angry at me.
I'm not angry at anyone.
Why didn't you tell them?
You won't be able to help us
in this fight
if I let them murder you first.
What about afterwards?
How do you know
there is an afterwards?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[MEN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
SOLDIER 1:
Next up.
SOLDIER 2:
Put a marker in the ground!
Bring it up to the wall!
SOLDIER 3:
Up to the wall. All right.
SOLDIER 4: All right.
SOLDIER 3: All right.
TYRION:
Well, here we are.
Yes, here we are.
Together again.
[MAN CLEARS THROAT]
[SPITS]
And the masses rejoice.
How do they feel
about their new queen?
She's your new queen too.
They remember what happened
the last time Targaryens
brought dragons north.
They'll come around
once they see
Daenerys is different.
And she is? Different?
TYRION:
She is.
-You're sure about her?
-I am.
She didn't seem sure about you.
It's hard to blame her.
I made a mistake
common to clever people.
-I underestimated my opponents.
-Hmm.
Cersei told me the pregnancy
had changed her.
A chance for you both
to start again.
And I believed her.
MAN:
That stuff can go on the end.
Was she lying
about the baby too?
No, that part is real.
She's always been good
at using the truth to tell lies.
I wouldn't be
too hard on yourself.
She's fooled me
more than anybody.
CHILD:
No, he's right there.
What?
She never fooled you.
You always knew
exactly what she was,
and you loved her anyway.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
So...
[HORSE NEIGHS]
...we're going to die
at Winterfell.
Not the death
I would've chosen.
I always pictured myself
dying in my own bed,
the age of 80,
with a belly full of wine and
BOTH: ...a girl's mouth
-around your cock.
-around my cock.
At least Cersei
won't get to murder me.
I'm sure I'll feel
some satisfaction
denying her that pleasure
while I'm being ripped apart
by dead men.
[PEOPLE ARGUING]
Maybe after I'm dead...
I'll march down
to King's Landing
and rip her apart.
MAN:
You will see
the Army of the Dead.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Good.
[MAN GRUNTING]
[HOOFBEATS POUNDING]
[THUDS]
PODRICK:
Good. Yes, aim.
[BOTH GRUNT]
Don't rush.
Come forward.
-Come on.
-Ser Jaime.
Lady Brienne.
[SWORDS CLASHING]
-He's come a long way.
-He's all right.
PODRICK:
One more time. Come on.
-Still has a lot to learn.
-I'm sure you'll teach him.
PODRICK:
Better, better.
I've been told you're commanding
the left flank.
I am.
It's, uh... It's good ground.
It is.
The rise, it should give us
some advantage.
If we can keep
a tight formation,
we might be able
to beat them back.
[SIGHING]
Yes, I think you're right.
-What are you doing?
-What?
-I think you know.
-I truly don't.
We have never had a conversation
last this long
without you insulting me.
Not once.
You want me to insult you?
-No!
-Good.
I came to Winterfell because...
I'm not the fighter
I used to be.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
But I'd be honored
to serve under your command,
if you'll have me.
I better get back.
[DOOR OPENS]
JORAH:
Forgive me, khaleesi.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Have you done something
to offend me?
JORAH:
Many things.
Long ago and long forgiven.
But you did forgive,
despite my failures.
When I heard you'd named Tyrion
your Hand,
it broke my heart.
When I named him Hand,
I didn't know
if I'd ever see you again.
You made the right choice.
I wasn't under the impression
you liked him very much.
I didn't.
His mouth
hardly stopped moving
between Volantis
and Meereen.
It was all I could do
not to throw him in the sea.
[CHUCKLES]
But the mind behind
all those words...
He's made mistakes.
Serious mistakes.
As have we all.
He owns his
and learns from them.
You're advising me
to forgive the man
who stole your position?
I am.
And one other suggestion,
if you'll allow me.
ROYCE:
The moment we can get
the last infantryman
out onto the field,
we should shut the gates.
SANSA:
Keep them open
for as long as you can.
There are still people coming in
from the countryside.
Lady Sansa, I was hoping
we could speak alone.
I thought you and I
were on the verge
of agreement before.
About Ser Jaime.
Brienne has been
loyal to me, always.
I trust her more than anyone.
I wish I could have that kind
of faith in my advisors.
Tyrion is a good man.
He was never anything
but decent towards me.
I didn't ask him to be my Hand
simply because he was good.
I asked him to be my Hand
because he was good,
and intelligent,
and ruthless when he had to be.
He never should have
trusted Cersei.
You never should have either.
I thought he knew his sister.
Families are complicated.
Ours certainly have been.
SANSA:
A sad thing to have in common.
DAENERYS:
We have other things in common.
We've both known what it means
to lead people
who aren't inclined
to accept a woman's rule.
And we've both done
a damn good job of it,
from what I can tell.
And yet, I can't help but feel
we're at odds with one another.
Why is that?
Your brother.
He loves you, you know that.
That bothers you.
Men do stupid things for women.
They're easily manipulated.
All my life,
I've known one goal:
the Iron Throne.
Taking it back from the people
who destroyed my family,
and almost destroyed yours.
My war was against them.
Until I met Jon.
Now I'm here,
half a world away,
fighting Jon's war
alongside him.
Tell me, who manipulated whom?
[SCOFFS]
I should have thanked you
the moment you arrived.
That was a mistake.
I'm here because
I love your brother...
and I trust him...
and I know
he's true to his word.
He's only the second man
in my life
I can say that about.
Who was the first?
Someone taller.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
And what happens afterwards?
We defeat the dead,
we destroy Cersei.
What happens then?
I take the Iron Throne.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
What about the North?
It was taken from us,
and we took it back.
And we said we'd never bow
to anyone else again.
What about the North?
WOLKAN:
Apologies, my lady.
Your Grace...
What is it?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
THEON:
My queen.
Your sister?
She only has a few ships,
and she couldn't
sail them here.
So she's sailing
to the Iron Islands instead,
to take them back in your name.
But why aren't you with her?
I want to fight for Winterfell,
Lady Sansa...
if you'll have me.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
Milord, we're not soldiers.
You are now.
Look, I made it through
most of my years
without ever
getting near a fight,
but then I survived
the Battle of the Bastards.
Right outside these walls.
If I can live through that,
you can live through this.
They'll outfit you with weapons
at the forge.
Right that way.
Thank you.
GILLY:
When the time comes,
you'll be down in the crypts.
They're the safest place to be.
Through that archway
right over there.
Thank you.
WOMAN 1:
Hey, hey, who's next, lads?
WOMAN 2:
Thank you, sir.
Come back!
TEELA:
Which way should I go?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Which way do you want to go?
All the children
will be going below
when the time comes.
But both me brothers
were soldiers.
I want to fight too.
That's good to hear.
I'm going to be in the crypt
with my son,
and I'd feel a lot better
with you down there
-to protect us.
-I'm sure a lot of people would.
All right.
I'll defend the crypt, then.
[HORN BLARES]
MAN:
Riders coming in!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES]
My little crow.
I thought we'd lost you.
TORMUND:
Almost.
MAN:
Put them in the stables.
How did you find each other?
We met up at the Last Hearth.
The dead got there first.
The Umbers?
Fighting for
the Night King now.
We had to travel around them
to get here.
Whoever's not here now
is with them.
How long do we have?
Before the sun
comes up tomorrow.
The big woman still here?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
JON:
They're coming.
MAN:
Next.
JON:
We have dragonglass
and Valyrian steel.
MAN:
Arc it back!
JON:
But there are
too many of them.
Far too many.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
Our enemy doesn't tire.
Doesn't stop.
Doesn't feel.
We can't beat them
in a straight fight.
JAIME:
So, what can we do?
The Night King made them all.
They follow his command.
If he falls...
Getting to him
may be our best chance.
If that's true,
he'll never expose himself.
BRAN:
Yes, he will.
He'll come for me.
He's tried before, many times,
with many Three-Eyed Ravens.
Why?
What does he want?
An endless night.
He wants to erase this world,
and I am its memory.
SAMWELL:
That's what death is,
isn't it?
Forgetting.
Being forgotten.
If we forget where we've been
and what we've done,
we're not men anymore.
Just animals.
Your memories
don't come from books.
Your stories
aren't just stories.
If I wanted
to erase the world of men,
I'd start with you.
How will he find you?
His mark is on me.
He always knows where I am.
JON:
We'll put you in the crypt,
-where it's safest.
BRAN: No.
We need to lure him
into the open
before his army
destroys us all.
I'll wait for him
in the Godswood.
SANSA:
You want us
to use you as bait?
We're not leaving you alone
out there.
He won't be.
I'll stay with him.
With the Ironborn.
I took this castle from you.
Let me defend you now.
We'll hold off the rest of them
for as long as we can.
TYRION:
When the time comes,
Ser Davos and I
will be on the walls,
to give you the signal
to light the trench.
Ser Davos is perfectly capable
of waving a torch on his own.
You'll be in the crypt.
Your Grace,
I have fought before,
I can do it again.
Alongside the men and women
risking their lives.
There are thousands of them
and only one of you.
You can't fight
as well as they can,
but you can think
better than any of them.
You're here
because of your mind.
If we survive, I'll need it.
The dragons should give us
an edge in the field.
If they're in the field,
they're not protecting Bran.
We need to be near him.
Not too near,
or the Night King won't come.
But close enough to pursue him
when he does.
Dragonfire will stop him?
I don't know.
No one's ever tried.
We're all going to die.
But at least we die together.
Let's get some rest.
Your Grace.
[DOOR CLOSES]
TYRION:
Do you need help?
No.
You've had a strange journey.
Stranger than most.
I'd like to hear about it.
It's a long story.
If only we were trapped
in a castle...
in the middle of winter,
with nowhere to go.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
MISSANDEI:
Hello.
GREY WORM:
When Daenerys
takes her throne...
there will be
no place for us here.
I am loyal to my queen.
I will fight for her
until her enemies are defeated,
but when the war is over
and she has won...
[WHISPERS]
...do you want to grow old
in this place?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[NORMALLY]
Is there nothing else
you want to do,
nothing else you want to see?
Naath.
I'd like to see
the beaches again.
Then I will take you there.
My people are peaceful.
We cannot protect ourselves.
My people are not peaceful.
We will protect you.
[MEN GRUNT]
[MEN SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Yes, sir.
Have you told her yet?
No.
Mm-hmm.
Being careful.
Biding your time.
Waiting for the perfect--
And now our watch begins.
Gilly? Little Sam?
They'll be safe
down in the crypt.
If you want to join them...
To protect them.
Everyone seems to forget
that I was
the first man
to kill a White Walker.
-I've killed Thenns.
-Thenn.
I've saved Gilly
more than once.
I stole a considerable
number of books
from the Citadel library,
survived
the Fist of the First Men.
You need me out there.
Well,
if that's what it's come to,
-we really are fucked.
-Well, calling you "fucked"
wouldn't be strictly accurate.
[CHUCKLES]
Samwell Tarly.
Slayer of White Walkers.
Lover of Ladies.
As if we needed any more signs
the world was ending.
[SIGHS]
Think back to where we started.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Us, Grenn, Pyp.
Now it's just us three.
Last man left,
burn the rest of us.
TYRION:
I wish Father were here.
I would love to see
the look on his face
when he realizes his two sons
are about to die
defending Winterfell.
[SNORTS]
That would be something to see.
[WIND WHISTLING]
TYRION:
I remember the first time
we were here,
the first time
I saw this hall.
JAIME:
Mm.
You were a golden lion.
I was a drunken whoremonger.
It was all so simple.
It wasn't so simple.
I was sleeping with my sister
and you had one friend
in the world
who was sleeping
with his sister.
I was speaking
in relative terms.
-Do you miss it?
-Of course I miss it.
Well,
my golden-lion days are done,
but whoremongering
is still an option for you.
[SIGHS]
It's not.
Things would be easier
if it were.
The perils of self-betterment.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh!
My lady.
BRIENNE:
Oh, we didn't mean to interrupt.
We were just looking for
somewhere warm to--
To contemplate
your imminent death.
You've come to the right place.
You want some of this piss?
It's not bad.
-It's not good either.
-Thank you, milord.
I don't think that's wise.
The battle
might start at any moment.
Half cup.
-And you?
BRIENNE: No, thank you.
I should try
and get some sleep.
JAIME:
You really think any of us
are going to sleep tonight?
Join us.
All right.
Just a bit.
DAVOS:
Well, what do we have here?
Ser Davos, join us.
No, none for me, thanks.
Came here for this.
[SIGHS]
I figured I could wait to die
freezing my balls off
out there
or wait to die
nice and warm in here.
It could be our last night
in this world, you know.
Yes, well,
I'm glad you're here.
[STAMMERING]
Here fighting with us.
Glad you survived Eastwatch.
Would you like a drink?
Brought my own.
They call you "King Killer."
I'm sure someone does.
They call me "Giantsbane."
Want to know why?
I killed a giant
when I was 10.
Then I climbed right into bed
with his wife.
When she woke up,
you know what she did?
Suckled me at her teat
for three months.
Thought I was her baby.
That's how I got so strong.
Giant's milk.
[GULPING NOISILY]
Mm.
Maybe I will have that drink.
[TORMUND GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
You never used to shut up.
Now you're just sitting there
like a mute.
Guess I've changed.
What are you doing up here?
What's it look like?
No, I mean,
what are you doing up here?
You joined the Brotherhood.
You went beyond the Wall
with Jon.
You're here now. Why?
When was the last time
you fought for anyone
but yourself?
I fought for you, didn't I?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
May as well be
at a bloody wedding.
My lady.
It's good to see you again.
I'm sorry we parted
the way we did.
Was he on your list?
For a little while.
That's all right.
The Lord of Light has brought us
together all the same.
This is his moment.
-When light--
-Thoros isn't here anymore,
so I hope you're not
about to give a sermon.
Because if you are,
the Lord of Light's gonna wonder
why he brought you back 19 times
just to watch you die
when I chuck you
-over this fucking wall.
[CHUCKLES]
Where are you going?
I'm not spending my final hours
with you two
miserable old shits.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[BOWSTRING CREAKS]
ARYA:
That for me?
This'll work.
Last time you saw me,
you wanted me
to come to Winterfell.
Took the long road, but...
What did the Red Woman
want with you?
She wanted my blood
for some kind of spell.
Why your blood?
I'm Robert Baratheon's bastard.
I didn't know
until she told me.
Then she tied me up,
stripped me down,
put leeches all over me.
Was that your first time?
No, yeah, I've never had leeches
put all over my cock.
Your first time with a woman.
GENDRY:
What?
I-- I didn't--
I wasn't with her.
Were you with other girls
before that in King's Landing?
-[SCOFFS]
-Or after?
[STAMMERS INDISTINCTLY]
-You don't remember?
-[SCOFFS]
-Yes, I was.
-One?
Two?
-Twenty?
-Well, I didn't keep count.
Yes, you did.
[SIGHS]
Three.
We're probably
going to die soon.
I want to know what it's like
before that happens.
Arya, I--
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
I'm not the Red Woman.
Take your own bloody pants off.
[WIND WHISTLING]
It's strange, isn't it?
Almost everyone here's
fought the Starks
at one time or another.
And here we are in their castle,
ready to defend it.
Together.
At least we'll die with honor.
I think we might live.
-[CHUCKLES]
-[SNORTS]
[DAVOS LAUGHS]
I-- I do.
How many battles
have we survived between us?
Ser Davos Seaworth.
Survivor of both the Blackwater
and the Battle of the Bastards.
All without a shred
-of combat ability.
-Mm.
Ser Jaime Lannister, fabled hero
of the Siege of Pyke.
Fabled loser of the Battle
of Whispering Wood.
Hear, hear!
Ser Brienne of Tarth.
Defeated the Hound in--
Pardon me, Lady Brienne.
TORMUND:
She's not a ser?
You're not a knight?
Women can't be knights.
-Why not?
-Tradition.
Fuck tradition.
I don't even want
to be a knight.
TORMUND:
I'm no king.
But if I were,
I'd knight you 10 times over.
JAIME:
You don't need a king.
Any knight
can make another knight.
[CUP THUMPS]
I'll prove it.
[SWORD RINGS]
Kneel, Lady Brienne.
[SCOFFS]
JAIME:
Do you want to be
a knight or not?
Kneel.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
In the name of the Warrior,
I charge you to be brave.
In the name of the Father,
I charge you to be just.
In the name of the Mother,
I charge you
to defend the innocent.
Arise, Brienne of Tarth...
a knight of the Seven Kingdoms.
[ALL CLAPPING]
TYRION:
Ser Brienne of Tarth!
Knight of the Seven Kingdoms!
JORAH:
We have all we need
to win this war.
LYANNA:
I have trained my men,
women and children.
I have fought before.
I can fight again.
JORAH:
Please, listen to me.
You're the future of our house.
LYANNA:
I don't need you
to remind me of that.
You'll be safer in the crypt.
These things we're fighting--
I will not hide underground.
I pledged to fight
for the North,
-and I will fight.
MAN 1: I'm meant to relieve you.
-You got it?
MAN 2: Yeah, I got it.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to--
It's all right.
We're done here.
I wish you good fortune, cousin.
Thank you, my lady.
-My lady.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What have you got there?
It's called Heartsbane.
It's my family sword.
You still have a family.
Yes. And I'd love
to defend them with it.
But I can't really
hold it upright.
Your father,
he taught me how to be a man.
How to do what's right.
This is right.
It's Valyrian steel.
I'd be honored
if you'd take it.
I'll wield it in his memory...
to guard the realms of men.
I'll see you when it's through.
I hope we win.
-We'd better get some rest.
-No, let's stay a bit longer.
We're out of wine.
How about a song?
One of you must know one.
Ser Davos?
-You'll pray for a quick death.
-[CHUCKLES]
TYRION:
Ser Brienne?
Mm-mm.
Mmm...
♪ High in the halls
Of the kings who are gone ♪
♪ Jenny would dance
With her ghosts ♪
♪ The ones she had lost
And the ones she had found ♪
♪ And the ones
Who had loved her the most ♪
♪ The ones who'd been gone ♪
♪ For so very long ♪
♪ She couldn't remember
Their names ♪
♪ They spun her around ♪
♪ On the damp old stones ♪
♪ Spun away all her sorrow
And pain ♪
♪ And she never wanted
To leave ♪
♪ Never wanted to leave ♪
DAENERYS:
Who's that?
Lyanna Stark.
My brother Rhaegar...
everyone told me
he was decent and kind.
He liked to sing.
Gave money to poor children.
And he raped her.
JON:
He didn't.
He loved her.
They were married in secret.
After Rhaegar fell
on the Trident,
she had a son.
Robert would have murdered
the baby
if he ever found out,
and Lyanna knew it.
So the last thing she did...
as she bled to death
on her birthing bed
was give the boy
to her brother...
Ned Stark...
to raise as his bastard.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
My name...
my real name...
is Aegon Targaryen.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
-That's impossible.
-I wish it were.
Who told you this?
Bran.
-He saw it.
-He saw it?
And Samwell confirmed it.
He read about their marriage
at the Citadel
without even knowing
what it meant.
A secret no one
in the world knew...
except your brother
and your best friend.
Doesn't seem strange to you?
It's true, Dany.
I know it is.
If it were true,
it would make you the last
male heir of House Targaryen.
You'd have a claim
to the Iron Throne.
[HORN BLARING]
MAN:
Form up!
Get yourselves back!
[MARCHING IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ High in the halls
Of the kings who are gone ♪
♪ Jenny would dance
With her ghosts ♪
♪ The ones she had lost ♪
♪ And the ones she had found ♪
♪ And the ones
Who had loved her the most ♪
♪ The ones who'd been gone
For so very long ♪
♪ She couldn't remember
Their names ♪
♪ They spun her around
On the damp old stones ♪
♪ Spun away all her sorrow
And pain ♪
♪ And she never wanted
To leave ♪
♪ Never wanted to leave ♪