[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[SAMWELL SHIVERING]
NORTHMAN 1:
Oi!
NORTHMAN 2:
Mind out.
Move!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[MEN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
NORTHMAN:
Look, on the west wall!
SOLDIER:
Get down to the crypt!
[BABY CRYING]
SOLDIER:
Just hold.
MAN:
We'll take him.
-Come on, help the lads!
SOLDIER 1: Yes, my lady.
LYANNA:
Quickly, now! Quickly!
Get those in position.
SOLDIER 1: Come on.
SOLDIER 2: Close the gate!
SOLDIER 3:
That's it.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[DRAGON ROARING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
[HORSES SNORTING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You took your time.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[SNORTING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[DRAGONS GROWLING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Do you speak their tongue?
Tell them to lift their swords.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[SPEAKS IN DOTHRAKI]
[WEAPONS CLINKING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SPEAKING IN HIGH VALYRIAN]
[SOLDIERS EXCLAIMING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1:
SOLDIER 2:
Open the gate!
MAN 1:
Come. Come on.
Easy.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
There's no need to execute me,
Ser Davos.
I'll be dead before the dawn.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SOLDIER SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
[DOTHRAKI ULULATING]
SOLDIER [IN DOTHRAKI]:
[WIND WHISTLING]
[HOOFBEATS POUNDING]
[NEIGHS HOARSELY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[GASPS]
The Night King is coming.
The dead are already here.
[DRAGON ROARS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GREY WORM SPEAKS
IN VALYRIAN]
[UNSULLIED GRUNT]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[WIGHTS SNARLING]
[YELLS]
Stand your ground!
[SOLDIERS CLAMORING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
ARYA:
Get down to the crypt.
SANSA:
I'm not abandoning my people.
ARYA:
Take this and go.
I don't know how to use it.
Stick them with the pointy end.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[SOLDIER SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
SAMWELL:
Edd!
[WHIMPERING]
EDD:
Sam, get up!
[GASPING]
Oh, God. Sam.
[SNARLS]
WOMAN [SCREAMS]:
Edd!
[DOOR CLOSES, THEN LOCKS]
[PEOPLE WHISPERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[JON GRUNTS]
[DAENERYS GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Fall back! Fall back!
Fall back!
SOLDIER:
Come on!
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1:
SOLDIER 2:
Let us in!
SOLDIER 1:
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 3:
SOLDIER 4:
Keep moving!
SOLDIER 5:
Come on!
LYANNA: Keep moving, fast.
SOLDIER 5: To your posts.
SOLDIER 6: Go!
SOLDIER 7: Keep moving!
SOLDIER 1:
Come on, run!
Keep moving!
[IN VALYRIAN]
[UNSULLIED GRUNT]
[SOLDIERS CLAMORING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Dany!
[WIND WHISTLING]
SOLDIER 1:
Grab your weapon now!
SOLDIER 2:
Guard the barricades!
SOLDIER 3:
Through that pass!
BRIENNE:
Hey! Hey! Hey!
SOLDIER 4:
Close up the gaps!
Go! Hey! Go! Go!
Get in! Get in!
Get in! Come on!
[GREY WORM SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
[UNSULLIED GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
SOLDIER 1:
Move!
[SNARLING]
[SOLDIER WHIMPERING]
SOLDIER 1 [IN VALYRIAN]:
SOLDIER 2 [IN VALYRIAN]:
SOLDIER 1 [IN ENGLISH]: Come on!
SOLDIER 2 [IN ENGLISH]: Come on!
SOLDIER 1: Come on!
SOLDIER 3: Come on!
LYANNA:
Protect the gate!
SOLDIER 1:
They're coming! Come on!
Fall back!
[PANTING]
Light the trench!
SOLDIER 2: Wait!
SOLDIER 3: Light the trench!
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
She can't see us.
Light the trenches!
SOLDIER 1:
With a torch,
light the trenches!
-Right there.
SOLDIER 2: Torch it!
Light the trenches!
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLING]
[SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[UNSULLIED GRUNT]
[MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[SPEAKS IN VALYRIAN]
[UNSULLIED GRUNT]
[SPEAKING IN HIGH VALYRIAN]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[SCREECHING]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
Clegane.
[BABY CRYING]
WOMAN [SOFTLY]:
You must try
not to worry yourself.
[SIGHS]
At least we're already
in a crypt.
If we were up there,
we might see something
everyone else is missing.
Something that makes
a difference.
-[SCOFFS]
-What?
Remember the Battle
of Blackwater?
I brought us
through the Mud Gate.
And got your face cut in half.
And it made a difference.
If I was out there right now...
You'd die.
There's nothing you can do.
You might be surprised
at the lengths I'd go
to avoid joining
the Army of the Dead.
I could think of no organization
less suited to my talents.
Witty remarks
won't make a difference.
That's why we're down here,
none of us can do anything.
It's the truth.
It's the most heroic thing
we can do now...
look the truth in the face.
Maybe we should have
stayed married.
You were the best of them.
What a terrifying thought.
It wouldn't work between us.
Why not?
The Dragon Queen.
Your divided loyalties
would become a problem.
MISSANDEI:
Yes.
Without the Dragon Queen,
there'd be no problem at all.
We'd all be dead already.
[WIND WHISTLING]
They lit the trench.
Bran...
I just want you to know...
I wish--
The things I did--
Everything you did
brought you where you are now.
Where you belong.
Home.
I'm going to go now.
Go where?
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[RAVENS CAWING]
Man the walls!
SOLDIER 1:
SOLDIER 2:
Man the wall!
Man the walls!
Come on!
Get out there! Get moving!
Come on. Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go!
BRIENNE:
Come on!
[ROARS]
SOLDIER 1:
They're against the wall!
Get more men up here!
-Fill the gaps, quickly!
-Get in there!
SOLDIER 2:
They're climbing the walls!
-Relieve the archers!
SOLDIER 2: Relieve the archers!
Archers on top!
SOLDIER 1: Move up!
SOLDIER 2: Go, go! Come here!
-Come on!
SOLDIER 3: Move back!
SOLDIER 4: Stand away!
SOLDIER 2: Go on, go on. Go! Go.
SOLDIER 3: Step back.
SOLDIER 4: All the way, archers!
[SPEAKS IN VALYRIAN]
[SNARLING]
SOLDIER 1:
Hold the wall!
SOLDIER 2:
The wall, they're coming up!
SOLDIER 3: Hold the wall!
SOLDIER 4: Hold the wall!
Draw!
Come on!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[YELLS]
SOLDIER:
They're coming up!
Look out!
[WHIMPERING]
[SHUDDERING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
Clegane!
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
BERIC:
Clegane!
Clegane, we need you!
You can't give up on us.
Fuck off! We can't beat them.
Don't you see that,
you stupid whore?
We're fighting Death!
They can't beat Death.
Tell her that.
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[YELLS]
[ROARS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[DAENERYS WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIGHT CROAKS]
[SNARLING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[SNARLING IN DISTANCE]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SNARLING]
[PANTING]
[WIGHTS SNARLING IN DISTANCE]
[MEN YELLING IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR THUDS]
[ALL GASPING]
SOLDIER 1:
Open the door!
SOLDIER 2:
SOLDIER 3: Come on!
SOLDIER 4: Open the door!
Open the door!
Please!
Open it!
[SOLDIERS SCREAMING
INDISTINCTLY]
[SCREAMING FADES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[OBJECT CLATTERS
IN DISTANCE]
-[OBJECT THUDS]
-[GASPS]
[WIGHTS SNARLING
IN DISTANCE]
[SCREAMING]
Rah!
Aah!
[GRUNTING]
Come on! Go!
-Come on!
BERIC: Run!
We've gotta go!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
MELISANDRE:
The Lord brought him back
for a purpose.
Now that purpose
has been served.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
I know you.
And I know you.
You said we'd meet again.
And here we are.
At the end of the world.
You said I'd shut
many eyes forever.
You were right about that too.
Brown eyes...
green eyes...
and blue eyes.
[WIGHTS SNARLING
AND THUDDING ON DOOR]
What do we say
to the God of Death?
Not today.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[WIGHTS SNARLING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
Here they come!
Steady, lads.
Steady now.
Make every shot count.
[♪♪♪♪♪]
MAN 1:
Over there!
MAN 2:
There!
[♪♪♪♪♪]
JON:
Get off.
[GRUNTING]
[JON GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[ROARS]
[DRAGON ROARING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
Dracarys.
[DAENERYS GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[JON YELLS]
[WIGHTS RUSTLING]
[GASPS]
[SNARLING]
[BABY CRYING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Come on! Come on!
No! No, no, no!
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
-Bran!
DAENERYS: Go!
[WIGHTS SNARLING]
[DROGON ROARING]
[DROGON SCREECHES]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIMPERS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
[GRUNTS]
[SAMWELL SCREAMING]
[HISSING AND SNARLING]
[YELLS]
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DRAGON ROARS]
[GRUNTS]
Jorah!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[SNIFFLING]
[GASPS]
BRAN:
Theon.
You're a good man.
Thank you.
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[VISERION ROARS]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪♪♪]
I'm hurt.
[SOBBING]
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
[♪♪♪♪♪]