Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for being here.
It's a joyous day for me,
because my autobiography,
is being released.
I'm a very... misunderstood man.
If you want to know
the real Sanjay Dutt,
read my autobiography.
It's my story, but written by
my buddy, DN Tripathi.
And he wishes that
I read you a chapter.
Chapter one...
Bapu and Sanju.
Bapu is Mahatma Gandhi.
And, Sanju...
yours truly... Sanjay Dutt.
Our lives have followed
quite a... similar graph.
- Hey, Tripathi...
- Yes.
Killer opening!
Moved me to tears.
Your wish is my command.
I've put my soul into it.
Mohammad... Sudama...
come here.
Tripathi has written
a rump-ripping book.
Read us a chapter.
Nanny, take a seat.
The book is titled “Sage Sanju...
Chapter one...
Bapu and Sanju.
Bapu is Mahatma Gandhi.
And, Sanju...
yours truly... Sanjay Dutt.
Our lives have followed
quite a similar graph.
For instance... we've both spent
a lot of time in prison.
He's a national hero.
I'm a Bollywood hero.
He was against violence.
He walked with a stick
but never used it as a weapon.
I had an AK-56 rifle
and never used it either.
He dreamed of a free India.
I dream of... my freedom.
Maanayata, it's a slow starter.
Don't worry,
the story picks up later.
Hold this...
pick up the bell... ring it.
Go around and worship me.
You've elevated me
to Mahatma Gandhi in the first chapter.
By the end,
you'll turn me into God!
Find a temple for sale.
He'll put me on the altar.
Sorry... sorry.
Buddy, tell me...
are shoes allowed
inside a temple?
Not at all, Sanju.
Then how dare you wear shoes
in front of God?
Sanju... I'd told you,
I'm no biographer.
I'm a songwriter...
Sanju, stop it.
Sanju... please!
What about me
reminds you of Gandhi?
I'll write another draft.
Shithead, you jacked my book!
Our correspondent is outside
the Supreme Court.
In moments, we'll know
whether the actor Sanjay Dutt,
will go to prison or be free.
In 2006, the Anti-Terrorism Court
had sentenced Sanjay Dutt
to six years imprisonment
in the Mumbai bomb blast case.
He'd appealed to the Supreme Court
against the judgment.
The judgment was expected
next week.
But, we've just received information...
the Supreme Court
will give its verdict today.
Stay tuned, as we report live
from the Supreme Court.
Dinesh, give us an update.
The verdict is out.
Sanjay Dutt will go to prison.
The Court has sentenced him
to five years,
for possession of an AK-56 rifle.
When does he go to prison?
The Court has given him
a month to surrender...
so he can complete his films.
His father, late Sunil Dutt,
popular actor and politician...
his mother, late Nargis,
iconic actor of the '603...
the scion of this eminent family,
Sanjay, will go to prison.
Let's hear what people have to say.
Five years is nothing.
He should be hanged!
Traitor... a bloody terrorist!
Celebrities have it easy.
Such terrorists
should be shot dead!
Come inside.
Dear Maanayata...
When the kids start school,
they are sure to be asked...
"Where's your terrorist-dad?
In prison?“
It'll be easier for them to say,
"No, he's dead."
Sanju!
Suicide may solve your problem,
not your kids“.
They'll still be called
terrorist's kids.
We decided to fight,
didn't we?
That we'll get the truth out there.
Didn't we try?
What did we get?
Bapu and Sanju!
That's what you get
with knuckleheads.
Write it yourself.
Struggled with a four-line
suicide note.
Imagine a 400-page book!
We'll find a good writer.
Why Will they be interested?
It's said, "Bad choices
make good stories."
And you're the king
of bad choices.
Some writer out there
will understand this.
Sanju, be respectful.
She's no Tripathi.
She's Winnie Dias.
World's top biographer.
She's down from London.
Control slang like...
rump-ripper, jacked...
Got it. Okay... bye!
Winnie...
I won't take much of your time.
I wanted...
I can't write your biography.
I'm sorry.
Why not?
When your wife called,
I asked around and...
And they said,
"I'm a terrorist."
Yes.
Who are these people?
Do they know me?
Do they hang outwith me?
Then how can they be so sure?
Their opinion is based
merely on TV and print news.
And these TV anchors,
newspaper reporters,
who dish out opinions everyday,
haven't met me either!
The media has maligned me.
So, I need a good writer
to present my side of the story.
You think millions
will read your biography?
It doesn't work like that.
Thousands of books
rot away in book stores.
Once in a blue moon
a book comes that...
That's a rump-ripper!
My story's that!
What's there in your life story?
Drugs... alcohol... guns?
Give me just one hour.
Guns... drugs... alcohol...
Pick any chapter,
I'll tell you the story...
I guarantee...
you'll be jacked...
I mean... jack...
it'll be a J K Rowling.
I have a month to surrender.
This time I may not survive.
One hour, please.
Okay.
5 pm tomorrow.
Right here.
At 6 pm, I'll tell you
if I'm jacked or not.
Done.
Alright.
From Amitabh Bachchan
to Sachin Tendulkar...
you've upset everyone.
Sorry?
So many heroes, but you'll pen
a terrorist's biography!
Rubbish... this is fake news.
He too is a fake.
This is a pressure tactic.
- Who are you?
- Zubin Mistry.
Doesn't help.
I'm into construction.
I construct malls.
I suggest you don't
write this book.
And you came all the way
to "suggest" it?
I'm here daily... to jog.
Saw you here, so...
Jog in a suit?
Is work-wear shorts?
- Listen.
- Excuse me!
He's dangerous.
Look at this.
He hit me.
He's on cocaine, LSD, heroin...
A womanizer, too.
Ask him his score.
Any number less than 200,
he's lying.
Want to know his truth?
Call me.
Big fan.
Sanju.
For once, I feel like
thanking the press.
One headline... and you're here.
- Why did you get this printed?
- I didn't, Winnie.
Reporters live outside my gate.
They follow me everywhere.
If you were a doctor,
they'd print, “Sanju ill",
an actress... "Sanju's new lady.“
They want spicy headlines.
Not the truth.
- That's why we've come to you.
- Will he tell me the truth?
Nothing but the truth.
Fire away.
Okay. Alright.
Excluding your wife, how many women
have you slept with?
- Look here.
- Sure, of course.
Should I count the prostitutes or...?
No, let's keep them aside.
Never kept a score-card.
But once, I did the math,
I recalled around 308.
I must've missed a few.
On the safe side, let's say... 350.
Do you know him?
Zubinl
He was my friend.
I nicknamed him "God".
Since you picked him,
let's start with chapter "God".
My time starts now.
1981 my debut film.
He was always on the sets.
Dad was directing me
and I was nervous as hell.
♪ Is this love? J“
♪ Yes, my dove! ♪
Cut. . . cut.
Sonny, your lips are off sync.
Match them to the song.
And... a romantic reaction
when the girl sings.
But, dad... where's the girl?
How do I react
to a cold camera?
An actor's job is to imagine.
Imagine a beautiful actress
in front of you.
Ganpat, come here.
Observe.
Sound.
♪ Is this love? J“
♪ Yes, my dove! ♪
♪ In your absence
Day and night eclipse I
♪ And an hour is forever 3
♪ Is this love? J“
♪ Yes, my dove! ♪
Cut.
Come. Give it a go.
Let's give him a heroine.
Ganpat, come here.
Hold this and stand here.
- Don't move.
- Good idea.
Start sound.
♪ Is this love? J“
♪ Yes, my dove! ♪
♪ In your absence
Day and night eclipse I
♪ And an hour is forever 3
♪ Is this love? J“
♪ Yes, yes! r
♪ Yes, my dove! ♪
Cut it!
Well played, Ramu.
Ace!
Sonny...
- You've been smoking?
- No, dad.
Now you lie, too?
Thousands struggle to be
an actor... with no luck.
You've got it on a silver platter,
respect that.
Drinking, smoking...
will show on your face.
The camera spares no one.
Quit smoking
or I'll shelve the film.
Smoke with your left hand.
Fathers sniff the right hand.
Boys!
Bro, I'm the first actor in the world
to romance a bandit.
But, dad praised the cameraman.
"We“ flayed, Ram“
Ace?
However we” I do,
he never praises me.
He insults me publicly.
- Reason with him.
- That would be suicide.
You're too scared of your dad.
Hey, try this.
It bumps up confidence.
Gladiators would take
this before a fight.
Watch.
Put this in your nose...
and snort it all.
I make my Pomeranian snort it
and he thinks he's an Alsatian.
Try it.
Sanju, not good for health.
Hey! I've been taking it for years.
I'm stronger than you.
Try me.
♪  0 light of my soul! I
♪ If you're heaven's king,
I'm your queen' ♪
♪ If you're the needle,
I'm the thread I
♪ Then why our union
So half-baked, half-baked? I
Dad thinks that I can't
lip sync to songs.
He's wrong.
Watch me.
♪ I'm a fine catch,
so are you I
♪ Marry me, my love' ♪
♪ Let sparks fly,
so fine, so bright :
♪ I'm a fine catch,
so are you I
♪ But, I'm a free bird' ♪
♪ Keep your fireworks,
too fine, too bright :
1' Take my hand,
marry me quick I
♪ Make me yours in a click I
♪ Listen up,
I'm a wild stallion' ♪
♪ Why reduce me
to a mere medallion r
♪ I'm a fine catch,
so are you I
♪ Marry me, my love' ♪
♪ Let sparks fly,
so fine, so bright :
♪ No way, love!' ♪
♪ I'm a fine catch,
so are you I
♪ But, I'm a free bird' ♪
♪ Keep your fireworks,
too fine, too bright :
That night, one more Pomeranian
turned into an Alsatian.
God's powder was magic.
My confidence was sky-rocketing.
- Where's the bottle?
- Your dad chucked it.
Damn! For how long
will he control me?
My father controlled me
for 60 years.
- How did he let go?
- He popped it.
Dudes, don't leave.
The vodka's coming.
The bar's closed, Sanju.
Dad thinks cutting supply
will make us quit?
I have a back-up daddy.
Who'll fill up our mugs.
- Back-up dad?
- My girlfriend's pop.
Hello.
- I love you, Ruby.
- Love you too, baby.
Baby, I just dreamed of you.
Liar.
Is daddy home?
Yes, don't sneak in
through the balcony.
I'll ring the door bell.
Wake him.
At this hour?
What's so important?
I want something, baby.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, baby.
I'll be there in five.
Open the door.
Bye-
- Wake up your dad.
- Are you sure?
Dad, mom... wake up.
Sanju's here.
At 1 am?
Is everything okay?
Took him six months
to muster courage.
He'd said, once
his career kickstarted,
he'll ask for my hand.
Just the hand,
or all of you?
Dad, come on!
We'll ask for the
18 year-old scotch.
Will the old fart agree?
If he doesn't agree,
we grab and flee!
Hello, child.
How are you?
Before you ask for anything,
I have something for you.
Ten rupees?
My father's gift to me...
when I joined the Navy.
He said, "There are
two kinds of bills.“
"Real and fake."
When you tug at a real bill...
it won't tear.
You're starting your career.
Life will pull you left and right.
But, if you stay honest,
nothing can rip you apart.
My father's wisdom is now yours.
Homi, let him sit.
Sit.
Now, tell us.
What brings you here?
See, daddy.
The real reason we're here is...
we have... the midnight urge.
Can't control it anymore.
Look, we're weak with idioms.
Tell us clearly,
what's a "midnight urge"?
Midnight urge means...
desire...
need... want.
I'm 21 now.
It's a biological need.
As soon as midnight strikes...
the urge surges.
I need it now...
or I'm gonna explode!
But dad doesn't allow it.
He's orthodox.
So I sin in secret.
Once, I was enjoying an 18 year-old
on the terrace... dad walked in.
I told him frankly,
"Dad, I'm an adult."
"My friends do it every night.
Their parents never object."
He said, "Alright, have your
18 year-old. But don't hide."
"Do it openly on the dining table...
before the family.“
"And that too,
only once a month.“
Daddy, how will once a month
quench this thirst?
Now I frequent the illicit joints.
16, 18, 21
I grab whatever is available.
I park on a lonely stretch,
and indulge in the backseat.
Only fear is the cops.
They peek when
you're about to peak.
Auntie, try the backseat.
No fun!
You were a Navy Captain.
You must've tasted the best
on every shore.
Be kind, let us taste some
from your home.
- May we get one each?
- What!
- Okay, we'll share one.
- How dare you!
When daddy gets the urge,
you happily serve.
All we get is a "How dare you!“
Sorry, I've promised my friend.
I'm gonna grab one.
Stop!
- Soda or water?
- I'll help myself.
Sanju, you're drunk.
Just get out!
And return my papa's box.
Can I say something?
Your papa was wrong.
Life doesn't just pull you
left and right.
It also pulls you up and down.
I drank all night with my friends.
And returned home in the morning.
Good morning.
Good morning, dad.
I'm going for a jog.
Sit.
Sorry, sonny.
I yelled at you publicly.
I'm stressed...
couldn't control myself.
A request...
Please focus on your work.
Your mother should feel proud
when she sees your first film.
She may not be able
to see your next.
Why?
She has cancer
of the pancreas.
I'm taking her to New York.
Sloan Hospital.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
She hid it from you
so your work won't suffer.
She's been in pain all year.
But, acts fit in front of you.
Where are you?
In the dining...
Want some tea?
Half a cup.
Hide it.
Don't cry in her presence.
She's acting. So must you.
Make her happy.
Up so early?
Not bad.
Did you tell Sanju
we're off to New York?
What? Haven't shared the news?
Take a deep breath.
You're gonna be shocked.
I've been offered
a Hollywood film.
Now I'll mouth English dialogues.
My name is Bond.
James Bond.
I'm going to make him
an offer he can't refuse.
You talkin' to me?
I wish they had songs
like our films.
♪ This heart has lost its mate I
♪ No one knows
where my liver went 3'
A song here... a dance there...
and the Oscar's mine!
You shouldn't have retired!
Retired?
I still act... don't I?
Dad took mom to New York.
And I started spending
more time with God.
I feel your pain, man.
I was 18 when I lost my parents
in a car crash.
I was going to kill myself.
A fakir saved me.
He said, “The Lord who created pain,
also created a remedy.“
Here.
Put it under your tongue.
It'll melt away all pain.
He gets it from the Himalayas.
So it's expensive.
But, I'll send him the money.
The first time I did drugs,
was 'cause I was upset with dad.
The second time,
'cause mom was dying.
By the third time,
I was an addict.
Then I got the news...
mom was in a coma.
Dad summoned me to America.
I traveled with my sisters...
and 20 grams of cocaine.
Being caught at the airport,
would've meant...
20 years in prison...
even for my sisters.
But back then,
20 years in prison,
versus 20 grams of cocaine...
my choice was crystal clear.
I was so irresponsible...
that instead of spending
time with mom,
I'd smoke away in the fire exit.
Then one night,
walked into my life...
Mr. Kamlesh Kanhaiyalal Kapasi.
- What did you steal?
- Twins... twins... twins...
- O Lord Ganesha!
- This is Jesus' jurisdiction.
Lord Ganesha doesn't operate here.
What did you steal?
I'd gone to keep the idol inside.
I'm a fan of your parents.
Thought Lord Ganesha
will heal your mother.
Sorry, bro.
But, what's "Twins"?
Eggs... back home
we call them Twins.
Hope "The Twins“
haven't parted ways.
They are out of shape.
Come.
- Where?
- To get The Twins back in shape.
Hi-
- Two of us.
- Can't come in without a jacket.
Hey, bro. Nice jacket.
- How much?
-30.
What if I give you 50?
Take it, man.
Enjoy the show.
Ever seen a topless girl?
Of course, I have.
- Where? On TV?
- No... live.
My physics teacher, back home...
his mother slipped
in the bathroom.
I broke the door,
hauled her on my shoulder
and put her in the ambulance.
Stark naked... topless, bottomless.
How old was she?
90... no... 91.
I did see stuff...
I'm not naive.
- Ever had alcohol?
- Of course.
Hi... two vodkas, please.
Hey, sweetheart.
Can I have a private dance?
Okay.
For ten dollars.
I only have seven.
For seven, you get him.
There's a saying back home...
“ Jam-"3 am ham-ham.“
Translate that.
"Jam-jam" is money.
And “ham-ham“?
Sex.
Your jacket took away jam-jam,
I lost my bam-bam.
You owe me a blonde.
Cover me.
Don't! You'll land in prison.
Relax.
Sir, come with me.
It's all good, bro.
- Easy... easy.
- Call the cops.
Come on, man.
I didn't do anything.
Hold on, sir.
He's got cancer.
He will die in a week.
You think I was born yesterday?
See... I've got a hospital
visitor's pass.
I just got him from there.
His last wish... to do powder
and see a topless girl.
I gave him powder,
you give him girl.
- He'll die happy.
- He can't die here.
- Noble cause, brother!
- We don't want any trouble.
I'll take the body away.
No trouble.
Look... where would you
want to die?
In a hospital, hopeless
or in a club with a topless?
Go some place else.
Okay.
Let's go, brother.
These are emotionless people.
I'll get you a girl
more topless than here.
No... I want that girl!
- Call the cops.
- Run!
Get me a girl, brother.
More topless than there.
You promised, brother.
Stop joking.
We could've been arrested.
Noble cause, brother.
Please help. Get me a girl.
Your mom's in the hospital
and you're snorting?
Hey, Mr. Righteousness.
We've been friends
for just five minutes.
- Control your emotions.
- Friendship?
You aren't a good son!
How'II you be a good friend?
Get lost! I don't need a friend.
Hey, stop!
Okay, I'm sorry.
I just can't quit.
Alright... go!
If my friend was on drugs,
I wouldn't abandon him.
I'd thrash him till he quit.
Throw it.
- I'll quit... tomorrow.
- Now.
I promise... tomorrow.
- Let go my twins.
- Let go the powder.
- Twins first.
- Powder first.
- I'm desperate.
- It's the time to fight.
Say, “I'm a tiger."
- Now, To".
-'Ron"?
Once more.
I quit! I promise.
Never abandon me, Master.
Such words of wisdom...
Ron... "yam-3am barn-ham... tw'ms.
Guess what?
You didn't twist my twins...
but this.
I was seeking drugs in New York.
Instead, I found a friend.
Kamlesh Kanhaiyalal Kapasi.
They call me Kamli.
As Sex-spear has said,
"What's in a name?"
- Who?
- Sex-spear.
William...
- Sir, will you have snakes?
- Snakes?
Snakes... there are lots in the hole.
I'll get it, sir.
In his accent, snacks were "snakes“
and hall was “hole“.
He brought back our smiles.
And miraculously, his idol got
mom out of coma.
Ready, everyone?
Smile.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
At your film premiere,
I'll sit between father and son.
As you appear on screen,
I'll whistle.
Sorry!
At your wedding,
I'll dance on the table.
Warn Ruby
not to be embarrassed.
Mom didn't know
Ruby wasn't talking to me.
Mom didn't have
much time left.
I decided...
I'd apologise to Ruby's dad
and ask for her hand.
I love Ruby and I want to...
Hi, daddy.
I've come to apologize.
- I misbehaved that day.
- It's alright, child.
- A tipple often does that.
- No, daddy.
I wasn't just drunk...
I had also done cocaine.
Let me confess.
The next day I did LSD.
But I've been clean
for a month.
What will power!
Congratulations!
Thank you, daddy.
I'll go meet Ruby.
- Ruby.
- Wait.
Meet her on the 22nd...
at Hotel Sun and Sand.
With these flowers.
- What's on the 22nd?
- Wait...
That's for your parents.
And that's for you.
Write your name.
Ruby weds... who's this... Rustom?
Now, get out.
Bye-bye!
All this for a 10 rupee bill?
I'll glue it up.
I'm glad you tore it...
it led us to Rustom!
He's a doctor in New York.
Not a junkie like you... Out!
- Daddy, let me meet Ruby...
- Don't call me daddy.
- Papa?
- No papa.
- Okay... uncle?
- Don't call me uncle!
Then what should I call you...
Old fart?
Meet Ruby over my dead body.
Fine... I'll wait.
For what?
For you to die, old fart!
Rascal... scoundrel!
Get out!
I'll break your legs,
you swine.
Every addict looks for
an excuse to start again.
My excuse was Ruby.
♪ Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
Let's rendezvous A'
♪ To have you back,
Your old man I'll hack' ♪
♪ It's a win-win!
He gets heaven, I get you I
♪ The world has no heart
So leave it, old fart' ♪
4“ Goodbye, old man!
Just die, old man! ♪
♪ Your daughter... don't worry
Once you're dead... we'll marry' ♪
The sincerest prayers
are always granted.
The old man died
of a massive heart attack.
The news was tragic...
But, I won't lie...
I was ecstatic.
4' Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
Get set to rendezvous I'
♪ Ruby, Ruby, Ruby
You and I, we'll rendezvous I
This was my chance
to win back Ruby.
I had to show her, I was
more reliable than her fiancé.
A minor problem...
I was stoned.
Papa!
Don't abandon us, papa.
- Sanju, that's not papa.
- Wake up.
That's not papa!
Ha! I wondered how he'd
shrunk so much.
Is this our papa?
Papa... papa!
Why did you abandon us?
Wake up... try!
He isn't waking up.
Mummy, don't cry.
Your son-in-Iaw is with you.
Have you read the Holy Gita?
"Everything happens for the best."
Superb!
"Nothing we create...
so nothing should we mourn."
Did you create this old man?
Gave him birth?
Mummy, please...
Let her grieve...
When my puppy died,
I was bawling.
A full-grown husband's exit
deserves howling.
Take your time, mummy.
But remember,
only the body parishes.
The soul is eternal.
Away with this body.
Focus on the soul.
Baby, all okay?
Silly question!
Papa conked
and you say, "All okay?“
Stupid...
How shall we
dispose the body?
Bury it? Cremate it?
Papa.
God, that's not our papa.
Move that body.
It's freakin' confusing.
Move it.
So, Ruby...
What did I do?
No one can tell
it's secondhand.
A very fair price.
Five hundred dollars.
What's this?
Robbed a beggar?
Robbed a barber!
He cuts his own hair.
Puts three dollars
in the piggy bank.
- Who's gonna count this?
- Call from India... it's Sanju!
Awesome!
Sanju, perfect timing.
I'm buying my first car.
I need you here, bro.
Ruby's getting married.
Please... please come.
- You snorting again?
- No. I swear.
Please... come down.
Sanju... hello.
Sir, no need to count.
- The car will have to wait.
- Why?
Need to buy a ticket to India.
Sorry, sir.
Didn't want the car?
Why make me count?
Hello, Ruby.
I'm Kamlesh Kanhaiyalal Kapasi.
Sanju's friend.
Sir, can you go inside?
- Take a loo break.
- Why?
- Need to discuss a private matter.
- Come
Excuse me.
Whatever the matter,
say it in front of me.
It'll upset you.
Take a stroll outside.
Lovely weather.
No way.
We've got no secrets.
- I know everything about her.
- Really?
- Everything?
- Yes... everything.
Then name Ruby's
favorite animal.
Cat?
Dog?
You live in New York?
Ask any jeweler there...
They'll all say... “Penguin...
- Know why?
- Why?
For a month, Sanju hopped
from jeweler to jeweler.
For a wedding necklace
with a penguin pendant.
And finally got it!
But when he returned to India...
he discovered,
you were engaged.
He was shattered...
took to drugs again.
But yesterday, he braved up.
Flushed all the drugs
down the drain.
Swore never
to touch them again.
He prayed,
"Lord, bring Ruby back."
Sanju's back.
- Can you come back?
- Listen... it's too late.
The wedding date, venue...
it's all set.
Nothing changes,
except the groom.
Wedding cards... printed.
We'll put a "Sanju' sticker
over your name.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
I suggest you get out of here
before I smash your face.
Ruby, in America there'll be
no househelp.
You'll be cleaning,
mopping, washing...
Imagine washing
his sweaty underpants!
- Scumbag!
- I told you, you'd be upset.
Sanju will be at the Marriage Registrar's,
tomorrow 4 pm.
A penguin's not an animal.
It's a bird. Stupid man!
Mister, what's her favourite food?
Waffles. Sanju knows.
Her favourite film?
Mary Poppins.
Sanju knows.
You have no clue.
Ruby, 4 pm tomorrow.
The Marriage Registrar's office.
Where did you get money
for this?
Your wallet, cheques...
they're with me.
The wedding necklace...
What about it?
I sold it... to God.
- Where's he?
- He isn't home.
Woo-hoo!
Is this a joke?
I wait at the Registrar's office
and you get stoned here?
No sweat.
We'll marry tomorrow.
You'd flushed the drugs...
fished them out again?
I'm so stupid, I believed this.
Where's the wedding necklace?
Where is it?
Where's the bloody necklace?
The wedding necklace.
Please wait, Ruby.
I'm sorry...
Yuck.
He's not in his senses.
Won't remember a thing tomorrow!
I swear, he did buy
the wedding necklace.
He's too far gone...
and to expect you'll hang on
is not right.
You move on... I'm with him.
Kamlesh.
Yes, Ruby.
Don't ever tell him
what he did.
He'll be devastated.
Tell him...
that rotten Ruby,
never showed up.
May I come in, sir?
You've been drinking?
What I wanna say...
needs courage.
So I downed a couple.
Tell me.
Your son will die
before your wife!
He can't handle his life.
Why?
He sees you
nursing your ailing wife.
Any responsibility...
at home, film industry, society...
he sees you never shirk it.
You're a great man, sir.
And your son...
He's an ordinary guy.
No goals... no purpose in life.
He says,
"There are three things to life, bro."
"C... B... S...“
"Chew, brew and scr--"
Sorry... sorry.
The problem is...
you want him to be you!
He's buried...
buried under the weight
of your legacy!
He knows, however hard he toils,
he can never be as great.
So, he doesn't even try.
Feels a hero with
nobodies like me.
"Yo, Kamli...',
"Hey, Kamli...'
What should I do, Kamlesh?
Sir, you...
Just be his friend.
Sit with him.
Drink with him.
Use a few cuss words,
and say...
"Sonny, it's okay to be ordinary."
“You don't have to be Sun“ Dun.“
"It's okay to be Sanjay Dutt."
Please save him.
If he dies...
whom will I tell...
"Let go my twins."
Please, sir... save him.
Save him.
Good morning!
Morning, dad.
I showed the distributors
your film.
They went crazy...
"What a freakin' actor!"
Has mom seen the posters?
She's in hospital.
What happened?
She slipped into a coma again.
- I just met her yesterday!
- No... day before.
You've woken up
after two days. It's okay.
I've spoken to the doctors.
They recommend
a rehab centre in America.
Ready?
No... no.
Please don't send me there, dad.
Just a few days, sonny.
No... no.
Come out.
We won't send you anywhere.
I had one cigarette, you packed me off
to boarding school.
I was just six.
Couldn't even tie my Shoelaces.
I missed mom.
Sorry... sorry.
Please come out.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll stay with mom...
in the hospital!
Dad agreed... on one condition.
That I wouldn't do drugs
in the hospital.
And I promised.
I started spending
every night at the hospital.
I'd stare at mom for hours.
I'd hold her hand
and talk to her.
The premiere's next week.
Won't you come?
Get up, mom.
You gotta see me act.
You'll be proud, mom.
Mom.
Then one day...
I couldn't resist.
Sanju...
Dad...
Mom never saw my film.
She died three days
before the premiere.
She'd left a note...
"Even if I'm gone,
the show must go on.“
♪ They call me Rocky
Yes, my name is Rocky! I
♪ Friend and foe
To both I say hello' ♪
♪ They call me Rocky
Yes, my name is Rocky! I
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Excuse me, Mr. Dutt.
Is anyone sitting here?
Yes... my wife.
Sanju, congratulations!
Sanju, you'll be a film star!
I'll whistle...
I've been offered
a Hollywood film.
At your wedding,
I'll dance on the table.
Sanju.
What happened?
Mom opened her eyes
before she died.
She touched my head
to bless me.
But I was drugged, dad.
Not sure if it happened
or I was hallucinating...
I'm a mess, dad.
I can't tell what's real
and what's imaginary.
Are you real, dad?
Buddy, listen.
Is that Mr. Sunil Dutt?
- Is dad there?
- Yes.
Please save me, dad.
I want to quit drugs.
I want to live.
You'll be fine, sonny.
Dad got me to America
for treatment.
Mark the drugs
you've ever consumed.
I was given a list.
He was shocked
that I was still alive.
He has to be here for a while.
We'll look after him.
My treatment started.
As the drugs stopped,
my body rebelled.
A storm unleashed within.
Often I shivered
as if inside an ice slab.
Biting cold I couldn't bear.
Often my body was ablaze.
I was burning.
Bombs exploded in my head.
My pulse would spike up to 150.
My hands would tremor.
Depression... anxiety...
I couldn't bear it.
When you dance, the body generates
chemicals that heal.
Our motto... "Dance to recovery."
One, two, cha, cha, cha.
I couldn't take it.
I ran away.
I was desperate for drugs.
Hey, bro!
- Can I get a gram?
- Money. bro?
I'll give you tomorrow.
Hang off, man.
- Please, bro?
- Sorry, I'm broke.
A little bit, man.
The only person
who'd lend me money...
was 1500 miles away,
in New York.
Like a madman,
I took off for New York... on foot.
Can I get a lift?
Hop on.
I realized the power of attire.
When the clothes were clean,
I got rides.
When dirty... alms.
Both served well.
A few days of begging,
earned me a bus ticket.
In 12 days, I was in New York.
Hi, bro.
I'll have one drink
and go back.
Never had a drink with you.
Just one and I'll go away.
I'll be okay, dad.
When your mom was in hospital...
she'd send these recordings.
Ever listened to them?
Silly piglet, how are you?
Remember, when angry,
I'd call you “piglet"?
And you'd say, "Why are you
calling your husband names?"
“If I'm a piglet,
my father's the swim!“
Hello, Sanju.
This is Mr. Swine.
- Working hard?
- Don't worry about me.
I won't die before
I see your film.
I'm by your side.
Steadfast!
Like a Master said,
♪ Wherever you go, I
♪ my shadow will follow I
Tell him your theory
of the Masters.
Before the movies,
I was a radio jockey.
I encountered thousands of songs
with beautiful, deep verses.
I accepted those songwriters
as my Masters.
When in trouble, I say,
"Guide me, 0 Master."
And a song comes to rescue.
So which Master
can help Sanju?
Majrooh Sultanpuri.
Presenting from Sloan Hospital...
Water, please.
Dad, it's the tape...
Here's some water.
Please rest.
What about the song?
Tomorrow, I promise!
Rest now.
Which song was it, dad?
♪ Don't you ever stop, 3"
♪ with your head hung in despair :
♪ After this woeful walk over thorns, 4“
♪ you will enjoy
the embrace of blossoms' ♪
♪ Wanderer, O wanderer A“
♪ 0 Wanderer... J“
♪ Break every shackle, 4“
♪ Smith each into a sword :
♪ Fight every battle I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
♪ You may be shattered A“
♪ Show 'em you ain't battered 4“
♪ Hope still simmers in your soul! 4“
♪ When your spirit you wield a“
♪ The heavens will yield 4“
♪ Lead you unfettered to your goal I
♪ If by miseries you're hunted a“
♪ If your weapons are blunted a“
J“ Stop failure's advances
with those broken lances J“
♪ Climb every mountain I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
♪ Strive, do not bow down' ♪
♪ Attain what you seek! 4“
♪ Climb every mountain I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
♪ Strive, do not bow down' ♪
♪ Attain what you seek! 4“
A 14-day loo break!
That's a world record.
Welcome back.
♪ Take by the scruff of the neck 4“
♪ The dark clouds of misery 4“
♪ Rattle 'em till they reveal
the abode of Victory' ♪
♪ With the stars you'll be crowned 4“
♪ The sky, your playground A“
♪ Break away from the herd r
♪ Fortune will be yours
that so far frowned A“
J“ Stop failure's advances
with those broken lances J“
♪ Climb every mountain I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
♪ Strive, do not bow down' ♪
♪ Attain what you seek! 4“
♪ Climb every mountain I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
♪ Strive, do not bow down' ♪
♪ Attain what you seek! 4“
♪ Fight every battle I
♪ Conquer every peak 4“
He's off drugs for 18 months.
Wear sunglasses...
our boy is glowing like a floodlight.
Thank you, Kamlesh.
As your Sex-spear says,
"AII's well that ends well."
Take the bags.
The taximeter's on.
Hurry up.
It's not "the end“ yet.
The doctor warned,
he could relapse.
If he starts again, he'll die.
Please keep him away
from bad company.
Thank you, son.
Thank you.
Dad, you carry on.
I'll join you.
Dad, stop him.
For how long can we stop him?
Now he must fight
his own battles. Let's go.
I thought you wouldn't meet me.
How could I not?
I thought of you everyday
the past 18 months.
What an honor!
I have a special
welcome-back gift.
Haven't seen
such fine stuff in 18 years.
Just to celebrate your return.
Normally, I don't share
such exclusive stuff with anyone.
To your health.
Cheers!
Bro, that's my dose.
It's potent.
Too strong for you.
Doesn't such potent stuff
ruin your health?
Your parents must've
gifted you strong genes.
How are they?
They're fine...
by the grace of God.
Amazing! They're reborn
after the car crash?
Glucose powder suits me fine.
Now try that!
I cracked it!
You took glucose
and fed me drugs.
You aren't an addict...
you're a peddler!
Posed as a friend
for my money.
Bro, I'll return your money.
Great idea!
Return those five years
which I was too numb to feel.
My father hasn't slept in five years.
Return that lost sleep.
I lost Ruby.
Can you get her back?
My sisters stopped smiling.
Return that smile.
Can you? You peddler!
My real gods.
And one more.
Lord Ganesha, MD.
He's lived with me
in prison, too.
You're crying?
Was the story so bad?
Will you write it?
Yes, I'll write it.
Thank you.
So, I'll call you on Sunday.
We'll continue then.
Winnie, do you have a boyfriend?
- Yes. Why?
- Tell him, he's very lucky.
'Cause I'm intelligent
and good looking?
-'Cause I'm going to prison.
- Stop it.
Ignore him.
When he's happy
he blabbers.
He's harmless.
Hello?
Hello, this is Winnie.
Hello, mighty writer.
Hello... “God...
So, you met the terrorist.
Also figured why you're
desperate to stop me.
Once a drug-peddler,
now a big builder.
He fooled you.
He's an actor.
Even his lies seem true.
Ask him why
his best friend, Kamlesh...
hasn't spoken to him
in 20 years.
Ask him.
Hello.
Is that Mr. Kamlesh?
- Yeah.
- Hi, this is Winnie Diaz.
I'm a writer.
I'm writing a book
on your friend, Sanjay Dutt...
He's not my friend.
But he says,
"Kamli is my best friend."
In a past life.
Then in this life, why are you
glued to the TV watching his news?
Hello?
Excuse me?
Hi, I'm Winnie.
- You called from India?
- Right. And you hung up.
So, I'm here.
Look, I promise, I won't even
mention you in the book.
- Shall we sit somewhere?
- Sure.
I know a great place.
I think we should go there.
Where?
Head North and take a left
after 100 metres.
Follow Aunt Annie.
Remember this place?
He loves you.
Why did you cut off ties?
Do you know what RDX is?
An explosive. It was used
in the Mumbai bomb blasts.
And where was it stored?
In a truck parked
at Sanjay Dutt's house.
He knew Mumbai would
be bombed, but kept mum.
- Who told you?
- The man who loved him the most.
Who?
Sun“ Du“... h'vs father.
Tell me your side of the story.
If he's a terrorist,
I'll scrap the book.
I flew 12000 kms
just to meet you.
And I wasted 12 years
of my life with him.
No more time for him.
He's the one with no time.
He's off to prison.
Know what he's taking along?
This story has four characters.
San'yay Du“, Sun“ Du“...
I, and the Babri mosque.
Babri mosque was demolished
on 6th December, 1992.
Riots burned the country.
Mr. Dutt was then
a Member of Parliament.
He'd stopped making films.
All his time was spent
sewing people.
When riots erupted
in his constituency,
Muslim homes were burnt...
he plunged into relief work.
And his son, unconcerned...
lived in his own world.
He was no longer the drug-addict.
He reigned as an A-list film star
those 12 years.
As for me... my IT business
was prospering.
I made tons of money.
But, had one grouse...
I was still a virgin.
Then I met a girl, Pinky.
I flew every weekend to Mumbai,
hoping to get lucky.
Excuse me, sir.
The result...
I was jetlagged 24/7.
Still on the runway?
Not taken off?
Sir, we've landed.
Landed?
This time, Sanju had
invited Pinky for dinner.
The mission...
to make sure I score.
Pinky loves pink.
She asked for a pink t-shirt.
So you bought the store?
Superb!
Control... you're drinking too much!
Need courage
to open my account.
Account! Which bank?
My aunt's cousin is a banker.
You'll be done in a jiffy.
- You need an account, too?
- No, I have many accounts.
What's all this?
All for you.
This pink t-shirt, sweater,
“Mar-tee...
This pink nightie... just for you!
Try it.
No, I'll stick to the t-shirt.
Thank you, Kamlesh.
One moment.
Do you know why
nighties are called nighties?
Why?
'Cause they are worn at night.
Scriptures say...
hour and attire must match.
Give.
I've got her in the nightie.
- Your job... get her out of it.
- Done!
Don't overdrink...
or there'“ be no ham-ham.
I'm out of here.
Freshen up.
- I'll change, too.
- All the best.
♪ On a journey to the moon' ♪
♪ Let's dance, let's swoon :
♪ It's one night's delight 4“
♪ Then our paths will divide r
♪ On a journey to the moon' ♪
♪ Let's dance, let's swoon :
♪ Just one night's delight a“
♪ Come, set me alight a“
Kamli...
Kamli, wake up.
Get up.
Time for bam-bam.
Wake up.
You're a tiger.
Roar!
Come on.
♪ You are no saint I'
♪ Noramll'
♪ It's one night's delight 4“
♪ Let's not be uptight a“
♪ On a journey to the moon' ♪
♪ Let's dance, let's swoon :
♪ Just one night's delight a“
♪ Come, set me alight a“
Baby, you ready?
Have breakfast, Kamli.
- You're meeting some girls today.
- I have a girlfriend.
Forget her.
She's a floozy.
- Shush... she'll hear you.
- She's gone.
You were very irresponsible last night!
You passed out and
I had to bam-bam...
and then wrap up
your pink store.
Chill... I'll set it up
for the next attempt.
Tell me, you're lying.
I was checking
her loyalty towards you.
I held her hand,
she rubbed it with her thumb.
That's all she does.
Never goes further.
With me, she went further, bro.
I said, "Nightie."
She took it off?
It was clear,
she can't be my sister-in-Iaw.
No one cheats
on my best friend!
It was guilt free bam-bam.
What's her name?
You slept with her
and don't know her name?
Name after the game?
Bad manners!
You swine!
I've unveiled her true colors.
You should be grateful.
Hey, Sanju.
Your pop's buddying up
to the Muslims.
- Drill sense into him.
- Who the hell...?
You half-Muslim!
Your sister is sizzling hot.
Shall I get her raped?
Hey!
It's a stone.
Could've been a grenade.
Your pop's loading trucks
with relief material, right?
- I'll bump him off.
- HelloI
- Let's get out of here.
- We've got a threat call.
You wake up late.
I've already got five.
Barking dogs seldom bite.
Out here you can be shot.
We'll shield him.
We'll take the bullet.
We'll defend Mr. Dutt
till our last breath.
With that toy?
Does it even work?
Yes, it does.
When did you last fire it?
World War II?
Stop it, Sanju.
Hurry... load the truck.
Kamli, reason with dad.
He never listens to me.
Look at him,
and then at yourself.
He helps strangers.
While you bam-bam
your best friend's girl.
Hi! This is Kamlesh.
Sorry, I'm not home.
Please leave a message.
Hey Kamli,
remember the strip club?
I lost out on a chick
for your jacket.
Remember,
you owed me a blonde.
Let's say Pinky is the blonds...
we're square!
I'm in New York on the 22nd.
I'll wait outside the same club.
Wear that red jacket...
and I'll know you've forgiven me.
I love you, bro.
Kamli, please forgive me.
Kamli...
They say, "Life is what happens
when you're making other plans."
While he was planning his trip...
life had other plans.
Twelve bombs exploded that day.
250 people died.
800 were injured.
Police investigations
revealed a name...
Tiger Memon.
In the riots following
the Babri mosque demolition,
Tiger Memon's office
was burnt down.
He struck back.
As the truth unfolded,
many were arrested.
Kamlesh, read the news?
No... why?
Your friend was involved
in the Bombay bomb blasts.
He's been arrested.
He had an AK-56 rifle.
Did you possess an AK-56 rifle?
No, sir.
Did you possess an AK-56?
I'll tell you, sir.
I'll tell you everything.
But, don't tell dad.
- Babu?
- Kamli.
I knew you'd come.
I'm glad.
Sir, I'm sure
the AK-56 charges are bogus.
Here's Sanju's confession.
Read it.
Dad would send relief material
to riot victims.
Majority of them... Muslim.
Some people didn't approve.
They thought dad was pro-Muslim.
That's when the threats started.
To murder us...
and rape my sisters.
I was terrified.
Then there were
two attacks on dad.
I requested special protection,
but was denied.
I feared a mob attack any time.
Han“ and Sam“,
producers of my mm...
suggested I keep an assault rifle,
for protection.
In January, Samir, Hanif
and Abu Salem came home.
They gave me three rifles
and some bullets,
which I kept in my car.
Soon, I panicked.
I'll keep only one rifle...
till the riots and.
Please take away the rest.
They came back two days later.
I returned two rifles.
Kept one rifle and 250 bullets.
On 2nd April, I went to Mauritius
for a film shoot.
I got news of Hanif
and Samir's arrest.
I feared they'd rat me out.
I called my friend, Yusuf Nulwala.
Yusuf, go to my house.
Go to my room.
You'll find a black bag.
There's some stuff in it.
Destroy it.
Then one day, dad called.
The papers say,
you possess an AK-56 rifle.
AK-56? No, dad!
I've got you a meeting
with the Police Commissioner.
Come to Bombay.
Dad informed the cops
about my arrival,
and assured them he'll get me
to the police station.
But...
Mr. Sanjay Dutt.
Boarding pass.
Deliver the luggage to his father.
Come with me.
- What's the problem, officer?
- Come.
Sir, what happened?
Get in.
Last time, we won the fight
against drugs.
But this time, the battle
will be tougher.
- I'll need you, son.
- I'm not going anywhere, sir.
The "snakes“ are in the “hole“.
Grab a bite.
Sleep in Sanju's room.
I'll be here for a while.
Switch off the fan.
Sir, it's hot.
He sleeps without a fan, too.
For security reasons,
Sanju was kept in isolation
in a windowless cell.
His only companions... ants.
It's been seven days, soldiers.
When will I get bail?
Tell me.
Please...
Sir, the pot is overflowing.
Sir.
Please help!
Help!
He suffered inside prison
and his dad, outside.
Look... the terrorist's pop.
Come.
Give him a shave.
You're done.
Come... wash your face.
You speak English!
I've done my Masters.
Even had a bank job.
How'd you land here?
My wife cheated on me.
I killed her!
Chopped her into pieces,
stuffed her in a bag and left it
on along distance train.
A porter saw me...
and here I am.
- I'll skip the shave.
- Why?
Need a beard for my next film.
I'm playing Santa Claus.
He had a big beard.
I've to let it grow.
Hello! This is Sunil Dutt.
A moment.
Mr. Butt.
Sir, the minister's bathing.
Morning, noon and evening?
He's always in the bath!
Health reasons, sir.
He has a fungal infection
on his thigh.
I'll pass on your message.
Everyone avoided Mr. Dutt.
Terror charges being stigmatic,
no one wanted any involvement.
Partner, we've been
roomies for 180 days.
That's longer than any girl
I've been with.
Supreme Court will hear
my bail petition today.
Which means I'm a free bird.
I'll miss you.
- Your bail's been rejected.
- What?
Bail is always tough
in the Terror Act.
Sir...
Dad, what's up with my bail?
Don't worry, sonny.
We're going to the Supreme Court.
You get better.
Why are you lying?
I know my bail's rejected.
I've been in for six months.
You know the Prime Minister...
the President... speak to them.
What have I done?
Killed anyone? Fire a bullet?
Just kept a gun,
for your protection!
My protection?
I'd rather you shot me
with that gun!
Sir...
He'll never appreciate me.
Praises my sisters all the time...
"Ace! Well played!“
I want to die.
Please help me.
There's cyanide in the tea.
Drink up.
Vodka in the tea?
Now chill!
Don't blabber about dying.
Think of your dad!
He strives from dawn to dusk
for your bail.
Begs lawyers, politicians, cops...
Sleeps on the floor
'cause you have no bad.
Doesn't use the fan
'cause you don't have one.
People call him,
"Terrorist's pop."
You've twisted his twins...
spare him your suicide!
Fight! You'll definitely get bail.
Once out of prison...
get a sexy girlfriend.
I'll get you drunk
and bam-bam her!
Then, we're even.
"I want to die."
Enough! You're a tiger.
"Rorr'... come on.
“Rom.“
He spent 452 days in prison.
The Supreme Court finally
granted him bail.
But his name was now
synonymous with the word...
Terrorist!
The public and the press
hated him.
He was being tried
under the Terror Act...
he feared his bail
would be canceled.
His only hope...
political intervention.
An influential minister in the capital
agreed to meet him.
Hello, sir.
Come... sit.
How's daddy?
He has a fever.
Very good...
What brings you here?
Sir, I'll be honest.
I did possess a gun.
I should be tried
under the Arms Act.
But they've slapped me
with the Terror Act.
If I was involved
in the bomb blasts,
would I return to India?
I could've run away
from Mauritius.
Taken asylum in another country.
- He's dozed off!
- Speak louder.
Sir, I got a gun because
I feared a mob attack.
If the minister really slept
or play acted to avoid us...
is still a mystery.
How's daddy?
- He has a fever.
- Very good...
What brings you here?
Our legs brought us here...
we'll go back swimming.
Very good...
Let me know if I can help.
It was evident,
we were on our own.
I decided... till Sanju was cleared
of terror charges,
I'd be by his side.
But, the next day...
[RDX truck at Dutt house?]
Babu, where's Sanju?
In the preview theatre.
No one goes in.
Mr. Dutt's orders.
Tell the Court... you knew about
the bomb blast conspiracy.
Kamlesh...
please wait outside.
Where are you going?
FBI raided my office.
Why?
[RDX truck at Dutt house?]
What's that got to do
with the FBI?
My company works with
the American government.
Now they'll investigate
our association.
Terror charges freak them out.
Sorry, buddy.
I've put you through all this...
- Call me when you get there.
- No... my phone will be tapped.
We must disconnect
for a few years.
Don't worry. I understand.
Go...
Hey, Kamli. You're a tiger.
Let's go.
Bye!
First time ever...
I lied to Sanju.
I can be friends with an addict.
Even with a guy
who slept with my girl.
But with a terrorist?
I'm no fool!
Every time I drink,
I miss him...
yearn to call him.
Then I remind myself...
there was a truck full of RDX
at his house.
He's a bloody terrorist!
Are we done?
Mail from Winnie.
Where's she?
America.
She won't write the book.
Sanjay Dutt was given 30 days
to surrender.
That time is over.
He's on his way to prison.
Clothes off.
Raise your hands.
Turn.
Bend.
Cough.
Harder.
You dropped Sanju's story for a book
on museums? How boring!
- Museums don't lie.
- Nor did Sanju.
But a news report
became your gospel truth.
Here.
What's this?
Prison has a community radio
for prisoners' reform.
Sanju hosts a show.
He wants you to hear
this episode.
Took great pains
to smuggle it out.
Your coffee...
My number.
You'll need it after you're done.
Howdy, Yerwada!
This is your buddy, Sanju!
Today's topic... newspapers.
There were no newspapers
400 years ago.
News traveled word of mouth.
Then, someone printed
the first newspaper.
Soon, selling news
became big business.
Today, India has 105,437
registered publications,
thousands of radio stations,
TV channels and the internet.
And they're in a rat race...
fighting for readership.
More readers means
more money from ads.
And how do you lure readers?
With the truth?
No!
With news that's spicy!
And how do you that?
Easy! With a question mark.
When I was on bail,
these question marks were on my tail.
[Sanju in a brawl?]
[Feud in Dutt family?]
[Sanju bankrupt?]
[Sanju's film shelved?]
[Sanju sozzled?]
Dad decided to fight back.
Mr. Dutt, what a surprise!
How many pages
does your paper have?
Twenty four.
Cut it down to eight.
Then you won't need
fake news to fill pages.
Please come.
If our reportage
bothers you, sue us.
How can I fight you?
You have James Bond with you.
James Bond?
James Bond has a license to kill.
He has legal immunity.
Similarly, you have
these question marks.
In Court, you'll state,
"This isn't confirmed news.“
"Just speculation.
Don't miss the question mark."
"According to sources...
According to rumors...“
"It has been alleged..."
These are your James Bond!
Bandu Boss, I'll be there.
Tell me when.
Last day of Ganesha festival.
Done.
Your son graces events
by gangsters.
Cops have 60 such phone taps.
He's not focused on work.
His last 12 films tanked.
His bail can be revoked.
In short... he's finished!
Then state that with conviction!
Put a full stop.
Not a question mark.
[Not finished]
Mr. Editor, don't write
his obituary yet.
My son will rise again!
I'll prove you wrong.
I'm around... so are you.
We'll meet again.
A lousy editor writing me off
was unacceptable to dad.
He resolved to get my life
back on track.
If you hobnob with gangsters,
won't the press hound you?
Gangster? Who, dad?
Bandu Boss.
Aren't you attending his event?
What's the option?
They're dangerous.
Don't go.
They'll kill me...
They shot Gulshan Kumar.
Fired at Rakesh Roshan.
Don't go, sonny.
If the snoopy press
ensures my safety... I won't go.
Why are we here, dad?
When I was to marry your mom,
a notorious don...
Mastan, got livid.
“Nargis is the pride
of the Muslim community."
"If a Hindu marries her,
we'll slaughter him."
I called him...
"Let's meet... and talk."
He agreed.
1 am... right here.
- You came here alone?
- No.
My Master was with me.
- Which one?
- Sahir Ludhianvi.
I reached an hour earlier.
I let Sahir's song
play in my mind on loop.
When the don arrived,
I said, "I love Nargis deeply.“
"I want to marry her."
"And I'll keep her happy forever."
"If to love someone is wrong,
shoot me.“
"If right... give me a hug."
On our wedding day,
the biggest bouquet...
came from Mastan!
- What song was it, dad?
- Will you sing it?
Sing along with me.
♪ Vicious or vile, let no power I'
♪ Ever let you cower J"
- Dad, not here.
- Come on, catch the beat.
♪ Vicious or vile, let no power I'
♪ Ever let you cower J"
♪ Look evil in the eye,
Your head held high x
♪ So what if this
be your last breath? r
J" Rejoice, you never died
before your death! I
Sonny, go...
let Bandu Boss have it.
He'll never call again.
J“ Break every shackle,
Smith each into a sword I
I Fight every battle
Conquer every peak I
Stop!
Hey, the great Sanju!
Boss, look who's here.
The star!
Welcome!
No calendar at home?
You're ten days early!
Welcome... sit.
May I speak in private?
In private?
They're family.
Close your ears.
We reject condoms
and eject large families.
Now tell me...
I can't attend the Ganesha festival.
Are you sloshed?
I've already announced
to the world.
My parents are joining, too.
I too, have a father.
He disapproves.
He approves when you meet
the gangs in Dubai?
Did I have a choice?
I was scared.
You ain't scared of me?
Boys... show him fear.
Wanna see your brains?
Blow them out, but first...
hear me out.
If I attend your event,
the press will print...
"Sanju-Gangsters Romance."
If I don't attend,
"Gang kills Sanju."
Either ways,
it'll make headlines.
But, the second headline
won't shame my dad.
He'll cry gallons.
But when he faces the world,
his head will be held high.
Not bowed down in shame.
If this makes sense... fine.
If not... shoot me.
- Boss...
- Shut up!
I'll leave now.
If I've overstepped...
I'm sorry.
Dad was right.
Bandu Boss never called.
But he showed up!
Hey... out!
It's a family tradition.
No murders during
the Ganesha fest.
Decided to kill you
after the fest.
These ten days,
I only thought of you.
You risked life to keep
your dad's head unbowed.
Who does such a stupid thing?
Head, a few degrees up or down,
what bloody difference?
I prayed to the Lord for you.
Told Him... "He's one gutsy guy."
"Help him.
Get his charges dropped."
The Lord said,
“Bandu Boss... done!“
Here are the offerings.
Success guaranteed!
- Lord Ganesha...
- Glory be thine!
Be thine...
Stay in touch.
Let's go.
Get Bandu Boss teary-eyed often.
Free sweets will follow.
Sir, it's the director.
Yes, bro.
Where are you?
We are ready to shoot.
Insane traffic...
on the highway.
A truck hit a car.
Hey, move that taxi.
Listen... listen.
I've called the Iandline.
Landline's for all and sundry.
You're my bro...
always call on my cell.
We missed the sunrise shot.
Shoot it at sunset.
The audience won't know shit.
Now hang up
or we'll miss the sunset.
Time to introduce you
to Master no. 2.
He'll teach you to respect work.
If you keep missing
sunrise shoots...
the sun will set on your career.
Do good work and the press
will change its opinion, too.
Good work?
With such trashy scripts.
Here...
Kinky King, Rowdy Romeo...
Munnabhai MBBS,
Punky Prince...
Aamir and Shah Rukh
grab the best.
- Do you read these scripts?
- Cover to cover.
All read and rejected.
Munnabhai MBBS...
read this one?
- I did.
- What's the story?
It's trash!
There's a hospital...
where a patient
gets murdered... everyday!
Then... kidneys are stolen.
It's a horror story.
I need a family film.
The draft I read
has no murders.
Why did you read it?
I'm playing your father
in this film.
I'll set up Master no.2
in your car.
Listen to the song on loop
at full volume.
Okay?
♪ If you shirk from work' ♪
♪ You get no perk, you jerk I'
Turn it off!
Mr. Dutt's order... play this song
the whole month.
And check that you lip sync.
♪ If you shirk from work' ♪
I am singing.
♪ You get no perk, you jerk I'
J" If duties you duck
You land up in muck I
a“ On bankruptcy's brink
Not a dime for a drink 4“
♪ Toil hard buddy
Listen to your daddy I
- Lip sync fine?
- Yes.
Report to dad.
Bloody snitch!
Dad signed this film
after a 12 year gap,
just to discipline me.
Must an ER patient
fill an admit form?
He was always punctual
on the sets.
- Has the hero arrived?
- Yes, sir.
So I too, had to be on time.
Shall we rehearse?
Just for the shot, dad!
Hey, pal.
No fear, I'm here!
You lied to me shamelessly
for 10 years.
Scene 79, page 175.
Now that your father's proud,
why'd you fret?
That's my dialogue.
I'm playing the father.
But, father...
I couldn't become a doctor.
Again.
You lied to me shamelessly
for 10 years.
Now that your father's proud,
why'd you fret?
Once again?
Prison time was
easier than this.
Dad's discipline roasted me.
But, I won't ever forget...
that "magic hug" scene.
Your mom gets a thousand hugs.
Spare one for dad.
Neither of us heard it
when the director called, "Cut!"
We were weeping.
It was a lifetime since
we had hugged.
And the award for the best actor,
male, in a comic role goes to...
of course...
Sanjay Dutt for Munnabhai MBBS.
Go on, sonny.
Mr. Dutt, didn't I tell you...
“Sanju will be back."
Really? Did you?
Didn't I?
- I told... someone.
- Who?
Our Associate Editor.
Told him to print,
"Sanju will be back."
He must've forgotten.
Make it tomorrow's headline...
“Sanjay Dutt is back."
Without a question mark.
Look... Munnabhai's pop!
Look... the terrorist's pop!
What happened, dad?
It's the second time
you've made me cry with joy.
The first time dad cried with joy
was in our preview theater.
That day a headline read,
"RDX truck at Dutt house.“
Tell the judge... you knew about
the bomb blast conspiracy.
The first time dad cried with joy
was in our preview theater.
That day a headline read,
"RDX truck at Dutt house.“
But that's another episode.
I'll save it for another day.
Let's get back to dad.
I got another chance
to make dad happy.
Dad was being honored
at a Consulate dinner.
You guys never praise me.
So, here I am... as chief guest.
Dad was unaware, his son would
sing his praises tonight!
I was to make
the introduction speech.
Sir, could you come with me?
- Sir, please.
- Yes.
Dad, I'll be back.
Sir... a minor problem.
Today's headline said, "Blast suspect
to attend diplomatic event."
The Embassy wanted you
off the guest list.
We said, “That would be rude.“
"We'll seat him
away from the diplomats.“
That might be the best solution
for everybody.
Please cooperate, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please take your seats.
Sir, please.
Thank you.
My speech... when's that?
It's canceled.
I'm sorry.
I welcome you to our
Global Foundation Charity dinner.
We'd like to thank you
for joining us tonight...
in support of this noble cause.
Sonny, what's the problem?
I'm right here.
Read out your speech.
I wanted everyone to hear it.
They had no right to deny me.
Learn to ignore such people.
Tlme for Master no.3.
I'll set the song in your car.
Anand Bakshi.
He'll teach you
to deal with humiliation. Okay?
Sanju...
Hey, pal...
No fear, I'm here!
Go, sleep.
Wish I'd read him the speech...
for... the next morning,
he didn't wake up.
If life had a rewind button...
I'd go back and
read him the speech!
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Hi, dad.
Today, I'll try the impossible...
an attempt to thank dad.
In the past,
I never found the words.
To define what dad's done for me...
every word fell short.
1981...
a wife dying in the hospital,
a son destroyed by drugs.
Dad fought... all alone.
He's the reason I'm alive.
Tried to thank him then...
couldn't find the words.
Dad walked long peace marches...
from Hiroshima to Nagasaki...
Mumbai to Amritsar.
But none wore off his shoes
as much as...
the jostle between
courts and cops.
Legal costs forced
dad to sell his house.
Not once did he complain!
Wanted to thank him then...
couldn't find the words.
Now, after a lifetime...
I've found the words.
You deserved a better son, dad.
One who'd support you...
not be a burden.
One known for his honesty,
not his travesties.
One more like you...
and less like me.
But know what, dad?
That son would've
never loved you as much...
as this no-good sonny does!
I could never say it...
but you're my hero, dad.
You're my strength,
my solace,
my pride.
You're my world, dad.
Love you, sonny.
Love you, dad.
Had dad lived another year,
he'd have witnessed
what he yearned for.
Mr. Sanjay Dutt,
I want to go on record and say,
I do not find you to be a terrorist.
But, you're convicted
under the Arms Act for six years.
I was acquitted
from the Terror Act.
I got six years
under the Arms Act.
The judge clearly said...
I was not a terrorist.
But, the next morning...
no headline read
"Dutt not a terrorist.“
All said... "Dutt gets
six years in the blast case.“
Till date, I'm branded a terrorist.
I still feel insulted.
Master no.3 was to teach me
to deal with insults.
But with dad's death,
that song remains a mystery.
If you can crack that song,
do tell.
Until tomorrow...
Sanju says, "Adios, amigos."
Hello.
I want to meet Sanju.
How are you?
They don't let me step out,
the rest is fine.
Yeah. Sticklers for rules!
Weren't letting me in, either.
Missing me?
Boyfriend vamoosed?
Don't try this on me.
I'm no Pinky.
- You met Kamli?
- Yes.
In your recording, you say...
on the day the RDX news appeared,
your dad cried with joy.
Yes.
Kamlesh has a different version.
When he came
to the preview theater,
your dad was urging you
to confess in court...
that you knew about
the bomb blasts conspiracy.
The moron!
Get Kamli here.
- Tell me about it.
- No. I'll tell him directly.
It's hard to get permission.
Remember this number... 88.0.
- What's that?
- A radio frequency.
There's an FM mic
in our studio.
Park close to the prison walls
and tune in.
Kamlesh won't come.
Tell him... 6th June.
He won't refuse.
6th June?
It's his dad's birthday.
Bloody emotional blackmailer!
Will you come?
Please.
Howdy, Yerwada!
This is your buddy, Sanju!
Today's topic... friendship.
My best friend was Kamli
Great guy.
But fall prey to drugs.
No... not the psychotropic drugs.
But the ones that are slid
under our doors... daily.
We have them with
our morning tea.
Drugs called... "News".
These drugs are sold on TV, too.
Haven't you heard those
cacophonous debates...
that numb our minds?
Courts take years
to just understand a case.
But these panelists
pass verdicts in an hour.
Back then, a headline said...
"RDX truck at Dutt house."
It was fake news.
No cop, no prosecutor,
no Witness ever said...
there was a truck
with RDX at my house.
So, why this headline?
During riots, a truck with relief material
was parked at our house.
Some jerk spread a rumor
it had RDX.
And a journo printed
this spicy news.
Read my Supreme Court judgment.
I was never accused
of possessing RDX!
But which journo bothers
with facts?
All they want is
"Breaking News!"
This headline worked like a drug.
In Kamli's head,
I morphed into a terrorist.
He put a full-stop
to our friendship.
Didn't even notice...
the headline had a question mark!
[RDX truck at Dutt house?]
This news shattered Dad.
In desperation,
he brought in a lawyer.
- What's this?
- Your ticket to freedom.
Sign and turn approver.
- Approver?
- Government witness.
Dad?
Tell the Court... you knew about
the bomb blast conspiracy.
Kamlesh, please wait outside.
I knew nothing about
the bomb blasts.
But tell the Court... you knew.
Tell them who got the RDX...
who made the bombs...
Who planted them...
- I know nothing!
- I'll give you the names.
You help the State
with missing links.
In return, the State
will let you go soot-free.
- I'll be branded a terrorist.
- You're already branded.
It's a lie, a sign
will make it the truth.
The country will spit on me.
Leave the country.
London, Kenya... pick a place.
Get a new life.
And dad? My sisters?
Dad, heard that?
Don't worry about us.
Leave the country.
Sir, I don't have a law degree.
In fact, I'm a college dropout.
But I know, this is rotten advice.
I brand him "Terrorist's pop'
and run away?
People will hate dad.
His life's work... respect...
all down the drain!
- Listen to me...
- You listen to me.
Get lost!
You might be a great lawyer...
but with a broken nose,
you'll look like a clown.
- Is this any way to behave?
- No, sir.
Let me do it the right way.
You're going to pay for this.
You're going to pay for this!
I'm not a terrorist.
What happened, dad?
Ace, sonny!
Well played.
For the first time,
my father cried with joy.
That day, I was his hero.
The same day, I turned
villain for my friend.
Hey, Kamli.
Hope you can hear me.
When I come out...
meet me once, buddy.
If you do, I'll be happy.
If you don't...
I'll live with your fond memories...
I'll remember, the first nude girl
my friend saw was 91.
I'll remember, he perked me up
with vodka-infused tea.
And to meet me
he bought an air-ticket...
with the pennies saved
for his first car.
Hey, Kamli.
We're getting old, bro.
Give me one last hug.
Tiger, this one's for you.
♪ On the pathway of time,
At this band 1'
♪ I am glad I met such a friend' ♪
J" Scars are healed
And sorrows end I
J" Just at the thought
I have such a friend I
♪ On the pathway of time,
At this band 1'
♪ I am lucky to find such a friend I'
Sanju, take care.
Sanju... here...
A picture please!
Sanju!
Did you marry?
Opened your account?
Bam-bam without marriage?
At 80, we'll go to the holy river
to wash our sins.
If I don't sin, what'll I wash?
My underwear?
- One pic, please!
- Let's go.
Look here.
The book?
Master no.3's song...
I've cracked it.
Named the book the same.
I've cracked it, too.
Really? Which song?
Hey, terrorist!
Give me a bloody pic!
♪ Let them talk I
♪ Let them mock' ♪
♪ The path beckons :
♪ You just walk r
Let's go, Kamli.
♪ Let them talk I
♪ Let them mock' ♪
Thank you.
♪ The path beckons :
♪ You just walk r
Papa, what's this?
A story of two dads.
Your dad and my dad.
Read it someday.
And be like my dad...
not like your dad.
Your son resembles your dad.
It's him, reincarnated.
Just kidding.
J“ Woke up this morning,
Opened the newspaper I
♪ One fake news,
Gave me the blues 3'
♪ Yesterday, attended an event
Bored, I snoozed for a moment 3
J“ The two-minute nap
Was a front page snap! I
♪ “Butt drowned in booze”
Was headline news I
♪ Snooze turned to Booze! X'
♪ Who was the jerk
Who did this dirty work?' ♪
♪ The paper just said:
"According to sources. " J“
♪ Who is this Mr. Sources? 4“
♪ What are his resources? I
♪ Who turns a local spar
Into an global war 1'
♪ Man! That is rough!
Sanju says, enough is enough!' ♪
♪ Sanju says, enough is enough! I
♪ -According to the sources...
- Zip it! x
♪ Enough is enough! I
♪ Anyone in limelight
Is in Mr. Sources' sight I
J" Like a lamb to be slaughtered
You're gonna be rogered I
♪ If a tabloid carries your mug
RIP, your grave is dug!' ♪
♪ Mr. Sources has it figured 4“
♪ Repeats a lie till truth is buggered a“
♪ Turns a lie into Gospel truth I
♪ Man! That is rough!
Sanju says, enough is enough!' ♪
♪ Sanju says, enough is enough! I
♪ Then one day s
♪ I pulled up a reporter r
♪ Told him, “Control Mr. Sources" 1'
♪ "Bro, you have a kid and wife,
Let me also have a life" I
♪ Please! 4“
♪ "My brain is fried,
In the car I've cried" I
♪ "Popped pills to sleep,
Yet counted sheep" A'
♪ He listened to my plight
Then replied' ♪
♪ “Oh! I'm sorry." ♪
♪ I rejoiced, thought it was
The end of the story 3'
♪ But the next day, in the paper
Saw a new whopper :
♪ Another fake news,
Gave me the blues 4“
♪ Once more the reporter
Fried me proper r
♪ “Butt pops pills in the car
Suicide attempt by the film star!” 1'
♪ Cried turned to Suicide! r
♪ Who was the jerk
Who did this dirty work?' ♪
♪ The paper just said:
“According to sources.”' ♪
♪ Mr. Sources, the undertaker! 4“
♪ I'm alive and kickin'
He put me in a coffin I'
♪ He flips my life
Into endless strife 4'
♪ Man! That is rough!
Sanju says, enough is enough!' ♪
♪ Who turns a local spar
Into an global war 1'
♪ Mr. Sources has it figured 4“
♪ Repeats a lie till truth is buggered a“
♪ Sanju says, enough is enough! I
♪ He flips my life
Into endless strife 4'
♪ Sanju says, enough is enough! I