Mic testing 1 2 3...
OK
Women's day!
Rather than talking about ourselves,
let's welcome someone
who talks about us in his stories.
The most happening writer
in the country...
Mr. Amarendhar is with us.
Amar, the stage is all yours!
Hi Friends!
Hi Sir!
Didn’t expect this big a response!
Sir, we read all your books!
Thank you!
What’s your next book, sir?
I’m writing it...
Goddess Kali’s fury,
Goddess Sita’s calm...
come together for this age Satyabhama’s story.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes, sir!
♪ ♪
Hey!
Isn’t this the song you sang
for our University day?
I was in the library at that time.
I heard your voice and
went running to the auditorium.
Did you?
You didn’t tell me then,
that you went running?
You remember everything so well!
♪ I watched with my eyes wide open ♪
♪ wondering if it’s really you ♪
♪ if we both are the same ♪
♪ I hid you in my heart ♪
♪ wondering if it’s really you ♪
♪ if you are mine ♪
♪ The rhythm of whispers and
thoughts about you ♪
♪ is swinging me around ♪
♪ The utter sweetness of your chatter
has soaked my heart in a strange magic ♪
Where do you think our
journey is headed?
James street.
Your station is here!
Shouldn’t we have a destination
for our long journey?
♪ Do you know that it is your name ♪
♪ that my silence is calling out ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Do you know that it is with you ♪
♪ that my life is entwined ♪
Hey, give way.
Move!
Madam, catch hold of him!
You shouldn’t have let him go, madam.
Proxy!
Hi ma’am.
I’m sending his feed.
Sent it ma’am, take a look.
You want to file a complaint?
With whom?
With the police?
Or with your husband?
Okay!
Once this video goes viral,
your husband will
give the complaint.
It will cost you for that.
Forget about it...
Shall I put it out on the internet?
No?
OK then,
I’ll send you the scanner...
send me fifty thousand rupees.
Bro!
This MMTS train video will
fetch us One Lakh.
One Lakh, my foot!
Let’s squeeze two for this!
But there were police
in the train...
Hey!
Leave me.
Come on...move!
Move!
Leave me!
Hey!
Move!
My Lungi!
Come on...
Move!
All these rogues formed
a syndicate and,
were blackmailing girls
when we nabbed them.
And the credit goes to my SHE Teams.
Big round of applause for them!
And one more thing...
Girls!
SHE Safe App.
I installed it for myself.
You should do it too,
for your safety!
Your safety...
is our responsibility!
This is my promise to
all the women out there!
Thus, Satya became someone
whom all the girls could trust.
Coming to us,
our long relationship
reached a destination.
Hey Amar!
Where is Satya?
She’s coming, dude.
On the way.
Come on, have it!
Amar,
All the guests are here.
Satybhama is still not here?
You take care of the guests, dad.
She’ll be here soon.
Okay.
Hello, Amar!
Darling, where are you?
Remember our wedding is today?
Stop it, Amar. I’m coming.
Just two minutes.
Two minutes?
Satya, Come in!
Satya!
Amar, stay on the line for a minute.
OK.
Joseph sir, tell me.
We found the guys involved
with women trafficking.
But they are not revealing the location
of the girls in spite of thrashing them.
Take charge!
Tell me, you rogue!
Hey!
Start talking then!
Damn!
Heh!
I didn’t budge for him, after all!
I’ll talk, ma’am!
I’ll tell the truth, ma’am!
Should’ve hit him
without the bangles, ma’am.
He did that without them, didn’t he?
Did he budge?
-: SATYABHAMA :-
I need to meet ACP Satyabhama ma’am.
Madam is a bit busy today.
You cannot meet her now.
I watched madam on the TV.
Can you please make it happen?
You gave all your details...
I’ll tell her.
Hima!
What’s your name?
Haseena, madam.
What do you do, Haseena?
PeopleTech...
Haseena,
you need to talk.
I’m an...
IT professional, ma’am.
Is he a colleague?
No.
Tattoo artist.
Love marriage?
We could take action
only if you speak up!
His name is Yedhu.
Last week, he brought home
a girl he met on Tinder.
Who’s that?
I couldn’t bear it.
Heh!
Get out of here!
I called for divorce,
but he keeps bringing her home.
He came today too.
When my brother...
tried to stop him...
What do you want?
What do you mean, huh?
Tell me!
We are done.
- Done with what? What are you talking?
- Please don’t hurt my sister.
- Please let my sister go.
- Why is he interfering?
Yedhu, please!
- Listen to me!
Please...Please? For what?
- Let her go.
- HEH!
He hurt my brother too...
I mean everything to him, ma’am.
Other than your brother,
who else in your family knows this?
My mother...
passed away soon after
my brother was born.
My father...
I can’t tell him.
I’ll speak with your father,
file a complaint.
Haseena, please allow me.
Call that jerk!
No, ma’am.
Call him!
Hey!
Don’t move.
Special night...
Special tattoo.
Heh!
Why are you calling me?
Where are you?
She’s with me.
Who are you?
ACP Satyabhama.
Listen, I have some advice for you.
Don’t bother Haseena again.
If you do,
I will have to bother you!
I DARE YOU!
Haseena,
this is my number.
If anything, just call me.
Okay.
Ma’am, my brother.
She’s our family friend, Divya.
Nice. What’s your name?
Chotu.
I mean, Iqbal.
We call him Chotu, with love.
What are you studying?
Junior College, Ma’am.
In Bhashyam Academy...
Shh...Shh...
Won’t you speak?
Do they have to say it all?
Hmm? Doctor or Engineer?
Doctor, ma’am.
I wanna be a Doctor too, ma’am!
Good!
You should always take care of
your sister just like this!
Okay?
Don’t worry.
I’m there for you!
Thank you ma’am.
Mom...
Come on, Cheer up!
She is here now!
Isn’t it enough if we have
just our loved ones?
You are all that we have!
Amar, no!
Why?
I want a daughter like you.
Daughter?
I want a boy like you.
Hey Amar!
Satya!
It’s been ringing for a while, dear.
Thanks, aunty!
Amar, sorry.
I need to take this.
Okay...
Haseena?
Yedhu came home, ma’am.
HASEENA!
He came again?
He is screaming
and banging at the door, ma’am.
Haseena,
Calm down.
Just calm down!
Go to the door.
OPEN THE DOOR!
Ma’am?
Listen to me!
Block the door with some sofa.
OK ma’am.
HOW DARE YOU GO TO THE POLICE!
ARE YOU BLOCKING THE DOOR?
Hima!
Madam?
Send back up to Haseena’s house.
Immediately!
I’m on my way.
OK madam.
HASEENA!
ARE YOU BLOCKING THE DOOR?
Haseena,
talk to me.
Ma’am, I did what you asked me to do.
Just hold on for a few minutes.
I’m coming.
Ma’am, but...
HASEENA!
I’M TELLING YOU FOR THE LAST TIME!
WHERE ARE YOU?
HOW DARE YOU COMPLAIN AGAINST ME?
Huh?
How dare you complain against me!
Yedhu!
Yedhu, please!
Now go and complain!
Haseena!
Haseena, talk to me!
Haseena...
Haseena?
get out of there!
Do you hear me?
HEY!
Haseena!
I DARE YOU!
Madam,
take care of Chotu!
OK.
Let’s get to the hospital.
Haseena...
Who else in your family knows this?
My mother passed away
soon after my brother was born.
I mean everything to him, ma’am.
Stay strong, Imran!
Stay strong.
If only my daughter
said a word to me...
I would never have
let this happen.
While rescuing a girl,
SHE Teams ACP Satyabhama
fired a shot at the accused.
You emptied the entire magazine!
Did you realize that?
Human rights groups are outraged
by her rash actions.
If you had shot someone by mistake?
But Joseph, who fires a gun
in a residential area!?
ACP Anand Rao says that
Satyabhama will face reprimand.
Joseph sir spared you from
getting suspended.
Satya!
Haseena approached her with immense trust,
but she could not save her.
She never came to terms with that pain.
She kept looking for Yedhu since that day.
“He used to torture me a lot.”
“I don’t know where he is now, ma’am.”
“I don’t know anything about him.
Don’t ask me.”
Madam, we scanned all of Vizag.
He is not here too.
“Yedhu left me long ago!”
“He dumped me long ago!”
Satya, I circulated Yedhu’s photo
to all the police stations.
But, no use.
“He’s a cheat!”
Madam, he is not in Vijayawada either.
“Yedhu left me and went away long ago.
He was an expert at cheating.”
I searched all over Hubli, ma’am.
Found him nowhere.
Please don’t refuse, uncle.
Consider it as coming from your daughter.
This is for Chotu’s fees.
He got a scholarship, dear.
Have it dear.
OK Chotu, I’ll get going.
Chotu!
Chotu, why don’t you say hi...
Iqbal!
Iqbal?
Remember this...
you have another sister in me.
Dad!
She said she would be there for her.
I am there for you.
But she wasn’t!
Doctor, we are hale and healthy.
But, I didn’t expect it to be
negative even this time.
We really want to have kids.
Not sure what the issue is!
Physically, all your reports are good.
But...
Satya, the reason for you
not getting pregnant...
is stress and anxiety.
I suggest taking a break from work
until you conceive.
Joseph sir called,
I should go to the office.
Satya was inspired by Joseph sir
to become an IPS officer.
He too has every confidence in her.
We counseled them, sir.
I spoke with the victim too.
What happened, sir?
I knew an impulsive Satya...
I’m amused to see you
talk about counseling!
Come!
Here!
Intelligence reports are coming in.
Sleeper cells are very active.
So we formed a Crime team.
Sir,
I’m aware.
To replace you in the SHE Team,
I have a lot of options.
But for the crime team,
you are my best option!
Sir...
Satya,
if you get stuck at an unsolved case,
neither time stops,
nor does crime.
You have to move on!
OK,
How is Amar?
Did he complete that book?
He did, sir.
What’s the title?
After paying tribute to the
Queen of his heart,
and at that moment,
he stood with flowers in his hands,
right in front of her.
The End!
Thank you.
Sir,
We live in the age of million views,
and a million copies
of your book got sold.
How do you feel about that?
I’m writing for millions of smiles.
Not for views or sales!
OK, next question?
Sir!
You write very strong
woman characters.
Is there...any inspiration?
Yeah, she is beyond some inspiration.
No matter how many differences we have,
I want her to be smiling always.
Thank you...
Thank you!
♪ Under the blue skies ♪
Hi Thomas.
Hi ma’am.
Where?
♪ Smell the ocean waves ♪
♪ Feels like another day ♪
Ma’am...
The girlfriend’s name is
Jenny this time.
They are on a date now.
♪ Feeling of salvation ♪
♪ Stung into my mind ♪
♪ Step to the side as I walk into this violent maze ♪
♪ Been into this misery and this hate ♪
♪ Trained my fists to jab into your chest ♪
♪ Been no more as you think of me, powerless ♪
♪ I will remind you of unpleasant ♪
Ma’am.
♪ nightmares ♪
♪ Caught into your head and ♪
The girl in that black dress!
♪ Bound myself to glorify justness ♪
♪ I will revive and ♪
♪ terminate this madness ♪
Hi!
Hey Jenny!
Why don’t you wait for your
lucky hand boyfriend, huh?
He’ll be there in a bit.
I think he’s in the restroom.
Heh!
Let go of me!
Hey Yedhu, Stop!
Stop!
- Stop!
- Who are you?
Hyderabad Police!
Yedhu!
Are you okay?
Yedhu?
Yedhu...that ****** left me long ago!
Poor thing...
he doesn’t know anything!
What nonsense!
Are you out of your minds?
If you find him,
you let me know.
I will put a bullet in him myself.
Hi Satya!
Three days…
what?
It’s been three days
since we had coffee together!
Sherlock!
Hey Sherlock!
Still hunting?
That mouse is long gone.
Don’t waste your time.
Talk to me!
Why don’t you tell it
to me directly?
You are just like your mummy...
You don’t listen to me.
Stop it, Amar!
I will listen to whatever you say!
Why don’t you give a thought to
what the doctor said, at least now?
Uncle!
Iqbal is missing since
last night, dear.
We filed the complaint.
You can go now.
Ma’am!
When did you last speak with him?
Yesterday afternoon.
He didn’t come home for the night...
and you didn’t call him?
He sometimes stays back
at Divya’s house.
- That is why!
- Hmm.
Does he have any other friends?
No...
I don’t know.
Where did the phone trace to?
Sir,
one minute.
By evening 6:30,
the phone went off, madam.
Last location was traced
to a cafe called ‘Coffee Man’.
Madam...
This is my station,
my case.
Sir!
Satya,
why are you here?
Sir, why are ‘you’ here?
Prahlad started the
investigation already.
and it’s not even a
‘SHE’ that’s missing!
I’ll let you know if there is
any harassment case.
Sir, Iqbal is Haseena’s brother.
So?
- Sir!
- Satya!
Just follow...
PROTOCOL!
OK?
Haseena!
Madam...
take care of Chotu!
This is Iqbal and Divya’s
college, madam.
Coffee Man.
They regularly hangout at this Cafe.
Good Morning madam!
Hello Ma’am.
Are there any common friends of
Iqbal and Divya?
Iqbal used to come here
to study, ma’am.
Divya was also with him usually.
Did Iqbal have any
differences with anyone?
No madam, he was quite studious.
From what I know,
he always kept to himself.
Hima!
Ma’am, Coffee Man parking.
I can see him going in, but...
how did he get out?
He didn’t.
Some one must have took him out.
Let’s check the coffee shop.
Go back.
Play it in loop.
Something is fishy with
this CC TV, madam!
Now play the parking lot
footage again.
Looks like a maroon car
is heading out.
The footage was tampered ma’am.
Calling the Coffee shop?
Time waste.
Play our CCTV footage of that street.
I don’t see any maroon car
in this street, ma’am.
If it’s not in our footage too...
Someone from our department
must have tampered it.
Ma’am, how about checking the
neighboring building’s footage?
Good idea, play!
Ma’am, right there!
This looks like a VIP number.
Ma’am,
It’s registered under
the name of K Rishi Reddy.
Rishi...
MP Ramakanth Reddy’s nephew!
I mean...
He is in the medical college photos
clicked by Iqbal, ma’am.
Sir is meeting with visitors now.
Come back later.
We are here to meet Rishi Reddy,
not your sir.
Rishi is not here.
Go to his office to speak with him.
They aren’t letting me in
when I ask for Rishi, ma’am.
Hello Sir!
Have we met before?
Sir, I am ACP Satyabhama.
Need to speak with Rishi.
SHE Teams?
I mean Rishi...
If you speak with me,
it’s as good as speaking with Rishi.
But I don’t have the time.
Sir...
If there’s anything, you can
speak with DCP Anand Rao.
Madam,
DCP sir and Ramakanth Reddy were
classmates in Osmania University.
Why are you here?
I get it now.
Let’s go.
Usually Iqbal used to give the Insulin.
For the first time...
I don’t know where he is, ma’am.
Divya!
I noticed when I came for
Haseena...
and now when Iqbal isn’t around.
Did Iqbal tie this?
Hmm.
Divya,
How did you meet Iqbal?
Divya!
Who is the President of India?
APJ Abdul Kalam?
But...
this is Chotu’s writing, isn’t it?
♪ Treating me like a little princess
from a fairy tale ♪
♪ he moved with me like a shadow,
befriending me ♪
♪ I am a twinkling little star
by the clouds ♪
♪ and he is the sky that holds me ♪
♪ Like the apple of my eye ♪
♪ he stays with me so ♪
♪ When he is around me ♪
♪ the moon’s silvery shine
finds its way to me ♪
♪ He cannot stand it if I am worried ♪
♪ and takes care of me like a baby ♪
♪ Walking in unison ♪
♪ like words straight from the heart ♪
♪ as he moves with me like this... ♪
♪ Bringing me close to my dreams ♪
♪ he stands beside me like a dear friend ♪
Come on,
give me a smile!
If Iqbal is with me,
I feel strong, ma’am.
I know Iqbal has a
special place in your life.
But, who is this Rishi?
He was with you
at the police station.
If you want Iqbal to come back,
you need to speak up.
Did you smoke?
Did you drink as well,
in the last 24 hours?
Is this a joke?
What is this, sir?
Couldn’t you find a better donor for the kid?
Since he is a blood relation...
What has relation got to do
with donation?
Is there anyone with
A -ve blood group?
Hello!
Is there anyone with
A -ve blood group?
I will go check in the south block.
A -ve?
Hello!
Yeah.
Did you drink or smoke
in the last 48 hours?
I don’t have the habit.
Come!
Divya,
He is the chairman’s nephew...
Does the chairman’s nephew
not have blood?
Can’t he donate some?
- Hi!
- Hello Rishi.
-Can I go?
-Yeah.
Let’s keep everything
ready for tomorrow.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, bye bye!
Hi!
Huh?
When can I come back for this?
To have it again,
you have to wait
another eight weeks.
Oh!
How about a coffee then?
Classes...Internship...
and I have to be home by Nine.
So it’s tough.
Rishi...
Hmm?
It’s not a NO.
Just busy...
Hi!
My hand...
got sprained.
Let me know if it happens again.
Give me your number,
I’ll inform.
Are you done now?
with your classes...seminars?
Let’s go out?
Now!?
Hmm...
My house is too far away...
Isn’t this your house?
♪ A tickle here and a tickle there ♪
♪ A peek now and a peek then ♪
♪ Don’t you lure me ♪
♪ and hide away! ♪
♪ Entwine some and unwind some ♪
♪ Swerve a bit and straighten again ♪
♪ Don’t you follow me along my way ♪
♪ Your beauty that’s so precious ♪
♪ even if it’s a teeny tiny bit ♪
♪ won’t you pass me some ♪
♪ With a sullen pout ♪
♪ as you grow fiery ♪
♪ let’s indulge in all the fun there is ♪
♪ Don’t you cast your spells ♪
Iqbal, it’s my birthday tomorrow.
Please join us.
Seminar, classes...
have to be home by Nine.
♪ My entrapped heart ♪
♪ crosses all horizons
as the sun rises today ♪
♪ One life, one and only youth ♪
Happy Birthday!
♪ will they follow us again and again? ♪
♪ If we embrace them and walk in tandem ♪
♪ won’t we find a path to go ahead? ♪
♪ One life, one and only youth ♪
♪ will they follow us again and again? ♪
♪ If we embrace them and walk in tandem ♪
♪ won’t we find a path to go ahead? ♪
Girls, ready?
Smile!
Divya, move a little to your right.
Yeah.
Hey, move!
- Let’s get one together.
- Hey, don’t you get it?
Just one photo...
Hey Iqbal, you click it!
- Leave me!
- Abhi...
Abhi, let go of her hand.
Let me go!
Hey... you go and click the photo!
Let go of her hand first!
Take your hand off...
Get lost!
Rishi, I am speaking with him...
What is there to talk when
he lays his hands on her?
Rishi, keep calm.
- Who is that idiot?
- Rishi!
Why didn’t you tell me
that he is troubling you?
- Hold on, Rishi!
- I was dealing with him...
Iqbal, I’m not speaking with you!
Calm down, Rishi.
- I was handling it...
- Listen to me, Rishi!
Why is he interfering
when I am talking with you?
Rishi, relax!
I’m telling you
that I’m handling it...
- Rishi...
- Heh!
He hit Iqbal?
Hmm.
Hima?
Madam, your guess was right.
Rishi’s phone also traced
to Coffee Man that day.
I am so happy, guys.
Our game is about to reach
one million downloads.
I want you all to know that...
I’m so proud of you all!
Sir, please!
NINETY SEVEN!
Yes! We’ve done this!
NINETY EIGHT!
NINETY NINE!
ONE MILLION...YAY!
Do the chat messages in this game
get saved in the server?
They do.
Don’t worry, I’ll take care of it.
OK uncle, I will wait.
Suspicious about Rishi,
Satya started strict vigilance on him.
Where is madam?
Madam,
DCP Sir.
Sir!
Satya, why don’t you answer the phone?
What is this warrant about?
This is a very important evidence
in the MMTS gang case, sir.
OK, so?
What has the game got to do with it?
Got a complaint that the game
is being misused, sir.
Madam,
it’s last month’s date here!
Oh! Is it?
So sorry, sir.
Hey Hima!
Why didn’t you check it?
Hima!
Madam, the game is awesome!
Is that so? Let’s play!
Hey!
Can I buy you a drink?
I have a girl friend.
I just said hi...
did I ask about the girlfriend?
Why worry about the girlfriend
when I am here?
Good one!
Third level is quite convenient.
Did you check my feedback?
I already updated it.
Didn’t you notice?
I’ll check it, but...
will you beat my high score
at least this time?
I won’t miss this time.
Hmm? Let’s see!
All the played games have been
saved in the server, ma’am.
And this is the game
Rishi played with Neha.
This is all a game?
It felt so realistic!
Yes, madam.
You feel as if you are right there!
I played it that day!
Yeah ma’am, this game was
developed by AI technologies.
- It’s a very complicated design...
- Proxy!
Make me understand!
Ma’am, simple.
This is a firing game
designed with real places.
It has different levels like
pub, garage etc.
Also, like whatsapp and Instagram,
chats, voice messages, photos
and videos also can be shared.
You can choose an avatar you like
and enter this game.
More than users, there are misusers
in this game, madam.
What do you mean?
Yes ma’am, that MMTS black mailer gang
used this game and trapped women.
Okay.
Are there any chats of Rishi with Neha?
Ma’am, all these chats are encrypted.
I’m unable to open them.
Just give us some time.
Hmm...hurry up!
Let’s go!
I’m coming to Hyderabad in
January first week.
What...really?
Let’s catch up then!
Hmm!
Rishi!
Got the access, ma’am!
Did Rishi meet Neha?
Who is this Neha?
I feel there is a strong connection between
Iqbal’s disappearance and Neha.
What did they chat further? Look!
Rishi did message her, but...
there’s no reply from Neha, ma’am.
Who else did he chat with frequently?
Check it.
After Neha, Rishi chatted mostly with...
another player called Vijay, ma’am.
No, these are not important...
open the last chat.
Okay ma’am.
Voice clip!
Vijay, I dropped Iqbal at the
location you asked me to.
I’m done.
Oh, you’re so done!
Vijay...
Vijay, please answer!
The police came to my home
looking for Iqbal.
They came to my office too.
Vijay, please respond.
Vijay?
Who is Vijay?
Ma’am!
Ma’am, let me explain.
Ma’am, just listen to me once.
There are a lot of people downstairs...
it will be embarrassing.
Ma’am...
-Ma’am, please. Please, ma’am!
-Satya!
Hey, leave him...leave him now!
Satya, listen to me!
How did you even get in?
-Satya, it’s an order!
-Anand, ask her to leave him!
HEH!
Answer the phone, sir.
Don’t think you heard it.
Answer it.
Hello?
- Anand!
- Sir!
Satya took charge.
But, sir...
- Listen...
- Sir!
She will lead this case from now on.
Sir, this case...
-Ma’am, please!
-Hey, sit down!
Ma’am...
Where is Iqbal?
Please ma’am,
just listen to me once.
Who is Vijay?
Ma’am, please listen to me.
Who is Neha?
Just once, listen to...
ANSWER, GODDAMNIT!
Neha said she would come to
Hyderabad in January, ma’am.
We wanted to meet up.
But I couldn’t find her
online for a few days.
All of a sudden, one day...
Can I buy you a drink?
Hmm?
What?
Sounds familiar, doesn’t it?
Lover boy!
Who are you?
I’m ACP Vijay.
Anti Terrorist Squad, Dehradun.
Who do you think Neha is?
She honey-trapped you.
What nonsense!
Look at this.
Neha has terror links.
They planned something big for January.
Still don’t believe me?
You want to see my ID?
Clueless what to do,
I approached DCP Uncle.
Uncle!
- Five minutes.
- OK.
Sir!
In the first week of January,
there could be a terror attack
in a political meeting,
according to intelligence report.
If we take immediate action,
we can avoid the damage.
And sir,
I hope you know what I’m saying.
I mean, your friend...
MP Ramakanth Reddy’s meeting?
Yes sir.
Alert all the forces!
The attack should not happen
at any cost!
OK sir.
Oh God!
I tried a lot to call
Vijay online, ma’am.
Hello Vijay!
Vijay, are you there?
Please come online once.
Are you there?
What’s your problem, man?
We are busy at work.
Don’t disturb!
Sir, I didn’t get it
when you tried to explain.
Tell me what to do now.
OK, will you give me Neha’s
chat data from the game?
Okay.
Not just your conversations with her,
I want all the conversations she had
with the other players too.
Sure, sir.
After sharing Neha’s chat data
with Vijay,
I was curious to know
what was in those chats.
She mostly interacted with
one gamer particularly, ma’am.
She asked him to meet a guy called
Akhtar, for the January attack.
I went there to find out
what it was all about, and...
Iqbal?
Iqbal...
Terrorist!
I couldn’t believe it, ma’am.
I’m sorry, sir.
I saw him holding this...
and didn’t know what to do.
You have to do
one more task for us.
While I couldn’t make up my mind
if I should follow Vijay’s orders...
-: 06 JANUARY 2024 :-
Sir,
In the first week of January,
there could be a terror attack
in a political meeting,
according to intelligence reports.
I’m coming to Hyderabad in the
first week of January.
They planned something big
for January.
-: 06 JANUARY 2024 :-
-: Anantagiri Hills :-
-: 2 KM :-
Vijay!
I dropped Iqbal at the location
you asked me to.
I’m done.
Iqbal!
What...
What happened?
Leave me!
Iqbal...
Iqbal, let go of me!
-: Anantagiri Hills :-
-: 2 KM :-
Iqbal is in Vijay’s custody...
Iqbal!
Iqbal, wake up!
Hima!
Ambulance!
HEY!
Take it slow.
Be careful!
Iqbal?
Emergency ward.
Nothing to worry,
he’ll come out of coma.
What do you mean?
It could take a day
or even a month.
Thomas?
Ma’am, I just crossed Mangalore.
I don’t care where you are!
Where is Yedhu? Where is he?
Ma’am, I’ve been searching in
all the places you asked me to.
I’ve been working on this
case full time.
That’s not where
you should be looking.
Okay, ma’am.
Madam!
Should we bring the
sleeper cell thing up with him?
What do you want to ask him,
Prahlad?
If his son is a terrorist?
If we believe everything
the accused says,
what’s the point of our investigation?
Madam!
The prime accused in the
highly sensational Iqbal case,
Rishi Reddy, has been granted
conditional bail.
As part of the rescue operation,
ACP Satyabhama found
a heavily wounded Iqbal in Vikarabad.
Getting the bail so quickly was possible
only because of you sir.
It’s okay Ramakanth, it happens.
Thank you sir.
No big deal...
I’ll meet you in Delhi, sir.
Yes, definitely!
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye.
I’m off too, bye!
Hey, what happened?
Rishi got out on just a conditional bail.
As if the case has been
closed completely...
you casually ask “ what happened?” !
It started off as a missing case.
It turned into a kidnap,
then to attempted murder,
and finally settled at terrorist case!
If that Iqbal dies,
it will become a murder case also!
Mm...murder case??
You first sit down.
Tell me what to do now.
If he wakes up there,
it’s a climax for Rishi’s life!
If he dies instead,
it’s THE END of your political career!
Make sure Rishi doesn’t
go out for a few days.
Especially, make sure he
doesn’t use his phone.
These games, browsing...
nothing doing.
Okay!
Why would Yedhu want to kill Iqbal?
How is Rishi connected to Yedhu?
Who are Neha and Vijay
that Rishi talked about?
If I learn more about them,
will I find Yedhu?
Still awake?
From Rishi’s story,
it’s true that he interacted with
Vijay and Neha.
You call it a story on the one hand,
and truth on the other!
Whatever it is Amar,
this should not have happened at all!
Had I saved Haseena,
Iqbal wouldn’t have been
in this situation now.
A typical police officer would have...
stopped at Haseena.
But you stayed put for Iqbal.
Satya,
whether I write a story,
or you take up a case,
we both strive for closure.
Hima?
Madam, Rishi is absconding.
He is no where to be seen.
What?
Did you check over there?
We are checking, ma’am.
What happened?
We covered a five km radius
around this area ma’am,
but couldn’t find him.
Do you think five km is enough?
Hima!
Search another five!
She says another five!
What’s happening here?
Is this how you work
in your department?
Let me talk with her...
Sir, why don’t you ask
your folks in Delhi?
They’ll find him in fifteen minutes!
Satya!
Sir.
Is there a conspiracy behind
Joseph Raj’s early retirement?
That is true -
say some sectors supporting him.
Joseph, my man!
Come on...click the photos!
Done?
Let’s go.
Why is Ramankanth still calling me?
We did transfer Joseph
on his demand, didn’t we?
That doesn’t mean
the case is closed, sir.
Just to close this case,
they will blame
Iqbal to be a terrorist.
Sir, that will only be an allegation.
You are right.
But once I’m out of the case,
that will become true!
Why don’t we just say that the guy
in coma is a terrorist,
and close the case?
Nope.
Why? What’s wrong with it?
There are still three days left for
Joseph sir’s transfer, sir.
Satya,
I can just give you three more days...
From Rishi’s statement,
Akhtar is the only one who’s real, sir.
and we hit a dead end
for his location too!
So?
Sir, that is why...
Akhtar’s co-ordinates?
That’s a very sensitive area.
It’s not safe for you.
Sir, I can’t take another chance
in Iqbal’s case.
Satya, we are done with
this conversation.
Guys, we only have three days.
Pull out all the details of everyone
linked with this case.
It’s a fake Id ma’am,
not in the records.
What if this Vijay is undercover?
If he is undercover,
why would he show ATS ID?
There’s no Neha in our Terrorist list,
nor a profile that matches this picture.
So, this is a fake profile too!
When Rishi spoke with Vijay and Neha,
they masked the IP address with VPN,
and changed the location
every five seconds, ma’am.
Akhtar.
He brainwashes youngsters,
and recruits them for
terrorist organizations.
Exactly!
Masjids and Madrasas are his targets.
What’s the kid’s name?
Iqbal, sir.
Digital Forensic Reports -
Iqbal’s phone, laptop, system...
everything is clean, madam.
There is nothing in them that suggests
that he contacted Akhtar.
If Akhtar contacted him, that means...
this kid is up to something.
How about we nab this Akhtar?
Six months of investigation!
Don’t mess our operation against him.
Rajan!
Satya, please stay out of this.
Satya, I know you will never stop.
But we are running out of time.
Off the records...
Akhtar’s co-ordinates!
Be careful!
♪ Thus, to bring welfare to the world ♪
♪ by destroying the demon Narakasura ♪
♪ Satyabhama steps into
the battleground and glances ♪
♪ all around the battlefield ♪
♪ She twirls her hair ♪
♪ binds it to a bun so tight ♪
♪ gracefully wraps the fabric
around her waist ♪
♪ Positions herself on Garuda ♪
♪ spreading across the sky’s clouds ♪
♪ Listen O Bharata’s valiant son ♪
♪ Satyabhama’s battle field story ♪
Come on...
♪ Listen O Bharata’s valiant brother ♪
Come in!
♪ I shall recount the brave heart’s story ♪
What’s your name?
Where are you from?
Wow!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Take it off too!
It’s private time!
Show me your face!
♪ She blows the conch ♪
♪ cleansing the enemy ♪
♪ with fierce eyes and
furrowed eyebrows ♪
♪ ignites intense fury ♪
♪ creates disaster ♪
♪ Oh Mighty Satyabhama! ♪
♪ She faces armies larger than an ocean ♪
♪ strikes an arrogant demon
with sharpened arrows ♪
♪ crushes the demon’s wings
and showers thundering blows ♪
♪ Oh Mighty Satyabhama! ♪
Let’s go!
♪ She chants to empower her weapon ♪
♪ while the world stands still ♪
♪ Shoots her arrow ♪
♪ to behead Narakasura
and puts an end to the battle ♪
♪ Oh Mighty Satyabhama ♪
♪ Like a sage in a battlefield ♪
♪ soothes after conquering ♪
♪ liberates young women ♪
♪ in the city of Pragjyotisha ♪
♪ illuminates a row of lights
with the bow string ♪
♪ Oh Mighty Satyabhama ♪
Hey...hey!
Who hit you?
I don’t know.
She was in a Burqa.
Didn’t you see her?
She wrapped me up in the Burqa.
♪ Rise to hunt like a lioness ♪
♪ Oh Mighty Satyabhama ♪
-Nothing to worry, Hima.
-Satya!
Where is Iqbal’s file?
You know how sensitive that area is.
Why did you go there, still?
Who said I went there, sir?
I got a call from ATS!
Didn’t they ask you not to
disturb their operation?...
Looks like you are more disturbed?
Forty Eight hours.
After all!
You only have two days left.
I will see to it!
Pull the car out!
Iqbal’s prescription?
Ma’am,
the prescription has changed.
-Okay, thanks!
-That’s OK.
Phone!
Who’s that?
Water, sir!
I don’t want it.
Hello Divya!
Rishi, what’s happening?
Why did you run away?
Where are you?
Divya, listen to me carefully.
What should I listen to?
Neha...Vijay...terror attack...
Why are you so mad at Iqbal?
If we get hold of Vijay,
everything will be clear.
Now his life is at risk.
If something happens to him,
I will never forgive you!
Police...Police!
Divya, does anyone know
that you are talking to me?
Police...Police...Police!
Where is he?
He is upstairs, madam.
Hello Divya!
Divya!
Satya!
Ma’am, if you scan this QR code with
Divya’s phone, her phone can be cloned.
Phone!
This way, madam.
This room.
Madam,
Rishi escaped again.
Isn’t that what we want?
I know where he would go now.
After all that happened to Iqbal,
no matter what you say,
it isn’t justified, Rishi.
You too?
Divya, at least you should trust me!
How could I?
Iqbal accepted us.
But you?
Just tell me, Rishi...
did you meet at least
one person from your story?
Syringe!
Divya, I did meet a guy!
He gave me a syringe in old city.
We should catch hold of him.
Trust me Divya.
One chance.
One last chance.
Please?
Iqbal is getting better now.
Yeah, I’m going home.
Yeah.
Dear...
did you find Rishi?
We couldn’t find him, Uncle.
Come in for some tea, dear.
Chotu!
Go get some tea leaves!
How much can he bear?
He is just a kid!
Everybody is worried about him.
Haseena left us.
I’m ACP Vijay.
Now Iqbal is suffering.
Who is he?
He is my brother-in-law, Riaz.
His daughter is getting married
next week.
Where does he live?
Istanbul.
It’s been three days
since he came to Hyderabad.
You never told me anything about him?
Well...
he promised to find a job for
Haseena sometime back.
After that, things went out of hand.
Forget it.
What exactly happened?
Riyaz landed from Istanbul,
that same day Iqbal went missing.
Madam, found Riaz’s location.
Prahlad Sir, I’ve sent it to you.
Prahlad!
Ma’am!
Not in our car!
Sir, a fine of five hundred just for insurance?
Hey, Just pay the fine!
I came the day before.
Yes...one...
Hey, one minute!
Hey, who are you all?
Why did you bring me here?
Vijay, why did you want to kill Iqbal?
Vijay?
Hey, my name is Riaz!
Why would I want to kill Iqbal?
Then, what is this?
Vijay again?
Why the hell are you calling me Vijay?
Hey, keep it down!
Just answer the questions.
Do you understand?
OK.
You aren’t Vijay, you’re Riaz.
Why did you trap Rishi posing as Vijay?
Rishi?!
Who is Rishi?
Madam, I do construction work
in Istanbul.
I move labour from here to there!
Then, Iqbal and Haseena?
Madam,
I am an NRI, OK?
I came to Hyderabad for my
daughter’s wedding.
If you have any questions,
talk to the embassy!
What’s there to talk?
Where’s your passport?
Look, you can’t talk to me like this!
Of course, I can!
Call my lawyer, then.
You are ‘some’ lawyer...
took so long to get here!
I’m here now, let it go!
If Vijay turned out to be Riaz,
Neha could be some one else too.
I want this girl in different looks
and age groups!
Send it to all the departments.
No need ma’am.
I found Neha.
This is her digital footprint
and live footage.
But there’s a bus ticket booked to
Vijayawada under the name Maya!
When is the bus leaving?
Now!
Look out, Hima.
-: VIJAYAWADA :-
Madam, there!
Vijayawada bus.
There!
-: VIJAYAWADA :-
Prahlad, why did you stop?
Go!
Prahlad, go!
Mm...ma’am...
Madam, I don’t understand anything!
I work at a music shop.
Who is Iqbal?
and Vijay?
Who are you for that matter?
I have no idea what
you are talking about!
Maya...err...Neha,
Why are you going to Vijayawada?
to a music shop there?
Madam,
Not Neha, it’s Maya.
All the details she gave are correct.
This is where he gave me, Divya!
Okay...
A brown cover with a syringe and vials.
Shall we check some
medical shops nearby?
Yes!
Divya!
Pen and paper?
I think I can sketch him!
Guys, we just have one day!
Hima... any update?
Madam, all that Maya said about the
music shop was fake.
I’m following her.
Good. Don’t lose her.
Okay ma’am.
Proxy!
Ma’am!
Looks like Rishi and Divya are looking
for the guy who gave him the syringe.
Keep a close track on them.
Okay, ma’am.
Prahlad!
Riaz is right in front you.
Red shirt.
Got it, Proxy.
Excuse me!
did he work here?
No.
Call everyone.
Excuse me, do you recognize him?
Yeah, he is a delivery guy.
Go straight and take a right.
You will find his house there.
Thank you.
Prahlad!
Madam, Riaz is talking with someone
in Balanagar industrial area.
Keep an eye on him.
Madam, she is going into 511.
Madam, by the way, where are you?
We are following Maya.
Hello!
You take care of Riaz.
I’ll call you back.
Madam...
Sir!
This guy...
Dad, who’s that?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Why did you give the syringe?
Who asked you to give it?
He was in a mask just like this.
He paid me to do the delivery,
and I just did that.
I mean...
we both met on Tinder.
After that...
I found her in Rishi’s game...
We have very common interests.
But, if we meet in public places,
people might misunderstand.
If it’s a farm house like this,
they won’t misunderstand.
Ha ha, yeah!
Customer care...
Sir,
- Satya madam is in the resort...
- I’m here sir!
Madam, you?
I’ve dealt with your sir,
you deal with Riaz!
What happened, Rishi?
Hey...
what happened?
Tell me!
My only hope, Divya.
It’s gone.
Nobody believed me.
They will never, now!
I believed you,
and now I’m with you, aren’t I?
Rishi...
Whatever may happen,
I will be with you.
Stay strong!
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hi!
Darling, where are you?
It’s our wedding anniversary.
Do you remember?
Stop it, Amar!
How can I forget?
OK, I’m preparing dinner.
Come home soon.
Hmm...coming.
Prahlad is not reachable.
Just a routine check.
Hello...
Hello?
Satya, can you hear me?
No signal there?
Hello?
Amar, I’ll call you later.
Satya surrendered there...
not because she could not fight...
but to learn the true colors of Riaz.
They brought another one.
Oh no...who could that be?
Will you go check?
No, no...I’m scared!
Shh...
Silence, everyone!
I’ll go check.
I’ll talk ma’am.
I’ll tell the truth, ma’am.
They are planning to sell all
the girls to Istanbul, ma’am.
Where does he live?
Istanbul.
What exactly happened?
Well...
He tried to destroy Haseena’s life.
He promised to get her a job in Dubai,
but he wanted to sell her.
Hey, give me your dupatta.
here...tie it tight!
Take my dupatta too.
Here...hold this.
Come...
Go!
Dump them all inside!
Girls...
Remember...
‘SHE Safe’ App...
I installed it for myself...
For your safety,
you should do it too!
Your safety...
is our responsibility!
Ma’am!
I watched you on TV,
talking about this app.
You will never learn!
Why did you do that to Iqbal?
Iqbal?
I didn’t do anything to Iqbal!
I’m just doing some
small side businesses...
Business with girls?
I agree, what I did was wrong.
I swear on Allah, madam!
I have nothing to do with
what happened to Iqbal.
♪ Radio City! ♪
Good morning, Hyderabad!
It’s really a Good Morning.
Because, last night our SHE Teams
rescued twelve girls from the
clutches of a women trafficking gang.
Really hats off to Hyderabad SHE Teams!
Why are you wounded?
What happened Satya?
I ran out of the three days
that Joseph sir gave me.
The case is not in my hands anymore.
Case!
You know what?
You lost the case long back.
Yes Satya!
You have been on the hunt
since the day we got married.
You are still on it.
Look at you!
Is there anything other than
this case since our marriage?
Everyday abuse...murders...
some crime or the other
keeps happening.
You deal with a lot of cases.
Haseena’s case is just one of them.
Why Haseena? Why this case?
Tell me one reason!
Tell me Satya, speak up!
Just tell me, damnit!
There is nothing more important
to me than you,
but for you…
She was pregnant.
What!?
Unable to disclose this information
to Haseena’s family,
I felt tormented...
and kept drifting away from my
desire to have children, Amar.
Satya...
He knew it and still killed her.
He didn’t kill Haseena alone.
How can I leave him like that,
Amar?
How can I let it go?
♪ Search on... Search on! ♪
♪ Search on, without turning your back ♪
♪ Search on, without hesitating ♪
♪ Search on, for hope within despair ♪
♪ Search on ♪
♪ Search on, for light within the darkness ♪
Sir!
How’s your inspiration?
♪ Search on, at the very place you lost it ♪
♪ Search on ♪
♪ Oh...oh...oh! ♪
♪ ♪
Ma’am...
Ma’am?
♪ Search on... Search on! ♪
♪ Search on, as you move ahead ♪
♪ Search on, as you stumble and rise up ♪
♪ Oh...oh...oh! ♪
♪ ♪
Madam, remember Divya’s classmate,
Abhinav?
This is his condition at a
hospital in Vizag.
I’ll update you the details.
Satya!
What?
Come here.
Something is off
about this chat, Satya.
What are you doing
with this data?
I got it from Hima.
- What?
- Listen to me!
Sit down.
Typing pattern!
What?
Now, look at this...
You use a lot of dots.
and I use quite a bit of emojis.
This happens involuntarily.
So?
So look at this...
Vijay is writing ‘Okay’ as ‘Okie’.
Neha is also writing ‘Okay’ as ‘Okie’.
And...
both of them are writing
‘night’ as ‘ni8’.
Why are they both talking
in the same style?
Or...
is one person acting as
two different people?
Hey...
Sherlock!
I’ll just be back.
You naughty fellow!
My laptop...hmm!
Thomas?
Ma’am,
I found Yedhu!
OK then, the baby must be up.
I’ll get going now.
Okay.
Did you bring it?
Shh!
Yedhu...Where is Yedhu?
That’s my husband.
- Yedhu?
- Who is Yedhu?
He’s Sekhar!
Sekhar?
What happened to him?
One year ago,
he met with an accident.
He isn’t able to get up since then.
Sorry ma’am!
He’s Sekhar, apparently.
It’s not the girl
that changed this time.
It’s his name!
You are not wrong, Thomas.
He is Yedhu, indeed!
She doesn’t even know that
his name is Yedhu, ma’am.
Looks like he took
good care of her.
All of a sudden,
he fell sick one day...
and his condition deteriorated
slowly to this stage.
On their doctor’s suggestion,
she brought him here for treatment.
Madam, remember Divya’s classmate,
Abhinav?
This is his condition at a
hospital in Vizag.
Hey, you click it.
I wanna be a doctor too, ma’am.
Yeah, Satya...
Is the letter ‘L’
missing in their chats?
What?
In Rishi’s chats with Neha and Vijay,
is the alphabet ‘L’ missing?
Hold on, let me check.
Not always.
Only some times.
Why are they both talking
in the same style?
Or...
Is one person acting like
two different people?
Doctor or Engineer?
He is the doctor, isn’t he?
Yes.
Doctor, ma’am.
Random news
...this case’s accused Rishi Reddy
is out on bail,
and is at large for a few days.
The Police continue to search for him.
Although this case is under the
purview of Crime branch DCP AnandRao,
ACP Satyabhama’s investigation
uncovered some crucial clues,
according to sources.
She says she will nab
the criminal at any cost.
Ma’am, why are you keeping
this case updates a secret?
Are you not in good terms with DCP Anand Rao?
Ma’am, did you find out where Rishi is?
Tell us, ma’am!
Are you responsible for that girl’s death?
Ramakanth Reddy’s party...
You couldn’t find any clue
about the culprit...
did you give up on this case?
Never!
“The person you are trying to call
is busy.”
Hima!
OK ma’am.
Satya,
listen to me...
More than finding out
who did that,
it’s important to know
why they did it.
At this moment,
what you need is to think well
rather than act in fury.
But...
Thought or a weapon?
You know which one to use.
The decision is yours!
White Brownie!
Will you sell it?
No. I’ll buy it.
I want to know who sells it.
Yedhu. Only he used to sell.
He is absconding though.
Search near Maharashtra,
Goa, Karnataka border.
You may find him.
♪ Search on... Search on! ♪
♪ Search on, for Justice ♪
♪ Search on, like a haunting death ♪
♪ Changing the fate ♪
♪ Turning into the Creator♪
♪ Am I the moving darkness? ♪
♪ Am I the invisible world? ♪
♪ Search on... Search on! ♪
♪ Search on, until you exact revenge ♪
♪ Search on like a death angel on hunt ♪
There’s a grocery shop over there.
Go look for him there, you will find him.
Would you write it down, please?
♪ Am I the engulfing sacrifice ritual? ♪
♪ Am I the merciless God of death? ♪
Iqbal?
Did they discharge you!?
How did you come?
Is Imran Uncle here, too?
I thought you would be
by my side when I woke up!
Blood!
Sit down.
Wait, I’ll bring First Aid.
Divya!
Where’s aunty?
She went to Srisailam,
to pray for your recovery.
Divya!
Divya, finally! Vijay...
Iqbal?
When did you come?
I’m really sorry.
I didn’t do this on purpose.
I didn’t mean to do that.
Please, try to understand.
Divya, he sent a message again.
What?
“Iqbal is downstairs,
what are you doing?”- he says!
Who?
Vijay?
Hmm.
What?
You...
Hey!
Rishi!
-Stop it!
-Why did you do this?
Why did you come here, huh?
Guys, stop!
What do you want?
Guys, let’s sit and talk!
Stop it, both of you!
Why did you come?
Rishi, stop!
Speak up!
Iqbal, why aren’t you
saying anything?
Rishi?
Rishi...
Rishi, what happened?
Rishi, what’s wrong?
Rishi!
Rishi?
Iqbal...
Terrorist!
So easy to believe, isn’t it?
Sedative...
I gave him just one ml.
Don’t worry.
I’ll give the rest now!
How happy we were, Divya!
You...
me...
our hospital...
This idiot, and his games!
How did you fall for him, Divya?
Why are you doing all this?
For you, Divya!
I... I never saw you that way, Iqbal!
How?
Oh!
You think all this is love?
I didn’t see you that way, either!
Chotu, for the sake of his loved ones,
he could go to any extent.
He travelled a lot,
and achieved what he wanted.
Hmm...that’s enough.
Go to sleep.
Tell me more!
It’s getting late, Chotu!
Go to sleep now.
I feel scared when you aren’t around.
You are growing up, dear!
You shouldn’t be scared.
There...now it’s as good as
I’m with you.
Having our loved ones with us...
gives us courage, Divya.
Don’t mix it up with Love,
and belittle it.
I felt the same when
Rishi was next to me.
What did he do?
Hey, tell me!
Yedhu,
we are done!
When I’m speaking with you,
why is he interfering?
Heh..why is he coming in between?
Yedhu, please!
Rishi, listen to me!
Rishi, let me talk!
HEY!
When my sister was no more,
you were there for me...
you will be there forever.
But now, if someone
comes all of a sudden and,
poses as a sister and
expects me to forget everything?
How can I forget?
Never!
Iqbal!
Iqbal, no!
Iqbal, please!
Thought or weapon?
The decision is yours.
Iqbal!
Chotu!
Don’t call me that.
Why?
What do you know about me,
that you call me Chotu?
I know.
I alone know...
Chotu!
Don’t you get it?
Didn’t I tell you not to call me that?
How else should I call you?
Vijay?
Or...
Neha?
Can I buy you a drink?
I have a girlfriend.
I just said hi...
did I ask about your girlfriend?
However,
why worry about your girlfriend
when I’m here?
And then...
after meeting Akhtar,
you realized that...
you could take advantage of your name.
Iqbal...
Terrorist!
It’s so easy to believe, isn’t it?
Then you brought in Riaz...
as...
ATS officer Vijay.
Who is this?
My brother-in-law.
A while ago,
he promised to find
a job for Haseena.
Forget it.
What exactly happened?
Send her to Dubai with me.
Dubai?
Everything will be alright,
brother-in-law.
I’ll take care of everything
over there.
But Riaz...
wanted to traffick Haseena too.
How could you do that?
You could have ruined Haseena’s life!
Aren’t we family?
And to get back at Riaz,
you turned him into Vijay.
Rishi, listen to me.
I’m Vijay.
ACP, Anti Terrorist Squad, Dehradun.
Who do you think Neha is?
She honey-trapped you.
And then,
you planned for Rishi to
kidnap you, quite cleverly.
Vijay, I dropped Iqbal at the
location you asked me to.
I’m done!
But things didn’t pan out
according to your plan.
When I found you,
I was worried what happened to you!
Iqbal!
When I found this,
I suspected you.
Yedhu had evaded capture
for very long,
but you made me realize
where to look for him!
That’s not the place
you should be searching!
It’s Hyderabad.
Looking for Yedhu who
cheated your sister,
you reached Maya.
I even know why you
setup Maya as Neha.
Do you know how?
Did anyone come looking
for your tattoo?
There was one guy, ma’am.
You look much younger than
your Tinder profile?
What’s this?
I want the guy who gave you
that tattoo.
Yedhu?
I don’t know.
He left me and went away.
With our story of searching for Yedhu,
if I was the one who started it,
you put an end to it much early.
Our story?
and you started it?
He’s taking these medicines, doctor.
But, he is not getting any better.
He’ll be fine.
Don’t worry.
We need to take him to Hyderabad.
Okay?
Be gentle!
Get in.
I was the one who started it,
and I was the one who ended it too!
If that was the end indeed,
this story wouldn’t have
come till Rishi.
That’s the mistake I made!
Instead of treating them all,
I should have killed them!
Is this why...
your sister wanted to see you
as a doctor?
He didn’t spare her to see that!
Now he will do the same to Divya!
Everybody is a Yedhu!
-Not everybody.
-Iqbal!
You!
You only saw fear for Yedhu,
in Haseena.
I saw the pain she endured, for not
being able to save the truth in her womb.
It’s true!
You only had one sister.
She didn’t die alone.
A beast,
in spite of knowing that she was about to
become a mother, killed her.
Tell me a story, sister.
Once up on a time, a death!
Ignited vengeance in one...
and left repentance in another.
They both set out to find the beast
responsible for the death,
and entered a dark jungle.
While one fought with
that darkness for light,
the other one turned into a beast
himself while hunting for it,
and became the darkness
that engulfed the light.
If Haseena was in my place today,
she would have done the same.
♪ I witnessed all the
little stars in your smile ♪
♪ but those stars slipped away
like teardrops ♪
♪ I set out to give you an
everlasting friendship ♪
♪ but I burnt like a furnace
that engulfed you ♪
♪ Before I could rejoice like a
raindrop reaching the river ♪
♪ I swelled up like an ocean
and caught you off guard ♪
♪ Wish I had a boon to change the past ♪
Iqbal!
It is in the right hands, indeed!
Ma’am, gun!
Ma’am, magazine?
Madam never used the gun
since Haseena’s death.
That Satyabhama,
slayed Narakasura
with her weapons.
This Satyabhama,
gave up her weapons,
and triumphed in a war.
Sir, selfie!
- Thank you, sir!
- Amar sir!
Hey!
That was wonderful,
what you said about ma’am!
Of Course!
Who knows Satyabhama
better than Sri Krishna?
Thank you.
Amar?
Satya, where are you?
You are coming, aren’t you?
Just two minutes.
I’m coming!
Two minutes again?
Satya, come in!
Amar, stay on the line.
Okay!
Tell me, sir.
They are asking us to form
the crime team again.
Apparently, a stubborn case!
What do we do?