Thad...
I said no toys at Grandfather's.
But it's Christmas.
- Stop it!
- Hey.
Hey, Dad!
Hey! Thad,
you can't go crying to
other people all the time.
A man needs to know
when to stand up for himself.
Dear Magic-Isn't-Real Ball,
will Thad ever be a man?
Ouch.
"Outlook not so good."
You broke it.
Dad? Sid?
Someone help me!
Help!
Hello?
Thaddeus.
Thaddeus Sivana.
Who are you?
How do you know my name?
I am the last of the
Council of Wizards.
Sworn to protect the realms
from the Seven Deadly Sins.
But years have passed,
and I grow weak.
That is why I seek a champion
to inherit my magic.
You want me to do magic?
With this,
all of my powers
will become yours.
Ah. But first...
you must demonstrate
that you're pure of heart
and strong in spirit.
He lies.
Don't be his champion.
We can give you power.
Take the eye.
Take it.
Your father thinks you're weak.
Show him your power.
Take the eye.
No!
What?
What happened?
Only the purest of hearts
can resist their temptations.
But you,
you will never be worthy.
Wait.
- I'm good enough, I swear!
- What?
Let me back in!
Calm down, Thad!
- Don't open the door!
- Stop it!
- Calm down.
- Stop!
Hey, I'm gonna kill
you, you little freak!
Stop... Oh!
I was just there.
This man, this wizard, he
took me to a castle and...
Stop. Stop!
Stop it!
You miserable,
whiny, little shit!
You could have killed us!
Do you understand that?
Dad?
Dad!
You're okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You did this.
You did this!
No.
Dad.
Your magic grows weak.
Soon, you won't be
able to contain us.
Seeking Spell,
find me one soul who is worthy.
No matter how long it takes.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Holy moly! The boys in blue!
Sure glad to see you.
I called as soon as I saw.
They're in there.
You stay here.
Police!
I saw 'em hide back in there.
- Police, coming in!
- Police!
- There's nobody here.
- What do you mean?
- It's a closet.
- You really bought that, huh?
- Hey, no, no, no!
- Hey!
Stop, stop, stop!
Open this up right now, kid.
That's a federal offense,
kid. You can't do that!
Do not go in that car.
Come on, open the door. Please.
Please, come on.
Open this, right now!
Very good, very funny.
Very funny. That's
great. That's hilarious.
Uh, Dispatch, we need backup at the
Laurelwood shopping center, please.
Dispatch, cancel that request.
Some kid stole
our walkie-talkies.
Walkie-talkies? How old are you?
No, no, no.
That's my lunch, kid!
Miss Batson...
I've been looking for you.
No. Gosh.
It's me. It's Billy.
Okay.
I want the tiger.
I know, honey, I know. But
Mom's not exactly going pro here.
We got one!
But I wanted a tiger.
Oh, but this is the
real prize, baby. See?
You can use that
your whole life.
You'll always find your way.
I can't let the ball get away.
Mom?
Mom!
Hey.
Who are you with, bud?
Yeah, he says it's Billy Batson.
Hey, don't worry, kid.
I'm sure she'll come
looking before too long, okay?
They always do.
Mom, I'm home.
Yes?
Yeah, uh, is this Rachel Batson?
Who's asking?
Um...
Yeah, see, the thing is...
I think you're my mom.
You sure about that?
Sorry to bother you.
Just had to take my lunch, huh?
You save me any fries?
Foster home in Pittsburgh
reported you missing two weeks ago.
You're sending me back?
No.
They don't want you.
- Harsh.
- You laugh,
but you've run from foster
homes in six counties, Mr. Batson.
From good people
who want you, all
in pursuit of someone
who arguably does not.
It's time someone looked you in
the eye and told it to you straight.
I don't need parents to
play make-believe with.
- I got a mom.
- Yes.
You're some detective.
Seventy-three Batsons
between the ages of 28 to 40,
and you've crossed out every one.
She's still out
there. I know it.
There's a couple
outside, Mr. Batson.
They run a group home.
I can take care of myself.
When you're 18.
Until then, I won't have
you living on the streets,
looking for someone
who never looked for you.
Give these people a chance.
'Cause that's what
they're giving you.
You're out of options.
I'm gonna skip the spiel.
Just know that me
and Rosa, we get it.
We were foster
kids back in the day.
Ooh, back in the Dark Ages.
Girl, I'm young at heart.
I got my finger on the pulse.
Yeah, that's a reference
to his blood pressure
because he's old.
Billy, do you have
any food allergies?
Gonna wish you
did. Darla's cooking.
What?
We know how
overwhelming it can all be.
New house, new faces.
All up in your face.
Just take it at your own speed.
Hello?
We're home.
That's what happens
when you suck!
So much for the welcome party.
Yeah, that thing
growing out of the couch
would be Eugene.
Is that him?
Oh, my gosh! Billy!
Whoa! Slow down, slow down.
Welcome home!
- And that's Darla.
- I'm Darla.
Big hugger.
I noticed.
Die, die, die!
He doesn't mean
that. It's a game.
Hey.
No sodas after dark, remember?
Whoa. When did it get dark?
Oh, the poster. I made you one.
Come look! Oh, no!
Sorry, Pedro must've
been working out.
His goal is to get swole.
Just one hit! Just one hit!
Oh...
Here.
Yes, exactly why your math
department is so uniquely suited for me.
Shut up! No!
I can't even with
Eugene right now.
I'm sorry. Mary, hi.
College interview.
I'm Billy.
What am I most excited about?
Oh! What a great question.
I was hoping you'd ask.
What am I most excited about?
Mention you're a foster
kid. Colleges eat that up.
What I'm most excited about
is the campus experience.
As a foster child, I'm a big
believer in finding family and friends
in the most unlikely of places.
I'm gonna miss
that girl so much.
It's Caltech. It's a
very prestigious school.
And also all the
way in California.
But we don't have to
talk about that right now.
It's a tough subject for me.
Do you like vegan food?
- Mmm-mmm.
- Because, see, I love animals.
Oh, no! The Tofurky!
Oh, no, we may have
to eat a real turkey!
- Is that...
- It's okay.
Come, I'll show you your room.
It's a bit of a madhouse,
I know, but it's fun.
Time to dance on your grave!
Watch the bum step. Pedro...
Say hi to Billy.
Don't take it personally.
He's like that with everyone.
Freddy.
This is Billy Batson.
Make sure you make
him feel at home.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Maybe don't say
anything too weird?
Oh, one weird thing is,
did you know that Romans used
to brush their teeth with their urine?
And apparently, it works.
Yep. Um...
Oh, it's a long way down.
Trust me, I speak
from experience.
Victor pushed me.
They seem nice,
but don't buy it.
It gets real Game of
Thrones around here.
What?
Dude, I'm just messin' around.
It's, um, terminal cancer.
I only have three months.
Kidding, again! You look
at me, and you're like,
"Why so dark? You're a disabled
foster kid. You've got it all."
Right?
Oh, yeah, that's
the old Batarang.
I mean, it's a replica,
but feel how sharp.
I could kill you in your
sleep with that thing.
You more of a Supes guy?
Yeah, me, too.
Behold, the holy grail.
One nine-millimeter round
shot at Superman himself.
It's legit.
Probably worth, I don't know,
five, six hundred, maybe more.
What's in the bag?
Hey.
Hey, it's all good. It's good
to maintain boundaries.
You don't gotta talk
so much, you know.
Anyway, this place is
great. You're gonna love it.
Dinner!
All hands on deck.
Thank you for this family.
Thank you for this day.
Thank you for this food,
even if it's not steak filet.
Big school. 2,000
students, you might think,
"Wow, so many strangers."
But not if you think of them
as possible future friends.
Then it's, "Wow,
so many friends."
The principal, her name's
Shirley. She's the best.
Next.
This is our security scanner.
Like in an airport.
It's totally safe.
I know what it is.
- Does she always do this?
- Mmm-hmm.
Silence makes me uncomfortable.
She's almost never
uncomfortable.
Have a good first
day, big brother.
Look, you don't have
to hug me all the time.
We're not actually
brother and sister, so...
I'm sorry.
- Hey.
I didn't mean to make her...
I was overwhelmed, honestly.
He said I must be pure of heart.
He call himself a wizard.
He even dressed like a wizard
from Harry Potter or some...
But you're saying that other
people have experienced this?
In a sense, yes. Do you
remember what he said to you?
He tested me.
There were these statues.
Their eyes, it's like they were
looking at me, making me think things.
Horrible things.
And do these
approximate what you saw?
Yes, that's exactly
how I remember it.
I don't understand.
How do you know...
Recurrent imagery has proven very
common in cases of mass hysteria.
Mass hysteria?
I know. The term's
a bit theatrical.
But take UFO
sightings, for example.
Lights in the sky,
flying saucers.
Isolated incidents of people
who do not know each other...
The symbols.
Ask her about the symbols.
Sorry, Ms. Kwan. But as an
example of recurrent imagery,
maybe you'll recall seeing
these symbols before
the alleged abduction.
I don't remember
any symbols, no.
I think I got it on video.
There was something, um...
I remember the numbers
on my alarm clock.
They kept shifting.
Video?
Show me the video.
Uh, Ms. Kwan,
this is Dr. Sivana.
Um, one moment, I can send it.
Hello? Oh, my God!
Who's there?
Hello? What's going
on? What's happening?
I'm going to call the police!
Then this blinding
light all around me
and I felt like I was getting
pulled down into something.
It felt like a temple
carved inside a mountain.
He looked exactly what you'd expect
from a guy who calls himself a wizard.
and how you were brought
there to save the world.
- Wearing a cape.
- And there's no ceiling.
We ran the numbers again...
Dr. Sivana!
I appreciate your enthusiasm,
but you're funding my project.
And when I'm interviewing,
I don't wanna be interrupted.
Fifty-six recorded abductions.
- I never saw it.
- Saw what?
Doctor, what is all this?
All these years...
I was convinced I had
the incorrect sequence.
Or perhaps the wrong symbols
to open the door.
But on that woman's alarm
clock, the seven symbols.
The sequence repeated
itself seven times.
That's the difference.
Is this some sort of joke?
It may seem that way to you
because we're not in actuality
studying mass hysteria.
What all these people have seen,
every single one of
them, is absolutely real.
An alarm clock malfunctions
and your first thought
is it's proof of a wizard?
- Hmm.
- Come on, Dr. Sivana.
You can't believe
any of this is real.
Why, yes.
Yes, I do.
I've been waiting for
this moment for so long...
and now here we are.
You don't remember me, do you?
I remember you.
You were a boy.
And now you dare
intrude in my kingdom.
Do you know what it's like for a child
to be told you'll never be good enough?
No, you don't.
What you said to me all those years
ago made me realize who I really was.
And you know something?
I am not pure of heart.
The wizard is too
weak to stop us.
No!
You never found your champion.
But we found ours.
You are the true champion.
They're using you.
You're nothing to them
but a means of escape.
Through you, they'll spread their
poison to everything they touch!
Make mankind turn on each other!
You seek a pure soul, old man,
but no one's worthy.
Flight or invisibility?
If you could have
one superpower,
flight or invisibility,
what would you pick?
I mean, everybody chooses
flight. You know why?
So they can fly away
from this conversation?
No, no. 'Cause heroes fly.
And who doesn't want people
to think they're a hero, right?
But invisibility, no way.
That's pervy.
Spying around on people who
don't even know you're there.
Sneaking around everywhere.
It's a total villain power, right?
Then they did this study,
and this is a real thing.
They asked people the same question.
You know, what power do you want?
But this time, they made it so
the answers were anonymous.
And most people, since they knew
that it was secret, said invisibility.
And I think that's
'cause most people
don't feel like heroes
on the inside, deep down.
You're gonna run away.
I mean, you stole
my Superman bullet.
Dude, I get it. I get it.
You've been screwed
over way too many times.
You don't trust anyone.
That's the thing about invisibility.
You end up all by yourself.
I didn't steal your dumb bullet.
Hey. How was it today?
That good, huh'?
Whoa!
Oh, my God! Freddy.
Are you okay?
- You okay?
- Yes. Yes.
What the hell?
- What is wrong with you two?
- Oh, ho!
No way that's gonna buff out.
You gonna pay for that, Freeman?
For the dent you
made almost hitting me?
Yeah, sure. Um...
You guys take these?
Brett, stop!
Don't touch my brother!
What, do you need your
fake family to stand up for you?
- Stand up for yourself, Freeman.
- Yeah, huh?
Hey, Freeman.
Freeman, here, stand up.
Stand up for yourself.
What are you gonna do,
go home and cry to Mommy?
Oh, yeah. You
don't have a mommy.
Hey.
Man, sorry about that.
That wasn't fair, but then
again you don't fight fair, so...
Back off, assbags. I know
how to use these things.
Hey! He's getting
away! Where you going?
Freddy, are you okay?
Hey, let's go through the back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nowhere to run!
Hey!
- Go, go, go!
- Grab him! Move!
- Get out the way.
- Move, woman!
Whoa!
No, no, no.
You're dead, kid.
Yeah, you think you're funny.
We know where you
go to school, buddy!
Woman on PM Next
stop, 30th Street Station.
Change for the
regional rail lines.
Uh... Hello?
What's going on?
Help!
Okay.
Holy moly.
Hello?
What the hell?
Who's doing this?
Hi. Um...
I was supposed
to get off at 30th.
Billy Batson.
How'd you know my name?
I am the last of the
Council of Wizards.
Keeper of the Rock of Eternity.
Oh...
You're...
that guy.
Hey, listen, I don't
have any money.
Do not patronize me, boy.
You are standing in
the source of all magic.
The Rock of Eternity. Seven
thrones of seven wizards.
But long ago, we
chose a champion
and we chose recklessly.
He used his power for revenge,
releasing the Seven
Deadly Sins into your world.
Millions of lives were lost.
Entire civilizations
erased from existence.
That is why I vowed
never to pass on my magic
until I find one
truly good person.
Strong in spirit,
pure in heart.
Look, man, maybe this is magic
and, I don't know,
but the people you're
looking for, good, pure people,
I'm not one of them.
I don't know if
anyone is, really.
You, Billy Batson,
are all I have.
All the world has.
Lay your hands on my staff.
Gross.
And say my name so my
powers may flow through you.
I open my heart
to you, Billy Batson.
And in so doing,
choose you as champion.
Thanks.
Real sweet of you, mister,
but I really gotta get going.
My brothers and sisters
were slain by the Sins.
Their thrones lie empty.
My magic must be passed on.
Now, speak my name!
I don't know your
name, sir. We just met.
My name is...
Shazam.
Wait, for real?
- "Say it!
- OKay!"
Jeez.
So just say it'? Like...
Shazam?
Yes!
Carry my name, and with
it, you carry all my powers.
The wisdom of Solomon,
the strength of Hercules,
the stamina of Atlas,
the power of Zeus,
the courage of Achilles,
and the speed of Mercury.
What happened to me? Why am...
What did you do to me?
What did you do to my voice?
You have been transformed to
your full potential, Billy Batson.
With your heart, unlock
your greatest power.
The thrones of our
brothers and sisters await.
Get me outta here!
Dope!
My brother, I applaud
your choices today.
Gold shoes, gold
belt, white cape.
It shouldn't work,
but hot damn, it does!
Ow!
Hey!
Hey, babe!
Yes, Officer.
I'm aware he's run
away in the past.
Twenty-three times?
Guy's got no social
media presence. At all.
The guy is a ghost.
You know, guys, I'm
happy to look for Billy.
More than happy.
But no, you gotta wash the
dishes. That's what's more important.
"What are you gonna
do, Freddy, run after him?"
Very funny.
No, I said, don't scream.
- Uh... Victor? Victor!
- No, no!
- Victor!
- It's me. It's Billy.
It's Billy!
You asked me flight or
invisibility. I thought that was stupid,
but now I look like this
and I need your help.
Meet me back
here after lights-out?
'Sup, bud? You all right?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm just...
I'm really sad
because Billy's gone.
And, you know, maybe
it's my fault. Maybe I did it.
Uh, you know, maybe I snore.
Hey, hey, hey. Not
your fault, son, all right?
We'll find him, 'kay?
You don't snore that bad.
But you kinda smell.
Oh, thank God!
Hey. Stop right there.
How do I know you're not a
supervillain using telepathic abilities
to make me believe
that you're Billy? Huh?
What?
All I have to do is
press "dial" on this thing.
No! No., I have proof.
I have proof. Here.
Look, I lied, okay?
I took your bullet.
- Oh, no! No., no, no.
- No!
Stupid adult hands.
But you saw it.
You saw it, right? Look,
Freddy, I swear. It's me, okay?
Look, I know we're not really
close friends or anything,
but you're the only
person that I know
that knows anything about
this caped crusader stuff.
- That's Batman.
- What?
Forget it.
Can l...
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
On... on, my God!
It's crazy, right?
What are your superpowers?
Superpowers? Dude, I don't
even know how to pee in this thing.
Okay. Can you fly?
Okay!
Let's do this.
How do we do this?
Just, um, like, Superman it.
Oh, my God. Obviously,
you have to jump.
Come on.
How is any of this obvious?
Okay.
Try, uh, to believe
that you can fly. Okay?
I read this deep dive
into peer-reviewed
studies about superpowers
and in six out of
ten, belief is the key.
Belief. Belief. Belief. Okay.
Okay. I believe I can fly.
I believe I...
I believe I can fly.
I believe...
Whoa!
Did you believe?
Yeah.
You wanna try invisibility?
How do I do...
Forget it. You know, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God! It worked!
Where'd you go?
I'm right here.
You can't see me?
Where?
I'm invisible!
I'm right here. Over here.
I'm invisible! I'm invisible!
Hey!
Nice outfit, dipshit.
I might've been
testing invisibility
and super-intelligence
at the same time.
Freeman, I'm gonna come
over there and beat you.
Oh, my God! The
lightning emblem!
It was staring us right in
the face the whole time.
Literally!
Okay, okay.
Clearly, we gotta give you a
lightning-themed superhero name.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
Hey, yo! Back...
off.
Hyper-speed, check.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I thought you were the
one who was screaming.
I doused him with pepper spray.
Smart move.
Yeah, hey, Mr. Mugger Guy.
Give the old lady her purse back.
I'm your age.
And he didn't get a chance to
take it 'cause I didn't let him take it.
Good. Yeah, good. You're
really on top of this stuff.
And that should teach
you that old ladies...
Regular-aged ladies like yourself
don't need your protecting, right?
So get woke, bro.
I'm sorry, who are you?
His name is Thundercrack,
hero to the people with all the
power and speed of lightning all in one.
Dude, that sounds
like a butt thing.
Mister Philadelphia.
That's a cream
cheese thing, dude!
Power Boy. 'Cause
he's got all the powers.
'Cause sometimes pepper
spray can't protect against evil.
Power Boy, do
you know this child?
Like a teeny little bit.
I don't really know...
Yeah. He's like a little
miniature manager.
I'm his manager.
But Power Boy's not gonna work,
either, okay? So work on something else.
Hey, bud, what could...
Electricity manipulation,
hyper-speed, super-strength.
Dude, you're stacked!
You're almost as cool
as Superman. Almost.
I didn't see you. I don't know
what just happened here.
I don't wanna know.
Just don't hurt me.
- I'm not doing it for the money.
- Thank you for your kind donation.
No, no, no, but if you
ever need any more help
just look for the
superhero that still can't fly.
Forget flying, man.
We just made 73 bucks!
Seventy-three bucks?
Come on!
Hey, wait a minute.
I just got an idea.
I'd like to purchase some
of your finest beer, please.
I don't know about this. I mean,
we don't have a fake ID even.
Freddy, Freddy, would you relax?
Look at me. I am the fake ID.
Everything from the register!
Go, go! Now!
Come on! We don't have
any time. Let's go. Move!
We want it all! Hurry.
This is your chance.
Oh! Okay.
Come on, come on,
come on! Let's do this!
That's it. That's it.
Gentlemen,
why use guns when we
can handle this like real men?
Billy, look out!
Bullet immunity. You
have bullet immunity!
I'm bulletproof.
Today is December 8th,
and this is video
proof of authenticity.
Shoot him again.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here, here. Go. Both of you!
Come on. Go to town.
Wait, wait, wait.
We still don't know if
the suit is bulletproof,
or if you are.
Shoot him in the face.
Shoot me in the
face. In the face?
It kinda tickles.
You're dead.
- Sorry about your window.
- Have a good night!
But you're welcome
for not getting robbed!
Come on! Let's get outta here.
Hey.
- To fighting bad guys.
- Yeah.
Bleh!
Ugh!
That tastes like actual vomit.
Hey, do you know habanero jerky,
if you eat enough of it, it can
burn a hole in your stomach?
Worth it.
Yeah. Probably not you, though.
You've probably got stomach superpowers.
Probably. Oh, hey.
What's up? I'm a superhero.
Yeah, his name is, uh,
Captain Sparklefingers.
No, it's not. No, it's
not! That's not my name.
Hey, we should hang out.
We're, like, the same age.
Oh, okay. I'm out.
Hey, wait up!
I mean, it's a pretty sick view.
I totally get why Rocky was
training so hard to get up here.
You know, I like you
like this. This is so cool.
I mean, no offense,
but, like, at first you were kinda
like the opposite of how Darla is.
A dick?
Your words. Not mine.
But yeah.
All right, well, I feel
like every criminal
is either on drugs
or asleep by now.
Wanna head home?
Looking like this?
Well, yeah,
I mean, usually, we'd
have a lair to go back to,
but that's long-term.
Right now, we have a bunk bed.
Just scares me thinking
of him out there all alone.
This is what he does, Rosa.
Difference is, when they find him,
we'll be the first to take him back.
With open arms.
Didn't even make it two
days. Not even two days.
Baby, we did our fair share
of running off back when.
At least I did.
- Yeah.
- Even Mary did it.
Hmm? Twice.
That second time she ran off,
you said something
to me I'll never forget.
You said,
"It's not a home until
you call it a home.
It's something you choose."
All we can do is give
him a place full of love.
Whether he chooses to call
it a home, that's up to him.
Yeah.
You gonna help
me with this tree?
This tree's so sad.
Hello?
Got lost finding the bathroom.
Oh, okay, Freddy,
sweetie. Good night.
- Good night.
- Night.
Freddy, who is that?
It's Billy. He's just really
tired and he has laryngitis.
What? Laryngitis!
I'm just kidding!
I'm just kidding.
He's really, really tired, and
he wants to go to beddy-bye.
- Beddy-bye? Who says beddy-bye?
- Just hide, hide.
Billy, you're back.
Let us see you.
We've been so worried about you.
I told you this was a bad idea!
Freddy?
Freddy, what
happened to the stairs?
Mmm!
Hey! Covering her mouth
like you're gonna kidnap her
is not gonna make
her less scared, okay?
Darla, it's me. It's Billy. I
know I don't look like me.
- A wizard made me look like this.
- Maybe don't start with "wizard."
It's just gonna make
her more confused.
Some old guy brought me to a
temple and he made me say, "Shazam."
Rosa!
Verbally triggered
body-manipulation properties!
You can switch by
saying, "Shazam."
Baby, was that
you? Are you okay?
Uh...
I was screwing in a bulb.
Listen to me, Darla. You cannot
tell anybody about this, all right?
But it's Billy. He's a hero.
Yeah, but if a supervillain
finds out that he's a hero,
that endangers us, okay?
A hero's loved ones are
the perfect bad guy target.
I mean, is she even
good at keeping secrets?
- Moderate.
- No.
Oh, God.
Okay, listen, D,
you cannot tell a single soul
about this, all right? Please?
Why? What if it's
people we trust?
Because good sisters
don't tell secrets.
- I'm a good sister.
- Yeah, you are.
You know what'd make
you an even better sister?
Is if you fixed the
doorknob for us, okay?
Yeah.
- Sweet dreams.
- Sweet dreams. Bye.
- See you in the morning.
- Good night.
Hello, sir. How may I help you?
Hi. Sir?
Sir, you can't go in
there. Excuse me!
You cannot go in there!
Sorry I'm late.
Thad, this is for
board members only.
I'm aware of that, Father.
Now, that night in the car.
I swore to you I saw something,
but you never believed me.
So much easier to
blame me, wasn't it?
And say that if I hadn't
screamed that night,
you'd still have your legs.
Well, now I have proof.
That's enough, Thad.
Dear Sid, you think?
You know, even before the
accident, you belittled me.
Don't make me throw
you outta here, Thad.
You don't need to make a scene.
Oh, brother,
the scene has only just begun.
Ask that if you
can throw me out.
What?
Ask the ball if you're man enough
to throw me out of this room.
Let me spoil it for you.
Outlook not so good.
I've come here during the
season of giving to give you...
what you deserve.
Run!
Oh, my God! No!
No! No!
Help!
Somebody!
Help me!
You can't go crying to
other people all the time.
What sin best befits
you, Father? Hmm?
I'll give you anything.
Money.
The company. You
want the company?
There it is.
Greed.
Do you honestly think
all this material
you've accumulated
amounts to actual power?
This is power.
More than you ever had.
More than anyone has.
There is one more powerful.
The wizard found his champion.
Kill the champion before
he learns his true potential,
or he will defeat you.
Show me where to find him.
Oh, Greed,
you can have him.
No.
No.. Oh, no!
No! No! No!
Family is more than just a word.
At Sivana Industries,
our focus is family.
Uh, Burke.
Where's the truck?
I can hear it.
Oh, my God!
My truck!
- My truck!
- Are you kidding?
You know, guys,
I don't think that's
gonna buff out.
Hey.
Making the crippled kid
do the dirty work. Wow!
I'm a better lookout.
I can play innocent.
And I can't?
Your face gives off a very strong vibe
of someone who's hatching schemes.
- My face? This face?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
You boys got a hall pass?
Oh, us? Yeah. Always.
You!
You look like you're
up to something.
Me? Up to something?
No. Never am I up to something.
Our dad's picking us up.
He got held up at the...
The business office.
The business office, huh?
Sure, kid.
Look, parents or guardians
must appear physically
to check out students.
Gotcha.
Okay, well, you hear that, Dad?
- Hey!
- Shazam!
Well, hey there, son,
and hey there, other
son that I also have
that's related to that son I
just passed in the hallway.
I'm so sorry I'm late. I got
held up at the business office,
doing all the work stuff.
This is the security guard
all the kids admire so much.
Oh.
Actually, that's the other
one. This one sucks.
That's not funny.
I'm gonna talk to him
about that. I apologize.
Anyway, this is me appearing
physically to check my sons out of school.
So, thank you so much for
keeping 'em safe, Detective Moron.
It's Moran.
- You ready?
- Algebra!
Science!
English!
Health!
Oh. Oh.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry!
More powerful than a locomotive.
Locomotive. What are
you? An old prospector?
Can leap tall buildings
in a single bound.
Single bound.
Oh!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry, people. Hi.
- Your phone's charged.
- Wow!
Your phone's charged.
You really need like a mic drop
catchphrase after you do some cool shit.
I've been thinking about that.
What about this?
"That's why you don't
mess with electricity."
Catchphrases obviously
aren't one of your superpowers.
And your phone's charged.
- Well, you think you can do better?
- What the hell?
Let there be light.
Yeah, yeah, baby.
Yeah, baby, okay.
How do I... Never mind.
Shazam!
What'd you see? What'd
you see? Were there boobies?
You see nipples?
Why aren't you talking?
We're gonna need more money.
Why? You were in there
for, like, five minutes.
Dude, they were very convincing!
Oh, get it, get it!
Go, go, go!
No!
Stop! No!
- I'm not even looking!
- Stop!
- I'm not even looking! Oh!
- Why?
- Oh, and done!
Finished him.
A lair.
Yes.
And obviously,
we're gonna have to
- be making this purchase anonymously.
- Mmm.
Obviously.
And, um, if you have
a location on a cliff.
Like a castle-esque type thing.
- Overlooking some water.
- Overlooking some water,
seas, below it.
Rough, you know...
Like a waterfall,
- so you can drive into...
- Waterfall, yeah. If you... Yeah.
Look, Maximum Voltage, is it?
You can call me Max.
Look, Max, why don't you just start with
how many bedrooms you're looking for?
- One!
- Seven.
- One?
- Seven?
What, am I running
a foster home now?
Have you seen the one where
he throws the football into space?
So dope.
Hey, you guys gotta wonder
who's filming those, right?
I mean, that's
bravery in and of itself.
I mean, is it, though?
Yeah. I'd actually argue
maybe even more brave.
Holding a camera?
Staring in the face of danger.
Like some weirdo fanboy.
Hey, Freeman.
I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
What, is your bestie gonna hit
us with a wheelchair this time?
No, maybe not him, but I
have another best friend
who might hunt you down
and destroy both of you.
Okay, Freddy.
You may have heard of him.
The Human Power Storm.
Frequency Flinger.
Sir Zaps-A-Lot.
Yeah. He's a man of many names.
You know the Red Cyclone?
You? My ass you do.
Oh, we're a lot
closer than you think.
Maybe even at this very moment.
Prove it.
I will, tomorrow. Tomorrow
he's gonna come to lunch.
Right, right, Billy?
Oh, yeah, and then Superman's
gonna be bringing us dessert, right?
Tomorrow at lunch. You'll see.
And when he doesn't show,
then we'll kick your ass.
So, wait, my identity's a secret
so no one I know can get hurt.
Except when it makes you
look cool, then it's all good.
Billy, it's not like
they're supervillains.
They're just super douchebags.
So, you're breaking
your own rule?
Got it.
This thing is as much
as mine as it is yours.
Starting to think you
think it's all your thing.
Billy, you're still gonna
do it, though, right?
I mean, what would
a good brother do?
All hands on deck.
Thank you for this family.
Thank you for this day.
Thank you for this food.
Sorry Billy's hand's on vacay.
Big news in Philly.
Got a costumed hero.
He's doing good.
Yeah, but is he, though?
Ooh! Controversy. Into it.
Share with us your
perspective, Eugene.
Just saying, he's what?
Charging people's phones?
So what? I can charge
a phone with a plug.
Preach.
Pedro, any thoughts?
Costume's stupid.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Big white cape like he's
getting married or something.
What if he didn't get
to pick his costume?
Ever think about that?
You're a specialist,
Freddy. What do you think?
Yeah, Freddy, let's
manage to see the positive.
Okay, Well, I
think it looks like
he doesn't have gratitude
for what he's been given.
Very specific. All right.
Maybe to the superhero,
gratitude doesn't mean
having to be clingy.
Clingy? Wow, interesting take.
You know, maybe sometimes a
superhero just wants a little me time.
You know, me time could also be
construed as pushing away his family.
Family. Is that
what they are now?
It's a classic symptom
of "Superhero Syndrome."
Coined by German psychologist
Heinrich Von German-something,
where superpowers become
an all-consuming narcotic.
Son, we're still eating dinner.
What he needs is a sidekick.
Name one cool sidekick.
Darla, why are you so
quiet over there, baby?
You're never at
a loss for words.
I'm eating.
Why am I still doing this?
Well, you can't skip every day.
Not at your age.
But I'm not your age anymore.
But I can go with you.
We just gotta trick the
guard out, you know?
Billy, where are you going?
You're still gonna have
lunch with me, right?
Billy!
Sir Zaps-A-Lot's still gonna
eat in the cafeteria, right?
All right.
Did you check it to...
People typically give me
a little money, you know...
You're a sweet couple.
You guys have a good day.
Ooh!
- Oh, my God.
- Mary, are you okay?
How do you know my name?
Uh... How do I know
your name? Uh...
One of my superpowers
is name guessing.
Which is really weird, I bet.
Uh, it's not as cool as
super-strength or super-speed,
but it's really helpful
when I meet new people.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay. Thank you. Um...
I just need a second to think.
This has been such a weird day.
Um, using my powers
of super-observation,
I see that you're holding a
letter from a college in your hand.
Are you upset because
you didn't get in?
I got in.
Well, now my superpowers are
failing me and I am very confused.
Yeah. Me, too.
I don't know. I know
I should be excited
'cause this is my dream and I've
worked really, really hard for this,
but it's like...
I don't know. Leaving my family
does not feel fun, you know?
Could I give you a
little piece of advice?
Don't be worried about everybody
else. Always look out for number one.
Gandhi said that.
- I don't think he said that.
- Yeah, he did.
- Gandhi did not say...
- Somebody like Gandhi said that.
"Take care of number one."
It was a really wise...
It might've been Yoda.
- Listen.
- I'm sorry, no.
Agree to disagree. The point
is, you do you, you know?
You gotta look out for you. And get
as far away from this place as you can.
I don't know if I want to.
Of course you do.
What're you gonna do?
You gonna live in a group
home for the rest of your life?
Look, families are for people
who can't take care of
themselves, okay? So...
And you can take
care of yourself.
Also, look both ways
when you cross the street.
I'll just call him.
I'll just make sure.
It's ringing.
Red Cyclone, hey!
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, that's crazy! Yeah,
it's Freddy, by the way.
Yeah, it's crazy! Great story.
He's not talking to anyone.
I was!
I was! We're friends.
I know him, I do!
I know him! I know
him! Uh, yeah.
Shit.
Come on now.
Hands! Lightning with my hands!
Lightning with my hands!
Hey. Hey.
Hey, young man! Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing? I'm in
the middle of a show right now.
How can I help you?
I just wanted to say thank you
for showing up to lunch today.
Yeah, I got a little something
called a, uh, suitcase wedgie, right?
I don't know if you've
ever heard of it,
but it's when someone
grabs your underwear like that
and holds you like a suitcase,
walks you down the hallway.
And this was my underwear.
Gross.
You said you'd come.
You said I would come!
I never said I was...
I'm a superhero, dude!
Well, you're acting real heroic.
How much people
paying you today?
Listen, I have serious
responsibilities now, okay?
But that's cool because I
can carry that burden with my...
Hands! Lightning with my hands!
Oh, man!
Holy moly.
Don't move! Nobody move!
Oh, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Stay, stay! Stay!
Oh!
Oh, that looked like it hurt.
It's him! It's that
superhero guy!
Help us! Save us!
Come on!
Come on... Yeah.
What's he doing?
What's going on?
No way.
Oh, no, no. Please
don't make me do this.
God, this is the
worst idea ever!
I did it! I did it!
I got the bus! I got the bus.
Nobody move in there.
Oh, I gotta put this thing
down. I gotta put this thing down.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no. Doggy,
doggy, you have to move.
Move! Move! Shoo! Shoo!
Please be a good dog, good dog!
You're being a bad dog!
Go! Go!
Please go. Please move.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, no, no, no, no.
I was in the neighborhood,
you know, so I thought...
Thank you!
It was kind of my fault anyway.
So, it seems Philadelphia has
gotten an early Christmas present
in the form of its
very own superhero.
And we're out.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, of course, yeah.
Dude! Dude, dude!
Dude, did you see that?
Yeah. You electrocuted a bus
and almost killed these people.
And then I caught it!
Freddy, I caught a bus
with my bare hands, man!
I caught a bus like
people catch fly balls.
Like, who does that? I do that!
Billy! You do nothing.
You take selfies and
make people pay you.
You know, forget it. I can't really
talk to you when you look like this.
You just wish it was you.
No shit!
You think? I would kill
to have what you have.
Because everything
I do is, like,
some desperate attempt
to get people to notice me.
To not feel sorry for me.
I mean, look at me! Look
at me. Do you even see me?
'Cause most people don't.
'Cause they don't want to.
And now you don't either.
I mean, you think
this is who you are?
I mean, Billy, you're 14,
and now you're no
better than the Breyers.
All this power, and all you did
was turn into a show-off and a bully.
Whatever, kid!
I do what I want!
And I'm, like, mid-20s probably!
Maybe even, like, 30.
Chosen one.
The so-called perfect man.
Pure of heart.
Flawless in every way.
What made you so worthy?
I'm sorry, can I help...
Do you want an
autograph or something?
Give me your power.
Or die.
Oh, snap! You're,
like, a bad guy, right?
Okay. Okay, okay, okay. Before
this gets really stupid for you,
you should know that
I'm basically invincible.
The weapons of man
draw no blood from our kind.
I said, stop right there!
The only thing that
extinguishes magic...
is magic.
Time to transfer
your power to me.
Oh, you did not see that
one coming, did you, grandpa?
Them's street rules.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I never should've punched
you in the nuts like that.
That was totally my bad.
We can talk about this.
You grovel like a child.
That's because I
am one. I'm a kid!
You don't wanna
hurt a kid, do you?
I believe I can fly! I
believe I can fly, I can fly!
Freddy said if I believe
I can fly, then I can fly.
So I believe! I
believe! I believe!
Okay.
Superman!
Superman! What arm is it?
Why am I not flying?
Please, I don't wanna die!
I'm floating!
What the hell was that?
I can fly!
Billy?
Freddy! I need your help!
You can fly?
Who's the other guy?
Santa!
So, like, what do you and Mrs.
Claus do in the summertime?
Well, in some ways,
Santa is always here for you.
Help Santa!
Santa needs help! Help!
Give us a shout if you need us.
I'm just gonna chill in here
for a little while, if that's okay.
This is crazy.
This is crazy. You don't
have to fight this guy.
This isn't your job.
You can run, right?
Yes, you can run. Awesome!
Get back!
Get away!
- I'm Batman!
- Get him, Batman!
Oh, sorry.
Come on!
Shazam!
Billy!
Billy, where are you?
Where are you, Billy?
Billy, come on!
Billy. Where is he?
Supervillain.
Supervillain! Supervillain!
Worse. Much worse.
Radioactive anthromorph?
Psychic energy manipulator?
I won't let you read my mind.
My mind is blank. You can't get in.
I don't need to read your mind.
Because you are going to tell me.
Where is he?
Oh, my God, honey, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What happened? Are you hurt?
Come inside.
We need to have a talk.
Just don't be so
hard on him, okay?
Running out on us! Lying!
Huh? Then I get a call from the school,
telling me you've been cutting class!
Getting in fights!
Bill, the man saved nine people.
Whoa! Is that...
I'm questioning his motive.
What's Freddy doing
with a superhero?
Or what's a superhero
doing with Freddy?
You remember dinner,
when Billy and Freddy were arguing
like an old married couple, like this?
When he rescued me, he
knew I lived in a group home.
He knew my name.
He called me Mary.
Wait, are you saying Billy's
the Human Power Storm?
Yes! You guys figured it out!
All on your own. I didn't help.
- I didn't break any promises.
- You knew?
I'm a good sister!
I mean, what were you thinking?
And then you
bring Freddy into it.
Give him some space,
guys. He's a little upset, okay?
Billy?
You're him.
You're the hero.
Yeah, well, not anymore, so...
Why do you have my notebook?
Eugene finished your search.
Look, I'm not a hacker, okay?
But I have played
Watch Dogs and Uplink.
And maybe I did pick up a few
skills, which maybe did get me
into federal databases
most people can't get into.
Good for you, but I'm gonna go.
Your parents' names are
Marilyn and C.C. Batson.
What?
You were born in
Zumbrota, Minnesota.
They divorced
when you were three.
Your mom moved here that year.
Twenty months later, you got lost.
You never found them
'cause your dad's been in
prison in Florida for ten years.
And your mom's...
What?
Is she dead?
She's two subway stops away.
What?
You know, you didn't find her because
she reverted to her maiden name.
Hey, Billy! Billy!
- Victor, get the keys.
- I got it.
Kids, stay here in
case Billy comes back.
Come on. Inside, let's go.
Wait. I thought we
were running after Billy.
No, we're gonna
wait here for now.
Billy?
Freddy?
Oh, how quaint.
Actually, I take that back.
What a shithole.
Just a second.
Hey, look, I'm late for
work already, all right?
We don't need any magazines
or whatever. Thanks, though.
Oh, I'm not.
You probably don't
recognize me...
but I found my way home.
Mom.
It's me.
Oh, God.
Is it?
Um... Hang on.
Who's at the door?
It's, um...
It's no one, Travis.
That wasn't Dad, was it?
No.
Listen, um...
It's really you, huh?
I didn't mean to run
away. You know that, right?
I let go, but it
was by accident.
Yeah, no. I know, yeah.
I saw you.
What?
I saw you after.
So, it was never your fault.
Look, I was 17, okay? And
my daddy kicked me out.
And your dad just decided
not to be a part of anything.
And I was hurting,
and I was screwed up.
- I want the tiger.
- I know.
I know, honey,
but Mom's not exactly
going pro here, okay?
Billy?
Billy!
Jesus Christ. Billy,
this isn't funny!
Here you go, buddy.
That should warm
you up. Is that better?
Look, it's just once I
saw you with the police,
I realized that they could do
a better job taking care
of you than I ever will.
But you're good, right?
I mean, you landed on your feet.
Because, I mean,
you look real good.
It's just...
now is not a really
good time for me, Bill.
All I wanted to do is let
you know I'm doing good,
but I have to get
back to my real family.
Here.
What's this?
Marilyn! What's
goin' on out there?
You might need it more than me.
Freddy, you were right.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Come home, Billy. Come home.
- Billy! Supervillain!
- Supervillain!
Shazam!
Who are you? What do you want?
What do I want?
I want...
That.
Whoa.
Kick his ass, Billy!
Yes, Billy.
Try it, by all means.
Let them go and
I'll come inside.
No, first, you come inside,
then maybe I'll let them go.
Good boy.
Because that's
all you are, isn't it?
How old are you?
- Basically 15.
- Hmm.
When I was a child, the old
man told me I wasn't good enough.
Yet here you are, a coward.
Run from me and the wizard
chooses you? You're not a hero.
But I'm gonna give you
the opportunity to be one.
Give me the power
of the champion.
No. Don't do it, Billy.
Give me the power
and I'll let them go.
Darla, no.
Don't go, Billy.
- Don't go, Billy.
- Darla, come here.
No, I have to.
It's what a good
brother would do. Right?
Billy.
I dedicated my
life to getting here.
I scoured the earth.
No one believed me.
No one helped.
Not the wizard.
Not my family.
I only had myself.
I get it.
I get what that's like.
Feeling like you're
all alone in the world.
Stand.
Feeling like there's that one
thing, and if you could just find it,
then you'd finally
be good enough.
Stand.
The champion's name.
Say it.
Look, no offense, mister,
but I don't think these things
have your best interest at heart.
Don't listen to this child.
Take the staff.
Hold it and say the
champion's name.
They're using you.
You have to see that,
that they are using you.
Say your name.
His name...
is Captain Sparklefingers.
And we're gonna keep
throwing things at your big,
fat, ugly-eyed head,
until you let our brother go.
Boy, am I glad I didn't
sell that Batarang.
- Pedro, is that a lamp?
- It's an ugly one.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Guys, I appreciate the thought,
I really do, but I don't think
your weapons are gonna help.
You can put 'em down now.
The door was right here.
Billy, how do we get outta here?
What, you think I
know? I don't know.
This way!
Go, go, go. Follow Darla.
Good job, Darla. Go, go, go!
Kids?
Why is this open?
Freddy? Mary?
Pedro, Pedro, come on.
Freddy? Freddy, keep up.
Darla, stay in front.
We gotta hurry.
Whoa!
So many doors.
One of these has to
be a way out, right?
Yeah, I would hope so.
Not this one.
Okay, no more doors.
Nobody open any more doors.
Come on, Billy. What
are we gonna do?
Darla, I don't know.
Yes, you do. Just think.
How'd you get out last time?
Uh, last time, I thought about the
subway, and I was on the subway.
Okay. Then, Billy, look,
think about the subway.
Think about any place
except for here, okay?
Come on, come on, come on.
Why are you covering my eyes?
Really? This is the first
place you think of? Wow!
You're welcome!
Why can't I see what's inside?
You are not old enough.
Old enough to know
that was great music.
Not my thing.
Where's Freddy?
Yeah, you, too, Sriracha.
Hey, have a holly
jolly Christmas.
Freddy! What are you doing?
Nice people.
Nice people? Come on.
Is that glitter? They have
glitter! Can I get glitter?
No, not from them.
Please?
No..
Darla.
Go, go, go. Everybody, go!
Freddy? Freddy, Freddy.
One, two, three.
Up, up. Up we go.
Carnival, go! Go, Mary, go.
Come on, Pedro. Come on.
Don't run, but don't
walk. Just be cool.
Act naturally, like kids
naturally act in a carnival.
- He's not gonna look for us here.
- Is that him?
- Oh, my God!
- Dude, it's Zap-tain America!
- Power Boy!
- He's an impersonator, okay?
Yeah, I'm an impersonator!
I'm a fake version of myself.
Don't take pictures.
Shazam!
Hey! Where'd he go?
What, is he invisible now?
Oh, man, I just spit on a baby!
Yo, what is that?
Who is that guy?
Champion.
You don't deserve that name.
See that? Look at that up there!
Hiding behind innocent
people who will now die.
Because deep down you're
still just a scared little boy.
Oh, no.
Run! Run!
- Oh! What do we do?
- Just hold on!
- To what?
- The bar, you idiot!
Well, you wanted
me to be a hero.
Are you kidding?
Okay, no. Old guy's up there
harboring multiple spiritual entities.
Plus, he has the
same powers as you.
Plus, I mean, he
knows what he's doing.
Plus, I mean, you're my best
friend. I don't want you to die.
If a superhero
can't save his family,
he's not much of a hero.
That was a decent catchphrase.
Shazam!
Now, let's try this again.
Or try that again!
Billy, look out!
Laser eyes! Guys,
he's got laser eyes!
Too bad your aim sucks balls!
That's his power matrix.
His what-what?
When the demon guys leave
his eye, he loses his powers.
That's why the
Batarang hurt him.
Hey!
Over here!
- Wait. What are you doing?
- Trust me. Divide and conquer.
We separate the Sins from the
eye, and he's just an old man.
Gather the mutts.
Run!
Darla, no!
Here. Take it.
Take it. It's for you.
Hold it tight.
Close your eyes.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Shazam!
Playtime's over, boy.
Your friends can't
help you anymore.
Shazam!
Hey!
Nice trick.
Catchy.
One simple word.
I have a better trick.
Four words.
Kill the little girl.
- Darla, no!
- Take me instead!
Stop!
Billy, there's one more
demon guy in his eye!
You gotta just rip it
out of his face hole!
It's where he gets his power.
Reach for it.
I dare you.
Wise decision.
Hands on the staff.
Billy, don't do this. Billy!
- Billy.
- Don't do it, Billy!
Don't!
Say my name so my
power may flow through you.
I open my heart
to you, Billy Batson.
And in so doing,
choose you as champion.
With your heart, unlock
your greatest power.
The thrones of our
brothers and sisters await.
All hands on deck.
Say my name.
Billy!
No, not my name.
Say the name that I
say to turn into this guy.
Shazam!
Guys.
What's happening?
I can fly!
Guys.
Check out these guns.
No. It's not possible.
Gee-whiz, mister.
Sorry I took your cane.
Do you want it back?
Guys, I don't
believe in violence,
but I think we should kick
this guy's butt, like, really hard.
Whoa!
Guys, I think I
can move really...
fast.
Hyper-speed! Check!
Billy! The eye!
Look out!
Whoa!
What?
- What!
- Dude!
You almost exploded me.
Dude, I've studied
the fighting techniques
of every single superhero.
What do you got?
Well, that's terrifying.
Enough games, boy.
You think a pack
of children can...
Wait, what?
You will beg for mercy
as I feast on your heart...
slow.
Are you making some big evil
guy speech right now or something?
You're, like, a mile away from me
right now. There's cars and trucks.
I will have the world eating
out of the palm of my hand...
All I see is mouth
moving. I don't hear any...
Only I have the
power to unleash...
Ah, whatever. Screw it.
Oh, my gosh. Those people!
Hi!
Wow. I caught you.
I got it. I got it.
Oh, my God. I do got it.
You're not gonna believe this,
but you're actually the
first villain I've ever fought.
It's kind of a huge deal for me.
Somebody help!
Hi. Wow. It's really you.
My name is Darla, and
I've been really good.
What?
Oh, crap.
No, no, no.
No, no. No!
No! No, no.
Oh, my God!
Is he giving us
suitcase wedgies?
So this is, like, the
Seven Deadly Sins, right?
I mean, I've never
been great at math,
but, uh, the big, angry
one, that's Wrath, yeah?
And then Gluttony, obvi.
Pride, Greed, Sloth, Lust,
who I thought was gonna be
way hotter, if I'm being honest.
But that's only six. Where's
lucky number seven?
Where's little man?
Where's Envy?
Is he just scared of me and my
family because we're so awesome?
Because I get that.
Like, the other sins, they
get to come out and fight
because they're big
and strong and scary.
But Envy...
he's just the runt.
And that's why all the other sins
never invite him out to play, man.
Because they all know who'd win.
And it's not weak,
worthless, ugly Envy.
Gotcha.
Shazam!
Ready to go round
up your buddies?
No. No!
Here's the thing about power.
What good's power, if you
got nobody to share it with?
- Nice.
- Ta-da!
That's disgusting.
Fatality.
I got the voice.
What's that?
I can have anything
I've ever wanted?
Billy.
No, no, no!
- Stop it!
- Don't look at that!
Billy, don't do it!
Ah!
- You should hear yourselves!
- Not funny.
You think I'm gonna put
a demon ball in my head?
That's disgusting.
That's funny. That's pretty
funny. You got me going.
- You got me going.
- Uh... Guys.
What?
Oh. Hey.
Oh, wow.
All right, We did it!
Hey, all right, yeah! We did it!
We did it!
Hey, you guys are all safe.
There's no more danger anymore.
- We're fine. It's okay.
- All right, all right, all right.
We're good.
You sure this is gonna work?
Told ya.
Whoa!
You guys know what
this place is, right?
A dark, haunted cave
with demon statues.
Well, yes, but also...
Lair! We got a lair!
- Lair.
- Yeah.
No, you right.
We got a lair.
What's a lair?
And thanks to six superheroes,
citizens are back in their homes,
safe again with their families.
And here with an eyewitness
account of the events...
It was crazy, man!
Creatures from hell!
Lightning coming out
of everyone's everything!
And that is not cool, man!
So, first day as a superhero.
Automatic top
spot for best ever.
The man shattered
the glass noodle ceiling.
- No. That's racist.
- Not if I say it.
Guys.
- All hands on deck.
- Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Thank you for this food.
Thank you for this day.
Thank you for this family.
I thought maybe
this time I'd stay.
I mean, after all,
I'm home.
He better not sit at our table.
Nope!
Okay.
What are you doing?
Waiting for your
imaginary BFF to show up?
Yeah.
What are you guys doing here?
Well, we're having
lunch with you.
But you guys have
different lunch periods.
Well, we made a very
special arrangement.
- Darla, what's going on?
- Why are you asking me?
Freddy Freeman.
This guy taught me everything I
know about being a dope superhero.
True story. You should
get some pointers from him.
What's going on, my best
bud in the whole world?
And also new kids that I'm meeting
for the first time but seem very cool?
Uh...
I invited another friend.
I hope that's okay.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Sun of Ra.
Ouroboros.
Solomon's...
Knot.
No! No!
Primitive symbols.
You walking, talking monkeys
with your cave drawings.
You assume there's only
one way to gain magic.
No, no, no.
There are more ways
than a mind can imagine.
What in God's name?
I name the gods, Doctor.
Not the other way around.
Oh, what fun we're
going to have together.
The Seven Realms
are about to be ours.
Don't beat yourself up, buddy.
You're gonna find someone.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Because there's
plenty of fish in the sea.
Of course it's not
real. I can't talk to fish.
Even if I could, I mean, honestly,
what could we do with that that's cool?
I don't know, maybe command
an army of billions in the ocean.
Oh, yeah. Well,
that's not that cool.