Sir, I'm sure you remember
that massive gang war
that took place between
all the drug dealers in Mumbai.
It was about three years ago, you know?
All of them were busy killing each other.
And the ones who were left,
police killed them.
Some of the policeman were given medals,
some of them lost their jobs.
Why did all this happen?
Not because the police wanted
to get rid of the drug business here...
but because Nayak wanted it that way.
He could see that Mumbai had the potential
to become the drug capital of Asia.
The supply chain would start from here
and reach the smallest dealers
in every corner of Asia,
ten times more than before.
Millions of people
would become cocaine, heroin addicts
for the first time through this network.
So, the old drug business
and the new drug empire
will end up having the same ruler:
Nayak.
This is Nayak's five-year plan, sir.
The whole operation...
is run by a network of 365 people.
Three sixty-five, as in the number of days
in a year. Like that.
Everyone is given their duty.
And inside the network,
the one in front and the one behind you
are the only two people you know.
That way, if they get caught
and start talking...
then the police can never link them
back to Nayak.
This is why everyone thinks
that Nayak doesn't exist. [chuckles]
That is the trick.
In this game,
there is only one king - Nayak.
The rest are all his slaves.
Suppliers, shooters,
then those investors, transporters,
politicians, police -
everyone.
How many policemen?
Fifty-two.
Like the number of weeks
in a year. Like that.
They all have only one job:
To keep all the supply routes
and warehouses clear,
so that the consignments
can come and go easily.
And how many warehouses does he have?
-I have told you sir, 12.
-The number of months in a year.
Correct. This whole plan
has been designed like one year.
[Mathur] Sir, we did a random check
on the warehouse locations given by Sasya.
And so far, every piece of information
has been correct.
[DCP Mumbai] I want all the locations
to be raided at the same time.
We don't want Nayak
to get any kind of warning.
Yes, sir. Right now,
only the core team has this information.
Mathur, we can't repeat the Karwar case.
If Nayak gets away this time,
then he's going to return years later
with another dangerous plan.
-We can't let that happen.
-Yes, sir, I understand.
This is where Bhumi comes in, sir.
Because Nayak doesn't share
his complete plan with anyone.
Certain things he keeps only in his head.
Nayak's mind is always working, sir.
Full time, you know?
It's like horses running inside.
[imitates horses running]
It's fucking crazy, sir.
If I spend too much time with him,
I start feeling exhausted.
He's like that.
Sometimes, he also gets very exhausted.
So, when he wants to relax...
he picks up girls at night.
Whores, you know?
I mean, his timetable is like that.
Who else would he get?
After he spends a night with a girl...
then he starts feeling like you and me.
A little bit normal.
His brain switches off...
and he relaxes.
There is only one way
you can get to him, sir.
A girl.
What makes you think I believe you?
Sir, I know we have just met. That's why
you don't believe what I'm saying.
But, sir, have patience,
you will see I'm telling the truth.
[no audible dialogue]
Tell me the names. Write them down!
[suspenseful music]
I know his taste very well, sir.
The kind of girl he likes.
He will definitely like
my girlfriend, sir.
-I guarantee you.
-Motherfucker, you think we're pimps?
[laughs] Sir...
It's not like you caught me
in a temple, sir.
I am just taking your plan forward.
We've interrogated three policemen
from Nayak's network, sir.
Their records perfectly match
with Sasya's information.
But don't arrest them right now,
otherwise Nayak will find out.
We will take action
only after this operation is over.
Yes, sir.
I've told all of them to report for duty
regularly, but they know we're watching.
Nayak is the only one who knows when
the drug consignment will be delivered.
Only after he has fixed everything,
he tells the others.
And now the time has come
for Nayak to make an entry in Mumbai.
[theme song]
[man] Okay, boss?
[talking on TV]
Isn't she as hot as her photo?
In reality, she's much hotter.
My little mister is cold.
Only the heat coming out of her
will satisfy him.
It's a beautiful night, isn't it?
Come. Come on.
Hold this.
Come.
[Bhumi whimpering]
What are you doing?
This is just a short interval
in our story, darling.
Don't mistake it for the climax.
You like how it feels?
I know you can feel how happy I am, right?
I only asked Fernandez Sir
not to tell you that I will be here today.
If my boys suspect anything,
then they would bury us together
right now, you know?
[Bhumi grunts]
Good things come to those
who wait, baby. Come.
Now we have to go downstairs
and make up a new story. Come.
Everything is in control.
Sasya is doing exactly
what he said he would do.
No surprises.
Yet.
This next part is tricky.
Let's hope Sasya manages
to convince his men.
[men chattering]
[Sasya mutters] Son of a bitch.
I have made a big mistake.
Go and drop her back.
[man] Eh? What's happened?
You were ready for her just now.
I am ready for her now, also,
but I would have committed a sin.
I mean, do you know
what kind of potti she is?
She is totally our boss's type of potti.
He would enjoy her a lot.
This is the kind of potti
he's driving around all night to find.
-But, boss--
-Drop her back where you found her.
Maybe he will pick her up one day,
if he's lucky.
Who knows when boss will be coming?
And when he is here,
who knows if he will pick her up or not?
And if he picks her up then?
I don't want two brothers
fighting each other over a whore.
If he picks her up, great;
if he doesn't, hell with it.
-Darling, please leave.
-[man] Okay. When the boss comes--
-Put it down.
-We know where to pick her up from.
Do whatever you want.
You want to please the boss,
go ahead, do it. Just go.
Let's go, madam. We'll drop you back
from where we picked you up.
Okay, sister. Be safe.
Bye-bye.
[man] ♪ I am bad, I am bad ♪
♪ I am really, really bad ♪
♪ Come, baby, and dance with me... ♪
Sir, why didn't you tell me
Sasya was going to be there today?
Hasn't Sasya already told you why?
He knew everything, and I knew nothing.
Bhumi, come back to base
and then we'll talk.
Sasya bothers you. I know that.
Sir, I have absolutely no idea
what he has told you about me.
The truth.
If there's any woman in the world that
Sasya truly respects, it's you, Bhumi.
I doubt he has any respect for me.
And why would he?
You're uncomfortable with him. I know.
That's because he wants you
to feel like that.
That bastard wants to overpower me.
When I first saw you at the barricade...
you were standing there
on the side, so quiet.
But even then, I could clearly see
that you were a powerful girl.
There was something special in you.
And that is why you've been chosen
for this special operation, Bhumi.
Sasya's not the problem anymore.
His work is over and done with.
And now it's time for Nayak.
And we don't know what he's capable of.
You need to start mentally preparing
for Nayak now.
That's your job.
-[Rupa] I'm going home.
-[Hemant] Where are you going?
Listen.
-Give me a little kiss before you go.
-No.
There's no one here. Come on.
-Get lost. Okay?
-Now you get lost.
-Give me the phone.
-No, I won't.
-Give me a kiss.
-Give me the phone.
Stop it!
Why are you behaving like this?
Fine, keep the phone with you.
[chuckles]
Load.
[Atul] See! Grab! Pull!
[grunting]
Harder! Faster!
Power! Kick!
Use your heel.
[Female trainer] Here, here and here.
Over here.
[no audible dialogue]
What are you looking at?
It is coming outside the lips.
I know, I'm doing it like that.
This is how men like it.
It looks a little cheap.
You're going to teach me
what looks cheap, huh?
If you think you know so much,
go try it on your husband.
[scoffs] That asshole has been dying
to have sex with me.
He told me, if I sleep with him,
then he'll give you your divorce.
[coughing]
See how smart she is?
Started coughing at the right moment.
Aai, drink some water!
[water running]
[Rupa humming tune]
[coughing]
What time is your shift tomorrow?
I'm on night duty nowadays, Aai.
So, Aai, your cough became Okay
without drinking any water?
Do you still have some tension at work?
There is always a little tension, Aai.
But there are some good things
also happening.
[indistinct chattering]
Excuse me.
Do you have change for Rs. 2,000?
Let me check.
Are you one of Anand's girls?
I don't work on this road.
I just came for tea. Thank you.
[man] Hey, stop the bike. Hey. Hello.
Come here.
-No.
-Why not?
I'm on my break.
-[laughter]
-What the hell? She's on a break!
Hey, enough of that! How much?
Tell me.
[men chattering indistinctly]
One tea.
[men laugh]
[train horn bellows]
[homeless man] One more night has passed.
Huh? Where did time go?
It ran away again!
Catch it.
Go catch it!
I will punish it for... uh...
for not following my orders!
Catch it now! Bring to my court.
Mhatre.
Are we going to do this every night?
I feel more like a watchman
than a policeman.
Then talk to Fernandez Sir.
He personally requested that I be here.
But you?
You and your daily parade?
What's the point? [scoffs]
-But weren't you enjoying all this before?
-Looks like you are enjoying it now.
[door opens]
-[door shuts]
-[engine starts]
What?
I get my salary every month.
I'm happy with that.
-Stop the car on the side.
-Now where do you want to go?
I'll meet you at the base later, okay?
Just stop the car.
Stop, stop, stop.
Yes, ma'am?
Excuse me? Hello? Hello?
Don't worry, she's with me.
Close the door.
How come you are here?
Shh.
Go back.
Keep going.
Go a little more.
I wanted to click your photo...
t-to show Rupa.
Only see.
Don't show anyone, hmm?
Okay.
Show me.
In the first time, you won't be able
to take more than this.
I'll try my best... to take it all.
You keep trying...
you never know, you might just get lucky
sooner than you think.
[door opens and shuts]
-[Rupa] From where did you get this?
-Keep it.
Did you go and meet Hemant?
Bhumi, how did you get this phone?
I got it my way,
not the way you got it from him.
Why did you meet Hemant?
Didn't I tell you to stay away from him?
I have no interest in meeting him, okay?
I did it just for you.
You don't need to give so much of yourself
just for a phone, Okay?
Remember, you're not that cheap.
Look, we don't need you to interfere.
-My boyfriend and me--
-He is not anybody's boyfriend.
Hey! First, why don't you go get
a divorce from your husband?
And if you're so tough,
then don't send me to have sex with him
just to get your work done.
[scoffs] You are teaching me.
I already told you,
there is no need for you to go there.
Yeah, Okay.
I will see.
-[Fernandez] Exactly as we planned, sir.
-[Mathur] Hmm.
As promised,
Sasya has returned to his gang.
-Hmm.
-And we're tracking his every move.
-You remember all the instructions, right?
-Yes, sir.
There won't be a moment
we won't be tracking you.
Sir, you still don't have any faith in me?
-I thought we had become close friends.
-Don't worry.
I'll keep you really close.
If something seems
even a little bit off...
we'll shoot you in the chest.
I'm quite sure
you're going to double-cross us.
At least you will only shoot me, sir.
But do you have any idea what Nayak
would do to me if he found out?
He would slit my throat.
He would cut me like a goat
and let my blood flow into the gutter.
So you can say whatever you want,
but it's him I'm really scared of.
-And Nayak?
-Any day now, sir.
-He should be in Mumbai very soon.
-Hmm.
And we're ready for him.
And Bhumi?
Sir, we'll be shifting her
to a hotel very soon.
She won't be traceable there.
It will be a lot safer.
What are her orders once she's picked up?
You know what I mean.
[snooker balls clattering]
I know, sir.
We've planned everything, sir.
Plan?
Is Nayak going to work
according to our plan, hmm?
He is Nayak.
He ran an arms-dealing operation in Karwar
for four years and nobody had a clue.
And when the police cracked the case,
do you know who they arrested?
Local laborers and the drivers.
The police didn't even know
if there was a man called Nayak or not.
Four senior police officers -
I mean, IPS officers -
were suspended in this mess.
And this girl is going to be with him,
at his place, alone.
Don't you understand that?
What will she do?
How is she going to protect herself?
[Fernandez]
It's not your job to catch Nayak.
You just have to pass on the information.
Every little thing
that you see, you hear...
just try and remember it,
and then come here
and put it all on record.
-That's it. That's your job.
-Yes, sir.
With Nayak, don't ever try to rush things.
He'll sense it.
You're going to have to win his confidence
and gradually become a part of his life.
We'll always be there to back you.
Atul will always be close to you.
Whenever there is an emergency,
if you think you're in danger,
instantly inform the team,
and we'll get you out of there.
[mobile phone ringing]
[Sasya] Sir, I have some big news for you.
And if you are looking for a promotion,
then it's absolutely perfect.
A very large consignment has arrived, sir.
One came yesterday, one arrived today,
and one will come tomorrow.
I haven't seen any of this myself,
but I got this information from my boys,
Sir, all the fishermen in the village
are waking up early,
going out of their houses,
and throwing their nets into the water
to catch some fish.
But, sir, they are catching
everything except fish. [chuckles]
Cocaine, guns - everything.
You understand, sir?
Something big is about to happen.
You should get ready, sir.
[horn blaring]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, sir.
It's time.
He's coming.
Hello, Bhumi?
[stammers] Yes, sir?
You need to get ready.
We'll be moving you to the hotel.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Okay.
[tensed music]