[door opens]
[Fernandez] You talk shit like that with
her again, I'll rip your ass wide open.
-[coughs]
-[door opens]
Bhumi, I don't think
you should take him so seriously.
He's going to do something.
-He will surely take revenge.
-Relax.
What can he do in there?
Huh?
Look at me.
I'm the one who chose you.
You were at the barricade one day
and I was passing by.
I saw you.
There was something about you.
I knew you could do big things.
And I'm proud of what you've done.
But, Bhumi,
you have only just started here.
There's so much more you can do.
I have a feeling.
Sir, all this sounds nice,
but I know what he's capable of--
I'm not just saying this
for the sake of it.
He's going to talk a lot of bullshit
during these sessions.
So what are we going to do, hmm?
Run out of the room every time?
What did the lady constable say?
"Into one ear and out the other."
Be stronger than you're being.
Show him you're confident.
Why should he be the one to scare you?
You scare him.
Control him.
Look him in the fucking eye.
And then we'll see
how he tries his bullshit.
I'm going in now.
You come in a minute later
and start all over again,
this time with confidence.
Come.
No more talking shit, asshole.
Where is the base of this operation?
-Your tone is a bit weak--
-Hey! Answer my question!
[chuckles]
Since you're asking me so nicely,
I will tell you anything that you want.
So, listen.
Cocaine and heroin.
Cocaine comes from South America,
heroin comes from Central Asia.
Both come into India
through different routes.
The problem is business is not well set.
So to set this up properly
we made a big plan.
After researching for five years,
we found that, in India,
Mumbai is the perfect city
where this business can grow.
Here we don't have one,
but one dozen warehouses,
you know?
I will give you all the addresses
if you want.
You know why?
Because you asked me a question, darling.
You can give all the addresses
to Fernandez Sir.
Tell him to go check them out.
Once he checks them, I'll give you more.
And please tell Fernandez Sir...
Tell him that Sasya is his friend.
Tell him Sasya said this.
[no audible dialogue]
[aggressive music]
[indistinct chattering]
What is it?
Why are you staring at me?
No one has ever looked at you
the way I look at you.
Hey, this is a police station.
You're in custody.
Think before you open your mouth.
Your face, figure,
they're all very ordinary.
Nothing special. I have had girls
who are much hotter than you.
You are nothing in front of them.
But there is something inside you.
I just can't look away.
I bet it's the scorpion inside you.
-I can feel its heat calling me.
-Just shut your mouth.
-I can actually feel it.
-Keep your mouth shut.
I don't know about other men.
Don't they feel it?
Look...
don't think you can get personal with me.
Personal?
You were a cop pretending to be a whore.
But what happened between us was personal.
Remember?
I remember.
That was not personal at all.
I was doing my job.
I was there that day.
And so were you.
I know what happened.
[door opening]
What happened to your questions?
You're not asking any questions.
Fernandez Sir is also here.
Come on, ask your questions.
I have been waiting for hours.
I have a lot to tell you today.
[interview playing over speakers]
[Fernandez] Let's continue.
[Sasya] Now I'm going to say one name.
Nayak.
Known to his people as Nayakudu,
meaning leader.
The police thinks that he's just a myth.
A legend.
They wonder if he really exists or not.
Because the police
have never seen his face.
But I'm telling you...
Nayak is real.
All of us work for him.
He meets very few people personally.
Most of them have no idea
that they're actually working for Nayak.
He keeps all his plans in his head.
He never tells anyone for safety.
He only tells us what we need to know.
I am special to him, so he tells me a lot.
And you are special to me,
so I'm telling you a lot.
[Sasya] Do you remember Karwar, darling?
Five years ago, that arms-smuggling case?
There were dead bodies, shootouts.
That whole thing was planned by Nayak.
All this because he wanted to set up
his narcotics business.
He has been fucking with you cops
for many years now.
-[reporter] Who is Nayak?
-We have only heard the name.
But we have no real proof that he exists.
[Sasya] All the police did was seize
some guns and grenades.
And you were happy.
You posed for photos, took selfies,
patted each other on the back.
And he slipped away
from right under your nose.
But now, sir...
I am, uh...
I am not working for Nayak anymore.
I'm working for you, am I not?
If you plan this properly, sir...
maybe...
I don't know...
you might get Nayak this time.
Deep, check and see if the whole
conversation has been recorded.
Sir, is this the same Nayak?
Huh?
-Nothing, sir.
-I'll have to inform Mathur Sir.
Double-check the recording.
Leena, I want that transcript
in ten minutes. I'm coming back.
Bhumi, good job.
You also want to finish
what we started that night, right?
What nonsense is this?
Finish what?
Don't get so angry, darling.
-Keep quiet.
-Baby, your blood is boiling.
You're burning hot but still ice cold.
You haven't fucked in a long time?
Don't you dare say one more word.
You don't know yourself at all.
You don't even know
the scorpion inside you.
I... I will tell you all about it.
I have touched it.
For so long, I have been trying so hard
to romance you like a true lover.
But you refuse to listen to me.
In the beginning,
I was alone in this story.
Then you entered.
Now both of us are here.
One day, we are going to be together.
And that day I am going to give you...
something that you truly deserve...
something that you so desperately need.
[tense music]
REAY ROAD POLICE STATION
-Bhumi.
-Yes, sir.
Headquarters has sent some orders for you.
They have asked me
to relieve you of your duty.
What does that mean?
It means you have to leave
this police station.
Why?
Orders have come from above. I don't know.
Sir, I have some paperwork pending here.
[sad music]
[theme song]
POLICE STATION
[Mhatre] Bhumi, I am telling you...
go and say sorry,
and rejoin the interrogation.
So you are also blaming me,
like it's all my mistake.
Don't you understand how the world works?
What did Sasya say
that made you forget about your duty?
He was saying dirty things to me.
I'm a woman, right?
-So he was trying to overpower me.
-Here we go again. Woman.
[slurps] Now she realizes she is a woman.
What the hell is wrong with you?
What is wrong with me?
I'm still the same.
It is the operation
that has ruined everything.
Become a call girl, wear dirty little
clothes, get close to those dirty men.
Everything was going so well before this.
Drawing lines in the police register,
keeping the accounts,
standing on duty in the baking-hot sun.
That was "going well" for you?
This is so much better now.
It's like you are in a film.
Going in disguise, setting up a criminal.
International criminal.
Just the thought of it,
it's so exciting! [chuckles]
You looked so amazing,
I couldn't recognize you!
But now the film is over, right?
Now what?
Go and say sorry to them,
and hide your ego deep inside you.
You saw how they threw you
out of the police station.
If you don't have a job,
what are you going to do?
[detector beeping]
Excuse me.
You don't have permission to go in there.
Bhumika Pardeshi, Senior Constable,
Reay Road Police Station.
-I'm going for the interrogation.
-Your name is not on the list.
I am working with Fernandez Sir.
He only took your name
off the list. Sorry.
-Then I would like to go and meet him.
-He's busy now.
-Okay, then I'll wait for him.
-He's going to be busy for a long time.
Okay, then I will wait for a long time.
[indistinct chattering]
[Fernandez speaking indistinctly]
-Wait! You can't just go in like that!
-I'll call you back.
-What do you think you're doing?
-I would like to get back on the case.
To do the interrogation.
I'll do it properly, sir.
No need now. Go home.
Sir, I'm very sorry, sir.
Please.
You know, all this happened so suddenly,
so I got a bit scared.
But I won't repeat that mistake.
Bhumi, I'm looking at you right now,
but my mind is working on something else.
Do you understand?
[Rupa] Are you stressed?
No.
You should be.
Hemant told me what you tried to do.
If you have a problem with me
then you should have talked to me.
Huh?
You think you can raid
my boyfriend's hotel and scare him?
Taking advantage of the uniform, huh?
That's why you're stressed,
that he'll complain about you.
I'm not stressed because of that.
Then what?
I don't know
if I still have my job or not.
What do you mean?
I have a feeling
that they're going to fire me.
What?
How can they just fire you?
Huh?
Bhumi, what has happened?
Did you do something?
-It's nothing.
-Then how can they just throw you out?
This is a government job.
No, I mean...
it's just a feeling I have.
They are not going to fire me.
You said that a minute ago.
It's nothing. You don't worry.
If they fire you from your job then
how will we pay the rent of this place?
Hey.
That will not happen, Okay?
You don't worry about it.
What will we do?
Hey, Rupa...
you asked me, so I told you
what was going on in my mind.
I just said it without thinking.
Then don't do that.
Please don't do it again.
I promise, I'll never ask you anything.
As it is, you still have to get a divorce
from bloody Lokhande.
Asshole.
The man of the house
only made us homeless.
Go to sleep, go to sleep, hmm? Lie down.
Sleep.
[cell phone ringtone chiming]
-Sir, Bhumi's calling.
-Just cut it.
[phone ringing]
Yeah, I know that.
Just tell her we are busy.
Just look at her, Fernandez.
Do we really think this girl has
what it takes to face Nayak?
Sir, that's all she's required to do.
We are there to support her.
We'll be her brains and hands.
Fernandez, you can't be with her
all the time, can you?
There are bound to be times when
this girl is going to be alone with them -
alone with Nayak!
That's the hope, sir.
And if this hope becomes a reality,
what will this girl do?
I'm sorry, sir,
but it's not just Bhumi's life in danger.
Every Indian life is at risk if their plan
turns out to be a success,
and Mumbai becomes the new drug capital.
How will their plan be successful?
You have Sasya's information with you.
Use it!
Sir, the information we want
is in Nayak's head.
He doesn't tell Sasya everything.
Sasya is telling us whatever he knows,
but that's not all; there's much more.
Sir, Sasya has 100% faith in this girl.
He believes that Nayak will like her.
She's his type, sir.
Why this covert operation with a spy?
Sir, to begin with, how else will we know
if this is the real Nayak or not?
-Sasya will tell us.
-[Mathur] No, sir.
We cannot just blindly trust Sasya.
And we have no information so far
as to what Nayak really looks like.
That's why, just like this girl
verified Sasya's identity for us,
exactly like that,
Nayak's identity has to be verified.
Secondly,
if we start by arresting Nayak,
then all his operations will shut down.
And along with those operations,
all of the activities
and all of the people involved with them
will suddenly disappear.
So what I suggest is, the first thing
we do is to try and locate Nayak,
and then we track all his activities
with high-caliber secret surveillance.
So, this girl's job is to try
and identify Nayak?
No, sir. I'm sorry.
[Mathur] No, no, it's Okay. Carry on.
Sir, if Bhumi somehow invades
Nayak's personal space--
That is if Nayak
begins to trust her - only then.
...then Bhumi will be in a position
to get the kind of information
that nobody else knows.
Personally, I think this plan
is a little too weak.
And we cannot afford to have
a repeat of Karwar here.
Exactly, sir.
The Karwar case had no covert operation,
no information breakthrough,
like this one.
And even in Sasya's case,
we weren't very hopeful, sir.
But because of Bhumi,
he's in our lock-up today.
To be honest,
in Sasya's case we were fortunate.
But we can't rely on good fortune
every time.
Sorry.
I will be coming tomorrow.
So don't say sorry today,
say it tomorrow, hmm?
You have been coming here for three days
now. It won't make any difference.
Orders have come from the top.
You won't be given permission
to go back in.
But I don't have any other work to do.
And I cannot stay at home.
They start worrying
why I'm not going to work.
So I have no other choice
but to come here and wait.
So, actually, I should say sorry. Sorry.
Well, what can I say?
But at least you spoke to me.
At least someone spoke to me.
Thank you.
I have been sitting here for six hours.
No one has even looked at me.
-How are you?
-Huh? I'm good.
[cab door shuts]
[birds chirping]
[sad music]
RAJESH LADIES TAILOR
FAMILY COURT, MUMBAI
[indistinct chattering]
[Lokhande] Hey, Rupa!
What are you taking nowadays?
Your body and face is looking amazing.
You need to take something
to control yourself.
And look at you.
You're not even divorced yet
and you're hitting on your sister-in-law.
-That, too, standing outside a court!
-You'll tell the police?
Good morning, sir.
Why don't you explain to her
that my complimenting her
on her looks is not a crime?
Look, Lokhande,
let us just finish this once and for all.
This divorce is between you and me, right?
So please don't create a problem
in front of the judge.
Otherwise, he will ask us more questions.
This case will drag on
and the lawyers will take more money.
It will not be good for both of us.
You understand?
Let's go.
Ajay Khanna, Binita Khanna.
Ritesh Kerkar, Mansi Kerkar.
Why didn't your client come
to the last hearing?
We waited here for so long.
My head was not clear then.
It's clear now.
And I don't want to pay
the alimony amount.
What is he saying?
Everything's decided.
It's all in the agreement.
-Now, what is his problem?
-She is the one with the problem.
They made a fool out of me.
-Listen--
-Hey, she is not worthy of being a wife.
-Why?
Hey, sir, what do you say?
Shall I tell them?
Hey, don't touch me!
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Listen, can you come out? I want to talk.
No. Say whatever you need to, right here.
[clerk] Karman Sheikh, Laila Sheikh.
Anil Dalve, Sunita Dalve.
Listen.
Come outside for two minutes.
I'll come wherever you ask me to.
I'm coming.
What is the point
of saying all this, Lokhande?
What do you want, huh?
And what the hell?
Why do you keep saying
she's not worthy of being your wife?
-How is she not worthy?
-She is not worthy like you.
Look, Lokhande, listen.
As far as alimony is concerned,
I'm willing to take less, Okay?
Not less, nothing.
Okay, fine. I'm ready to take half
of what he had decided.
I'll just open the agreement on my phone,
and let us finalize it
once and for all, Okay?
Do I get your sister in this deal?
-[cell phone chimes]
-I can't believe you said that.
-I have to go right now!
-What?
-I got a call from work.
-But you finally got him here.
The judge is going to call in ten minutes!
-They are calling me right now--
-So tell them you're busy!
-It's urgent. I have to go right away.
-It can't be so... Bhumi!
Hey, it must be a big case.
That's why they want
the top policeman in the city!
[traffic blaring]
[Bhumi panting]
-Fernandez Sir?
-Fifth floor.
[fast-paced music]
[panting]
[panting continues]
[footsteps approaching]
-Sir, this--
-Sit.
This is a psychometric test.
You need to take it.
Whatever the right answer is,
mark it with the pen.
And where it says "explain,"
give a detailed answer.
Sir... Sir, why am I doing this test?
I don't have any answers,
so don't ask me questions.
I am doing what I have been told to do.
You have only one hour
to complete this test.
Your time starts now.
[male voice] "I respond well
to instruction by seniors."
[female voice] "I can work for
onger hours without getting tired."
[male voice] "...calm under pressure."
[male voice] "I'm a bad judge
of character."
[female voice] "I get my ideas of right
and wrong from other people."
[male voice] "I'm experienced
in getting people to talk."
[male voice] "I can judge a situation
and know what course it will take."
[female voice] "...right and wrong
from other people."
[male voice] "I can lead people
and get them to do what I want."
[female voice] "I respond well
to instruction by seniors."
[female voice] "People often rely on me
in tough situations."
"I can think about a situation
from all angles, and take a decision..."
[voices repeat and overlap]
[voices stop]
I will send the results to Fernandez
by 12 tomorrow.
[Bhumi] There was no time to think at all.
I wrote whatever I thought was right
at that time.
I have no idea what it was.
Some psychometric thing.
I had never even heard of it before.
Come here.
Mhatre, one minute.
Yes, madam?
Were you staring at me right now?
Madam, I'm a waiter.
I have to keep an eye on things.
In case someone wants anything.
Forget about other people.
I'm asking about me.
Mhatre, I'll call you back.
Were you staring at me...
or not?
Have a look.
Excuse me.
Where is the toilet?
[waiter gasps]
[breathing shakily]
Is something happening?
Now?
Did you feel anything?
Touch me.
Touch.