Brother!
Get up.
-Come on.
-Hello, sister-in-law.
...and keep them in control.
Hey! Don't interrupt me! Get lost!
Sources have revealed that
30 bodies have been found 12 days
after the Anantpur Massacre.
It is being estimated that the massacre
is the result of an internal conflict
between local groups.
However, if the sources are to believed,
the issue seems to be
way more complicated.
The CEO of Sunshine Group,
Suresh Krishnamoorthy
was arrested on Wednesday
for possession of close
to 120 kilograms of narcotics
found at multiple construction
sites listed with the company.
Further investigations reveal
that this is the third such arrest
in a span of a month
linked to the increasing
narcotics trade in the country,
leaving the police department baffled.
Nayakudu!
Nayakudu, forgive me!
Forgive me!
The police think that Nayak
is just a figment of the imagination.
A story.
But I'm telling you...
Nayak...
Is...
Coming.
I fell asleep...
in someone's presence...
for the first time.
Feels nice.
Bhumi!
Hey! Are you alright?
Here's your stuff.
It was in the hotel room.
How many men did you
see at Nayak's hideout?
Seven or eight.
Give me the exact number.
Seven or eight?
Sir, how can I give you the exact number?
Why?
You were an undercover agent.
You were trained, no?
Sir, I was locked up in a room.
Chained to the bed.
So, there could be more?
It's possible, sir.
Then what is the point of saying,
"Seven or eight"?
-Sir!
-Is she in there?
Yes, sir.
And what were they talking about?
Are you hurt?
Medical examiner has
done a full-body check-up.
No sign of any injuries.
Sir, the DCP wants to
meet you in his office.
Bhumi, are you alright?
Yes, yes, she is totally fine!
We haven't done the
psychological evaluation yet.
We'll do it at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
And who the hell are you?
Dilip Nambiar.
Head of Intelligence Unit.
Why are you questioning her?
I am her commanding officer!
She works for me.
Bhumi works for Crime Branch, sir.
And I have instructions from
DCP Alam to record her statement.
Sir, please, sir!
Bhumi...
don't worry. I'm here.
Yes, sir.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
ACP Jason Fernandez, sir.
Khurshid Alam.
Sir, why are we questioning Bhumi?
She's just come back
after seven days, sir.
She has managed to survive alone
in the midst of those criminals!
And now some joker is interrogating her
like she's a criminal?
We can't do this to her, sir!
We can't put her in that position.
We did not put her there, Fernandez.
You did.
You were handling this case.
Bhumi went missing.
DCP Mathur had to be replaced by me.
These are your failures.
Because you think you are
smarter than everybody else,
so you don't have to follow procedures.
This case has been assigned to
Officer Nambiar and his Intelligence Unit.
And you will not interfere.
Sir, she has just come back.
-I'll have to at least...
-Are we clear?
Jaya Shinde.
The department issued
you a phone for that identity.
-Did you have it with you?
-Yes, sir.
Was the number
of the officer in charge on it?
Yes, as the pimp.
Did you try calling it?
Sir, Nayak had hacked into that phone.
He would've found out about all the calls
and messages I'd received.
Coming to the agreement
between you and Nayak.
When you made him the offer...
what was your location?
In the... room.
I was on the bed.
And Nayak?
Was he on the bed as well?
No.
He was sitting on a chair.
And what did he say?
He said he didn't believe
I was a call girl.
I thought it was all over.
I thought he was gonna kill me.
That was when you made the offer?
Yes.
And the next day, when I woke up...
No, no. That day, that time.
The agreement?
Didn't I just tell you?
Detail. Detail. This is most important.
I told him I was a cop.
I'm sure he already knew.
But I said it anyway.
I told him I'd work for him.
Be his mole in the police department.
Give him all the inside information.
And?
That's it. He left.
-And the next day, when I woke up...
-That is today?
Yes, sir.
There was no one there.
What?
That's very simple.
You just said it and he left you alone?
Just like that?
Nayak, the criminal mastermind...
fell for your trap?
Are you that smart?
My life was in danger, sir.
I said what I could.
And he just...
lapped it up?
Really?
What are you trying to say, Fernandez?
It doesn't add up, sir.
Nayak is a very smart man, sir.
Why would he confide in her?
Who's she?
She's just a constable.
She's also our undercover agent
and the centerpiece of the
police's Anti-Nayak operation.
Nayak must've thought...
that he could get information
on this operation through Bhumi.
I agree with you.
But do you think he'd trust her
to come here and not tell us
everything she just did?
You don't trust me, sir?
Your statement isn't convincing, Bhumi.
Alright.
Why don't you answer
one question as well, sir?
Where's Sasya?
What do you mean?
How is he connected to any of this?
No, you had said Sasya's
one of your guys, right?
You let him out to get more
information on Nayak, right?
Why has he joined hands with Nayak again?
You saw Sasya?
I saw Sasya there, sir.
I met him.
He's working with Nayak again.
And you told me Sasya's in Hyderabad?
Sir, he's been missing
for the last 36 hours.
My team has been trying to track him.
We're... we're on it, sir.
When did you see Sasya?
Yesterday.
He was there last night.
This is really unexpected, sir.
Please step out of the room, ACP.
Right away.
Did you find anything?
Then what the fuck are you doing?
Carry on, Nambiar.
Yes, sir.
Did you see Sasya again?
No, sir.
Sir...
I think she might be
hiding something, sir.
She isn't telling us the whole truth.
And I have a feeling she
might be compromised.
That's why we are evaluating her.
And now, we'll also have to check...
if you're compromised or not.
So...
I'm ordering an inquiry on you.
Sir, Nayak's sketch is ready.
-Send Bhumi in.
-Yes, sir
Please wait here.
Sir, this is the first time we have
some visual representation of Nayak.
Well done, Bhumi.
Well done!
Let's not try to fix something
that isn't broken.
We'll continue what we're doing.
You will continue...
making appearances
on that very street.
And let's hope that
Nayak picks you up again.
And when he does...
you must ensure that he doesn't find out
that the police know about your deal.
Yes, sir.
"The lion will ride the rat!"
Dumbass! Won't the
rat die if the lion rides it?
Bloody writers!
Hey!
-Why the hell are you still here?
-What?
-So?
-Does your father own this road?
Yes!
I'll put you behind bars!
You?
Did you forget who I am?
I don't know who you are!
And you don't know who I am either!
I'm a big shot with big contacts!
Idiot.
You really forgot who I am, eh?
Buzz off!
-Ruined my mood!
-Get lost!
Bhumi is on the street.
Watch her closely.
Hey, hottie! Wanna join me?
How much?
How much do you think?
One grand.
Look closely.
2,500 for the whole night.
It'll just be me.
No sharing.
You really think you can last all night?
Two grand.
Buzz off!
Yes, sir?
No sign of Nayak, sir.
Oh, my Pardesi, don't take my heart away.
If you do, never come back!
And if you leave, never come back!
Three cups of tea.
Hi!
You work for Ismail Seth?
Who's Ismail Seth?
Who's your handler?
I handle myself.
Hey!
Stop fooling around.
Come on, tell us!
How's that possible?
It's possible.
You handle the work yourself?
The money as well?
You take all the money?
I'm the one who does all the work.
Why would I pay any commission?
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Bloody hell!
Why the hell are we paying commission?
Did you record all your calls with Sasya?
Yes.
Has the Intelligence team
analyzed these calls?
No.
But why?
This is standard procedure.
I know the goddamn standard procedure.
But why would we involve the Intelligence
team if there was nothing suspicious?
But you're not in Intelligence.
How can you say if it
was suspicious or not?
So, people outside the
Intelligence team are not intelligent?
Please cooperate, sir.
Please fix your goddamn questions.
Okay.
Did you purposely hide the recordings
of the call from the Intelligence team?
What?
No, I did not!
Can you prove that?
How am I supposed to prove that, Nambiar?
Why don't you enlighten me?
Come on!
Next question.
Listen!
Are you working for a gangster?
Gangster?
Yeah, keep up the act.
I know how cops work.
If you really are working for a gangster,
tell him to get you your house back.
The one your ex-husband has latched on to.
Do it.
I don't need a gangster to get it back.
Right, you just need your sister.
Look!
It's your apartment and your husband.
Don't you dare try to
pimp me out for it!
Tell me something, Rupa.
If I really were to pimp you out...
do you really think you could do well?
What are you saying?
Is that what you want me to do?
You wouldn't be able to do it.
It's not your cup of tea.
Hey!
You...
Watch your tongue, Bhumi!
-Bhumi!
-Bye!
What's wrong?
You don't like me?
You don't like me touching you?
You really don't like it, do you?
Bloody whore!
Hey! Stop!
Hey! Why are you following me?
Who sent you?
I know every single detail
about who's touched you!
Get lost!
Hey!
You can run, but you can't hide!
That's her.
Hey, why are you running away? Stop!
-Hey!
-Stop!
Stop!
Where do you think you're going?
What did you say to my girls?
If you're the one who
does all the work...
why would you pay the pim...
What did you say?
Look, I'm not talking to you.
You're gonna talk?
I'm the one who does the talking!
I'm the controller... of this area.
If I see you again,
I'll thrash you so hard,
no one will ever take
you for a ride again.
Get lost!
Oh, you're gonna...
stare?
You fucking whore!
Who the fuck do you think you are?!
Looks like Bhumi is in trouble, guys.
Okay, copy that.
But why isn't Bhumi giving us a signal?
-Mhatre...
-Yes, sir?
Go, have a look.
Fucking slut!
Didn't you hear him?
Go on!
Fuck off!
Look, I'm...
-warning...
-Just shut up and listen.
I will work on this street.
I've made my decision.
You can do whatever you want.
Hey!
Come on!
Give it another shot!
Bhumi! Bhumi!
What the hell was going on?
-Nothing!
-Why didn't you give us a signal?
I don't need cops to
deal with scummy fucking pimps!
I can handle them.
Nothing has changed.
But I won't be commanding
the operation anymore.
ACP Jadhav will do it.
All the best.
Thank you.
I need to talk to you
for a couple of minutes.
Why can't you say it here
in front of everyone... sir?
Okay.
I don't think I trust you.
I think you're hiding something.
Alright.
You can file an official complaint
if that's what you feel.
This is a really dangerous
operation, Bhumi.
You have no idea.
You make one small mistake...
and you could end up in deep shit.
I can handle myself, sir.
But I can't help you with your jealousy.
You're my greatest achievement, Bhumi.
Do your best.
-This is my corner, you leave!
-Shut up, you old woman!
-How dare you say that to me!
-Both of you shut up!
-She started it!
-I didn't, you bitch!
Hey!
Hello!
Hey, darling!
Excuse me?
How much for the night?
Seven grand.
What?
Alright. Okay.
-Alright.
-What "Alright"?
Nothing's alright.
Darling, please tell us
if you're not in the mood.
It's about one night, man.
What does it matter?
She's being a bitch, man.
Listen.
It's a friend's bachelor party.
The groom's the only one who'll do it...
if, and that's a big "if",
he's interested in you.
But I think I'm interested
in this other friend of yours.
I'll come if he's coming.
What the hell are you talking about?
Will you?
Sorry.
Actually, I don't pay for sex.
It's my rule.
Hey, madam!
Sure?
Yeah.
Sure.
Give me your phone.
What the...
If you ever feel like
breaking your rule...
call me.
She's ruined my bloody mood!
Why the hell are you grinning?
Leena...
What's happening? Any update?
Nothing on Nayak or his men, sir.
Hey, let me go!
Stop!
Look at me!
Pick her up!
Move.
Next time...
I'll mess up your cherry so bad...
you won't be able to work on any street.
An insect eats grass.
A small animal eats the insect.
The large animal devours the smaller one.
Which one are you?
You tell me.
Did you bring any money?
No, right?
You're the one who must answer.
Seth, they're here to see you.
Ismail Seth.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sir. The Inspector requests that
you meet him at the police station.
He says he has a special message for you.
Hello, Mr. Shinde. What is it?
Ismail Seth!
One of your controllers,
I have a message for him.
Please, let's talk inside.
Salaam, Ismail Seth!
Are...
Are you all right, sir?
I have a special message for you, Tipu.
-Tell me, sir.
-Give me your hand.
Hand?
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Don't move your hand.
No!
Please, forgive me! Please!
Please!
Forgive me.
I think you got my message.
Yes, I did.
But...
after...
that...
Hey!
Five days!
They kept me there...
for five days!
And I can only bow down
to the mind that can be so...
cruel!
Please...
Please forgive me!
Please accept my apology.
Are you watching me, Nayak?
Can you see me?
Why don't you reach out
to me if you're watching?
Okay!
Let's do this.
We'll give it another week.
If Nayak picks Bhumi up
again in the next week, great.
Otherwise...
this undercover operation is closed.
But, sir...
We'll find another way.
Has he sent you?
Has he called me?
Let's go.
Come on.
Get out!
Hey!
-Where have you brought me?
-I'll tell you.
Come on.
Why are you pushing me?
-Tell me what's going on.
-I'll tell you.
-Huh?
-I'll tell you. Come on.
Come on.
What?
Sit.
Sit!
Look...
me...
and you.
Let's kill Nayak together.
That fucking asshole!
He killed my husband!
I've vowed to kill him!
Hey!
You know where he is, right?
What he looks like?
Please tell me.
I...
I'll make you rich!
I'll give you anything you want.
Promise!
This is a test, right?
Right?
Alright.
Go ahead.
Hey!
What the hell is going on?!
Please stop!
You love fucking Nayak, right?
Why don't you try me?
I'm gonna make another vow right now.
If you don't help me kill Nayak...
I'm gonna kill you.
Right now.
Right here.
Who's Nayak?
Hey! Hey!
You loved fucking Nayak, you bitch!
You're going to give me attitude?
Come on!
Say yes or I'll kill you right now!
I'll have to do it!
I've told you my secret.
Do you understand me, you whore?
Fucki...
Hey, stop! Stay away!
Stay away from me!
Go on. Do it.
Shoot me, you fucking whore!
Have you never held a gun before?
-Shoot me right here!
-Hey! Stay away!
I'm warning you, I'll shoot you!
Go on!
End my wretched life!
Go away! I'll shoot you!
"I'll shoot you. I'll shoot you!" Do it!
Hello?
Hello, Fernandez, sir?
Get me out of here, sir.
I'm in trouble, sir.
Get me out of here.