Sir, cocaine is produced
largely in South America.
They cultivate it just like
we cultivate wheat and rice.
These are coca leaves.
And in labs like these, they process it
and transport it in this form.
Heroin, on the other hand,
is largely grown in South East Asia.
And they bring most
of it to India via this route.
Cocaine is far away.
Bringing it here from
South America can be difficult.
If they wanna bring it in,
they have to do it by air.
Now, Nayak.
See, Mumbai has had its share
of the illegal drug trade for decades.
But small scale, unorganized.
We've found out through Sasya
and the others that Nayak
is planning to make Mumbai
India's drug capital.
Sasya has also told us
that this is a five-year plan
that is currently in phase two.
And phase one was...
mass killings.
If you have a closer look,
most of the drug gang lords have
been executed in the past five years.
And we know that it was Nayak.
He was just clearing out the space
before building his empire.
Hey, stop!
The motherfucker's dead!
Look!
Look at him staring at me!
I've seen his dead face!
I can now die peacefully!
Leave her.
She will be useful.
Sir, in the past three years, we've
tracked around ten isolated events
concentrated around South Bombay.
But where is it coming
from to South Bombay?
The same route, sir...
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Did they take you to the same location?
It was some other bungalow, sir.
Any idea where it was?
Nambiar, relax.
Bhumi...
your family had called.
I've spoken to them, sir.
I didn't really get any important
information this time, sir.
I was there for two days.
But I met Nayak just once.
And he didn't talk much either, sir.
Shit.
That means we've wasted two days.
Sorry, sir.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
Sir, please excuse me.
I'll be back.
My phone's bugged, sir.
He can hear everything.
And he can see everything
through my phone's camera as well.
He records everything.
He stops recording only when I'm with him.
Sasya's information is useless, sir.
Nayak has completely
changed his operation, sir.
Shit!
How did you go to Nayak?
We last saw you going to that
hotel room in the evening, right?
Sorry, raise your hands.
First, they took me
to a different location.
I think it was outside Mumbai.
It was an open ground.
Like a farm, maybe.
I saw...
them burying loads of dead bodies there.
Exact...
I didn't have the luxury of
counting the exact number of bodies.
But I'm sure there were more than 20.
Nayak is doing it again.
Mass graves.
We had seen the same pattern in Karwar.
And there's one more important thing, sir.
I saw Sasya's dead body.
They buried him there as well.
But why would Nayak show it to you?
He trusts me, sir.
Why did he kill Sasya?
He must've killed him
because he saw his face.
Sir, Nayak doesn't show
his face to any outsiders.
And maybe Sasya's job was done.
Well, that lets you
off the hook, Fernandez.
You can now officially
be a part of the team.
And good news, Bhumi.
You don't have to do the
prostitute charade anymore.
Nayak knows how to pick you up now.
The cheap clothes, make-up, attitude,
parading on that bloody strip,
I'm sure it was hell for you.
Bhumi!
Are you all right?
Repeating the same
question is useless, sir.
It won't help you get rid of your guilt.
What guilt?
You threw me under the bus, didn't you?
-Why do you even care if I'm all right?
-Listen...
did they assault you?
Sexual?
I'm gonna end up dead.
Forget about sexual...
I've seen his face!
He'll bury me in the ground as well!
We have found another set of
fingerprints on Bhumi's phone.
Could be Nayak.
I think we should check the police
database and see if we find a match.
Yeah.
Everything all right?
Yes, sir.
-Have you done what I had asked?
-Of course, sir. What are you saying?
This isn't official, Raja.
It's off-the-record.
Hey, Aanchal!
Get out of my way.
Come on, sir.
Please come.
Hey.
Durga.
I have some questions.
Come closer.
Hey!
I can't hear him, man.
Nayak.
Who?
You work for him.
I know it.
Right now, you're the
only one I know, handsome.
Hey!
All right.
My source will inform Nayak...
that you aren't dead.
That might remind you.
What do you want?
You ruined all the fucking romance.
The whore is your source, right?
You saved me, so she can be safe, right?
Are you fucking her?
He won't spare you.
I've saved you, right?
Come on, tell me about him.
We're playing for the same team.
But your whore...
she's on the other team.
She's with that asshole Nayak.
I tried my best to
scare the fucking whore.
But she wouldn't betray Nayak,
not even to save her own bloody life.
Didn't say a word.
How do I get to Nayak?
He's the one who contacts me.
He doesn't give anyone
any information about himself.
And he won't contact you anymore.
So, you're useless.
No, I'm not.
Give it a try.
You'll love using me.
Hey!
What the hell!
Stay here...
if you wanna live.
He won't stop coming here.
This is a new headache.
What if Nayak finds out?
We should move you.
The handsome motherfucker
will keep an eye on us.
Hey!
Don't say that.
What do you want me to do?
Just keep me alive.
I didn't cry when they killed Shetty.
I'm collecting my tears.
I'll only cry after that
asshole Nayak is dead.
Look after me, all right?
Look after me.
My uniform's gonna change tomorrow.
This is my final show.
What's gonna happen?
Listen...
will I be caught?
It's like a video game.
But it's a dangerous one.
I can't stop playing.
I'll have to keep running...
all my life.
And this pounding inside my chest...
this won't stop.
I wanna get used to it.
I wanna enjoy it.
It is what it is.
They've deployed more
security at the airport today.
I think it's a special checking.
WE KNOW. LET IT BE.
Sir, it's heroin.
Heroin.
Sir, I've been following
them for three weeks,
some staff from Rwanda Airlines.
Total eight mules, sir.
Eight mules.
Meaning, ten crores worth of heroin.
But, sir...
we believe this is just
the tip of the iceberg, sir.
What will we gain by arresting this crew?
Just some heroin?
But we were thinking,
what if we let them go?
And then track them.
According to Intelligence,
there is a chance that
this exact crew that
is carrying the heroin,
will return with cocaine.
He's right, sir.
In narcotics, they use the
mules on both sides.
And we're tracking them anyway.
We can hopefully get a lot of
information on Nayak's operation.
I think we should let them go, sir.
I will take responsibility for it.
Don't get cocky, Fernandez.
This is my responsibility.
Okay.
Let them go.
Officer, my bag?
Here you go.
We thought it was a lighter.
We've marked eight people, sir.
They're scheduled to come
back to Mumbai after five days.
Okay, copy. Yeah.
Sir!
Five days.
-Sir, it's a stupid question...
-Of course.
Go on.
We can track Bhumi and
arrest Nayak next time, right?
We haven't found a match for the
fingerprints recovered from Bhumi's phone.
But we can confirm it
by arresting him, right?
What if fingerprints don't match?
And even if they do,
what evidence do we have against him?
He doesn't carry any proof.
Then why can't we just finish him?
Unofficially.
Firstly, it could
compromise Bhumi's safety.
Secondly, we won't be
able to seize his operation.
We need to catch him red-handed
and also seize his operation.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Right, sir.
Show me.
What happened?
I don't wanna live with you anymore!
Hemant?
Did he hit you?
Why don't you tell her
what you did with him?!
What did you do with my boyfriend?
Hemant!
Call him!
-Look, it was mistak...
-You hit her?
We had a fight.
And it was a mistake...
Rupa, hit him.
What?
Hit him like he hit you!
Hit him!
I said hit him like he hit you!
-Bhumi, let it be...
-Look...
I'll show you.
Bhumi!
-You bastard!
-Bhumi, what are you doing?
These bloody assholes!
-What are you doing?!
-Assholes!
Assholes like him shouldn't dare...
They shouldn't dare touch us!
-They shouldn't dare!
-Bhumi! Bhumi, stop!
-Let him go! What are you doing?
-Fucking asshole!
Hey, Rupa!
-Don't touch me!
-Rupa...
This is what we must do
to survive in this damn world!
They won't let us live peacefully.
Who's "they"?
And who are you?
What have you become?
Listen...
I just can't live with you anymore.
You leave the house or I will!
All right.
I won't come back home.
I'LL BE WORKING TONIGHT
-Now, I'm gonna find...
-Guys!
Nayak has picked Bhumi up.
How come you're here?
How are you feeling?
I'm changing.
Look.
How do you feel...
when you see all of this?
Relieved.
Your Fernandez was lucky...
to catch them.
Two of my informers reported that
the police have beefed up security.
One at the airport, and the other at...
By the time I got the information,
it was too late.
The carriers were inside the airport.
But now that the mess
has been cleaned up...
I feel relieved.
Watching it really stresses me out.
My body heats up.
I feel like my blood's boiling.
I feel my stomach churning.
I think you need a check-up.
Take your clothes off.
I'll have a look.
Here?
Yes.
And?
Why don't you check?
These symptoms...
I used to have these as well.
I miss these.
You'll miss them as well.
I'm setting up the pipeline for
the whole operation right now.
Will you help me?
Yeah.
I need to distract the police.
Will you help me?
Yeah.
Because if...
THE FLYING BIRDS WON'T RETURN
Sir, Inspector Karmarkar from the airport.
Yeah, Karmarkar?
Sir, I have some news from Rwanda.
The airlines' staff we've
been tracking are missing.
They're missing?
Yes, sir.
Shit...
How can eight staff
members just disappear?
You must have some records.
Please check!
The bastards killed them.
We have to kill the bastard!
TODAY'S A BIG DAY
Something's gonna happen today.
Come on, get ready.
-Here. Take this.
-Yeah.
Come on. Settle in. Quickly.
Where's my feed, Leena?
Sir?
What's the status, Fernandez?
More information coming from Bhumi, sir.
I've sent it to the Intelligence Unit.
But we'll need more
forces on the ground, sir.
Guys, come on.
It's the same pattern.
Location coordinates, truck numbers,
highway numbers, sub-routes.
As soon as you find it and confirm it,
I want it on the screen.
Pin it!
Guarding the airport is pointless.
He already knows.
Leave the airport.
And report to the assigned
locations with your teams.
-New forces assigned to the locations?
-Yes, sir.
Follow the marked vehicle, sir.
Copy, sir! Come on!
Guys, I'm sending 12 back-ups
at number six.
We must strike all the routes
and locations at the same time.
If Nayak gets a whiff,
all our leads will be compromised.
Sir, but we have the same problem, sir.
Bhumi is still with Nayak.
And he'll easily find out, sir.
We have to strike this time, Fernandez.
Ask Bhumi to get out of there immediately.
Right?
MOM:
COME HOME. IT'S GETTING LATE.
Yes, the arrangements are in place.
Supervise the people who need to go.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll completely cut all the contact.
Our last phase...
begins now.
BHUMI: I'M BUSY.
I DON'T HAVE PERMISSION TO LEAVE.
Command to strike, ACP.
Just a few more minutes, sir.
MOM: THE STREETS ARE DANGEROUS AT NIGHT.
Come on, it's time!
We can't wait any longer, Fernandez.
BHUMI: I KNOW IT'S DANGEROUS. BUT I
NEED TO FINISH THE JOB. IT'S TOO LATE.
All units in position?
Yes, sir.
-Yes, sir.
Get ready to engage.
On my command...
Now!
Go! Go!
Call Bhumi.
Nayakudu wants to see you.
We'll meet again.
It's time for my flight now.
How are you gonna get a flight right now?
Private flight.
Go.
Brother, can I make a phone call?
My phone's dead.
It'll just be a minute. Thank you.
Yeah, so put them...
Hello?
Bhumi?
-Are you all right?
-I'm not sure, sir.
-Has the operation started?
-Yes.
And you were right, Bhumi.
Something big's going down today.
Listen to me, sir.
Nayak's planning to escape on a plane
from the private airport.
Please kill him, sir.
He won't spare me, sir.
Are you sure he's leaving?
Yes, he said so himself, sir.
He's worried. He wants to get out.
Please get him, sir.
Excuse me.
Sir, I need to speak to you for a minute.
It's urgent.
We've found Nayak, sir.
He's escaping on a plane.
The devil himself?
Go for it, Fernandez.
I'll get that bastard, sir.
Alive, Fernandez.
I know, sir. I won't kill him.
Even though I want to.
Target is on the way.
Copy that.
We have to arrest the target.
Wait for my command.
Open fire! Open fire!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Everyone, push up!
They're going towards Zone B.
Officer hit!
They're going to Zone C.
Sniper, take position.
He's dead.
Check the fingerprint sample
against the body's fingerprints.
Hello?
It's for you.
-Hello?
-Bhumi!
Fernandez sir wants you to
come to the private airport
and identify Nayak's body.
Okay.
Guys, give us a minute.
Yes, Fernandez?
She's here, sir.
Yes, sir.
That's Nayak.
Are you sure, Bhumi?
We got him, sir.
We got Nayak!
But he's been killed, sir.
Accidentally.
It was an accident?
I'm not too sure.
Well, I'm willing to
face another inquiry, sir.
Yes, sir, one second.
Good job, Bhumi!
Well done.
I'll be your Sasya!
That's what he looks like.
Sir, this is the first time we have
some visual representation of Nayak.
Tell the cops that Nayak
has hacked into your phone.
He has bugged my phone, sir.
Tell them the truth.
They were burying loads
of dead bodies there.
Add a pinch of lie.
I saw Sasya's dead body.
You must gain their trust.
And then we'll use that trust...
to give them false information.
BHUMI: HOW ARE YOU, MOM?
Did you text your "Mom"?
Nambiar, sir.
Same types of routes.
Nayak's fingerprints.
Sir!
The body's fingerprints
match those on Bhumi's phone.
We need to distract the police.
Will you help me?
Yeah.
The locations are correct.
They will seize my stuff.
The cops will be busy.
And I'll be busy setting up the
pipeline for my operation.
I'll cover everything.
I'll weed all the weaknesses out.
The large animal devours the smaller one.
Which are you?
Guarding the airport is pointless.
The police will think they've
ended Nayak's entire operation.
And they'll close their investigation.
That is when phase three will begin.
How are they gonna look for a dead man?
...no clue we'd be able to do this, sir.