How did it feel?
Taking a life...
for the first time?
How does it feel?
I'm sure you know.
It's been a long time.
I don't quite remember.
Tell me.
How are you feeling?
I feel like everyone's staring at me.
Everyone knows what I did.
I feel like something's stuck...
right here,
inside me.
And it's choking me.
Yes.
What have I done?
You'll do it again.
And again.
Yeah.
You're a natural.
Hello?!
Fernandez sir!
Please get me out of here, sir!
I'm in trouble, sir!
Please get me out of here.
Calm down, Bhumi.
What's going on?
I thought Nayak had called me.
That's the reason
I came here with a Hijra.
I don't know...
I... I accidentally shot her, sir!
Bhumi, listen to me.
Can you see anyone around you?
Sir, there's a dead body, sir.
Is there anybody else?
There was a driver here.
But he's not here right now.
Where are you?
-Can you describe the place?
-I'm in a room, sir.
Some old dilapidated room.
There's a ton of scrap here.
And the Hijra's corpse.
Bhumi, focus. Okay?
Check the area around the dead body.
Can you see any of your stuff around?
You need to move it.
Phone, bag,
and the gun!
Take the gun, hide it,
and just get out of there.
Keep talking to me, Bhumi!
I'm outside the building, sir.
Keep walking, okay?
And don't take the main road.
Use the alleys.
And walk slowly, Bhumi.
Control your pace.
Send me your location.
I'm coming, okay?
Bhumi!
It's me.
It's me. Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
This is not me, sir.
-This is not me.
-I know.
I know, Bhumi.
I thought Nayak was testing me.
I... I don't get it.
No, Bhumi, listen.
Everything's alright, okay?
Where's the gun?
Bhumi, where is the gun?
Do you have it?
Gun! Where is the gun?
It's in my bag, sir.
Bhumi.
You can use our room, okay?
No, I'll sleep here.
You'll feel better in there.
We'll sleep here.
No.
I'm filthy.
The floor is all I deserve.
I'll be alright here.
This feeling that I have right now...
it will eventually go away, right?
No, it won't.
But one gets used to it.
You'll get used to it as well.
In fact, you'll start enjoying it.
"I'll shoot you!"
Come on.
Wildfire in a jungle...
it always starts out small.
But it could destroy the
whole jungle if it's ignored.
When a tree catches fire,
it'll always burn the tree next to it.
Distance!
That's the reason it's
important to maintain distance.
Exactly!
I had to control the fire.
My supply chain...
is spread all over the country.
Many people are involved.
But they only know the person...
before and after them in this chain.
That's all they know about this network.
But it's enough to burn my network down.
I had to stop it.
Which is exactly why, from time to time,
I need to chop off a few trees...
to stop the fire from burning
the whole jungle down.
Cut him off.
Look!
Watching it will help you.
These are trees in my jungle.
The fire will get to me
if I don't chop these off.
Earlier, I used to do it myself.
But I don't have the time anymore.
When I watch this on a screen in a room...
it feels like a video game.
No one seems to be getting hurt.
No one seems to be dying.
That's the reason it's important to walk
out into the real world and feel it again.
I'm coming off as evil, right?
But you'll get what I mean.
And you will become like me.
No.
I don't think so.
I...
Why did I shoot her?
She would've shot you if you hadn't.
That was the plan.
What if the whore doesn't comply?
What if she doesn't rat on Nayak?
Kill her regardless.
Or we'll kill you.
That's the order.
Was she really gonna kill me?
Yes.
And that was your order?
One of you had to die.
You've seen my face.
And I wanted to test...
if you really have what it takes
to live with me.
But I was sure...
that you'll pass the test.
I was sure about it...
when I saw you for the first time.
I really like you.
And you like me as well.
But to be with a man like me...
it was necessary for you to
have killed a human being.
The feeling that you spoke about...
it was necessary for you to feel it.
Do you still wanna be with me?
One second.
-Sir?
-Calling you early, Fernandez?
No, sir. Tell me.
Bhumi has been missing
for ten hours, Fernandez.
Maybe Nayak has picked her up,
but we're not sure.
You know the most
about this operation, so...
What's her last known location, sir?
Last night, at her hotel room.
The police guard had
made a note of the time.
7:45 p.m.
Please hold off all forces, sir.
Local stations have no
training for such operations.
I'm going to her hotel. Alone.
Please keep this information
only to the core team, sir.
Sure.
It has to be done fast, Fernandez.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
I'll call you.
HOW ARE YOU, MOM?
MOM - I'M ALRIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M OKAY
WHERE ARE YOU?
THE WORK HAS BEGUN.
Sir, the message says,
"The work has begun."
I think that means
Nayak's operation is on, sir.
Sounds far-fetched, Fernandez.
Sir, I'll try another message.
IS THE WORK ON ROUND THE CLOCK?
NOT SURE.
I like it...
when you look at me.
You were watching me, right?
For the past month?
Through this.
Here's your stuff.
I told him I'm a cop.
I told him I'd work for him.
Be his mole in the police department.
I saw Sasya there, sir.
I met him.
He's working with Nayak again.
Are you watching me, Nayak?
Can you see me?
Why don't you reach out
to me if you're watching?
I was watching you every day.
IS THE WORK ON ROUND THE CLOCK?
Your mother is really worried about you.
Well, she's using a new phone.
She's just learning how to text.
The recording stops...
when you're with me.
There are no photos or videos of Nayak.
The statement you gave to the police...
Sugar?
Yeah.
It told me that...
you're on my side.
Why didn't you call me earlier?
If I would've called you...
many chapters of your story
wouldn't have begun.
Please...
forgive me!
Have a seat.
Please.
What the hell is going on?
We wanna join you.
All of us.
We wanna stop paying these asshole pimps...
just like you.
We want you to support us.
How can I support you?
Yes, you can.
Tipu told us...
what you did to him.
Yeah, I told them.
I'm not here to support anyone.
I'm just gonna look after myself.
And him?
Standing here with his
cock between his legs?
Do you remember how he
hit thrashed me that night?
But...
And you just stood there and watched!
No one's here to support anyone.
Forget about it.
Don't risk your lives.
Just do what you're doing.
Hey!
Do you think we aren't
already risking our lives?
STDs, pregnancy, violence,
the bloody cops as well.
We risk our lives every second we breathe!
We don't mind the risk!
We don't!
We'll become our own pimps!
No one can touch us if we're all together!
Wow!
What a speech!
That was powerful!
-That was powerful.
-Mary, just shut up!
You guys are gonna kill it!
-You are gonna smash the system!
-Hey, auntie!
This is none of your business.
Why the hell is he here?
Well, I'll be your manager!
Attendant.
Your house, your rent,
your groceries, your appointments,
I'll handle it professionally!
-I'll handle the planning!
-Planning!
You fucking whores have lost your minds!
Hey, auntie, has anyone bothered
to fuck you for the past three years?
We're talking about call girls here.
We don't need scrap dealers!
Get lost!
Come on. Scram!
Fucking whore!
You're gonna be just like me one day!
Remember!
No one's gonna sleep with you
even if you offer to do it for free!
And you!
You look like a skinny lizard right now!
I don't think men like lizards!
-Hey, Mary! Shut up!
-Stop!
You really think
she's gonna be your savior?
Who is she?
You'll find out when you're
in a stable with the buffaloes!
Shut up!
She'll protect you for two flowery days.
What are you gonna do
if she fucks off for good?
Mary, just leave!
Get the fuck out of here!
She's right.
Do whatever you wanna do
if you have the power to do it.
Who the hell am I?
I saw a lot more.
What?
Everything.
Every single thing.
You don't have to pay to watch.
It's free.
You can touch me...
if you wanna do it.
That's free as well.
Sorry.
Why?
You didn't like it, right?
Maybe I did.
Need a room.
Stop.
You'll have to pay if you wanna proceed.
What?
That's my rule.
Alright.
How much do you want?
You're gonna break your rule?
For me?
Tell me!
I wanna hear you say it.
Say it.
Yes.
I'm breaking my rule...
for you.
Tell me.
How much?
It really didn't bother you?
Does the fact that it didn't bother me...
bother you?
No.
I'm feeling really free right now.
Wow!
One should feel free, Bhumi.
It's really important.
Chinnanna.
My uncle.
He was having an affair with my mother.
I used to love thinking...
that maybe I was Chinanna's son.
I really loved them.
But they weren't free.
They used to meet secretly.
They were scared.
I used to think...
why must a man or a woman
sleep with just one person?
What's the big deal?
If it wasn't a big deal...
my life wouldn't be so messed up.
Forcing a person kills trust.
A man and a woman...
their minds should be connected.
Their bodies don't matter.
You're here right now.
With me.
You're completely here.
Free.
That is all I want.
Everything else is irrelevant.
Bhumi was last spotted at 7:45 p.m.
as reported by the
constable who was on duty.
From today morning onwards,
she went missing.
We do not have any information
about her whereabouts.
-Leena, are the ground units ready?
-Sir?
Sir, I'll get it
double-checked immediately.
So, guys, just note that...
-Bhumi?
-Yes, sir.
There's a mention of today's date.
-What are these numbers?
-I have no idea, sir.
21,2787,
81,8661,
2365130.
Sir, the system isn't able
to recognize these codes.
-Reverse these variables and try again.
-Okay.
-Nambiar!
-Sir?
She's sent more numbers.
I've sent it to you.
Yes, sir.
Please tell me we're getting
somewhere with this, man.
We're trying all the combinations, sir.
Phone numbers, bank account numbers,
PAN card numbers,
alphanumerics, everything.
Still no match, sir.
This shouldn't be that difficult.
There's a map in every picture.
There's a map.
What do they need for this transit?
Location! We have here two-digit numbers
with decimal points
then a four-digit number.
Two of them...
Could be one...
Vehicle! Vehicle number!
Highway! Highway number!
Then... Two digits...
Could be a sub-route!
Sir, please come here!
Sir, first part...
location coordinates.
Everybody, come here. Come!
Sir, after that...
vehicle number.
Next...
highway number.
And next...
sub-route.
-Check!
-So, maybe, we're on to something.
-Sir?
-Fernandez.
Our next move will be really critical.
Yes, sir.
Will you command it?
Unofficially?
Of course, sir.
Sir!
We've spotted three vehicles at
the check posts at the locations.
-Number plates match.
-Sir!
Two more vehicles.
Total five, sir.
Sir, three more!
Leena!
Divide the decoded locations into zones.
Alert all the ground units.
We need to dispatch them
to the nearest locations.
-Put everything on the live feed.
-Yes, sir.
Sir?
Okay, listen to me carefully.
You just need to secure
the locations right now.
-You have to wait for my command.
-Copy, sir.
And good to have you back, sir.
Unofficially.
Yes, sir.
Now that's a definite lead from our asset...
which may take us close
to the target very soon.
Yes, Fernandez?
All locations are covered, sir.
Great.
But we can't raid them right now, sir.
Nayak will find out how
the coordinates have leaked.
And Bhumi is with him.
MOM - YOU SHOULD COME HOME
What's your mother saying right now?
She's asking me when I'll be back home.
Tell her...
duty always comes first.
Perimeter secured, sir.
Copy that.
Are we going ahead?
Stand by.
Follow the vehicles.
And report their final locations.
Ready to strike, sir.
Maintain position.
Strike canceled.
Maintain positions for now.
I repeat.
Strike canceled.
Sir, it's not just about Bhumi.
But... do seven-eight trucks
and a couple of warehouses really matter?
Would it really affect Nayak?
Sir, I believe that Bhumi is
on to something bigger here.
We should wait for her.
Yeah, well, maybe.
But as soon as you
have an update on Bhumi...
let me know.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Hello, Aai!
Lokhande, come in.
How are you?
Well, what can I say?
Where is she?
She's outside.
She hasn't come home
for a couple of days.
Why?
Has she found a new boyfriend?
What are you saying?
Duty.
She's been working
round the clock these days.
What?
When did Rupa start working?
No, not Rupa.
I thought you were asking about Bhumi.
Why would I ask you about Sir?
I know everything about her.
I'm not interested in here anymore.
And you know what I'm interested in.
How dare you say that about Rupa?
Bhumi and you aren't divorced yet.
And you're already talking
about second marriage?
Aai, I've already gotten married once.
I'm not interested in
marrying dozens of women.
What?
Come on.
Aai, listen to me.
A man and a woman...
they can do many things together.
Why must they get married to do it?
You must have an open mind, Aai.
Open up your mind!
You want the apartment back, right?
I'll give it back!
Of course, I will!
That is exactly
what I wanted to talk about.
Listen to me.
Just ask Rupa to pay me
a visit at the apartment.
Alone.
We'll spend some time together.
And I'll give you the apartment!
Why wouldn't I, Aai?
I'm a member of this family!
What's wrong, Mom?
What's wrong?
Lokhande, the bastard, was here.
Do you know what he said?
He reminded me of
how alone I really am!
Of how weak I am!
Any damn loser can screw over women...
who don't have a man to protect them!
What happened?
He walked into my house,
and made a deal about my daughter!
How dare he say those filthy things!
And I didn't stop him!
I couldn't stop him.
I can't look after you two anymore.
I can't do it. I'm done!
She's the one who should've
stopped him a long time ago!
She's the one who's weak!
I'll deal with him today.
I am gonna end it!
Come with me!
Wait here.
What the hell, Lokhande?!
How dare you say those things about Rupa?!
Talk to me!
Why?
What am I gonna get by talking to you?
I've already seen
everything you have to offer.
Let me know if you've grown
something new down there.
Come on! Have you grown
something new down there?!
Do you really think you've
got anything that I'd like?
Do you?
No, you're just the same.
The same manly body.
Damn.
But Rupa has it!
Rupa has what I want!
And you're lucky she does.
And we'll talk about the
apartment only after I get it.
What the hell is going on?!
Hey, Rupa!
Come on, Sir!
Why didn't you tell me Rupa's here?
What the hell is going on?
You really do have it, Rupa!
Come on, let's talk.
Privately.
Private?
What's private?
Come on! I spoke to Aai about it!
She's sent you here, right?
How dare you talk to her like that?
I'll tell you.
Come on, have a seat.
Come on.
We can talk about it.
Bloody pervert!
Hey!
What are you staring at?
Come on.
Rupa!
Are you just gonna lie
there like a bloody corpse?!
You're colder than a bloody corpse!
You'll turn me into a wimp as well!
Get lost!
I can't talk to you right now.
Amey!
I want to meet you.
Please, Amey.
I wanna meet you right now!
I'll call you later, okay?
Bye.
Hello?
Stop calling me, Bhumi!
I told you I'll call you later, right?
Bye, bye!
-Hi!
Let's go?
Okay.
Hello, Amey.
Amey!
I wanna meet you right now!
It's really important, Amey!
If you really like me...
and if you wanna meet me,
just get up right now and leave!
Meet me at the hotel!
I'll be there.
I told you, I can't come right now.
Please try and understand.
I'll call you back tomorrow when I'm free.
What?
Grab the keys.
Why are you teasing me, man?
Come on.
Oh, come on!
Why are you rubbing salt on my wounds?
Are you having fun doing that?
What the fuck!
But I know it's just
gonna be a warm-up.
I know it.
Are you sure?
I know you.
Right now, even I don't know myself.