The recipients of the special
award for distinctive service.
Senior Constable Bhumika Pardeshi.
Bhumika Pardeshi?
She's not here.
You can move on to the next award.
-Alam Ji?
-Sir?
Bhumika Pardeshi was our undercover
agent for this operation, right?
Right, sir.
And she's not here?
-Cheers!
-Cheers! Well done, team!
-Nice! Yeah, okay.
-Leena, come here. Let's take a selfie!
250 crore!
Do you think you're ever
gonna see 250 crore rupees?
Kamble Ji, I haven't seen more
than 2,500 bucks in my dreams.
It's true!
Come on, Karmarkar!
What's wrong, sir?
Withdrawal symptoms?
I don't believe it.
That's true.
No, not like that.
I still think there's something wrong.
It was a little too easy.
Sir, you should stop worrying.
That's our job.
Khan!
Come, like always,
let's hope I'm wrong.
Sir.
Come, Bhumi.
Sit.
You didn't come to the
felicitation yesterday?
Sir, I'm an undercover officer.
I'm better off in the background.
You could've at least come to the party?
Anyway...
the operation is now over.
But you could still be under threat.
You cannot live at your
home for a few more days.
Continue living in the hotel room.
And take a break!
You deserve it.
Yes, sir.
She isn't here, right?
Mom!
You've lost more weight!
Forget about my weight, Mom!
Listen...
I have a few days off.
Would you like to go to
Solapur to your sister's?
I would love to.
But Rupa won't come with me.
She isn't a child anymore, Mom.
She can live alone for a few days.
What's the big deal?
-Hey, Shushila!
-Welcome, Sunita!
-It's been a long time! How are you?
-How are you?
Bhumi, you're looking
so pretty, sweetheart!
-Mom, I'll get going.
-What is it?
What?
Do you really have to leave?
I just got a call from the office.
I'll have to leave.
Can't you stay here for a night?
You said you had a few days off, right?
I'll come back in a couple of
days to pick you up, alright?
This is our native village, ma'am.
Our families live here.
"Nayakuddu" means leader.
He's our leader.
Do these people know what Nayak does?
No, they don't.
They don't care either.
-Nayakuddu's the only one who knows.
-Hey!
Come here. Have a look.
After I saw them,
I wanted to feel like them.
Yes, it's wrong.
But it's fun.
Young Nayak must be watching us right now.
Let's run away.
Brother will get to us if we don't.
I'm glad you're enjoying the food.
I've specially cooked
all these dishes for you!
She's saying these are my favorite dishes.
Do you remember?
He used to love fried
eggplant when he was young?
Of course, I remember!
He used to throw a
tantrum if he didn't get it.
Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you.
What a life!
I've never had the
privilege to enjoy this life.
By chance...
if you get this life,
would you like it?
No.
Not even with you.
We are the same, you and I.
Scumbags!
I don't remember the last time
I've laughed out loud in this house.
One day's enough.
The horrors of this house will
start haunting me if I stay here.
I won't repeat myself...
I'm warning you for the last time!
Will you do it again?
Oh, God!
Marrying you was the
biggest mistake of my life!
This house starts suffocating me
if I live here for more than a day.
I understand.
Exactly.
The child inside me
and the child inside you,
they're friends.
They're happy when we're together.
I want to bring this to your notice.
Although, you might think...
"Why does the Commissioner of
Mumbai Police need to hear it?"
Infiltration has increased
dramatically on the border.
Armed terrorists.
And this is a well-researched fact.
Global terrorism and the drug mafia...
are usually connected.
You see, Alam, both need to
infiltrate national borders.
The drug mafia funds the terrorists...
for buying arms and all.
And terrorism facilitates
drugs crossing the border.
What if we didn't catch everyone?
Some people must be
outside Nayak's network.
The movement of drugs hasn't stopped.
There's no evidence, sir.
If these are the reports on the surface,
the underground operation
must be much bigger.
Mom!
Come on!
No, Mom.
Oh, come on!
Mom!
I've given Rupa my word.
How are you?
Did you hear me?
You said you wanted to be my Sasya.
But I had to finish him off.
It must bother you.
Not anymore.
But it does bother me.
What?
You've seen my face...
just like Sasya had.
And one day, I won't need you anymore.
And with the kind of person that I am,
why would I let you go?
But I would like to try.
I'll try and ensure that you'll
never be useless to my operation.
That should save you.
-But I'll never...
-I know.
I can see you're coming on my side.
I'm already on your side.
Trust me, I am!
Not completely.
But you will be.
You're getting there.
You're slowly becoming like me.
You're close.
Tell me.
What do I need to do?
Set up a new drug
distribution network in Mumbai.
And then, in some other cities.
Sasya had set up my network.
But he turned out to be a rat.
I was forced to revamp it...
in a hurry.
The network's functioning...
but it isn't solid.
We need to change it and
set up a new network.
And you'll do it.
How?
Wouldn't you be "useless"
if I tell you how to do it?
You need to get the drugs to
the drug consumers in Mumbai.
How will you do it?
These women are willing to do
anything to make a decent living!
They aren't cowards either.
They know how to deal
with the cops as well.
And they have nowhere to go.
They'll be loyal to us.
And there's no dearth of these women.
No one's interested
in them after they age.
Like I said...
you're a natural.
Where have I landed up?
Twenty-four!
What am I gonna do?
Twenty-six!
Hey, stop disturbing me!
I need to finish my workout!
Who am I supposed to talk to?!
Who will listen to me?
Should I talk to that lamp post?
Why would I care?!
I'll pay you.
Really?
Go on.
You see...
I was never "good"...
at anything.
I used to work really hard.
I used to prepare for my exams all night.
But my grades were always mediocre.
I was the one who
practiced volleyball the most!
Do you know where I was on match day?
On the bench.
Extra.
I was always an extra.
Just pay up.
Hurry!
Yeah, I'll give you more,
please listen to me!
My father...
he always treated
me as an extra as well.
I used to get him piping
hot tea every morning!
But who was his favorite?
Rupa.
I tried really hard...
to make my marriage work...
by pleasuring him.
By pleasuring him with this body.
But I failed.
Look, just pay up and scram!
I finally feel like...
I can be good at something.
But this path I'm about to take...
is a one-way street.
But I'll handle it.
And I will succeed.
Because I know one thing for sure...
I'm not gonna die.
They're all living!
They're all happy!
Why should I die?
I'll be happy as well.
Sources report a rise in illegal
drug consumption in metro cities.
The spokesperson of
Gaamdevi Medical Hospital
says that there is increase in patients
with illegal drug usage at the hospital.
What is this?
Look what Bhumi's got!
Microwave!
And look at this TV!
It's brand new!
Look at how slim it is!
It's beautiful, right?
Right?
Why has she sent this?
Why's she doing it?!
How did she get the money?!
How?!
Are they really paying a
police constable a hefty salary?!
Get it out!
Get it out of my house!
Come on!
Let's throw it away!
-Calm down.
-This money is tainted!
And I don't want it in my house!
I don't care what "business"
your daughter's into.
I don't want a penny from her dirty pile!
People might hear you!
-Calm...
-"What will people say?"
"What will people say?"
That's all you care...
That's all you care about.
This is our business.
It means we bear the risk as well.
Every single person
who walks into this group
must be extremely trustworthy.
If you break the trust,
you will lose your life.
The rest of the group will kill you.
We need to support each other.
They're all out there, waiting to pounce.
But we'll get to them...
before they get us.
I'm giving you a number.
Use it for coordination.
They'll answer all your questions.
Give them the names and
numbers of your agents.
Give them the weight of the
material that the agent can transport.
You can expect a reply...
in exactly 15 minutes.
You'll get a drug consignment.
Use your network
and take it to the customers.
First, in Mumbai,
and then you'll set up
networks all over the country.
You will do it.
I don't exist.
You do.
Will you do it?
I will try.
Hey, Maya!
Kitty!
Kalyani!
Oh, wow!
You're looking like James Bond!
But don't get too big
for your boots, alright?
Text me as soon as the goods are...
...delivered. I'll do it.
And ch...
And I'll change my phone every week.
I know!
Alright, I'll get going. Bye!
-Go!
-Come on.
-Buh-bye!
-Handle them.
Get going and...
be careful!
And don't be scared.
Ma'am!
Delivery...
complete!
Recent spike in drug consumption
has now spilled out to the streets.
In a recent trend,
many users have been seen
on the streets in
a state of unconsciousness.
This trend has been observed
largely in Mumbai.
But there's more to the story now.
What the hell is going on?
We're looking like fools here.
Did we really kill Nayak?
Or we helped him spread his
tentacles deeper into the system?
Hey, Kamble! Stop!
Alright, goodbye!
So, Bhonsle?
Want me to wait for you?
He'll be back in five minutes.
-We can wait.
-Fuck off, assholes!
-Take him away, Kamble!
-Let's go.
Hey!
You making a comeback, darling!
What's up?
Well, I was in demand.
So, I'm back.
-Really?
-Wanna give us a shot, Bhonsle sir?
No way!
I'm gonna go to my girl!
I see!
Collecting your "protection charges"?
Well, you could say that.
Hey, handsome!
Up here!
Hey, Tipu!
You seem to be offering a
variety of products these days!
Greetings, sir.
Hey!
Yasmin, come on.
Come, sir.
You seem busy.
-No, it's just...
-Who are you texting?
-No, sir...
-You wanna sleep with him tonight?
My love!
Do you really think I'm gonna leave you?
-You're my love!
-Really?
-You are my queen!
And?
I'll tell you. Let's get a room.
With the growing conversations
about the sinister link between
terrorist infiltration and
drug movement in the country,
metropolitan cities continue to
show a sharp rise in drug usage.
-And we were celebrating out here.
-It is conjectured that this is the result
-How can Nayak not die?
-of a vast and well-established
-How's it even possible?
-supply chain and distribution network
which caught police and
civil authorities napping.
Damn!
There are three and a half crore
drug consumers in this country.
Only 2,5 percent.
I've slogged for this opportunity
for the past five years.
Secured tie-ups with partners
from other countries,
cleaned Mumbai up,
built a supply chain,
and a distribution network.
So that I could easily get drugs
to more consumers.
I wanna take the 2,5 percent
to seven percent.
That's all.
Take the number of drug consumers
from 3,5 crore to 9,5 crore.
That's it.
That's my target.
And your operation is rapidly
taking me towards my target.
You will get a huge
consignment in a few days.
Be ready.
Everything else is irrelevant.
I had made my decision that day.
You will be my priority.
I'll give up everything for you!
I think I should leave my family as well.
Should I?
Your wife?
Should I divorce her?
Why?
The cup!
If she holds it gently,
she loves the man on top.
If she holds it tightly...
she wants to be in control.
Like that.
But if she holds a cup from the center...
she loves it from behind.
We'll always be together, right?
Forget about the future.
Focus on the present.
Laila has had a word with the other girls.
We'll be alright.
What about the girls from Thane and Vashi?
Don't worry about it!
Our girls are smart.
Why are you trying to
get into our business?
Why?
Does one have to be old
to be in this business?
Mind your tongue, Yasmin!
My tongue's always been foul.
And I'm already a part of this business.
-Mind your own business.
-What did you...
She's welcome.
She can join us...
if she has the stomach for the risk.
And that should be our policy.
Only the people working with us
will know what we do.
So, if someone decides
they wanna be a little rat,
they'll drown with the ship.
Did you hear that?
Hey, cold hag!
-Did you hear her?
-Fuck off, dumbass!
Please tell her to be respectful!
Of course, I'll be really respectful!
"Ms. Mary!"
Will that work?
-Is that what you called your father?
-I'll be back.
Well, I've never spoken to my father.
Hey, what the hell are you doing here?
Do you think I'm a fucking fool?
Look at your ugly face!
Have your stocks fallen?
How much will you pay me?
I'll gift you a fucking mirror!
That should help you.
-Get lost.
-Fuck off!
Bitch...
Whoa! My bride for the night!
Your face's darker than the night!
And you're charging the moon?
Why do you show up every night?
Get lost, beggar!
Have you lost your mind?
-Dumbass!
-Have you seen your face?
Come here when you can
afford to pay us. Scram!
-You should get some face cream.
-Fucking loser!
Hello, ma'am.
Has this man come to you before?
He's an asshole.
He shows up often.
He's a really foul-mouthed man.
Has he ever hired you?
He's a bloody miser.
He just fucks with us and leaves.
He's never hired me.
Has he ever hired you?
No!
Why would I sleep with him?
Hey, Sita-Gita!
What's up?
So, who would you like to go with?
Fuck off!
I don't need your dusty fucking scraps.
"Who would you like?"
You don't deserve a man like me!
Anyway, how much do you charge?
-2,500 rupees.
-What?
I'm not gonna sleep with you forever!
"2,500!"
So, what would you like to pay?
250 rupees!
'Cause, that's what you fucking deserve.
Alright, come on.
Hey, I'm gonna fuck you all night.
Yeah, alright, come on.
I'll need a bang for my buck.
Where's that cold fucking hag?
I'm here for you.
Do you have some fire in your belly?
Come on. I'll give you a peek.
Really?
The rate remains the same.
Come on.
Send this video to Tipu.
I'm fighting a case.
I can use these videos as evidence.
Look at him go, dumbass.
Here's your money.
You don't have to pay us.
It's your business.
It's the standard rate.
Keep it.
Oh, come on!
The jackass couldn't do anything.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
What?
He's a bloody limp-dick, ma'am.
Dumbass!
What the hell are you laughing at?
Give...
Give me your hand!
Come on!
Enough!
Cold fucking hag!
You've killed the fucking mood!
Fuck off! Bloody wimp!
It's always the wimpy
ones who love to act tough.
And I've asked around.
He's quite popular on the street.
They know him really well.
Are you just gonna lie there
like a bloody corpse?!
You're not a woman.
You're a bloody man!
Cold fucking hag!
Who is it?!
What the fuc...
What the fuck!
Haven't you had enough?
Do you love getting humiliated?
What?
You're used to getting fucked in the ass.
Because that's all you've fucking got...
Bloody...
You had called me a "man", right?
Let's see who's the real man!
Hey...
Hey... Hey!
No?
Oh, shit!
What the hell is that? Jelly?
I've had sex with a lot of men!
A lot of times!
I can definitely do it, you wimp!
Can you?
Come on.
Do it!
Stop!
I'm not a fucking "man"!
And neither are you!
It was my wedding night!
Mom had dressed me up!
My Mom!
For you, you bastard!
For you!
Do you know how much I cried?
You ruined my life!
You're the bloody corpse, motherfucker!
You're a cold wimp!