Every month the complaints
against you are increasing.
Misdemeanor,
insubordination,
no-show!
Sometimes, you just
don't bother reporting!
And even now, you're drunk!
There's no point in warning you anymore.
The committee has decided that
you're gonna retire voluntarily.
You think I'm gonna do...
what the committee decides?
You'll be expelled if you don't!
Expelled!
That will be the perfect
end to my police career.
I WANT TO MEET YOU
RIGHT NOW.
NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME.
CAN THERE EVER BE A GOOD TIME
FOR US TO MEET?
Fernandez.
Let him in.
Stop.
Don't worry. She won't molest you.
-Come on.
-Flask.
Aw! You really miss her!
What are you saying, Yasmin?
-Done?
-Done!
-Yeah?
-Yeah!
You'll get it tomorrow.
-The stuff...
-Tipu!
Only call me, alright?
Just me.
Tipu.
You don't need to do that anymore.
I've been expelled.
I don't feel sorry for you.
Me neither.
Actually...
I'm feeling free.
Rules,
orders,
protocols...
They're all part of a technique...
to shackle police officers.
Being a criminal is better.
Right?
What are you waiting for?
Enjoy!
Why did you wanna meet?
I've quit drinking.
Cheers!
7th September!
The famous night!
The police cracked down on Nayak!
What an eventful night!
But what exactly
happened that night, Bhumi?
My statement is on the record.
You had ordered an inquiry against me.
Well, the inquiry's over.
The case is over.
And today...
ACP Jason Fernandez is over!
So, even if I find out anything...
what am I gonna do, Bhumika Pardesi?
Anyway...
what could the police do...
to stop you for the past five years?
Come on.
Tell me the truth.
Let it be, sir.
Forget about it.
I really do try...
to forget about it.
But...
I'm stuck!
I think about it every day.
What could've happened that night?
What did Bhumi do?
My Bhumi!
My discovery!
My pride!
My bloody doom!
Was I right... about you?
I really want to know.
For...
For my mental peace.
Please!
You want to know.
But why should I tell you?
Who else could you talk to?
Who else can you share it with, Bhumi?
Sir!
Come. Sit, Bhumi.
Our intelligence team has found
many login IDs through the darknet.
Some of those definitely belong to
the members of the Nayak syndicate.
We need to find out
exactly which of those IDs are.
This will be your final
task for this operation.
You'll have to go back there, Bhumi.
And verify this information somehow.
But you've only got five days.
Can you do it?
Let's consider, hypothetically,
that Nayak's not a syndicate.
It's just one man.
Hypothetically?
Yeah.
When I come to see you...
I don't like it anymore.
Because as soon as I meet you,
a timer for my return
starts ticking in my head.
Tick!
Nayak...
he was smarter...
shrewder, and more dangerous...
than any man...
any of us would've ever seen.
Conning him...
it would only be possible in a dream.
Can't I stay with you longer?
You need to note the exact login time.
You don't talk to me like you used to.
About Rupa,
about your mom.
I'm not the same girl anymore.
Run it through all the programs we've
got and make a backup of it, okay?
Sir, most probably, there are six
top-level members in the syndicate.
And the darknet activity suggests
that they all have equal powers.
The extent is massive, sir!
Too many locations, routes,
vehicles, all across the country.
It's way bigger than what we had expected.
I'll make the calls, Alam.
All the task force you need...
-I will make sure you get it.
-Sir.
Station the teams and be ready.
We'll strike all the locations at once.
7th September.
You have two days.
Gorai!
These jetty areas, immediately.
Mostly in North Bombay.
We've decoded new information, Bhumi.
And it seems to be completely
unrelated to any other activity.
One of the syndicate's IDs has
marked five jetty areas for 7th September.
Manori, Gorai, Uttan,
they're all in Northern Mumbai.
But we've no clue what's
gonna happen here.
Do you know?
My job here will be done in two weeks.
I might go away for a few days.
I could've told you then,
what I'm about to tell you right now.
I wanted to tell you.
I don't know, sir.
But you didn't.
And Nayak...
who we're assuming, hypothetically,
was one single man,
had planned some activity
at those five jetty areas.
Maybe...
he planned on getting out of Mumbai
on the last night of the operation.
But you were found there.
What was your plan?
I'm just a Constable, sir.
I don't have "plans".
I do shit...
and then think about what I've done.
None of it would've happened
if I had planned it.
What wouldn't have happened?
Everything!
Nayak letting me off the hook
even after finding out I was a cop.
He chopped Sasya up,
right in front of me...
but let me go.
How could I have planned that?
That I would end the
biggest drug operation ever?
Me?
And get away with it?
Get away unscathed?
That the danger...
would just magically disappear,
and I would get...
way more than I could even dream of?
BHUMI - WHEN ARE WE MEETING?
UNKOWN - BEFORE I LEAVE.
-Do you want the leg piece?
-No, I'm not hungry.
Come on, for me! Please!
Chinese.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I'm just thanking you for paying the
hospital bills and getting Chinese food.
You haven't really done anything
else that's worth thanking you.
Schezwan fried rice.
-Why?
-Keep it.
I'll look after her...
and you.
But I want you to look
after your girlfriend as well.
TOMORROW 9:00 P.M.
-Move now.
-Ok, sir. Let's go.
Everyone stay on your comms.
No zone should be left out.
Every area should be covered.
Follow that truck to the
delivery location.
There.
Send a team to the coast.
Talk to the locals there.
Check the tracking devices and
attach them to the boats.
Sir!
Do we have Nayak's complete plan?
Some pieces of the
puzzle are missing, sir.
But we have enough to
end the Nayak syndicate.
You know about my health, right?
I went to the doctor for common cold
and he wants to conduct multiple tests!
It's so silly...
Yes, thank you.
Eat.
-How's Meena?
-Hey, try this!
-She's a good cook.
-Mom!
There's a locker in the new apartment.
There's some cash and
some bank account details in it.
It's all in there, alright?
Why are you telling me all this?
Mom, you should know about it.
You never know when you might need it.
-Be careful with it.
-Is this one ready?
Sir, as per the ongoing landing patterns,
the expected delivery time
for the last batch is 9:00 p.m.
So, we strike at 9:00 p.m.?
In two hours, sir.
-Fernandez.
-Sir!
-You're commanding the ground units?
-Yes, sir.
Keep us updated and all the best.
-Thank you, sir.
-Come, Alam.
-Sir.
All ground units, alert!
We strike at 9:00 p.m.
I repeat,
we strike at 9:00 p.m.
-Nambiar?
-Sir.
What about those five jetty areas?
-No update?
-No, sir.
-Leena...
-Sir?
I want you to constantly
keep an eye on Bhumi.
I've asked the cybercrime
unit to track her cell phone.
Only you will be getting the signal.
Sir, is she supposed to go somewhere?
Her role in this operation is over.
But I have a feeling
something could happen, so...
keep your eyes on her.
Sir, Bhumi just got into
a cab outside her hotel.
Where is Bhumi?
Sir, she's just left Malad station.
That's where those
five jetty areas are, right?
Yes, sir.
Call Khan and his team.
Ask them to get there immediately.
Position them at a place that gives
them easy access to all five jetty areas.
She's come to Uttan-Gorai.
Why's the whore taking a
dip in the ocean this late?
Sir!
We lost her.
Her phone's been switched off.
And then you disappeared.
So, you were tracking my phone?
I didn't trust you completely.
Or maybe I was trying to protect you.
I don't know.
Confused.
Okay, call Khan.
Ask him to get to Bhumi's
last known location quickly.
She has no business being there, Leena.
Copy, sir.
Sir...
five minutes to engage.
Hey, wait, wait.
Why are they checking her?
They're taking her somewhere.
Come on, come on.
Stand by. Wait for my command.
All units engage!
Strike now!
Go! Go! Go, guys! Go!
Barge in! Barge in!
Team A, barge in!
Leena, mark the locations
that we've struck on the screen.
Copy, sir.
Okay, seal all the entry
points at all the locations.
Copy, sir. Get them in a group.
Go wait on the boat.
These two are leaving.
Where's the whore?
Bhumi!
Yeah?
Why am I ruining you?
Ruining me?
How?
I'm turning you into Nayak.
But I don't want to be Nayak either.
The darkness...
the loneliness...
I was stuck being this Nayak.
But then I met you.
What you and I have...
it's powerful.
If it can change you...
why can't it change me?
I don't get it.
Finishing Rupa off...
just because I had
finished off Chinnanna...
Cancel it.
Forget about it.
Please be Bhumi...
because I like Bhumi.
Not Nayak.
Please change me.
Come with me, Bhumi.
Right now.
Don't worry about anything.
I'll look after you.
The world's out there, Bhumi!
I would love to see it with you.
And there would be
no timer ticking in your head!
Tick! Tick! Tick!
You could stay forever.
We'll do everything
the way you wanna do it.
Come.
No one's ever been so nice to me.
I've betrayed you, Nayak.
I gave all the information to the police.
They're attacking your
whole network right now.
You'll learn about it soon.
Liar.
I need something sharp.
I'll have to slit her throat.
Will have to kill her
by slashing her throat.
It's always like this.
Calm down, Nayak.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm right here.
Alright!
Stay there!
Shooting you would be a
waste of this opportunity!
I've never lost like this!
I'm furious!
Yes.
I'll carry this fury...
as long as you live!
This rage will drag me back to this city!
You must live...
to fuel my fury!
And this rage will help me get
back everything that I've lost today!
And that is when I'll kill you...
by slitting your throat!
One swift clean stroke.
That's the way to do it!
Full blood drain-out!
I refuse to be killed.
I'm gonna live!
I matter more than you do...
Nayak!
People you hate...
killing them is ordinary.
It's easy.
But killing someone you love...
it gives you real power.
I want every evidence bagged.
Don't leave anything behind.
Be very careful about the evidence, guys.
Hey, where is she?
No clue.
But we heard a gunshot from there.
Come on, get up.
Get up.
Get out of here.
Pick her up. We need to get
this asshole's body out of here.
Leena, no sign of Bhumi yet.
Look over there. Check in the back.
Give it to me.
Come on.
Go. Alright?
Go.
Check the boats.
I'm proud of you, Bhumi.
The biggest criminal
I've seen in my life...
Nayak!
You defeated him.
But you lost to crime.
I'm gonna take this guilt to my grave.
That I put you on a path...
you couldn't come back from.
This filthy world sucked you in.
You were from a simple
middle-class family.
What have I done to you, Bhumi?
Don't flatter yourself, sir.
You could've chosen any other girl.
But only I could've made it here.
This life.
The danger, the filth, and the...
loneliness.
No one else could've lived this life, sir.
This is my life.
And I have snatched it for me!
Because here, I get respect.
Respect, that I never got in
my "simple middle-class family".
Real criminal...
is the man who couldn't give his
wife the respect she deserved!
The man who couldn't
love his own daughter!
Who chucked his love-starved
daughter out into the world...
to beg... for love!
I met you really late, sir.
I was always ready.
We're not sure who among the
casualties are the syndicate ID holders.
Hopefully, we've got them all.
We've seized 80-90% of the
syndicate's narcotic material.
Some of it could be floating around,
we're not sure.
But we are keeping an eye, sir.
We have two more
rooms full of this stuff.
You'll be getting a huge consignment soon.
Be ready.
This is a mistake.
It must be an old order.
What do we do with it?
What if someone finds it?
How much is this worth?
It'll take us two months to
even flush it down the drain.
Why would we flush it?
What would we do after that?
What do you wanna do?
Start our own business?
But how would we do that?
There's no one to protect us now.
Why do we need a protector?
-We have you!
-Hey!
Do you realize what you're getting into?
Cops, as well as criminals,
will both be coming for us!
What will they come for?
We have nothing left.
What are they gonna take?
All we have is our life.
That is all they can take.
But we'll get paid, right?
Our kids could go to decent schools.
This is a one-way street.
There's no coming back.
Who's waiting for us to return anyway?
Who's gonna take us back?
And who the hell wants to go back?!
We'll meet again someday.
No, sir.
I'm not someone you
should be meeting anymore.
I saw it all today.
The good. The bad.
Crime. Police.
Humans.
Humans and the thin
line that separates them.
The law.
Bhumi...
the girl we had sent to seduce Nayak,
who was scared about
getting killed by Nayak,
she killed Nayak.
But Nayak managed to seduce her.
Nayak faded into oblivion...
but Bhumi became Nayak.
How did this happen?
What power did this girl have?
Which I did sense, but...
neither I could control it,
nor could she.
Something that changed
all our calculations.
It created something new.
Something that is neither good...
nor bad.
Nor is it the law, nor the police.
Something that is just human.
A woman.