One swift clean stroke...
right across the neck.
It should drain all the
blood out of his neck.
You must've hated it?
I didn't.
Because I realized I was capable...
of killing someone I love.
I felt powerful.
People you hate...
killing them is ordinary.
It's easy.
But killing someone you love...
it gives you real power.
You'll do it as well.
No.
You will kill someone you love.
I'll never do it again.
I'll never kill anyone.
I know you don't wanna do it right now.
I understand the feeling.
But you will do it.
The sooner you do it...
the sooner you'll become like me.
The keys to the apartment.
Lokhande gave it to you?
I took it.
I'm just here to give you the keys.
The apartment is yours.
Lokhande won't bother you anymore.
-Bye.
-Wait. Please have some tea.
Rupa!
Your cup...
it's in the kitchen.
How did you manage to kick Lokhande out?
Are you alright?
Why?
Don't I look alright?
You look tired.
Yeah.
I'm growing old, you see.
I'm getting dark circles.
Rupa...
are you doing alright?
The expenses, I'm sure it's tough.
We're getting by.
Keep it.
You can always come
to me if you need money.
We need to look after each other, right?
Are you getting me?
If you ever need anything...
just let me know.
Take care.
What's up, whore?
Why are you running?
Are you feeling disgusted, you whore?
You're the one who's really disgusting!
Hands up, please.
What's going on?
Sir, I've received a text from Nayak.
What?
N - TOMORROW
BHUMI - WHO ARE YOU?
N - IT'S ME
BHUMI - BUT HE'S DEAD
N - DON'T WORRY WE'LL PICK YOU UP TOMORROW
But how?
How is it even possible?
Sir, what should I do?
Is it possible we killed
someone else in the encounter...
and Nayak's still alive?
I don't know if there really is a Nayak.
Bhumi is the only one who knows.
You don't trust her?
But we have to use her.
Right now...
she's the only connection
we have to Nayak.
Yes, sir.
They've instructed me to
find out who the real Nayak is.
"Go to him if he calls you...
and stay there as long as you can."
So, call me?
Checking?
You shouldn't skip it.
The world's a terrible place.
Come on. We've been told
to drop the blindfold as well.
Serious?
You'll be their only
source of information.
They'll be forced to lap up
everything you say.
I met a new man yesterday.
He was ordering people around.
He looked like a leader.
Maybe Nayak?
Maybe.
Police's operation against Nayak...
will be controlled by Nayak himself.
Through you.
We'll have them running
around like headless chickens.
It'll make our lives easier.
Our policy stays the same.
The truth...
with a pinch of lie.
Sir, I met a different man today.
He seemed to be the boss as well.
Sir, I met a third man this time!
Sir, I met the first guy again.
I made a joke about
him being the real Nayak.
He said, "Everyone here is Nayak."
We have three different
descriptions from Bhumi,
so we don't know who
we are tracking right now.
I think the real Nayak never shows up.
He likes functioning from the shadows.
Sir, as it is, he was always a myth.
Maybe "Nayak" isn't one single man.
Like an organization?
Nayak could be a syndicate.
And Nayak...
will become a myth once again.
Ooh la la!
Never show up early.
I'm not ready for you yet.
You're looking alright.
You can't do much better anyway.
Shut up, Scrubby.
I'm talking to him.
My heart's beating really fast right now.
Is Nayak one man?
-What do you mean?
-Or is it a group?
Did one man call you from a single
number or were they different?
The numbers are unknown.
I would just get calls...
and instructions...
from different voices.
Sure?
Nope.
Your whore might know "for sure".
And whatever she tells you...
the opposite will be the truth.
Nayak's just one man.
But you've never seen him?
Shetty used to always talk
about him like he's just one man.
But why did you lie to the hunk?
You know me, right?
My mouth spits out lies
before I gather my thoughts.
But what the hell is going on?
I don't get it?
-We could talk to the whore?
-No!
She'll blurt it out to her pimp! Nayak!
But that's if Nayak
really does exist, right?
He could be one man
or he could be a group.
What does it matter?
Hey, shut up!
You guys are bumming me out.
Just...
keep prodding the whore, alright?
We haven't covered
Navi Mumbai and Thane yet.
Yeah, we'll need 17 girls in
Navi Mumbai and 19 in Thane.
Who's gonna go there and talk to them?
You won't be going?
I can't do it all.
We're gonna get a huge consignment soon...
for Mumbai.
If we execute it properly...
we can move on to the next city.
I'll do it.
Sheela, you'll come with me.
And keep it tight.
I don't want any confusion.
Give me a mawa. 120-300.
Hello, darling!
How's your grand comeback going?
Super-hit!
Super-hit? Really?
He dropped you off in two minutes!
Yeah, he was done in two minutes.
Really? I pee for more than two minutes.
Hey!
Listen to me.
I was just kidding!
-Look, your age...
-Why do you care?
Why would I care?
I'm just making small talk.
You should leave.
Hey!
What's with the tone?
-You know who I am, right?
-Yeah. What are you gonna do about it?
What's going on?
What are you guys doing?
Nothing. What did we do?
Why are you adjusting your treasure trove?
What are you saying?
What are you hiding?
Show me!
Hey, don't touch me!
-Stop! I'll file a complaint against you!
-Fuck off! How dare you!
You're gonna file a complaint against me?
Stop!
What the fuck!
-What the hell are you doing?!
-Give it back!
-You're making a mistake.
-Are you threatening me?
You fucking whore!
You're making a huge mistake, Bhonsle sir!
-You're making a huge mistake.
-You're going with her, you fucking hag!
You think you can threaten a cop?
Come on, fucking bitches!
Jai Hind, sir!
-What's up?
-Sir.
Look, Tipu!
I'm not gonna let them
off the hook this time.
I was being polite, alright?
-And your bloody...
-Go.
Hey! What the hell?
-Sir gave me the order.
-Who's "Sir"?
I gave her the order, Bhonsle.
Come on. Let's forget about
what happened, alright?
-You may leave.
-Okay, sir.
Hey, stop!
Sir, I've arrested them last night.
But you didn't file
an official report, right?
That's great.
Sir, they were carrying...
Shut up.
Sorry, Tipu Seth.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you, sir.
Come on.
Sir!
Sir, you humiliated me in front of
that bloody pimp and his whores...
I had received an order from the top!
Please try and understand.
Forget about it.
An order from the top?
For him?
It was from the bloody summit.
If you ever see them again...
just look away, alright?
Get back to work.
-A call from the top?
-Yeah!
But I didn't talk to anyone.
Who called them?
Well, that's your...
power, right?!
You don't even need to make
a bloody phone call anymore!
It was all automatic!
Hey, tell her about Bhonsle's sad face!
Oh, yeah!
That was fun!
When we gave him a glare he
acted like his lips were sewn shut!
This can't go on, sir!
Every time she comes
with some new information,
she drops it on us like a bomb!
We have to sit and figure this out, sir.
Okay.
Now let's debate this.
Right?
Say, I am for Bhumi
and you are against her.
And then we'll switch sides later.
Alright?
Okay.
We executed some man named Nayak,
just because Bhumi said so.
And the Nayak syndicate has
no clue about her involvement?
Maybe the syndicate
wanted that Nayak dead.
But that means she's working for them.
Probably, she doesn't know.
She doesn't know?
Bhumi knows everything, sir.
She knows everything.
Do you think so?
You know her really well, right?
I used to, sir.
But she's changed.
Probably, that's just the nature
of this operation, Fernandez.
But, sir, all the information
that we've received
about this whole syndicate theory so far,
we've got it from Bhumi!
We don't have any other source
to confirm this information either.
It's too much power to
give to one single person.
What are our options, sir?
Just keep going.
At the same time,
keep these doubts in our minds.
Give me a mawa.
Rupa, I'm reheating the chicken for you.
How many seconds
do I keep it in the microwave?
Ten? Twenty?
Tell me.
Hey!
Rupa!
Why can't you answer me?
Hey, Rupa!
Rupa!
Hello?
Bhumi! Ru... Rupa!
"Rupa" What? Mom, what's wrong?
Bhumi, please get here as soon as you can!
-You're her sister?
-Yes.
What's the patient's name?
Rupali Pardeshi.
Did she have any allergies?
Was she on any medications?
No, she didn't even need a Crocin!
She has ingested something.
Could it be a suicide attempt?
-What are you saying?
-No!
Was she using any substances?
I mean, drugs?
Okay, please have a seat.
We had to pump her stomach.
We've found psychotropic drugs.
Are you getting what I'm saying?
Rupa was using drugs?
You didn't know about it?
It's a case of drug overdose.
I never tried it again.
Just... one time.
But Rupa wanted more.
I tried to stop her!
Hey, Rupa!
You should stop it.
-Please stop.
-Shut up!
Aren't you ashamed to even talk to me?
Rupa, listen to me.
-Stop!
-I won't!
What are you gonna do about it?
Sleep with my sister?
Bloody perverts!
I told my friend,
warned him to stop selling to Rupa.
But everyone's selling it
like chewing gum these days.
She found it somehow.
I've found 17 girls in Vashi.
Here are their names and numbers.
Vashi is set.
You can tell us where
we're focusing next...
Are you alright?
It's fine for now.
But we need to supply it throughout
Mumbai, all at once, next time.
I'll tell you when it's time.
And who's gonna tell you when it's time?
I mean, we should know who
we are working for, right?
You're working for me.
That's all you need to know.
Is that alright?
Of course!
The less we know the better.
No, you say it!
Is that alright?
Yes, of course.
I was just curious.
Hey!
Yasmin, what's wrong with you?
You should handle your lover, Bhonsle.
He seems to be equally curious.
-Are you calling me a rat?
-Yeah.
He's already sniffing around.
Let him!
Last time? You remember, right?
We'll handle him.
Hey, I don't need you all.
I can handle him by myself.
Can you?
He could be a pain in the ass.
But you could...
bring him on our side.
How?
I'll tell you.
Hey, what happened?
I think he's consumed poison.
The body has turned blue.
Or he could've eaten some junk.
I had to.
You had told him too much.
It isn't easy.
Not everyone can tread this path.
This pain...
this "dirty" feeling...
it'll never go away.
You'll have to become strong.
That's the only way.
That's the only way you can handle it.
You wanna be strong, right?
Yes.
Please.
Good.
That boy, Amey...
do you love him?
No.
But you do like him, right?
Do you feel for him?
Kill him.
He has to go anyway.
He does have a hint about what you do.
And he's weak.
He really loves you.
His love for you won't be wasted.
It'll make you strong.
Hey! Give me a gun.
Thank you.
You decide how you wanna do it.
And do it alone.
It's easier.
I want the power...
you have inside you.
You'll get it.
You're a natural.
Please pull over.
Bhumi!
Bhumi?
Give me your phone.
Bhumi!
I was thinking...
we could leave Mumbai for good...
if you wanna come with me.
What do you think?
What's wrong?
-Sit here. Just stay there.
-What's wrong, Bhumi?
-Are you okay, Bhumi?
-Just sit there!
Sit down.
What's going on, Bhumi?
What's wrong?
Are you mad at me, Bhumi?
-Bhumi, we could...
-Stay away from me!
Stay away!
Just tell me what you wanna do, Bhumi.
I'm ready to do anything...
Bhumi, what's...
You're right. You should
leave Mumbai for good.
Okay?
Take your family and get out of here.
And delete everything you have
about me on this phone.
Go away, as far as you can.
Alright?
And never come back.
Sorry.
I couldn't do it.
I rushed it.
It's my fault.
No.
Yes.
I expect a lot from you.
And I like that.
Come.
Watch.
Do it.
Watch it!
Don't waste it!
Look!
I'll give you another shot, Bhumi.
It's way better than this idea.
And you don't have to rush it this time.
You can take it slow.
Take your time.
Do it when you're mentally ready.
You have two weeks.
Okay?
My job here will be done in two weeks.
I might go away for a few days.
And after I leave...
you can finish off Rupa.
Perfect.
You hate her.
But you love her as well, right?
A lot more, right now.
She's your sister.
You've grown up together.
She might give you more power...
than the power Chinnanna gave me!
And then, Bhumi...
you'll never be weak again.
I've left my phone at the hotel.
I want to talk to you, sir.
Translator Credit