Hello, Nayak. I know,
you're suspicious about me.
There was a police raid
and they nabbed me.
They asked me many questions.
You must be wondering
what all Sasya revealed.
I thought, let me personally tell you
about what happened there.
I want to clear the air.
You already know, I book an entire floor
of the hotel for me.
The police got suspicious
and they came to check.
So, they came. And the raid was for...
it was a raid to nab
those prostitutes, actually.
You must be thinking
Sasya has all important...
documents and papers.
What if... something got exposed?
But they came only to nab girls.
They opened the wardrobe,
closed it on finding no girl there.
They checked under the bed, found no girl.
They didn't check for anything else.
They took me to the police station
and I played smart there. I said,
"Sir, you are on duty
and are doing your job.
But you cannot behave like this
with an honest man.
I don't deal in flesh trade."
I told them clearly.
They heard me out and agreed
with what I said.
And then they asked me to leave.
I said, "Okay, sir."
I knew, they could follow me
and so, I did not go to the hotel.
I checked-in to an ordinary hotel in Vashi
that was close by.
It was a cheap hotel.
I stayed there for three days.
Then I left from there
and went to the hostel.
So that they think, I have no money.
I then went to a charitable inn
and stayed there.
I did all this to confuse them,
if they were tracking me.
That is when I got your message
asking me to go to Hyderabad.
So, then I came to Hyderabad.
Right now, I am here.
Look, this is today's newspaper.
Sir, I've been working
for you for five years. I mean...
to be honest,
I've literally struggled for you.
Are you still suspecting me?
Please talk to me on direct line,
at least once.
Do at least that.
What should I do?
My brain doesn't stop working
at my behest.
I can shut my eyes, but not my brain.
It keeps working.
So, Sasya is in Hyderabad
on Nayak's orders?
Yes, sir.
Sir, if Sasya is not in Mumbai,
then Nayak won't be able to connect him
with Bhumi mentally.
And Bhumi hates Sasya anyway.
It's good for her, if he is not around.
Does she even hate anyone?
She is turning out
to be quite a bitch actually.
Pardon my French.
What if I am creating a monster, sir?
-Hey, Rao!
-Hi.
Your tummy is walking ahead of you.
Yes, I've grown fat.
-How are you?
-I'm absolutely fine.
ACP Fernandez. He is my friend.
He used to be in the police force
as an ACP.
-ACP was your final rank, right?
-Yes.
In Karwar, during the case
of arms smuggling...
I was suspended.
You can say it openly. I wouldn't mind.
It's good that you were suspended.
You are earning good money.
He mints money.
Nayak or Nayakudu, whatever his name is,
I heard it during Karwar case.
I thought it was only a story, a myth.
I never found any evidence.
See, there is no evidence.
But are you sure, he exists?
Yes, sir.
During the Karwar incident,
the story was that
he hailed from Andhra Pradesh.
From Rayalaseema area.
Like a scene in Telugu movies,
ten to twenty people in uniform
came with swords.
He belonged to one such family.
Very big, rich landlords.
It's their trademark
to slit one's throat and kill.
He caused a bloodbath
for a couple of years.
And then, sold his property and vanished.
That is the story I know.
Sir, if you don't mind, can I bother
you more about Nayak and Karwar?
Of course, you must bother him.
Don't call me to the police station.
Those flashbacks still haunt me.
Four...
three...
two...
Mhatre here.
She is in their car.
Sir, she is in the car.
They're taking another route.
-They're changing the route, sir.
They're taking her towards a ferry.
Bhumi has worn a black burqa.
Sir, they're taking her in a boat.
Sir, the boat is leaving.
Leena, inform Kihim and Alibag
police stations immediately.
Yes, sir.
Fuck! How the fuck did that happen?
Nayakudu...
Yes?
Confusion, right?
Here, there, boat, bikes...
it was necessary.
But now it's easy.
Tell her what you want to eat.
Order for me too.
I made you wait too long, right?
So, I'll take better care of you.
Tell me your phone number.
Why are you quiet? Tell me.
-9819...
-9829764325.
-This is my new phone.
-You've had this phone for six months.
So?
Sometimes... I tell my brain
that it's enough. Stop.
Sometimes I feel
it's better to get caught.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Let me explain.
Your phone is mirrored on this phone.
All your contacts and their numbers
are on this phone.
Open the list now...
and call any number.
Anyone.
Call anyone listed under alphabet - B.
Keep the phone here. Let me see.
Now call anyone
whose name starts with the alphabet - B.
You can't?
Now, call anyone listed
under alphabet - M, except your mom.
You won't be able to...
because all numbers are fake.
That's not true.
All the numbers in this phone
are of my clients.
Once their work is done, they block me.
Yeah.
That's possible.
I hope that is the truth.
But my brain... is saying something else.
Anna...
Sit.
Have you seen them before?
Do you recognize them?
How many times have you seen them before?
Twice.
Including today or excluding it?
I mean, I'm seeing them today
and once before.
You are a call girl.
You are into flesh trade.
There was a raid
at Sasya's room for call girls.
Is it possible that...
Sasya...
has Sasya sent you here?
-Who Sasya?
-She met him one night, sir.
I might have met him.
The clients don't tell me their names.
If you were in Sasya's room
at the time of the raid,
the police must've caught you too.
What do I say?
Don't say anything.
I'll ask Sasya.
It was working so well.
I felt calm. Everything is ruined.
Sir, we'll tell you everything.
We got her that night for Sasya.
He took her in
but came back in five minutes and said,
that she is your type.
And if destined, you two might meet.
That's why,
we took you to her spot on purpose.
We made a mistake, Nayakudu.
Excellent!
Basically,
again we have no idea where Bhumi is.
This is our level.
Shameful!
Nayakudu, we swear by God
that we didn't mean to betray you.
We only wanted to please you.
Forgive our lives, please.
-Forgive us.
-What are you doing?
Go. Go and watch movies.
Go on, boys.
What is this?
I don't know what they see in me.
They never make eye contact.
They have a picture of me in their minds
and they assume that's me.
What was your sister's name?
What?
Deepa?
-Rupa.
Did Mom decide the name or your father?
Rupali is a nice name.
I don't know who chose it.
I don't like... Rupali.
Do you?
It's okay.
Not the name.
I'm talking about your sister.
Everyone has spoiled her.
Right from childhood, she used to roam
around wearing Mom's lipstick and stole.
Nothing changed as she grew up.
She thinks that she's very beautiful.
I don't know what her problem is.
She always boasts
that all men are crazy for her.
Like all men want to have sex with her.
And with you?
Not even my husband
wants to have sex with me.
-Husband?
-That's what Rupa says.
And the husband?
What does he say?
Have you ever told Rupa,
that you earn your income from sex?
How much do you earn for an hour?
Thousand to two thousand bucks.
And according to you,
how much would Rupa get?
Obviously more than what I get.
Sure?
You aren't sure, are you?
Even you don't like her, do you?
Rupali.
She enjoys when men stare at her.
Men are assholes.
Do you know what makes her happy the most?
When I walk with her...
and no one looks at me.
I see... happiness in her eyes.
And drama...
that men cause tension to her.
When men will stop looking at her...
then she'll get tensed.
I won't look at her.
She isn't here, is she?
Imagine, she is here.
I will not look at her.
I will look at only you.
-I'll be back, Mhatre.
-Okay.
-Yes Rupa, tell me.
-Any updates on Bhumi?
Bhumi is at the camp. She must be fine.
What kind of training is it?
Don't they allow to call home?
There is network issue there.
I've told you this before.
-Mom is worried.
-Why?
She enjoys being worried,
but you have some connections
with the officers, right?
Please talk to them.
Yes, okay. I'll do something.
Tell your mom not to worry.
It'll affect her health even more.
Take care.
You should've seen her face
when I returned her the phone.
And I told her that I didn't have to give
all that to Hemant...
that he was asking her for.
It felt good...
seeing her face.
I too never bonded well with my family.
We were always in danger.
We used to get threats all the time.
I was born in such a family
that I believed
families are meant to be that way.
Homes are meant to be that way.
But then I grew up,
met people... and realized that...
a home can mean something different too.
Since then, I am searching for a home...
which is free of danger.
But do you know what I think?
I mean I'm scared
that I'm addicted to danger.
I want to go far from danger
but somehow manage to come close to it.
I want everything to be easy and normal
but being normal isn't easy for me.
I try again.
I told you... I try.
-What will you do with me?
-We won't speak about work.
Who sent you? Why did they send you?
Torturing you to get the truth out...
it's such a wastage of time.
I'll get to know about it.
My people will find out.
We will only... talk.
Our personal conversations.
Let's do that and see what happens.
-Where are you?
-I'm in Hyderabad, sir.
How will I know where they took her?
You tell me.
Nayakudu hasn't spoken to me
even once since I came here.
Aren't your men there?
Can't you get information from them?
Sir, no one is telling me anything.
Everyone is terrified of Nayakudu.
They aren't speaking to me properly.
Sasya, we didn't agree on this.
You told me that
you'll keep me informed every minute.
Sir, everything is clear.
I work for you, sir.
If I get any information,
I'll call you first.
Can I trust you?
Do you have any other option, sir?
I think Sasya is double-crossing us, sir.
This was Nayak's plan
from the start and we are trapped now.
For God's sake, Fernandez.
Stop flying from one pole to another.
Okay, tell me...
is Sasya's information accurate?
Yes, sir.
And information about Nayak's operation
is recorded on the tape.
Yes, it is recorded.
So, if Sasya is with Nayak,
why will he give us
all the information on record?
Why will he give us
the details of the operation?
Sir, what if Sasya
is double-crossing Nayak?
There you go.
And... he used us for his mission, sir.
Even if it's true, what is wrong in it?
We will still catch Nayak
and stop his operations.
This is our objective, right?
I don't know, sir.
They belong to a different breed, sir.
The way they think, the way they work...
there is no limit.
Finally, the day has come
when the hero and heroine
of the story meet.
The game my finger started...
will reach its climax here.
Weren't you in Hyderabad?
Yes, but I am here now.
Close to you.
And your boss, Fernandez Sir
knows nothing about it.
-Come on. Come here. Where are you going?
-Stay away from me, Sasya.
Go, run.
The more you try to escape,
the more warmed up I get.
And the harder I'll come for you
A damp squib.
You called me a damp squib.
I'll show you my strength.
A woman... you tried to dominate me?
You wanted to overpower Sasya?
I put in so much efforts to get you
out of interrogation room and here.
I said that Nayakudu was impotent.
But that's not true.
He is exactly like me.
If he gets a chance, he will mount you.
Like how I'm going to mount you... now.
Does Nayak know...
that you became a police witness?
Everything is good
between me and Nayakudu.
He himself called me here,
told me that there's a girl in his room
and he was going out for a day.
He told me,
"Sasya, brother look into it...
do something so that the girl
can never open her mouth."
But why will you open your mouth?
I am going to kill the scorpion
inside you... on this bed tonight.
I'm going to take my revenge
from you all night...
N... Nayakudu...
You... Nayakudu, before you do anything,
please hear me out just once.
Listen to me just once. I can...
I'm sorry... sorry...
There's not even a little fire inside you.
Bhumi isn't a woman.
Your looks are quite ordinary. Body too.
Has it been too long since you had sex?
The scorpion inside you is real.
You are not a woman.
You're a man.
There's not even a little fire...
Bhumi isn't...
Has it been too long...
The scorpion inside you is real.
Sasya has not sent me here.
I am a cop.
I know everything about your operation.
I am the only one
in the entire department...
whom Sasya told everything.
He told me every single thing.
You can do whatever you want with me.
I cannot change your mind.
But I have an offer for you.
Nayak... look carefully at me.
This is me talking to you.
Sasya is dead!
I will take Sasya's place for you.
I will give you all the information
that Sasya told the police.
I will give you his testimony.
If I do... what I'm promising you now,
if I am of any use to you,
you give me money or whatever you want.
This is my offer to you.
Accept it,
or else slit me with your sword.
Do as you please.
Whatever you feel is right.
You do it.
I told you,
I will never hurt you.