Two of my informers reported that
the police have beefed up the security.
One at the airport and the other at...
By the time I got the information,
it was too late.
Clear this space.
-Move to the next location.
-Okay, brother.
Come on! Move! Move!
How's Rupa?
Alright.
You said two weeks, right?
It's just been a day.
Why the blindfold?
Are you planning something special?
I thought you wouldn't
insult me by asking me why.
Why?
I told you about the airline staff.
ACP Fernandez's
special operations police team
is questioning the staff
at the airport right now.
The double-life I'm living...
do you have any idea how difficult it is?
I feel like I'm walking on a knife's edge
every single second of my life.
You're just "Nayak"!
You don't need to be anybody else.
Keeping up the act, keeping secrets,
remembering what's supposed
to be a secret and what's not.
One wrong word...
and I'll be done!
You think I betrayed you.
Maybe.
But that man...
your man...
the airline guy...
he's living the same double-life, right?
Why can't he be the rat?
But you're sure that it's me.
Alright.
Punish me.
Come on, punish me.
You're playing me?
And I'm getting played.
-Your department?
-Ground staff.
Here's the muster for 5th April.
The in and out timings of all the
employees have been recorded.
-Is anyone missing?
-No.
-Check the CCTV footage.
-Sure.
Give me your phone.
Should I check the footage?
Sure. Go on.
-Check it again.
-I've double-checked it, sir.
We've found nothing suspicious.
Beef up the security...
...at all places.
Nayakudu...
I'm sorry to say,
but we shouldn't trust Bhumi.
You told me that you
wanted to be on my side.
You had sex with me...
to save your life.
I get that.
But why would you risk
your life to be with me?
Double-life?
Betraying the police?
Giving up...
your old life in a heartbeat?
One day is all it took
to "fall in love" with me?
I won't explain myself, Nayak.
You're a sharp man.
Really smart.
But you're not a woman.
A woman who's lived
all her life thinking that...
she's not good enough for any man.
She's a "cold hag".
She's dull in bed!
Who's been told all her life that...
"You're a man!"
"Shoving it in you
doesn't give me pleasure either!"
And who has believed that it's all true.
Then I meet a man.
I touch him.
He likes it.
He wants to have sex with me!
He does have sex with me!
Not with himself!
He holds me...
with love!
All this love...
for me!
I would be a slave to a man like that
for the rest of my life!
But you won't get it.
And I'm not gonna bother explaining.
What am I becoming, Nayak?
I have no control...
over myself, over my life!
Who am I?
What happened, Fernandez?
We've found nothing at the airport, sir.
But Bhumi had confirmed that
the airline staff was involved, right?
Yes, at my home!
At 4:30 a.m.
I've left my phone at the hotel, sir.
I want to talk to you.
They have an informer
in the airline staff.
He was the one who
informed the Nayak syndicate...
that we were gonna
check the cabin baggage.
She seemed really sure, sir.
How could it be wrong?
What about the other leads she gave you?
First, they gave me a number.
Phone number.
Use it for coordination.
They'll answer all your questions.
This one.
I'm told to be in touch with this number.
I'm connected to the whole
drug supply network in Mumbai.
I've sent names and numbers
of a few girls on this number
to expand their network.
There's only one way I can
connect to this number.
I send a text between 4:00 to 4:30 p.m.
And I get a reply in exactly 15 minutes.
And in those 15 minutes...
the whole chain is completed.
And the syndicate is informed.
And thirdly,
the final date of this operation.
Their operation style
could be cyclical, sir.
That's exactly what it was in Karwar.
There are particular dates in every cycle.
The movement happens
only on these dates, sir.
And there's one more
date left in the current cycle.
What's the date?
I don't know the date, sir.
But I know that the
date's really important.
Most of their work happens online.
But every member in the network
will be on the move on that date.
And his whole network will be exposed.
And his whole drug business will be set.
The syndicate will be
vulnerable on that one date!
Absolutely!
This might be our last opportunity
to catch them red-handed.
Anything else?
She's telling us the truth, sir.
But my instinct says she
isn't telling us the whole truth.
Call me back soon.
Before you leave.
I want as much time as I can get.
What's wrong?
Sir, there's a mole in your team.
He's giving him all the information.
I told you about his airline informer.
How did he find out?
That's impossible, Bhumi.
You know I personally choose
every single person on my team, right?
I trust them, there's no
scope of them betraying me!
I'm the one who's risking my life, sir!
I'm the one who has to live with him.
I don't care who you trust.
You're the only one I trust.
And you should do the same, sir.
Sir, did you tell this to anyone else?
The syndicate gave her his number?
Keep watching, Kamble.
Copy.
You text him?
I think he's illiterate.
I don't think this is the guy.
Sir, it's 4:00 p.m.
I need to send the text.
He's on the move.
Copy.
I should get a reply in 15 minutes.
It goes to me as well as
the other syndicate members.
If I don't get a reply in 15 minutes,
it means that something's wrong.
Okay.
We'll try it again tomorrow.
And if the pattern is repeated,
then we strike.
I'm gonna drizzle my love...
So, how's Whore Inc. doing?
Stay out of it, alright?
It's really filthy.
You cheat on your wife by sleeping
with me in the name of protection costs.
Isn't that filthy?
Look, Yasmin.
People like you and me...
our lives aren't black or white.
We're somewhere in the middle.
But the whole drugs business...
it's the scum of the earth.
Everyone who gets involved ends up dead.
Bhonsle...
how can I end up dead
if I have you with me?
-Right?
-Me?
You'll protect me, right?
You want me to join Whore Inc.?
Why not?
I'm saying it for your own sake.
What the hell is going on?
A whore's threatening me?
"For my own sake"?
How the mighty have fallen, Mr. Bhonsle!
What are you doing?
Listen to me. Bhonsle!
Bhonsle, come here.
So, you whores have
really made it big, huh?
Where are you going?
Every bloody pig's telling me...
"Bhonsle, ignore Whore Inc.
Look away! Look away!"
They're all pressuring me to look away.
I think I should take a peek.
And I will take a peek.
Bhonsle...
if you do that... you and I are done.
Alright?
Get lost!
There's no dearth of prostitutes.
I'll find another!
-Bhonsle!
-Get lost!
Stop.
What's going on, Bhonsle sir?
I'm told you're hanging out with
senior call girls these days?
What's so funny?
Every man has different interests.
He's interested in the seniors.
Oh, come on.
Don't mind me, Bhonsle.
We're just kidding.
Why would Bhonsle mind?
Bhonsle is just a dumbfuck!
-He drinks and he sobs like a weakling!
-Hey!
Fuck Bhonsle up his ass!
-Come on.
What's wrong with him?
I'm not gonna spare those whores!
I'm gonna screw them!
Please use a condom, alright?
Yeah.
This is what I deserve.
Kanitkar sir insulted
me the other day as well...
in front of those whores...
in the bloody police station.
Of course!
If you poke your nose where it
doesn't belong, it will be chopped off!
Because there are
bigger powers at play here.
What are you gonna do?!
Look, Bhonsle, only bark at a person
who's scared of getting bitten.
Are you getting me?
Otherwise, just keep a low profile.
Am I right? Of course!
-Give it to sir.
-What's "Sir"?
Hey, take the premium stuff away.
I'll have the bloody country liquor.
I don't deserve this premium whiskey.
-I'm a bloody cockroach!
-Drink up, buddy!
No, stop! I'm just a bloody cockroach!
"Bloody! Bloody!"
Just take a bloody sip!
-Come on!
-Drink up, Bhonsle. Come on.
Open up!
Yasmin!
Open the door!
Pooja Jadhav. Seven packets.
Ma'am...
Bhonsle's here.
Hey!
The door's closed. Can't you see that?
-Who's in there?
-Why?
What do you want?
You bitches love humiliating me, right?
Hey!
Go away or these bitches
are gonna give you stitches!
-Get out! Leave!
-Don't touch me.
I'm here to make you an offer.
Why? Aren't you done humiliating me?
You've shown me that
I'm just a bloody cockroach.
Why would you make me an offer?
Because you're right.
You're a cockroach.
And cockroaches can go to
places that elephants can't.
The whole system...
every drain, every gutter,
how to maneuver it,
you know it.
Because you're a cockroach.
And we need you.
She's leaving.
Let her go. Don't look.
-Oh, God!
-Speak up!
-What?
-Who's sent you?
Tell me!
I'm letting you go right now.
But if I see you again...
I'll blow your brains out!
Stay away from me.
Are you alright?
I can save you.
Really?
Do it.
Look...
we know who has pitted
us against each other.
Who?
We have nothing against each other.
If we had met under
different circumstances...
we could've been friends.
I won't touch you.
But you'll have to stop
obsessing about revenge.
I don't care if I die,
I'm gonna get my revenge!
That asshole, Nayak...
he made me a widow.
I will exact revenge...
not on you.
I'm talking about that asshole Nayak.
Tell me something.
Is Nayak one man or is it a group?
Bitch.
You've slept with him
and you have no clue?
Did you sleep with one man or many?
Do you really want me to give you a count?
So, you're saying...
it's a group?
That's what they say.
I used to think it was one man as well.
And I get my commands on the phone.
Listen...
I won't tell anyone about you.
Otherwise, you know...
Get some rest.
The bitch is tough.
Great actress.
"I used to think it was one man as well."
Was she lying?
I have no idea how
these perverts live their lives.
-What should we do?
-What can you do?
-Keep following her.
-But Nayak's one man, right?
He has to be!
How many men am I gonna kill?
-Chembur?
-Okay.
-And Mahim?
-That's in control as well.
Ma'am!
-Well...
-Good morning, ma'am.
I'm from the office of the
Municipal Commissioner.
Hey, move.
Please have a seat, sir.
Have you lost it?
Keep me away from
public officials, alright?
Your request has been sanctioned.
We've received an order from the ministry.
We need you to sign some papers
and the lease can be finalized.
You can go and see the
building anytime you want.
What building?
The building for your social organization.
Women Welfare Organization?
The building for your NGO.
-You have an order from the ministry?
-Yes, we got it today.
You see, these are old
buildings tied up in litigation.
These can be leased
out to social organizations
only after the ministry clears them.
Please sign these.
Can we see the building today?
Of course.
There you go.
That's your building.
Please come.
Wow!
-There's more!
-This is awesome!
-This is huge!
-Come on!
This a sprawling mansion!
-Look at that...
-Hey, Tipu!
Hey, Mary!
Fort! It's a bloody fort!
We can have a whole army!
-This will be our office, right?
-Hey!
We can live here as well!
Do you think...
I can't handle it myself?
-You can.
-Then why are you helping me?
Getting the girls out of jail?
And this social welfare building?
It was just a gift.
I won't help you anymore.
You don't need it either.
But what am I gonna do
with that huge building?
That building will be
too small for you soon.
You have no idea...
what you've become.
And where you're heading.
I've received a text from Nayak.
He wants to see me immediately.
-I think something's wrong.
-Why?
Sir, he suspects my motives!
They suspect my motives.
And his mole must've informed him.
What should we do?
I'll have to go.
And I need to send the text
between 4:00 and 4:30 p.m.
Okay.
I'll go.
It's me.
Did you send the text?
Yes.
I'll get a notification in 15 minutes...
if no one messes up.
We don't have much time then.
Leena, inform the second unit.
Take position.
On mark.
Look properly.
-Hey, what's happening?!
-Down! Get down!
Hey!
-Stay down!
-We've got him, sir.
We have three minutes
to send the notification.
Is the cybercrime team working on it?
-How do you send the notification?
-I don't know, sir.
I have no clue...
Tell me how you send the notification.
Sir, my parents have no idea I do this.
Please, it'll ruin my life!
How do you send the notification?!
-What's happening, Kamble?
-The boy's nervous, sir.
He isn't thinking straight.
Slap him into thinking straight.
Check the message history on the darknet.
Check yesterday's messages.
-It's been cleared, sir.
-We're out of time, goddamn it!
Message sent, sir.
Nayak syndicate handles all
its dealings through the darknet.
Every link in the network has a unique ID,
that they use to
communicate with each other.
These operators handle all the
communication that happens on the darknet.
Just like the one we've caught.
You mean there could be more
such operators in Nayak's network?
Highly possible.
My God!
Did you give some
information to the police team?
About a suspicious workshop?
Yeah, I mean, Fernandez sir
keeps questioning me.
I gave him a bait to
get myself off the hook.
I told him, "Maybe there's a workshop."
Alibaug, right?
Kihim.
Kihim, Alibaug...
same.
-Good morning, sir.
-Morning.
What's going on?
-Check it.
-Sir, my phone...
Sit down, Karmarkar.
Sit down, guys.
Sir, there's a mole in your team.
Bhumi had told you guys
about a suspicious workshop.
Nayak syndicate has a workshop...
in Palghar.
I overheard them.
They were talking about...
a workshop in Khandala.
Where?
Kihim.
Alibaug.
Sir, I had given everyone
a different location.
And I had told Karmarkar about Kihim.
Do you want me to check the footage?
We need to keep it a secret.
The Nayak syndicate shouldn't
find out that we've caught him.
What if...
Karmarkar tells them himself?
He's the first guy they'll kill.
I feel like such a fool here.
I've never chosen the wrong
man in my life, Karmarkar!
You didn't select the wrong guy, sir.
But I'm not lucky like the other officers.
I have an eight-year-old son.
They kidnapped him.
I did what I had to.
We'll deal with this later.
Karmarkar is out of the operation.
No one's gonna give him any information.
And no one outside this room should
know about this new development.
-Sir!
-It's alright.
Sit.
Thank you.
So, how's it going?
It's the same, sir.
You tell me.
How is Commissioner Bhat feeling?
I could be transferred.
What?
They need a scapegoat.
And you know how bad
our reputation is right now.
The media is useless, sir.
They have no clue about the
size of this drug operation, sir!
But now we're making some progress, sir.
But not fast enough, I guess.
These things take time, I understand.
Sir, we're close to exposing
Nayak syndicate's entire operation soon.
We don't have the date, Fernandez.
This information is
useless without the date.
I need the Karwar files again.
All the links of the syndicate
seem to know about the date.
But no one's mentioning
it on the darknet.
Get me all the statistics we have!
Air, land, sea, check posts,
get me everything!
Any headway on the date?
Not yet, sir.
Sir, it's like this.
Day one, drug movement.
Day two, drug movement.
Day three, drug movement.
Day four, nothing.
Day five, drug movement.
Day six, seven, nothing.
-Day eight...
-Nambiar! Nambiar!
Sir, Fibonacci series, sir!
Sir, zero, one, one, two,
two plus one, three,
three plus two, five,
five plus three, eight,
eight plus five, thirteen!
Sir, this is the working
pattern of the syndicate, sir.
So, what you're saying is...
on the first, second...
third, and fifth, we have a
record of syndicate's movements?
-Yes, sir, this is the pattern!
-No!
There was no drug movement
on the first and the second.
But that's the pattern, sir!
They followed the same pattern in Karwar!
There's no date.
We need the date, Nambiar!
Poor girl, she was born on the
thirteenth day of the lunar calendar.
The moon's position in her
birth chart isn't auspicious.
Do you really believe these
charts about the sun and the moon?
Don't underestimate the moon.
It's really powerful.
Moon!
-The moon!
-Dear?
Dear, what's wrong?
Sir!
He's back!
And he's got some
calendars with him this time!
We got distracted by the sun, sir.
The Fibonacci series is the right pattern!
But they aren't using the solar calendar!
Lunar!
He switched to the lunar
calendar based on the moon.
Sir, solar is western, sir.
The Indian calendar is the lunar calendar.
-Telugu calendar.
-Okay.
Now you see.
Day one.
Day two.
Day three.
Day five.
Day eight.
Day thirteen.
30th August!
There's been no movement
after 30th August!
That's right, sir.
So, what's left?
Day 21, day 34, etc.
But day 34 etc., won't be possible because
there are just 28 days in the lunar cycle.
So, one day left, sir.
Day 21.
September 7th?
Precisely!
We've got the date, sir!
7th September.
Five days to go.
Just five days to go, Bhumi.
And then, one way or the other,
we'll close Nayak's chapter forever!
Do you like the sun...
or the moon?
I've never thought about it.
I like the moon.
Me too.