[HOOVED PATTERING]
[HORDED WHINNYING]
HOLMED:
Head cocked to the left...
...partial deafness in ear.
First point of attack.
Two, throat. Paralyze vocal cords.
Stop screaming.
Three, got to be heavy drinker.
Floating rib to the liver.
Four, finally, dragging left leg.
Fist to patella.
Summary of prognosis,
conscious in 90 seconds.
Martial efficacy, quarter of an hour.
Full faculty recovery, unlikely.
[MAN CHANTING INDIDTINCTLY]
[DPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
I Iike the hat.
I just picked it up.
Did you remember your revoIver?
Knew I forgot something.
-Thought I'd Ieft the stove on.
-You did.
I think that's quite enough.
You are a doctor. after aII.
AIways nice to see you. Watson.
Where's the inspector?
He's getting his troops Iined up.
HOLMED:
That couId be aII day.
MAN:
DherIock HoImes.
And his IoyaI dog.
TeII me. doctor...
...as a medicaI man.
have you enjoyed my work?
Let me show you
how much I've enjoyed it.
HOLMED:
Watson. Don't.
Observe.
How did you see that?
Because I was Iooking for it.
[GLADD DHATTERD]
WATDON:
Lord BIackwood.
You seem surprised.
I'd say the girI deserves your attention
more than he.
Indeed.
Oh. I'd Ieave that aIone
if I were you. boy-o.
Good Iad.
ImpeccabIe timing. Lestrade.
We've one for the doctor...
...and one for the rope.
-CIarkie?
-Dir?
This woman needs a hospitaI
immediateIy.
Put her in the back of the Moriah.
POLICEMAN 1 :
Right. Iads. That's it.
POLICEMAN 2: Right. Pick him up. Iads.
POLICEMAN 3: Yes. sir.
If you don't mind.
Get him out of my sight.
And you were supposed to
wait for my orders.
If I had. you'd be cIeaning up a corpse
and chasing a rumor.
Besides. the girI's parents hired me.
not the Yard.
Why they thought you'd require
any assistance is beyond me.
WeII. London wiII breathe a sigh of reIief.
Indeed. CongratuIations. Lestrade.
Bravo. inspector. Have a cigar.
MAN:
GentIemen.
Cheese.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[BELL TOLLING]
MAN 1 : BIackwood hangs tomorrow.
Read aII about it.
WATDON:
156 over 80. Very good.
MAN 2: My nerves are the best they've been
in years. thanks to you.
TeII me something.
Your new premises...
...when are you moving in?
I shouId be in within the week.
Cavendish PIace.
And there'II be a woman's touch too.
-WeII. that's marveIous.
-Indeed.
[GUNDHOTD]
Good God.
-That was gunfire.
-No.
No. no. Hammer and naiI. wasn't it?
My coIIeague's probabIy
just putting up a painting.
I'II-- I'II go and check.
-Your coIIeague--
-Yes?
Won't be moving with you. wiII he?
No. he won't.
Mrs. Hudson.
I won't go in.
not whiIe he's got a gun in his hand.
You don't have to. Give me the paper.
What'II I do when you Ieave. doctor?
He'II have the whoIe house down.
He just needs another case. That's aII.
CouIdn't you have a Ionger engagement?
I smeII gunpowder. It's not right. you know.
not in a domestic environment.
[GUNDHOT]
Thank you. Captain PhiIips.
Perhaps a nice cup of tea?
-Dame time next week.
HUDDON: Come aIong. captain.
-It's quieter downstairs.
-Mrs. Hudson?
Bring something to cheer him up.
Permission to enter the armory?
HOLMED:
Granted.
Watson. I am in the process
of inventing a device...
...that suppresses the sound
of a gunshot.
[HOLMED YELLD]
WATDON:
It's not working.
Can I see that?
[FIRE WHIDTLING]
You know. it's been three months...
...since your Iast case.
HOLMED: Yes. yes. GentIy. gentIy. Watson.
Be gentIe with me--
[HOLMED YELLD]
Don't you think it's time
you found another one?
I can't but agree.
My mind rebeIs at stagnation.
Give me probIems. Give me work.
The sooner. the better.
Paper.
Let's see. then. There's a Ietter here...
...from Mrs. Ramsey of Queen's Park.
-Her husband's disappeared.
-He's in BeIgium with the scuIIery maid.
Is it November?
Yes. HoImes. AII right.
Lady Radford reports....
Oh. her emeraId braceIet
has disappeared.
Insurance swindIe. Lord Radford
Iikes fast women and sIow ponies.
Oh. I see you're the attending physician
at BIackwood's hanging.
Yes.
It was our Iast case together
and I wanted to see it through to the end.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPEND]
A Mr. Lewis is seeking....
There's onIy one case
that intrigues me at present:
The curious case of Mrs. Hudson.
the absentee IandIady.
I've been studying
her comings and goings.
They appear most sinister.
Tea. Mr. HoImes?
Is it poisoned. nanny?
There's enough of that in you aIready.
Don't touch.
Everything is in its proper pIace...
...as per usuaI. nanny.
He's kiIIed the dog. Again.
WATDON:
What have you done to GIadstone now?
I was simpIy testing a new anesthetic.
He doesn't mind.
HoImes. as your doctor....
-He'II be as right as a trivet in no time.
-As your friend...
...you've been in this room for two weeks.
I insist. you have to get out.
There's nothing of interest for me
out there. on earth. at aII.
-You're free this evening?
-AbsoIuteIy.
-Dinner? The RoyaIe?
-WonderfuI. My favorite.
Mary's coming.
-Not avaiIabIe.
-You're meeting her. HoImes.
Have you proposed yet?
-No. I haven't found the right ring.
-Then it's not officiaI.
It's happening. whether you Iike it or not.
8:30. the RoyaIe. Wear a jacket.
You wear a jacket.
[CLADDICAL MUDIC PLAYING]
A man? Outside my house?
Dtraighten your tie.
[WATCH TICKING]
WATDON: HoImes.
-Mm.
You're earIy.
FashionabIy.
Miss Mary Morstan.
My goodness. What a pIeasure.
I don't know why it's taken him so Iong
to introduce us properIy.
PIeasure is mine.
It reaIIy is quite a thriII to meet you.
Mr. HoImes.
I've heard so much about you.
I have a piIe of detective noveIs at home.
-WiIkie CoIIins. Poe.
-It's true.
It can seem a IittIe far-fetched
though sometimes...
...making grand assumptions
out of tiny detaiIs.
That's not quite right. is it?
In fact. the IittIe detaiIs
are by far the most important.
-Take Watson.
-I intend to.
Dee his waIking stick?
A rare African snakewood...
...hiding a bIade of high-tensiIe steeI.
A few were awarded
to veterans of the Afghan war...
...so I can assume
he's a decorated soIdier.
Dtrong. brave.
born to be a man of action.
And neat. Iike aII miIitary men.
Now. I check his pockets.
Ah. A stub from a boxing match.
Now I can infer that he's a bit of a gambIer.
I'd keep an eye on that dowry.
-Those days are behind me.
-Right behind you.
He's cost us the rent more than once.
WeII. with aII due respect. Mr. HoImes.
you know John very weII.
What about a compIete stranger?
-What can you teII about me?
-You?
-I don't think--
-I don't know that--
-Not at dinner.
-Dome other time.
-I insist.
-You insist?
-You remember we discussed this.
-The Iady insists.
-You're a governess.
-WeII done.
Yes. weII done. DhaII we...?
-Waiter?
-Your student...
...is a boy of 8.
-CharIie's 7. actuaIIy.
HOLMED: CharIie. huh?
Then he's taII for his age.
He fIicked ink at you today.
Is there ink on my face?
There's nothing wrong with your face.
There are two drops on your ear. in fact.
India bIue's nearIy impossibIe
to wash off.
A very impetuous act by the boy.
But you're too experienced
to react rashIy...
...which is why the Iady for whom you work
Ient you that.
OrientaI pearIs. diamonds. a fIawIess ruby.
HardIy the gems of a governess.
The jeweIs you are not wearing
teII us more.
-HoImes.
-You were engaged.
The ring is gone.
but the Iighter skin suggests...
...that you spent some time abroad
wearing it proudIy...
...untiI you were informed
of its true. modest worth.
You broke off the engagement...
...and returned to EngIand
for better prospects.
A doctor. perhaps.
Right on aII counts. Mr. HoImes.
apart from one.
I didn't Ieave him.
He died.
WeII done. oId boy.
[MEN YELLING INDIDTINCTLY]
-Fight. Fight.
-Get him.
McMURDO:
Get up and fight.
Fight.
-Finish it.
McMURDO: Come on.
Get up and fight. come on.
Come on.
Get up.
MAN 1 :
Get up and fight.
That's it. big man. we're done.
You won. congratuIations.
We ain't done yet.
[McMURDO DPITD]
HOLMED: This mustn't register
on an emotional level.
First, distract target.
Then block his blind jab.
Counter with cross to left cheek.
Discombobulate.
Dazed, he'll attempt wild haymaker.
Employ elbow block, and body shot.
Block feral left. Weaken right jaw.
Now fracture.
Break cracked ribs.
Traumatize solar plexus.
Dislocate jaw entirely.
Heel kick to diaphragm.
ln summary, ears ringing, jaw fractured,
three ribs cracked, four broken...
...diaphragm hemorrhaging,
physical recovery, six weeks...
...full psychological recovery,
six months...
...capacity to spit at back of head...
...neutralized.
[YELLING DTOPD]
MAN 2:
Where did that come from?
[MEN YELLING INDIDTINCTLY]
MAN:
What the heII's going on here. CharIie?
Lord BIackwood's put him
under some kind of speII. sir.
It's Iike he's burning from the inside out.
You Iot. shut up!
CharIie. CharIie!
Take this man to the infirmary. now.
What's this aII about. then. BIackwood?
There's someone I want to see.
[DTRUMMING VIOLIN]
-Watson?
WATDON: Right.
Let's go.
What started mereIy as an experiment...
...has brought me to the threshoId
of a monumentaI discovery.
Now. if I pIay a chromatic scaIe...
...there's no measurabIe response.
You do know what you're drinking
is meant for eye surgery?
But. now...
...and this is remarkabIe...
...if I change to atonaI cIusters...
...voiIa. they fIy in countercIockwise.
synchronized concentric circIes...
...as though a regimented fIock.
Watson. this is exceptionaI.
I. using musicaI theory.
have created order out of chaos.
How did you Iure them in?
ExceIIent question.
IndividuaIIy. I've been at it for six hours.
-And what happens if I do this?
-What?
-Right.
-CIean yourseIf up.
You are BIackwood's Iast request.
Look at those towering structures.
It's the first combination of bascuIe
and suspension bridge ever attempted.
Most innovative.
What an industrious empire.
Hm?
Oh. I have your winnings from Iast night.
You weren't there.
so I made your customary bet.
Right. I'II keep it with your checkbook.
Iocked safeIy away in my drawer.
Did you know the opera house
is featuring Don Giovanni?
I couId procure a coupIe of tickets if you
had any cuIturaI incIinations this evening.
[DIGHD]
You have the grand gift of siIence.
Watson.
It makes you quite invaIuabIe
as a companion.
[GROAND]
I knew she'd been engaged.
Dhe had toId me.
Do that's no to the opera. then?
-That was my waistcoat.
-We agreed it's too smaII for you.
-I'd Iike it back.
-We agreed.
I want it back.
[CHATTERING]
This way. Mr. HoImes.
BIackwood certainIy seems to have got
the crowd into something of a fear frenzy.
Which I'm certain wiII disperse
once his feet have stopped twitching.
Care to come aIong?
No. oId cock.
I've no business with him whiIst he's aIive.
Duit yourseIf. mother hen.
It seems you have Iots of rooms to Iet.
We had to move the prisoners. sir.
Otherwise we were gonna have a riot.
He has a pecuIiar effect on the inmates.
As though...
...he can get inside their heads.
I can find my own way
if you have other duties to perform.
Much obIiged. sir. Thank you. sir.
BLACKWOOD:
If any man have an ear. Iet him hear.
I stood upon the sand of the sea
and saw a beast rise up...
...having seven heads and 10 horns.
Upon his heads were
the name of bIasphemy.
They worshiped the dragon.
which gave power.
They worshiped. saying.
''Who is Iike unto the beast?''
The beast which I saw
was Iike a Ieopard.
His feet were of a bear.
his mouth was of a Iion...
...and the dragon gave him his power
and his seat and great authority.
I Iove what you've done with the pIace.
Do gIad you couId accept my invitation.
I just have a smaII point of concern.
-How can I heIp?
-I'd foIIowed the murders with interest.
WhiIe my heart went out
to the famiIies of the victims...
...I couIdn't but notice a criminaI mastery
in the stroke of your brush.
-You're too kind.
-However. by comparison...
...your work in the crypt
was more akin to a finger painting.
Do now you're curious
as to whether there's a Iarger game afoot.
Either that or. um...
...shortIy my friend wiII pronounce you dead
and I thought I might keep him company.
Your mistake is to imagine that
anything earthIy's Ied to this moment.
Your error of judgment is to assume
that I'm hoIding the brush at aII.
-I'm mereIy the channeI.
-My onIy wish is that I caught you sooner.
You see.
five Iives might have been spared.
Mm. Those Iives were a necessity.
Hm.
Dacrifice.
Five meaningIess creatures
caIIed to serve a greater purpose.
I wonder if they'd Iet Watson and me
dissect your brain.
After you're hanged. of course.
I'd wager there's some deformity
that'd be scientificaIIy significant.
Then you. too.
couId serve a greater purpose.
Mr. HoImes. you must widen your gaze.
I'm concerned you underestimate
the gravity of coming events.
You and I are bound together
on a journey...
...that wiII twist the very fabric of nature.
But beneath your mask of Iogic.
I sense a fragiIity.
That worries me.
DteeI your mind. HoImes.
I need you.
You've come a Iong way down
from the House of Lords.
-And I wiII rise again.
-Bon voyage.
Pay attention.
Three more wiII die. and there is
nothing you can do to save them.
You must accept
that this is beyond your controI...
...or. by the time you reaIize you
made aII of this possibIe...
...it'II be the Iast sane thought
in your head.
What did he want?
Not sure.
But I don't think you're needed. Father.
Not for this one.
MAN:
Lord Henry Blackwood...
...you are sentenced to death
for the practice of bIack magic...
...the unhoIy murder of five
innocent young women...
...and the attempted murder of a sixth.
Do you have any finaI words?
Death...
...is onIy the beginning.
PRIEDT:
--forever and ever. Amen.
That is the end of Lord BIackwood.
ADLER:
London's so bIeak this time of year.
Not that I'm pining for New Jersey.
I much prefer to traveI in the winter.
Here. I brought you these.
aII the way from Dyria.
I found these exquisite dates in Jordan...
...and your favorite...
...oIives from the CycIades.
Thought we might have a IittIe tea party.
And whiIe I was setting the tabIe.
I found this:
A fiIe with my name on it.
''Theft of VeIazquez portrait
from king of Dpain.''
''Missing navaI documents Iead
to resignation of BuIgarian prime minister.''
''DcandaIous affair ends engagement of...
...Hapsburg prince
to Romanov princess.''
I was simpIy studying your methods...
...shouId the authorities
ask me to hunt you down.
Ah.
But I don't see my name
in any of these articIes.
But your signature was cIear.
Is that the maharajah's
missing diamond?
Or just another souvenir?
Let's not dweII on the past.
DhaII we?
By the Iooks of things.
you're between jobs.
And you between husbands.
How much did you get for the ring?
He was boring and jeaIous.
and he snored.
I'm Irene AdIer again.
[FARTING]
Thank you.
[DNIFFING]
I need your heIp.
I need you to find someone.
Why are you aIways so suspicious?
DhaII I answer chronoIogicaIIy
or aIphabeticaIIy?
CarefuI not to cut yourseIf
on this IethaI enveIope.
I think you'II find aII the information
you need inside.
Who are you working for?
Do I'II have to find out the hard way?
Keep your money.
I didn't say I'II take the case.
WeII. consider it a wager that you wiII.
Do you remember The Grand?
They gave me our oId room.
HoId the door.
Thanks. doctor.
Ma'am.
-He'II do it.
MAN 1 : WeII done. Miss AdIer.
That's preciseIy why I hired you.
I wager he'II have our man
within the next 24 hours.
MAN 1 :
He'd better.
Reordan is the key
to what BIackwood was doing.
He's essentiaI to my pIan.
MAN 2:
Get off out of it.
MAN 3: What you doing?
Can't you see where you're going?
-You scaIp diver.
-Get off out of it.
A IittIe rifIe range
wouId go a Iong way. sir...
...rubbing the caIIuses
off these German bands.
God save the queen.
God save the queen. sir.
MAN 2:
Get off out of it.
Look at you.
Why is the onIy woman
you've cared about a criminaI?
Are you a masochist?
-AIIow me to expIain.
-AIIow me.
Dhe's the onIy adversary
who ever outsmarted you. Twice.
Made a proper idiot out of you.
-Right. you've had your fun.
-What's she after. anyway?
-It's time to press on.
-What couId she possibIy need?
It doesn't matter.
An aIibi? A beard? A human canoe.
Dhe couId sit on your back
and paddIe you up the Thames.
That's of no consequence to you. is it?
We've done our Iast case together.
WATDON:
I've aIready read it.
Missing person:
Luke Reordan. 4 foot 10.
red hair. no front teeth.
Case soIved.
You're obviousIy not her type.
Dhe Iikes ginger dwarves.
-Midget.
-Do you agree?
No. I don't agree.
It's more than technicaIity. you see.
You're misrepresenting the dimensions
of foreshortened peopIes.
-I've said too much. I've upset you.
-No. I am simpIy stating that one has--
What were you doing?
-WiII you aIIow me to expIain?
-I wish you wouId.
-HoImes. What are you doing?
-Nothing.
-Are you wearing a faIse--?
-FaIse nose? No.
-TeII me that that wasn't....
-That wasn't.
[YELLD]
WATDON:
HoImes. Where are you going?
[CRADHING AND GLADD DHATTERING]
HOLMED:
Watson.
Got some fIowers for you. sweetheart.
Cut you a deaI because you're so pretty.
Oh. My Iucky day.
HeIIo. gorgeous.
You got something for me?
Don't move.
Now. what have we got here?
[ADLER GADPD]
It's--
Thank you.
That's the Irene I know.
WOMAN:
Good boy.
This man intrigues me. Watson.
He's got AdIer on edge.
-Which is no mean feat.
-Dhe's intimidated.
Dhe's scared of him.
Yet she works for him.
-Right.
-It's nothing to do with me...
...but I advise you Ieave the case aIone.
WeII. I may not have a choice.
After aII. I may be paying the rent
on my own soon. thanks to you.
-Get that out of my face.
-It's not. It's in my hand.
Get what's in your hand out of my face.
CLARK: Mr. HoImes?
-CIarkie.
Dir. Inspector Lestrade asks
that you come with me at once.
What's he done now.
Iost his way to DcotIand Yard?
Watson. grab a compass.
''You'' means ''us.''
No. ''you'' means you.
CLARK:
It's Lord BIackwood. sir. He. uh....
WeII...
...it appears he's come back
from the grave. sir.
-Most engaging.
-Very cIever.
I pronounced the man dead myseIf.
What are the facts?
Groundskeeper saw him waIking
through the graveyard this morning.
I'II Ieave this in your capabIe hands.
-I have an appointment with Mary.
-It's not my reputation that's at stake here.
Don't try that.
-The newspapers got wind of it?
-That's what we're trying to avoid.
CertainIy.
What's the major concern?
Panic. Dheer bIoody panic. sir.
-Indeed.
-You're not taking this seriousIy. are you?
Yes. as you shouId.
It's a matter of professionaI integrity.
No girI wants to marry a doctor
who can't teII if a man's dead or not.
Who do you think won the match.
CIarkie?
-Dir?
-The rugby match.
Your boys have done a magnificent job
obIiterating any potentiaI evidence.
Yes. But at Ieast they never miss
an opportunity to miss an opportunity.
LEDTRADE:
You took your time. HoImes.
HOLMED:
''And on the third day''....
These sIabs are haIf a ton each
if they're a pound...
...and they're smashed open
from the inside.
Lestrade. what of the coffin?
-We are in the process of bringing it up.
-I see.
Hm. Right. At what stage of the process?
ContempIative?
Anyhow. where's our witness?
He's over there.
And apparentIy. he is cata--
Cat--
Catatonic. sir.
-He's not feeIing very weII.
-Yes.
If you Iot don't stop behaving Iike quivering
miIkmaids. you're on doubIe-time.
Now. you get down there
and you bring that coffin up now.
Good day. sir.
HeIIo.
It's aII right.
I'm a doctor.
The man's in shock.
He may need a few moments.
The witness stated that he saw
Lord BIackwood rise from the grave.
WeII?
-WeII?
-You pronounced him dead.
He had no puIse.
MAN:
Ready.
Down.
Good Lord.
That's not BIackwood.
WeII. now we have a firm grasp
of the obvious.
Time of death?
Diptera is...
...approximateIy...
...two thirds of an inch
which wouId put the time of death...
...at between 10 and 12 hours ago.
May I borrow your pen?
-AdIer's dwarf.
-Midget.
GROUNDDKEEPER:
I know what I saw.
It was BIackwood.
As cIear as I see you.
And when the dead waIk...
...the Iiving wiII fiII these coffins.
WeII. um....
[CLEARD THROAT]
LEDTRADE: Right.
Put the Iid on and cIean this Iot up.
WATDON:
You reaIIy beIieve he was resurrected?
HOLMED:
The question is not if. but how.
-The game's afoot.
WATDON: FoIIow your spirit--
HOLMED & WATDON:
And upon this charge. cry:
''God for Harry. EngIand and Dt. George.''
There you are.
Why that certain chips staII.
I don't understand.
There's a particuIar beer in their batter.
A northern stout. to be exact.
WATDON: You know. HoImes.
I've seen things in war I don't understand.
I once met a man
who predicted his own death...
...right down to the number
and the pIacement...
...of the buIIets that kiIIed him.
You have to admit. HoImes...
...that a supernaturaI expIanation
to this case...
...is theoreticaIIy possibIe.
WeII. agreed. but it's a huge mistake
to theorize before one has data.
InevitabIy one begins to twist facts
to suit theories...
...instead of theories to suit facts.
That said. I beIieve AdIer's midget
is the key to this.
WATDON:
Hm.
HOLMED: Right. Dcratches around
the keyhoIe where the watch was wound.
-What does that teII you?
-The man was IikeIy a drunk.
Every time he wound the watch
his hand wouId sIip. hence the scratches.
Very good. Watson.
You've deveIoped considerabIe
deductive powers of your own. Hm.
Let's see now. there are severaI
sets of initiaIs scored--
-Pawnbrokers' marks.
-ExceIIent.
Most recent of which are ''M.H.''
M.H. M.H. is for?
-Maddison and Haig.
They shouId be abIe to
give us an address.
What a coincidence.
There's one thing you've
faiIed to deduce from the watch.
HOLMED:
ReaIIy? I think not.
WATDON:
The time. I have to get back. HoImes.
Taking tea with the in-Iaws.
-Reckon your future. sir?
-AbsoIuteIy not.
WATDON: No. thank you.
-You need to hear what I have to teII.
We have no need of your Iucky heather.
gypsy woman.
Even if it's to do with Mary?
Oh. Oh.
I see two men. Brothers.
Not in bIood. but in bond.
What of Mary?
M for Mary. for marriage.
Oh. you wiII be married.
Go on.
I see patterned tabIecIoths...
...and. oh. china figurines...
...and. oh. Iace doiIies.
DoiIies.
Lace doiIies? HoImes.
Does your depravity know no bounds?
-No.
-Oh. she turns to fat...
...and. oh. she has a beard and....
-What of the warts?
-Dhe's covered in warts.
-Enough.
-Are they extensive?
PIease. enough.
It's the most apt prediction
FIora has made in years.
And preciseIy the reason
you can't find a suitabIe ring.
Do you have my money?
You are terrified of a Iife
without the thriII of the macabre.
-Do you have my cut from the fight?
-Admit it.
-Give me my money! HoImes.
-Admit it!
HOLMED:
I see.
Thank you.
HOLMED: WeII. you've got your ring and
I've got my address for the ginger midget.
-DhouId be just there.
-I think she'II reaIIy Iike this.
And I have some change in my pocket.
-DhaII I Iook after it for you?
-No. no.
-Don't give it away here.
-No.
I have to go see Mary.
Give her my best.
And her famiIy. as weII.
It does make a considerabIe
difference to me...
...having someone with me
on whom I can thoroughIy reIy.
WeII. you can reIy on me
for exactIy 10 minutes.
He cIearIy feIt something
was coming to get him.
HOLMED:
Domething did.
Irene AdIer was here.
Either that or the ginger midget
wore the same Parisian perfume.
[INHALED]
Ah. Putrefaction.
[DNIFFING]
Ammonium suIfate. among other aromas.
[FLIED BUZZING]
Phosphorous.
FormaIdehyde.
It Iooks Iike...
...he was attempting to combine...
...some kind of sorcery
and scientific formuIa.
HOLMED:
More importantIy...
...Iet's see what he was
trying to dispose of.
-Potassium. magnesium.
-DuItaphytic acid.
It'II suck the iron right out of the ink
as Iong as it's not too burnt.
PecuIiar.
Hydrated rhododendron.
[DNIFFD]
-HoImes.
-Hm?
Look at the crest.
Reordan was working with BIackwood.
Of course he was.
The question is. to what end.
Whatever he was working on.
he cIearIy succeeded.
How so?
Otherwise. he'd stiII be aIive.
Which is why Miss AdIer
is so desperate to find him.
HOLMED:
Yes.
There is one odor
I can't quite put my finger on.
-Mm?
-Is it candy fIoss? MoIasses?
MapIe syrup?
BarIey sugar.
Toffee appIe.
Let me guess.
Judging by your arsonist tooI kit...
...you're here to burn down the buiIding
and extinguish aII evidence therein.
Just one minute. boys.
Oh. Dredger.
[HEAVY FOOTDTEPD APPROACHING]
[DPEAKD IN FRENCH]
Meat...
...or potatoes?
My 10 minutes are up.
[GRUNTING]
[IN FRENCH]
WATDON:
You aII right?
[BUZZING]
[GROANING]
HoImes...
...what is that?
DREDGER:
[GRUNTD]
[GRUNTING]
[THUDD]
HOLMED:
WATDON:
HoImes!
[IN ENGLIDH]
Watson...
...what have you done?
WATDON:
I haven't sIept aII night.
Not a wink.
Why I ever beIieved...
...that I wouId get to have tea
with Mary's parents is beyond me...
-...having been taIked into going with you.
-We were set upon. It was seIf-defense.
I've been reviewing my notes
on our expIoits over the Iast seven months.
WouId you Iike to know my concIusion?
-I am psychoIogicaIIy disturbed.
-How so?
Why eIse wouId I continuaIIy be
Ied into situations...
...where you deIiberateIy withhoId
your pIans from me? Why eIse?
You've never compIained
about my methods before.
-I'm not compIaining.
-What do you caII this?
How am I compIaining? I never compIain.
Do I compIain about you practicing
the vioIin in the morning...
...or your mess. your Iack of hygiene.
or the fact that you steaI my cIothes?
We have a barter system.
Do I compIain
about you setting fire to my rooms?
-Our rooms.
-The rooms.
When do I compIain
that you experiment on my dog?
-Our dog.
-On the dog.
GIadstone is our dog.
Where I do take issue is your campaign
to sabotage my reIationship with Mary.
I understand.
-Do you?
-I do.
-I don't think you do.
-You're overtired.
-Yes.
-You're feeIing sensitive.
I'm not sensitive.
What you need is a rest.
My brother. Mycroft.
has a smaII estate near Chichester.
BeautifuI grounds. There's a foIIy.
We can throw a Iamb on the spit.
We? HoImes. if I were to go to the country.
it wouId be with my future wife.
-WeII. certainIy. if we must--
-No. not you. Mary and I.
-You are not--
-What. invited?
Why wouId I not be invited
to my brother's country home?
Now you're not making any sense.
You're not human.
MAN:
John Watson?
Yes.
Your baiI's been posted.
WATDON:
Mary.
Just Watson.
I hope you get baiI by breakfast.
because the boys are getting hungry.
[CHATTERING]
LEDTRADE:
Dtep IiveIy.
Back off. Back off.
To which the barman says.
''May I push in your stooI?''
[MEN LAUGHING]
Right. you. you're out.
UntiI next time. Big Joe.
AIways a pIeasure. Mr. HoImes.
Thank heaven you're here.
I'd aImost run out of jokes.
In another Iife.
you'd have made an exceIIent criminaI.
And you. sir. an exceIIent poIiceman.
Tomski. thank you.
Now. pIease teII me you have answers.
AII in good time. Lestrade.
''AII in good time''? Is this some parIor game
where we guess what you're thinking?
I've got a pubIic in frenzy out there.
If you don't fiII me in...
...I'II have you in there pIaying Victoria
and AIbert quicker than a bookie's runner.
Now. cIean up
and make yourseIf presentabIe.
For whom?
Friends in high pIaces.
They're the ones who baiIed you out.
[BLOWING NODE]
I'm terribIy sorry
to inconvenience you. sir...
...but I'm gonna have to put this on you.
Mr. HoImes.
apoIogies for summoning you Iike this.
I'm sure it's quite a mystery
as to where you are and who I am.
As to where I am...
...l was, admittedly, lost for a moment
between Charing Cross and Holborn.
But I was saved by the bread shop
on Daffron HiII...
...the only baker to use a certain
French glaze on their loaves...
...a Brittany sage.
The carriage forked Ieft. then right.
a teIItaIe bump over the FIeet Conduit.
And as to who you are. that took every
ounce of my not inconsiderabIe experience.
The Ietters on your desk are addressed
to Dir Thomas Rotheram.
Lord Chief Justice.
that'd be your officiaI titIe.
Who you reaIIy are is. of course.
another matter entireIy.
Judging by the sacred ox on your ring...
...you're the head of
the TempIe of the Four Orders...
...in whose headquarters we now sit...
...on the northwest corner
of Dt. James's Dquare. I think.
As to the mystery. the onIy mystery is
why you bothered to bIindfoId me at aII.
Yes. weII. standard procedure.
I suppose.
[DOOR OPEND]
I daresay we have the right man.
gentIemen.
DherIock HoImes.
Ambassador Dtandish from America...
...and Lord Coward. the home secretary.
I suppose you aIready have some notion
as to the practices of our order.
HOLMED:
Yes. Um....
They're practicaIIy interesting.
Be as skepticaI as you Iike.
But our secret systems have steered
the worId towards good for centuries.
The danger is they can aIso be used
for more nefarious purposes.
What some caII the dark arts.
or practicaI magic.
DTANDIDH: We know
you don't beIieve in magic. Mr. HoImes.
We don't expect you to share our faith...
...mereIy our fears.
Fear is the more infectious condition.
In this instance...
...fear of your own chiId.
BIackwood is your son.
You have the same irises.
a rare dark green...
...with diamond-shaped hazeI fIecks...
...together with identicaI outer ears. which
are onIy passed down through bIoodIine...
...which makes you either brothers...
...or. in this case. more IikeIy.
father and son.
Very few peopIe
are privy to that information...
...and we want to keep it that way.
He was conceived
during one of our rituaIs.
His mother wasn't my wife...
...but she shared our beIiefs.
Dhe was a powerfuI practitioner...
...though not enough
to survive giving birth to him.
Death foIIowed him wherever he went.
Those five girIs were not the first
to be butchered.
He kiIIed many more.
using them to enhance his powers.
No one couId prove anything.
of course. but we aII knew.
The boy was a curse.
We've done our best to stop him.
but it's not enough.
His power grows daiIy.
His resurrection is evidence of that.
But what he does next
wiII be more dangerous.
ROTHERAM: His secret Iies in the book
of speIIs. This is the source of his power.
He's gonna raise a force
that wiII aIter the course of worId.
We want you to find him
and stop him before he does.
COWARD: We'II give you any assistance
that we can.
As home secretary. I have considerabIe
infIuence over the poIice.
HOLMED:
Hm. yes.
COWARD:
Do...
...name your price.
The benefit of being
a consuIting detective...
...is that I can pick and choose
my cIients.
Do consider it done. I'II stop him.
But not for you.
And certainIy not for a price.
-I do have a parting query. Dir Thomas.
-What is that?
If the rest of his famiIy's dead.
how Iong do you expect to survive?
Food for thought.
WeII. perhaps you'II have better Iuck
opening that.
Margaux '58. A comet vintage.
How fascinating that an astronomicaI event
can affect the quaIity--
How is it going with our case
you refuse to take?
--of the wine.
Oh. I've hit a dead end. IiteraIIy.
I found your man.
He's buried in BIackwood's tomb.
If you stiII need him.
Oh. dear.
Hope my cIient
doesn't come Iooking for a refund.
He's a professor. isn't he?
Couldn't see his face,
but l spotted chalk on his lapel.
I've never known a professor to carry a gun.
and on such a cIever contraption.
Eye patch. nice touch.
Do case cIosed...
...which makes this a sociaI visit.
No. it's a ''you're in over your head.
Irene'' visit.
Whoever kiIIed Reordan
was covering their tracks...
...which makes you the next Ioose end
to be snipped.
[CORK POPD]
Let it breathe.
I've never been in over my head.
Leave now. Disappear.
You're good at that.
Or stay and voIunteer
for protective custody.
If I'm in danger. so are you.
Come with me.
What if we trusted each other?
Hm?
You're not Iistening.
I'm taking you to either the raiIway station
or the poIice station.
[DIGHD]
Do....
-Which is it to be?
-CarefuI.
You decide.
-Which wiII it be?
-What--?
I toId you to Iet it breathe.
Can you taste the comet?
Why couIdn't you just
come away with me?
Never.
[CAWD]
[MAN DPEAKING INDIDTINCTLY]
[GADPD]
[DCREAMD]
Madam. I need you to remain caIm
and trust me. I'm a professionaI.
But beneath this piIIow
Iies the key to my reIease.
-She misinterpreted my intention entirely.
CLARK: Naturally, sir.
That's why I find this modern
reIigious fervor so troubIing.
-No Iatitude for misunderstanding.
-Faith runs right over reason. sir.
Indeed. And chambermaids
were once such a IiberaI breed.
My wife's a chambermaid. sir.
Anyhow. a good thing she was offended.
or we may never have found you.
The inspector's been over to Baker Dtreet
himseIf this morning. sir.
-Just joking about the wife. sir.
-Oh.
CLARK:
We've checked everything. sir.
No sign of a break-in
and the butIer didn't hear a thing.
Do body in the bathtub...
...his eyes were wide open.
and the onIy thing missing was...
...his ring. sir.
Why did you drain the water?
-Out of common decency.
-Crime is common. Iogic is rare.
The decent thing to do is to catch the kiIIer.
not provide comfort for the corpse.
What is that?
[DNIFFD]
-Jasmine bath saIts. sir.
-Duperb.
ProbabIy comes from a Iarger container.
It'II either be in the pantry...
...high up where it's warm and dry.
or in a Iinen cupboard with a vent.
ConstabIe. you couId do worse...
...than to check the ground under
the rear windows for any footprints.
Data. data. data.
I cannot make bricks without cIay.
[DOOR OPEND AND CLODED]
CLARK:
Mr. HoImes?
[HUMMING]
Was it in the cupboard or the pantry?
It was in the pantry. sir.
I don't know what to make of this.
ExceIIent work.
Adieu.
[BELL TOLLING]
What's the meaning of this. Coward?
Why have you caIIed this meeting?
Dir Thomas is dead.
I nominate Lord BIackwood
as head of the order.
[CHUCKLED]
Have you Iost your mind?
You know damn weII
what he's capabIe of.
BLACKWOOD:
Of course he does.
That's why we're here.
That's why we're aII here.
My powers and my assets
were given to me for one purpose.
A magnificent but simpIe purpose.
To create a new future.
A future ruIed...
...by us.
Tomorrow at noon. we take the first step
towards a new chapter in our history.
Magic wiII Iead the way.
Once the peopIe of EngIand
see our newfound power...
...they'II bow down in fear.
Across the AtIantic
Iies a coIony that was once ours.
It wiII be again.
The CiviI War has made them weak.
Their government is as corrupt
and as ineffective as ours...
...so we'II take it back.
We wiII remake the worId...
...create the future.
These men are with me. Dtandish...
...but...
...are you?
No. sir. I am not.
These powers that you're pIaying with...
...no man can controI.
WeII. gentIemen...
...someone has to stop him.
even if you won't.
Oh. I wouIdn't do that if I were you.
[YELLING]
DTANDIDH:
Dave me!
GentIemen...
...don't be afraid.
As you can see...
...we are protected.
Come. drink your aIIegiance here.
You controI the poIice. now use them.
Didn't know you were here.
Dince this room is no Ionger yours.
do you mind if I utiIize it?
Be my guest.
-In here. chaps.
MAN: Where wouId you Iike me...
-...to put him. sir?
-Anywhere is fine.
WATDON: Who is he?
-The man who tried to kiII you at Reordan's.
His neck didn't survive the impact
of Dredger Ianding on him.
Yes.
Thanks for that. by the way.
There is consoIation in the knowIedge that
he couId be of service to his feIIow man.
EIbows and arms stained with bIood.
but it's oIder than his own injuries.
None of it human.
He's not a butcher. Iet me see.
YeIIow fIame. green bursts.
An industriaI worker.
[DNIFFING]
Pff. CoaI.
River siIt.
The sIag on his trousers
shouId put him squareIy in....
-Nine EIms.
-Dorry. what?
The area you're Iooking for is Nine EIms.
I wondered.
Do you remember where I put
the Lords Register of members' interests?
It's on the stepIadder.
WeII. BIackwood's had his hand in just about
everything that's corrosive to the spirit.
WooIwich ArsenaI.
Limehouse ChemicaI Works.
It'II probabIy be a factory by the river.
What's that?
Never mind.
You don't know where
my rugby baII went. do you?
No. not a cIue.
Queenshithe DIaughterhouse.
Nine EIms.
A factory by the river.
WeII done. That shouId Iead us
to BIackwood. dead or aIive.
Not us.
You.
Yes.
Just a figure of speech. oId boy.
He's Ieft it there on purpose.
[GRUNTD]
[GROAND]
[MEN LAUGHING]
More coaI. doctor.
That's a good one. He's such a tit.
Oh. God. Yeah.
WATDON: GIad to see you two
are working hard.
And I thought we were
trying to be discreet.
You wouId not Iast one day in the navy.
Are you sure there isn't an aIternative
means of water transportation than that?
I guarantee you nobody knows
London's waterways better.
-Tanner's practicaIIy a fish himseIf.
-He certainIy drinks Iike one.
Oh. you found a sense of humor. doctor.
If onIy just a sense.
I better take over. there.
Bit tricky down here.
Come on. come on.
WATDON: Look famiIiar?
HOLMED: Yep.
AII that's missing is a ginger midget.
They cIeared something away from here
not minutes ago.
Like what?
Not sure. Domething mechanicaI.
HoImes.
Look at this.
-1 :18.
-Chapter and verse.
ReveIations 1 :18.
''I am he that Iiveth. and was dead.''
BLACKWOOD:
''And behoId. I'm aIive for evermore.''
I warned you. HoImes. to accept
that this was beyond your controI...
...beyond what your rationaI mind
couId comprehend.
-What a busy afterIife you're having.
BLACKWOOD: I want you to bear witness.
Tomorrow. at midday.
the worId as you know it wiII end.
Dhow me your face.
it'II be the end of your worId.
Dave your buIIets. Watson.
A gift for you.
[GUN CLICKING EMPTY]
What was that about saving buIIets?
[GRUNTING]
BLACKWOOD:
Dhe foIIowed you here. HoImes.
You Ied your Iamb to sIaughter.
HoImes.
This game was designed to hurt.
Watson!
It's warm in here. Watson.
In over your head yet. darIing?
WATDON: HoId on there.
ADLER: I can't.
Let me take your weight.
HOLMED:
Give us a Ieg up. oId boy.
[GROAND]
These German Iocks
aIways give me troubIe.
[METAL CREAKING]
It's a band saw.
No matter. we have pIenty of time.
HoImes.
-It's not working.
-Keep caIm.
HoImes. hurry up.
Don't get excited. Turn off that vaIve.
And we'II bounce in three. two...
...one.
Thank you.
I'm gonna get after BIackwood.
We shouId heIp the doctor.
HoImes!
CLARK [IN DLOW MOTION]:
Mr. HoImes.
Dir.
Mr. HoImes. we have an order
for your arrest. sir.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Dir!
Lord Coward has issued a warrant
for your arrest. sir.
Now. Watson's aIive.
Just get out of here. sir. Go. sir. go.
[WHIDTLE BLOWD]
WiII the train be departing on time?
The train's been deIayed. madam.
DhouIdn't be Iong now. though.
MAN:
The train wiII depart when I teII it to.
And you wiII Ieave my empIoyment
when I aIIow you to.
I fuIfiIIed my contract.
I found Reordan.
He's in DcotIand Yard's mortuary.
Do that's me. finished.
MAN: Your job was to manipuIate HoImes'
feeIings for you...
...not succumb to them.
You have fuIfiIIed nothing.
I want what Reordan was making
for BIackwood.
Finish the job or the next dead body...
...wiII be DherIock HoImes.
DOCTOR:
The surgeon shouId be aIong shortIy.
He shouId be abIe to rest now.
Excuse me.
Is that the best you can do?
Yes. for now.
I must attend to my other patients.
MARY:
Doctor.
PIease.
I know that you care for him
as much as I do.
This is not your responsibiIity.
it was his choice.
He'd say that it was worth the wounds.
[DPEAKD INDIDTINCTLY]
DoIve this.
Whatever it takes.
[VOICED CHATTERING]
BLACKWOOD:
This is beyond your control.
CLARK:
Sheer bloody panic, sir. Panic.
-lt's Lord Blackwood, sir.
ADLER: l've never been in over my head.
WATDON: lt's nothing to do with me,
but l advise you leave the case alone.
MARY: Solve this.
WATDON: Are you, Holmes?
BLACKWOOD:
Accept that this was beyond your control.
-Tomorrow, at midday, the world will end.
LEDTRADE: l've got a public in frenzy.
WATDON:
Holmes!
BLACKWOOD:
Widen your gaze.
You must widen your gaze.
You and l are bound together on a journey
that will twist the very fabric of nature.
Steel your mind, Holmes.
Widen your gaze.
ROTHERAM: He's gonna raise a force
that will alter the world.
COWARD: His power grows daily.
ROTHERAM: This is the source of his power.
BLACKWOOD:
l need you.
ROTHERAM:
His secret lies in the book of spells.
BLACKWOOD:
Three more will die...
...and there is nothing you can do
to save them.
DTANDIDH:
We know you don't believe in magic.
WATDON:
Reordan was working with BIackwood.
ADLER:
Is that better?
WATDON: He clearly felt something
was coming to get him.
His eyes were wide open
and the onIy thing missing was his ring.
BLACKWOOD:
Give up, Holmes.
This is a riddle you cannot solve.
ADLER:
Good morning.
Now. you need to work.
FamiIiar artwork.
You Iook gorgeous.
HOLMED:
Domehow I knew you wouIdn't Ieave.
You made the front page.
OnIy a name and no picture.
Do it Iooks Iike you'II be needing to
work outside the Iaw now...
...and that's my area of expertise.
I feeI safer aIready.
You seem to be making a rapid recovery.
Yes.
Took the shrapneI out myseIf.
Mary said I had a Iousy doctor.
WeII. I'm....
I'm just so...
...very gIad that you're...
...weII...
...with us.
[BOTH CLEAR THROATD]
Now that you're sitting comfortabIy.
I shaII begin.
My initiaI approach was far too narrow.
When BIackwood invited me
to PentonviIIe Prison...
...he suggested I widen my gaze
and. at minimum. I have done just that.
In fact. I may weII have reconciIed
thousands of years of theoIogicaI disparity.
But that's for another time.
BIackwood's method is based on
a rituaIistic mysticaI system...
...that's been empIoyed by the
TempIe of the Four Orders for centuries.
To fuIIy understand the system.
to get inside it...
...I reenacted the ceremony
we interrupted at the crypt...
...with a few enhancements of my own.
My journey took me somewhat further down
the rabbit hoIe than I had intended...
...and though I dirtied my fIuffy white taiI.
I have emerged enIightened.
The fraternity who siIentIy controI
the empire...
...share the beIief with the kings.
pharaohs and emperors of oId...
...that the sphinx was a door
to another dimension...
...a gateway to immeasurabIe power.
It's made up of four parts:
the foot of a Iion. the taiI of an ox...
...the wings of an eagIe.
and the head of a man.
ln Sir Thomas's secret chamber,
l found the bone of an ox...
...the tooth of a lion, the feather of an eagle
and hair of a man.
Map.
The points of the star
represent the five murdered girIs...
...but the cross
is what we're now interested in.
It's a wideIy heId beIief...
...that within the architecture
of the great cities...
...are coded references to this system.
Dince he rose from the grave.
BIackwood has kiIIed three men...
...each committed at a Iocation
that has a connection with the tempIe...
...therefore the system.
Reordan, the ginger midget,
represents man.
We found his body here.
Dir Thomas. master of the tempIe.
wore the ox ring.
He died here.
Dtandish. ambassador to America...
...where the eagIe has been
the nationaI embIem for over 100 years.
The headquarters of the TempIe
of the Four Orders where he died...
...is here.
CorrespondingIy. the map wiII teII us
the Iocation of BIackwood's finaI act.
Do we have man. the ox. eagIe.
OnIy the Iion remaining.
Right here.
ParIiament.
Right.
You four stay here
and the rest of you come with me.
LEDTRADE: Get out of the way. you IowIifes!
-Right this way.
Ladies first.
LEDTRADE:
Now.
HOLMED:
FoIIow these instructions.
-Aren't you--?
HOLMED: Go.
HeIIo. heIIo. heIIo.
Did the deviI turn up?
WeII...
...never mind.
You got the next best thing.
Beg your pardon. my Lord.
I know that it's unorthodox...
...but Mr. HoImes here...
...he's been making some
serious accusations about you...
...and the order.
I see.
WeII. at Ieast that soIves the great mystery
as to how you became inspector.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[HOLMED COUGHD]
Excuse me. my Lord...
...but I've been wanting to do that
for a Iong time.
WeII. inspector. I have five minutes
before my next engagement...
...so why don't you regaIe me
with your stories of conspiracy?
Thank you. Lestrade.
My Lord.
I'm curious. Coward. Did you assist
BIackwood in aII the murders...
...or just the one I prevented?
Very distinctive.
those handmade shoes of yours.
But the price of quaIity
is often the unique imprint they Ieave.
NonetheIess. I confess to being
compIeteIy outmatched.
I couId deduce very IittIe
from my investigation.
FortunateIy.
there's nothing more stimuIating...
...than a case where everything
goes against you.
How many members of ParIiament
do you intend to murder at noon today?
Man. ox. eagIe. Iion.
The Iion is ParIiament. isn't it?
Very cIever.
But it's not murder. Mr. HoImes.
It's mercy.
We are giving the weak masses
a strong shepherd.
Don't you see that it's for their own...?
HOLMED:
No. but I don't care much what you think.
I simpIy wanted to know the Iocation
of BIackwood's ceremony...
...and you've given it to me.
I've toId you nothing.
HOLMED: But your cIothes say
infiniteIy more than you couId ever hope.
The mud on your boots
from where you've been walking.
A touch of red brick dust on your knee
from where you've been kneeling.
A small bandage on your thumb
from where you've been vowing.
A faint aroma of excrement
from where you've been standing.
You and BIackwood Iaid the finaI touches
to your ceremony...
...in the sewers beneath ParIiament
Iess than an hour ago.
Both houses meet today.
The whoIe government wiII be present.
COWARD: It's a shame you made an enemy
out of BIackwood. HoImes.
You wouId have made a vaIuabIe aIIy.
How terribIe is wisdom...
...when it brings no profit to the wise.
We take power at noon.
There isn't any time to waste then.
is there?
TANNER: I toId you he'd be coming
out the top window.
There isn't any way
he'd be coming over that terrace.
TechnicaIIy. that isn't the top window.
is it. saiIor boy?
-What is it?
-WeII. it's the middIe window.
Anyway.
You'II be pIeased to know
Lestrade performed perfectIy.
In fact. I think he enjoyed it.
I hope you know what you're doing.
Here's the key.
-You got aII you needed from Coward?
-Yes. I smoked him out with reIative ease.
-Tanner?
-Dir?
If you wouId. captain...
...take us under the bridge.
port side. 100 yards.
Beyond that you'II find the tunneI
that Ieads us to the sewers.
Right away. sir.
[HORN BLOWD]
[CHATTERING]
The end is nigh.
BIackwood's come back from heII
and Iaid a curse upon this Iand.
He waIks in every shadow
and every puff of smoke.
BehoId. he cometh with cIouds...
...and every eye shaII see him...
...and every souI shaII waiI
because of him.
You cannot stop him!
No one can!
[WHIDPERING]
BehoId. BIackwood's magic reveaIed.
ADLER [WHIDPERING]: What does it do?
HOLMED: It's a chemicaI weapon.
The first of its kind.
You deduced that how?
From my pocket.
I snipped this off a rather recumbent rat
at the sIaughterhouse.
Note the bIue discoIoration.
the faint smeII of bitter aImonds.
-TeIItaIe traces of cyanide.
ADLER: Cyanide.
WATDON:
Dhh.
HOLMED: Now we know
what the ginger midget was working on.
It'II revoIutionize warfare.
[WHIDPERING]
Yes. kiIIing a Iot of peopIe.
Now. it's seven minutes to noon.
What are we gonna do?
Right. How many men
did you count on the--?
[GUNDHOTD]
Dhe Ioves an entrance. your muse.
HOLMED [IN NORMAL TONE]:
Woman!
Dhoot him. Now. pIease.
My Iords.
The time has come...
...for onIy those who beIieve to remain.
BehoId...
...Lord BIackwood.
[MURMURING]
You seem surprised.
I have returned from beyond the grave
to fuIfiII EngIand's destiny...
...and extend the boundaries
of this great empire.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
IN DIDTANCE]
Listen to the rabbIe outside.
Listen...
...to the fear.
I wiII use that as a weapon...
...to controI them...
...and then the worId.
I've never seen anything Iike it.
Look at this.
DpecificaIIy designed
to prevent us from disarming it.
These appear to be designed
to receive a signaI of some sort.
EIectromagnetic waves?
HOLMED:
When triggered, the electrodes...
...will send a charge
converting the chemical into gas.
The gas will travel up that shaft
and filter through the ventilation system...
...that leads directly to Parliament.
Within seconds...
...the most powerful men in the world
will be choking on death.
BIackwood must have some transmitter
that he can activate remoteIy.
Three minutes. 10 seconds.
I wiII create an empire
that wiII endure for miIIennia...
...indestructibIe...
...and eternaI.
Move it. Move it.
We don't actuaIIy have to
disarm the device...
...we just have to remove the cyIinders.
Yes. except that they're weIded in.
What we need is a controIIed expIosion.
We'II need a container to direct the bIast.
My cIay pipe shouId service that ambition.
[GRUNTD]
[GUN CLICKING EMPTY]
[IN FRENCH]
I rather wish you hadn't done that.
Irene.
[BELL CHIMING]
On the 12th chime.
I wiII summon the dark powers.
AII those of you who are with me
shaII be protected.
AII others...
...wiII perish.
I need your pipe.
Nut him!
-Right.
-What?
-Coat.
-Got it.
The new order...
...begins now.
Woman.
What are you waiting for?
[POPD]
[GROAND]
That.
MAN:
Apprehend Lord Coward.
-Can you manage?
-Course I can.
ReIax...
...I'm a doctor.
[DCREAMD]
Did you take a wrong turning
somewhere?
We're safe now.
Interesting assessment.
Run off.
I won't be chasing you anymore.
Fare thee weII.
I don't want to run anymore.
-I'II teII you everything.
-I wish you wouId.
No!
There was never any magic.
OnIy conjuring tricks.
The simpIest invoIved
paying peopIe off...
...like the guard who pretended
to be possessed outside your cell.
Your reputation
and the inmates' fear did the rest.
Others required
more eIaborate preparations...
...Iike the sandstone sIab
that covered your tomb.
You had it broken before your buriaI.
then put back together using an adhesive.
An ancient Egyptian recipe. I beIieve...
...a mixture of egg and honey...
...designed to be washed away
by the rain.
HoImes!
Arranging for your father
to drown in his own bathtub...
...required more modern science.
Very cIever of Reordan
to find a paraIytic...
...that was activated by the combination
of copper and water...
...and was therefore undetectabIe
once the bath water was drained.
That might've been a chaIIenge for me...
...had he not aIso tested it
on some unfortunate amphibians.
The death of Dtandish
was a reaI mystery...
...untiI you used the same compound
to bIow up the wharf.
An odorless, tasteless flammable liquid...
...yet it burned
with an unusuaI pinkish hue.
Did Dtandish mistake it for rain
as he entered the tempIe?
AII it took was a spark.
A simpIe rigged buIIet in his gun.
lngenious.
Like aII great performers. you saved
your piece de resistance for the end:
A chemical weapon distilled from cyanide
and refined in the bellies of swine.
Had it worked...
...your foIIowers in ParIiament
wouId have watched unharmed...
...as their coIIeagues
were dying around them.
They didn't know
you'd given them the antidote.
lnstead,
they would've believed it was magic...
...and that you'd harnessed
the ultimate power.
And the worId wouId've foIIowed.
fear being the most powerfuI weapon of aII.
[CREAKING]
You'd better hope
that it's nothing more than superstition...
...as you performed
aII the rituaIs perfectIy.
The devil is due a soul, l'd say.
For God's sake. HoImes. cut me Ioose.
[METAL CREAKING]
HOLMED: First. the worId wiII see you
for what you are. A fraud.
Then you'II be hanged.
ProperIy. this time.
It's a Iong journey from here to the rope.
[YELLING]
[GRUNTD]
I've never woken up in handcuffs before.
I have.
Naked.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
ADLER:
Dtorm's coming.
HOLMED:
WeII. we've stiII got a moment.
Moriarty.
What?
That's his name.
And he is a professor.
Everyone has a weak spot...
...and he found mine.
Where was it. preciseIy?
-PIease don't underestimate him.
-Mm.
He's just as briIIiant as you are...
...and infiniteIy more devious.
We'II see about that.
You'II miss me. DherIock.
DadIy...
...yes.
WATDON:
Just keep it under your hat.
DRIVER: Afternoon. sir.
I put the notebooks in this one. sir.
WATDON: Thank you.
-What's in these. John?
DcribbIes.
-DcribbIes?
-Notes.
MARY: They're your adventures.
I'd Iike to read them.
[WATDON CHUCKLED]
Come on. what's wrong?
Do you think he's come to terms
with you Ieaving?
Mary. Iook at the ring he's given us.
Now. five minutes here
and we'II go home.
Our home.
Get up those stairs.
[KNOCKING]
Don't worry. dear.
Duicide is not in his repertoire.
He's far too fond of himseIf for that.
HoImes.
Oh. Good afternoon.
I was trying to deduce the manner
in which BIackwood survived his execution.
CIearing your good name. as it were.
But it had a surprisingIy
soporific effect...
...and I was carried off in the arms
of Morpheus Iike a caterpiIIar in a cocoon.
Good afternoon. dear.
WATDON:
Get on with it. HoImes.
CIeverIy conceaIed in the hangman's knot
was a hook.
Oh. dear. my Iegs have faIIen asIeep.
I shouId come down.
John. shouIdn't we heIp him down?
No. no. no.
I hate to cut him off midstream.
Carry on.
WeII. the executioner
attached it to a harness...
...allowing the weight to be
distributed around the waist...
...and the neck to remain intact.
My Lord. I can't feeI my cheeks.
Might we continue this at ground IeveI?
How did you manage it. HoImes?
I managed it with braces.
beIts and a coat hook.
PIease. my tongue is going.
I'II be of no use to you at aII.
-Worse things couId happen.
-John.
Yet none of this expIains
BIackwood's Iack of puIse.
HOLMED:
Right.
Now, the medical mystery.
We must restore your reputation, Watson.
There is a toxin refined from the nectar
of the rhododendron ponticum.
lt's infamous in the region of Turkey
bordering the Black Sea...
...for its abiIity to induce
an apparentIy mortaI paraIysis.
Enough to misIead a medicaI mind
even as weII-trained as your own.
-It's known as--
-What's wrong with GIadstone?
HOLMED:
--mad honey disease.
Oh. he's demonstrating
the very effect I've just described.
He doesn't mind.
Mary. don't worry. he's seen far worse.
CLARK:
Mr. HoImes?
Doctor. Miss Mary.
Dir. Inspector Lestrade asks that
you come with me right away.
-What is it is this time. CIarkie?
-It's one of our sergeants. sir.
He went missing
the day you stopped Lord BIackwood.
l'm afraid sewage workers
found his body just this morning, sir.
We beIieve the sergeant
was our first man on the scene.
Can I heIp you. officer?
Dhot in the head.
Was it a smaII caIiber buIIet?
Yes.
Were there powder burns
on his eyebrows?
Indeed. sir.
Point bIank range?
Moriarty.
Professor Moriarty.
MARY:
Oh. there's a good boy.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Where is BIackwood's device now?
Decret Dervice have it. sir.
They've taken over the case.
I'd wager there's a piece missing.
Do Moriarty was after
a piece of the machine...
...not the poison.
There's nothing more eIusive
than an obvious fact.
The wire-free invention
was the game all along.
And AdIer was just the diversion.
He knew l'd chase her,
leaving the machine accessible.
A technology of that kind
would be worth an untold fortune.
Imagine being abIe
to controI any device...
...simpIy by sending a command
via radio waves.
It's the future. Watson.
[KNOCKING]
I've Ioaded the Iast of your boxes. sir.
-WeII....
[GLADDTONE GROAND]
MARY: GIadstone.
-Dtop him before he gets to the front door.
HOLMED:
CIarkie.
Case reopened.
[ENGLIDH DDH]