(RETCHING)
Pull yourself
together, Teddy.
Pull yourself together.
(GROANS)
It's just water.
It's a lot of water.
A lot of...
(RETCHING)
Come on.
You okay, boss?
Yeah, I'm fine
, I just...
I just can't...
Can't stomach the water.
You're my new partner.
That's right.
Not the best way to meet,
with my head halfway
down the toilet.
Doesn't exactly square
with "Teddy Daniels,
the man, the legend,"
I'll give you that.
?
The legend
What the hell
you boys smoking
over there
in Portland, anyway?
Seattle. I came from
the office in Seattle.
How long you been
with the Marshals?
Four years.
So you know
how small it is.
Sure.
What about you?
You got a girl? Married?
I was.
(INAUDIBLE)
(WAVES ROARING)
She died.
Jesus. I don't...
Don't worry about it.
There was a fire
at the apartment building
while I was at work.
Four people died.
It was the smoke
that got her,
not the fire.
See, that's important.
I'm sorry, boss.
?
Where are my
goddamn cigarettes
Oh, here,
have one of mine.
I could've sworn
they were in my jacket
before I got on.
Government employees
will rob you blind.
Thanks.
They give you a briefing
about the institution
before you left?
All I know is it's
a mental hospital.
For the criminally insane.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, if it's just
folks running around
hearing voices
and chasing
after butterflies,
they wouldn't need us.
Is that where
we're headed?
Yep.
The other side
of the island
is rock bluffs
all the way down
to the edge
of the water.
The dock,
it's the only way
on or off.
We'll be casting off
as soon as you two
are ashore.
I'd appreciate it if
you'd hurry up about it.
Why?
Storm's coming.
Never seen
a Marshals badge before.
I'm Deputy Warden McPherson,
gentlemen.
Welcome to Shutter Island.
I'll be the one taking you
up to Ashecliffe.
Your boys seem
a little on edge,
Mr. McPherson.
Right now, Marshal,
we all are.
Electrified perimeter.
How can you tell?
I've seen somethin
g like it before.
All right.
You gentlemen will be
accorded all the help
we can give,
.
but during your stay,
you will obey protocol
Is that understood?
Absolutely.
The red brick building
on your right is Ward A,
the male ward.
Ward B, the female ward,
is the one on your left.
Ward C is that building
on the bluffs.
An old Civil War fort.
The most dangerous patient
s are housed there.
Admittance to
Ward C is forbidden
without the written consent
and physical presence
of both myself
and Dr. Cawley.
Is that understood?
You act like
insanity is catching.
.
You are hereby required
to surrender your firearms
Mr. McPherson,
we are duly appointed
federal marshals.
We are required to
carry our firearms
with us at all times.
Executive order 319
of the Federal Code
of Penitentiaries
states that when
inside a penitentiary,
the officers of
that institution
have final authority.
Gentlemen, you will not
get through this gate
with your firearms.
Okay. Now that
the official stuff's done,
come on, boys,
what do you say
we go find Dr. Cawley?
When did she escape?
This prisoner?
I'm afraid Dr. Cawley
will have to fill you in
on the situation.
Protocol.
Correctional officers
at a mental institution,
that's a weird sight,
if you don't
mind me saying.
McPHERSON:
It's the only facility
of its kind in the U.S.,
even the world.
We take only
the most dangerous,
damaged patients,
ones no other
hospital can manage.
And it's all
due to Dr. Cawley.
He's created something
really unique here.
It's a hospital for
people our society
normally considers
beyond treatment.
Top of his class
at Johns Hopkins,
then Harvard...
(BUZZER RINGS)
IDs, gentlemen.
Show your badges, gentlemen.
Dr. Cawley's been consulted
numerous times by Scotland Yard,
MI5, the OSS...
Why?
What do you mean?
What do intelligence agencies
want to consult
a psychiatrist about?
I guess you'll have to ask him.
(BUZZER RINGS)
Marshal Daniels.
.
Doctor
Marshal Aule.
Thank you, Deputy Warden.
That will be all.
Yes, sir.
Pleasure, gentlemen.
He had a lot to say about you.
McPherson's a good man.
He believes in
the work we do here.
And what would
that be, exactly?
A moral fusion
between law and order
and clinical care.
CHUCK: Pardon me, Doc.
A what between
what and what?
Those paintings
are quite accurate.
Used to be the kind of patients
we deal with here
were shackled and left
in their own filth.
They were beaten,
as if whipping them bloody
would drive the psychosis out.
We drove screws into their brains,
we submerged them
in icy water until
they lost consciousness.
or even drowned.
And now?
We treat them.
Try to heal,
try to cure.
And if that fails,
at least we provide them
with a measure of comfort
in their lives. Calm.
These are all violent offenders,
right?
I mean, they've hurt people.
Murdered them in some cases.
In almost all cases, yes.
Then, personally, Doctor,
I'd have to say,
screw their sense of calm.
It's my job to treat my patients,
not their victims.
I'm not here to judge.
So this female prisoner...
Patient.
Excuse me. Patient,
one Rachel Solando, escaped
sometime in the last 24 hours.
.
Last night between
10:00 and midnight
Is she considered dangerous?
You could say that.
She killed all three
of her children.
She drowned them
in the lake behind her house.
She took them out
one by one,
held their heads
under till they died,
then she brought
them back inside
and arranged them
around the kitchen table.
She ate a meal there before
a neighbor dropped by.
And what about
the husband?
He died on the beaches of
Normandy. She's a war widow.
She starved herself
when she first came here.
She insisted
the children weren't dead.
(DISTORTED CHATTER)
Sorry, Doctor.
You don't happen to have
an aspirin, do you?
Prone to headaches,
Marshal?
Sometimes. But today,
I'm a little more
prone to seasickness.
Ah, dehydration.
You all right, boss?
Yeah.
In that case,
you're quite right.
The simpler the better.
Thanks so much.
Rachel still believes
the children are alive.
She also believes
this place is her home
in the Berkshires.
(CHUCKLES)
You're kidding me.
She's never once
in two years
acknowledged that
she's in an institution.
She believes
we're all deliverymen,
milkmen, postal workers.
To sustain the delusion
that her children never died,
she's created an elaborate
fictional structure,
and she gives us all
parts to play in that fiction.
So have you searched
the grounds yet?
The warden and his men
scoured the island.
Not a trace.
And what's more
disturbing is
we don't know how she got out
of her room.
It was locked from the outside,
and the only window is barred.
It's as if she evaporated
straight through the walls.
I brought her right back
here after group therapy,
locked her in,
came back for midnight rounds,
she was gone.
Seriously, Doctor,
how is it possible
that the truth never
gets through to her?
I mean, she's in a mental
institution, right?
Seems like something you'd notice
from time to time.
How many pairs of shoes are
the patients given?
Two pairs.
Sanity's not a choice, Marshal.
You can't just choose
to get over it.
So, she left here barefoot?
Come on, Doc, she couldn't get
10 yards in that terrain.
CAWLEY: Marshal?
This is definitely
Rachel's handwriting.
I have no idea what the law of
four is, though.
It's not a psychiatric term?
I'm afraid not.
"Who is 67?"
.
Fuck if I know
I have to say
that's quite close to
my clinical conclusion
Think it's just random scribblings?
Oh, no, not at all.
Rachel's smart. Brilliant, in fact.
This paper could be important.
Excuse me, Doctor,
but we're gonna have
to hold on to this.
Of course.
CHUCK: And you say
she had to come
through here?
.
After lights out, the orderlies
play cards in here
Last night,
there were seven men
sitting at the base of those stairs
playing stud poker.
Yet somehow, Rachel managed
to slip past them.
(ANGUISHED) Why?
How? She turns invisible?
Doctor,
we're gonna need access
to the personnel files
of all the medical staff.
The nurses,
the guards, the orderlies,
anyone who was working then.
We'll take your request under consideration.
(CHUCKLES)
This is not a request, Doctor.
This is a federal facility,
and a dangerous prisoner...
Patient.
...patient
has escaped.
Now, you will comply or...
.
All I can say is
I'll see what I can do
Doctor, we're gonna need to speak
with the staff.
Do you understand?
I'll assemble them in the common room
after dinner.
If you have any further questions,
feel free to join the deputy warden
in the search.
McPHERSON: It's 11 miles
to the nearest land
and the water's freezing.
Current was strong last night,
tide pushing in.
She'd have drowned
or been crushed on the rocks,
and her body would have
washed back up on shore.
TEDDY: What about
those caves down there?
Have you checked them?
No way she could get there.
The bases of those cliffs
are covered in poison ivy,
live oak, sumac,
a thousand plants with thorns as big
as my dick.
You said yourself, Marshal, she's got no shoes.
All right, let's check
the other side.
What's that tower?
.
It's an old lighthouse
The guards already
searched inside it
What's in there?
More patients?
Sewage treatment facility.
It's getting dark soon . I'm calling this off
for tonight.
Let's go, boys!
TEDDY: You were on watch
on the landing, huh?
Yeah. Couldn't nobody
get in or out
of their room on that corridor
without me seeing.
Okay, Rachel Solando,
who else does she have to pass
to get down here?
Me. Glen Miga.
Sir, I didn't see nothing.
And you were at your post all night?
Yeah, but I didn't see a thing.
Glen.
(INSISTENTLY) Glen.
Tell me the truth.
I...
I maybe went to the bathroom.
What? You breached protocol.
Christ...
I wasn't gone more than a minute.
All right, look. Let's back up here.
Let's all just back up
Miss Solando was put in her room
for lights out.
Does anyone here know
what she did before that?
Anyone?
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
Come on, anyone, anyone,
anyone, anyone.
She was in a group therapy session.
Huh.
Anything unusual occur?
Define "unusual."
Excuse me?
This is a mental institution, Marshal,
for the criminally insane.
Usual isn't a big part of our day.
(STAFF CHUCKLING)
I will rephrase.
Did anything happen last night
during group therapy
that was more,
let's say, I don't know,
memorable than...
Normal?
Exactly.
No. Sorry.
Did Miss Solando say anything
during group therapy?
She was worried about the rain.
And she hated the food here.
(STAFF LAUGHING)
Complained constantly,
last night included.
So you were there. Was there a
doctor present?
Yes, Dr. Sheehan led the discussion.
Dr. Sheehan?
Yes, he was running the session.
He's Rachel's primary,
the psychiatrist who directly
oversees her care.
Huh.
We're gonna need
to speak with Dr. Sheehan.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
He left on the ferry this morning.
His vacation was already planned.
He'd been putting it off too long.
You're in a state of lockdown,
a dangerous patient has escaped,
and you let her primary doctor
leave on vacation?
Well, of course. He's a doctor.
(STAFF LAUGHING)
Do you have the phone number
for where he's gone?
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Anybody there?
I'm sorry, sir, but it's all down.
All the lines.
The storm's hitting the mainland
like a hammer.
If you get it working,
come find me immediately.
The marshals need to make
an important call.
Yes, sir.
Hello? Hello?
CAWLEY: I'm afraid
I have evening rounds
in the wards,
but I'll be having drinks and a cigar
at my house around 9:00,
if you'd care to drop by.
Good.
We can talk then, right?
We have been talking, Marshal.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHISTLES)
Gotta say, I'm thinking I got in the wrong
line of public service.
It is a little overwhelming.
It was constructed during
the Civil War,
the same time as the military fort
housing Ward C.
This is the original
commander's quarters.
When Uncle Sam got the bill,
the commander was court-martialed.
I can see why.
Nice music.
Who is that? Brahms?
No.
It's Mahler.
NAEHRING:
Quite right, Marshal.
CAWLEY: Forgive me, gentlemen.
My colleague,
Dr. Jeremiah Naehring.
Quartet for Piano and Strings
in A minor.
Your poison, gentlemen?
Rye, if you got it.
Soda and ice, please.
Thanks.
Oh? You don't indulge in alcohol?
I'm surprised.
Isn't it common for men in your profession
to imbibe?
Common enough.
And yours?
I'm sorry?
Your profession, Doctor.
Psychiatry.
Yes.
I always heard it was overrun with
boozers and drunks
(CHUCKLES)
Not that I've noticed.
What's that? Iced tea in
your glass, there?
(DOCTORS LAUGHING)
Excellent, Marshal. You have outstanding
defense mechanisms.
You must be quite adept
at interrogations, hmm?
Men like you are
my specialty, you know?
Men of violence.
Now that's a hell of an assumption
to make.
No assumption. No, not at all.
You misunderstand me.
I said you are men of violence.
I'm not accusing you of being violent men.
That's quite different.
No, please. Please
. Edify us, Doctor.
You both
served overseas, huh?
It's not much of a stretch, Doc.
For all you know, we were both paper
pushers over there.
No, you were not.
Since the schoolyard,
neither of you has ever walked away
from a physical conflict.
No, no,
not because you enjoy it,
but because retreat isn't something
you consider an option.
We weren't raised to run, Doc.
Ah! Yes. "Raised."
And who raised you, Marshal?
Me?
Wolves. Ah!
(DOCTORS LAUGHING)
Very impressive defense mechanisms.
NAEHRING: Do you
believe in God, Marshal?
(CHUCKLES)
No, I'm quite serious.
(MUTTERS IN GERMAN)
You ever seen a death camp, Doctor?
(REPEATS IN GERMAN)
Huh?
(CONTINUES IN GERMAN)
His English really is very good.
You hit the consonants
a tad hard, though.
You're a German?
Is legal immigration a crime, Marshal?
Oh, I don't know, Doctor.
You tell us.
Now, listen.
We're gonna need
those files on Sheehan
and the rest of the staff as well.
No personnel files will be
released to you. Period.
(FIRMLY) We're gonna
need those files.
Out of the question.
Bullshit, out of the question!
Bullshit!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Just who the hell's in charge here,
anyway, huh?
Dr. Naehring acts as liaison to our
Board of Overseers.
He relayed your request,
and it's been refused.
Refused? They don't have the authority
to refuse,
and neither do you, sir.
Marshal, continue your investigation
and we'll do all we can to help.
.
This investigation is over
We're gonna file our reports
and we're gonna hand it over to...
CHUCK: Hoover's boys.
Hoover's boys.
That's right.
We'll be taking the ferry back
in the morning
.
Come on, Chuck
McPHERSON: Nice night.
.
You'll be bunking
in the orderlies' quarters
Hey, boss.
We really packing it in?
Why?
I guess... I don't know,
I just never really quit anything before.
We haven't heard the truth
once yet, Chuck.
Listen, Rachel Solando didn't slip out
of a locked cell, barefoot,
without any help.
I think she had a lot of help.
Maybe Cawley's sitting up
in his mansion right now
rethinking his whole attitude.
Maybe, in the morning,
we'll be...
You're bluffing?
I didn't say that.
(EARLY 1950s
ROCK 'N' ROLL PLAYING)
I found a whole stack of these, Teddy.
Jesus, are you ever sober anymore?
I killed a lot of people in the war.
Is that why you drink?
Are you real?
No.
She's still here.
Who?
Rachel?
She never left.
Remember when we stayed in the cabin
in the summer, Teddy?
We were so happy.
She's here.
You can't leave.
I'm not gonna leave.
I love you so much.
I'm just bones in a box, Teddy.
No.
I am.
You have to wake up.
I won't go.
You're here.
I'm not.
You have to face that.
But she is.
So is he.
Who?
Laeddis.
I have to go.
No.
No, please. Please.
I need to hold on to you.
Just a little bit longer, please.
(GROANING) Oh, God, Teddy.
You have to let me go.
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
I can't.
(GASPS)
Ain't gonna be no ferry in this shit.
Doctor!
Doctor, Doctor.
We need to interview
the patients
who were in Rachel's
group therapy session.
I thought your investigation
was finished.
Well, it's not like
we could take the ferry.
Now, was Rachel receiving
any other treatments for her illnesses?
(SIGHS)
Do you know the state
of the mental health field
these days, gentlemen?
.
No, not a clue, Doctor
War.
The old school believes
in surgical intervention.
Psychosurgery.
Procedures like
the transorbital lobotomy.
Some say the patients
become reasonable, docile.
Others say they
become zombies.
And the new school?
Psychopharmacology.
A new drug has just been approved
called Thorazine,
which relaxes psychotic patients,
you could say tames them.
And which school are you, Doctor?
Me?
I have this radical idea that if you treat a patient
with respect,
listen to him, try and understand,
you just might reach him.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Come on, Marge
. It's okay.
These patients, huh?
Even these.
What should be a last resort is becoming
a first response.
Give them a pill, put them in a corner,
it all goes away.
Rachel Solando was
on a combination of drugs
meant to keep her
from becoming violent,
but it was only
intermittently effective.
The greatest obstacle
to her recovery
was her refusal to face
what she had done.
"Was."
Is there a reason you keep referring
to your patient
in the past tense, Doctor?
Look outside, Marshal.
Why do you think?
Next up is Peter Breene.
Assaulted his father's nurse
with broken glass.
Nurse survived, but her face is
permanently disfigured
I can't wait.
She'd smile at me.
She was so sweet,
but you could see it in her eyes.
She liked to be naked,
to suck cock.
Okay, Mr. Breene.
And then she asked me if she can have
a glass of water?
Alone, in the kitchen,
like that's no big deal?
Well, why was that
a big deal?
It was obvious.
She wanted me to pull out my thing
so that she could laugh at it.
Mr. Breene.
We need to ask you
some questions, okay?
When I cut her, she screamed.
.
But (SNORTS) she scared me
What did she expect?
Interesting.
But we're here to talk about
Rachel Solando, okay?
Rachel Solando.
Do you...
Do you know that
she drowned her own kids?
She drowned her kids!
This is...
This is a sick fucking world we live in,
I'll tell you that.
But you know what?
They should be gassed.
All of them. The retards,
the killers, the niggers.
You kill your own kid,
gas the bitch.
(PENCIL SCRATCHING LOUDLY)
Could you stop that?
That nurse...
Please, stop that.
That nurse,
maybe she had kids, huh?
A husband.
Just trying to make ends meet,
lead a normal life.
It says in your file that
you tore her face off.
Didn't you?
Congratulations.
No more normal for her,
not ever again. No.
Do you know what
she was afraid of?
You.
(LOUDLY) Could you
stop that? Please?
Stop that!
Please! Stop!
Do you know a patient
named Andrew Laeddis?
Do you?
No! No.
Boss. What's up?
Fine.
I wanna go back. I wanna go.
Peter!
Come on! I got him.
Peter! Peter!
Hey, Peter!
PETER: Go back.
I wanna go back.
TREY: Come on, Peter.
I don't wanna see him.
Easy now.
I don't wanna
see him anymore.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Oh,
I'll never get out of here
. I'm not sure that I should
Excuse me for saying this,
Miss Kearns...
Mrs.
Mrs. Kearns.
But you seem quite normal.
I mean, in comparison to the
other patients here.
Well, I have my dark days.
I suppose everybody does.
The difference is
most people don't kill
their husbands with an ax.
Ah.
Although, personally,
I think if a man beats you
and fucks half the women he sees,
and no one will help you,
axing him isn't the least understandable
thing you could do.
Maybe you shouldn't get out.
(CHUCKLES)
What would I do if I did?
I don't know the world anymore.
They say there are
bombs that can reduce
whole cities to ash.
And what do you
call them, televisions,
voices and faces
coming from a box.
(CHUCKLES) I hear
enough voices already.
What can you
tell us about Rachel?
Um...
Not much.
She keeps to herself.
She believed
her kids were alive.
She thought she was still living
in the Berkshires,
and we were all her neighbors,
the milkmen, postmen...
Deliverymen.
And Dr. Sheehan
was there that night?
.
Yes. He talked about anger
Tell me about him.
What's he like?
Uh, he's, uh...
Okay. Nice.
Not hard on the eyes,
as my mother would say.
(CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
Did he ever
make a pass at you?
No.
No, Dr. Sheehan's a good doctor,
he would never...
Um...
(STAMMERING) Could I have
a glass of water, please?
No problem.
Thank you, Marshal.
CHUCK: Sure.
TEDDY: I just have
one more question for you,
Mrs. Kearns.
Did you ever meet a patient named
Andrew Laeddis?
No.
(VOICE BREAKING)
Never heard of him.
TEDDY: She was coached.
She used
practically the same words
as Cawley and the nurse,
like she'd been told
exactly what to say.
Who's Andrew Laeddis?
You asked every one
of those patients
back there about him.
Who is he?
(SIGHS)
What the hell, boss?
I'm your partner,
for Christ's sake.
.
We just met, Chuck
You've been on the beat for a long time.
You've got a duty.
You've got a career.
What I'm doing,
it's not exactly
by the book.
I don't give a damn about
by-the-book, boss.
I just wanna know
what the hell's going on.
When this case
came over the wires,
I requested it specifically,
you understand?
Why?
Andrew Laeddis,
he was the maintenance man
in the apartment building
where my wife and I lived.
Okay.
He was also a firebug.
Andrew Laeddis
lit the match
that caused the fire
that killed my wife.
GUARD: Let them out!
CHUCK: What happened
to Laeddis?
.
TEDDY: He got away with it
Laeddis got away with it
and then he disappeared.
About a year ago,
I open up the paper
and there he is.
Ugly-looking
son of a bitch.
Huge scar
from his right temple
down to his left lip.
Eyes different colors.
Not the type of face
you'd forget.
He burned down
a schoolhouse,
killed two people,
said voices
told him to do it.
First he went to prison,
then he got transferred here.
Then what?
Then nothing.
He vanished like
he never existed.
No record whatsoever.
Pretty sure
he's not in Ward B.
That leaves Ward C.
Or he could be dead.
So could Rachel Solando,
for that matter.
Lot of places to
hide a body here.
Only one place no one
would really notice.
That patient,
Bridget Kearns,
when she sent me
for water,
she said something
to you back there,
didn't she?
No.
Come on, boss.
She wrote it.
.
Boss! We gotta get indoors
It's turning into a fuckin
g Kansas out here.
Hold on.
No, let's go!
Watch out!
Jesus!
Come on! Up there!
Let's go!
CHUCK: Get in there!
Boss!
(GRUNTS)
God!
Jesus Christ!
Damn it. God!
You okay, boss?
Yeah, I'm all right.
So if Laeddis is here,
what are you
gonna do about it?
Mmm.
I'm not here
to kill Laeddis.
If it was my wife,
I'd kill him.
Twice.
TEDDY: When we got
through the gates
at Dachau,
the SS guards surrendered.
The Kommandant
tried to kill himself
before we got there,
but he...
He botched it.
Took him an hour to die.
When I went outside,
I saw all the bodies
on the ground.
Too many to count.
Too many to imagine.
So, yeah, the...
The guards surrendered
, we took their guns,
and we lined them up.
(INDISTINCT MUTTERING)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(MEN GROANING WEAKLY)
It wasn't warfare.
It was...
It was murder.
Yeah, I've had
enough of killing.
That's not why I'm here.
So what is this all about?
(SIGHS)
.
After Laeddis vanished
, I started doing some
checking on Ashecliffe
A lot of people
know about this place,
but no one wants to talk.
You know, it's like it...
It's like they're
scared or something.
You know,
this place is funded
by a special grant
from The House
Un-American
Activities Committee?
HUAC? And how exactly
are we fighting
the communists
from an island
in Boston Harbor?
By conducting
experiments on the mind.
At least that's my guess.
And you think
that's going on here?
Like I said,
no one would talk, right?
Till I found somebody
who used to be
a patient here.
Guy's name is George Noyce.
Nice college kid. Socialist.
He gets offered some money
to do a psych study.
Guess what
they were testing?
Toothpaste.
So, he starts seeing
dragons everywhere.
He almost beats his
professor to death.
Ends up here
in Ashecliffe, Ward C.
They release him
after one year, right?
And what does he do?
Two weeks on the mainland,
he walks into a bar,
stabs three men to death.
His lawyer pleads insanity,
but Noyce, he stands up
in the courtroom and he...
He begs the judge
for the electric chair.
Anywhere but
a mental hospital.
Judge gives him life
in Dedham Prison.
And you found him.
Yeah, I found him.
Well, he's a mess.
But it's pretty clear
from what he tells me.
What?
They're experimenting
on people here.
I don't know, boss.
How do you believe
a crazy guy?
That's the beauty
of it, isn't it?
Crazy people,
they're the perfect subjects.
They talk, nobody listens.
I stood at Dachau.
We saw what
human beings
are capable
of doing to
each other, right?
For Christ's sakes,
we fought a goddamn war
to stop them,
and now...
Now I find out it
may be happening here?
On our soil? No.
?
So what are you
really here to do, Ted
I'm gonna get the proof,
I'm gonna go back,
and I'm gonna blow
the lid off this place.
That's it.
Wait a minute.
You started asking around
about Ashecliffe,
waiting for a chance
to get out here,
and then suddenly
they need a U.S. Marshal?
Yeah, I got lucky.
There was a patient escape.
It was the perfect excuse.
No, no, no, boss.
Luck doesn't work
that way.
The world doesn't
work that way.
They got an
electrified fence
around a septic facility.
Ward C is inside
a Civil War fort?
A Chief of Staff
with ties to the OSS?
Funding from HUAC?
I mean, Jesus Christ,
everything about
this place stinks of
government ops.
What if they
wanted you here?
Bullshit.
You were asking questions.
Bullshit! Bullshit!
Bullshit. We came here
for Rachel Solando.
Where's one
shred of evidence
she even existed?
There's no way
they could've known
I'd be assigned
to this case.
There's no way.
What if while you were
looking into them,
they were
looking into you?
All they had to do
was fake an escape
to get you here,
and now they have you.
Now they have us both.
Here! Now!
McPHERSON: (ON MEGAPHONE)
Marshals, are you out here?
This is Deputy
Warden McPherson.
Marshals!
How about that?
They found us, huh?
It's an island, boss.
They're always gonna find us.
I know you're in there.
We're getting off
this goddamn island.
You and me. Come on.
Come on!
Go, go!
McPHERSON: Get dried off.
Dr. Cawley wants to
talk to you now.
And hurry up!
This thing is turning
into a goddamn hurricane!
I dropped those
suits off to be cleaned.
Should be ready by tomorrow.
That is, if we all
don't wash away first.
You know,
speaking of which,
I'm afraid your smokes
are pretty much done for.
So...
This is our
only choice, huh?
Got something really nice
in a prison gray if that
don't work for you.
Now that you mention it,
these are just fine.
That's why I must
repeat my insistence
that all Ward C patients
be placed in
manual restraints.
If the facility floods
, they'll drown.
You know that.
NAEHRING: That would take
a lot of flooding.
CAWLEY: We're on an island
in the middle of the ocean
during a hurricane.
.
A lot of flooding
seems like
a distinct possibility
DOCTOR 1:
It's a gamble, Stephen
. Say the power fails.
.
There's a backup generator
And if that goes,
the cell doors will open.
Where are they
going to go? Mmm?
They can't jus
t hop a ferry,
scoot over to the mainland
and wreak havoc.
.
NAEHRING: Oh,
you're quite right
They're far more likely
to wreak havoc
right here on us.
If they're manacled
to the floor, they'll die.
This is 24 human beings.
?
And you can live
with that, can you
Well, frankly,
if it were up to me,
I'd put all 42
in Wards A and B
in manual restraints as well.
Excuse me! Excuse me.
CAWLEY: Marshal.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I just have one
quick question.
Yes, I'll be with you
in a moment.
When we spoke
this morning about
Rachel Solando's note...
"The law of four."
I love that.
...you said
you had no idea
what that second line
could refer to, correct?
"Who is 67?" Yes,
I'm afraid I still don't.
None of us do.
Uh-huh.
Nothing comes to mind?
Nothing?
Because I believe
I just heard you say
there are 24 patients
in Ward C
and 42 patients
in Wards A and B,
which means
there's a total of, what,
66 patients
at this facility?
That is correct, yes.
Well, it seems to me
Rachel Solando
was suggesting
that you have
a 67th patient, Doctor.
But I'm afraid we don't.
(CHUCKLING)
This is ridiculous.
What are they doing here?
We're doing
our goddamn job.
?
Didn't McPherson
tell you the good news
(SIGHS) No.
What's the good news, Doctor?
Rachel's been found.
.
She's here
Safe and sound
(SOFTLY) There's not
a mark on her.
Who are these men?
(WHISPERING)
Why are they in my house?
Police officers, Rachel.
They have a few questions.
Ma'am.
There has been
a sighting of a known
communist subversive
in this area,
.
passing out literature
Here?
In this neighborhood?
.
Yes, I'm afraid so
Now if you could tell us
what you did yesterday,
where you were,
.
it would really help u
s narrow down our search
Yes, um...
Well, I, um...
I made breakfast
for Jim and the children,
and then I
packed Jim's lunch
and he left.
Then I sent the children
off to school.
And then
(CHUCKLES)
I decided to take
a long swim in the lake.
I see.
?
And after that
(SNIFFS) Um...
After that,
I thought of you.
(STAMMERING)
I'm sorry, ma'am,
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't you know
how lonely I've been, Jim?
You're gone.
You're dead.
I cry every night.
(SOBS)
How am I supposed
to survive?
God.
Rachel, it'll be all right.
I'm so sorry,
but every...
?
Everything's gonna
be all right. Okay
I buried you.
I buried an empty casket.
Your body rained down,
lumps of flesh
splashing into the sea,
eaten by sharks.
My Jim's dead,
so who the fuck are you?
(SCREAMING)
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's okay. Rachel.
Rachel, it's all right.
(SHRIEKING) Let me go! No!
TREY: Rachel, it's okay.
Look at me, look at me.
(TREY SHUSHING SOOTHINGLY)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't want to interrupt.
I thought she might
tell you something.
We found her down
by the lighthouse,
skipping stones.
We've no idea
how she got out, but...
I'm gonna have to
ask you to go down
into the basement.
.
There's food,
water and cots
It's the safest place to b
e when the hurricane hits.
Are you all right?
You look pale.
I'm fine. It's just...
CHUCK: Boss, are you okay?
It's just
so goddamn bright,
isn't it?
Photosensitivity,
headaches sometimes.
Marshal,
are you having a migraine?
I'll be all right.
.
Come on, I got you
(RETCHING)
CHUCK: What's wrong
with him?
Take these, Marshal.
Couple of hours, you'll be
as clear as a bell.
What's wrong with him?
He's having a migraine.
Imagine someone
sawed open your head,
filled it with razors,
and shook it as
hard as they could.
Take the pills, Marshal.
.
I don't...
I don't want the pills
It'll stop the pain.
Marshal, take the pills.
He's going to
need to lie down.
Oh, my God!
NURSE 1: There's broken glass
all over the floor.
Make sure all the meds
are locked up.
Watch your back.
NURSE 2: Make sure
everything's okay
in Ward B.
DOCTOR: Go down
to the infirmary and see
if there's any more...
NURSE 3: All right, Doctor.
Give him a bed.
This one here.
Over here.
All right, boss.
Yeah, that's it.
You have him?
TREY: Yes.
.
Careful. All right
Could be worse right now.
He'll be all right.
Who is that?
TREY: Him?
That's the warden.
Don't you worry
about him, all right?
.
Come on.
Lay back. Lay back
He looks like
an ex-military prick, huh?
Well, you know what?
I ain't gonna argue
with you on that one.
(WOMAN MURMURING)
GIRL: (WHISPERING)
You should have saved me.
You should have
saved all of us.
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES) Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Laeddis.
Yeah.
My...
My buddy.
No hard feelings, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
No hard feelings.
A little something
for later,
'cause I know
how much you need it.
(CLOCK STRIKES)
(CLOCK TICKING)
The clock's ticking,
my friend.
We're running
out of time.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Give me a hand here.
I could get into trouble.
I'm dead.
I'm so sorry.
?
Why didn't you save me
I tried. I wanted to,
but by the time I got there,
it was too late.
See?
Aren't they beautiful?
(GASPS)
Why are you all wet, baby?
Laeddis isn't dead.
He isn't gone.
He's still here.
I know.
You need to
find him, Teddy.
You need to find him
and you kill him dead.
(SHUSHING)
(STIFLING SOBS
)
It's okay.
(BREATHING TREMULOUSLY)
(SHUSHING)
MARINO: Security to Ward A.
Okay.
ORDERLY 1: Ward A.
I got it.
NURSE 1: The generator
room's flooded.
ORDERLY 2: Ward A. Ward A.
See what we
need in Ward B.
NURSE 2: Let's go.
You okay, boss?
This goddamn migraine.
The backup
generator's failed.
The whole place
has gone crazy.
What do you want to do?
(SIREN WAILING)
Christ.
Dan? Relax.
Nope, nope, nope.
You don't wanna do that.
Put it down. Now.
Put it down.
Grab him, grab him,
grab him, grab him!
Get him, get him!
ORDERLY 1: You need
to go find him 'cause
he needs to be here.
You think the whole
electrical system is fried?
I'd say it's a goo
d possibility, yeah.
All the electronic security,
the fences...
Why are you
always running?
...the gates, the doors.
Why is it you
every time?
Come on.
.
Nice day for a stroll,
don't you think?
To Ward C, for example
Come on.
Maybe we'll run
into Andrew Laeddis.
TEDDY: The guy
I told you about,
George Noyce?
He told me this
is where they keep
the worst ones.
Guys even the other inmates
are scared of.
Did Noyce
give you anything
on the layout?
Not really.
All he remembered
was people screaming
day and night,
no windows and
iron bars everywhere.
MAN: Watch your head!
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Jesus.
First time on Ward C, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
We heard stories, but...
.
Trust me, son,
you haven't heard shit
We got most
of the bugsies
locked down now,
but some of them
are still loose.
And if you see one,
don't try to
restrain him yourselves.
These fuckers
will kill you.
Clear?
All right, get your asses
moving then. Go on.
(INMATE LAUGHING CRAZILY)
(DISTANT INSANE LAUGHTER)
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
He's here.
Laeddis. I can feel him.
(TEDDY EXCLAIMS)
Tag! You're it!
Wait! Boss! Ted!
Hey! Hey!
Teddy.
Listen to me.
Listen, I don't
wanna leave here,
all right?
I mean, why would
anybody want to?
We hear things here
about the outside world.
.
About atolls,
about H-bomb tests
CHUCK: Teddy,
where are you?
You know how
a hydrogen bomb works?
I know.
With hydrogen!
With hydrogen.
Ah, that's funny.
Boss!
?
Other bombs explode, right
But not the hydrogen bomb.
It implodes,
creating an explosion
to the thousandth,
the millionth degree!
Do you get it?
Yeah! Yeah.
Do you?
I get it, I get it!
Let him go!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
CHUCK: No!
No! No!
?
What are you doing
!
Jesus Christ, Teddy. Jesus
Oh, you got Billings.
What the fuck's
the matter with you guys?
Catch them,
not kill them!
He jumped us.
GUARD: You, give me
a hand with him.
We've gotta get hi
m to the infirmary.
God damn it.
No, no!
Not you, not you.
Take a walk.
Come on.
Cawley's gonna have
my goddamn balls for this.
MAN: (WHISPERING) Laeddis.
(RATTLING)
(WHISPERING) Laeddis.
(INMATES MOANING)
(INMATE WHISPERING
TO HIMSELF)
INMATE: (SOFTLY)
Stop me, please,
(SOBBING) before I kill more.
Stop me before I kill more.
MAN: (WHISPERING) Laeddis.
)
(SCREAMING
(INMATES SCREAMING)
INMATE: Please, please.
MAN: (WHISPERING)
I see you all.
Laeddis.
You told me I'd be
free of this place.
You promised.
You lied.
Laeddis.
Laeddis?
(CHUCKLES) That's
pretty damn funny.
Your voice.
Don't you recognize it?
After all
the talks we had?
After all the lies
you told me?
Let me see your face.
They say I'm theirs now.
They say I'll never
leave here.
Your match is
about to go out.
Let me see your
goddamn face! Now!
Why?
So you can lie
to me more?
This isn't about the truth.
Yes, it is.
.
It's about
exposing the truth
It's about you!
And Laeddis.
That's all it's
ever been about.
I was incidental.
A way in.
.
George... George Noyce
No. It's not possible.
You can't be here.
You like it?
?
Who did this
to you, George
You did.
What the hell do you mean?
All your talk.
All your fucking talk,
and I'm back in here
because of you.
George,
how did they get you
out of Dedham, huh?
(STAMMERING) However this
happened, I...
I'm gonna find
a way to fix this,
you understand me?
I'll never get out now.
I got out once.
Not twice, never twice.
Just tell me how
they got you here.
They knew!
Don't you get it?
Everything you were up to.
Your whole plan.
This is a game.
All of this is for you.
You're not
investigating anything.
You're a fucking rat
in a maze.
Georgie...
George, you're wrong.
You're wrong.
Oh, really?
Been alone much
since you got here?
I've been with my partner.
You never worked
with him before,
have you?
He's a U.S. Marshal.
He's...
(INSISTENTLY) You never
worked with him before,
have you?
George, look,
I know people.
I trust this man.
Then they've already won.
(WHIMPERS) Fuck.
(SOBBING)
And they're gonna take me
to the lighthouse.
They're gonna
cut into my brain.
And I'm only here
(SHOUTING) because of you!
George, I'm gonna
get you out of here.
You're not going
to the lighthouse.
You're not.
You can't dig out the truth
and kill Laeddis
at the same time.
You gotta make a choice.
You understand that,
don't you?
.
I'm not here
to kill anyone
Liar!
I'm not gonna kill him,
I swear to you! I swear.
She's dead.
She... Let her go.
Let her go.
DOLORES: Tell him, Teddy.
Tell him why.
You gotta do it.
There's no other way.
Let her go.
Tell him about the day
you brought me
my locket.
You gotta do it!
How I told you
my heart was breaking
and you asked me why.
She's fucking with your head.
And I told you
it was from happiness.
She's gonna kill you.
You wanna uncover the truth?
You gotta let her go.
!
I can't.
You have to let her go
I can't! I can't.
Then you'll never
leave this island.
Dolores.
He's not in this ward.
He was transferred
out of here.
If he's not in Ward A,
there's only one place
he can be.
The lighthouse.
Hey,
God help you.
Boss, we got problems.
McPherson and Cawley
are in the building.
They heard an orderly
went batshit on a patient.
They're looking all
over the place for him
and they're on
their way to the roof.
Let's get the hell
out of here. This way.
Just keep going.
We belong here.
(TEDDY GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
What happened to you?
What do you mean?
I mean,
where were you?
After we got that guy
to the infirmary,
I took a little detour
to patient records.
Did you ever find Laeddis?
No. No, I never found him.
Well, I got
the next best thing.
His intake form.
It was the only thing
in his files.
There's no session notes,
no incident reports,
no photographs, just this.
It was weird.
Here. Take a look.
I'll look at it later.
What's the matter, boss?
I'll look it over later,
that's all.
Ashecliffe's that way.
I'm not going
to Ashecliffe.
I'm going to
that lighthouse.
I'm gonna find out
what the fuck is happening
on this island.
TEDDY: There it is.
Damn. We're too far south.
We're gonna have to
double back.
There's no way we could
cross those rocks.
There could be a way
behind those trees.
Maybe a path that goes
around the rocks
and leads over
to the lighthouse.
Boss...
Come on.
Wait, wait,
what are we doing?
We got the intake form.
It's proof
there's a 67th patient,
which they said,
repeatedly, doesn't exist.
I'm getting to
that lighthouse.
You understand?
What the hell
can I say to you
to stop you?
Why would you want to,
Chuck? Why?
Because climbing
down there when it's dark
is a thin step
short of suicide,
that's why.
Okay, maybe you better
sit this one out then.
You brought me
into this, boss,
and now we're trapped
here on this rock,
on this island,
with no one to rely on
but each other,
and now you're acting like...
Like what? Like what?
How am I acting?
What the hell
happened back there
in those cells, Ted?
?
What do you think
the weather's like
in Portland, Chuck
I'm from Seattle.
Seattle.
I'm going on
alone.
I'm going with you, boss.
I said alone.
Fine.
Damn it!
Damn it.
I knew it wouldn't take long,
but I couldn't get to it.
The tide was up.
Chuck!
Come on!
(EXCLAIMS)
Chuck!
Where are you, Chuck?
(SQUEAKING)
Chuck!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
Who are you?
I'm Teddy Daniels.
I'm a cop.
.
You're the marshal
That's right.
Would you mind
taking your hand
from behind
your back, please?
Why? Why?
I wanna make sure that
what you're holding
won't hurt me.
I'm gonna keep this
if you don't mind.
Fine by me.
You're...
You're Rachel Solando.
The real one.
Did you kill your children?
I never had children.
I was never married.
And before I was
a patient at Ashecliffe,
I worked here.
You... You were a nurse?
I was a doctor, Marshal.
You think I'm crazy.
No. No, no, I never...
?
And if I say I'm not crazy
Well, that hardly helps,
does it?
That's the Kafkaesque
genius of it.
People tell the world
you're crazy,
and all your protests
to the contrary
just confirm
what they're saying.
I'm not following you.
I'm sorry.
Once you're declared insane,
then anything you do
is called part of
that insanity.
Reasonable protests
are denial.
Valid fears, paranoia.
Survival instincts are
defense mechanisms.
You're smarter than you look, Marshal.
That's probably
not a good thing.
Tell me something.
Yeah.
What happened to you?
I started asking about
these large shipments
of sodium amytal
and opium-based
hallucinogens.
Psychotropic drugs.
.
I asked about
the surgeries, too
You ever heard of
a transorbital lobotomy?
They zap the patient
with electroshock,
then go through the eye
with an ice pick,
.
pull out some nerve fibers
Makes the patients
much more obedient.
Tractable.
It's barbaric,
unconscionable.
Do you know how pain
enters the body, Marshal?
Do you?
Depends on where you're hurt?
No,
it has nothing
to do with the flesh.
The brain controls pain.
The brain controls fear,
empathy, sleep, hunger,
anger. Everything.
What if you could control it?
You mean the brain?
Recreate a man
so he doesn't feel pain or love or sympathy.
A man who can't
be interrogated,
.
because he has
no memories to confess
You can
never take away all
a man's memories. Never.
Marshal, the North Koreans
used American POWs
during their
brainwashing experiments.
.
They turned
soldiers into traitors
.
That's what
they're doing here
They're creating ghost
s to go out in the world
and do things sane men...
Sane men never would.
To have that kind of ability,
that kind of knowledge,
that would take years.
Years. Years of research.
Hundreds of patients
to experiment on.
Fifty years from now,
people will
look back and say,
here, this place,
is where it all began.
The Nazis used the Jews,
Soviets used prisoners
in their own Gulags,
and we,
we tested patients
on Shutter Island.
No, they won't.
No.
You do understand
that they can't
let you leave.
I am a federal marshal.
They can't stop me.
I was
an esteemed psychiatrist
from a respected family.
Didn't matter.
Let me ask you.
Any past traumas
in your life?
Yes.
But why would that matter?
Because they're gonna
point to some event
in your past
and say it's the reason you lost your sanity.
So that when they
commit you here,
your friends and
colleagues will say,
"Of course he cracked.
"Who wouldn't after what
he'd been through?"
They can say that
about anyone,
anyone at all.
The point is they're gonna
say it about you.
How's your head?
My head?
Any funny dreams lately?
Trouble sleeping?
Headaches?
I am prone to migraines, yes.
Jesus.
You haven't taken
any pills, have you?
I mean, even aspirin?
The aspirin?
Jesus.
And you ate the food
in the cafeteria
and drank the coffee
they gave you?
You tell me, at least,
that you've been smoking
your own cigarettes.
No.
No, I haven't.
It takes 36 to 48 hours
for neuroleptic narcotics
to reach workable levels
in the bloodstream.
Palsy comes first,
first the fingertips,
then eventually
the whole hand.
Seen any walking nightmare
s lately, Marshal? Huh?
Tell me what goes on
in that lighthouse.
Tell me.
Brain surgery.
The let's-open-
the-skull-and-see-
what-happens-if-we
- pull-on-this kind.
The learned-it-
from-the-Nazis kind.
That's where they
create the ghosts.
Who knows about this?
On the island, I mean. Who?
Everyone.
Come on. The nurses?
The orderlies?
They couldn't
possibly know...
(FIRMLY) Everyone.
You can't stay here.
They think I'm dead,
that I drowned.
I'm afraid if they
come looking for you,
they might find me.
.
I'm sorry,
but you have to go
I'm gonna come back for you.
I won't be here.
I move during the day.
New places every night.
But I could come get you,
get you off this island.
Haven't you heard
a word I've said?
The only way off
the island is the ferry,
and they control it.
You'll never leave here.
I had a friend.
I was with him yesterday,
but we got separated.
Have you seen him?
Marshal,
you have no friends.
(GRUNTING)
There you are.
We were wondering
when you'd show up.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Taking a leisurely stroll,
were we?
I was just looking around.
Did you enjoy
God's latest gift?
What?
God's gift.
The violence.
When I came downstairs
in my home
and I saw that tree in my living room,
it reached out for me
like a divine hand.
.
God loves violence
I hadn't noticed.
(CHUCKLES) Sure you have.
?
Why else would
there be so much of it
It's in us.
It's what we are.
,
We wage war,
we burn sacrifices
and pillage and plunder and tear
at the flesh of our brothers.
And why? Because God
gave us violence
to wage in his honor.
I thought God
gave us moral order.
There's no moral order
as pure as this storm.
.
There's no
moral order at all
There's just this,
can my violence
conquer yours?
I'm not violent.
Yes, you are.
You're as violent
as they come.
I know this because I'm as violent
If the constraints of
society were lifted,
and I was all that stood
between you and a meal,
you would crack my skull
with a rock and eat
my meaty parts.
Wouldn't you?
Cawley thinks
you're harmless,
that you can
be controlled,
but I know different.
You don't know me.
Oh, but I do.
No, you don't.
You don't know me at all.
.
Oh, I know you
We've known each other
for centuries.
If I was to sink my teeth
into your eye right now,
would you
be able to stop me
before I blinded you?
Give it a try.
That's the spirit.
Don't worry,
because we're going to
get you back to your room.
Not really.
Something I've seen.
Okay.
Where have you been?
Oh, just wandering.
Just looking at your island.
Oh, I forgot
you're leaving now that Rachel's been found.
GLEN: Stop looking at him.
For sure. Yeah.
Stop looking at him.
Big meeting?
Oh, yes.
It's okay. I'm...
I don't like that.
Apparently there was
an unidentified man
in Ward C yesterday.
He subdued a highly dangerous patient
quite handily.
Is that so?
It seems he had a long conversation
with a paranoid schizophrenic,
George Noyce.
BRIDGET: Well,
I don't remember
what I'm supposed
to remember.
We're gated down.
We're fine.
This Noyce,
you said his name was,
he's delusional?
Oh, extremely.
He can be quite upsetting.
As a matter of fact,
two weeks ago,
a patient got so
wound up by one
of Noyce's stories
that he beat him up.
Hmm.
Cigarette?
No, thanks. I quit.
?
So you're taking the ferry
Yes, absolutely.
I think we've gotten
all we came here for,
so...
"We," Marshal?
Speaking of which,
have you seen him, Doctor?
Who?
My partner, Chuck.
.
You don't have
a partner, Marshal
You came here alone.
You know, I've built
something valuable here,
and valuable things
have a way
of being misunderstood
in their own time.
Everyone wants a quick fix
. They always have.
I'm trying to do
something that people,
yourself included,
don't understand.
And I'm not
going to give up
without a fight.
I can see that.
Mmm.
.
So, tell me again
about your partner
What partner?
(LAUGHING)
It's fine.
(GASPING)
(1940s POPULAR MUSIC
PLAYING FAINTLY)
ORDERLY: She made a mess.
I cleaned it up.
She made a mess again.
Marshal,
going somewhere?
(STAMMERING) I'm just
heading out to the ferry,
so...
Ah! Oh, well,
I'm afraid
it's the other way.
Oh?
If you'll wait a moment,
I'll find you someone
who can take you
to the dock.
What's this, Doctor?
Huh? What's this?
It's just a sedative.
A precaution.
Oh! A precaution.
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
What are you
going to do?
Kill me?
Marshal.
You think you deserve it?
For what, hmm?
Provoking you?
Well, forgive me.
What doesn't provoke you?
?
Remarks? Words
Nazis?
Well, that, too.
And, of course,
memories, dreams.
Did you know that
the word "trauma"
comes from the Greek
for "wound"?
And what is
the German word
for "dream"?
Traum. Ein Traum.
Wounds can create monsters
, and you...
You are wounded, Marshal.
,
And wouldn't you agree
, when you see a monster
you must stop it?
Yeah.
I agree.
Yes.
Yeah.
(GROANS)
ORDERLY 1: I told him
that we'd take about
an hour to do it.
ORDERLY 2: Yeah.
Did they say we're going
to do the first floor?
ORDERLY 1: How long
you been the clock?
ORDERLY 2: I've been on
for 18 hours straight.
ORDERLY 1: Nice paycheck.
DOLORES: What are
you doing, baby?
You gotta get to the ferry.
No.
No, no.
Yeah.
,
If the world think
s that Chuck is dead
then he's perfect
for their experiments.
There's only one place
they'd take him.
.
You go there
and you'll die
He's my partner.
If they are hurting him,
if they're holding
him against his will,
I've gotta bring him out.
I can't lose anyone else.
Don't go, Teddy, please.
Please, don't do this.
Don't go.
I'm sorry, honey.
I love this thing
because you gave it to me,
but the truth is
it is one fucking ugly tie.
No.
.
Don't move.
Stay where you are
Are you gonna kill me?
No, I'm not gonna kill you.
(RATTLING)
(METAL CLICKING)
Why are you all wet, baby?
What did you say?
You know
exactly what I said.
The rifle's empty,
by the way.
(BREACH OPENING)
Have a seat.
For God's sake, dry off.
You'll catch cold.
All right.
How badly did you
hurt the guard?
(STAMMERING) I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yes, he's here.
Have Dr. Sheehan
take a look at your man
before you send him up.
So Dr. Sheehan
came in on the ferry
this morning, huh?
Not exactly.
You blew up my car.
I really loved that car.
Sorry to hear about that.
Tremors are
getting pretty bad.
How are the hallucinations?
DOLORES: Get out
of here, Teddy.
This place is gonna be the end of you.
Not bad.
They'll get worse.
TEDDY: I know.
Dr. Solando,
she told me about
the neuroleptics.
Did she, now?
And when was this?
I found her, Doctor,
in a cave out by the cliffs.
But you'll
never get to her.
I don't doubt it,
.
considering she's not real
Your delusions
are more severe
than I thought.
.
You're not on neuroleptics
You're not on anything
, as a matter of fact.
Then what
the fuck is this?
Huh? What the fuck is this?
Withdrawal.
Withdrawal? From what?
I haven't had
a goddamn drink
since I've been
on this island.
Chlorpromazine.
I'm not a fan
of pharmacology,
but I have to say,
in your case...
(STAMMERING)
Chloraproma-what?
Chlorpromazine.
.
The same thing
we've been giving you
for the past 24 months
Oh, so for the past
two years, you...
You've had somebody
slipping me drugs in Boston.
Is that it?
Not Boston.
Here.
You've been here
for two years.
A patient of
this institution.
After everything
I've seen here, Doctor,
you really think
you're gonna convince me
I'm crazy, huh?
Do you know
the kind of people that
I deal with every day?
I'm a U.S. Marshal,
for God's sakes.
You were a U.S. Marshal.
Here's a copy of
the intake form
you broke into Ward C for.
Proof of the 67th patient.
If you'd gotten it
to the mainland,
you could have
blown the lid
off this place.
Wait. Where did...
Where did you...
Yet somehow,
you couldn't find
time to look at it.
Well, read it now.
Go ahead.
"Patient is
highly intelligent,
"highly delusional
decorated Army veteran.
(STAMMERING) "Present for
the liberation of Dachau.
"Former U.S. Marshal.
Known proclivity
for violence.
"Shows no remorse
for his crime
"because he denies
the crime ever...
"Ever took place.
"Highly developed
and fantastical narratives,
"which preclude
facing the truth
of his actions."
I've had enough
of this bullshit!
Where's my partner, huh?
Where's Chuck?
Where is he?
.
Let's try this another way
Your wife's
maiden name was Chanal
, am I correct?
Don't you even
talk about her.
Don't you...
I'm afraid I have to.
Notice anything
these four names
have in common?
It's your rule of four.
Andrew, what do you see?
If you've done anything
to my partner, Doctor,
that is a violation of...
Focus, Andrew!
What do you see?
The names have
the same letters.
Edward Daniels has exactly
the same 13 letters
as Andrew Laeddis.
The same as
Rachel Solando
and Dolores Chanal.
The names are anagrams
for each other.
Your tactics,
they're not gonna
work on me.
You came here
for the truth.
Here it is.
Your name is
Andrew Laeddis.
The 67th patient
at Ashecliffe
is you, Andrew.
Bullshit.
You were committed
here by court order
24 months ago.
Your crime is terrible,
one you can't forgive
yourself for,
so you invented
another self.
(BREATHING TREMULOUSLY)
All right.
(STAMMERING) Let's get down
to the facts, all right?
You've created a story
in which you're not
a murderer.
You're a hero,
still a U.S. Marshal,
only here at Ashecliffe because of a case,
and you've uncovered
a conspiracy
so that anything
we tell you
about who you are,
what you've done,
you can dismiss
as lies, Andrew.
My name is Edward Daniels.
I've been
hearing this fantasy
for two years now.
I know every detail.
Patient 67, the storm,
Rachel Solando,
your missing partner,
the dreams
you have every night.
You were at Dachau,
but you may not have
killed any guards.
(SIGHS)
I wish I could
let you just live in
your fantasy world.
I really do.
.
But you're violent
, trained, dangerous
You're the most
dangerous patient
we have.
You've injured
orderlies, guards,
other patients.
Two weeks ago,
you attacked
George Noyce.
No, no. I am fucking
on to you, Doctor.
!
You had Noyce beaten.
Of course I didn't
Give me one reason
why I would even touch him!
,
Because he
called you Laeddis
and you'd do anything
not to be him.
I have a transcript of the conversation
you had with
Noyce yesterday.
"This is about you
, and, Laeddis,
"that's all it's ever
been about."
No, no.
He's saying this is
about me and Laeddis.
When you asked him
what happened to his face,
he said, now here
I'm quoting again,
"You did this."
No, no, he meant
that it was my fault.
You almost killed him.
The warden and
the Board of Overseers
are determined
something be done.
It's been decided
,
that unless
we can bring you
back to sanity now
right now,
permanent measures
will be taken
.
to ensure you can't
hurt anyone ever again
They'll
lobotomize you, Andrew
. Do you understand?
Yeah, I understand.
I understand just fine.
If I don't play along
with your little game here,
Dr. Naehring's
gonna turn me into
one of his ghosts.
But what about my partner?
You gonna tell
the U.S. Marshal's office
that he's a defense mechanism?
Hello, boss.
(SOFTLY) What the fuck
is going on here? Hmm?
Huh?
You working for him?
I'm sorry.
There wasn't
any other way.
Someone had to
stick with you,
keep you safe.
You been watching me, huh?
Watching me every minute.
Who are you?
Who are you? Tell me.
Don't you
recognize me, Andrew?
I've been
your primary psychiatrist
for the last two years.
.
I'm Lester Sheehan
I told you... I told
you about my wife, I...
I know.
I climbed down
a cliff to get you.
I trusted you.
I risked everything
to come in here after you.
Everything!
I know, boss.
We're running out
of time here, Andrew.
I swore before
the Board of Overseers
that I could construct
the most radical,
cutting-edge role-play
ever attempted in psychiatry,
and it would bring you back.
I thought that if we
let you play this out
we could get you
to see how untrue,
how impossible it is.
You've had the run
of the place for two days.
Tell me, where are
the Nazi experiments?
The satanic ORs?
Andrew, listen to me.
If we fail with you,
then everything that
we've tried to do here
will be discredited.
Everything.
We're on the front lines
of a war here, old boy.
And right now,
it all comes down to you.
Don't move! Don't move!
Andrew! Andrew! No. No.
(ENUNCIATING) My name
is Edward Daniels!
This one's loaded.
I can tell by the weight.
I see. And that's
your firearm, Marshal?
You're sure?
My initials are on the side.
There's a dent in the barrel
from when Philip Stacks
shot at me.
You're not gonna
fuck with my mind
on this one, Doctor!
CAWLEY: Then blast away.
Because that's
the only way you're ever
getting off this island.
Andrew, please don't.
My gun.
What did you do
to my goddamn gun?
It's a toy, Andrew.
We're telling you the truth.
.
Dolores was insane,
manic-depressive, suicidal
You drank, stayed away
, ignored what everyone
told you.
You moved to that lake house
.
after she
purposely set your
city apartment on fire
You were...
(SCREAMING) You're lying!
Andrew!
Andrew, stop. No.
You drugged
the cigarettes!
All you've done is lie!
Andrew. Andrew.
Your children.
Andrew, your children.
Simon. Henry.
I never had any children.
Your wife drowned them
at the cabin by the lake.
And here,
the little girl,
the one you dream of
every night.
I never had a little girl.
The one who tells
you over and over
that you should have saved her
.
saved them all
Your daughter,
her name was Rachel.
Are you going to deny
that she ever lived?
Andrew, are you?
DOLORES: (WHIMPERING)
I'm so sorry, baby.
I told you not
to come in here.
I told you this
would be the end of you.
I'm back!
We got him just
outside of Oklahoma.
Must've stopped 10 places
in between here and Tulsa.
I could sleep for a week.
(BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
Dolores?
PREACHER: And he said,
"Take up your bed and walk."
But God?
Dolores?
PREACHER: Then he said,
"Take up your bed and walk."
Forgive sins, but God?
Dolores?
Baby,
why are you all wet?
I missed you.
I wanna go home.
You are home.
Where are the kids?
Hmm?
They're in school.
It's Saturday, honey.
School's not in
on Saturday.
My school is.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
(GASPING)
Oh, my God, no.
Come on, come on.
No. No. Please, God.
Please, God, no!
No!
(CRYING)
No.
Baby.
Let's put them
at the table, Andrew.
We'll dry them off.
We'll change their clothes.
They'll be
our living dolls. Huh?
Tomorrow we can
take them on a picnic.
If you ever
loved me, Dolores,
please stop talking.
I love you.
Set me free.
Oh, baby.
We'll give them baths.
I love you, baby.
I love you, too.
I love you so much
.
I love you so much.
I love you. I...
(GUNSHOT)
(INHALES WRETCHEDLY)
(SOBBING)
.
(SOBBING) Oh, baby
Andrew.
Andrew, can you hear me?
.
Rachel. Rachel, Rachel
Rachel?
Rachel who?
.
Rachel. Rachel Laeddis
My daughter.
Why are you here?
Because I killed my wife.
And why did you do that?
Because she murdered
our children,
and she told me
to let her go.
Who's Teddy Daniels?
He doesn't exist.
Neither does Rachel Solando.
I made them up.
Why?
We need to
hear you say it.
After she tried
to kill herself
the first time,
Dolores told me she...
She had an insect
living inside her brain.
She could feel it
clicking across her skull,
just pulling the wires
just for fun.
She told me that.
She told me that,
but I didn't listen.
I loved her so much,
you know.
Why did you
make them up?
Because I can't take
knowing that Dolores
killed our children.
And I...
I killed them 'cause
I didn't get her help,
you know.
I killed them.
.
Here's my fear, Andrew
We broke through
once before,
nine months ago,
.
and then you regressed
I don't remember that.
.
I know
You reset, Andrew.
Like a tape
playing over and over
on an endless loop.
I hope that
what we've done here
will be enough
to stop it from
ever happening again,
but I need to know
you've accepted reality.
You came after me,
huh, Doctor?
You tried to help me
when no one else would.
My name's Andrew Laeddis,
and I murdered my wife
in the spring of '52.
How we doing this morning?
Good. And you?
.
Can't complain
So what's our next move?
You tell me.
We gotta get off
this rock, Chuck.
Get back to the mainland.
Whatever the hell's
going on here, it's bad.
(INAUDIBLE)
(WHISPERING)
Don't worry, partner,
they're not gonna catch us.
That's right.
We're too smart for them.
Yeah, we are, aren't we?
You know, this place
makes me wonder...
Yeah, what's that, boss?
Which would be worse,
to live as a monster
or to die as a good man?
Teddy?
(THIS BITTER EARTH PLAYING)
%%  This bitter earth
%%  Well, what fruit it bears
%%  Ooh
%%  This bitter earth
%%  And if my life
%%  Is like the dust
%%  Ooh, that hides
%%  The glow of a rose
%%  What good am I
%%  Heaven only knows
%%  Lord, this bitter earth
%%  Yes, can be so cold
%%  Today, you're young
%%  Too soon, you're old
%%  But while a voice
%%  Within me cries
%%  I'm sure someone
may answer my call
%%  And this bitter earth
%%  Ooh
%%  May not
l
%%  Oh, be so bitter after al
%%  This bitter earth
%%  Lord, this bitter earth
%%  What good is love
%%  Mmm, that no one shares
%%  And if my life
%%  Is like the dust
%%  Ooh, that hides
%%  The glow of a rose
%%  What good am I
%%  Heaven only knows  %%
}}