TELEGRAM : @ddmoviechannel  | Join And Download
RAPI FILMS PRESENTS
IN ASSOCIATION
WITH SKY MEDIA &amp; LEGACY PICTURES
ADAPTED FROM THE TURKISH FILM SICCIN,
WRITTEN BY ERSAN ÖZER, ALPER MESTÇI
NEVER CHEAT, FOR INDEED, THOSE
WHO DO EVIL ARE RECORDED IN
THE BOOK OF SIJJIN AND BOUND
FOR HELL. (AL-MUTAFFIFIN VERSE 7)
NEVER CHEAT, FOR INDEED, THOSE
WHO DO EVIL ARE RECORDED IN
THE BOOK OF SIJJIN AND BOUND
FOR HELL. (AL-MUTAFFIFIN VERSE 7)
A FILM BY HADRAH DAENG RATU
Sis.
Why are we here?
-Isn't this where you do black magic?
-Quiet!
Recite any prayer that you know.
Oh, you, the bearer of knowledge.
We summon you with blood
of the exalting soul.
Humans are weak in the eyes of spirits.
Women are weak in the eyes of spirits.
You, bearer of knowledge.
You, who were born of fire.
Answer our prayers,
we who are born of soil.
What's your name?
Irma.
Why did you come here?
I need guidance.
It's about a man.
I want to know if I can marry him or not.
I only want to be with him.
What is his name?
Galang.
Who is he?
This is Galang.
He is our cousin.
He is the son of my mother's sister.
To the jinn who holds power
over spirits...
...give the answer...
...to the empty souls.
She will answer your question.
Galang is your cousin.
He is not the right husband for you.
Women are weak in
the eyes of the spirits.
Let it be between the
soul or life that melts.
Stay away from that man.
Or he will be the cause of your death.
12 YEARS LATER
-Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
Come, Irma. We're late.
Sis, come on.
Mom.
Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
-Auntie Irma.
-Peace be with you.
-Hi, sweetie.
-You smell so nice.
-Here's your gift.
It's big.
-Auntie.
-Nisa.
-Careful, it's heavy.
-Yes, thank you.
Nisa, what did the doctor say?
It's still the same Auntie.
There is no progress.
Yesterday, one of her friends came over...
...and said that this sickness
is not medical.
Should we look for alternative treatment?
Yeah, maybe someone
is deliberately trying to hurt her?
-Using black magic.
-Shush.
You two.
And you, Nisa.
You studied in nursing school.
Why would you believe in such things?
Excuse me, Auntie.
Galang, stop working. Aunt Farah is here.
Stop working.
Nisa, look. He's still working
on his daughter's birthday.
I know, just drag him Irma.
Listen to your wife.
Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Sofia
Happy birthday to you
-What is that?
-What is it?
It's a beautiful doll. It's gorgeous.
Cute.
Who is it from?
From Auntie Irma, Auntie Wulan,
and Grandma Farah.
-Wow.
-What do you say Nisa?
-Be right back.
-Okay.
Thank God.
Please don't leave her alone.
Galang should look after her too.
-Poor thing.
-Don't worry, Auntie.
Thank you.
Auntie, look who has come.
Hey.
Are you crazy?
This is my house.
So what? Cousins can't hug?
Stop messing around, Irma.
So all these years,
we've only been messing around?
I told you I need to speak
with you privately.
Typical.
Men only want one thing.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid your wife
will find out about us...
Watch your mouth.
We've agreed there's nothing
between us anymore.
We are related by blood.
You should have known that.
So what if we're related?
You married someone else...
...and your daughter is disabled.
This, we don't know yet.
This.
We're not certain
if our child would be disabled.
Dad?
I got a doll and a lipstick
from Auntie Irma.
She said I could be as pretty as her.
Am I pretty?
Auntie Irma?
Sofia.
Auntie Irma is not here.
Why do I smell her perfume?
Should we show it to Mom?
We've been dating for three years...
...and then you suddenly
agreed to get married with Nisa.
My mother arranged this marriage.
I only love you, Irma.
I promise I won't leave you.
No matter how you hide it,
they will eventually find out.
Do you think Nisa doesn't know?
You won't understand.
Maybe to you, I've always been
just a little girl, right?
But let me remind you.
You are not a lovesick teenager anymore.
Just so you know.
This isn't just about love.
You'll never understand.
Pick up.
Dit.
-Yes?
-Please check the stock in the back.
-You mean the fresh meat?
-Yes, now.
We're not done talking.
Irma, not here.
If you really care about your child...
Sofia isn't the only one.
Irma, I understand.
-But can we please not discuss it here?
-No.
I don't want us to be over.
You need to take responsibility.
I'm really pregnant.
Galang.
-Irma.
-Take responsibility.
Irma.
Take responsibility.
The child I am carrying in my womb is...
Irma!
Sir, are you alright?
I'm fine, Dit.
Do you need help?
No, no need. I just dropped some meat.
Please check the stock in the back again.
Yes, Sir.
Come, Irma.
We lost our baby.
And it's all because of you.
What is this?
Are you paying me off?
To cover the hospital bills.
I'm sorry.
What we did was wrong, Irma.
I'm asking you not to bother me again.
Our relationship ends here.
What?
Ends here?
It ends here?
What do you mean?
You're the one who said
that you'll always love me.
You told me you'll love me.
You promised to give me everything.
You lied to me, Galang.
You can't leave me like this.
Irma. I'm sorry.
I have a family, Irma.
Do you think I care?
Galang!
I don't need your money.
You promised me!
Galang?
-Hi.
-Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
-Yes.
I was just about to go to your house.
Happy birthday to Sofia.
This is for her.
A prayer set.
It's time Sofia learns how to pray.
Learns about worship.
Galang.
If you can...
...come pray at the mosque.
I've never seen your family
praying at the mosque lately.
If the world feels heavy
on your shoulders...
...ask for help from Allah.
Insha Allah, there will be a way.
Alright. I'll take my leave now.
Okay.
Thank you for the gift.
You're welcome, Galang.
-Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
Dad?
Galang.
What happened?
I was slaughtering a goat.
Dad?
Sofia.
Next year, I want these as a gift.
Please help me put it on,
Dad, I can't see.
Galang?
-What's wrong, Nisa?
-Galang.
My stomach really hurts.
I think it's time.
It's only been 6.5 months.
It's not possible.
But it hurts so much.
It's probably just cramps.
Her optic nerves
were pinched during birth,
and thus severely damaged.
I'm sorry, we couldn't save
your daughter's eyes.
If your wife had come to
the hospital sooner,
it might have been different.
Dearest brothers,
in Surah Al-Mutaffifin
Allah says,
"and the deeds of all evil doers...
...are all recorded
in the book of the damned."
Imam Ibnu Kathir RA conveyed
that Allah SWT says
"Inna kitaabal fujjaari lafee Sijjeen."
And they shall return to Sijjin.
Because the evil deeds
are serious matters,
Allah says that they belong in prison.
A painful punishment awaits them.
Allah says, never be dishonest.
For the deeds of all evil doers
is locked up in sijjin.
Welcome back.
It's been a while
since you lost your sandals, right?
What's wrong?
Is there a problem?
Sometimes, we forget Allah
when there are no problems, right?
Careful, He might give you more problems
just so you'll remember.
Leave me and my family alone.
Galang.
Mom.
Mom?
What's wrong, dear?
My stomach hurts.
How bad is it?
It hurts a lot.
Can I take a look?
Right here?
I wonder why...
I've lost so much.
I want to be the only woman
in Galang's life.
You have sacrificed too much.
Yet you are still not satisfied?
Here.
This is all I have. Take it all.
What matters is I...
...become the only woman in Galang's life.
I beg you.
What is his wife's name?
Nisa.
Who else lives with him at home?
There's Sofia,
their daughter.
And also Galang's mother who is sick.
Among the many evil jinns,
there is one clan of jinn, Anzar,
that is known for its hatred
towards Muslims.
I will communicate with them,
and convince them to possess Nisa.
Then what will happen?
The jinn will kill Nisa
within five nights.
All her blood relatives will die.
Die?
Only those related by blood.
Within five nights, they will all die.
But their daughter is still very young.
-Is there no other way?
-You also had one.
The baby that died in your womb.
Do they care?
To convince jinn Anzar
to help with this black magic,
I will write
the incantation on the shinbone
of a freshly
deceased corpse.
Then wrap it with buffalo intestines.
But I need something from Nisa's body.
Hair, blood, or nails.
You also have to bring her photo.
Nisa's photo.
Alright.
Do what you have to do.
To the jinn who holds power over spirits.
Give the answer.
To the empty spirit and soul.
To the jinn who holds power over spirits.
Irma, what brings you here?
Are you alone?
Yes, I had some errands to run near here.
But Galang is still at the market.
I'm not here to meet Galang.
I'm here for Sofia.
-Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
Did you like my gift?
I really like it, Auntie.
But my mom said
I'm not allowed to wear lipstick yet.
When I'm older, can you teach me?
Of course.
I'll teach you other things too.
Not just lipstick. So you can be pretty.
Your drink, Irma.
Why didn't you bring Aunt Farah
and Wulan with you?
She wasn't ready and I was in a rush.
Besides, if she finds out
I came here empty-handed,
she'll scold me.
Well, that's what parents do.
Be grateful you can still
hear her nagging.
Sometimes, I miss hearing
Galang's mother nagging.
You do?
You're right, Nisa.
I hope Auntie Tety can walk again soon.
And nag us like she used to.
Nisa, can I use the bathroom?
Oh, sure, of course.
Irma?
Yes?
Is the water running?
-Yes, it's running.
-Okay then.
Galang should be home soon.
Do you want to wait?
No need, Nis. I can't stay long either.
Alright, take care then.
Auntie, don't you wanna play
with me a bit longer?
Later...
We'll play again later, okay?
Alright, you promise that
we'll play again.
Auntie, why are you crying?
We'll meet again soon.
No.
I'm not crying.
I should go now.
-That hurts.
-What are you doing here?
It hurts!
I'm just visiting my aunt.
And my niece.
Leave my family alone.
Please don't drag Sofia and Nisa
into this.
Why would I...
...disturb my own family?
After all, we are family, right?
Don't you worry.
Blood will be more powerful.
More than hair.
From the male devils and female devils.
Truly you will not break promises.
For the bearers of knowledge,
bearers of glory.
We seek refuge in you
from all abominations.
Oh, receiver of spirits and empty souls.
Unite me
with Ifrit,
Elzeri, and the Ruler of jinns.
Unite me with Ifrit, Elzeri,
and the Ruler of jinns.
The Ruler of jinns. the Ruler of jinns.
Put this in the dog food.
One portion for each day.
Feed them at night.
After five nights have passed...
...all your wishes will be fulfilled.
She will die.
Along with all her blood relatives.
Starting from tonight.
The first night.
May God forgive all our sins.
THE FIRST NIGHT
God is Great.
God hears whoever praises Him.
God's peace and blessings be upon you.
All praise belongs to God,
Lord of all that exists.
I seek forgiveness from God.
-Nisa. Nisa!
-I seek forgiveness from God.
What's wrong with you, Nis?
There's a buffalo head!
There's nothing, Nisa.
I'm not lying. There was a head...
Do you know what time it is?
It's three in the morning.
I don't have time to listen
to your nonsense.
THE SECOND NIGHT
Galang, where have you been?
The market. Where do you think?
Why did you come home so late?
I was working, Nisa. Working!
Enough with the questions.
I'm sorry, Nisa. I'm tired.
I was just saying.
There is something strange going on
in this house.
Can we talk about it later?
Galang. Wait for me.
Irma, what is wrong with you?
Why do you stay out so late?
The neighbors will talk.
-Leave me alone, Mom.
-Irma, listen to me.
Sis, what's going on?
My bracelet is missing.
I can't find your jewelry in the cupboard.
Where are they?
You used it to pay Ikhsan, right?
That shaman.
You really are a heartless woman.
What?
Heartless?
Yes.
My feelings are numb.
Are you happy?
You're just like mom.
You never supported me.
Enough.
-What's wrong with you?
-Just go!
Wulan?
Mom?
Wulan.
Are you alright?
Allah is Sufficient for us,
and He is the Best Guardian...
...He is the Excellent Protector
and the Excellent Helper.
Mom?
What's wrong?
Mom, what's wrong?
Mother? Oh, God forgive me.
Mother. Mother.
God, forgive me. Mother.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
I...
Please forgive me, Mother.
Mother.
I...
I'm going to change the water mom.
Mother?
Mother!
Mother...
THE THIRD NIGHT
Mrs. Tety is actually older
than all her siblings.
How do you know?
Mrs. Tety has been bedridden for years.
They say it's black magic.
Someone put a curse on her.
-Did you see the body?
-No, I'm scared.
Mom?
God is Great.
God's peace and blessings be upon you.
Peace be upon you and the mercy
and blessings of God.
God, forgive me!
Everybody calm down!
Bayu, help me. Hold Nisa.
The rest of you,
please help carry the body to the back.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed,
with God's name, the
Beneficent and Merciful.
Leave this woman's body.
Who are you?
Telling me to leave?
I am a servant of Allah.
Leave.
Do I have to force you?
God, forgive me.
I want to stay here.
Don't interfere in my business!
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed...
...with God's name, the
Beneficent and Merciful.
God is Great!
O Allah, send blessings upon Muhammad...
...and upon the family of Muhammad.
Nisa.
Praise be to Allah,
the Lord of the Universe.
It's not your fault, Galang.
I think Nisa is possessed by an evil jinn.
Nisa told me something strange
has been going on.
I didn't believe her.
I understand.
God willing,
I will help you find a way out.
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
Liar! You think I don't know
what you've been doing with Irma?
Dad?
Dad, what's wrong?
Nisa.
I'm sorry.
I should have believed you.
You were right.
Something strange is happening
in this house.
Don't worry.
I will ask for help from Aa' Syakir.
This time, it won't be easy.
The jinn that has possessed her
is terrifying.
I often classify it as a hired jinn.
The type of jinn
that is frequently used...
...as a source of black magic
that instills pain...
...and destroys the people you hate.
Black magic has existed since the time
of the Prophet Muhammad PBUH.
Related to the many evil deeds,
narrow, and dark
recorded in the book of the damned.
So, what should I do?
You don't need to worry.
No matter how powerful the jinn is...
...God and His faith will always prevail.
You just need to have faith
and believe in His power.
God willing, I will help you
to the best of my ability.
Put some of this water
on Nisa's forehead before prayer time.
But make sure you perform ablution first.
Nisa?
Nisa!
This is from Aa' Syakir.
Nisa.
Mom is gone.
I only have you and Sofia now.
Please don't do this.
I don't know what to do.
Now you get some rest.
Careful.
THE FOURTH NIGHT
Peace be with you.
Mom?
Forgive me God.
Oh my God, Mom!
Oh, God. Mom.
Oh, God.
Mom!
MRS. FARAH DAUGHTER OF CAHYONO
We'll leave now.
We take our leave now.
Irma.
It's just the two of us now.
It's my fault.
I was wrong, Wulan.
I really am a heartless woman.
This is my fault.
What did you do?
I think Auntie Tety...
...and Mom died because of me.
I went to the shaman again.
Forgive me God.
Forgive me, Wulan.
Oh, God.
What did you do?
Forgive me.
I'm scared.
Tell me.
This is all because of Galang, isn't it?
I had a miscarriage.
I lost Galang's baby.
I was angry.
I didn't think twice
and went to visit the shaman.
That shaman deceived you.
Oh, God, forgive us.
Wulan, the shaman
only asked for Nisa's blood.
He said...
...all of Nisa's blood relatives,
all of Nisa's blood relatives,
will die.
But Mom and Aunt Tety are not
blood relatives of Nisa.
It shouldn't have been like this, Wulan.
It shouldn't.
Then what do you want now?
You are cruel. Heartless.
What happens after this?
Mom died because of this.
That means we're next, right?
Do you want me to die?
What should we do now?
What now?
I'll make things right.
I won't let anything bad happen to you.
You will be fine, Wulan.
Please forgive me.
Mom.
Is Grandma Tety in heaven now?
How do you know for sure
that people who die go to heaven?
It's possible that...
...Grandma Tety will meet
Grandma Farah in hell?
Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
Nisa! Nisa!
Nisa.
Nisa?
Peace be with you.
I seek forgiveness from God.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
O Allah, send blessings upon Muhammad,
and upon the Progeny of Muhammad.
There are preparations we need to make
before Nisa's healing.
Tonight, bring Nisa to the hall
behind the mosque.
What should I do?
I'm afraid of losing her again.
Even though we will face
a very evil and powerful jinn...
...we must not be afraid.
We must believe that we can defeat it.
We have Allah.
Wipe Nisa's face with the holy water
I gave you.
And put a veil over Nisa's head.
Galang.
There is a way to seek forgiveness
from Allah...
...for all the sins
that we have committed.
By doing prayer of repentance.
-Peace be with you.
-And also with you.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you satisfied yet?
Galang.
I am sorry.
This is my fault.
All these deaths...
My mother,
Auntie...
That Jinn...
It was you who've been sending it
all this time?
You're out of your mind.
You're crazy!
You think I'm the only one at fault?
Huh?
You're also at fault!
You're the one who drove me crazy!
You played with my feelings!
But I didn't kill my family!
Okay, fine.
I was wrong.
I was wrong to let a man
like you ruin my life!
I don't care about the consequences.
I just...
I just want to protect my family.
THE FIFTH NIGHT
Wulan.
This is the final night since the ritual.
We need to hurry back to that shaman.
Wulan.
I seek forgiveness from God.
Come here, Irma!
Wulan!
Wake up, Wulan!
It's me, Wulan!
Oh, God.
Sis?
Sister.
Wulan?
Wulan is going to die.
Oh, my God. Wulan! Wulan!
Wulan. Wulan!
Oh, God.
No, no, no!
No, please! Oh, God, no!
No! Wulan, no!
Wulan! Wulan, please no. Oh, God.
Please, don't. Wulan!
Wulan?
Wulan!
No!
God is great.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
We address this
Al-Fatihah reading to Allah...
...and His reward for all
of them. Al Fatihah...
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
All praise is for Allah
Lord of all worlds...
...the Most Compassionate, Most Merciful,
Master of the Day of Judgment.
You (alone) we worship
and You (alone) we ask for help.
Guide us along the Straight Path...
...the Path of those You
have blessed—not those...
...You are displeased with,
or those who are astray.
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you and the mercy
and blessings of Allah.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
Peace be upon you, Prophet of Allah.
Peace be upon you, my beloved,
Messenger of Allah.
Ikhsan!
Where is Ikhsan?
He is not home.
No, wait. Wait, wait!
You have to help me.
You have to help me stop all of this.
It's too late.
A Jinn that has been summoned
cannot be controlled.
Then why did my mother and sister die?
Whose blood did you bring here?
No.
Ikhsan must be inside.
Move.
Move. Get out of my way!
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
God is Great.
Hold her!
Get a rope.
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
Ikhsan!
I don't care!
I don't care if I'm not with Galang!
Save me. Please help me!
I was stupid!
I was wrong.
Ikhsan!
Stop everything. Please, I beg you.
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
Allah, bestow Your favor
on Muhammad...
...and on the family of Muhammad...
...as You have
bestowed Your favor on Ibrahim...
...and on the
family of Ibrahim.
Allah, bless Muhammad
and the family of Muhammad...
...as You have blessed Ibrahim
and the family of Ibrahim...
...You are Praiseworthy,
Most Glorious.
God is Great!
It's my fault. It's all my fault.
I regret everything.
Nisa.
Nisa?
Oh, God.
Keep praying.
What's happening?
There is none worthy of worship
except Allah.
With Your permission, Allah.
No one else should die.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
Allah, there is no
deity except Him...
...the Ever-Living, the
Sustainer of (all) existence.
Neither drowsiness overtakes Him
nor sleep.
To Him belongs whatever is in the heavens
and whatever is on the earth.
Who is it that can intercede
with Him except by His permission?
He knows what is (presently) before them
and what will be after them...
...and they encompass
not a thing...
...of His knowledge except
for what He wills.
His Kursi extends over the heavens
and the earth...
..."and their preservation tires Him not.
And He is the Most High, the Most Great."
I seek forgiveness from God.
You son of a bitch.
You will die just like
Irma's baby that you killed.
And your whole family...
...will perish.
Oh, God. Faiz, get my staff.
-God is Great!
-A'! No, please!
Galang, what we're facing now
is not Nisa anymore...
...but an evil jinn!
-Nisa.
-God is Great!
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
Nisa?
Nisa, wake up.
Please.
Galang, if Nisa is indeed possessed
by a jinn...
...this staff should not harm her.
Nisa, please wake up.
I can't go on without you.
The jinn possessed Sofia.
She's the one controlling everything.
And has caused all those deaths
in your family.
-Galang.
-Sofia.
Do you know why your stomach hurts?
It's because you got your period.
My daughter is a teenager now.
Sofia gave me a fright.
Turns out she just got her period.
It's her first day today.
Only those related by blood.
Within five nights, they will all die.
Mother! Mother!
Mother!
Wulan, no! Oh, God!
Wulan.
Wulan! No! No!
Forgive me, Sofia.
Please forgive me.
I seek refuge in Allah
from Satan the accursed.
God is Great!
A FAMILY WAS FOUND
IN A HORRIFYING STATE
IN THE BASEMENT OF A
MOSQUE IN PANDEGLANG.
THE HUSBAND WAS FOUND
DEAD WITH A BROKEN NECK
WHILE HIS WIFE AND
DAUGHTER WERE UNCONSCIOUS.
THE POLICE ALSO FOUND
THE HUSBAND'S TWO COUSINS DEAD
IN TWO DIFFERENT LOCATIONS.
THE WIFE, WHO WAS IN
CRITICAL CONDITION
WAS RESCUED, NOW EXHIBITS
UNEXPLAINED MEDICAL CONDITIONS.
THE DAUGHTER HAS
FULLY RECOVERED
HAS NO SURVIVING RELATIVES
LEFT TO CARE FOR HER.