..
[I’m finished and right by your place,
should I drop by so I can buy you some beer?]
[Just wait downstairs and I’ll be right there]
..
- Hi.
- Hi!
My name is Håkon and I’m the
new chairman of the apartment complex.
- Hi!
- Is your mom home?
No, unfortunately, she’s not.
Can I help you with something?
Yes, I’m just saying hi
to the neighbors and ...
Your mom hasn’t paid the fees ...
- Oh!
- So I was just wondering if she has been notified?
- She probably just forgot!
She works a lot, but I’ll tell her.
- Yes. You can?
- Yes!
That’s it. Bye.
Bye!
[SANA: Dear Vilde. I don’t think I’ve
told you, but I just wanted to say
that I admire you so much for
being so strong. No matter what
happens, you never give up,
you keep on going. You’re
the first person I would bring with me to
war, and I love you so much.
I’m inviting you to an
Eid party at my place on Saturday. Eid is
a holiday that marks the end of Ramadan.
Saturday is the last day of Ramadan
and I’d like to break the fast with all the
people I love. Lots of food,
a chill atmosphere and only
good people. I’ll be
so happy if you come. Sana]
Mom?
- Mamma? I'm going out.
- Mm ...
Who rang the doorbell?
It was someone collecting signatures.
Oh, ok then.
- Sorry, I lost track of time!
- No worries.
My mom and I got carried away chatting.
- Should we get outta here?
- Yes!
Hurry!
Hey.
- Did you sleep well?
- Mhm.
- I just dreamt something fucked up.
- Yeah, what?
I dreamt that I was at
my old elementary school.
And ...
we were eating lunch outside.
Me and Caroline,
who was my girlfriend in fourth grade.
and then you were walking past
and I was like “Wow, damn”!
And then I walked up to you and was like ...
“Hey, do you wanna date me?”
in front of Caroline.
What did I say?
You said yes, of course.
Yeah?
Of course.
Okay, well ...
I guess that means your dreams aren’t real.
And that’s supposed to mean ...?
That we’re never going to be together.
- Why not?
- Why?
- Because ...
- Because?
- You are ...
- I am? What am I?
- A cheating fuckboy.
- Ouch.
- Hi, Vilde.
- Hi, what are you doing?
Nothing in particular ...
Listen, I wanted to do something nice for
Sana at that Eid-celebration, to show her how much we love her.
Yeah, we can do that.
So I’ve read a bit about Eid and
it’s common to give gifts.
But it’s often just to kids and money and stuff,
and it’d be a bit weird to give her money.
I wanna give her something really special,
so do you have any ideas?
Uhm ...
No, I don’t know.
But we should probably ask someone for some advice,
maybe someone who knows more than us.
Yeah, I agree. We’ll ask a Muslim.
Yes.
Hey, but listen, maybe I’ll
call you up a bit later or something?
- Okay.
- Okay, good bye.
Where were we?
We were talking about whether we should get together.
- I don’t think so.
- I think that was it.
- You don’t? Because I think you may want to.
- No.
You sure?
- Yes, I’m sure.
- Totally sure?
Yes, very.
Eva?
- Hide!
- Why?
Oh, I’m sorry!
Uhm ... I have a guest.
Yeah.
- This is ...
- Hey!
- Chris.
- Hi.
Chris.
Is your name Chris too?
Yeah, no, my name is Anne Marit.
Oh, okay. That makes sense.
- Yeah ...
- Yeah.
I’m sorry for just..
I didn’t know Eva had a boyfriend.
We’re not together.
Yet.
Yes.
But that’s...
I’m sure you’ll figure that out. Okay!
Why did you stand up?
I had to introduce myself! I was raised well.
You have to say hi to people
You could’ve introduce yourself another time!
No. Love me.
One time, he forgot to bring his bike so I had to ...
I had to take ...
You had to take his bike?
- But I’ll text you.
- Yeah, talk later.
Where are you going?
- The A building.
- Okay.
- And you?
- I’m going to the B building.
- Yes ...
- What is it?
- Nothing, is there something?
You go first, because you’re so embarrassed of me.
I’m not embarrassed of you!
You’re embarrassed of me ...
No ...
It’s just ... People...
- You’re embarrassed of me.
- No, I’m not!
I have like this bad feeling.
I have this nervous, sinking feeling ...
- Hey!
- Why?
- Because girls are good at side eyeing.
- You’re the best, so you’ll win over everyone!
But think about it, if I’m invited
so they can like fuck with me or something.
That won’t happen. She just wants peace, right? It’s like this ...
Declaration of peace to invite someone to their Eid celebration.
Exactly what is an Eid party?
What do you do? Is there any alcohol?
- You can manage one party without alcohol?
- Yes, I was just asking!
Yeah, sorry, but I don’t think there’s going to be any alcohol.
But I’ll be there anyway.
See you there!
Hey, boys.
Where have you been?
Where the fuck have you been?
I went to McDonald’s.
McDonalds?
Did you sit by yourself at McDonald’s?
- No ... Yes ...
- Alone.
Is that so fucking ...
Imagine, him sitting by himself,
eating a burger at McDonalds.
What the fuck is up with you? It’s McDonald’s.
- Where did you get money?
- Yeah, I was also wondering about that.
- I borrowed money.
- From who?
- Julian Dahl.
- The ATM.
I don’t get why you dislike Julian Dahl. He’s rich!
It’s always about money! He doesn’t even know
Jonas and he can just ask?
I saw him go to school in a suit one time, that’s a bit weird.
- Fucking Julian Dahl.
- Julian fucking Dahl.
[Hey, this is maybe a bit far out,
but you dated Eva once. I’m crushing
a bit on her, but I don’t really get her,
from one bro to another, do you have
any advice? Like what kind of flowers
does she like hahaha]
- The fuck?!
- What’s up?
Okay, I just got a message.
- From Penetrator-Chris.
- Penetrator-Chris? What does he want?
- Listen... “Hey, this is maybe a bit far out”.
- Yeah, I think so too.
"But you dated Eva once.
I’m crushing a bit on her."
- "But I don’t really get her,
from one bro to another, do you have any advice?"
- Bro?
"Like what kind of flowers does she like hahaha."
I love that ending.
- Are you bros?
- Ending the message with “hahaha”.
- No. Why should I give him advice?
- Why not?
- It’s Penetrator-Chris!
- He’s not good enough for her!
- I think he’s pretty hot, though.
- Eva is like up here! And he’s like ...
- Hi!
Hey, Mahdi? We’re buying Sana a gift to show her
how much we love her and we don’t really know what.
I was wondering if there are any Muslim traditions
of what to give as a gift on Eid?
Uhm, I’m Catholic.
- Oh, sorry.
- You don’t have to apologize.
Who should I ask then?
If you wanna tell Sana how much you love her, -
Tell her in a card! Or what, baby?
- Yeah.
- Do that.
Vilde?
What’s up with Chris and Eva?
I don’t know, I think they’re just sleeping together.
Eva is maybe a bit in love with him, but ...
I don’t think he’s keen on something more.
- Bye!
- Bye. Give me a kiss before you leave.
- Bye.
- Bye, baby.
But fuck! With Penetrator-Chris.
That was brave of him.
It’s brave to send a text to the ex and ask about flowers.
Yeah, yeah. Do you think it’s like Vilde said
or is he serious or just fucking around?
I actually think it was awesome of him to text you.
People change and maybe he has changed! People change!
It’s pretty awesome to text the ex and ask about your girl.
It was pretty brave and it seems like he’s serious.
He was talking about flowers!
Who’s the last person you gave flowers to?
My mom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
You won’t get a lot of flowers from Mahdi, at least.
He’s an alright guy.
If Eva likes him, and he likes Eva, just give him some advice.
Yeah, but he’s not like he seems. Remember when we
had that beef with Yakuza?
All that planning was me and Chris who did and he’s an alright guy.
He was the one who wanted to stand up against
the biggest douches in all of Oslo.
He had your back?
Anyways, it turned out he was a really nice guy and, -
[Fuck flowers, take it down a notch, just
ask if she wants to watch Fresh Prince and
eat nachos or something.]
And we thought ‘fuck it’,
let’s try to take them Yakuza on ...
Were you keen on him?
- Huh?
- Were you keen on him?
No, no, no, but ...
Was he the one who knocked
that guy down with the bottle?
No, that was William.
Poor guy.
- What happened to the guy after?
- He deserved it. He’s the worst cunt in all of Oslo.
Did he pass out?
Almost. I was in the middle of the fight ...
- Who?
- Did you fight?
Yeah, it was this rich preppy guy from Bærum.
Who won? Is it fun to have beef?
[Hey, sorry for being lame, come
with me to a party on Saturday?]
- They had a plan of beating up everyone in their way, they had to be stopped.
- That’s fucked.
It was fucked! They beat up Jonas!
- That’s not cool.
- No! They did?
Yeah, without any reason!
- What’s up with your William hair?
- That’s not William hair.
I’ll show you William hair.
- Can’t we think of anything else to give her?
- Like, giving her a card...
- I don’t know, can’t we perform something? Make a...
- Yes! Something like...
- Something Moroccan?
- Something you’ll remember very well.
I don’t want to perform ...
[Hi Chris, do you have some
money I can borrow?
Like 1000 kr [118 USD]?
It’s okay with less too,
I promise you’ll get
it back on the 1st of
July, plus the 750 [88 USD]
I owe you from beforehand.
There’s just this top on sale
right now that
I’ve wanted for a really long time.
And I don’t want to ask mom
because I’ve borrowed
a lot from her lately.]
It would be fun.
- We can hold a speech!
- Yes!
- You can write it, right?
- Yes.
- And then we can ...
- Hi!
Hi.
Are you going to that Eid party at Sana’s?
Yeah.
- Are you going too?
- Yes, or uhm ...
Jonas asked if I wanted to come.
And I was a little stressed because I don’t really
know anyone else who’s going.
But then I thought about Kosegruppa.
Yay ...
And then I thought that maybe you’re going?
Yeah, we’re going.
We’ll take care of you.
Great!
We have to take care of each other.
- See you later.
- Good bye!
- But ok ... Speech.
- Yes.
- What are we going to write?
- Come in! Hi.
- Hi, do you have a few minutes?
I have two hours, seventeen minutes and fourteen seconds
until I’m going on summer vacation!
Welcome, Christina Berg.
Sit down.
- How do you know my name?
- I know the name of every student in this school.
- What can I help you with?
- Uhm ...
I just have this friend who ...
That’s not 'just' that.
There are lots of people who don’t have friends.
Lots of people who are lonely.
Take the retirement homes in Oslo, for example.
They’re overflowing with old people.
Think about that.
All of their friends are dead.
No one comes to visit and they’re all by themselves.
All those people have, are the memories from a lost time.
That’s so fucking true!
I haven’t thought about that before,
but if you get really, really old, -
And all your friend just ... die ...
- Then it’s not awesome to live at all.
- No.
Tell me about your friend.
Yeah ...
I have a friend who I’m pretty worried about.
I don’t think she has a good home life and ...
I think her mom is pretty depressed.
I feel like I should be a better friend, -
But I’m not any good at that stuff and I can’t ...
I can’t talk to her about it.
So I was wondering if maybe you
could talk to her about it.
You know what I think this sounds like, Christina?
I think it sounds like you’re lying.
- Are you?
- No!
Because what it sounds like is:
“I’m not good at that stuff”.
But I think you are.
I’m not! I’m seriously really bad at that stuff!
As soon as there is just a little conflict, I just ...
Everyone thinks conflicts are uncomfortable!
But that doesn’t mean you should avoid them!
Do you know what, Christina Berg? I think you
should be very careful with these “truths” -
You tell to yourself about yourself.
I don’t see what you’re describing
right now. Do you know what I see?
I see a girl who’s more
than enough of a good friend.
I see a girl who
Talks to her friend.
And I see a girl who loves conflict!
A bit over the top at the end.
- But you know what I want?
- Yes.
[Did anyone remember to buy mustard and ketchup?]
[Did anyone remember to
buy mustard and ketchup?]
[We’re already in Urraparken.
When are you coming?]
[I’m waiting for him.
We’ve bought
enough beer, right?]
[It’s important!]
[For the third time,
we’ve bought enough beer]
[Sorry. I just
want his birthday to be perf.]
[You’re overreacting, he doesn’t
give a fuck about ketchup]
[Let me overreact.
You don't know
what he has to deal with
the other 363 days of the year.]
[He’s way too good for me]
[That’s not what I see. I see a boyfriend
who’s more than good enough. Someone who
has made a pretty mad boy into a pretty happy boy.]
[What’s up with you, Chris?]
- Hey.
- You can open it yourself.
- Beer at school? Amazing!
- Cheers.
- Did you find your film?
- No, I didn’t.
- I can’t find it. I don’t know where it is.
- It’s on YouTube!
It’s on Youtube? That helps me a lot.
There are like ten billion videos there.
But if you don’t understand the title,
you won’t get to see the film.
You can’t give me a little hint?
- It starts with G.
- G?
I tried "Yellow curtains", but that wasn’t it.
You’re not that far off.
"Green curtains"?
"Grey curtains"?
- "The Genius of Hartvig Nissen".
- I would never write that.
- What is it then?
- I’m not telling.
- "God"? God, that’s me.
- Yes, the film is called ‘God’.
- Good. I’ll check it out later.
- Do you think I would call a film ‘God’?
- Yeah, if it was about me.
- That’s so pretentious.
Get a room!
Fags!
What did he say?
What?!
- What did you say?
- It’s fucking disgusting!
Fuck! Huh? Do you think you can go
around and just do that stuff? Come here!
Fucking cunt face! You’re fucking ugly, you know that?
I can’t with that stuff. He can’t say stuff like that!
- Look at me.
- Yes. Yes!
It’s fine. Okay?
We’ll take it totally chill.
And we’ll go meet our friends.
And we’ll go to the park.
And drink beer.
Okay?
Yeah?
- Shall we leave?
- Yes.
What are you doing?
- Can’t you help me instead?
- I can’t write.
You don’t know how to write?
I know you know how to write.
Tell me a bit about her then.
[Hi, in the speech for Sana, you have to remember
to include how insanely strong she is. I don’t think
many people understand how much bullshit she
has to take. Just something I thought of. ]
She seems a bit badass.
No. Or. Not really.
It’s just on the outside, like.
Because she has a really soft side.
Like if it hadn't been for Sana,
then we wouldn’t be laying here.
It’s not because of that e-mail.
But once upon a time -
There was a person who persuaded me -
To try and understand you, you know.
But! But she’s a bit into,
or she’s really into science, right?
So I thought maybe that I
could write something about that.
Or like … Include something about science.
So I thought that, or I tried to
write what was inside Sana’s atoms.
Yes.
But it’s just turning into ...
No. It’s just a mess.
Linn! She’s called me 10 times today.
I’m not kidding.
Yes, Linn? Hello.
- Hi.
- Yeah, hi.
I was just wondering if you could remember
to buy toilet paper on your way home.
Yes, I just. I don’t know how long I’ll be.
So if it’s, if it’s a real emergency
you’re just going to have to buy it yourself, okay?
Okay.
- When are you coming home then?
- I don’t know yet, Linn.
I’m just going to have to see,
because I have a few things to do and stuff.
- Are you going to sleep at home tonight?
- Yeah, yes, I’m sure I will. Maybe.
Maybe we can watch Twenty Years with Espen Eckbo together?
- Yeah, maybe. Okay?
- Okay.
- Bye.
Okay.
Atoms. Science.
- Didn’t you have science?
- Yeah.
Well, then help me.
You can write about the butterfly effect.
What’s that?
A concept within the chaos theory.
Look.
You look so good, Linn!
You’re so pretty.
- Can’t I just wear the blue summer dress?
- No, you can’t just wear the blue summer dress!
Okay, this is the most important holiday to Muslims.
It’s not a whore and pimp party.
- But do I have to wear a veil?
- Yes, you have to wear a veil, Linn.
It’s like if Sana showed up to your
place on Christmas in sweatpants.
Do you think your mother, Mette, would’ve been happy about that?
She wouldn’t. She would’ve been angry.
Linn ... What’s up with you these days?
Do you think Noora is going to move out?
Come sit down.
You know that Noora loves us a lot, right?
And that.. Even though
we’re not fans of William ...
Noora is much better than him.
But she should be allowed to live her life, right?
And I think we just have
to be very good friends to her -
And support her
no matter what she does.
And I think that even though
she doesn’t always show it, -
Noora loves us very much.
And wants us to be happy.
And we’re going to be happy.
And you know why?
Because we have each other.
And I’m going to take care of you.
And you’re going to take care of me.
It’s you and me against the world.
The two of us against the world.
You look so nice!
I also want one.
A veil, but I can’t.
Should we drink some Pepsi Max?
You had a booger.
- He’s the one who bought the toilet paper rolls.
- Oh, that’s right!
- Where did they end up?
I just sold them to some friends
at the Mosque. Nothing big.
Oh, okay.
- Eid mubarak! Eid mubarak.
- Hi!
- Hi. Welcome.
- Thank you.
- And I just wanted to say Eid mubarak!
- Eid mubarak!
- Eid mubarak.
- You look so nice!
Thanks! I’m the one who chose
the outfits for tonight.
I went to Grøndland and did some shopping.
- Hijab and everything.
- Hijab and everything!
And I brought a little present!
I brought a gift for the hostess.
It’s two boreks that I put in a nice box.
- That’s very nice of you.
- You can put it on the table for the guests.
- Yes, thank you so much.
- And I didn’t find an Eid mubarak card, so I bought
a Merry Christmas card, because it’s the same.
- Aww, thank you.
- And you look very nice. Much nicer than ... Yeah.
- Thanks.
Very pretty. And you too, even though you
haven’t dressed up. In your own way.
You didn’t go for an ‘original’ outfit,
but you look very nice.
We’re more cultured.
Are you going to say anything?
- It’s been a while since you’ve had this?
- We ate this every day after school.
Why don’t you try making it yourself?
- There are so many spices and herbs and ...
- Expensive?
No, it’s not really expensive, it’s just
a totally different way of cooking.
Can’t we just have an afternoon where we ... I mean you,
just make a lot of Moroccan food for me?
Yeah, it’s a date.
- Great.
- And some delicious tea.
These potatoes are really good.
Yeah, it’s good? Let me have a taste.
They’re not like Norwegian potatoes.
Delicious!
Potato salad.
- Are those just normal meatballs?
- No, it’s in a pretty hot sauce.
- Chili!
- Hot sauce, yeah.
- Are we going on a vacation together?
- What kind of vacation?
I wanna do stuff with you.
We’re doing that anyway.
Yeah, but ... It would be awesome
to go abroad or something.
But I’m so impulsive - I can’t plan that stuff.
I can check out plane tickets
to Morocco or something.
Seriously?
Yeah. Wouldn’t that be cozy?
The two of us in Marrakech?
- Yeah.
I’ve always wanted to go.
Then I’ll check it out.
Dad sent me a lot of money for summer, so ...
Chill! Plus all the tips I get at Kaffebrenneriet.
Yeah, right.
Where?
- Isn’t your car ...?
- The car?
Wow.
It’s not far.
We haven’t done it in that car, have we?
No. Let’s do it.
- Hi.
- Hi!
It’s just that Linn wanted to say something.
I don’t know what.
But she really wanted to talk a bit.
We just wanted to say
that we love you a lot.
And that if you want to move in
with William, we support you.
Aww! Oh my God, you’re so cute, but I haven’t ...
It’s so nice that you’re supportive.
That makes me very happy.
But I’m not going to move.
- Aren’t you going to move in with William?
- No.
You’re choosing us over William?
I’m not choosing anyone over anyone. I just ...
We’re just not moving in together yet.
Yeah, but you’re choosing us over William.
Oh my God, then we’re ... We’re Kollektivet together!
- Yeah.
Yeah! Kollektivet! Kollektivet!
Jump and dance and be happy.
Oh, I have an idea! William can
move in with us and we’ll be four!
It’ll be cheaper with toilet paper and dish soap
and everything that’s cheap and good.
Maybe if we make a Powerpoint presentation and
sell it a bit better, you can decide later.
If you agree, Linn? Do you agree?
It’ll be so fucking good.
It’ll be a fashion Kollektiv! We can have guests over and ...
Oh! You smell good!
- Thanks you too.
- Yeah, he does.
Thanks. New perfume.
Eskild! Hands off.
My man.
Yeah. Your man, but when we all move in together,
we’re going to share a lot of stuff.
- Him? No.
- Yeah, him too.
Shampoo and William and ...
Dish soap and everything else.
We can have Sunday board game night
where we can play Ludo and stuff.
- The three of us can do that.
- But then we’ll only be three, not four.
It’s so boring with only three.
You can have the blue chip, Linn can have the green one.
You can have the red one. Because of the lipstick!
Not because of something else.
- Good watermelon.
- You’ve had that before, at least.
It’s not Moroccan.
Yeah. Even fed me lots of delicious food a few moments ago. Very, very good.
He has had it before.
We have to celebrate!
The both of us got 6’es!
- Yeah, I got a 6 at least.
- I got a 6 too.
Why are you lying?
I did!
You didn’t get a 6.
- You didn’t know ... I had to help you!
- Yeah, you helped me and then I got a 6.
I didn’t help you that much.
Wow! You tried to help me
a bit, but not enough.
No, but I thought ‘Wow, he doesn’t even know the basics’.
You can’t have gotten more than a 5, tops.
- I got a 6.
- You can tell me.
- No.
- Tell me you got a 5. It’s okay.
I’m just getting shy because you’re so beautiful today!
Awww, thanks.
- Like seriously, you’re very beautiful.
- Thanks.
But uhm ... No.. I got a 5.
- Yeah, you got a 5?
- Yeah, but don’t tell anyone.
Yeah, but it’s ok.
I got a 6!
- Hey, girl.
- Hey.
- Good food.
- Very good.
So good. I think I’m on
plate number four or something.
Okay, I have to say something.
What?
I just wanted to say that if ...
If you need someone to talk to ...
I’m here.
Okay?
We can talk about difficult stuff.
Do you know why you’re
my very best friend?
It’s because ...
No matter how bad of a day I’m having, -
You always find a way to make me laugh.
It’s not like you always have to talk.
Sometimes, it just helps to
pretend that you’re fine.
But it’s important that you
have someone to talk to, right?
I do.
We talked about going to Morocco.
Should be bring the guys?
Of course, it’s a boys’ trip.
Boys’ trip in Morocco. It can go very wrong. It’s worth a shot.
- Hi. Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, good. I was just wondering
who’s going to hold Sana’s speech.
Wow! Ingrid, do you want to try?
The closest thing I’ve tried is one of those juice cleanses,
and it didn’t work very well.
Yeah, but that’s just drinking juice. They can’t drink.
- You can’t even drink?
- No.
- Not even water?
Then this has to be fantastic.
A celebration with lots of food and ...
Yeah, I know, right?
I just had some salad before. With tomatoes and ...
- Tomatoes? Ew. I don’t like them.
- Why not?
- They’re slimy and gross.
- They’re not. You eat ketchup all the time. That’s tomatoes.
No, it’s not! It’s the stuff
inside the tomato that’s gross.
- Yeah, but like..
- The mushy stuff.
- Just don’t eat that part then.
- Eat the part around it? Yeah, that’s good.
You don’t have a lot of delicious stuff on your plate either.
What’s that purple stuff?
- That’s ...
- Yeah.
I think it’s ...
- You think it’s better than tomatoes?
- I haven’t tried it. It was okay.
It seemed very delicious.
There’s lots of good food here!
Have you tried these?
- No.
- They’re so good, you have to try them.
- I didn’t even know they had that here.
- They’re like meatballs. Like the best I’ve ever had.
- I know, right?
- Where?
I found them at the other end of the table.
In a big pot.
Hey.
Who are you?
Chris.
Your new boyfriend.
Hi, my new boyfriend.
What’s even happening right now?
I think we’ve been ditched.
You have a little ...
You have something there.
- Here?
- No, on the other side.
Where? Here?
Take it off!
Eva, do you wanna hold
the speech for Sana?
[Hey, girl. Is the party any good?]
[Really  good]
[I’ve been here today.]
[One day, I’m bringing you there]
It’s time for the speech.
Speech, speech, speech!
I didn’t write it. It was Noora.
And William!
And Isak helped a bit.
Dear Sana.
This speech is for you.
And you’re getting it because
what you’re inviting us to today, -
Overthrows American
presidents tomorrow.
We live in a chaotic world where
it’s difficult to understand the rules.
Because why are some people poor,
and other people rich?
Why do some people have to be refugees,
while others are safe?
Why are some people spit on
in the street?
And why is it that sometimes, even though you try
to do something good, it’s still met with hate?
It’s not weird that people give up,
that they stop believing in the good.
But thank you so much
for not giving up, Sana.
Because even though it sometimes feels like it,
no one’s ever alone.
Each and every one of us
is a part of the big chaos.
And what you do today,
has an effect tomorrow.
[We should maybe ask someone for advice.]
It can be hard to say,
exactly what kind of effect.
And you usually can’t see
how everything fits together.
[We have to take care of each other.]
But the effects of your actions,
are always there. Somewhere in the chaos.
In a hundred years,
we may have machines that can, -
Predict the effect of every action.
But until then, we can trust this:
Fear spreads.
But:
Fortunately, love does too.