- Have you heard they started their bus already?
- No?
One month into high school
and they started a bus.
Ingrid... I miss you.
You look like a slut.
She seemed cool.
Maybe I can get a friend of yours?
You invited people to a cabin trip
that was supposed to be just us.
Two guys?!
- Can I see your messages, then?
- I already told you it's ridiculous!
Why don't you just trust me?
SHAME
SATURDAY, 5:11 P.M.
- I'll call you later, okay?
- Yeah.
Eva... I'm sorry.
If I knew how important this cabin trip
was for you, I wouldn't have invited the guys.
I didn't know
it wasn't that important to you.
It was important to me!
But...
It's important to me to
also spend time with my friends.
It used to be important to you, too.
It is important to me.
But it's not important to me to
spend time with your friends.
I said you could bring friends!
- Can't you just--
- Get some friends?
That's not what I meant.
But it's what you're thinking.
I don't know what the right answer is.
Just be completely honest.
Completely honest?
Eva, you are the coolest girl I know.
You're pretty, sweet, smart, and funny.
But...
I don't know what the problem is.
You have to find new friends!
Get yourself new friends!
Anyone who gets to be your friend
is really lucky.
- Don't know what to say, huh?
- I nailed it.
You nailed it.
Hope you had a nice trip!
Love you! Mom.
Noora has accepted your friend request.
Congratulations on having me as a friend!
Hey girl!
Hey girl! W
Hey girl! Wh
Hey girl! Wha
Hey girl! What
Hey girl! What'
Hey girl! What's
Hey girl! What's u
Hey girl! What's up
Hey girl! What's up?
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed t
I pressed th
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the
I pressed the s
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the se
I pressed the sen
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send
I pressed the send b
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send bu
I pressed the send but
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send butt
I pressed the send butto
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button
I pressed the send button a
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button an
I pressed the send button and
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and s
I pressed the send button and so
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so i
I pressed the send button and so it
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it w
I pressed the send button and so it wa
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was
I pressed the send button and so it was j
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was ju
I pressed the send button and so it was jus
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just
I pressed the send button and so it was just "
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H"
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H".
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". H
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". Ha
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". Hah
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". Haha
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". Haha.
Hi, is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
"Hi" is what I meant. Wanted to write "Hi", but then
I pressed the send button and so it was just "H". Haha.
MONDAY, 10:29 A.M.
Hey.
How are you doing?
I'll sit here, then.
Hi. Or... H?
H. H.
- Did we have homework over the autumn break?
- Yes.
- Fuck!
- Eva?
What does the main character of this story do?
She feels alone.
Noora, I don't want you to respond for Eva.
She hadn't found her homework yet.
I was just helping. You asked it the wrong way.
The right way would be:
What are the main characters of the story like?
You're right. I'm sorry!
- I lived in Madrid.
- Okay, okay.
That's why I don't have friends. In Oslo.
Oh.
So what's your excuse?
Strong body odor.
...I got it, listen. "Cultural relativism..."
TUESDAY, 11:50 A.M.
- How did you pronounce it?
- Yeah, "cultural relavitism".
- No, it's not "relavitism", it's "relativism".
- Oh, yeah.
You should have gotten a 6, but you got a 5.
You're not so damn smart after all.
- Hi! Thanks for last time.
- Hi!
I can't remember if I greeted you properly.
I was a bit out of it.
- Vilde.
- Eva.
I just wanted to say that
it was so nice of you to help me!
No, no. It was nothing!
We were wondering
if you're already on a russ bus?
- No.
- That's perfect!
We just formed a completely new bus group,
and we really want you to join.
I don't know, I haven't really started
thinking about russ time.
It's pretty important to think about it,
if you want to be on a bus.
I don't know what it's like in Trondheim,
but here in Oslo
you have to start planning really early,
otherwise you end up on a bad bus,
or you have to be a walking russ.
Being a russ is not
just about russ time,
it's also about being social
and coming together.
Yes, think of it a like a sect, right?
Once you're in, you can't get out.
It all ends in a collective suicide
in a hookup ring at Tryvann,
on the night of the 17th of May in 2018.
She's just joking.
Would you like to join a bus meeting?
Friday, after school.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- Yeah?
That's so cool!
If you have any friends, just take them with you!
- I can ask around.
- See you later, then.
- What the fuck was that?
- What?
She was sucking on that spoon,
and looking him straight in the eyes.
- Chris?
- Yes!
Who is she?
THURSDAY, 2:02 P.M.
H. As in, "Have you got a drug problem?"
Or H as in, "Have you got any plans for Friday?"
Hi!
Hi.
- Vilde, this is Noora.
- Hi.
- I was going to ask if you talked to Chris?
- No.
We can't have the bus meeting at hers,
her mom is having a wine reception.
And we can't have it at mine,
because it's too much stress.
- So I was wondering if we can do it at yours?
- My place?
Yes! But how many are coming?
- Do you want to join?
- For what?
- Bus meeting.
- Bus... meeting, what?
We're going to make the world's coolest russ bus.
Do you want to join?
No.
- Then we'll be three.
- Hi, guys, say hi to Sana, she wants to join.
Yeah... how do you know each other?
We met at a Ramadan programme
in the mosque.
She's joking. We have German together.
- But you want to come to our bus meeting?
- Yes.
Yeah... is that okay, then?
- What's the problem?
- No…
Since you're Muslim, isn't it true that
Muslims aren't allowed to be russ?
No, it's punished by stoning.
- When is the meeting?
- Tomorrow. Who's hosting?
- Me.
- Just text me your address, so I can GPS it.
- Auf Wiedersehen!
It means "see you later".
- She can't be on our bus.
- Why not?
- We'll give her a chance, she was really cool.
- We? You're not even on our bus.
- No, but if she's joining, so am I.
- Awesome!
Shit!
FRIDAY, 6:50 PM
We have a really big advantage
over the other bus groups.
I already bought a lot of toilet paper.
Vilde managed to buy toilet paper for
40,000 kroner with a credit card for another bus.
Anyway, we're left with a profit of
60,000 kroner. So I've made a budget.
According to this budget,
you need to make 50,000 kroner
in addition to the toilet paper sales.
So I need all of you to have an individual plan,
for how to make the rest of the money.
- What is it?
- We're wasting time on toilet paper.
No use having a budget
without enough people.
It's important that we
have a grip on the budget.
Listen,
we're the biggest losers at school.
If we don't want to end up in a loser van,
we need a strategy.
- We're not the biggest losers of the school!
- Weren't you thrown out of another bus?
- I wasn't exactly thrown out...
- Yes you were.
Listen, Hilde. It'll be really hard
to work together, if you're in denial.
Just acknowledge that we're losers?
Do you think so yourself?
Hello?! I'm a Muslim girl
in this white, faithless, country.
I'm the biggest loser of them all.
- You talk really maturely.
- Thanks.
But what do you want us to do?
First, we need to get more girls for the bus.
Cool girls. How do we do that?
- Ask them?
- Wrong.
We ask no one. We want the cool girls to ask us.
But first,
we need to get something we don't have.
It's a four-letter word.
- "Spenn".
- Cred.
- "Spenn" has five letters, Chris.
- Do we know any '97 guys?
Okay, then we need to find out
which of the '97 guys have the best bus,
get ourselves invited to bus parties,
and get seats.
Any ideas on how we'll do that?
- You guys have to hook up with them.
- Are you serious?
- "You guys"?
- I'm not hooking up!
Okay, so we'll hook up.
What will you contribute?
Are you kidding me?
I'm saving your lame meeting
with a good, strategic plan,
and you're wondering what I'll contribute?
- Does anyone have a boyfriend?
- I do.
- How old is he?
- He's a '99.
- Dump him.
- You're not serious now?
She's the prettiest of us all.
It's a waste if she has a boyfriend.
But...
- Honestly, now. This is really stupid.
- What is?
You can't sit here asking us
to use our sexuality in exchange for cred!
- That's... you're crazy.
- No, I'm honest.
Norwegian girls exchange sex for
money, popularity, and affirmation every day.
You might not agree with that,
me neither.
But you can't pretend this is news to you.
It's your culture!
So if you think it's crazy,
I suggest you go out there and change it
instead of sitting here
criticizing it.
But it's a bit too much to ask Eva to
break up with her boyfriend.
It was a suggestion. If she loves her boyfriend,
then that has more weight than what I say.
She can think for herself, she's not a child.
I have a good feeling about this.