Watch where you're going!
Hey.
What's up?
Neh...
Not much.
Is Mahdi still mad at me?
No one's mad at you, man.
You sure?
Yeah.
We're just worried, man.
We don't really get what your thing is.
My thing?
Yeah!
You've been...
Acting so strange.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about that. It's just...
A lot is happening right now.
Lately.
Family and stuff as well.
And I can't sleep, so...
I lose my temper like, so damn quickly.
But I'm sorry about that.
Okay...
But... Let me know,
If you want to talk about it.
I don't know, but there's...
That's what I'm thinking as well. That...
Yeah.
When you're in love...
You think love is just like in the movies.
But...
That's not how it works.
I...
I mean, I seriously thought William and
I would be together forever.
It ends where it ends, you know...
No one lives happily ever after.
You know, because in...
Real life...
Like, in the end...
No one's willing to sacrifice anything
for love in 2016.
Did I wake you?
What are you doing here?
No, just... Uh, Eskild
brought a guy home.
So, I just moved here.
The walls are pretty thin in the
living room, to put it that way.
Yeah, well the walls aren't so fucking
thick here either, though?!
I, I need to sleep!
And I can't sleep when you lie here and...
talk a lot of shit!
It's 2 AM! Have some respect!
Okay...?
Yeah. I'm sorry, but...
I have to sleep!
Yeah, I get that.
I...
Of course, I can...
I can talk to Eva tomorrow.
Yeah...
Say hi, though.
I'll do that.
And...
William is an...
an idiot if he gives up on
the two of you.
Good night, Isak.
G'night, Noora.
That'll be 22.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot. Bye!
Do you have more cheese sandwiches?
I can heat one up.
Can you heat one up for me as well?
Yes!
That'll be 25.
Uh, I think there's one crown missing.
There you go.
Thank you.
Hey.
No... cardamom?
Cardamom.
No, so...
- But, uh...
- I think I gotta go.
The urine just kept
running out of her?
Yeah.
It was just running out, you know.
She had started working out,
and so it just kept running down
her pants, and into her shoes.
She was very upset, though.
I see. But, uh...
I mean, it does get very loose
if you don't squeeze at all.
Didn't she squeeze at all, then, or?
You know what, I asked
if she had taken that test.
I mean, I said
"Have you put your finger inside?"
And then squeeze real good.
And you know what she said then?
She didn't feel a thing...!
No...
Isak Valtersen.
She was almost on her way
over to Aleris.
You know, start having surgery and such.
Yes.
Just have a seat.
Thanks.
You're...
You're the school doctor?
Yeah, I mean, not exactly a doctor.
Yeah, kinda.
It said... It said doctor on...
Mhm. Well, that sign is from 1962.
What can I do for you?
I'm having trouble sleeping lately.
Yeah, I've had a lot of
trouble sleeping lately.
And it's starting to affect
school and stuff.
That's shitty.
Yeah.
So, I was wondering if I could
get some pills or something.
Because, yeah...
Even though, even though
my problem isn't the worst...
Sleep deprivation is very serious.
You have to think about how many
accidents could've been prevented
If people hadn't fallen asleep
behind the wheel, for example.
I don't... I don't drive a car, though.
No. But you're moving around in traffic...
Yeah.
And that's one inattentive moment, and then
'Bam!', you slam into a
semi truck, break your
neck, and get paralyzed
from the neck down.
You'll go straight into a wheelchair.
It happened to a friend of mine,
she's still in that chair.
Isak.
For how long have you had trouble sleeping?
It's been a while, really.
But it's been worse over
the past couple of weeks.
Like...
Last night I slept for maybe...
One hour.
Yeah.
We'll refer you to BUP then.
(= Child and youth psychiatric polyclinic)
What does that mean?
It means that you'll
get to talk to someone
who can help sort out some of
the thoughts in your head.
No. I'm not doing any of that.
No.
No, it's not like that...
No. I'm not going to do that. Then...
I'm completely serious, I'm not
doing something like that.
Isak.
Do you like other people?
Sure, yeah?
Mhm.
Because you see...
Every person is an island. ("Kvart mennske
er ei øy", a poem by Tarjei Vesaas)
And the only bridge across to others
Is through words.
And as long as we don't talk to each other
We end up becoming lonely little islands
That are high on pills. Just like Ibiza,
do you get what I'm saying?
No.
No...
I understand that, because I mixed
in a poem by Inger Hagrup
So it didn't make total sense
But the point is
That you can't keep isolating yourself.
Everything is harder on your own.
Hey.
Don't you have someone you can talk to?
Do you have any plans for tonight, or...?
Nah, I don't really know.
I was just thinking I'd...
Go home and watch a movie or something.
Okay.
What are you doing now, though?
Now...
Now I was just thinking of going home.
What about you?
Will you join me for a Kebab?
I've got money.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Who would say no to Kebab.
No one.
- Can you hold...
- Yeah!
Where should we...
Where should we go?
Over there.
Not over there?
No, not over there, because...
Dressed. And he was like...
Wearing a shirt and everything.
And I saw that he was flirting with a girl
And I thought like, "Alright."
And then...
And I saw that he was standing with
that girl, then he leaned forward
And then he started vomiting...
Like crazy.
On, like, on her feet.
And he just kept vomiting.
And then he stopped for a few seconds.
And then she had time to start
yelling, like, "What the fuck?!"
And then he started vomiting even more.
It came out like a pressure washer,
and it was absolutely awful.
I was laughing so much!
The ones who vomit are always
the ones you'd least expect.
Yeah!
And... Yeah, I felt really bad for him.
Yeah.
You know...
You know that thing about me
being a little weird lately...?
Mhm?
It's...
It's because of a person I like.
That, uh... Emma?
No, not Emma.
Take a guess.
A guess?
I can't guess...
Try.
Is it Vilde?
Vilde?!
Who do you think I am?! Vilde?!
Yeah, I don't fucking know! What...
No...
Can't you just tell me?
I'll give you a hint.
A hint?
It's not a girl.
Hmm.
Is it me?
No!
You?!
No, no, no!
What the fuck?
Yeah, I don't fucking know.
Just tell me then.
"No, no, no!"
What, am I completely unattractive or what?
No, not like that, but...
No, it's not you.
Is it that...
Is it that guy from Vilde's revue group?
Yeah.
What's his name?
Even.
Good...
Good-looking guy, though.
What?
Yeah? What else am I supposed to say?
I don't even know myself.
But...
What's the thing between the two of you?
Nah...
Nah, I'm not actually sure, right now...
I don't understand shit, because he's a
really back and forth kind of guy
And...
And he has a girlfriend.
Oh, I see.
I think it's mine.
Hey.
Nah, I'm eating a Kebab is all.
Tomorrow?
Okay. Where?
I'm not sure I can be bothered going
that far just for a party...
(Cheese toastie without cardamom.) (Meanwhile in
another universe: Cheese toastie with cardamom.)
Okay, I'll see you there, then.
Maybe... Okay, bye.
What's that?
It's from Even.
Like, he's got to break up
with his girlfriend.