Toughes girl, real!
- You can not handle the ball.
-I can handle it better than you do.
-What?
-I do not really want to be there,
- when Sana learns that she is
Can not be on the bus.
I left the bus.
It contradicts mine
Values ​​to be observed,
-like girls their entire self-respect
For a fuck in the forest.
8th
Sara does not like Vilde!
I have heaps of insults
Have to read about their bus friends.
You do not want it all
Share your own past.
You are a good person.
Will you give it to me, please?
Come and get him.
Really now, I do not feel like it.
Just throw it over.
Come and get him.
I have no desire!
All right. Then I take the ball with me.
-And disappear.
-I am serious.
Bye!
Let me play!
I'm playing alone.
How long do you want
Still be sour, Sana?
Sana?
I did not know Isak was a friend
Of you. I told you!
I swear, she remains angry,
No matter what I say and do.
I warn you,
It is really crass on it.
Sunday
Frida said today that she
To become a doctor. LOL
I'm sorry for her. I believe,
Her mother is alkie or junkie
Matilde has seen her with a woman,
Which looked like a homeless,
And as Matilde wanted to say her "hello"
Vilde has tried to hide.
Fuck! Olivia has yesterday one of
The new one blown. Pääädoo
... Eva behaved like a bitch ...
... Vilde is the purest cliché ...
Ingrid is annoyed with her grief
And their insecurity
You know Sana from the Vilde clique?
That is totally psycho I've heard today-
-that she's on the Urra school
In the sweatbox
(Voices from outside)
... with couscous.
I am getting hungry,
If I only talk about it.
Why are you wailing,
If you have already eaten?
- He's eaten something.
-Adam has his days and does not fast.
I'm sick.
-All are sick.
- No, I'm really sick.
Unlike you, I-
- in the paradise 72 young women get!
Because I am a good Muslim!
Just because you're fasting one day a week.
-You must begin right now.
Look at the sun, it's warm.
I am proud, I am a good Muslim.
Hey, hey, hey!
What do you want with 72 young women?
You can not even make it,
To make a 00er clear!
(They talk.)
- You know it yourself. 00er do not go at all.
-And 72 young women go clear?
Says, where is Yousef?
-Where is that?
-Yousef meets with Noora.
-Noora? The girlfriend of Sana?
-Yes, the Noora.
That's true. I have seen,
As they have been sleeping together.
Is that your seriousness?
That's stupid ...
-He is jealous!
-Hey, chill times!
- That's a woman!
- She's damn sweet.
He is jealous, old man!
Tuesday
There you are!
Yes, im learning.
Yes, you learn and learn and learn.
I wanted to tell you something.
You do not have to say it.
I already know it.
What?
With Yousef.
Yes...
Did he tell you?
Or what?
And how do you think about it?
I do not think anything.
-Do you like him?
-No!
For sure?
Just because you find him sweet,
-this does not mean that all
Others.
OK...
I said I was trying,
Me to focus on the exam.
What the hell is this ?!
-No idea!
- Did you write about me?
No! Why should I have done this?
Somebody's kidding me.
You can see that it is gephotoshopt.
Delete that! I want such crap over
Do not see me on Instagram!
Wednesday
... have 300,000 for a bus
And are now split.
I would die if the whole
School my chats would have read!
I looked at myself, how much crap
I write about the people in chats.
This is a lot! You have to be real
Be careful to whom you write that.
How many times have we tried?
You are using your data volume.
I have a flat rate.
-Was they?
-No.
-Is she currently active on Facebook?
- Before a while, but not now.
-You wrote to Facebook?
-More than a message.
- Did you call her parents?
-No. We could go to her.
-What's happening?
-We can not reach Sara.
She is ashamed because everyone has read the crap
They is writing about people.
Are we really sure,
That Sara wrote that?
That she hopes Iselin's school
She had also written to me.
That Olivia is pedophile,
She wrote to me.
-Ob someone hacked their account?
-Shoes, is the creepy!
There is still much more creepy that ours
Bus boss so talking about the people on the bus.
I will log off from the bus.
It is really important that we get along
Which can not be broken.
We will be attacked and should
As a bus group.
This is really a serious thing!
To publish the chats!
Is not that criminal?
(They talk.)
Drama?
Yes.
Have heard that Sara is some crap
About the girls on Instagram?
Yes...
Believe me; You do not want to know that.
I really do not want that!
Are you ready for the exam?
Yes. You also?
I'm Stephen Hawking on Redbull,
What do you think?! Yes Yes Yes. See you!
delete account
Clear account permanently
Thursday
(Notification)
GROUP FOR ALL THAT FROM
CYBERMOBBING ARE CONCERNED
(Ingrid :) Hi have made the chat for all
Who were attacked on Instagram.
I finally reached Sara
And she is of course totally finished.
She is in the cottage on Kragerø and
Will return to school on Monday .
She wanted me to see you
Which leads here:
Tell the girls that I'm never angry
And I love them all.
If I wrote this crap really
Should, then the long-
-and I did not mean anything seriously.
I do not know who did this to me,
-but I'll find it out.
Sara is so ready that she today
The exam did not write
(Iselin :) Greet her and tell her that it is
Okay, no one cares what, -
-all tell crap about all.
The Arms
(Lea :) Nobody deserves it,
To experience something like that.
(Ingrid :) The real problem is,
Who has done this to Sarah and us.
Sara tried to do the things
In their chats,
-but she has not yet succeeded.
She will look further.
Some of us know they are us
Some of these things has been written.
Therefore, we know that there are extracts
From different chats.
Maybe Sara is
Victims of faceraping.
(Olivia :) Sorry ...
Now I think of something
Was not Vilde last week in Saras
Facebook? When she posted the photo?
(Ingrid :) Shit, right!
(Leas :) Right!
If the speech bubble were not blue,
If this comes from Saras Facebook?
(Lea :) And she said yesterday that Sara
No more bus boss should be !!?
(Iselin :) So stupid is she not?
(Ingrid :) Yes, could be!
She must have been it !?
And she wanted to
Always be bus boss!
(Lea :) And there stands The one and only
Perfect Bus boss on the Insta account !!
The same was above the photo !! It must
So be someone from this group !!
(Ingrid :) AND:We have it already
Once thrown out of the bus, -
- as she has tried,
The bus boss to overthrow.
Hello, Sana.
Hello.
I really wanted to
To report a while ago.
What happened?
When I wanted to do it, I knew
Somehow not what I should write.
I've heard you're doing now
A nurse training?
Mm.
- How is that?
-It's OK.
-You still go to the Nissen?
-mm.
Yes.
-What do you have?
-I have biology, chemistry, math ...
What is your chemistry teacher?
-Lars?
-The great? With brown hair?
-Yes. Did you have it, too?
-mm.
He always wore the same shirt.
A blue shirt.
Is he still wearing it?
Yes. He already had that when you
With him? The whole advanced level?
The whole advanced level.
Bah!
That is already special.
Then I'm not the only one,
Which finds him somehow special.
-Du fastest, right?
-mm.
-You also?
-Are you hungry?
-Little.
-Yes.
But it becomes easier every day,
When one has got used to it.
-Maghrib is today at 22:25.
-22 ...?
22.25 hrs.
-How many hours are they still?
- Hours and 40 minutes.
So long still!
This is full of humor. Even Elias
Know now when Maghrib is.
You know it, too
Such people who say -
- that you can not sing, dance or
Listening to music while you're fasting?
There are also some who say,
That you can not.
And many of them make up their makeup
Not even while they are fasting.
Yesterday I was made up, and
Then someone stared at me.
Certainly because I was made up.
I've heard that some
The whole time spit out.
They think their own spit
Do not swallow because that is a violation.
-I have such a girlfriend.
- She always spits?
She spat at school.
She spits out at work.
She makes it quite self-confident.
About ...
This is funny.
- You're fine, right?
-Yes.
Friday
- He will separate from me.
- He will not.
These were some assholes.
This is totally unjust to you.
It will certainly be all right.
You're just sad.
What happened?
Someone has started "ellevillevilde2"
And heaps of crap over Vilde.
This is really bad.
-That's gonna be back, it's ...
This is still really bad.
-This is so unnecessary.
-Yes, unnecessary!
I just do not understand,
Who does that?
Who opens hate accounts
And published chats?
How shit can someone be?
The account saranors2
Is not from Vilde.
(Ingrid :) We know that
It was Isak
No, Isak was not
(Ingrid :) Yes? He admitted it
Sara has read all her chats
And found it out.
And then she asked him and he
Said he has been it.
(Lea :) Why does he have
Actually done?
(Ingrid :) Because Sara hurt him,
When she left him?
(Lea :) ???? What is he not gay?
What do you think you are doing?
Were not you the one,
Which has said,
-that she abhors people,
Which their friends leave behind?
It was...
It was not my intention that
Which affects you. I'm so sorry.
What was your plan? How should
Does not that affect me?
It's a shame to me, Saras
Clique has something against me.
But you might have
Can ask before you ...
Before you take photos of mine
Private chats.
Excuse me.
I just wanted the other girls
See how Sara is in reality.
They know how she is.
They are themselves.
What did you actually do about Sara?
She is a racist Tussi, who ...
She lied to me and
Wanted to get me out of the bus.
Maybe she wanted to throw you out because
You're a derelict, bossy bitch?
Why are you human
So hard, Sana?
Try it, without hardship in this country
As a Muslim girl.
I tried to be as gay
Youths.
That is not the same.
Nobody looks at you,
That you are different.
You will not get the
Same looks as I do.
You know what people think when they do
see me? When they see my headscarf?
That I wear it because I have to
Not because I want it.
And when I say I wear it,
Because I want it, I am brainwashed.
Because I do not have my own opinion.
We are talking about religion-
Freedom and all possible freedoms,
-but if I wear an extra layer,
Then what is wrong with me?
People think we're getting married
However, that everything is arranged,
-and that I'll be tomorrow
My cousin was forcibly married.
You know what people do when Elias
And I am together on the road?
People spit at him because they
Believe that he oppressed me.
Elias!
He does not even want me to wear a headscarf
Wear so I can not get hate!
You know how exhausting it is, every day
With the knowledge to go out of the house, -
- that you can prove again today
Must not be suppressed?
Do you think people think that?
Wear a headscarf for one day.
Then you realize that most
Norwegians are racists.
This is bullshit.
-What?
-This is bullshit.
Most Norwegians
Are not racists!
Are interested in ...-
- Freedom, peace ... other cultures
And want to know more about it.
They want other cultures
Feel comfortable here.
But it is not surprising that so
Many are afraid of Muslims,
- if they are affected by genital mutilation, the
IS, terror and "foreign fighters".
You know that most do not
so are. So only damn few.
When you first meet a Muslim,
You do not know what to say.
If one says "foreign"
"Multiethnic" or "multicultural"?
What is right? You do not know if you
Women shaking hands with headscarf.
And is it disrespectful,
To ask for Allah?
And then you ask
Nothing at all because ...
Is perhaps also better so.
I've had enough in my life
Stupid, racist issues.
No, Sana! The stupid questions
Are damn important!
People must not stop,
The stupid questions.
For otherwise they seek their own
Reply. And that is dangerous.
Listen for racism in
The stupid questions.
Even if they're damn annoying
And feel racist,
- it's totally important that you have them
answered. You have to answer them.
Who the hell are you really ?!
I swear, you sound
Like my Imam.
This is something new.
Imam Valtersen. I like it.
I'm not saying that there are no racists in
Norway. There are certainly many.
I am not a Muslim
Girl grown up, -
- but believe me:I was
Even where you are now.
Once you start,
To look for hatred,
- you will find what.
And if you find hate,
You start hating yourself.
I am sorry, that i
Read your chat.
Do not worry about that.
I've also done stupid things.
And...
Sorry that Elias and his
Boys are homophobic.
Are the homophobes?
Yes, did not they ...?
That?
No no no.
It has nothing to do with it.
I had struck Michael.
I..
I was a little jealous.
And then Elias came and hewed me
A pure one. He is much stronger.
I had earned it. If someone
Jonas, I would be ...
No, I would not,
Because I'm not strong enough.
No no no.
Who would have thought?
The Homo and the Muslima
- best buddies.
We are not the best buddies.
Are you serious?
We are buddies?
Okay, we're buddies.
We are buddies.
Who is your best buddy?
I'm not sure,
Whether I have any more.
Of course you have some.