Previously...
* Search on Maniac
And Bipolar Disorder *
SATURDAY
* Search on Maniac
And Bipolar Disorder *
Do you need something?
No, I'm not well.
This is going to pass, Isak.
Even if it doesn't look
like it for now...
Even though ... it's painful.
Broken hearts always hurt.
You may think it will not happen, but it will.
But...
Let me know if you want to chat or ...
If you need anything.
From Even:
[Lyrics of "Cherry Wine" by NAS]
[Hi Even,  I do not know a damn thing
right now. Stop sending messages.]
[To Isak, my son: From the first second
I saw you on July 21, 1999 at 21:21 p.m.
I loved you and I always will.
Love you, forever.]
TUESDAY
Yes, but I do not understand why.
they are friends? Is he Kim?
-They're just colleagues-
-Hi.
Are you kidding?
Are there waffles in the canteen?
-Yes.
-We'll talk later.
Why did you miss school?
I was a little sad.
What happened?
Even surged.
What did he do?
He went out on the street.
Naked in the middle of the night.
Apparently he's bipolar.
-Hi guys.
My mother is also bipolar.
You have a crazy mother too?
She's not crazy, she's bipolar.
Yeah, but ... What's she like?
She is amazing.
You've met her, haven't you?
Yes, I met her, but
she was normal.
She is normal.
But ... She only has a few moments.
When she's depressed and happy.
Who were you talking about?
Even. He is also bipolar.
He left naked in the
Street in the middle of the night.
-Oh really?
How hilarious!
It's not funny.
But it's comical. Oh really.
Do you know what my mother did?
She was so angry
With the NSB (Subway),
That she discovered
The name of the manager
And sent a letter of
Resignation in his name.
Like: "I give up, I cannot
work anymore. Bye!".
Where's Even now?
At home, I guess.
Not physically but mentally.
Is he happy or depressed?
I have not talked to him yet.
Why not?
Because it was all a lie
From him.
What you mean?
He was a maniac!
Been with him for a long time.
He was not a maniac all the time.
Because when my mother is maniac,
I cannot get in touch with her.
You can get in
touch with Even?
Yes, but Sonja said that he's
been a maniac all the time.
Who is Sonja?
- His ex.
Then,
You believe when his ex says
That he has no feelings for you?
Well smart, Isak ... That's it.
The best thing I heard today...
Wow! Wow!
Asked Even
how he feels?
He no...
He is not brain dead
Because he had a maniac episode.
Talk to him when
He is calm.
You're very nice, Magnus.
Did you realize that just now?
-Yes?
-Okay, thanks Jonas.
You're very cool too.
WEDNESDAY
*Phone off,
leave a message*
[DAD]
Hello?
- Hi, Isak.
Hey you. How are you doing? Wanted
To know ... are you really going to go on Friday?
-Yes I will. When...
-How nice.
-When does it start?
-20: 30
Right.
-But hey ... cool.
So you have a boyfriend?
I was just,
just kidding.
Yes, OK.
But we'll see you on Friday.
I'm excited to see you.
And Mom too.
-Yes.
Yeah ... Okay, great.
Dad
-Yes?
I was not joking.
It's just over.
And That's it.
Ok but you are sad
About it, or?
-No I'm well.
-OK.
-Well, then...
-Yes Yes.
So...
-Bye Bye...
From Even:
[Dear Isak. I'm sitting on the spot
Where we met for the first time
And I'm thinking of you. It is almost
21:21. I want to tell you a thousand things.
Sorry if I frightened you. Sorry that
I have hurt you. Sorry for not
Telling you that I'm bipolar. Was with
afraid to lose you. I had forgotten
That it is impossible to lose someone,
Since all humans are alone.
Somewhere else in the universe
We are together for infinity,
remember this.
I love you. Even.]
You are not alone.