I'll just take it then, Jesus Christ.
What would you guys do without me?
I want 10% of your drugs, and I want you
and your friends to join the kose group.
Yeah just find a seat,
then we can start.
Come outside.
So that's why I was wondering if you wanted
to be in a group with me.
Yeah, I kind of already agreed to
be in a group with...
- With...
- Even.
[Hello again.]
[Hi how's it going?]
[Horny, you?]
[Location?]
Look at this guy.
Do you think he's handsome?
This guy.
- I don't fucking know.
- Look!
Definitely handsome.
Isak, you can say a guy's
handsome without being gay.
I said he's definitely handsome.
I'm going to meet him, you know.
You need my confirmation that
he's hot before you meet him?
He writes that he isn't gay, but
likes to suck cock for fun.
My boy, you have one year and
then you'll be out of the closet.
Eskild, why do you think every guy is gay?
I don't think every guy is gay, Isak.
But I have quite a good gaydar.
You know?
How does this gaydar work?
What's the characteristic of a gay guy?
Okay.
A clue, for example, is when someone starts
talking about sucking dick with a stranger.
Right?
It's also a bit suspicious
when you have a Grindr profile.
Hi!
Noora.
I'm in Isak's room.
No, it's better now. He's cleaned
up a little. However, it smells…
Yo, what's up people?
Straight out of Elvebakken.
Today I'm talking to my best buddy Even.
What's up, bro? Tell us about your movie.
The movie is about Captain
America and Vladimir Putin
who are in love with each other.
But they can't be together because
Sarah Palin has bewitched them.
So when they kiss, a cat dies of AIDS.
Who is this Barbie? Sarah Palin?
No! She's just Barbie.
You always have to have a hot woman.
- Sarah Palin is considered a hot woman.
- What?!
Who's your favourite director?
Baz Luhrmann.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
- Are you kidding me?
- No I'm not kidding you.
- Baz Luhrmann?
- Why are you so skeptical?
He makes cliché movies where the leads die.
He makes epic love stories, man!
The lead must die,
otherwise it's not an epic love story.
Hello.
Do you have my stuff?
What stuff?
What stuff?!
I thought you said it wasn't yours.
Can't you just give it to me?
I didn't see your friends at the meeting.
I can't force them to come, can I?!
Control yo hoes, is all that I'm saying.
- I can't be bothered with this anymore.
- Neither can I.
- Where do you want it?
- You have it?
No! The big compartment.
Sana and Isak! What are you guys doing?
What was it you put in your burqa just now?
- My burqa?
- Niqab, then.
Niqab? You can't name the
garment 10% of your students wear?
Are you a racist?
- What's it called then?
- It's called a hijab!
Great. Hijab.
But now you guys need to pay attention.
Please, class starts now.
Vilde?
Hi!
I was just thinking, are there
any more kose group meetings?
How unbelievably nice that you're engaging!
We won't have a group meeting this week,
but next week there's the theatre party.
So we'll have a group pre-drink.
Could the pre-drink maybe be at yours?
Why?
Because my mom is hosting a wine reception,
Eva's house was completely trashed
and Sana's parents are Muslim.
But it could be at yours!
- Maybe...
- What's up here?
Isak will throw next week's pre-drink.
Do you guys want to come?
Eh, group pre-drink?
What the fuck…
Why are you laughing?
Do you think the theatre is stupid?
The theatre will lay the social foundation
for how you'll be at school if you engage.
That's where class, age,
race, sexual orientation...
Hi!
Did you get my messages?
Sorry. No I didn't get them.
We'll have a pre-drink on Friday.
We were wondering if you guys want to come.
Friday?
I don't really know. I think…
- Isak has brain damage. We're coming.
Okay, yeah. Cool. I'll text you.
What the fuck is your deal?
Are you gay or what?
Where do these first
year girls get the confidence?
Why are first year girls inviting
second year guys to a bus pre-drink?
Are they complete noobs?
They're not meant to go after you?
What's the problem with that?
The problem is that there's a system!
If first year girls start sleeping with third
year guys, and second year guys as well...
Who will we sleep with?
I'm available if you want to have sex.
Don't be rude.
- Dude, you're such an idiot.
- What the fuck did you mean by that?
Is she playing me, guys?
I'm so damn hungover.
It's Wednesday...
You always have to have a hot woman.
- Sarah Palin is considered a hot woman.
- What?!
Who is your favorite director?
Baz Luhrmann.
Seriously?
[Horny?]
[Hi. Top or bottom?]
[Is your cock thick?]
[Squirt a lot?]
[You can fuck and
come in my ass.]
- You owe me a drink. Yeah.
- Huh?!
That party Ina and Hedda had together...
You drank almost all of my six pack.
It's you who owes me.
I gave you like three beers at a party.
That was ages ago!
At that one party you didn't have shit,
and I had a six-pack.
You almost finished the
entire fucking six pack.
When I came up to you, you gave me some.
- Why are you saying it's true?
- He gets it!
It goes without saying.
- Eskild will get it for sure.
- Eksild? Eksild will get it.
- Later, guys!
- Text me when we're leaving.
- I'll find out.
- Bye!
[Are you home and can you buy beer for me?]
[Sorry, working until 9PM]
Hello.
Going home?
Yeah.
You too?
Nice chat...
This is line 12 via. Grünerløkka
and Torshov to Disen.
You're 18, right?
Could you maybe buy some beer?
I forgot my ID.
I have to go home and get it.
You coming?
Hello?
Nice.
Don't know where I've put it.
Did you draw these?
Yeah.
- They're good.
- Thanks
- Really funny.
- You think so?
- Here it is.
- You found it?
No, but...
Haven't you skipped school yet?
I just skipped class earlier.
You didn't get caught yet?
I skipped a few hours.
- What's the limit?
- The limit is 10 hours.
But if the principal likes you it's 15.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But I don't think the principal likes me.
What do you listen to
when you listen to music?
- I'm quite a big N.W.A. fan.
- That's what gets you going?
That's what you listen to
when you want to feel though.
Have you listened to anything from Nas?
Nas?
Are you kidding?
You haven't checked that out?
- I've listened to it. Nas. Nas?
- Nas?
- Have you even heard of it?
- I have heard of it!
It doesn't sound like it.
I've heard of it...
You should listen to it later.
That there is a sweaty cheese, man.
I know, I forgot about it
when I went to school today.
It has almost melted.
- Has that happened to you before?
- Yeah, I always forget the cheese.
- You do that too?
- Yeah.
Fuck, that's a problem.
Cheese and keys. Especially cumin cheese. (Word
play on nøkler = keys, and nøkkel = cumin)
Those are the things I forget most.
Beer?
There you go.
- Cheers.
So, what kind of spices do
you want? Let's start with...
- Caribbean Jerk Barbecue.
- Caribbean Jerk sounds perfect! Go ahead!
- Chili?
- Chili? Always chili.
Rosemary?
- Rosemary? Yes, loads.
- Loads of rosemary? Okay.
Let's do this.
- Even more?
- No, this is great.
- Pottagaldrar?
- Pottagaldrar? Eh, yes!
[When should we be at Emma's?
Did you get beer? Answer.]
[Hi we'll start the pre-drink at 7PM. Maria
lives in Torshov, just call when you
[guys are outside the 7-eleven, I'll come
out to meet you. When are you guys coming?]
[My friends are also wondering if you
could bring some of the stuff you
[gave me in the bathroom at that party.
Only if it isn't much trouble.]
Cinnamon?
Yeah, fuck it!
I think it's gonna taste like balls.
But we can't go back now.
No, we can't go back now.
[Sorry man, Emma and her friends cancelled the
pre-drink soooo I think I'm just gonna chill at home.]
I'll just put a little bit more pepper. [Sorry man, Emma and her friends
cancelled the pre-drink soooo I think I'm just gonna chill at home.]
[Sorry man, Emma and her friends cancelled the
pre-drink soooo I think I'm just gonna chill at home.]
[Sorry we forgot some other stuff we were
doing, but we'll join another time.]
Should we put it in the oven?
- Let's do it.
There's something that doesn't
taste right in there.
- It's absolutely terrible.
So bad that it was good in a way.
No, it's so bad that it's even worse.
It was you who wanted
to use all the spices.
A lot of cardamom is essential.
Is that the trick?
For it to be good?
- Have you heard rumors about my rapping?
- I actually have.
Come on! Focus!
- What time is it?
- Ten to eight.
I've invited a few friends.
But just stay. We have lots of beer.
- Hi.
- Introduce yourself.
- Hi. Elise. Nice to meet you.
- Isak.
- And this here is Sonja. My girlfriend.
- Sonja. Nice to meet you.
Isak.
Your girlfriend became the
saleswoman of the month.
- Really? What?!
- You're so smart.
- Yeah, yeah.
You must be quite proud.
[Why are you lying?
Talked to Emma and her friends.]