Why did you have to cheat
just because you thought I was?
Call me when you've figured that out.
You just made out a bit?
- It was your boyfriend who tipped me off.
- Did Isak send the tip?
I think it's completely psycho!
Do you have feelings for me?
As if you didn't know.
- Want to go to my place to do homework?
- No.
Let me know when you change your mind.
- What are you doing on your plate?
- I'm just sorting my salad.
I'm not on the bus anymore.
She started staggering, and then she tripped.
She's not responding.
I think I killed William's baby tonight.
SHAME
You kept pushing me out of bed.
SATURDAY, 10:21 A.M.
- You pulled away my comforter like ten times!
- It was cold!
- Yeah, I know!
- Sorry...
Is your mom never home?
She is, but she got a new job
at the Ministry of Environment, so
ever since that she's been traveling a lot more.
So she's home only every other week.
- You're home alone a lot! Isn't that cool?
- Sure is.
You can do whatever you want.
- Where's your dad?
- He lives in Bergen.
- Chris! You get to clean that up.
- Yeah, I'll clean it up.
Dad lives in Bergen,
since mom and dad are divorced.
- I think we moved from Bergen when I was twelve?
- Do you have any contact with him?
No... yeah, I have.
But we kind of lost contact when we moved.
Dad got remarried,
and his wife was a bit jealous.
- Hi!
Hi.
- We made breakfast.
- Yeah, Noora made pancakes.
Yeah, let's eat.
You can sit here.
- Have some pancakes.
- It smells really good!
Just start! Sana?
Do you want some juice, Vilde?
Here!
Oh, shit. I just spilled a bit.
Do you want some jam with that? So you can...
I can't remember anything from yesterday.
It doesn't matter. It'll be fine.
Blackouts are God's way of telling you that
you don't need to worry about anything, Vilde.
You did nothing special.
You just passed out,
when you came to Iben's party.
So we brought you here. And then you just slept.
Vilde...
every girl with self-respect
has blacked out at least once.
Thank you.
I mean it.
You don't have to thank us. That's why
we're on a bus together. To help each other.
You still want me on your bus?
What are you talking about?
You're our bus boss!
You think any of us want to do
the financials and the budget?
But... it can be a bit stressful as the bus boss.
I mean...
if it interferes with other things.
That could happen fast.
- Yeah, like what?
- Well, like school and...
things like recreational activities...
or...
children.
Vilde...
are you pregnant?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
How sure?
Yeah... yeah, yeah.
We'll probably have to take
another little trip...
to doctor Skrulle, then.
MONDAY, 1:39 P.M.
- It's quite captivating.
- Who are you talking about?
Justin... your crush.
- Eva, that's between us.
- You have to look, look here!
- Yeah, yeah. I've seen that.
- Yeah, it's probably hanging over your bed.
Hi!
Hi.
The stage group invites you
to the Christmas tree lighting on Friday.
Are you coming?
- Maybe...
- You have to. The entire school will be there.
- Okay, we're coming.
- Good!
- Hey... he's hot!
- Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah. I've seen it.
Hi, beautiful.
Willhelm! Wow.
You're not answering my messages?
I ran out of battery.
For two weeks straight.
Want to skip the next class?
- You have to give up now.
- Give up?
I'm not going to give up.
You're wasting your time.
Listen, Noora Amalie Sætre.
You're a smart girl, and you have to realize
that every time you reject me...
it only makes me want you more and more.
So if you really want to get rid of me,
just go on a date with me.
Stop acting like you're so damn interesting.
Great logic.
Was that all, or?
No, one more thing.
Fuck, you're beautiful.
Just tell me what I should do, then!
- Hi...
- Hi.
- We should probably have a talk.
- Yes.
When can you talk?
I have lots to do this week.
And I really need to study,
unless I want to fail in all my subjects.
- But... Thursday maybe?
- Thursday is fine.
What's up with you guys?
He's in love with me.
- You're kidding!
- No, it's--
THURSDAY, 10:30 A.M.
Hi, there!
Hi. Hi, hi.
There we go, she's new. Salaam Alaikum?
Vilde is pregnant!
Oh... that went fast.
Vilde Lien, what should I say? Congratulations?
- She's not going to keep the child!
- We don't agree on that.
She's sixteen years old!
She's way too young to be a mother.
Well, not that young, the world's youngest
was 5 years and 7 months, that's young.
But she wasn't from Norway.
She was from some place in South America.
I want to say Chile.
Or was it Peru?
- Yeah, hello?
- Hi. Yes.
- What should we do?
- Yeah,
what should we do? We need to start with...
- taking a blood sample.
- I took a test.
- When did you take the test?
- I took it last Friday.
Last Friday?
And have you had sex since Friday?
- No!
- Are you really sure?
There were a few hours
where it went a bit black...
Okay, girls. This here is an ovulation test.
An ovulation test?
This means that if you
haven't had sex since you took it,
you're most likely not pregnant.
Really?
But there's other things as well,
I'm sick in the mornings, and...
I have a pretty bloated stomach.
It's gotten a lot bigger.
It probably hasn't grown all that much,
but I can take a look. Let me see.
Yeah... okay...
- Does this hurt?
- Yes.
Okay...
- How's your diet?
- Good.
- What did you eat today?
- It's still really early, so a Cola Light...
and a piece of gum.
Yeah, got it.
Vilde, I don't think
there's a baby in your belly.
It's probably just
air in your intestines.
That happens when you cram down
Cola Light and gum all day —
you produce more gas.
Do you fart a lot?
- No.
- No?
You should. Because you're
pushing up too much air in your intestines.
That gives you a stomach ache,
so you have to fart it out.
In the worst case we have
to give you a colostomy.
You know, a poop bag on your stomach?
- Are you serious?
- No, of course not.
But you can't live on Cola Light and gum.
That's my point.
Yes! We're not having a baby!
I'm so relieved!
Vilde...
I see what you're doing.
And you have to stop.
You don't really know
what you're talking about.
Yes...
I do.
Not to be rude... but you stuff yourself
with chocolate milk and pancakes,
and you look like a super model.
What are you talking about?
You look like a super model.
Vilde, you're super pretty.
But not pretty enough.
THURSDAY, 2:23 P.M.
Isak...
I need you to be completely
honest with me now.
Yeah.
Because if I don't believe you...
I'll ask Jonas.
And then I'll tell him why I'm asking.
I understand.
When we were at the cabin...
I asked you if you knew
if Jonas and Ingrid were texting...
I...
I knew he... texted... with her
because of her brother.
So it wasn't about French?
No.
Well, maybe that too, but...
I remember Jonas was stressing like crazy
about getting weed for the cabin trip, but...
He couldn't reach her brother,
so... he sent her a message instead.
Huh?
You guys were smoking at the cabin?
Yeah, that's why Elias came,
because Jonas couldn't get any before we left.
Not to criticize you...
but we were pretty high.
I'm surprised you didn't notice it.
Okay.
Anyway.
What about that other time? When I...
thought I heard Ingrid over the phone.
And I asked you.
Did you know anything about that?
No.
I could imagine that it was because...
he wanted to reach her brother.
But...
I had promised Jonas not to tell...
you anything about him... about him smoking.
So... I kept my promise.
But you advised me to ask Ingrid?
That was shit advice.
Plain and simple.
I should've just told you that you...
shouldn't worry about her.
That he was more in love with you than...
ever.
It would have been pretty cool
if you had told me this earlier.
One more thing.
If you wanted to fuck things up
between me and Jonas...
why didn't you just advise me
to tell him about Chris?
I knew that if you told Jonas,
he would have forgiven you.
Don't you get how messed up that sounds to me?
Suddenly it feels like I don't know you anymore.
I know it might be...
hard to believe,
but I never wanted to hurt you.
It just turned out that way.
I'm sorry.
Karma is a bitch.
If nothing else...
I finally understand what it was like for Ingrid.
Hi!
- How's it going?
- Good.
What are you doing?
- Just some Christmas shopping.
- You don't like Christmas shopping.
Who was that?
It was my sister.
Okay...
I swear!
Okay, I believe you.
Good.
- But...
- Yeah?
Remember that you told me to call
when I had figured out who I am?
Yes.
Do you want to meet?
Yes, of course. When?
No, you're probably going to smoke marijuana
with Ingrid's brother...
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
How about tomorrow?
Yeah, tomorrow is fine.
That's good.
Talk to you later. Bye.
FRIDAY, 2:32 P.M.
- Hi.
- Tea?
- Yeah.
That was warm.
Do you remember the first time we kissed?
- What? Why are you laughing?
- Of course I remember that.
Yeah? What do you remember?
What do I remember?
- Yeah. What is it?
- It's a bit embarassing.
No. Say it.
The thing is that I didn't know
if you were feeling the same as I was, right?
And since you were best friends with my
girlfriend, it was a pretty big risk to take.
If it hadn't worked out,
it would have been really embarassing.
So I just... I waited for a sign.
What kind of sign?
A sign that I should kiss you.
And...
You know that song "Take Me to Church",
that was playing all the time?
Yes.
I figured that if that was the next song
that came on, then I'll go for it.
- So did it come on?
- No, it didn't.
They played this Kygo shit...
But then it was you who kissed me.
It was me who kissed you.
What you didn't know,
was that I was thinking the exact same thing.
Oh, yeah?
I was thinking...
- I need a sign.
- Yeah?
"If the next song is by Kygo,
I will kiss you."
So funny.
But...
that wasn't really why you kissed me,
was it?
No.
That wasn't why.
I kissed you because I couldn't help myself.
It wasn't like...
I got together with you
just because it seemed cool.
No?
No.
And... you accusing me of that...
actually made me pretty angry.
Because it felt like I had to
give up everything, just to be with you.
I ditched my best friends.
So, you telling me that I'm just
doing what others think is cool...
and that I don't have my own opinions,
that's so damn unfair.
Because it's not true.
Because I chose you.
And it was...
a really stupid choice.
But at least I didn't do it to be popular.
A really stupid choice?
Yes.
A really stupid choice.
Because it made me feel like shit.
All this time I was paranoid that there
may have been something between you and Ingrid.
I thought that...
if you and I could do
something like that to Ingrid...
then you could do the same thing to me.
Do you understand?
Maybe...
I thought that I deserved it.
And then I just became...
insecure and...
desperate.
Your opinions meant more than my own.
And it shouldn't be like that.
No.
So I need to...
figure out what my own opinions are.
And I have to do that on my own.
Are we breaking up now?
I think so.
Is that what you want?
Yes.
Right now...
this seems like the most important thing.
As if nothing else has meaning.
We'll just stay here then.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Me and Jonas broke up.
I just thought I should tell you.
Are you okay?
- Hi!
- Have you seen Vilde?
- No.
But, she was coming?
Yeah, I think so.
- Okay, can I borrow your phone?
- Yes, of course.
I'm out of battery.
In 2015? Doesn't anyone have
a working piece of technology?
Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Can you unlock it?
- Do you have Vilde's number?
- No, I don't.
- Hi!
- I just wanted to say Merry Christmas.
- Yes, Merry Christmas, Ingrid!
- Vilde!
- Hi!
- Hey... Noora is looking for you like crazy.
- Why?
She's probably afraid
you've blacked out somewhere.
Very funny!
Vilde?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Do you remember when I said
you weren't pretty enough?
That was bullshit.
You're more than pretty enough.
Anyone who says otherwise is an asshole.
And that includes me.
Okay?
Okay.
What just happened?
I have to tell Chris and Sana!
Hey, I found Vilde.
You'll never guess what just happened--
Hey, I was just thinking. Remember when you
told me you thought it was a bit weird
when Isak said
he has feelings for you.
Yes?
Because...
I just think that...
that maybe it's not you
he has feelings for.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one!