You just betrayed us.
What's up with that?
Hey. You forgot this Friday.
Forgot where?
In the cafeteria.
Who's that dude?
Do you know me and Sonja have
been dating since she was 15 or something?
He only works.
Suddenly it seems like money matters most.
[Hey thanks for yesterday, what's the plan today?
He just...
He becomes completely different when he's around his father.
And his stockbroker colleagues.
He looks up to his father so much.
He lights up when he walks into the room.
I get it, because...
He never got that validation before.
But...
When he finally gets that validation,
he becomes...
He becomes a kid.
But I can't live like that.
No.
Alone in London.
Because I went there to be together with him.
And now we're never together.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I get it.
To be completely honest,
it hasn't been so easy here at home either.
I don't know, it's been a bit like…
There's been a lot of chaos.
One week I had to wipe myself with Linn's pads.
That's really...
And Isak, he's a really good guy, but he's like…
He's so lazy.
Eskild?
I'm sitting right here.
Yeah.
You have to endure hearing that I'm happy to see Noora again.
You don't have to be so jealous.
I love you too.
Jealous?! I'm not jealous.
But we have to find a solution
because Noora's going to live here now
we'll be with 4 in an apartment for 3.
Are you serious?
Noora just came home after being dumped by the man of her dreams.
The only thing you're thinking about is the sleeping arrangements.
Can't you sleep on the floor?
I haven't been dumped.
-No, you weren't dumped but...
It was me who left him there.
We didn't break up.
We have...
taken a break.
And if he really loves me,
he'll come after me.
I think that...
I don't know, but...
People leave their wives and children
to be together with the one they love.
And if he really loves you,
he'll choose you.
I think it'll work out.
At least it's really nice to have you home again.
Are you happy to be back home?
Does it taste good?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It was Linn who made it.
I don't believe it.
That's why it's not good.
Hey.
Hi!
Are you going to the Halloween thing?
Eh, no. Or maybe.
I don't know. Are you?
Join me?
Okay!
-Okay?
Yeah, hm.
-Great, then we'll do a pre-drink together?
Yeah.
Hey.
-Hi.
Did you do anything fun this weekend?
Eh, no.
I tried to call you on Friday.
Yeah I saw.
But so damn much happened this weekend.
Noora came home!
Did you hear about that?
Yes.
I heard you had a pre-drink.
Yeah, yeah I did. No, I didn't really have it, but…
Vilde pretty much forced me to have it.
She talked to Eskild.
In the end I didn't have a choice.
It was more like she was hosting it at my place.
It was really boring.
It's not like you were missing out on anything.
Magnus' birthday is on Saturday.
No?
-Yeah.
So Mahdi and me were thinking
of doing something cool for him.
Yeah, I'm in.
-Yeah?
We can make sure he'll have sex for the first time.
On his birthday, yeah.
That'll be awesome.
We need to call those dance chicks.
Yes!
-He likes them.
Or Vilde!
Yes! Oh my god.
So he can live out his SM dream.
Yeah, dominatrix. Dominatrix.
He isn't 100%. He's sick.
... the donor's genes are thus spread to the
next generation when the receiver splits.
Transferring genetics can be done in three different ways:
Through conjugation, transformation, and transduction.
Do you agree?
Can you focus?
Sana. I have a question.
No offense, but why are you actually religious?
It's 2016 and the world is progressing.
You are a smart girl and you study exact sciences.
Don't you get that it's nonsense?
Is something in my religion bothering you?
Nothing specific, just you believing
there is only a right and a wrong.
And that there's a god who decides
that and who says homosexuality isn't right.
Or to eat hotdogs or whatever…
What is it you believe in Isak?
Me? I believe in science.
The theory of evolution. Nothing else.
Okay.
So let's look at the theory of evolution.
How do you explain homosexuality within natural selection?
Hm?
Evolution wise homosexuality is a genetic dead end.
Gay people don't progress the world.
So according to the theory of evolution,
they should have already been extinct millions of years ago.
Unless homosexuality is not genetic, but rather a disease.
Or a choice people make.
What do you think about that?
I don't fucking know. I don't go around
thinking about homosexuality all the time.
No.
So since you don't have the answer to everything
can't we just agree that there's a lot
between heaven and earth none of us know about?
Instead of sitting here criticizing my religion,
just respect that we have chosen different beliefs.
Okay, whatever.
-Hey!
I talked so Sonja and she was wondering
if we could have the pre-drink at your place?
Huh?
Sonja. Even's girlfriend.
Yeah?
She said you and Even planned a
pre-drink before the Halloween party.
With us.
Yeah, hm-hm.
-Yeah! Cool.
Sonja and Even will dress up as God and an angel.
So I thought it'd be awesome if we matched as well.
If we dress up as a cat and a mouse,
or Batman and Batwoman or something?
If you think that's fun?
Only if you think it's fun.
But I'll text you.
Hello?
What is it? Shit.
… sexual reproduction.
Or was that what you just talked about?
No? Okay.
Should I read it out loud?
(more biology talk)
Sounds easy!
Now that I'm not going to school,
I don't really know what to do.
I miss having something to do.
What do you miss most?
Having something to do during the day.
I'm pretty bored.
I've thought about that as well.
We've gone to school for 10 years.
But just going to school.
Being in the theatre for example.
Are you with the theatre?
-Yes! I don't understand people who don't want to join.
It's a bit weird.
-It's really weird.
Were you in it?
-Yes, all three years.
All three years?
-Yeah, I'm three years older than you.
Are you from '97? No!
It's really nice.
Despite the age difference.
It's so nice talking to you, I didn't notice...
-Yeah, same for me!
Didn't think of the age difference.
Are you one year older than Even?
No, I'm from '97 too.
Can you please calm
down a little with the beer?
Can you stop watching over me?
I mean it, stop monitoring me.
Where the toilet?
-In the corridor, on your right.
I heard a lot of people are coming to the party.
-What time is it?
Hm?
21:21
Seriously?
Yeah, why?
We're going.
Where?
Wherever.
I feel like swimming.
Don't you?
Swimming?
-Yeah!
Who lives here?
-My aunt.
And she's okay with us being here?
-Of course. Not a problem.
Where is your aunt?
She's on holiday.
Why don't you have the keys?
Because she's on holiday.
That's the answer to everything.
-Relax! Don't worry.
You coming?
Okay!
Why are you so skeptical?
I'm not skeptical, but it's a bit weird we're going to...
-Are you scared of swimming?
Scared of swimming?
-Yeah.
Do you have a fear of water?
-Fear of water?!
Fear of water, yes.
It isn't my aunt's house.
So you're just scared to fuck up your hair?
You think I care about my hair?
-What should I think?
It looks like it.
-Does it look like I care about my hair?
Not right now, but usually it does.
You thought I died?
-Yeah I got so scared.
You suck at holding your breath?
-I suck? Try it yourself.
Are you challenging me?
I'm the master at holding my breath.
-Show me.
Okay fine.
Wow!
You never cease to impress.
-I got water in my lungs.
Yeah right!
-I swallowed water!
Okay!
-I'll try again.
Now together.
-Together?
On three?
-Last one to come up wins.
Ready?
-We're going together on three.
No, on 1.
3, 2, 1!
Yes!
-Yes what?
I won!
Yes?! No! That was cheating.
-I won! Are you kidding?
What?!
That was cheating.
You think there are rules here?
-Yes!
What did you think?
But that's just cheating!
You can't do that.
I don't accept losing like that.
-Then let's do it again.
MOM!
Fuck fuck fuck!
-Fucking hell!
Who the hell is she?!
Who lives here?
Someone I went to elementary school with.