I've decided that my life is better
without mentally ill people around me.
Then I'll ask you: What happens
after I've rescued you?
He's manic!
That's what's happening!
So can you please just stay away?
What about asking Even how he feels?
He isn't brain dead just because
he had a maniac episode.
Just talk to him when he has calmed down.
Hi Sonja. I just wanted to tell you that
Even is with me if his parents are worried.
And I am sorry if it's because
of me that he is not doing well.
SATURDAY 10:15
Hi!
I don't have...
The telephone number of his parents so...
Yeah.
But they know that he is with you.
He has sent them a text.
Okay.
I just called to say
that I am sorry for the last time.
It's okay.
No, but I didn't mean
to get angry with you.
It wasn't your fault.
At all.
Yeah, but...
Well you...
You were worried. So I understand.
Hmm.
And it's not your fault
that Even is depressed.
He is bipolar and...
Well, it's not your fault.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
But...
Should I get him to his
parents or something?
I actually think it's good
for him to be with you.
Okay.
I don't know. Is there anything I can do?
For him?
No, not really.
You just need to...
Be there for him.
And when everything seems
hopeless, you just
Take one day at a time.
And if one day becomes too much,
then just take one hour at a time.
And if one hour becomes too much,
then just take one minute at a time.
Hi.
Hungry?
What time is it?
Around...
Ten thirty or something.
I should leave.
Why?
Because I don't want you to lie here and
feel like you have to take care of me.
I don't feel like I am looking after you.
And why?
Why is that wrong?
There's nothing wrong with it.
I just can't stand that
you lie here all sad.
I am not sad.
I just know that this
isn't going to work out.
Why do you say that?
Because it's true.
I'm just going...
to hurt you.
And then you'll hate me.
No.
You don't know shit about
how this is going to end.
We might get a nuclear bomb dropped
on our heads tomorrow and...
and then discusing this is
just a waste of time, so
I suggest that you just stop
talking about the future.
And then the two of us will just
take this thing completely chill.
Let's play a game.
It goes like this...
It's called
Isak and Even: Minute a minute.
It's about...
The only thing we have to worry about
is the next minute.
Are you up for it?
Okay.
What should we do this minute then?
This minute we'll kiss.
That's chill.
MONDAY 10:36
But Eskild, if he is asleep
just let him sleep, you know?
Shouldn't I wake him up and
ask him how he is doing?
No. Why would you do that?
I don't know. It was you who
said to take care of him.
Yeah, I asked you to keep an eye
on him because he is depressed,
not to look after him as he was a baby.
Just let him sleep.
Okay. I think he just woke up.
Yeah, okay. Talk to you later.
Hi, Isak!
Hi, Vilde!
Have you seen the message I
posted on the kose group?
Kose group?
No, no. I haven't seen it.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing, I just...
Had almost forgotten that the
kose group even existed.
Are you still in it?
This is when the revue starts.
You can't just be part of the
partying and not do any work.
No, of couse I'm still in
the kose group, Vilde.
Who do you think I am?
Okay, because all the groups have
this Christmas get-together.
And it went so well the last time we
had the pre-game at your place.
That I was wondering if we
could have it at yours?
Yeah!
Yeah?
Is it okay with your roomies?
I am sure it is. Jesus Christ, yeah!
Okay. I'll send out the invites then!
Go ahead!
Hello.
Hi.
There's this asshole in second year.
Who will be hosting this Christmas
get-together with the kose group.
On Friday?
So, he was wondering
if you wanted to come?
Because he thinks that
would be really nice.
I have switched to the PR-Group. So...
But...
You...
Should tell the asshole that
I am very glad he asked.
I'll tell the asshole, yeah.
He'll appreciate that.
Do that.
Yes. Bye.
Bye.
WEDNESDAY. 16:01
Linn, that way.
I was going to kick!
No, no, no.
Back to him?
Yeah!
Do you want him to score?
No! No, no, no, no!
Come on!!! Fucking spanish fucker!!!
Hello.
Nice, you are at home. I
am fucking exhausted!
Sore loser?
I'm going to sleep!
Cool hanging out with you, Linn!
Hello.
Everything okay?
Did you ask all of your
roomies to look after me?
Hm? No.
Holy fuck! You are such a bad liar!
Uh? Am I a bad liar?
Yeah!
I am a bad liar?
I am the fucking master liar. There's
no a better liar than me!
I mean, you have no idea what
I've gotten away with.
Tell me! What have you gotten away with?
No, I mean, you don't want to know.
I like seeing you laugh.
Holy fuck, Vilde...
Nagging me so fucking much
about that kose group stuff.
The kose group?!?
I had completely forgotten about it!
Yeah. Don't tell her that
because she'll get pissed.
She was terrified people just joined
for the revue parties or something.
Well, I was there to meet you.
Seriously?!
Yeah. Did you think I
was there to have fun?
Had you seen me before
that first kose meeting?
Yeah.
I saw you the first day of school.
Wow!
Fuck!
Hi, Vilde!
No, we don't have a Christmas tree here.
No.
Yeah, but...
If you are so fucking keen on a Christmas
tree you'll have to buy one yourself.
Well, you can buy a Christmas
tree anywhere, Vilde!
In Kiellands plass! There's...
Yeah. Okay, cool.
Bye!
Christmas tree?
Yeah!
I haven't told you...
Speaking of the Kose group. I'll be hosting
a Christmas get-together here on Friday.
Here?
Friday?
Do you wanna come?
I have actually promised my mom that...
I talked to her today.
And she really wanted
me to stop by at home.
To eat and stuff.
I don't know. I was thinking maybe
I'll just stay there for a while.
Just take it one day at a time.
THURSDAY. 13:55
Hey, boys!
Hey, Isak.
What's up?
All good! All good!
Peace!
How is it going with Evak?
Good, I guess. We are taking it
day by day, minute by minute.
Minute by minute. Oh holy shit! Listen!
Even and Isak, minute by minute.
That's the kind of shit
you can sell to NRK.
People would dig it, man!
I'd watch it myself!
That's kind of fucked up to think about.
Why? If you like, banged on TV.
You don't think I can handle
watching to guys bang?
No, it's more me it's fucked up for.
That you'd be watching us bang.
Because that would be a real turn off.
You think I am a turn off?
You are definitely not a turn on.
Bullshit! You'd so bang me if
you had the chance. I know!
No!
Okay, bullshit. Who would you bang first?
Out of all of us?
Mahdi, Jonas or me?
Jonas!
Right! That's what I thought!
Okay, between me and Mahdi, then?
Oh! That would be you...
Mahdi!
Second place, bro!!
What the fuck? Why doesn't
anyone want to bang me?
You are just desperate.
It's just how it is!
I'm not desperate. I'm super chill.
Oh shit, bro! There
are the dance chicks!
Hi! You are Isak, right?
Yeah!
We just heard that you have a
thing with Even in third year.
And so we just wanted
to say that we dig it.
It's insanely cute two
guys being together.
Not big deal.
And the dance-group will have a
Christmas meeting this Friday.
You can join, if you want to.
I don't think I can because I am going to
the kose group Christmas get-together.
- That's too bad.
- We'll see you around.
Bye.
- What the fuck?
- Bro?!?
What?
Christmas get-together
with the kose group?
Yeah. I'll be there, you
are welcome to join, guys.
And like I'm hosting, you are
more than welcome to come!
The gate to paradise was wide open
and you are talking about a
get-together with the kose group. Man?
Guys, you need to start
getting chicks yourselves.
Fucking hell! The world is so unfair!
Fucking hell!
What did he say?
Should we ditch him and
go to the other one?
@Ledgerina
- Now it is straight.
- No, it is loopsided.
- Now it is loopsided.
- No, it is straight.
- Oh, now it is loopsided.
- No, it's straight.
- Yeah.
- Maybe you are loopsided, Linn?
- No.
- Yes.
- I did it!
- I can help you.
Where's that from?
Drummer boy!
Justin Bieber.
What? He sang that one?
Yeah! He is the one who sings it!
Did the exams go all right for you guys?
No. I got a message that I am
failing German and English.
I didn't know there was
a 10% absence limit!
How could you not known about that?
I have told you the entire school year!
Yeah, but I thought
you said that because
you were jealous that I was
hanging out with Kasper a lot.
Why would I be jealous?
Because you are not getting
any dick yourself!
I get plenty of dick!
Chris...
Well, she can have this one.
And this one!
That one is beautiful!
It might be more fitting.
Is it used?
Is it from Eskild?
Where is it from, Noora?
Oh! Holy fuck!
Where is it from?
Take it away! Take it
away from the table!
I don't know! I don't know!
- Oh my God!
- Smell it then!
No? Smell it?!?
God! What is your problem?
Smell it to see if it smells like dick!
You smell it then! Oh my God!
But Eskild is your friend.
Yeah! That's pretty obvious!
You can do it!
Hey!
- Is it a fight?
- You are on, you are on.
Exactly! Now you've got the attitude.
You are not going to hit Vilde that hard
or anything like that but...
What should I do then?
You are a predator and she is your prey.
Do you get what I mean?
She is what?
She is your prey. You are a predator.
You are a lion and she is...
Oohhhh! Okay! Okay!
Yeah? You know?
But you can't make a big deal of it
because then the prey will flee.
Seriously, I am really nervous.
You shouldn't be... Are
you in love or what?
I don't know. Maybe.
- Oh.
- No!!
Yes, I think so.
What if she doesn't say yes?
- That's life.
- What is the hint, then?
It's not the end of the
world if it doesn't work.
Just think that it is a positive
thing if it works so...
It's fucking awkward if I
stand there and she says no.
Yeah, but you don't ask her right
away: "Hey, should we hook up?"
- Straighten back, smile a little.
- Should I touch her?
If it's appropiate.
Do I look good?
Yeah! Nice!
It's a little pumped. I see it.
This sweater... I bought
it a size too big.
I have to drink more. Where is the beer?
- Hello.
- Hey.
Be cool, you know?
What's up?
We are helping Magnus to bang Vilde.
Wow!
How is it going?
He shouldn't be so desperate.
Then I think he's got it!
It's fucking impossible
not to be desperate
when I don't get what it
means to be desperate!
Just imagine... Who do you think
of as a really cool, laid-back guy?
Pretend to be like him.
Try to be that person.
- James Bond, then?
- Yeah, sure.
You know what, Magnus?
I think you should go
all in and be yourself.
Take desperate to a whole new level.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's into something.
What do you mean?
Show her how desperate
you really are, then!
Let it all out!
Take desperate to a new level.
Fuck! I am going to do it!
Bye. Talk to you later.
I gotta see this.
- Hello.
How is it going?
I'm fine.
I have just talked to my mum.
And...
The reason she is anoyed is because
she really wants to meet you.
Okay.
So...
What do you say if we drop by tomorrow?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
You don't think this is weird?
No. I don't find anything weird anymore.
Okay.
As long as you are smiling and...
I can do that.
Wearing clothes, then...
Then life is chill.
I promise that I will wear clothes.
Hello.
Sana!
Hi.
- You have met each other, right?
- The Kose group.
Yeah.
My biology partner.
And friend.
Yeah, how is Isak really
doing in biology?
He is useful.
Huh?!?
I guess...
Sana, that's such bullshit!
I helped you towards a fucking 5 while
I have been on that 6 the whole year!
I have a Christmas present for you.
For me?!?
What is it?
Open it!
Okay. I will open it.
10%!
Thank you!
What a cool biology partner!
It wasn't of any use for you after all?
I used it right now, didn't I?
True!
You are not getting any of this!
It's not good for you.
Then it's not good for you either!
It's completely fine for
me, but not for you.
Are you going to be the one who
tells me if it is good or not?
Of course I am!
That's my job!
- You've got a job?
- Yeah, it's literally my job.
That's why I am doing all this, you know?
I found this poster on Løkka that said
"Even Bech Næsheim needs a
support person and boyfriend".
And then you applied?
Yeah.
I thought, "Holy fuck, he is so hot!"
That was nice.
Yeah.
You are so nice.
I could have done it for free
but it's nice I'm getting...
Are you getting paid?!?
Yeah, your mom pays me 500 a week.
What?
Yeah!
- No wonder...
- Are you kidding me?
There's no wonder why
she wants to meet me.
Holy fuck!!!
I'm getting some of that money.
- No.
- Yes.
It's my money! You are not getting any.
- Yes! Come one!
- No.
Hello.
Hi.
Do you like cats?
Yeah, a lot.
I do too.
Meow.
What was that?
Nothing.
Yes, do it again.
Meow.
I have never had sex before and
I really want to have sex.
You are welcome to fuck me.
Thanks.
Hi!
Hello there!
- May I sit down?
- Yeah, absolutely.
I'm sitting here with my angel.
Yeah.
- Does it look nice?
- Very nice.
How are you doing?
It's been a long time
since last time we spoke.
Yeah! It's been a fucking long
time since we last spoke.
It's a little weird. I've
been thinking about it. We...
We used to hang out all the
time, but now it's like...
We only see each other at school.
Yeah.
And then it's just "hi" and...
We should hang out more.
- Absolutely.
- We should.
We really should do something because...
I honestly miss the time when we...
When we used to hang out more.
First upper school
secondary school and...
Yeah.
The summer vacation before...
Before Nissen when it just...
was a lot of drama and
all that stuff, but...
But, hey! You've gotten a boyfriend!
Yes. I have.
He is really handsome.
He is.
You, lucky pig!
You better watch out for me!
I might steal him.
I have...
I have been thinking about something.
What's that?
Nah, just...
I actually wanted to say sorry
for that stuff last year.
When I was...
When I was ruining it for you
and Jonas and all that stuff.
It's not okay.
What I did.
I've been thinking about that.
You didn't fuck it up
between Jonas and me.
It was Jonas and I who
fucked it up between us.
Might be, but...
I still feel like I tricked you.
And..
When I told you that I had feelings
for you. That wasn't truth.
Hey, I figured that out.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
I'm over it.
And you should be too.
Seriously.
Can't we talk about
your boyfriend instead?
Is he "the man of your life"?
I don't know that.
No?
Is it important?
No...
But...
Is it okay between the two of you?
Yeah, yeah!
I mean, right now it's amazing
but a week ago it was very bad so
it's a bit up and down.
Stressful.
Yeah, or...
Anyway.
The fact that it is so good when it's
good it's also kind of the reason of
why it is so bad when it's bad.
Does that make any sense?
And...
It can all suddenly
be over tomorrow but
I'm still insanely happy
that I have met him.
Because...
That's when you were certain
that you like boys?
Yeah.
I mean, no.
More because...
I was fake before.
I mean...
I...
I was only lying at home watching
Narcos or gaming or stuff.
And I'm over that. Now I
want my life to be real.
Even if that means it will be
absolutely awful at times,
it's still way better than
to be fake and boring for everything.
Well said.
It's a little bit cliché but...
You never know who will die tomorrow.
You know?
And...
Wheter you believe in
Allah, or Jesus or...
The theory of Evolution, or...
Parallel universes.
There's only one thing
we all now for certain.
What's that?
That life is...
NOW.
EVERYTHING IS LOVE.