Hello.
- He's on a bus with William.
- Who's William?
He's the hottest, coolest guy
in all of third-year.
Invite me to dinner with your mom.
- Friday.
- Yeah, Friday.
Guess who's invited to a pre-party
with the Penetrator guys?
- Are you kidding?
- Really, Eva?
William asked me if I wanted to
go outside with him. I think he wants to hook up.
Jonas (27 minutes ago):
What about that dinner?
SHAME
FRIDAY, 4:11 P.M.
- Hi, Thea! Is Jonas in?
- Yeah, he's in the living room.
Your girlfriend is here.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What are you playing?
FIFA.
- What's up?
- What?
Where's your russ crew today?
Don't you have a shitload to do?
It's only two years and seven months until
russ time. You'd better start working.
I know. I'm really jealous of you guys
who spend your time
on more constructive things...
like playing video games all day long.
What are you mad about now?
I'm not mad.
I'm kidding, have a sense of humor!
I need to talk to you.
Drama!
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with me.
Okay... so...
why haven't you replied to my messages?
I was busy.
So you're not...
You're not mad I forgot
our thing yesterday?
No, no. I...
- I don't care.
- You don't care?
Yeah, don't worry.
- Okay, good.
- Good.
Fine.
- Yeah, I'll be on my way.
- You're welcome to stay.
No, I have a lot of stuff to do.
- Yeah, I'll call you.
- Yes.
MONDAY, 3:11 P.M.
He doesn't want to talk about it,
and he claims he's not pissed,
but I don't believe that.
But isn't he just pissed because he thinks
you don't want him to meet your mom?
Maybe he thinks you're
embarrassed of him?
You think so?
- Just let him meet your mom. What's the problem?
- Long story.
Just so you know, I told Chris to tell Sana
that she can't be on our bus any longer.
- Why?
- Hello?!
She nearly ruined our entire social status,
and I had to fix it.
I had to explain to the Penetrator guys
that we're not the kind of girls
who create a lot of drama.
We made a really bad impression.
- Might it not have been Sana's fault?
- Have you met Sana? She's incredibly rude.
Well, Sara and Ingrid
aren't the nicest people in the world either.
I know Sara and Ingrid really well, and they're
not the kind of girls who start drama.
Well...
William...
What's up with you two?
I think we're going to sleep together.
Okay?
Not to be a prude, but don't you think you should
get to know him a little better first?
Why? He's perfect.
I'd much rather want my first time
to be with the hottest, coolest, '97 guy
than someone random.
- You'll always remember your first time.
- It's your first time?
I've also heard that William is
really, really good in bed.
You don't usually get an orgasm your first time.
But with him, you do.
- I've heard about five girls who got it.
- Okay...
Hello?! Show some support,
I'm doing this for you guys too!
This will guarantee us
a spot on their bus.
Vilde...
But I was wondering something...
- Can I borrow the pill from you guys?
- You can't borrow the pill.
I didn't mean one pill,
I meant like for a week or something.
- I'm not on it.
- Me neither.
Aren't you sleeping with your boyfriend?
I use a NuvaRing,
and you don't want to borrow that.
- Where can you get it?
- At the doctor's.
So much effort,
can't you just order it online or something?
- I don't know.
- Just go to the school doctor, then?
- Can you come?
- Why?
Because it's really embarassing
to go there alone.
And it's so much less embarassing
if we came...
Of course we can come, Vilde.
William!
WEDNESDAY, 12:35 A.M.
- Hey, are you awake?
- Yeah, I can't sleep.
- What are you doing?
- It's just boring work.
No wonder your grades are going down,
if you don't sleep at night.
I definitely won't get any sleep
if we're going to talk about grades.
- How are Ingrid and Sara doing?
- Why do you have to interrogate me all the time?
Sweetie, it was just a normal question.
Yeah. Yes, they're doing fine.
I got myself a boyfriend.
Oh?
- Who is it, then?
- Who?
I thought I could just introduce you to him.
Yes!
- I mean, before you leave again?
- Uh-huh.
Maybe... we can invite him over for dinner?
Yes.
- When are you leaving again?
- Saturday morning.
Maybe Friday night, then?
How nice.
WEDNESDAY, 1:15 P.M.
Hi!
Are you friends again, or what?
This is Noora. I've told you about Noora.
- Noora.
- Hello. Jonas.
- We have an appointment at the school doctor.
- Yeah, where is Vilde?
Vilde will meet us there.
- What's going on at the doctor's?
- We're helping a friend get laid.
- Okay, good luck with that.
- Thanks!
- You guys are so slow!
- Sorry!
- But, are you doing anything on Friday?
- There you are!
- What is she doing here?
- I have something to tell you!
- How did you know we were here?
- Eva's boyfriend told me.
- Did you tell your boyfriend?!
- I have the best news in the world!
- Sana sold all the toilet paper!
- Vilde Lien?
- I'm serious!
- How did she manage that?
I don't know! She said you just had to
send her your account number and address.
- Are you kidding?
- No!
- Can she please join our bus?
- It's not something illegal?
- No, no! She's Muslim.
- What's that got to do with it?
No, but Muslims go to hell
if they do something illegal,
and I don't think she wants to do that.
- Welcome! Everyone. What can I help you with?
- She's going to sleep with a guy.
You're so lucky!
For the first time.
Yeah. That's not so simple.
- What do you mean?
- My cousin bled so much that she got anemia.
- That's bullshit.
- No,
you might bleed during your first intercourse.
Large bleedings should be taken seriously
,because they can in fact kill you.
She just got a little weak.
Then she was lucky.
I actually had a patient once who bled so much
that we feared she would die.
- Because she had sex for the first time?
- No, she cut herself. Tried to commit suicide.
She bled so much that we had to
give her something called a blood transfusion.
But she just wants to go on the pill.
Right. When will the intercourse take place?
On Friday.
- On Friday?!
- Friday?
- On Friday?
- That's what I was trying to say,
I'm meeting William on Friday,
and I thought we could pre-party at Eva's.
Are we drinking?
Aren't you the one having sex with him?
I can't drink by myself,
you have to support me.
Why do you have to drink at all?
That's not possible anyway,
my mom will be home, and Jonas is coming.
- Please, we'll just--
- Have you girls seen one like this before?
Can anyone show me how to put on a condom?
It's difficult to open...
It tends to be...
Let's see now...
There we go!
FRIDAY, 7:47 P.M.
Honestly now, how painful is it?
I don't remember anything
from my first time.
Just drink, you won't feel anything.
Do you want to be so drunk
that you don't remember anything?
- Were you drunk your first time?
- Me? No.
Pinch my arm. How much does it hurt?
- Seriously?
- It doesn't resemble pinching.
If you just relax, it won't hurt.
How do you know? You haven't had sex!
Okay, seriously. William needs to call soon.
What was his last text?
"Picking you up at 7,
we'll do something chill. W."
It's ten to eight, can't you just call him?
I don't want him to think I'm desperate for dick.
- But what if he doesn't send a message?
- Then I would be a little bit relieved.
Vilde, you don't have to have sex with him
if you don't want to.
- I want to! But I just don't want it to hurt.
- No, but that's why you have to relax.
- What about him turns you on?
- Turns me on?
- Yeah, what makes you horny?
- Horny...
- Nothing. I don't get horny.
- You're never horny?
No. Are you?
Yes!
Then I really don't get why you don't have sex.
Hey, I bet I can make you horny.
I'm not doing some kind of lesbian thing.
Vilde, it's not some lesbian thing.
Just listen to me, turn around to
lie on your back and close your eyes.
Imagine you and William
standing in the bedroom.
Are you imagining it?
- Yes.
- What's happening?
- Yeah, describe it.
We're standing in the bedroom.
- I'm wearing a white dress.
- That's good, continue.
Okay!
The dress is almost the same as that
Stella McCartney dress,
with lace at the bottom.
Except it doesn't have lace at the bottom.
I have my hair down. No! I'm wearing it up.
But it's a bit loose so my hair falls down some.
I'm wearing light pink lipstick. Not the lightest
from Mac, but the one that's kind of medium.
This actually works!
- Really?
- I think so.
You get horny by talking about
clothes and make-up?
Yes!
People get horny from different things.
I was watching a documentary about
a whole village that got horny from donkeys.
Eva?
I'm coming!
Okay, you guys have to leave now.
We can't go. He hasn't texted yet.
Go to your place, then.
I can't go home, I've been drinking.
Can't we just sit here?
We'll be quiet.
Eva?
Yeah, I'm coming!
Okay, okay! But you have to be really quiet.
And leave through the window, okay?
- Hi!
- Hi. Shouldn't your boyfriend be here by now?
Yes, but... he sent a message
that he's a bit delayed.
Okay.
To Jonas:
Where the hell are you?
- It smells good, do you need help?
- No, it's fine.
What was that?
I think I forgot to turn off the movie.
I'll fix it.
- What are you doing here?
- Is Vilde here?
No... yes, but you can't come here.
- Hi! Nice to meet you.
- Hi. William.
No, no. This isn't my boyfriend.
This is Vilde's boyfriend.
Oh, really? Who's Vilde?
A friend. William thought Vilde was here,
but she isn't, so he's leaving now.
Chris! Noora! Vilde!
What are you guys doing here?
We...
remember when I borrowed your jacket?
Well, we thought we'd bring it over.
But... you weren't in your basement,
so we left it outside your bag.
No, I mean the window!
Yeah, thanks.
But I'm sure you're leaving again, right?
Yeah, we have so many jackets to deliver.
So we'll just...
- See you! Come on.
- Bye!
- What's going on here, Eva?
- Nothing's going on.
- Were those girls drunk?
- No.
- Where the hell are you?
- Sorry, but I can't come tonight.
What do you mean?
- I forgot I had to help my mom with a thing--
- Can't you help her tomorrow?
No, it's really important.
I have to do it now.
- Who was that?
- That was my sister.
- Jonas!
- I'm sorry, but I really have to go now. Sorry.