- Seriously. I can’t be bothered. Just pass it.
- Seriously. I can’t be bothered.
Just come and get it.
- Yousef is meeting Noora.
- Seriously? Noora, Sana's friend?
Yes, Noora.
- That sucks.
- He’s getting jealous!
- There’s just something I have to tell you ...
- I know already.
- What?
- The thing with Yousef.
Do you like him?
Just because you think a guy is cute,
doesn’t mean everyone else thinks so too.
What the fuck is this?!
Why are you so cold towards people, Sana?
Who’s your best bud, then?
- I’m not sure if I have any anymore.
- Of course you do.
There is nothing enthusing anymore,
Or that feels like a real feeling.
[Hi. There’s something I have to tell you.]
[Hi. What are you doing today?
Can we meet up?]
[I'm hungover af]
[Magnus and I are talking]
[How are you doing Vilde?]
[He thinks I’ve cheated on him with Elias.]
[Vilde <3 We’re gonna kill those
who made the hate account.
Sana: I’m also hungover
af and dad is visiting from
Bergen to celebrate my
18th birthday. Yippee!]
[No Yippee]
[Plus fml]
[Eva!! Mom said it’s okay
for us to celebrate your
18th birthday at my
place on Friday!!]
[SHE DID?? Fucking hell!!]
[She asked why
you couldn’t have it at your
place, and I was like… ehhh..
they’re renovating]
[After the last party]
[Hahahaha!! Awesome!!
Who are we going to invite??]
Hi.
Talking to me?
Sorry for being mad.
So you’re no longer mad?
That’s good. I thought
you were going to be mad for the rest of your life.
(Okay, are you ready?)
Why aren’t you friends
with Even anymore?
No, the guy doesn’t want to be with us anymore -
So we can’t make him.
So it’s not because he ...
... tried to kiss Mikael?
Because I heard Mikael freaked out.
That’s not why. It’s ...
A lot happened.
The guy just started
doing a lot of random stuff.
Then he tried to
kiss Mikael, among other things.
And we tried to get him to chill out,
but it didn’t work.
Then he started to skip school, -
And I talked to Sonja and
she told me he was depressed.
And when she told us,
we tried to call him and text him a lot,
But ...
It’s his deal if he -
Doesn’t want to hang out with us.
You know he’s dating Isak?
I think he misses you guys.
Because he asked
about you the other day.
He did?
Tell him hi, then.
Hey?
You know Yousef?
Just forget about it.
I’m over him.
... Yeah, but I’m wondering
if someone like planned it or...
Yes, it seems like it.
Of course! With World Web Wide.
What if that happened to one of you? Oh my God, it’d destroy you.
Especially you! It’d ruin your whole reputation.
Imagine just taking a picture ...
It doesn't mean that! It just means you
forgot to take off the tag ...
- You guys?
- Everyone! Ingrid answered.
"We were sure Vilde made saranors2.
Again, sorry. We seriously feel so bad."
*Eva is using an Oslo accent.
"If we have ruined anything between
her and Magnus, we’re soooo sorry,"
"- but it was Isak who started everything. You should me mad at him,
it’s so important that we stand together as one bus."
I just think it’s so weird that Isak -
Would make a hate account
on Sara. Like ... why?
He’s probably pissed
at her for some reason.
I don’t know
what’s going on in Isak’s head, -
But I actually thought he’d
changed. Apparently not.
I’m really disappointed.
What are you writing?
"You can stand together, we’re out.
We won’t be on a bus with people who hate."
We’re without a bus again, then.
She's saying ...
I know about a cheap van we can buy.
"Hello! We have to talk before
you drop out of the bus."
What is there to talk about?
If you make a hate account, I don’t
want to be friends with you.
There’s nothing to talk about!
Don’t you agree?
People are totally crazy.
I think it has something to do with that Trump being the president.
You! You!
We thought we’d all chip in for this
for Eva’s birthday. Isn’t it cool?!
It’s six litres!
You’re in, right?
You know that saranors2 account?
It was me.
Do you think Eva will forgive me?
Do you have to tell?
Of course I have to tell.
She can’t go around
hating on Isak.
But that’s ... hate disappears ...
It’s gone tomorrow.
[Dear Eva. Please don’t be mad at Is ...]
[Eva. I’ve tried writing ...]
[Sara Nørstelien has published
something in Flawless 99]
EXTRAORDINARY BUS MEETING
We’re calling you in for an extraordinary bus meeting. Because there are oral exams tomorrow, and most people won’t be at school, we’ll take it on WEDNESDAY after school (SARA: IMPORTANT that EVERYONE comes, also the ones who have dropped out of the bus)
As you all know, there has been a lot of drama surrounding hate accounts lately. There are lots of rumors, and today I got a question from the teachers about it. I said nothing, of course, because we’d like to keep this outside of school. We remind you that this actually can lead to expulsion. It’s not worth it. It’s very important that everyone agrees we won’t involve the school in this, which is why it’s important to have a meeting. The meeting will take place on the benches outside the B-building kl 16 ON WEDNESDAY.
[I honestly think it should be reported to the school.]
[Me too.]
[Come to the meeting and talk to us!!
We haven’t had the opportunity to properly explain what’s happening]
Hey! You’ve reached Chris ...
[Did you see the
post on Flawless now?
They’re talking about
reporting it to the school,
I have to tell them it was me,
Isak can be expelled]
[It’s totally nerdy to report it to the school.]
[I’ve made up with Isak, and he has apologized. I understand you’re angry with Ingrid and Lea for the ellevillevillde2 account, but talk to them. If they report it to the school, everything will be exposed and Isak can be expelled too. It’ll also be very bad for the bus.]
[??????]
[I don’t think that message was for me??]
[Is this for real??]
Welcome to voice mail from Telenor.
Please leave a
message after the beep.
Hi, Eva.
I just wanted ... I just called
to say I’m sorry again.
[Dear Sana, happy birthday
to you and Jesus Christ*,
you’re AWESOME!! We dig you
and we love you a lot Sanasol!
Love from Eva, Chris, Noora, Vilde]
*Sana was born on December 24th.
(Norwegian Christmas)
I’ve said sorry to everyone on the bus
that it was me, not Isak.
And I’ve apologized to Sara.
Yeah ...
Yeah, that’s all I wanted to say.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Have you talked to them?
No, I haven’t talked to them yet.
Nothing at all?
No ... We chatted a bit.
Yes? What did they say?
No, they’re a bit mad,
but I think it’ll pass soon.
Just be honest. What did they write?
Uh ...
They wrote that
ever since the bus ...
That ...
You’ve changed and that ...
They don’t like you as much anymore. I don’t know.
Do you know if they'll come
to the bus meeting tomorrow??
I don’t know.
But I’ll be there.
Don't be upset, okay?
I'll get them to come to
the bus meeting. I promise.
They’ll be there.
I’ve tried to write something.
- To them?
- Yes.
What did you write?
I wrote ...
Hi.
In the 9th grade,
there was a social worker
- who told me
I had an anger issue.
I thought: Fuck her,
she doesn’t understand shit. Because ...
She didn’t understand shit.
But now I’m wondering if
maybe she was right.
Because I am angry.
I’m angry because ...
Because I’m not Muslim enough.
And no matter what I do,
I’m never Norwegian enough.
And I’m not Moroccan enough.
And I’m not chill enough.
And I’m not pretty enough.
I’m angry because I made it so
important to fit in on a russ bus.
I’m angry because I don’t fit in anywhere.
Because I always get angry
and fuck up.
But most of all, I’m sad
because it affected you.
Because that bus is not important to me.
It’s not important to me to be Muslim enough, -
Or if I fit in with Moroccans or Norwegians.
[Because that bus is not
important to me. It’s not
important to me to be Muslim
enough, or if I fit in with Moroccans or
Norwegians.
As long as I belong
with you guys. The biggest losers
in school.
I’m sorry for what I’ve
done, I don’t give a shit
if I’m expelled, just please,
forgive me.
Sana]
There is nothing enthusing anymore.
[Are you coming?]
Or that feels like a real feeling.
And it just started pouring down.
Do you know if they’re coming?
I think they’re coming.
Because it’s a bit meaningless without them.
Everyone here agree we
won’t report it to the school?
You agree too, right?
Did anyone have their last
class with them or something?
- No.
- Not me.
I saw Eva during the break, at least.
They haven’t written
to you or anything?
- No.
- Maybe you could try calling them?
Hey, you’ve reached Chris.
I can’t pick up the phone right now, sorry ...
I can’t ...
But do you think Eva
and Vilde wanted to report it to the school?
I don’t know.
But they haven’t said anything about it?
But they understand that
if they do that, we have to tell them -
Why we made the Vilde account
and that’ll affect you too.
I think they understand that.
But seriously, how long are we supposed to be bothered with sitting here?
- It doesn’t seem like they’re coming.
- There’s not point in sitting here.
What time is it anyway?
4.20 ...
- Should we just leave, you guys?
- Yeah, let’s go.
- Can you check when the 19 bus is coming?
- We can take this one.
Let's go.
Sana! Sana!
Sana!
I hope you have room,
I hope you have room.
I’m coming all by myself
and without any baggage.
You can tell me to get it together
and put me in my place,
- if you find a window for me.
Catch me when I fall
or lose myself,
- and the last flame or spark.
I’ll let you finish crying
for a life at my expense
- if you find a window for me.
Where did you get this?
Was it you?
If you fuck with Sana,
you fuck with us!
Bye Bitches!
Bitches!
We’re fasting.
We’re not having hotdogs.
Is that Fedon Lindberg,
or who is it?
I’ve probably had chlamydia like thirteen times.
- It’s like ... just take some antibiotics and it’s gone.
- Yeah.
But in the eye?
I haven’t heard that one before.
You can just do it from your side.
Should I do it now?
Bad hit!
Awesome! Look what he did now!
Hey guys.
- Hello!
- Hey.
- Hey. Magnus.
- Elias.
You know my girlfriend.
- Oh ... the blonde one?
- Yeah.
Right! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She has talked lots about you.
- No, she has?
- Yeah, she talked about you a lot.
Ah!
What does she say about me?
- Hey! Can I also have some?
- No!
- Please?
- You have your own drinks, you’re eighteen!
- Exactly! I’m eighteen!
- Drink your own drinks!
Should we play a drinking game? You, me and Chris since we’re looking to hook up tonight?
- The drinking game of pointing.
- Pointing?
Okay, so we’re supposed to point at each other ...?
It’s like ... “Most likely to ... fail their exams”
... Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
You have three significant others!
- That’s me!
- Do we have a knife so we can cut the cake?
Move it, move it, move it! We have a gift!
Open it! Put down the cake!
Open! Open! Open here!
Open, open, open!
What the fuck?!
- Are you crazy?!
- It’s 1,5 ...
- No, it’s 7,5!
- It’s six litres!
- Oh my God! Did you guys get this? I don’t know what to say.
- You’re going to open it now, right?
- Open! Open! Open!
- Eva, come on, do it!
- Shake it!
- No,no, no!
- Hi.
Here you’re sitting?
Yeah. You get a bit tired when fasting.
Yeah, is it ...
Is it going well? The fasting?
Now there are only 3 hours,
14 minutes and 32 seconds left.
Yeah ...
- But I just ...
I just wanted to ...
I like Yousef.
You’re kidding? I knew it!
And when I understood there
was something between you two ...
No! There’s nothing between us.
But there’s something between you.
I saw you guys hooking up.
I can’t even be bothered.
Just look at this ...
From there.
[Hi sorry I just freaked out
and suddenly took off
yesterday. It didn’t have anything
to do with you.]
[Don’t worry about it,
sorry for being all over
you, it didn’t have
anything to do with you.]
[Haha ok]
[But I was just
wondering one thing, have you
talked to Sana?]
[Sana? No, what’s up?]
[if it’s okay if you maybe
don’t say anything to her]
[Is there something between you!?!!]
[No or I don’t know I like her a bit]
[But does she like you?!?!
I’m FREAKING OUT here!
I DIDN’T KNOW!!]
[No! Relax! I don’t
think she likes me.
Nothing has
happened! We walked
home together
after you last Friday,
and I thought maybe
she liked me, but the next
day she blocked
me on Facebook, so I don’t
think she’s that interested.]
[but anyway I don’t want
her to think that I’m hooking
up with her friends.
Or hooking up with anyone.]
[Ok. I won’t say anything,
after all, it was nothing.]
[you haven’t said anything?
she’s super cold]
[I haven’t said
anything, but
she’s a bit strange
nowadays towards
everyone.
I think she’s really
stressed about
her mock exams …]
[Do you think maybe
she heard about it
from someone else?]
[I don’t know, I doubt it,
I haven’t heard
any rumors about it]
[Do you want me to try
talking to her about you?]
[Yeah, maybe?]
[What are you going to say?]
[I can say that you like her.]
[Is that a good idea?]
[At least then you’ll
know if she
likes you back.]
[Ok do that]
[Did you talk to her?]
[Noora?]
[Hi, sorry. I sent her a
text but I haven’t
gotten a response..]
[What did you write?]
[Just that I wanted
to tell her
something nice.]
[What are you doing?
I seriously need
some advice.
I met Sana. I think
she hates me.]
[I don’t want
her to hate me.
I swear that
we’re soulmates.]
[Aw <3 soulmates <3
She doesn’t hate you]
[I wanted to tell her that
I like her, but instead
I was just an
asshole and took
her ball.
Fuck am I
12 or what]
[I’m at st. hanshaugen
in the sun and having coffee
if you want a therapist.]
[What’s your number?]
[Have you told
Sana you like her?]
[No?]
[Ok. We talked
about you at
school today.]
[What did she say?]
[I think she likes you.]
[Did she say that?]
[She said she didn’t,
but she said it
in a way that seemed
like she did, if you
know what I mean?]
[No, I don’t
understand shit.]
[Just forget it.
don’t talk about
me anymore.]
[Ok :(]
Noora?
I have something to tell you.
And please don’t be mad.
What is it?
- I ...
- Noora?
Thanks for the e-mail.