I can have Norwegian friends and
be myself at the same time.
Come on! Are you all deaf?!?
- Now!
- Come on!
Out, out, out!
Two conditions: You pay for the
bus and I become the bus boss.
Maybe we are better off
with someone else.
If I think about him being with
someone else, then I'll just break.
Why don't you believe in Allah?
Islam... or religion in general, just
creates a lot of anxiety in people.
Sana!
SATURDAY
09:58
-
- Where have you been tonight?
- I slept at Yousef's.
- Yousef?
- Yeah.
I saw Yousef with Sana outside last night.
Mom, I am 20 years old!
I can go out. Oh my God!
Don't "Oh my God" me. Hello?
My phone died.
Why didn't you tell us?
Why didn't you call?
I've just said my phone died!
I haven't done anything wrong!
Where were you last night?
I don't understand you.
You don't need to understand,
this is very easy, Elias!
Tell me where you were last night!
- What do you want, mom?
- I want to know where have you been.
It's very simple.
As long as you live in this
house, you follow our rules.
- Oh my God!
- No discussion.
And you know you have a
sister who is 17 years old!
You have to be a role model for her!
Why do you bring her into this?
She'll be 18 in a few months.
She can take care of herself now!
Yeah, but... listen!
I know she is mature enough but...
I am not thrilled about her and Yousef
spending so much time together.
- What's wrong with that?
- Is there something between them?
Don't ask me! You have
to ask her about that!
I see... Sana told me she met
Yousef outside by chance.
Yeah! If she said that
you have to trust her.
You have to stop being so skeptical
and start trusting your children.
Oh my God!
When Elias woke up, Eskild was sitting
there and started hitting on him.
He was like: "Hi, are you
waking up with me?"
Elias didn't understand anything!
He looked terrified and
threw up all over Eskild!
Then he stopped hitting on him.
- Vilde!
- No.
Hi!
Hi.
- What's up?
- We are talking about last Friday's party.
You should have been there! It was so
fucking fun! So many handsome boys!
Yeah! Are you crazy? You
took them for yourself!
There is something about those
west-side boys... They are like...
- That Alexander!
- Yeah. The tall one?
Yeah! He was something...
He was so cute with those curls!
- Didn't you hook up with him?
- Huh?
You have to take the
chance once it's there!
You went around both, in the
front and in the back.
And not only in the bus,
to put it that way...
You really enjoyed yourself, at least!
- We texted you, though.
- Yeah. What were you doing on Friday?
Nothing, we just...
Nothing special. Chilling out.
We were tired.
- But you'll join the Karaoke on Friday?
- Yes, you must!
- It will be fucking fun!
- Karaoke?
Yes, you have to check out the event
Sara posted on our bus page.
There's a karaoke party. Lots of
people from school are coming.
I think it will be fucking fun!
- We should invite those boys.
- Yeah! Then you could get to meet them.
- Yes. Oh my God!
- It will be so fun!
The bus page?
Yeah! On Facebook.
Yes. It is actually our old bus
group, but I added you, didn't I?
I don't think so.
Didn't  I? Okay, sorry.
I'll do it right away.
It will be fun as fuck. Is Magnus coming?
Of course Magnus is coming.
If I come, he comes.
And in more that one way...
TUESDAY
10:01
Karaoke party
- It will be great.
- Hope you have singing voices.
Vilde: It will be super awesome!
Did you feel that Sara was trying to
hide something from us yesterday?
No... What's that?
I don't know, I just have a bad feeling.
If you think about it...
those girls can simply take the
whole bus and throw us away.
They are paying for it.
Yeah, but...
Why would they bother joining forces with
us if they are going to throw us out?
Because they wanted that bus!
I don't think they are that psycho.
And didn't Sara say that she would
send me a copy of the contract?
Yeah... I don't know. Maybe?
- Yeah. She said it but she hasn't done it.
- No...
When did all this Russ stuff
become so important to you?
I have to ask her about that contract.
Sara! Can I talk to you?
I was just wondering what is
going on with the bus contract.
What do you mean?
Weren't you supposed to send me a
copy of the contract proposal?
I did! Didn't I? I think I did!
I don't think you did.
Maybe you forgot to do it?
Like when you "forgot" to add
me and Noora to the bus page?
No, I think I did.
Maybe I have the wrong e-mail address?
Or did it end in the spam filter?
Spam filter?
Because Mari's copy did that.
Oh, yeah...
Here is it.
Good.
Mari sent me a message saying we have
to have a contract meeting on Monday,
and you have to come because
you are the boss, so...
Sana, I don't mean to
lead things so much.
I am just so used to be the bus boss...
Then stuff just happens.
I don't mean to override you, in any way.
No, it's all right.
But, did you see the Karaoke event?
Yeah.
- It would be cool if everybody came.
- Yeah! We are coming.
Cool! I feel like we have to
merge the buses a little more.
Get to know each other.
True.
THURSDAY
15:43
What are you doing?
Have you seen my green veil?
You are looking through my things!?
No.
Yes!
Why?
Because I don't know what
you're doing anymore.
I am not doing anything!
You go out with all your friends and
suddenly I see you outside with Yousef.
You don't tell me anything. I
am worried, don't you see?
You talk about my friend as if
they were criminals or something!
It's not like all non-Muslims lie
or drink or have lots of sex!
I know that, Sana.
Then why can't you trust that I
have friends who are good people?
I trust you, Sana.
But I know many young people don't
follow the same rules as you.
And you know Norwegian society has
lots of customs that don't suit us.
There are lots of things on
Islam that don't suit us!
That don't suit me!
Like its view on homosexuality
and why Islam says that Muslim men
can marry non-religious women,
but Muslim women can't.
Isn't that a bit gender discriminatory?
At least in the society we live in?
When Islam says that the Quran should
adapt to any society you live in?
Where is all this coming from?
I am just asking!
Am I not allowed to?
Yes, you are allowed to ask.
You are allowed to ask.
And what? Don't you
have any answers?
I am just worried about you, Sana.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I won't get hurt!
Were you fighting with mom?
Could you tell?
I heard it.
What did you do with
Yousef the other day?
With Yousef?
Yeah, mom told me she saw you together.
Oh, yeah.
He just walked me home from Noora's.
You like him?
Huh? No!
Yousef is a nice guy.
It's just that he is not a Muslim.
Yousef is the most Muslim guy I know.
He doesn't drink, he is always
respectful to everyone.
Yes, but he doesn't believe in Allah.
"Doesn't believe in Allah..."
You know how many people I know
who say they believe in Allah?
But they still drink, steal or vandalize?
What's more important?
Saying that you believe in Allah?
Or living as if you believe in Allah?
The most important thing for me at
least, is that my sister...
is doing well,
with a good guy.
Not with one who just
goes to the mosque.
I don't think that mom agrees with you.
Do you know that mom only
wants the best for us?
It's just she was born in a totally different
country in a totally different time.
She doesn't know what
is to be like us.
Now you have to stop
showing such a sad face.
Because when you are sad, I am sad too.
I am not sad.
That's good.
There is a party in Løkka tomorrow.
If you want to come.
With your friends?
Those who were in the
apartment the other day?
Fun! Fun!
Yeah, yeah! Of course! We'll come!
- Bring Yousef!
- Yeah! I'll do that.
FRIDAY
20:39
- "So then, you are Elias, right?"
- Elias? Your brother?
Then I go up to him and I stroke
him, just a little bit on his side.
And then I feel a shiver
going through him, like...
He left pretty early but he...
He seemed open for...
- For more fun!
- Are you crazy?
I can send you the money with Vipps.
- Vipps me?
- Yeah.
- How much?
- How much does it cost?
Hello?
- 112.
- It's not!
- 112 Kronen for a beer.
- I can give you...
It's 112,40 or 112,50.
To Elias Bakkoush:
ARE YOU COMING?
Imagine there's no heaven.
It's easy if you try.
No hell below us,
above us is only sky.
Imagine all the people
living for today.
Imagine there's no countries...
... nothing to kill or die for.
And no religion too.
Imagine all the people
living life in peace.
You may say I'm a dreamer,
but I'm not the only one.
I hope someday you'll join us,
and the world will be as one.
Imagine no possessions,
I wonder if you can.
No need for greed or hunger.
A brotherhood of man.
Imagine all the people
sharing all the world.
You may say I'm a dreamer,
but I'm not the only one.
I hope someday you'll join us.
And the world will live as one.
Thank you!
- Super!
- My God.
- Oh, I love you so much.
- I love you too.
Do you remember the first time
I introduced you to the girls?
Yeah!
It's so weird thinking about it!
It was so long time ago!
And you were standing there like:
"We met at Ramadan in the mosque".
- I remember.
- You were so...
Okay, we'll talk later. I'm going to meet
Eskild, I want to tell him something.
(Mama) SORRY FOR LOOKING
THROUGH YOUR STUFF.
YOU ARE SMART AND STRONG. YOU CAN
MANAGE WITHOUT MY DUMB ADVICE.
William has a new girlfriend.
Did you know it?!
You knew it?!
- I was going to tell you, but...
- Did you know it last week?!
I sat there and I told you lots of
things about William and you knew it?
I am sorry, I should have told you.
Sana, Elias is in trouble.
(Yelling obscenities to each other)
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Elias! Elias stop!
Leave!
Elias, leave!
Elias stop!
Elias! What are you doing?!
Fucking kids!
Elias!
Are you all right?
We have to go to the emergency room.
Let's go then!
- Are you coming?
- Yes, of course.
- What has just happened? Really scary.
- Why did they do that? I don't get it.
- It is probably because they are gay.
- No! Do you think so?
Yes, they are Muslims and
the other guys are gay.
That's a reason to fight.
It's insane if it's the case. I think
her brother is a little crazy.
Do you remember that bus
meeting at Sana's place?
Her brother totally snapped!
He screamed and...
- Do you know what Vilde said?
- No.
That he called Sana "slave".
Seriously? That's sick. No
wonder why she is psycho.
No, I don't want to be there when...
Could you just check that
there's nobody in those stalls?
Nobody. What were you saying?
I don't want to be there when Sana finds
out she is not going to be on the bus.
- Did they sign the contract?
- Yes, earlier today.
Sara was really paranoid because Sana was
starting to suspect anything, right?
But fortunately she managed
to get away with it.
I feel sorry for her.
But, hello? She is really stupid
if she doesn't get we own the bus
cause we are paying for it and
she doesn't have any rights.
Do you know she wasn't the real bus boss?
It was Vilde!
I don't get why she bothered joining
the bus in the first place.
Isn't that really disrespectful
to her religion?
Specially if she wears a hijab.
She is supposed to be a good
representation for Islam.
- The other girls seems cool though!
- I agree.
Specially Noora!
Oh my God! She is so pretty.
@Ledgerina