- Maybe I can get a friend of yours?
- Maybe Chris?
I got Chris for you.
- This is Chris.
- I am Chris.
You have to get new friends.
- Hi! Thanks for last time.
- Hi.
We were wondering
if you're already on a russ bus.
Say hi to Sana,
she wants to join the bus meeting.
We have a really big advantage
over the other bus groups.
I already bought a lot of toilet paper.
- We're wasting time on toilet paper.
- But what do you want us to do?
Do we know any '97 guys?
You guys have to hook up with them.
SHAME
SUNDAY, 10:11 A.M.
What are you doing?
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
No.
I had a nightmare.
About what?
I dreamed that you wore red clothes.
You were completely drunk and singing:
"Tonight it's allowed to be a whore."
Ha-ha. Really funny.
You're the one who said I should get friends.
- Yeah.
So what's the problem?
The problem is that you don't understand
that russ time is just a capitalistic event--
Bla, bla, bla...
You know Sana said I should dump you.
- Did she?
- Yes.
You couldn't manage without me
for a single minute.
You couldn't, could you?
You couldn't...
Eva?
- Hi!
- So good to see you!
- It's good to see you, too.
- Did you just get here now?
- Yes. I got an earlier flight.
- Were you sleeping?
- No, no!
Should we make breakfast?
- Yes, let's. Are you hungry?
- Yes, I'm really hungry.
MONDAY, 2:47 P.M.
Hi, dear. I saw a history test
lying on the table here
where you got a 3-. Is it recent?
Mom:
- Eva! I have to talk to you.
- Yes?
I was wondering,
and I don't know what you think,
but do you think Sana is a good fit
for our bus group?
Maybe she's a bit harsh?
Hey, she asked you to
break up with your boyfriend!
But you do agree that she can't join our bus?
Because I talked to Chris--
Hey! Sana was wondering something.
How much toilet paper do you have?
- Why?
- Do you want to get rid of them or not?
- Eight pallets.
- Hello!
- You said you didn't know any '97 guys?
- I don't.
- He's on a bus with William.
- Is he?!
- Who's William?
- You don't know who William is?
No.
He's the hottest, coolest guy
in all of third-year.
That is William.
Are you following that guy Chris
on Instagram?
No.
- Do it.
- Why should I?
So you can get to know him.
I don't want to get to know him,
I have a boyfriend.
I told you, this is becoming a problem.
You don't have to hook up with him,
just get to know him,
so we can go to
a bus pre-party with William.
You can tell your boyfriend that
that's your reason.
Yeah, because he'll surely
respect and accept that?
Yes! Just follow him.
Give me your phone.
Do you know what he's called on Insta?
Hey, that's enough!
When he sends you a message,
reply, and flirt.
Why would he message me?
Just flirt with him, okay?
- I have to go. Tschüss!
- Tschüss!
She's just like the lady
from Åndenes makt.
I know. She's completely raw.
TUESDAY, 3:41 P.M.
- Who is this Julian Dahl on Insta?
- No idea.
He's stalking me.
- Want to go to your place?
- No, let's go to yours.
Eva doesn't want to tell her mom
we're together.
Why not?
- Because she's embarrassed of me.
- That's not it.
I don't want her to meet you
when you're lying in my bed.
Okay...
Then invite me to dinner with your mom.
Thanks for the likes.
Never had a stalker before.
- Huh?
- Invite me to dinner with your mom.
- Yeah, I'll invite you to dinner.
Okay, when?
Hehe! Yes, a real stalker,
be careful, I'm standing
outside your house.
When?
Yeah... today, tomorrow, on Friday,
or next month?
Haha! Freaky. I'm actually
a bit scared now.
Christmas? May 17th?
Haha! Freaky. I'm actually
a bit scared now.
And horny.
Hello?
- Friday.
- Yeah, Friday.
- Who are you texting with?
- Vilde.
The russ bus boss.
Russ bus boss? You're not on a bus.
- She is, and it's really messed up.
- Stop saying I'm messed up.
You were saying it yourself
two weeks ago.
Yeah, maybe I changed my mind?
- Yeah, maybe you did.
- Okay.
THURSDAY, 12:10 P.M
Guess who's invited to a pre-party
with the Penetrator guys?
- Are you kidding?
- Really, Eva?
- Check it out.
- William will be...
That's great, Eva!
Oh, my god, you did this for us!
"Penetrator pre-party at Borkis' on Friday."
- "Cool. Can you bring some friends?"
- "Are they hot?"
Yes!
Shh! Relax. Try to be cool.
- We have to get alcohol!
- Yeah, I'll call the beer man.
- Does anyone have a fake ID?
- What's wrong with the beer man?
Are you looking at me? Do I look like I drink?
- I don't drink, either.
- What an awesome gang...
- I can probably take some wine from my mom.
- Could you?
How much? Can we share?
I can pay if you want.
I could take from my mom, but her wine
is so expensive, so if I took some,
- she would notice--
- Stop talking.
You talk too much.
- Excuse me?
- Shh!
Seriously?
She can't be on our bus,
she's completely psycho!
It's the beer man.
Yes, please.
We'd like some beers for...
four girls.
And a hundred boys!
Do we have to pay? If we have a friend here
who's called Vilde, if she maybe can flash?
So we don't need to pay in cash.
Maybe we can...
Or maybe we can get...
get... Noora to do it.
No, we don't do that. Hello?
Hello? Are you in prison?
FRIDAY, 6:41 P.M.
Fuck.
What are they doing here?
Hi!
Wasn't it them who threw her off their bus?
Wasn't it her who called you a slut
at that revue-party?
Don't leave me. Either Christoffer will rape me,
or those girls will kill me.
Okay. I won't leave you.
...he had one goal — to get this girl pregnant,
but he couldn't find her, so he had to...
You're kidding!
Is that why you're called the Penetrators?
That's why we're the Penetrators, because...
William asked me
if I wanted to go outside with him.
- I think he wants to hook up.
- Fucking hell! Go for it, you little slut!
- "Little slut"?
- Yeah, she's really slutty!
No, no! I'm also slutty.
Hola!
Well, just talk politics with him or something!
He's going to lose his boner right away.
3 missed calls from Jonas
Jonas (27 min ago):
What about that dinner?
Hey.
Hi.
- Are those like your crew, or what?
- My crew?
- Yeah, I mean, are you on a russ bus with them?
- No, I'm not on a russ bus.
- I'm not going to be a russ.
- Okay?
I just think russ time is pretty lame.
Okay, why?
Because russ time is just
a capitalistic event governed by market forces.
Okay... okay.
You're a bit brainy.
I mean, I like it!
I think it's kinda hot.
You think it's hot?
Damn rude! What the fuck!
Drama!
Yeah, I have to go.
- What's up?
- It's an emergency!