IT’S TIME FOR DUHR
(PRAYER)
JOIN THE THEMED-EVENING AT
THE MOSQUE THIS FRIDAY
IT’S ABOUT WOMEN’S ROLE IN ISLAM
IS JAMILLA COMING?
COME ON, SANA
I DON’T THINK SO
I’LL BE THERE
- We have to celebrate.
- I've bought sparkling wine.
Sparkling wine?
Don't people
celebrate with that?
I want beer.
So you are here now.
Am I late?
Yeah, we are done.
Oh, no! I am sorry. I took
the streetcar the wrong way.
Yeah! I have heard that one before.
- What?
- Taking the streetcar the wrong direction.
You?
Isn’t that what you usually do?
Yeah. I do that when I don’t
want to attend things.
Listen, then you can join Even and
me helping with the wrapping up?
That sounds like so much fun, but I am
super busy. Are the girls upstairs?
Sure.
Sana, can you tell Vilde that I miss her?
What?
You say that to a girl and
they go like “awwww”.
No, they don’t do that.
Awwww!
Does it work that way with girls?
You are cute together.
Yeah. We are cuter tan you two.
Ooh! You wish!
No, it’s just something about
the colour “ocean blue”.
Ocean blue?
Ocean.
Is it like royal blue?
No, royal blue is like your jacket.
It’s blue like a beach on Marbella.
A beach on Marbella?
Have you been there lately?
Hello.
Hi!
How are you?
Noora’s got her room back!
But what I was going to say was that...
Want some pizza?
Yesterday we tried a new position
we found online.
We also have cow meat.
I was over him, sitting.
Like a cowgirl but reversed.
So it was reversed cowgirl.
So he was sitting.
It’s a bit uncomfortable
in the beginning.
I felt like he was watching straight
up, because his head was like... on...
If we did it the right way. It was so, so
good. It hit something, it hit the G-spot.
No. Isn’t G-spot on the upper side?
No, I have heard that the G-spot is anal.
Isn’t that only for boys?
It’s really common to have several G-spots.
Anyways, the thing is that I have never
had such a good time with anyone before.
I have never came as much as
I do when I am with Magnus.
It’s amazing!
I just come, and come, and come, and come.
Don’t you have any limits?
About what it’s okay to share?
Like what?
Do you have to share every detail
about you and Magnus’ sex life?
I get that it’s difficult for you
to listen since you can’t have sex...
I can have sex, Vilde.
I just choose not to.
Yeah, I am just saying that it is totally
fine if you are sexually frustrated.
I am not sexually frustrated.
I don’t go around thinking about boys and
sex feeling like I am missing something.
I am just saying that...
sex should be something nice
between you and Magnus.
And not everybody else.
Anyone want some tea?
Yeah! That would be great...
Okay. I have to say something,
but I don’t know if it’s true.
I have heard that William has
a new girlfriend in London.
What?! Are you kidding?
Chris told me that.
Should I tell her?
Of course you have to tell her!
But, shouldn’t William
be the one to tell her?
Yeah, but obviously he hasn’t told her.
But I don’t know for sure if it’s true.
Also, I don’t understand the thing between
William and Noora. Are they together?
What’s up? What are you talking about?
Anal sex.
Magnus and I were thinking about trying.
Have you tried it?
No.
You and William, no...
Vilde. No.
At the subject of William. How is he?
Fine...
Yeah. We don't understand what’s the thing
between you two. Are you together or not?
It’s always going to be William and me.
TUESDAY
17:50
Hello?
- Try again! Throw it!
- Wrong! You are so bad!
Tell me when. Do it again!
Let Yousef try. Yousef will do it!
He is going to miss again. He's tried ten
times and he is still not able to do it.
When does it come?
Let me hear!
Throw it then!
Bad! I knew it!
I couldn’t hear, calm down.
What’s going on here?
Hey, let Sana try.
She will make it, bro!
She is good at basket, she can actually
throw, unlike some other people here.
She learned from me.
What do you mean “learned from me”? Even
mom is better than you at basketball.
Ohh!
That hurts.
Listen. If you make it, I’ll be your slave
for a whole week.
Man, don’t do that.
Chill. I am confident, man.
Drive me around? Clean my room?
Whatever you want, the whole package.
Swear on it.
Wallah! And these guys are my witnesses.
No, no. You won’t make it.
It will be fine. Chill. I’ll fix it.
What do I have to do?
Explain it to her.
You take this, throw it and
make it go into the lamp
exactly as Snoop Dog sings:
“Smoke weed every day!”
Just that?
Just that.
She is going to make it.
But if you miss, you will
be my slave for a week.
That wasn’t part of the deal.
Well, you said “just that”?
Are you scared or something?
She is going to make it!
You were so confident, come on!
Give me the ball.
You are going to regret this, Elias!
I am going to win this, relax.
I’ll be fine. Play the music.
Looking forward to see Elias crying.
She missed.
Aahhh! Nooo!
It’s just what I thought.
Way too early.
Now, can you please make some tea for us?
I am not your friends’ slave.
I know, but they are my guests.
Thank you, slave woman!
That came out wrong. I’m sorry. Calm down.
It was wrong of me to say that.
- Don’t talk to your sister like that!
- That’s your sister!
Everything is fine. Relax guys!
Stop it!
WEDNESDAY
14:06
Yours looks like shit.
But it's the truth!
Eva, how old are you?
- It looks like poop emoji.
- Can I try yours?
- Can’t you feed me?
- Oh my God! You want me to feed you?
Okay, all right.
Yours is good! What is it? Banana?
I don’t know. I think it’s mango.
No, it’s not!
Isn’t it lemon?
No, I would have known if it was lemon.
But that tasted like...
Does nobody want to taste mine?
Yeah, it really tasted...
Isn’t that vanilla?
You know what? I think Easter
holidays are boring as shit.
We should have gone to your cabin.
No. I am not going there, it
just makes me think of Kasper.
ARE YOU HOME? I HAVE FORGOTTEN MY KEY
It was amazing when
Kasper was in the window.
- You both got so scared!
- I thought somebody died!
CALL MOM
- You were the most scared.
- It was because of the mask!
- I’m crying!
- No, I didn’t do that.
Listen, girls. I’ve been
looking at travelling websites
and it’s not that expensive to rent
an apartment in a foreign country.
We should go to France, that would be cool.
Just us lying on the beach.
THEY ARE COMING LATE. I
NEED TO GET HOME NOW.
MEET ME. YOU ARE A SLAVE,
SO YOU HAVE TO DO IT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
You want to go to my place
and watch Paradise Hotel?
Yeah!
- Can I invite Magnus?
- Sure!
I think I’ll just go home then.
Why?
It’s nothing important, Eskild...
Linn sent me a message and told
me that he is furnishing my room.
Which I haven’t give him permission to do.
- I’ll text you later.
- All right.
Bye.
AT THE GYM. COME HERE.
Have you told her about
William’s new girlfriend?
No, I thought we agreed not to tell her.
Maybe he told her himself already,
she seemed a liittle down.
I have to give a key to my brother.
Where?
Not far away.
Should we go there before
we head to my place?
Yes.
I think the best solution
is to find Noora a new boy.
So that she falls in love and
can forget about William.
Well, she likes bad boys. Do we know any?
We should look for a bad boy.
Jonas and Mahdi! It would be so fun if any
of you got together with any of them.
Really? No, Vilde.
I just think it’s so boring that I
am the only one with a boyfriend,
because I have to be with Magnus
when you hang out together.
Can you wait here?
Why?
I don’t think Noora will fall in love with
any boys we already know.
We need someone new.
And where would we find
new, cool and hot boys?
¡Elias!
Hello, slave.
Here.
Who are your friends?
Vilde.
Elias.
Yeah, I think we have found them...
No, no, no.
FRIDAY
20:17
I need to pee.
Go pee then.
No, you can get fined for that.
What’s the sense of hanging
out with your brother now?
I don’t know. Ask Vilde.
No. I just think it would be nice
to meet some new cool and hot boys.
Have you meet Sana’s brother? He is so hot!
Don’t you have a boyfriend?
Fuck! It’s really cold.
They are on their way.
They know about a party.
They are not coming. They
are childish assholes.
No, they are not assholes.
They are 97 guys.
Just like William...
for example.
Hello, boys.
You hate hanging out with us, don’t you?
We are going to a party!
Where is the party we’re going to?
Hello?
Hello, where are you?
Shit! I forgot.
I had to help Noora.
Well, where are you right now?
On a streetcar.
We are on our way to a party.
I can hear what you are thinking.
I’m thinking it would be easier if you
had friends more similar to you...
I am able to have Norwegian friends
and still be myself.
Okay.
I trust you. See you later at home.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
TIME FOR PRAYER