How does it actually happen to you this
Party stuff has become so important?
Are you joining SING on Friday?
-That's going to be real.
-Sing?
Take a look at the event, Sara
On our bus page.
-What is with the contract for the bus?
-I really do not want to leave you.
All right.
I do not know anybody,
Who is as muslim as Yousef.
8th
-Yes, but he does not believe in Allah.
-What is the most important thing?
To say that one believes in Allah
Or to live like you would?
-Elias! Stop!
-Disappears!
Sara had really panicked,
Because Sana probably had noticed.
I do not understand why she is at all
Where the bus took part.
Is not that quite disrespectful
Against religion?
(Sana praises in a whisper)
If you pour acid into your face,
If you do not wear a headscarf?
Sana you are circumcised
Hope you will be forced to marry after
Africa, then I am rid of you
... I'll tear you down!
... this shit
... forced to marry ...
...Africa...
... pull it down ...
...Headscarf...
Monday
Hello Jamilla
(Jamilla :) -Whats the hell do you drive?
(Sana :) - SORRY !!
That was a misunderstanding! I thought,
You would have shit about me posted !!
I can explain it!
Call at once!
(Jamilla :) I'm just trying,
Protect you.
(Sana :) Thank you, that is not necessary.
Do not talk to me,
Do not talk to me, no.
No no.
Do not talk to me,
Set my phone on silently.
Do not talk to me, no. I am
Timeless, about me like night and day.
I know they know this bitch guy
Is crazy (crazy, crazy ...).
This bitch type is crazy.
Do not talk to me, no.
You know me, no. Do not speak
With me, no. I do not want to know you.
I know you like it,
If I retain everything.
Always call me at night,
I do not want to talk.
What's this?
-I've logged off from the bus.
-What ?!
-I'm not there.
- Now, where we got a bus-
-and people and everything runs,
Do you report?
What's happening?
It just does not matter to me,
To be part of the Abi move.
It was you
But still quite important?
Maybe I noticed that it was all
Contrary to my values,
-like girls their entire self-respect
For a fuck in the forest sacrifice?
- How's yours?
-Good. Everything OK.
-Sorry again, that my brother ...
-No, that ... Do not think about it anymore.
Okay, folks, we've got a lot going on.
Next week we will write the exam.
With some of you it does not look
Well, so watch out now.
-That is true for me.
-We are now going to the chapter ..
Can you help me, Sana?
I'm full of ass.
I totally depend on it.
Sorry. You must be the hard one
To look truth in the face.
That I only get a 3?
That you are alone.
Please hit page ...
Tuesday
I do not want to drive it anymore.
Today he has stopped again.
-Hello.
-Hi!
-Is the food ready soon?
-Not quite yet.
But you can have a carrot
If you like.
No thanks.
-What the guys are always here?
-We are now hospitable.
They are always here.
All are welcome.
-Your girlfriends. The guys are okay.
(Noora :) -Welcome to meet?
Why are you interested in this?
Sana? Do you have today
A bad day
I'll write next week
An organic exam.
But you're good at it.
Where is the problem?
Well, if I do one day
As you want to be a surgeon,
I use good grades.
You can do it.
You can do it, I promise you.
You have better notes
Than I had. It will.
-This car really annoys me.
-I can understand that.
How is Jamilla?
She's fine.
Nice to ask you. She is doing now
An education to the nurse.
I think she likes it very well.
(Notification)
(Noora :) Something wrong?
Are you so quiet
(They talk about each other)
- That's the guys!
-I'm fine?
Yes. And even?
-Now everything is good; You are together
-As always.
-And what's up"?
-We want to go to the football field.
Soccer? Do not forget the bottle.
The water bottle, I mean.
The bottle! Yes / Yes!
-Behave!
-Yes, of course.
- Are not you with us?
- I'm not so hungry.
- Do you have carrots?
-Yes. We'll take it.
Serve you.
-Good, we have to go.
-Take care. Have fun!
-Likewise!
-Tschüs.
Thanks for the carrot.
Thank you for being here.
Bye.
Then we agree,
That we buy a new one?
-Yes, but we have to plan that.
-We need a new one. Very easily.
I am only stressed because of the exam
(Noora :) I'm also on the bus
deregistered. Do not carry it without you
Wednesday
I wanted to write a gloss,
But I'm not at all funny.
- I do not even know what a gloss is.
- That was really bad.
How should I be in a good mood,
When we write an exam?
(Loud noises from carrot chewing)
Are you coming with me?
Sana!
-Hä?
- Are you coming to Mäckes?
-No, I'm learning for the exam.
-OK.
Shall we bring you something?
No thanks.
-See you!
-Tschüs.
- Did Sara pimp your girlfriends?
-Hä? No!
OK. It was just a joke.
Fake, fake, fake, fake ...
Girls ...!
Sara does not like Vilde!
-How do you know?
-Because she talks badly about her.
-Towards you?
-mm.
-Are you friends with Sara?
-We were once a couple.
That's right.
How can you be with
You be together?
What you do not say...
That was certain
No sexual relationship.
We were mainly chatting.
I was more of a network psychologist
As a lover.
I should have paid the time
Which I have spent with it,
- assassinations about her
Abi bus friends and so on.
It was shitty to me!
Hey! Sister types are species,
Which are determined only morphologically?
No. Sister types are species,
Which are similar in appearance,
-aber genetically complete
Can be different.
I'm going to hang out.
Thursday
(Jamilla) A good advice:Take it
William and Co from my class in eight!
(Sana :) Thank you. You were
My angel in the eighth.
Hopefully I will not land
Again in a racist class.
(Jamilla):-You are going to the nits now?
(Sana :) -Ja! Will be great but exhausting.
(Sana :) Do not know anyone but you.
Nice to have someone there.
(Jamilla :) I'll be around you
To take care of. Just like on the Urra school.
SARA - the perfect bus boss
(Sara :) Hahaha facerape,
I have not posted
(Vilde :) Hihhihi that I was sorrii
(Cathrine :) Still have not got it,
Why Sana does not want to join?
(Vilde :) She told us that it was
Because of the values ​​of the Abi time is ...
... but is strange because they used to be
Never had anything against these values ​​...
(Sara :) Determines her parents. she had
Full of panic that they come-
As we celebrated with her. Definitely not
Simply as Muslima in the Abi-moving
However,
That she is not there.
(Kjersti) She is
Still on this site?
It's not that I'm Muslima,
But because you're a damn wrong
Should I teach you for
The final exam?
(Isak :) Your serious? What's happening?
Because my brother and his duff-
Pals have beaten you,
- I believe that I am
I owe you this.
(Isak :) They did not hit me.
Should I help you or not?
(Isak :) Yes, of course!
Tomorrow after school?
Or do you want to drink?
(Isak :) Morning after school is fat.
I am finished at 14.30. You?
16.00, wait for me in the canteen
(Isak :) Can not you be easy
Come to my house?
Yes.
Friday
-Hello.
-Hi.
Hello, Sana.
-Where did you last see him?
- In bed, but I can not find him.
Sorry for the stress. I wanted
Exceptionally times on time to work.
- Nice here.
-Thank you.
I'm rumbling on flea markets
And only took the cheapest.
-You call the "rumbrödeln"?
-Yes, it was so.
We have quite there
Beautiful much taken.
Yes.
You should have seen,
As it was before.
Did you find anything?
- Do you remember the crispbread?
-I will.
Look on the way outside
Wash basin and take the laundry ...
-Now? I have to be there in five minutes.
-Yes. From the washer into the dryer.
- It takes ten minutes.
-This does not take ten minutes!
When you had forgotten this,
Smelled of mold. For real!
You're just sensitive.
That was two hours.
If it is so important to you,
I do it. OK?
See you later. It was nice to see you,
Sana. Good luck studying!
I always confuse
Protists with prokaryotes.
They are ...
That is ... Yes ...
OK. "Back to basic", in principle.
-Yes.
-Prokaryotes are the first living organisms,
- which was 3.5 billion years ago
In the sea.
According to the prokaryote organisms
Emerged the protists.
And protists are unicellular beings.
From these monoclinic creatures have
Developed multicellular organisms,
-the colonies have formed,
From which larger animals emerged.
With "larger animals" I mean, for example,
-Fishing jellyfish and mussels,
Which you see on the model.
Do you know the model?
-No, not memorized.
-Then learn the model by heart.
You must be able to do this in the exam,
Because this is guaranteed.
Just write the explanation,
Which I have just given you.
Yes.
232 ...
If you ever open Facebook ...
I have a link for you
To "I love science", -
- which is exactly relevant.
Did you find him?
Yes...
Yes, okay ... In English ...
I can certainly translate.
Were not you offering me anything?
Uh ...
Yes, would you like something to drink?
-Tea.
-You want a tea? Gladly.
I'll make you a tea.
Search for "sara" in messages
-What are you doing there?
-Nothing.
I just have to
The WiFi name.
You could have asked me.
He is "Yellow Curtains".
- Yarn Curtains?
- Yellow curtains.
What tea do you want?
"Green tea and lemon"
-or "apple and cinamon"
- "pomme et canelle"?
Green tea.
(Notification)
(Noora :) Hey girl.
Shall we meet?
I know you're stressed because of the exam
But it has been so long ago.
And something great happened, of which
I have to tell you. Do you have time?
So...
You just have hot water
Taken out of the tap?
Yes.
We do not have a water cooker, so ...
I do not know how Even it creates,
Without boiling water to cook tea.
I know he's at it
Not in this way.
You, Sana ...
I have to ask you something
Why do you really have me?
Not said you know Even?
Because I knew you were me
Would ask for him.
And what is so bad about it?
I think Even should be self
May decide,
-how much of his past
Price.
You do not want it all
Share your own past.
You are a good person.
(A phone rings)
Hello?
Shit, Even!
You have done it? Surprise...!
So, I can do that then
Also make it yourself.
Have fun.
You also. Yes. Bye.
Take care.
I have to go now
Down into the wash basement.
I will be back soon.
... You will always have a place in my
Hearts. You were my first love ...
You also
Have you heard what Vilde about the
Solarium chain has said? Totally dumb
She says:"The solarium chain stands for
The values ​​of women. "Your seriousness?
(A door is opened
And again closed)
OK.
- Now we must get a tooth.
- "Let's go, bitches."