- Ingrid... I miss you.
- You look like a slut.
- How are Ingrid and Sara doing?
- Why do you have to interrogate me all the time?
Stop walking around like a fucking cliché.
I trust you 100%.
Chris hooked up with someone at the Halloween
party, his girlfriend found out and went psycho!
SHAME
SATURDAY, 11:32 A.M.
To Jonas:
ANSWER!
Have you talked to him?
Yes.
What did he say?
Isak!
Let's sit down.
He's...
He's not very happy.
But... he has to talk to me.
He has to let me explain.
Maybe he just needs some space,
or something.
How did he find out about it?
The entire school is talking about it.
Yeah, but how did he find out?
Elias...
- And then he just believed it?
- But it's true.
But...
I don't understand how he can believe a rumor
without talking to me first?
He said he should've figured it out earlier.
You...
You've been acting a little random lately.
Maybe it just made sense.
From Jonas:
Don't think we should talk now
Is it Jonas?
To Jonas:
You have to let me explain!!!
From Jonas:
If I see you now, I'm going to say things
I'll regret so I suggest that I'll call you
when I'm ready to hear your explanation
for why you chose to fuck up
everything that's good between us
It'll be okay.
MONDAY, 11:58 A.M.
- How are you doing?
- I'm fine.
I thought about you all weekend, and if I were in
your situation, I would have been really upset.
I've been asking around, and Ulla in 2STE says
that it was the boyfriend who told her.
Chris told her himself?
One more thing. Quite a lot of people are saying
you're slutty now.
Vilde!
I'm just telling the truth.
Rumor has it the Rad girls
have blacklisted you.
- What does that mean?
- I'm not really sure, but
Tiril from 2STE was blacklisted last year.
- They cut off her hair.
- Hello?!
I'm just telling you what I've heard!
Good job, Eva!
Excuse me?!
Excuse you for what?
You seem like really charming girls.
Oh, how sweet!
Defending your friend like that.
It seems like you have a very close relationship.
I'm sure you'll keep having that.
Until she pisses on your entire life.
Then I don't think you'll be
so damn charming anymore.
What did she mean by that?
Did you and Ingrid used to be friends?
It was a long time ago.
What did she mean by
- "pissing on your entire life"?
- I don't know!
- There must have been something?
- I'm sure she said it to create drama, okay?
Okay.
TUESDAY, 4:29 P.M.
But how long do you
think it will be
until he wants to talk to me?
From Isak:
I don't know, Eva
But is he still mad at me,
what's he saying?
From Isak:
He hasn't talked about you
- What are you doing here?
- What do you think?
I came home because I got a call from school
that you had been in a fight!
- That's why I came home.
- You could've spared yourself.
No, I couldn't. I found a letter saying you won't
receive a passing grade in math for Christmas.
Christmas grades don't count.
- What's going on?
- Nothing's going on. Some girls who attacked me.
- Just like that? Unprovoked?
- Yes.
- What kind of girls were they?
- Some cunts from the second year, okay?
- Eva!
- Mom!
- I can't deal with this conversation.
- You have to! We have to talk about--
No! We actually don't have to.
You can't be gone all year,
and then suddenly start meddling in my life.
- Eva!
- It doesn't work like that.
I just want to help!
If you want to help me...
then stop yelling at me!
The entire school hates me,
and Jonas wants to break up,
so the last thing I need now
is for you to come home and bitch at me!
Jonas?
Are you dating Jonas? I mean Jonas Jonas?
- But Jonas is--
- Mom! I know who Jonas is.
You don't need to tell me.
WEDNESDAY, 2:28 P.M.
Don't you think Vilde is really...
like far out? She's just floating on a pink cloud
with all this russ stuff.
Russ time is her life.
But it's like three years left,
and I just don't get what the big deal is.
But...
it's kind of nice though. It's...
He still hasn't called?
But... you know you don't have to wait
until he is ready to talk, right?
You have the right to explain yourself.
You know what always gets me in a better mood?
Okay, promise you won't hold it against me?
- Yes.
- Seriously, you can't tell anyone.
This is between us.
If this song doesn't put you
in a better mood, then...
♪ Oh, whoa... ♪
♪ Oh, whoa-haa... ♪
♪ You know you love me, ♪
♪ I know you care ♪
♪ Just shout whenever, a-ha, ♪
♪ and I'll be there, a-ha ♪
♪ You are my love, you are my heart ♪
♪ And we will never, ever, ever be apart ♪
♪ Are we an item? Girl, quit playing ♪
Justin Bieber?
Cool...
It's not something I usually listen to, but...
yeah, it was because... or, yeah... whatever.
I don't need to explain myself to you, anyway.
What is it? Did you want something?
Want to go to my place to do homework?
- Excuse me, Willhelm.
- William.
Well...
That pretty much answers your question,
don't you think?
- What?
- I don't even know your name.
Doesn't matter to me, call me what you want.
Yeah, but then...
then I choose to call you "asshole".
- You think that was funny?
- Are you coming?
I thought my answer was pretty clear, but...
No.
Let me know when you change your mind.
Yeah, you just go home and wait for that.
Who does he think he is?!
- Why did you call him Willhelm?
- Huh?
You called him Willhelm,
but you know it's "William".
Oh, yeah,
that was a suppression technique.
Okay?
I saw it on Suits once.
- I've always wanted to use it.
- Wow.
- Impressed?
- Mostly surprised.
Both that you watch Suits,
and listen to Justin Bieber.
Was that a little joke?
You made a joke, Eva!
That's a good sign! That's good.
We like that.
From Vilde:
I'm calling an extraordinary
russ bus meeting tomorrow
at 3 p.m. Important that
everyone shows up.
Extraordinary bus meeting?
It's funny she's calling it "extraordinary",
since we have so many ordinary bus meetings.
THURSDAY, 3:01 P.M.
- The toilet paper, Sana, is that taken care of?
- Mmm.
- And the money? Has Vilde received the money?
- She got the money--
Will this extraordinary meeting take a long time?
Because I have other things to do.
I'll go straight to the point.
As everyone knows, Eva had an
unlucky incident at the Halloween party.
Quite a lot of people are upset with her.
The Rad bus group has blacklisted her.
Vilde...
I got a pretty unpleasant phone call
from the Rad girls yesterday.
They're saying that as long as Eva is on our bus,
we are all blacklisted.
- Huh?!
- Don't laugh, it's actually pretty serious!
Last year a bus was blacklisted,
and someone destroyed their brakes.
All of them could have died.
We don't even have a bus.
No, but they can do other things.
Cutting our hair, or... throw us in the water.
- I know of several girls that went too far.
- Yeah, they can just try.
We have to talk about this.
It's unfair that all of us will become unpopular
because of Eva being slutty.
It's interesting that you
who describe yourself as a feminist...
are calling other girls slutty.
I think Penetrator Chris
is slutty as well.
It's unfair that he doesn't get
the same reputation.
But it's not my fault that's the way things are.
Chris doesn't get that reputation, because
guys don't go around calling other guys sluts.
So if you think it's unfair, then you have to
stop calling girls sluts. It's not hard--
Don't yell at me! I'm not even done talking.
It's not just the thing with Chris
that makes Eva slutty. There's more to it.
This isn't the first time
Eva has ruined a relationship.
Vilde...
That's between me and Ingrid.
It's actually not that simple, Eva.
Because Ingrid told
Iben and the Rad girls.
And what you did
affects all of us girls.
What are we talking about?
Eva used to be best friends with Ingrid
from the Pepsi Max girls.
In the 9th grade, Ingrid got a boyfriend.
She was really in love with him, and they were
the cutest couple in the entire school.
Everyone thought they
were perfect for each other.
Even their parents thought
they would get married.
But just before summer, in the 10th grade...
he started to behave strangely. He became
dismissive and stopped replying to her texts.
Ingrid, of course, got really sad.
Eva was there for her, comforted her,
and pretended like she had no idea.
Even though she knew
why he was acting so strange.
Because Eva was seeing him behind Ingrid's back.
Jonas, was his name.
Jonas and Ingrid used to be a couple.
So I think Eva only has herself to blame
for being in this situation.
Because it's pretty messed up
to steal your best friend's boyfriend.
You can't steal anyone.
Do you want a friend who
hits on your boyfriend?
Rather that, than a friend who calls
girls sluts and judges them based on rumors.
It's not a rumor, it's true.
Just ask Eva.
I don't understand why you're attacking Eva,
when the Rad girls are the enemy.
They can try. We'll just get back at them.
That might be the way it works
in your Muslim gangster world,
but for us, it doesn't work like that.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- I can't be bothered to listen to this.
You're completely psycho.
You threw water in Ingrid's face.
You're crazy!
I threw water in Ingrid's face,
because she and her friends called you a slut
for hooking up with William.
Because for me, in my "Muslim gangster world",
that's how it works.
You don't judge your friends...
and you stand up for them, no matter what.
For once it would have been really nice
if you could have defended me, Chris!
FRIDAY, 2:33 P.M.
Okay, Eva. Let's hear it.
I just want you to know,
I didn't hook up with Chris
because I liked him.
I have never liked him.
I just did it because I thought
you and Ingrid had been hooking up.
That's your explanation?
Ironic.
I've taken so much crap from you
because you thought I was messing with Ingrid.
But... then it was actually you who cheated.
And lied about it.
- And I had to find out through Elias?!
- But...
It was you who lied to me first.
You said you hadn't been with Ingrid,
but you had.
And... I only hooked up with Chris
because I was hurt.
It never would've happened
if you hadn't lied to me first.
- Okay... so it's my fault?
- No!
That's not what I meant.
I'm just trying to explain
why I did what I did.
I fucked up, okay?
I'm sorry.
I wish I'd never done it. Really.
Jonas...
I love you.
You're saying you hooked up
with Christoffer,
just because you thought
I was with Ingrid.
Why did you have to cheat
just because you thought I was?
I'm sorry.
Eva, it's actually not about
you cheating or lying.
It's about me not understanding who you are.
When we were in middle school,
and you, Sara, and Ingrid were best friends...
and I was with Ingrid...
you suddenly found that exciting,
and wanted to be with me.
But now that you've got new friends...
and they are into third-year guys,
then you suddenly
want to be with them all the time.
That's what I don't understand.
You just follow
what everyone else finds exciting.
You don't have your own opinions.
Because...
what do you like, really?
Who are you?
Call me when you've figured that out.