Hi. I have bought tickets for a Christmas
concert in Sagene church next week.
I was thinking you and I could bring mom,
it would mean a lot to her.
It's my thank you
for letting me borrow your shower.
You used our shower?
I used your shower, yeah.
It's not...
The hair products aren't mine.
At least not all of them.
But you're welcome to use some.
Feel free to borrow some shampoo.
Hi! Good morning.
I made us some breakfast.
I hope you're hungry cause
I've made lots of food.
Yeah. Should we get change? For the...
For the..
Should we get change for the yoga? Or?
- Oh! You're doing yoga?
- We're doing yoga?
Eh, Yeah? Yeah!
We do! Oh, that kind of yoga!
Yes! I'd forgotten, we're doing yoga now.
We're doing bathing yoga.
- Bathing yoga?
- At Bisleth bath.
So we have to...
So we have to leave.
Just help yourself to some
cayenne pepper from the freezer.
Or, I mean, from the pantry.
It's in the middle of the fridge...
- So... Bye!
- Bye!
Oh, sorry. Bye!
Hey, I didn't know what you like so I just...
I made everything.
What movie?
Movie?
Taste this.
Is it good?
Mhm.
The secret is
a tablespoon of sour cream.
When I woke up, I...
I thought you'd left.
Hey.
I was just here cooking.
And chatting with your friends.
Does Sonja know where are you?
Fuck Sonja. We're not together anymore.
Well, the last time you said it was over,
you we're making out with her
like two days later.
It's not..
It's not easy for me to not
give a fuck about her, Even.
No, but you've got to understand,
the thing with Sonja is...
that she's controlling.
Sometimes I feel as
she knows me better as myself.
Because everything she says is true.
And...
That's why I'm so freaking tired of it.
I feel as though
she can't feel what I feel
or think, for that matter.
You know?
Only you can feel what you feel.
And I haven't felt anything
quite like this...
Ever.
Neither have I.
This song though.
Huh?
Gabrielle?
Are you kidding?
No?
Jesus Christ, this is like hashtag.
What the fuck.
What?
When you found a man of your dreams,
and it turns out he likes Gabrielle.
Am I the man of your dreams?
Or?
Is it me you were talking about?
- Am I the man of your dreams?
- That's how the hashtag goes, you know...
No! Excuse me.
You said I'm man of your dreams.
Say it again.
You're the man of my dreams.
It's shit!
Seee! You're dancing! You are!
No?!
Come on, then.
"You make me fired up,"
"There's nothing that can cool me down."
"You make everything go up in smoke,"
"There's no one else I'd rather do this with."
"Five fine ladies in the club, we command."
"Turn it all the way up in the skies."
Isak! That's it! Ive been trying
to get a hold of you for days!
I kniow that you're mad at me and probably
think I'm a coward for leaving mom,
but I could not help her. I hope you'll understand
that one day. I'm trying my best.
Fine. I'll come with you
to that Christmas concert.
I'm bringing my new boyfriend.
His name's Even.
I don't know if you're joking right now?
If you've gotten a boyfriend, that's very nice,
Isak, and I would love to meet him.
But you know how mom is,
she gets very easily stressed.
Hey.
Forgot to do the assignment?
Yeah.
Did you see that...
That link I sent you?
Uh, no.
What was it?
Just a link to this article.
Okay? What was it about?
Just some...
Research done on
the theory of evolution and
homosexuality.
I was just thinking about
the discussion we had while back.
And...
It's not often that I am wrong, but...
It turns out I was wrong.
In that discussion.
Because...
Homosexuality has had a...
Has played a natural part in the evolution.
And...
They had done a lot of
new and interesting research on it.
So...
I was wrong.
What about...
What about Islam?
Anything new and exciting on that part?
Or is it still the same?
Islam
says the same as always.
That all people in this world
have the same worth.
And that no person
should be spoken about behind their back,
be violated, judged or mocked.
So if you hear anyone use religion
as an argument for their hatred,
don't listen.
Because hate doesn't derive from religion.
It derives from fear.
Can we begin class by everyone turning in
their assignement to my e-mail?
I'm pretty starved.
Me too.
I'm really tired.
I want food.
Are you coming or not?
I am not coming.
Oh, come on!
It's the best pizza, you know that.
Can't you ask somebody to take notes for you?
And just go. 99 crowns for a pizza.
It's that fucking simple.
You guys don't have to ship,
but I'll have to if-
One hour!
Yeah, one hour.
You can study for that fucking test at home.
No! I can't do that.
Yes, you can!
No, you learn more by attending
lectures. Research shows that.
Research?
What did you just say?!
Come on, why are you even thinking about it?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey
Guys, this is Even. Even, this is the...
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
- Hey, Even.
- Hey.
Magnus.
Mahdi, pleasure.
So, what's up?
We were gonna get some food,
but he got one more class, so...
Mhm.
- Sucks.
- I don't fucking care, but he's not interested.
- Oh! You're Even!
- Yeah.
Oh yeah. Holy fucking shit! I thought...
Err, sorry! Hey!
Magnus, pleasure.
A pleasure.
I completely forgotten!
He's the guy who threw us out, right?
It's exactly-
Nah.
No, it was you, but it was...
But because of him.
Yeah, because of you!
You're the one who threw us out.
Because of this hottie. Because...
I didn't throw you out!
Yes, you did.
They we're going to a party.
With you!
It was very sudden. Like,
"Guys, get out! Even's here!"
You were going to a party.
With you.
But then it didn't happen because
you wanted to hang out with him.
Yeah, but I think it was
for the best you weren't there.
No, but seriously guys.
We got to get some food.
Okay, done. We're getting pizza.
Enjoy, guys.
- Nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you.
You two enjoy as well.
Yeah, we always do.
Bye!
Nice.
- Bye.
- Pizza!
Hello, this is Isak?
Hi. Uh, it's Sonja.
Even's-
It's Sonja.
Don't fucking call Isak.
What? Why did you do that?
Don't talk to her.
Why? What does she want?
She wants to control you.
Control me?
How would she control me?
Because she...
Doesn't like people
who live freely and are real.
You're so fucking hot, Isak!
Hi mom.
I've started dating a boy.
I know you believe in God
and the Bible says it's a sin.
But you don't have to be afraid
because it's also says that
God created man in his image and
that everyone is of equal worth.
I'm sorry if it makes you sad.
Hugs, Isak.
Hey Isak, this is Sonja.
Could you call me when you won't be with Even?
It's important.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Do you wanna go to my place?
No, I don't want that.
Okay? What do you want to do, then?
I want...
Check in to...
A fucking suite!
A suite?
Yeah?
Why'd you always walk like that?
Huh?
Hello.
We have booked room for a name Evan Bach Næsheim.
Yes, welcome!
Thank you very much.
Can I see some ID?
Of course.
Are you Danish?
Yes, I am.
You're Danish?!
Wow.
How fun, I'm a huge danish fan.
Yeah?
Danish movies, danish people...
Carouselles.
Antichrist.
It's very good.
Brothers.
That one too.
Stars without brains.
Maybe not that one,
but the other ones are very good.
Don't you like Denmark?
Yeah, I do.
Denmark is great.
This is my boyfriend.
How nice.
Yeah, it's very nice.
Isn't he handsome?
Handsome?
Yeah.
How would you say it in Danish, uhm...
Hot?
Eh, what do you say?
Isn't this man beautiful?
Yes, very.
Very beautiful.
How many
Isaks and Evens are lying
just like this, what do you think?
Try this burger.
Good?
You know, at our wedding we'll only serve
mini burgers.
At our wedding, really?
You don't think we'll get married?
We're so fucking getting married!
Grand fucking wedding.
And we'll show up as...
God and Julius Caesar.
No, you know what? We'll show up as...
Just completely naked.
Completely naked. No clothes.
From now on, we'll do everything naked.
Okay.
And I'll propose to you from a balcony.
Just imagine me driving up
in a white limo Tesla.
I'll be driving up
and yelling, "Princess Vivian!"
Princess Vivian?
It would be completely genius
if that was your answer!
Because then,
the whole joke is that you think
it's a Romeo and Juliet reference.
But you don't get it
until you enter the balcony
and you see me sitting naked
with a tie. And that's when you get the reference.
And after I've climbed up the balcony,
I'll ask you.
"What'll happen after I save you?"
And then you answer...
"I'll save you right back."
It would be so fucking funny.
It's actually one of my dreams.
It's one of my dreams.
How many
do you think are lying
like this, right now?
Infinite.
In infinite time.
You know, the only way
to have something for infinity,
is by losing it.
Don't say stuff like that
I'm only joking.
Don't you ever sleep?
Not when you're lying here
looking so fucking hot.
Baby!
Come lie down with me.
Yeah, I'll just go buy some
McDonald's first.
Even?!
Where did he go?
Hello, Sonja?
Some-something happened to Even.
Can you check where the closest McDonald's is?
If he's walking around in Grønnland right now,
he'll get beaten up! He's naked!
Okay, thank you.
The police has got him.
So he's safe, at least.
What just happened?
He's manic!
That's what's happening now.
He's not well!
Do you think he's in love with you?
He's not!
It's just a sick idea he has right now.
Last year he memorized the Quoran.
In Arabic!
Because at the time
he thought it was a good idea.
He's also not supposed to smoke,
because that's not good for him,
as you might understand.
So can you just please...
Stay away?!