Did you hear William beat up
someone from Hansen this weekend?
You're going on a date with
William... for Vilde's sake?
for Vilde's sake?
It was good that you
apologised to Vilde.
About her not being good enough for you.
I hope it was a smart plan.
Because now she's keen on me again.
I'm not keen on her.
Where are you?
We have to go.
SATURDAY, 11:05 AM
Eva?
Eva!
Noora!
Hi.
I slept here.
I can see, you know.
Who is he?
- His name is Håvard.
- Halvor.
How was your date yesterday?
Eh... fine.
How was he?
- Nice.
- Nice? You have to tell me more!
- Good morning!
- Hey birthday boy!
You know what?
I think I'm still drunk. A little.
Could you be a little bit more quiet?
Okay, Linn! We'll be quiet all day!
I need some water.
Eskild!
What did you say to Eva?
I didn't say anything.
I said you'd gone on a
Tinder date with a guy.
Tinder?!
Hello, what world do you live in?
I had to say something about
why you weren't out
celebrating my birthday with me.
Eskild, it wasn't your birthday.
You can't just hang out with
my friends when I'm not here.
We chatted a little on Facebook.
She said she wanted to party.
I wanted to party too, so...
Eskild, you...
Are you jealous?
Jealous that I'm
taking all your friends?
Because I'm popular? Because I'm hot?
Because...
- I won't take your place in your friends gang.
- I'm trying to be serious!
You are hugely popular and
so funny! Pretty! Smart! Good!
- Do you need a hug?
- No! I don't need a hug.
Bear hug.
Is it better now? Do you want a hug?
You... Are you okay now?
- Just take me serioulsy!
- Yes, I am taking you seriously!
- MONDAY, 11:45 AM
- The Yakuza-boys were like:
Hey, guys! Stop, you're killing him!
He sat on top and hit and
hit him, but he screamed:
Haven't you had enough now?!
He just lay there and
wasn't even able to respond.
He just spit up blood.
Did you see the video?
It was so rough!
The Yakuza-guys fought with a knife.
He found his mother dead in the bathtub.
After that something snapped in him.
And so I wrote to him:
Heard there was a fight
on Friday. Are you okay?
He didn't answer. I
was terribly worried.
I heard that he wasn't even there.
- Who did you hear that from?
- I was talking to Iben,
and he told me it was only Chris
and a few others who were there.
That's why it was really unfair.
Because the Yakuza-boys were around 20.
They were looking for William,
but William wasn't there.
So they were beaten up...
While William was at
home fucking some girl.
What girl?
It's just a rumor. I
don't know if it's true.
- Did William reply?
- No, he didn't reply. So I sent:
"William, could you answer,
so I know you're alive?
I'm terribly worried."
Then he replied at
11.33: "Alive. I'm alive."
Has anyone seen them?
Chris is definitely
still at the hospital.
Isn't that William's car?
Did Iben say more about
the girl William was with?
- WEDNESDAY, 12:55 PM
- It could be Olivia from the third year.
Or Marte from 1STA.
No, she's a bit strange.
What's the name of the girl
that came out of the cafeteria?
She's quite pretty.
Or maybe the dark girl?
Isabel?
- Wasn't she with Jonas...
- Hey!
It could be Anja from 2STB,
but she isn't really his type.
She is a bit...
- thick.
- Huh?
You have to stop now. She's fat?!
Not fat-fat. I'm just saying
William likes skinny girls.
That's the dumbest
thing I've heard, Vilde.
I'm just saying that boys
like different things.
Some like small butts,
others like big ones.
Not everyone has to be super skinny, but
William likes girls who are model thin.
Like you.
If it's true that
William's dating a girl,
she's definitely really skinny.
It's not to diss Anja.
Gum?
I'm going to find out
who it is on Friday.
Friday... ?
If William's actually dating someone,
she's definitely coming to his party.
Party... ?
Oh yeah! We can't drink at my place.
Mom's coming home.
Can we do it at your place?
Eh, yeah. But I won't
be at William's party.
Why not?
Because I can't on Friday.
You never want to go out anymore.
You didn't go out last weekend, either.
There was no one who
could go out last weekend.
Is there someone you're hiding from us?
A little girlfriend, maybe?
Bring her to William's party.
Seriously? I can?
- That's so amazing, Vilde!
- Maybe she can come to the cabin?
A lesbian couple in Hemsedal.
That would be so cozy!
Right, Eva?
Yeah!
- What do you have now?
- Chemistry.
I have class in the B-building.
Bye!
Vilde...
Fucking hell, it's you! Isn't it?
You're dating William!
Eva, before you freak out here...
Fucking hell.
Fucking hell!
Hallo, okay. We've been on one
date and I did it for Vilde.
Why for Vilde?
Because the stuff he said
to her during Christmas,
he just said it because I
promised I'd go on a date with him.
Are you kidding me?
Am I on an episode of Gossip Girl?
Eva, you know I hate that show.
***
This is totally sick!
But you don't like him at all, right?
Eva, it's William we're
talking about here.
- So how was your date then?
- Weird!
Do you realise now why
I can't go to the party?
If William starts to
make a move on me...
Vilde will start to realise it.
***
I just hope she doesn't
start asking him about it.
I don't trust him at all.
Fucking hell.
This is Gossip Girl.
Okay, maybe a budget version.
But it's fucking Gossip Girl!
I've had it with all the
Gossip Girl references now.
Funny!
Noora, you're impressive.
Thanks.
FRIDAY, 9:22 PM
I don't understand how
Eskild can party so much.
I think it's lovely to
just be at home and relax.
Don't you agree?
Hm-hm.
Does school suck?
I hated high school.
It truly sucked.
The teachers had no sympathy.
"The curriculum is
the same for everyone."
Easy for them to say.
***
We are the performance generation.
We have it a little worse than they had.
At first I was like that as well.
"Fuck this shit."
"I need a year off."
Drama between Vilde and William.
Vilde is crying in the bathroom.
Since you're already standing up...
could you hand me a Fun light?
Noora! Hi!
What happened? Where's Vilde?
She ran away.
But you're here now!
But... what happened?
You said there was some drama
between Vilde and William.
Shit!
She's so in love with William,
but I don't think he's in love with her.
They didn't say anything about me?
They said nothing?
- No.
- No?
Shhh. Shhh!
You were on a date!
***
I don't know, but I have to...
Yeah, you have to go say hi!
Halvor... and Jacob!
He is so sweet. He's
almost my boyfriend.
No! Jonas! You came!
We are best forever, right?
I love you so fucking
much. Did you know that?
I've said it a few times already.
Drink a little, guys.
You should meet girls.
***
Where are you going?
- To the toilet.
- You can't leave her.
It'll take two seconds.
***
I'll be back soon, okay?
- You came.
- What did you say to Vilde?
- What?
- She walked out crying.
She wanted to hook up,
but I wasn't interested.
You didn't say anything about me?
About you? Who are you?
I'm kidding. Of course I
didn't say anything about you.
Fuck off!
What the hell is going on here?
- Who are you?
- William.
William? Axel.
The party you're having here...
You have to put an end to it.
We've gotten complaints
from your neighbors.
Music off, and people out.
Everyone. Great.
Eva?
Hello!
The party is over, ladies and gentlemen.
William, I have to
borrow your cellphone.
Eva left with all my stuff.
Hi Eskild. I have lost
everything. My phone and keys.
Call me when you get this message.
On this number.
Chris.
It's time to leave.
***
Are you coming with me?
Kidding...
Did you get to her?
No.
But I left a message on the voice mail
of someone I live with so...
He'll definitely call back soon.
When are your parents coming home?
They're not coming home.
Where are they?
Dad lives in London and mom
lives on Snarøya with a new man.
You live here by yourself?
More or less.
I don't drink.
Shocking...
Don't you have siblings?
My brother studies in Stockholm.
Do you want something else?
Do you have... cocoa?
Baking cocoa?
Yeah, I don't know why I got it.
The lady at the check out
got it for me so it was okay.
It says something about
dark cocoa drink here.
Extra dark and powerful cocoa.
Five tablespoons
of Freia baking cocoa.
Four to five tablespoons of sugar.
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
- Don't you remember how to make it?
- I do,
but I just want to do it right.
Okay.
Why don't you live with your mom?
Because my mom is a cunt.
Hey...
What?
- It's still your mom.
- So what?
Should I not be honest?
Sure, but you don't need to be
a complete misogynist about it.
So you only want me to be honest
if it's politically correct?
Has Eskild called?
No.
You have to check your cellphone.
Fuck.
Do you want one?
Oh my god, seriously?
Can I have it?
Do I look good?
It's the sweater of all sweaters.
Many at school have acquired it.
Insanely popular.
Then I would've been just like
you. That's the dream, right?
A guitar too?
Have we really come to this point?
There's nothing missing
then, so to speak.
Do you play for girls?
So sweet.
- Sweet, indeed.
- Yeah.
Do you play for them
before you take them to bed?
You have to, right?
You have to do something.
- What do you play?
- I don't play for girls.
Yes you do. What else? Oof.
There's sound! It's a real one, then?
You obviously play for girls.
I know it. What do you play?
Is it country?
I know what you play.
You just...
♪ I feel it in my fingers ♪
♪ I feel it in my toes ♪
♪ love is all around me ♪
♪ and so the feeling grows ♪
Was that it? No? No...
Then it's more like...
♪ It's amazing ♪
♪ how you can speak right to my heart ♪
♪ without saying a word ♪
♪ you can light up the dark ♪
With a little rapping. No? Really?
Now I know, William. I know it.
I know, I know what you're playin'.
Other than girls.
♪ Saying "I love you" ♪
♪ Is not the words I
want to hear from you ♪
♪ It's not that I need you ♪
♪ not because but if you only knew ♪
♪ How easy ♪
♪ It would be to show me how you feel ♪
♪ More than words ♪
♪ Is all you need to do to make it real ♪
♪ Then you wouldn't have to say ♪
♪ That you love me ♪
♪ Cause I'd already know ♪
♪ What would you do? ♪
♪ If my heart was torn in two ♪
♪ Then you couldn't make things real ♪
♪ Just by saying "I love you" ♪
♪ What would you say ♪
♪ If I took those words away ♪
♪ Then you couldn't make things true, ♪
♪ Just by saying "I love you" ♪
I think it's for you.
- Hello, where are you?
- At home. What's up?
I lost all my stuff. Keys,
cellphone, everything.
- Okay, so... That sucks.
- It really sucks!
At least I'm at home now.
Just call from downstairs
and I'll let you in.
Yeah...
Yeah okay. Bye.
Is he home?
Eh, no. No. He...
he is in the city with some people.
So...
I can sleep on the couch.
Oh, no.
This works, right? Just...
just stick to your
side of the bed, okay?
It's my bed, so both sides are mine.
No. That's not how it
works here now, William.
You may not be used to this, but...
There are sides to this bed.
This is your side. This is my side.
I suggest that we build a little border.
So don't come over
and invade my personal space.
Are you going to sleep
with all your clothes on?
Yes.
Okay.
What do you want for breakfast tomorrow?
I won't be eating breakfast here.
Eggs and bacon? Great.
You are the biggest cliché I've met.
Ever!
I was never validated as a child.
Mom never came to graduation.
Dad never complimented my drawings.
Okay.
But you like me for it.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do. You like me.
What is it?
Is there someone you have to beat up?
It's a message from Eskild.
He doesn't want to stay up and
wait for you any longer and wonders
when you're coming home.
I'll answer: Noora is
so keen on me... that
she failed to get away.
- Excuse me? No! You're not writing that!
- Excuse me, you're on my side now!
- Can you... please get over on your side?
- Can I?
That's your side of the bed.
And this is my side of the bed.
***
So we're going to let the
cellphone and pillows be.
Let go, let go, let go!
Just write that I'm
coming home tomorrow.
You like me.
Goodnight, Willhelm.
Goodnight, Noora.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -