The global mentality is moving towards
free world trade and increased market liberalism.
A world full of opportunities.
A world where dreams can come true.
It sounds fantastic,
and it is fantastic.
For a very small percentage of us.
But for the vast, poor majority,
the capitalist system
only means one thing:
death and suffering.
While we live out our days thoughtlessly,
and stuff ourselves with cheap food...
the poor people of the earth
struggle in factories.
Wages are forced down to the minimum,
while the work hours keep increasing.
Unionization is illegal,
and the working conditions are intolerable.
Before applauding freedom,
we must remember one thing:
Our over-consuming society stands on
the shoulders of the coffee farmers from Peru.
We gorge on cheap food produced by
underpaid children's hands from India--
SHAME
- Was it good?
- It was really good!
What about the title? Should I change it to:
"Working conditions are inhumane"?
- No, it was good the way it was.
- Yeah?
Is there anything else you thought of?
You know, you wrote
"gorge on cheap food" twice in a row?
- Yes?
- Maybe you could change that.
No, no, I meant to write it twice.
Because I use repetition
as a literary tool to emphasize--
- Was it good?
- Yeah, that was good. Cleverly written.
Hehe! I got a 5.
5+? Nice. Really good!
- Eva, what did you get? Come on!
- I'd rather not talk about it.
The thing is, Jonas is your boyfriend,
so you have to tell him everything.
Jonas is my bro, so he has to tell me everything,
so I'll know anyway.
It's true.
Okay, yeah. I got a 4-.
You got a 4-?
- That's bad.
- Yeah. You're good at a lot of other things.
You're able to dress yourself,
you can brush your teeth by yourself.
Think of that.
Jonas, we're leaving.
- Now?
- Yeah.
- Where are you going?
- To Elias'.
- I'll call you later.
- Okay.
TUESDAY, 8:32 P.M.
T
TA
TAS
TASK
TASK 1:
The subscriber cannot be reached--
- Hello!
- Hey!
- What's up?
- Nothing special, really.
- Are you with Jonas?
- No, not now.
Weren't you going to Elias?
- Yeah, but that was a few hours ago.
- Oh.
Did you see Sara's picture?
I think she got fake lashes.
- No way?!
- Yeah, check the picture on Facebook.
- What's up with those girls?
- I know.
Have you heard they started their bus already?
- No.
- One month into high school they started a bus.
With who?
With some other girls,
they're calling themselves the Pepsi Max girls.
You know you can just talk to her, right?
She won't bite.
- Jonas is here. I have to go.
- What are you going to do?
I tried to call you,
but you never answered your phone.
Yeah, my battery was dead.
- Can't you just charge it at home?
- I wasn't home.
- Where were you then?
- I was at Elias'.
- Until now?
- Yeah.
But I talked to Isak.
He said you guys left Elias' hours ago.
Why so many questions? Isak left, I stayed.
Don't you trust me?
Huh? Why don't you trust me?
- You're heavy.
- You're crazy...
- 3+? You said you got a 4-!
- It's almost the same.
- "Whoever has expelled..."
- Jonas!
"...must be blamed for their behavior.
In psychology, as well as..."
- Jonas!
- "...is guilt a state one experiences."
"A state one experiences"?
That was really sweet.
- What do you think you're doing?
- A kiss.
"A state one experiences."
WEDNESDAY, 11:30 A.M.
Task 1:
A society is
- What's your name?
- Ingrid.
- Are you guys in the same class?
- 1STA, yeah.
It's 150 kroner per ticket.
It'll be good. Are you guys excited?
Hi! Are you joining the revue?
We're from the stage group,
and we want to have you!
What do you do in the stage group?
We're hammering till we wail, we're sawing till
we complain, we're measuring till we drink,
we're painting till we purr, like a cat!
We have a pre-party tomorrow.
You're going to the party, right?
You have to go to the revue-party,
everyone is going!
You're a first-year.
This is when you lay the foundation of
your social life for the next three years!
Wake up!
Nah, but if you want to come to the pre-party,
add me on Facebook:
Argentina Mikolovna Hoshka!
I don't think anyone actually likes him.
And when the teacher asks
obvious questions...
THURSDAY, 8:30 A.M.
- Hey... can't we go to the revue-party?
- Why?
Because the entire school is going.
And we are first-years.
This is when we lay the foundation
of our social life.
"Foundation of our social life"?
Come on! It's a revue-party.
It'll be so much fun!
- I promise.
- Yeah, okay, I'll come.
If...
Isak can come to the cabin next week.
Please! I know it was supposed to be
just the two of us,
but it's autumn break,
and Isak has nothing to do.
He's just going to sit around, all alone.
You can bring a friend as well.
What do you say?
- Okay, Isak is allowed to come along.
- I can come along to what?
- My cabin.
- The cabin? I'm going to the cabin?
On one condition.
That you guys come to
the revue-party tomorrow.
- We can't.
- Why not?
The Kindred Fever tickets.
I completely forgot about those!
Sorry, but I didn't remember them at all!
Don't walk away, Eva!
FRIDAY, 7:37 P.M.
He's been pretending to go to work
for the past five years.
I was playing Solitaire.
After leaving the Air Force,
I did feel pressure, to land a great job.
The first job Mike lied about was
the government contracting job
in Germany.
Mike had me quit my job of...
about eighteen years, and...
in retrospect, I think there were warning signs.
What do you hear me telling you?
I know, it's just...
it's hard, I don't...
I'm hard on myself, I feel
like stupid, I feel like...
you know, I'm gonna be judged,
that I'm an idiot,
I didn't see this.
You're gonna decide
that you're either gonna be
a broken betrayed victim,
who has lost all confidence
because you didn't see
what was happening to you,
or you are gonna say,
as expensive as it was,
this was tuition,
and my image is,
"I am a stronger woman for it.
"I will lead myself,
"I will lead my son,
"I will not be broken by this,
"I will stand strong
"and I will walk out of my history--"
Hi! You came!
You can't ignore me forever.
We have to have a talk eventually.
Ingrid...
I miss you.
Come on, say something.
I would've lost the eyeliner
if I were you.
You look like a slut.
Vilde snapped.
She seemed cool.
I think we have Spanish together.
- Noora.
- Eva.
Girls who call other girls sluts
have a 90% higher risk
of getting chlamydia.
- Seriously?
- No.
But it would've been very cool
if it was true.
- Are you okay?
- Yes... yes.
Are you sure?
Maybe...
Maybe I can get a friend of yours?
- Maybe Chris?
- Chris?
It was 40,000 kroner.
I don't have that much money!
It's toilet paper, Vilde!
Toilet paper! It's not so bad.
We can't use that much toilet paper.
I don't mean to interrupt,
but I got Chris for you.
Here I am!
- This is Chris.
- I am Chris.
- Are you also called Chris?
- Oh, my god!
- Twin names!
- Yeah, twin names!
We were actually
in the middle of something...
Yes, of course.
- Come, we're leaving.
- What's up? Weren't we going to talk?
You! Where are you going?
Hey, don't be such a dick tease!