I spotted them on Friday.
This is good shit. Fuck!
Both her and Emilie are so hot.
No...
She isn't doable.
Huh?!
What do you think?
I think that she's doable.
- Yeah?
- Emilie as well.
Emilie is even better.
What's up with you guys,
lowering you standards.
What's up with you?
What are you talking about standards? You should
be much less picky, considering how ugly you are.
Is there not a single hot girl? Not one?
- I could've gotten with all the first years.
- There is one!
Listen to me. One!
Short, dark hair. Don't know
what she's called. But she's hot.
She's pretty. I saw her.
- The one resembling Natalie Portman?
- Yes, yes, yes. That one.
I don't think you have a chance.
Not in this life, maybe the next one.
I do have a chance!
Last guy she was with was a 20-year-old
model. He was tall and dark. You are neither.
Why should I care about that?
Because then you know
what her standards are.
When a girl dates a 20-year-old model,
she won't date another guy like that.
I have a chance.
- You have to take the stash.
- No!
I'm too stressed when I have it.
Take it yourself.
I can't have it with me.
Then I'll take it. Jesus Christ!
It isn't yours!
- Just let him take it.
- I don't even know him!
- Don't know me? What are you talking about?
- It's 1000 kroner!
You know... What the fuck?
You're sitting here smoking it with him.
Of course you know him!
He's in, I'm in, he's in...
Him... I don't know what he's doing.
Just let him take it. I'm really certain.
Thanks.
What would you do without me?
What's going on? Shut the door.
- I need to pee.
- Then shut the door right now.
Hello?!
Don't just leave.
I was stuck there with that nerd.
I had to pee.
- Your girl.
- It's so boring here.
Hello.
Remember when we were at Sana's
place and took some pills?
- She was so out of it.
- They weren't blue.
I think they're the same.
Do you know who you look like?
Yes.
The little boy in Stranger Things.
You know! The little boy
who's actually a girl. Eleven.
So damn rude.
No!
She's sweet.
If you're into 13-year-old boys.
- Huh? What?
- I'm only kidding!
Seriously. I'm only kidding. I'm sorry.
- My name's Isak. What's yours?
- Emma.
Emma? You're really beautiful.
We're leaving.
Do you know how this works?
Let me see.
Zyrtec? Those are allergy pills.
They'll make you tired.
- Do you want something that works?
- Do you have that?
Maybe.
I'm leaving.
Uh yeah. We'll check if there's
some food around here.
Really nice, Isak.
- Hey...
- Hey, what?
Emma, Yousef is here.
- Have you seen Eva?
- No.
Hi.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
- You're going home? Over the fence?
- Yeah.
Everybody else has gone
through the gate over there.
Do you have some ID on you?
With your name etc.
Bank card? Driver's license?
- No.
- Nothing?
- What's your name?
- Adrian Eksett.
Adrian. How old are you?
Wait a minute.
Yes? Answer.
[Mamma, Exodus 20:4]
[Do you still have our stash? Call me when you wake up. Police found
some stuff at Eva's place. She's really mad and thinks it's mine.]
[Pick up your phone then. Sorry I had to hide it at Eva's. But it's
not possible that they found it because I hid it really well.]
[Promise I'll fix it. Call me.]
Isak! Hey, he's awake.
With morning wood straight up.
Look! Devil's cave is what I call it.
Want to say hi?
Hi, good morning!
Did you sleep well?
Say hi.
- Hi.
- Say hi then!
Hi!
He's a bit crabby and tired.
- Hi Isak!
- Hi. Hi, Noora.
- Piss off, Eskild!
- Relax!
- What are you guys doing today?
- Relax, I think.
Yeah. Relax.
So nice.
I'm going to sell my Warhammer collection
on the flea market. No, I'm kidding.
I'm going to the supermarket
to buy fish cakes. Kidding.
I'm going to fill up a big can with
Fun Light and watch a movie. With Linn.
- Ah, so nice.
- Yeah.
We'll snuggle up together.
What are you going to do?
I don't know. I'll just find something.
Something like what?
William's working, so I just have to...
I don't have that many friends yet.
What I think, Noora...
You are in London. Best city in the world.
I know! I'm having a lot fun!
I'll have lots of fun today.
Or I'll go to a museum.
- You're going to a museum?
- Yeah!
Don't go to a museum, Noora. Do something fun! Don't
go to a museum and be boring. Do something fun.
- Go to a club. Get some drinks.
- Yeah, relax.
- I'm having lots of fun.
- Yeah...
- I want you to be doing well, Noora.
- Yeah, really well!
So what's it like living with Isak?
Is it all right?
- He doesn't pay rent, you know?
- I will pay.
And he smells like farts. Guy farts.
While you smell good.
You smell like delicious lavender.
Love you.
I hooked up with a girl of who I
legitimately thought had a cat tongue.
I'm not sure if it was a
tongue, or a fake tongue.
Fake tongue?!
- Like making out with a cat.
- Have you kissed a cat?
- No, but it was really small and thin.
- Cat size?
I didn't see her tongue, but...
You know that party at Johanna's?
I hooked up with a chick there.
- The blonde one?
- Yeah, the blonde one.
She didn't have a clitoris.
- What?!
- Yeah, I swear. She didn't have it.
- How do you know?
- I saw it.
[Dad: Hi Isak. Do you want to have dinner
with me on Wednesday night? Hug from dad/]
I saw it! I know where the clitoris is.
And I saw it when I went down on her.
[I need money for my rent. 4000 Kroner]
Are you joking?
- No...
- You went down on her?
- Yeah.
- You go down on chicks?
Why are you so surprised? You don't?
- Eh, no!
- Why not?
I don't know. Should we go down on chicks?
Why the fuck...
- Because they love it. Why do you ask?
- Do you also go down on chicks?
Isak?
Hi!
Do you guys perhaps want to
join the theatre this year?
Don't really know.
We are group leaders of the “kose” group.
(kose = a good vibe/feeling/atmosphere)
We want to have you guys!
Kose group? What does a kose group do?
We make sure there's a good atmosphere.
We spread love, bake bread, we cook.
We have a group meeting next Friday.
Maybe you guys want to come?
Friday...?
No. I don't really know.
It's Friday, you know.
But you're second years.
You're neither third years nor first years.
You guys should make yourselves known socially
to avoid becoming completely anonymous.
Do you guys want that?
To walk around being a nobody?
Eva!
Did you see my messages?
I forgot my sweater at your place.
Yeah, I saw. I'll look for it.
No, but I have to come get it at your
place because I know what it looks like.
Can't you just describe it?
Yes. I can.
It's black…
Okay... A black sweater. Got it.
Let us know if you want to join!
Yeah, we'll do that.
Bye.
A sweater?!
What's up?
- I had to hide the shit at Eva's place.
- Are you kidding?
- I'll fix it.
- That's 1000 Kroner.
Mahdi, I'll fix it.
Was it not good?
Ask first. Cat guy.
- Hi.
- I have your drugs.
- What?
The stuff you left at Eva's place.
I have it.
You have it?
If there's one thing I don't like,
it's when someone fucks over their friends.
What do you mean?
Eva could've been in a
lot of trouble if they had found it.
Could have... but they didn't find it.
They didn't find it because I took it.
Okay, I'm sorry for leaving it there. Thanks
for taking it, but it's not even mine.
I should get something in
return for rescuing it from the police.
Do you think this is a fucking
Narcos episode or something?
Can't you just give it to me?
I want 10% of your drugs.
Do you use then?
No, but it's great to have.
I also want you and your
friends to join the kose group.
Kose group. That's the best
theatre group of them all!
Okay.
Whatever. We can join the kose group.
- So then you'll give it to me?
- Yes.
So just give it to me now.
Do you think I'm dumb? You get it when I see
you and your friends at the group meeting.
Sana and Isak can work together.
Huh?! No, I'm not sitting here.
Can't you work with Isak? It'll be fine.
Guys and girls can work together.
We do that in Norway.
Hi! Welcome!
[Where the fuck are you guys? I can't be
bothered to sit here by myself, it's your shit.]
Chris! [Where the fuck are you guys? I can't be
Chris!
Can Kasper join the meeting?
Kasper doesn't go to this school though.
Yes. That'll be fine.
Right Vilde?
It's quite unhealthy that
they're together every single second.
- Hello.
- Hi!
So nice that you wanted to come.
Yeah just find a seat,
then we can start.
Some bread? I baked it myself.
Cool. Looking forward to it.
[Sorry man, I have to help my mom with
something. I'll come as soon as I'm done.]
[Fuck was that today]
- Hello.
- Kose group, yay!
- Yay...
We looked at the group list during break.
Where are the awesome people of this school?
Kose group, of course.
Cool.
Hi and welcome.
We are overjoyed that you
guys are here today.
You guys can introduce yourselves.
This here is...
- Eva.
- Sana.
- Vilde!
- Vilde.
So I thought I'd explain
what kind of vision we have.
We have our group meeting 3 weeks before the others
because we are an important aspect of the theatre.
More than, for example, PR or costumes.
We thought it's best to have a good system
throughout the entire theatre event.
That's why we'll divide you into groups.
Or duos, so that you'll be in pairs.
Then it's not a group, but a duo.
You guys will divide the days between
yourselves. That's what we'll be doing.
So that... I'm a bit nervous!
So that you will pair up and
someone will cook every day.
It's really important in the kose group that
you spread a lot of good vibes, and love.
Spreading love is not something
that comes naturally to everyone.
So I thought we could all do a love
exercise. If everyone can get up...
If everyone can stand in a circle here,
then we'll grab each other's hands.
Do you also need tissues?
Come outside.
You know the group leader?
Vilde?
- With the love game?
- What was that?
I had to bail. I can't be bothered
with that stuff. What happened?
She got us to go and feel eachother in a dark room.
If you walked into a dick, you had to suck it.
- No?
- No!
- What class are you in?
- 3STB
You didn't go here before?
No, Elvebakken.
You transferred in your final year?
Hey you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
We're setting up the cooking system.
We should be in pairs.
I don't know that many people. Well I
know Maria, but she's going with Lea.
So that's why I was wondering
if you want to be in a group with me.
I thought we were in a group together.
Yeah, I had in a way already
agreed to be in a group with...
- With...
- Even.
Emma.
I'm sure we can be in a group of three.
I think she said we should
be in pairs, but I don't care.
It seemed like Vilde was
really clear on wanting pairs.
Can't you just ask?
Yeah, okay. Then we'll do that.
Yes, we'll do that.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Can I have a drag?
Thanks.