Sana! Sana!
What the fuck ?!
I like Yousef. When I realized
that there was something between you...
No! There is nothing between us!
There is something I need to tell you.
And please do not get angry.
Thanks for the mail.
Welcome to voice mail from Telenor.
Leave a message
after the beep.
Noora, please call me.
-Hello?
-Eskild? Is Noora home?
It's Sana.
Oh my God, they’re just in William’s penthouse to fuck.
She’ll be back when she’s newly fucked, my generous, little girl.
-I think they went to London.
-Yeah you think they went to London, but you also thought ...
... Grunde was going to win Paradise,
so you have bad judgement, Linn.
Have some manners.
I’m just a little worried she’s mad at me.
She didn’t look very mad when she went off in that
3 million kroner Aston Martin. 3 million is a lot of money.
I sent an email to William.
E-mail? It’s been a while since I’ve written one of those.
Yes, but I sent it from Noora’s account.
You sent an email from Noora's account
to William? Ok, what did you write?
Eh...
I just wrote ...
"I love you and if
you love me, come to Oslo."
That's what made him
come? An email ?!
Why didn't you think to do that
before ?! You write e-mails all the time.
You’re a grown up, Linn. Is that what it took?
She’s been stomping around in this self-pitying heartache for 8 months and then all it took was an e-mail?
You shouldn’t feel bad about that, that was well done.
I'm really a bit proud of you.
High five!
But I didn't
really do it for Noora's sake.
I did it because ...
she was with a guy I like.
-Which guy?
-Just a guy called Yousef.
Yousef? Isn’t that the guy you were
trying to pick up last night?
Once I sent a used tampon ...
... to a girl who made out with my ex.
-Have you had a boyfriend ?!
-Yes, in 7th grade.
-That was the first and last one?
-Yes.
But now we’re talking about Sana, Linn.
We can talk about you later.
Right now we’re talking about
Sana and the cute Muslim boy.
-He's not a Muslim.
-He's not?
Ok ...
Hm.
-Do you want some guru-advising?
-What's that?
I was with this guy, a year ago, a very good relationship
... the best I’ve ever had.
It was a Turkish ambassador's son.
His name was Lito. You remember him?
He was really cool. Went to Blinder'n ...
was concerned with human rights,
Sensitive soul, shared a lot about himself.
the most well-shaped cock I’ve ever touched.
He was also a Muslim.
and not that I'm religious, or anything,
because I'm not ...
- but I have browsed the Bible
a couple of times ...
... there it says that the most
important thing is love.
Or "Love on Top," as Beyoncé says.
So I think what would Jesus and Mohammed do?
And that would be "let the love flow."
So we tried that. Love on Top. I was the
top. You know, you know about that
because you heard it.
So we did that lots of times. Then we began
to talk about other things, important things.
Grown up things like life and humanity
and stuff and we disagreed a lot.
So the conclusion is that relationships
between religious and non-religious people are difficult.
I cried a lot.
Aren’t there some other hotties in that gang?
That Elias, isn’t he cute?
-He's my brother!
-That's ... yes, that's your brother.
That won’t work. That would be weird.
Which religion would you follow?
Buddhism or something?
-Bahá'í, maybe?
-Bahá'í, maybe.
Now I've become a bit inspired to research
and stuff online. What are you doing today?
(No, I still haven’t heard anything…. And you?
-No, have you made Chris call William?
-William isn’t answering either….
-But think about it, they’ve been apart for a very
long time, they’re probably just chilling, and
don’t give a fuck about anyone else)
(Boys in the yard)
-Come on then! Throw!
-Guys, guys, listen now!
Okay.
(BALLOON BOYS TALKING AND YELLING ABOUT THE GAME)
Try then, Elias
I'm so bad at this!
Throw, then!
-There, yes!
-Good throw!
Hey!
-What's up, Sana?
-Join us!
We're in the middle of a tournament!
She can join later.
Mikael, your turn.
Two against two, it's over.
-You throw it, and then...
-Bad! Bro, go home.
The two of you against the two of us.
Hey.
Did you have a nice time at Eva’s birthday party?
Yes! It was very fun.
And you?
It was fun
The gift she got was pretty awesome.
Eskild just popping the champagne bottle and stuff.
It wasn’t even his gift.
-He didn’t even bring one
He’s awesome.
Yeah.
And Even. It was good to see him again, at least.
Guys, it’s the third time we’ve beat you.
so please, just put up a bit of a fight.
I thought of something. We have to break
the fast together tonight.
-With some delicious food.
-Balkan! Balkan Kebab.
No, bro, Istanbul, right?
-But we have to do it before Yousef leaves.
-Yousef? When are you leaving?
- I talked to Noora.
-Yousef! When are you leaving?
- Saturday.
-Saturday?
-Done. We eat together on friday
-No!
-Why not? Relax. We’ll eat on Friday.
Friday is better.
We can chill all night.
-I can't on Friday.
-What are you doing on Friday?
Where... where are you going?
I’m going to Turkey.
Oh yes?
Will you be gone long?
-No, Thursday is better guys.
-We have one last night with him.
So should I just ditch the dude?
-Let him join.
-Yousef, it's your turn.
-???.
-Why am I always the one who has to switch?
Guys, I’m missing a stick, give me one.
-Okay, Mutta, which one should I hit?
-Hit this one.
-Great.
-If you hit it, you’re good.
You see? Lovely.
-Therefore he is on my team!
-It’s beginner’s luck, man.
If you hit it once, you’re the king.
If you hit it now, you win the whole thing.
It's the first time you play,
so it's okay.
-It’s always Elias and me, man.
-It's always me and Yousef.
(Message Sound)
Let’s play another round, guys.
Another round? Okay, one more.
If I hit it now...
Then we eat at Balkans.
We won.
-Ahhh,done!
-You said that one.That one.
-Yeah that one too.
Come on bro, throw it, then!
I don’t think you should be worried. I’m sure it’s fine.
Yes ... I just have a bad feeling in my tummy.
-What’s that supposed to mean?
-I think there's something wrong.
Something wrong ?!
-How do you know that?
-Hey, should we contact the police?
-What if he has killed her?
-He hasn’t killed her.
We can’t know that for sure.
He has shown violent tendencies in the past.
his brother is a psychopath. We don’t know if William
is or not - those things are genetic.
Oh my God.. They’re fucking!
Stop nagging!
-For four days?!
-Yeah.
- Without making a sound?
-Well I don’t know, I haven’t been listening
to them.
Hey.
Fucking hell, William’s car is so cheesy.
Shocking!
She's alive!
Hi!
-Hi!
-Hey.
Eh ... William?
I have to leave.
It's ...
It's just that ... Ok because...
We only... I just feel...
I just feel...
Now I feel that...
That we have talked about everything.
At ...
That we only... He just opened up completely.
Do you understand what I mean? And...
I didn't know what I was doing before,
but I know what and how he thinks now.
Sana Bakkoush,
this is the best thing you've ever done!
Thank you!
But hey! Oh my God, how did it go with Yousef?
I do not know completely ...
But you talked, right?
I ... yes, or ...
I tried talking to him.
Eh ...
But ...
He’s going to Turkey and he’s staying all summer ...
... and he's not a Muslim, and ...
But you have to talk to him!
Just talk to him before he leaves!
Send him a text! Now!
Eh... I don't have his number.
Then write to him on Facebook.
-We are not friends on Facebook.
-Oh my God, Sana! Add him then!
Now!
Seriously! Come on!
Yes ... And then you write:
“Do you want to hang out with me?”
Sana! I swear I’ll log onto your account and write it myself ...
... and hit "send." I'm not kidding, you know that.
Ok ...
Yeeeah! Good!
Oh my God!
That wasn’t so hard, was it?
You know what ...
Now life is smiling
Now we can do anything we want!
And I suggest...
That we skip!
Are you in?
Yeah, but I think we already are
(skipping).
Class started a long time ago.
Is that true?
Oh my God. Yeah, well, then that’s it.
I thought it would be ...
a bit more difficult. But it feels very natural.
Maybe because we’ve been good all year.
Summer vacation starts soon.
Yes, now we’ll just go and hide, and wait for the summer.
-What if he doesn't answer?
-No! Everything is falling into place now, Sana.
Look, then!
Yes, it is.
-This is me and Noora at a café.
-Red lipstick?
- She’s always wearing red lipstick.
-Yeah? It suits her.
Yes, it suits her very well. And here
she’s also wearing red lipstick.
And this is at school
- She's very pretty girl.
-She's very pretty.
-And this is Chris.
-She looks like a lot of fun.
Yes, she's awesome.
Why don’t you invite them here?
-Wow.
-That's a picture of Vilde and Eva.
(Of course I want to hang out with you! What about Friday? I’m leaving on Saturday.Yousef Acar accepted your friend request.)
Aaand ...
This is another picture of Noora.
-What's with the sunglasses?
-It’s just this halloween party.
We were ...
We had dressed up.
Nice pictures!
I like Yousef.
Mm.
And ...
He ... he is not a Muslim.
And now you’re going to hang out?
I know...
I know that Islam says that ...
... I can't marry him.
but I just ... I don’t understand that because ...
... Yousef is a really good person.
You are only 17 years old.
You are not getting married yet.
No, but ...
what about three years from now?
If I still like Yousef,
why can’t I marry him?
When you are so young,
You think crushes and love are the same thing.
Crushes pass,
but love and a marriage last for your whole life.
It's almost like a partnership.
where you give all the love inside
of you to that partnership.
It’s also about having someone by your side your whole life.
No matter what happens.
And I think that if your faith is strong
you’ll get a bit lonely in that relationship,
... if you’re the only one who believes.
Because there are always times in your life
where you doubt everything. Even God.
And then I think it's important that you
have have someone by your side ...
... who reminds you why you’re a Muslim
And who understands what you believe in.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
(Phone ringing)
It will be fine. Hello?
(Yousef-Of course I want to hang out with you! What about Friday?
I’m leaving on Saturday.
Sana-Oh are you leaving this Saturday? I can’t this week.
I hope you have the world’s best summer.
Chris-Yo girls. What about test driving the van this Friday?
I know it’s not Russ Time 2018 yet, but a little trip has to be fine?
VILDE-YEEEES!!!)
Please accept my fast ...
... even though I've behaved badly.
Please watch over Eva and Vilde ...
... and Noora.
And Chris.
Please watch over Isak and Even.
And Elias.
And Yousef.
(Music Outside)
(Message Sound)
(VILDE-Hi, are you ready to meet up?
EVA-Sana! Chris and I will pick you up with the van in 20 minutes.
SANA-Ok cool
SANA-I regret cancelling the date with Yousef
NOORA-YEEES! Call him! Go!
EVA-Do it girl!! Life is NOW!!
SANA-According to Islam, life is after death. Which is one of the reasons why I should stay away from him
CHRIS-According to me, the pudenda is dead after death. Which is one of the reasons why you should meet him!!
VILDE-Yousef! Yousef! Yousef!
SANA-Hahaha I get why mom is worried that I don’t have any Muslim friends
NOORA-Hello! OK!! I can argue from an Islamic perspective
SANA-Now I’m intrigued
NOORA-Ok, doesn’t Islam believe in destiny?
SANA-Yes.
NOORA-So if you believe in destiny, and you believe Allah is almighty, there has to be a reason why Yousef became a part of your life? It’s not necessarily because you should be together, maybe it’s something else, but you won’t find out if you avoid him?!?!?!
CHRIS-Wow that shit is deep.
SANA-You’re right
NOORA-Oh yeah bitches, I got a 6 in religion.
VILDE-But Noora it IS because they’re going to be together.
NOORA-Okay, they’re going to be together
SANA-Thanks)
Hey?
-Hi.
-Hey.
I was just wondering ...
What you’re doing right now?
Nothing special, really.
Um ...
I  was just wondering ...
... if you still wanted to meet up?
Oh, shit...
Sorry, umm ...
I’ve made other plans.
Oh okay.
Yes yes.
I understand that.
I'm joking! Of course we can meet up!
When do you want me to meet you?
Where? I’ll meet you wherever you’d like.
Don't want to?
(Talking while Cezinando - Vi er perfekt, men verden er ikke det plays)
Ouch!
I got it in my eye!
Oi!
Why didn’t you tell me? That sucks!
It could’ve bit my finger, you know.
I’m so scared!
I’m terrified of those.
It was just suddenly there
Right now I'm actually really scared.
I'm just tough next to you.
- Oh look, there’s a spider here, Sana!
-Where?
Okay, I’m gonna see if you trust me.
Just stand here.
I'm waiting.
It's wet here!
-If I trust you?
-Yeah, come on. Stand there,
It's a test of whether you
trust me or not.
Don't you trust me?
Hello, if I ...
I’m standing here! Look!
Listen. This is an even better game. I’m gonna be
like this and you’ll stand there for at least 10 seconds.
Come on.
I’ll count out loud
I promise, I’ll count out loud. Stand there.
You’re looking at me now!
-Come on.
-Then you also have to.
Ok, we can stand together then.
Look. I’m standing here. I dared to. Come on.
I’m not doing anything. There’s no stress. Now it’s your turn.
It's about trusting...
-’m standing here!
-I can tell you’re standing there! Okay, fine.
-Yeah, 10 seconds.
-One, two, three ... Look! I trust you!
You’re supposed to stand here!
-Don’t you trust me?
-I do. Come on!
Press it, Press it! Come on!
What are you going to do? You're bad.
It doesn't help.
-Okay, we trust each other.
-Yes, we do.
-How long?
-Ten seconds.
Ten, nine, eight ...
seven, six ...
five, four ...
three, two, and ...
Boom!
That was a sick remix, wasn’t it?
That's enough, Sana. Hero.
Was it good?
Really good.
-Are you hungry?
-Yeah, I’m super hungry.
I think we have to buy some food.
Don’t you think I brought food?
-You brought food?
-Of course I brought food!
I’m not going on a date with a girl who’s been
fasting for 19 hours without bringing food.
Don’t make me throw you into the water!
Seriously! Of course I brought food.
I am, afterall, Yousef!
-Awww ...
Don’t ‘awwww’ me. I get really embarrassed, seriously.
- I can’t even look at you now.
-That's what the backpack is for!
MMM. Did you make this?
No. I wish it was me.
But it’s not. It was my mom.
-What’s in this?
-It's a secret recipe.
Mom made it.
It’s this amazing recipe.
Think it's
bit too complicated for you.
Why?
Because the recipe says you have to be able to peel carrots the right way.
I don’t think you’re the right person for that.
Ok ...
It was really nice of you to bring soup, though.
See? I can be a good person even
though I'm not fasting.
I have not been a good
person during this fast.
No?
I’ve behaved really shitty.
There’s still a week left of Ramadan.
You can spend this week making up for it.
True.
I was actually bullied in middle school.
So every time I experience something like that, I just ...
... I don’t know. Black out.
But I'm trying to practice ...
... thinking that people don't
have prejudices against Islam.
But it’s pretty difficult.
Even you think that
religion divides society.
To be completely honest,
I think society would be split ...
... even if religion didn’t exist.
-You think so?
-Yes.
For example ...
when you get into a revue party ...
The first thing you look for,
is people you know,
... so you won’t be there on your own ...
I think the whole world is like that.
You think of the whole world as a big revue party?
Yes. On one side, there are the gangsters
from the ‘Sound and Equipment’ group ...
... who talk shit about the preps who form the
‘PR’ group on the other side of the room.
And everyone agrees that their group is the
best and that their pre-parties are the best.
But in reality, everyone is all the same.
Everyone thinks they’re the good guys.
but in reality, there’s no such thing as good or bad.
There are just lots of people trying to stand together in groups ...
... to not be alone.
So you're saying that ...
All people are the same?
Yes.
Scientifically, people are totally different.
Maybe that's why society needs religion, then.
Democracy is not built on the idea
that all people are different.
It is based on the idea that
all people are equally worthwhile.
That idea does not come
from science.
But I do not know if it helps
to pretend that ...
... prejudices don't exist.
What you have to do,
is show what Islam is.
You're really a Muslim, aren't you?
You just say you're not.
Unfortunately, I'm not.
But how can you be entirely sure that you don’t believe in God?
I do not feel what you feel.
But I don’t feel like that all the time.
I doubt sometimes.
Yes, but you believe in God.
How can you know for sure?
No, I do not know.
But should I tell you something awesome?
Did you know that...
Inside the heads of cockroaches there are
nine different amino acids ...
- that are stronger than
any medicine we have today.
-Amino acids?
-Yes? Isn’t that what the fuck they're called?
-Aren't they amino acids?
-Antibiotic molecules.
Wow. Really?
Like okay, okay.
I'm trying to save religion here,
And you’re spending your time dissing me?
You got my point, though? Do you think
that all this is completely random?
Yes or no?
-No.
-No. Exactly.
But if you ever stop believing in god,
- Then you are welcome in my religion.
The big revue party religion.
I don't really know.
Is it okay to marry non-religious people in your religion?
Yes, it's totally chill.
I wish it was chill in my religion too.
Why? Are you going to marry
a non-believing man?
Yes, maybe?
Who?
Stephen Curry.
Wow. Big man.
-We’re going to make a basketball team together.
-What will you call it?
Six children then, maybe?
Yes.
Ok.
When are you leaving tomorrow?
Tomorrow morning.
But I'll be back.
When you're over Stephen Curry.
Ok!