Eva, this is Iben. My girlfriend.
You just made out a bit?
You just follow
what everyone else finds exciting.
Chris hooked up with someone at the party.
I saw it.
- You saw it?
- Yeah, on the stairs.
On the stairs?
I got a pretty unpleasant phone call
from the other girls yesterday.
They're saying that as long as Eva is on our bus,
we are all blacklisted.
I don't understand why you're attacking Eva,
when the other girls are the enemy.
Jonas and Ingrid used to be a couple.
So I think Eva only has herself to
blame for being in this situation.
SHAME
MONDAY, 7:28 A.M.
HI, EVA
WE WANTED TO WISH YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS GOOD LUCK
WITH THE REST OF THE
SCHOOL YEAR, YOU'LL NEED IT
GREETINGS FROM RAD
PS. ON THE BACK THERE'S A
GREETING IN PERIOD BLOOD
WE WANTED TO WISH YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS
GOOD LUCK WITH
THE REST OF THE SCHOOL YEAR,
YOU'LL NEED IT
GREETINGS FROM RAD
PS. ON THE BACK THERE'S
A GREETING IN PERIOD BLOOD
GREETINGS FROM RAD
PS. ON THE BACK THERE'S
A GREETING IN PERIOD BLOOD
Hi.
You were right.
The Rad girls are after the entire bus.
Whatever. I'm not on the bus anymore.
Why not?
Why bother being on a blacklisted bus,
where everyone hates me?
No one hates you, Vilde.
Sana made it pretty clear.
Anyway, I'm back with the Pepsi Max girls.
Oh.
Vilde...
I just... want you to know...
that I'm not the kind of person
who steals other people's boyfriends.
What kind of person are you then?
TUESDAY, 6:32 P.M.
The image I see when I think of Foss
is a dude jamming on his guitar.
When I enter through the front entrance,
I see that majestic staircase.
I strongly recommend this school.
How can you change high school
How can you change high schools?
Is it possible to change high schools?
If it is, how can you do it?
To: Oslo Municipality's Admissions Office
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year.
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year.
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any o
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one th
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that ha
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an av
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an avail
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an availab
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an available
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an available spot
Hi!
I would like to change high schools
in the middle of the school year. Immediately.
From Nissen to some place else. Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.
But any one that has an available spot
SKYPE: Isak calling
Hi.
You weren't at school today.
No.
I think it's...
really unfair that you
get this much hate.
I have decided to change schools.
- Why?
- Because everything is fucked at Nissen.
So because of that
you're just going to change schools?
Yes.
Okay...
Okay, what?
It's just not very typical of you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I didn't know you were a quitter.
What is this bullshit
about what kind of person I am?
Maybe I am a quitter.
I don't know!
How can I know what kind of person I am?
Everyone is like: "What kind of person are you?
You have to know who you are!"
It's a fucking cliché.
Yeah, okay.
Just chill.
I didn't mean it like that.
Sorry.
No, no...
But...
It's actually...
not that complicated, Eva.
You...
You are what you do.
So... if you change schools,
because things are a bit fucked up, then...
you are a quitter.
I'm not five years old.
Do you think that
reverse psychology shit works on me?
I don't know. Does it?
You've got to fight back, girl.
WEDNESDAY, 1:30 P.M.
What is it?
Are you Maria? The bus boss from Rad?
Yes.
- I'm Eva.
- Okay.
I'm that Eva.
Okay.
I just wanted to say that I got your letter.
I know I fucked up,
but I think it's unfair to blacklist
the entire bus. My friends didn't do anything.
It was me. So, take me, not them.
Okay, Eva...
You can tell your friends that
we won't "take" them.
We have way more important stuff to do
than blacklisting first-years.
So...
okay, what's up with the letter then?
We haven't given you any letter.
Someone's fucking with you.
So...
you guys aren't mad
that I hooked up with Chris?
Eva, we don't give a shit
who you've hooked up with.
Even though it's Iben's boyfriend?
Even though it's Iben's boyfriend. Eva, listen.
I'm sure that in your head,
this hook-up
is the most important and dramatic thing
ever in history.
But for us who have been here for a while,
it's just a little footnote.
So I suggest you talk to the ones involved, okay?
Okay.
And relax. Right?
You're supposed to fuck up,
you're in the first year.
You're supposed to hook up a lot.
But don't sleep around.
That's different, ok?
When we were in our first year,
we had a chlamydia epidemic.
- Did anyone find out who started it?
- It was William.
- It wasn't William.
- Weren't you...
- Chris had it too, right?
- Yeah, Chris had it too.
It was one of those guys for sure...
THURSDAY, 1:00 P.M.
- I see where you went wrong.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- It's okay to make mistakes, Sana.
- The answer key is wrong.
The answer key isn't wrong, Sana.
It is wrong!
Because it's not the same as what I got.
Hi!
Hi.
I talked to the Rad girls.
- And... they aren't after us.
- Wow, now I can finally breathe again!
Hey, it's Vilde
who cares about that stuff,
and is peeing her pants
about some blacklist.
Vilde...
- She isn't on our bus anymore.
- Huh?
She said she didn't want to be
on a bus where...
everyone hates her.
Something's wrong.
At the bus meeting,
she was mean, and Vilde isn't a mean person.
What?
It seems like you just defended Vilde?
I'm just saying, something's wrong.
We are her friends.
You guys should care more about her.
Okay...
Guys...
I feel like I owe you guys
an explanation.
About what... Vilde said
about me and Ingrid.
But I don't have one.
- I know I should've done things differently--
- Eva.
- Save that speech for Ingrid.
- Fuck Ingrid!
You don't owe her shit. She was sucking up
to Iben and hooked up with Chris herself.
I'm sure it was her who sent that period letter.
- Wh-What did you say?
- Don't you think it was her? I think so.
Did Ingrid hook up with Chris?
Yes, I told you, at the Halloween party,
she and Chris were making out on the stairs.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I saw it!
And you're telling me this now?!
What? I told you before.
I thought I had already told you.
FRIDAY, 1:40 P.M.
We have to talk.
Unless you want me to tell Iben
that you hooked up with Chris,
I suggest you change your attitude.
I know you don't want to listen to me,
but you have to now.
Whether you want to or not, we'll be going
to the same school for the next three years.
We have to figure out
how to make this work somehow, because...
you can't keep trying to freeze me out,
talking shit, or sending me threat letters.
Just hear me out, okay?
When I moved here... from Bergen...
in the 7th grade...
And...
no one wanted to hang out with me,
because I talked weird.
Then you were the only one who took care of me.
And I...
remember how proud and lucky...
I just couldn't believe that
the most popular girl in our class
wanted to be friends with me.
I have...
always looked up to you like crazy.
You're the...
best friend I've ever had.
And just...
the thought...
that I managed to destroy that...
makes me feel sick.
More than sick.
It made me stop liking myself as a person.
But I can't keep regretting it...
for the rest of my life.
It wasn't going well
between you and Jonas.
You talked about
breaking up with him every day.
And I know that's not an excuse, but...
I loved him.
I wish I could do it all over again,
in a completely different way.
But I can't.
I'm just going to have to accept that.
And move on.
So, I'm saying this for the last time.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I lied to you,
and went behind your back.
I'm sorry that I ruined our friendship.
You didn't deserve it.
I'm not trying to say...
you should like me, or...
or that we should be friends again or something.
I just...
I can't take any more
shit talk or threat letters, okay?
Okay.
No more shit.
But I didn't send any threat letters.
And I barely knew Iben when I
hooked up with Chris at the Halloween party.
Fucking hell!
Seriously? You have serious issues!
What's wrong with you?! You can't just
jump people! Pull yourself together!
You're with the school's largest douche.
He's hitting on everyone,
and your way of coping with that is to
jump people, beat them up, send threat letters?
I have a better suggestion for you.
Break up with your fucking boyfriend.
He's a fucking asshole.
I didn't mean it like that.
No, it's okay.
I know it's true, so...
I just...
I think you deserve better.
Everyone deserves better than that.
I love him.
Maybe he'll change.
It was good that he told you, at least.
What?
That he had cheated.
He didn't tell me.
- He didn't?
- No.
Oh... because someone...
told me that's how you
got to know about it.
That your boyfriend told you.
My boyfriend?
It was your boyfriend who tipped me off.
Yes.
But... my boyfriend didn't know.
He must have known.
He's the one who sent the tip to Nissenhook.
That's how I found out about it.
Huh?
The little blonde guy.
The one you're always with.
Isn't he your boyfriend?
Isakyaki? Isak?
Isn't that what he's called?
Did Isak send the tip?
I thought you knew.