I'm just sorting my salad.
I'm not on the bus anymore.
Anyway, I'm back with the Pepsi Max girls.
Eva, this is Iben. My girlfriend.
You just made out a bit?
Why did you have to cheat
just because you thought I was?
It was your boyfriend who tipped me off.
- But my boyfriend didn't know.
- The little blonde guy. Isakyaki? Isak?
Isn't that what he's called?
SHAME
Hello! This is Isak.
I'm a bit busy at the moment.
SATURDAY, 11:04 A.M.
But you can leave a message after the beep.
BEEP! Kidding, here comes the beep.
Isak, pick up your damn phone now,
because I need to talk to you.
HERE LIVES
Terje and Marianne Valtersen
Isak and Lea
Hi.
Where's Isak?
Isak is a bit upset.
What's happened?
Well, his father left,
and his mother had a breakdown.
Oh. Shit!
Yeah, it's pretty shit.
But...
is he doing okay?
I don't know really.
His mother was already pretty crazy.
Yeah.
Were you picking something up, or?
No... I just wanted to
talk to him about something.
- But he's not answering his phone.
- Yeah, I think he turned it off.
How are you doing?
Good!
Or...
you know.
Yeah, I know.
But...
Say hi to him.
Yeah, but don't you want to come in?
I'm sure he wants to see you.
No... I think...
He has you, so...
Yeah.
Bye.
MONDAY, 12:05 P.M.
Okay, what's the symbolism of porridge?
I'm really struggling here.
"In the barn sits Santa
with his Christmas porridge."
What is the porridge? Porridge is porridge.
- Why did you choose that song?
- Because I thought it was going to be easy.
- You have to hand it in next class.
- I know. And I forgot. That's the way it is.
The porridge symbolises...
- Life?
Fits perfectly. Life.
- Did you do it? Which did you pick?
- Mhm. "Deilig er jorden".
- Isn't that a really Christian song?
- It has a beautiful message.
Fuck! Message! I need to write about that.
What's the message in "På låven sitter nissen"?
Vilde?
Hi!
Hi.
- How's it going with you?
- Really good! And with you?
Good.
Come sit with us.
I would really love to, but me, Sara, Ingrid,
and the Pepsi Max girls are going to the café.
So... maybe next time?
- How's it going with your bus?
- Good.
- Did you find a sponsor yet?
- Not yet.
You just gotta work on it.
Then they'll come running to you soon.
Hi! Are you guys here? Are we...
do you want to eat here?
Because then I'll just go and get my jacket,
and I'll be right back.
What...
what happened just now?
TUESDAY, 10:11 A.M.
Hi.
- Watch out when you go up the stairs.
- Me?! It's you who has to watch out.
Okay...
- How's it going with Isak?
- Yeah, it's going better now.
But he's not at school?
No, he's chilling at home for a bit.
Taking a break.
But you should call him, or text him
or something. He would like that.
Yeah, I'll do that. I just forgot.
- What do you have now?
- I have French.
And you?
Awkward...
Jonas!
What the hell are you doing?!
- What the fuck, you have to back me up!
- You hooked up with his girl.
- If I were him, I would've killed you.
- Calm down.
WEDNESDAY, 12:09 P.M.
Hi!
Hi.
How's it going?
Good. Or...
it's going fine.
- How's it going with you?
- It's going good.
I've.. I've dumped Chris.
- Did you?
- Mhm.
- That's good, Iben!
- Yeah.
Also, I'm having a girl power Christmas party
on Friday.
You have to come.
- Girl power Christmas party?
- Yeah, and no third-year guys are invited.
Okay.
They have too much power at this school.
All the drama is because of them.
Us girls have to start sticking up
for each other.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
So, an all girls party?
No, no. We need guys there. So I thought
we could maybe invite some first-year guys.
- Okay?
- They're the most...
undervalued group at school.
- See you on Friday then, bring your friends.
- Yeah, cool!
If you know any hot first-year guys,
just invite them.
- Yeah, I'll find some.
- Okay, good.
But, I was just wondering...
- Could you maybe ask Vilde if she wants to come?
- Vilde?
Yeah, Vilde Lien. She's a first-year.
Of course, you can just bring her.
But...
I think she'd be very happy
if you invited her.
Yeah, okay! I'll find her on Facebook.
Thanks!
FRIDAY, 7:52 P.M.
I need water!
Have you heard anything from Vilde?
No.
- Eva, Have you heard anything from Vilde?
- No.
- Iben, did you invite Vilde?
- Yeah, she said she would come.
Check out this Snapchat filter.
Yay, even more first-year guys!
- Isak?
- Hi! Eva!
- How's it going with you?
- It's going...
- better.
- Good.
How's it going with your mom now?
Good. Who the hell knows, but...
it's a lot of stress.
- I'm sure she and dad will work it out.
- That's good.
So, you're doing better, then?
I'm doing better now.
- I have some news for you.
- Yeah?
Me and Jonas are back together.
Seriously?
He hasn't said anything yet, but...
that's great!
Yeah, I know.
He hasn't...
he has forgiven you and everything?
Yes!
That's great!
So... I just wanted to say...
thank you so much for being there for me.
I don't know what I would've done this autumn,
if it hadn't been for you.
I don't have a lot of...
people in my life
that I feel I can trust. But...
you're one of them. So, thanks.
I'm just...
glad that you guys worked it out.
Yeah. I'm glad you're
cheering for me and Jonas.
Team Jonas!
There's just...
one thing I was wondering.
Mhm?
When you outed me on @nissenhook
that me and Chris had hooked up,
where you cheering for us then?
Because... our relationship
went to hell after that!
Or, my whole life went to hell after that!
So you have to tell me what you were thinking.
Because I think it's completely psycho!
Why did you do it?!
What were you thinking?
You really don't know why?
No, I really don't know why!
Think about it.
What? Do you have...
Do you have like...
feelings for me?
As if you didn't know?
- No... I... I didn't know.
- Well...
So it's not that damn fun for me
when I have to sit and listen to you...
talking about Jonas, and me having to be
your fucking counselor.
It's not that damn fun for me.
I'm sitting there like a damn idiot,
hoping that one day you'll understand...
that he's not good enough for you.
Isak, I... I didn't know.
Honestly, Eva.
How could you not understand?
But anyway, that's not an excuse
for what you did.
- You outed me to the whole school!
- It was stupid. I fucked up.
I was drunk and...
I... was also... pretty mad... at you.
Because I was thinking you were using me.
I also didn't know Chris had
such a psycho girlfriend,
who would make a lot of drama.
- Then of course I wouldn't have done it.
- Eva, come.
Now!
Eva.
Don't...
you can't tell Jonas anything about this, okay?
- Call an ambulance!
- Let's call an ambulance.
- Vilde!
- What happened?!
She came in, started staggering,
and then she tripped. She's not responding.
- Is your mom home?
- No, no!
I think I killed William's baby tonight.