I can have Norwegian friends
and still be myself.
We are looking for someone
who wants to buy our bus.
There is only one other bus
that's coming to take a look.
The Pepsi Max Squad.
I feel like we are more like you, guys.
Cool, normal, Norwegian party girls.
We will get that bus.
We don't have the money!
I'll fix it!
Who is that?
SATURDAY
11:31
What’s that, bro? What are you doing?
Throw it to me! Throw it to me!
Hello.
Hi, love.
Where is dad?
At La Mocca.
Let’s play with the ball.
Play it with your feet.
There were a lot of people asking
for you at Friday's prayer.
Oh, yeah. I was supposed to
go, but I couldn’t make it.
No. But it’s been a while.
It’s not been that long.
Why do you never say that to Elias?
He is never at Friday's prayer.
No, right... Elias is just as
lightheaded as your father.
While the two of us, we are
a little more focused.
Don’t you agree?
I’ll be there next Friday.
We are going to Mahmoud’s
wedding next Friday.
Do you want to come?
No, thank you. I think I will pass.
So, what did you do yesterday?
Yesterday?
Mhmm
I just hung out with Noora
and Eva and all them.
But, do you need any help cooking?
You want to help me cook?
No. Not really.
“No, not really?”
Honestly, what are you going
to do when you get married?
Are you going to let your children starve?
No. My husband is going to cook.
Your husband is going to cook?
Huh. Inshallah.
Hello? Hi.
Hi.
Hi!
I’m just getting something to drink.
Do you need any help?
Huh? No.
Listen.
I don’t want to be rude but...
you are doing it all wrong.
Like, completely, completely wrong.
Oh, yeah?
Should I show you?
Okay.
You need to drag it towards
yourself, not push it away.
Okay?
Otherwise you will make a mess
and you won’t have any
control over the carrot.
Pull it towards yourself.
Then you turn it over
and do the other side.
Wow.
How did you get so good at peeling carrots?
I work in a kindergarten.
So I peel a lot of things for the kids.
Do you work in a kindergarten?
Yes.
So, do you like kids then?
Yes, of course!
Don’t you?
How can you not like kids?
I like kids...
Well, how many do you want?
Two, maybe?
Two?! Two kids!
Okay, two kids.
Then you don’t really like kids.
How many are you going to have then?
Twelve!
Twelve kids?!
Yeah.
I am thinking long term.
I will make a football team with them.
There are eleven people on a football team.
- Are there eleven people on a team?
- Yeah.
Or are there eleven people
on the field, maybe?
What if someone gets hurt?
Exactly.
Yeah.
Exactly. You hadn’t thought about that!
Do you want to try?
There.
Don’t keep peeling outwards!
You need to peel it inwards.
Drag it towards you! Try!
Use you thumb. Use your thumb.
My thumb?
Yes, use your thumb.
And drag, yeah, just like that.
Fine.
Easier?
Much better now.
What’s happening here?
I’m drinking some juice.
Weren’t you going to get
a drink and come back?
Yeah, but your sister doesn’t
know how to peel carrots.
You haven’t taught her properly, man!
- I don’t care about cooking.
- But Elias...
No. The boys are waiting. Stop
flirting with my sister, man.
Flirting, dude? I’m fixing
the food for tonight.
Come on. Let’s get out of here.
VILDE: MARI CALLED, WE GOT
THE BUS FOR 300,000!!!!!
NOORA: CALL AND SAY WE DON’T WANT IT.
VILDE: SANA SAID SHE WILL
FIX IT, SO SHE WILL FIX IT.
DON’T YOU REMEMBER THE
PAPER ROLLS LAST YEAR?
SHE FIXES EVERYTHING! SANA
IS THE BOSS. RIGHT, SANA?
MONDAY
12:11
300.000 KRONE. APPLY ON
FINANCIALAID.NO TODAY
LENDER’S APPLICATION IS FREE
YOUSEF - I’M HURT BECAUSE YOU
NEVER REPLIED TO MY MEME
THE KIDS AROUND YOU ARE HURT BECAUSE
YOU ARE CHATTING DURING WORK TIME
HAH! I’M FREE ON MONDAYS. YOU
THOUGHT YOU WERE SMART NOW.
HOW IS THE RUSS BUSS?
IT’S GOING GREAT IF YOU TELL ME
HOW TO EARN 300,000 KRONE FAST.
Hi!
We heard you got the bus.
Congratulations!
Thanks.
So we were wondering...
Would you want to join us?
We just thought that you
are 5 and we are 20.
There are 25 seats on the bus.
Perhaps it could be a match?
We know that maybe we haven’t
been the world’s best friends,
but we don’t really understand why.
Because you called Vilde a slut at
Borkis’ bus pre-grame in October 2015.
Right.
I had completely forgotten about that.
But I apologize.
We’ll merge our buses...
on two conditions.
Okay?
You pay for the bus and
I become the bus boss.
We have to discuss that
with the other girls...
Either we make the deal now
or there won’t be a bus.
Yeah.
Okay.
We are in.
Good!
Send me the name of everyone on the bus
and I will invite you to a bus meeting.
Okay?
What did they want?
Have you talked with them?
I have news. Where is Chris?
She is in Berlin. What’s up?
We have merged with the Pepsi-Max.
Are you joking?
What does that mean?
They spend money on the bus
and I become the bus boss.
Why are you the bus boss?
Would we get along with the Pepsi Max?
Either we join with Pepsi Max group
or there won’t be a bus.
So we have a bus meeting this week.
Eva, can you host?
I can’t host again. Like, ever!
Noora, kollektivet?
Those girls are not going
into my apartment.
Vilde?
No, my mom...
Your mom is not having a
wine tasting party, Vilde.
Why can’t you host for once?
TUESDAY
19:05
HOW TO SUCCEED WITH A GOOD
NAME AND RUSS BUS CONCEPT
THE IDEA BEHIND THE NAME
MAKES A LOT ABOUT PROMOTION
BUS MEETING. COVER NAME. LOTS OF PROMO
MIX MYSTERIOUS WITH HUMOR
MAIN CONCEPT AND NAME
MUST BE CONNECTED
YOUSEF: DID YOU GET THE 300,000?
EASY
YOUSEF: ARE YOU JOKING?!?!?!?
Hi!
Hello!
Gone to bed already?
No.
Do you need that cup or
are you done with it?
I’m done.
Listen, Mom?
Yes?
I was wondering if I could invite
some girls to come over on Friday?
Yes.
Yes, is that fine?
It is.
How many are you?
Or are you not that many?
Not that many.
No?
What are you going to do?
Mhmmmm
I ask too much. Don’t I?
I do, right?
No.
But that doesn’t mean
that I don’t trust you.
I do.
I just miss talking with you.
You used to tell me all your secrets.
Do you remember that?
Do you want to hear a secret now?
Yes.
There is a boy I like.
Muslim?
Yes.
Tell me more.
He is funny and smart.
Good looking?
Yes, really handsome.
And I even think he can cook.
Perfect for you!
Yeah!
Do you think I can meet him?
I don’t think we are there quite yet.
I have only talked to him a little.
And...
I don’t even know if he likes me.
If he likes you?!
Of course he likes you!
Who doesn’t like you?
Do you think so?
Yes, I do.
I hope so.
THURSDAY
10:04
BITCH!!!
MOM: ARE YOU GOING TO
SERVE ANYTHING ON FRIDAY?
DAD AND I WILL GET HOME LATE BUT
I CAN MAKE SOMETHING TO HEAT UP?
SARA: IS IT OKAY ALCOHOL FOR THE BUS MEETING?
Hello.
Hi!
Everything good?
Yeah!
I heard you talked to
Isak about Mikael.
Oh, yeah! He saw a picture
of Mikael on my Facebook.
Okay?
We didn’t talk about him or anything.
How are the boys doing?
Good.
What’s Elias doing these days?
Elias? He is taking a gap year.
Messing around, as usual.
Living off mom and dad.
You have to say hi to your mom and
tell her I miss her shebbakiyya.
I will.
Hello.
Hi!
I was just asking Sana where you were.
Yeah, I am here.
Are you joining Jonas and I for McDonald’s?
Of course!
Lovely. Are you joining?
No, thank you.
Okay. Should we go now?
Yes.
Good bye!
Bye! Talk to you later.
FRIDAY
19:43
That’s why I think we
should be very ambitious
and a clear goal should be to win
at least one of the bus prizes
at Tryvann in May 2018.
Yes?
It’s pretty easy to say that you want to
win prizes, everyone wants to do that.
Now that you are the buss boss. Do
you have a plan on how to do that?
To start, I have had a look at your
budget and it needs to be redistributed.
For example...
there is not point in trying to compete
in lighting and sound rigging,
because then we are going to lose.
But what we can be
competitive in, is concept.
So the first thing I am going to do is to
move our resources from the
light and sound section
to the concept section.
I am sorry, but it is very hard
to win year’s best concept.
Yeah.
But if you do an analysis of the buses
that have won in the past three years,
you will see some obvious
things on common aspects.
The League 2014, a boy’s bus from Bærum with
a Pokeball bar and Pokémon decorations.
Montana 2015, a boy’s bus from Oslo-West
that put together three
versions of Montana.
Tony Montana, Hannah Montana
and the state of Montana.
Also we have Landslaget 2016,
inspired by football
spirit and nationalism.
Do you see what those
buses have in common?
All the concepts suck and we can do better.
To start, I will call all the
bus bosses for a meeting
where we plan what we are going
to do for the next six months
with some clear goals.
Any more questions?
Yes?
Well, so...
the Russ period is all about
partying and drinking,
and I have to ask, since you are muslim.
What do you think about drinking?
I judge no one.
So, can we drink?
When were your parents
coming back home?
Tomorrow morning...
I think.
They are at a Moroccan wedding.
It’s good to know.
ARE YOU HAVING A NICE
TIME AT THE WEDDING?
Sana?!?!
What’s happening here?
You know mum and dad are here?
Huh?!
They are down with the
neighbours, by the car.
DAD DIDN’T FEEL WELL, SO
WE ARE COMING HOME NOW.
DO YOU STILL HAVE GUESTS?
Okay. Everyone has to get out now!!!
Come on!!! Are you deaf or what?
Now!
Out, out, out! Come on, out!
Get out! Come here!
Close the door. Get
that bottle over there!
Which key?
Hi!
Hello. All good?
Yes. We are good.
We ran into Mikael and Adam outside.
Yeah, we were about to meet them.
Fine.
Where is Sana?
In the living room.
Hello!
Hi! Did you have a nice time?
Yeah!
It was fine.
What’s this?
That’s...
Vodka?
Vodka? Whose is it?
It’s not yours?
- No...
- Whose?!
It’s mine. Or, it’s not mine but...
Do you drink, Yousef?
No. I bought it for a friend.
You bought it for a friend?
Yes.
And then we find it here?
You know we don’t have that
kind of things in this house.
Yes, I am sorry. I...
THANKS
NO WORRIES
I WILL FIND A WAY TO CONVINCE
MOM YOU ARE A GOOD MUSLIM
EVEN THOUGH YOU DRINK VODKA
HAHAHA. THAT’S OKAY,
I AM NOT A MUSLIM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON’T BELIEVE IN ALLAH
@Ledgerina