He's the hottest guy in all of third-year.
I think we're going to sleep together.
I like it.
I think it's kinda hot.
Hey, don't be such a dick tease!
- Ingrid... I miss you.
- You look like a slut.
I'm not talking to Ingrid behind your back!
- Where the hell are you?
- Sorry, but I can't come tonight.
- Who was that?
- That was my sister.
- Jonas!
- I'm sorry, but I really have to go now. Sorry.
SHAME
SUNDAY, 2:42 P.M.
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Sad?
- No!
- I bought you a coffee.
- Thanks!
What are we talking about?
Nothing.
I just thought it'd be nice with coffee.
What did you do on the weekend?
Nothing.
What did you do on Friday?
- Mom had her birthday.
- So you just stayed home?
- Yes! Did something happen last Friday?
- No, I was just wondering what you did.
I think that maybe...
- Jonas was with Ingrid.
- Oh.
- Do you know anything about it?
- No. Why do you think he was?
I was talking to him on the phone,
and heard her voice in the background.
- Did you tell him?
- Yeah, but he said it's his sister.
- Maybe it was.
- Hey! I think I know Ingrid's voice.
- We were best friends for four years.
- Yeah.
But... tell him that, then? Push him a bit.
I have told him, but he got really pissed
and said I have to trust him.
Eva...
why are you together with him?
What do you mean?
Jonas is my bro, but...
I don't get why
you're together with someone...
you don't trust.
So...
you think I should trust him, then?
Or, you could go for option three.
You could ask Ingrid.
MONDAY, 2:15 P.M.
I'm going to see William soon again, and...
I think we have something going on,
it's just that... there's a big age difference.
I really think there could be
something between us.
He said he thinks I'm really special.
And I'm ready for it, even though...
Did I tell you I got an orgasm?
Smile then
Okay. What was it like?
You smile
It was a bit like a sneeze. Just down there.
- Like sneezing?
- Mhm.
I am smiling
And... I think I know
why everyone got an orgasm with him.
You're pissed
- Yeah, why is that?
- Because he was really big.
You can't go around talking about his dick size.
Why not?
Hello!?!!
You're asking me why you can't go around telling
people about his most vulnerable body part?
First of all,
that body part wasn't exactly vulnerable.
And secondly, I'm pretty sure
he'll talk about my body with his friends.
hello
Since guys do it, I think girls can do it too.
Sorry for being for equality and feminism.
But Vilde, first of all,
size doesn't have anything to do with orgasm.
And secondly, just because guys are idiots,
it doesn't mean we have to be as well.
It's got nothing to do with equality at all.
Okay, text me
when you're not pissed
Whatever...
But, it was good, then?
That's the important part.
It was really good.
But...
there's just one thing.
No one tells you that...
it actually runs out of you again.
Didn't you use a condom?
- No, he said he tends not to use one.
- Vilde...
What the hell is that?
- Where did you get those?
- Sana knows someone.
Someone will pick up the toilet paper tonight.
- But I need payment first.
- That's not how it works.
He needs the toilet paper
to get paid by his people,
and then he pays you,
so you can pay your people.
But I don't have "people".
Do you think MasterCard
operates without people?
Hey.
- Hi!
- Hey.
You coming to the Halloween party on Friday?
- Yeah, maybe.
- We're coming!
Good. Talk to you later.
Bye!
TUESDAY, 3:30 P.M.
You smell like smoke.
What's up, Eva?
I can't take this...
I think there's something
between you and Ingrid.
Really?
That's still what you're thinking?
What do you want me to think?
I know I heard her voice on the phone!
For the last time,
it was my sister in the background!
- What did your sister want with me?
- Because she thought it was my mom!
Wasn't your mom at home?
Jonas!
You said you couldn't come to me, because you
had to help your mom with something at home.
- But your mom wasn't even home?
- No, she came home later. That's why she called.
- You're lying! Why are you lying to me?
- I'm not lying!
I can't do this.
Can't do this?
What do you mean you can't do this?
Do you want to take a break or something?
- That's what you want.
- No, that's not what I want!
Stop being so insecure all the time!
What's up with you? Can't you just listen to me?
WEDNESDAY, 2:30 P.M.
...I got a glass of water and...
he's the kind of guy who sees others--
What about alcohol
for the Halloween party?
I texted William and asked
if he could get us some.
Could he?
He didn't reply yet, he's really, really busy.
He's in the third year, and he's the bus boss.
He has so much to think about,
I'd be really stressed if I were him.
So we haven't really talked since last.
But... we do keep in touch through Snapchat.
You know what I did yesterday?
No.
I sent William a topless picture.
- You did what?
- They're just boobs.
William likes confident girls.
What did he reply?
He didn't reply directly,
but he took a screenshot.
Listen up... Einstein.
William isn't interested.
- He could very well be.
- He didn't even reply to a topless picture.
There's a book called "The Game",
it says that "not replying is a strategy guys use
to get girls interested".
If I were you, I would put down "The Game",
and start reading "He's Just Not That Into You".
Why are you always so mean?
Hello?!
We are her friends. If not even we
can tell her the truth, who will?
She's sending topless pictures to a guy who is
lying about liking her, just to sleep with her.
- That's what's mean!
- You don't know if he's lying!
But you agree he doesn't seem like
the most trustworthy guy?
I mean, you can't just claim
that people are lying, without having proof.
- Sometimes you have to trust people.
- You know when guys are lying.
- And how do you "know" that?
- Their stories are inconsistent.
When you ask too many questions, they get mad.
Afterwards, they get a bad conscience...
and start drowning you in compliments.
Believe me,
just wait and see.
William will break her heart.
FRIDAY, 8:30 P.M.
You know you're
the coolest, best, hottest,
funniest, prettiest girl
in the whole world, right?
I love you <3 <3 <3
- Were you with Jonas last Friday?
- Hi, Eva!
Just answer me.
Last Friday?
Yes! Yes, I was with Jonas.
Oh. Didn't he tell you?
- Oops...
- Fuck you!
No, fuck you Eva. Fuck you!
I talked to Ingrid
and she told me
and she told me EVERYTHING!
I talked to Ingrid
You're sitting here?
I'm sitting here.
- Look's like someone is trying to reach you.
- Yeah.
- Who is Jonas?
- My boyfriend. Or, well...
- You don't know if he's your boyfriend, or?
- He is my boyfriend, it's just that...
We had a fight, so...
Hey, you...
Fuck him.
If he can make such a nice girl cry, fuck him.
I can't do this.
There you are.
What are you guys doing?
I was comforting Eva,
who had a fight with her guy.
Have you met Eva?
Eva, this is Iben.
My girlfriend.
I don't know why I'm the one talking to you,
Iben's really good with boyfriend troubles.
She had a fight with her boyfriend,
and is a bit down.
Oh, poor you.
I'll give you two some time.
I'm fine, really. You don't need to--
Believe me, I know what it's like.
You're a first-year, right? That's when everyone
tries to figure out who they are.
And that leads to people changing a lot.
People you thought you knew,
might not be the way you thought they were.
The same goes for boyfriends.
I had a boyfriend in the first year,
who was a complete douchebag.
He cheated on me like five times
without me knowing about it.
Oh.
But...
it gets better as you get older.
Like with me and Christoffer, it's going really
well, because third-year guys are more mature.
We can talk about everything,
and I trust him 110%.
You'll get like a more adult relationship,
if you know what I mean.
Are you also in the third year?
No, second. But there's so much that happens
between your first and second year.
My advice is to
not take relationships so seriously.
Think of it as something temporary.
Don't let him stand in your way.
Hey, it's Halloween!
There's a really cool party here.
And you're sitting here,
like a sad ballerina.
You agree, right?
Come on,
let's go out there and have a great time!
Thanks, you're really kind, but...
But I don't feel too good,
so, I think I'll just go home.
Are you sure?
Really sure?
It'll get better.
FRIDAY, 9:42 P.M.
Black Swan?
I can't handle us breaking up.
The thing is that Ingrid's brother is dealing.
Dealing what?
Weed.
Have you started smoking marijuana?
Why?
There's a reason I didn't tell you.
You're reacting as if it was heroin.
Marijuana is a drug.
- So you think it's as dangerous as heroin?
- Yes!
That's why I was at Ingrid's brother's
last Friday. To buy some.
And then Ingrid showed up. But she lives there,
so I couldn't say anything to you.
- Why didn't you say anything to me?
- Really? Did you see your reaction just now?
Anyway.
My point is that there's nothing
between me and Ingrid.
And there never will be anything, either.
And I... it was really dumb of me to lie.
But that you thought there was...
That really hurt me. It hurts.
Because, I trust you 100%.
You have to start trusting me.
Because I would never do anything...
I would never do anything to ruin things for us.
Because it is the two of us.
Right?
Don't cry.