I heard William has a new
girlfriend in London.
Should I say something to Noora?
Of course you have to say something!
I just don’t understand the thing between
William and Noora. Are they together?
What’s up? What are you talking about?
The best thing would be to find a
new boy so Noora can fall for.
I can have Norwegian Friends and
be myself at the same time.
(VILDE) YESTERDAY WAS AWESOME!!
(VILDE) HELLO NOORA AND YOUSEF!
(VILDE) AREN’T WE GOOD FRIENDS?
(EVA) REALLY GOOD. DID THEY HOOK UP?
(VILDE) DON’T THINK SO, BUT IT
LOOKS LIKE NOORA LIKED HIM.
(EVA) HE WAS REALLY HOT, THOUGH.
SANA, DO YOU KNOW IF HE’S SINGLE?
Shit!
I am sorry. I didn’t know you were home.
Hello.
Didn’t you go with dad and auntie?
I’m trying to pray, turn the volume down.
Chill.
How was yesterday? How were you?
Your friends were hot.
Why didn’t you tell me
you are on a Russ bus?
There’s a lot I haven’t told you, Elias.
But have you told our mom?
She doesn’t care.
You know she cares, right?
You were on a Russ bus yourself!
Yeah, but that’s because I’m a boy!
And?
You know what people think?
I just don’t want people to hate you.
I’m a boy so I don’t get hate.
I’m just chilling.
Thanks for the advice, Elias.
Chill!
Listen!
Say hi to Noora from me!
- No, chill!
- But she is hot though.
TUESDAY
13:55
Wasn’t it nice this weekend?
- At the party?
- Yeah.
- I thought it was really nice.
- Yes.
There were a lot of nice, new people.
Yeah. You liked them?
Yes! Like that guy, Yousef.
Do you know him well?
Yousef?
Yeah, your brother’s friend.
No, not that well.
Well, he was very charming.
Sure, if you think immaturity is charming.
I thought he seemed quite mature?
Trust me, you don’t want a Muslim boy.
Why not?
Because... just trust me, they...
They got together with Norwegian girls
just to take advantage of them.
And as soon as they want to get serious,
When they really want...
a proper woman in their life
they marry a Muslim girl and ditch you.
Don’t you think that’s generalizing a bit?
It’s not generalizing.
Muslims can only marry other Muslims.
It says so in the Quran.
Anyway, why are we talking about Yousef?
Aren’t you with William?
What...?
What is going on between you two?
Do you know...?
You know why I came back from London?
Because he worked all the time?
Wasn’t that it?
But...
That’s not really the whole truth.
Okay...
Hi!
I was just wondering, aren’t you on a bus?
Yes! It’s a russe bus, yes.
We are looking for someone to buy our bus.
We finish in May.
so we thought we would check with you.
How much do you want for it?
Yeah, Sana is on our bus.
Yeah, ż300.000?
What’s this?
We are selling our bus.
You are? That’s something we
are very, very interested in!
Yeah?
300.000?
That’s what a bus costs...
When can we come by and take a look?
Sometime this week?
- I can text you.
- Yes!
- Bye!
Hello?!
We can’t start buying buses for 300.000!
We are five people!
That’s what a bus costs.
All the buses are being sold now.
If we want to try buying a bus in
May 2018, it’s not going to work.
We have to buy a bus now
or there won’t be a bus!
I can join the bus if you need people.
I agree with Vilde.
But we don’t have 300.000 kroner!
It’s not like they need the money tomorrow.
We’ll sort it out.
How are we supposed to sort that out?
You know what, Noora?
You should read a book that
I’m currently reading.
It’s called “The Secret”.
And it’s about how if you
let the universe do it,
then everything will manifest
itself in your life.
You just have to be receptive.
You know so much about the universe.
How?
I am very interested in the universe.
Like planets and stuff.
And stars!
The stars are shining!
You are my star. You know that?
I’m yours?
You are mine! You are my sun!
The sun is a star.
WEDNESDAY
12:24
Was that a smile?
Hello!
Hi.
When do you finish today?
15:30?
But I have to stay late.
I have a chemistry test.
- Can’t you just study at home?
- I can’t study at home.
HI! WE CAN COME LOOK MARI’S
BUS ON FRIDAY AT 15:00
MOST OF THE BUSES HAVE ALREADY BEEN SOLD
SO THIS IS OUR ONLY CHANCE!
THIS IS WHAT WE HAVE DREAMT OF!
GOOD!
Why not? Am I distracting?
I can’t study at home when you are there!
When you look at me...
I promise not to look at you.
FACEBOOK: YOUSEF ACAR HAS
SENT YOU A FRIEND REQUEST
What’s the point then, Even?
Of studying at home if you
are not looking at me?
That’s true.
- So, is that how it’s going to be?
- What is?
That you are just going
to be out working and
I’ll be home waiting for
you and cooking dinner?
It’s not weird that I’m working!
I’m thinking of our future.
One of us has to...
make an income.
An income?
Yeah, but it doesn’t mean that if you
go to school you’ll get a good job.
THOUGHT OF YOU WHEN I SAW THIS.
FUCK HATERS, YOU GO GIRL
What’s the logic behind that?
All the richest people in the
world dropped out of school.
That’s like one person! Like Al Gore!
Three! Three!
All the people who drop
out school are like:
“You know, Al Gore, he didn’t go
to school and he became rich,
so I’m just not going to go to school
and then I’ll be just like Al Gore.”
Bill Gates? Steve Jobs?
Yeah, Bill Gates and Al Gore...
Who is that?
No one.
Isn’t that one guy called
Mikael or something?
Mikael...
How do you know them?
If everyone can be quiet,
we’ll start the lesson.
FRIDAY
15:32
I’m sorry we are late!
It’s really rude to come late now!
Aren’t we just looking at a bus?!
It’s not exactly a fucking job interview.
No, but we still have to present
ourselves at dependable
so they can trust that we’ll pay.
But they can’t trust us...
Because we don’t have the money.
No one says anything about
us not having any money.
Sana and I will take care of talking
and you guys can stick to the background.
I think I’ll do the talking.
I can contribute!
You can contribute a little.
Yes.
I don’t know. Doesn’t your dad
know about that kind of stuff?
Can’t we just ask him?
Hello!
Hi!
What an incredibly cool bus!
Yeah? I think it will be good.
But we are a bit behind. It’s a mess inside
but you can take a look.
Yes!
Holy fuck, it’s amazing! Oh my God.
Is it EU-approved?
Yes. And all yearly feed have been paid.
Does it have any economic liens?
No.
Are there a lot of people
coming to look at the bus?
Well, we haven’t put it up anywhere
because it’s important to us that
we like whoever takes over the bus.
So we just have another bus coming to look.
Okay. Who?
The Pepsi-Max squad.
Hi!
Are you here too?
So this is the bus? It’s really cool!
Yeah, it’s not quite done yet.
We are a bit behind schedule.
Wasn’t it One Oak that had it last year?
Yes and Vogue in 2015.
As I was telling the other girls,
it’s important to us that
we keep up the tradition,
that cool girls take over the bus after us.
I get that. There are so many weird
concepts and buses out there.
Yeah!
But...
now I’m not trying to sell my way in
but I feel like we are kind of like you.
Like we are cool, normal,
Norwegian party girls.
And you have such an awesome name...
The Pepsi-Max squad!
That’s no tour name anymore.
How many seats are there?
Twenty-five.
Enough room then.
How many are you?
Five.
We are twenty.
Yeah?
Well, as I was saying
the bus is EU-approved.
All the paperwork is taken care of
and the yearly fees have been paid.
Any questions?
Yes, was it 310,000 what
you wanted for the bus?
300.000.
Because we have a Budget for 310.000, so...
We will pay 320.000.
Okay.
Well, then, are you both interested?
Yes.
Great!
We want to make a decision pretty soon
so when do you think you could pay?
Straight away!
Cool.
Well, if you don’t have
anymore questions...
Bye!
Hello? What the fuck just happened?
We will get that bus!
We don’t have that money!
I’ll fix it.