- Did something happen last Friday?
- I think that maybe... Jonas was with Ingrid.
- You're lying! Why are you lying to me?
- I'm not lying!
Were you with Jonas last Friday?
Just answer me.
Last Friday?
Yes! Yes, I was with Jonas.
Eva, this is Iben. My girlfriend.
I'm going to see William soon again. I really
think there could be something between us.
The thing is that Ingrid's brother is dealing.
I trust you 100%.
SHAME
MONDAY, 11:32 A.M.
First there's Lord of Ringnes,
instead of Lord of the Rings.
Then we have the Lion Kink,
because you could have sex in the woods...
But I'm not going to do that!
Or, instead of the Hunger Games,
we'll say the Thirst Games.
The Thirst Games! Because we drink.
And we don't drink Pepsi Max,
to put it like that.
No, we're doing Smirnoff Light here.
Did you know Diet Coke won
in that Pepsi Max versus Coke test?
So Pepsi Max
really isn't that great. It's not!
No!
What are you doing on your plate, Vilde?
- I'm just sorting my salad.
- I don't think you can sort it more than that.
When are we going to talk about what
happened at the Halloween party? That...
- William and Sara hooked up.
- What about it?
Were you upset?
No, dear God. It was a hook-up party.
Everyone hooked up with each other.
Not just William and Sara.
Penetrator Henrik
hooked up with Frida from 1STE.
Felix and Malin in 2NBH did it.
Borkis hooked up with Elise from 1STB.
And... Chris hooked up with someone.
And then there's William and Sara.
- Chris, who did you hook up with?
- No, not her. Penetrator Chris.
Oh!
Who... who did he hook up with?
I don't know.
I just heard he hooked up with someone.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What's up?
- What are you doing today?
- I don't know, I thought I'd go skate.
- Can I come? And watch?
- Yeah... watch? When did you get into that?
I feel like being with you.
But I have to go now. We'll talk later.
- Love you!
- Yeah, you too.
Question.
Is that Isak guy available?
Yeah. Why?
No, I felt some "electric chemistry"
going on there.
Some really hot vibes between us.
Seriously.
MONDAY, 2:40 P.M.
I see it's going better
between you and Jonas.
Yep!
You...
you don't want to say why?
No, we just... talked some stuff out.
- I fucked up badly.
- What?
What did you do?
Isak...
If I tell you this, you have to promise
not to say anything to Jonas.
Okay, I promise.
Seriously.
You could ruin our relationship if you do.
I'm not going to tell anyone, okay?
You can trust me.
What did you do?
You know...
how I thought there was something
between Ingrid and Jonas?
So I asked Ingrid if they had been together.
And they had been.
- Seriously?
- But there was a reason for it.
It's just that...
Ingrid didn't tell me that.
So I got really pissed.
And sad, so...
So...
I...
I hooked up with Chris.
You hooked up with Chris?!
- The girl who keeps eye-fucking me?
- No, no!
Chris from the third year. Christoffer.
- So you hooked up with a third-year?
- Yes! Fuck! I'm the worst...
But...
you just made out a bit, right?
Nothing more happened?
No, no.
It would have...
it would have been worse
if it wasn't just hooking up.
If it had meant something to you.
But it didn't...
you were just angry.
Yeah...
It just feels shitty not telling Jonas.
Honestly, Eva...
If I had a girlfriend, who had hooked up with
someone else,
then I wouldn't want to know.
Things like that fuck up relationships.
You don't have to tell him,
because it didn't mean anything.
No...
Besides, you seem more in love with him now
than before. Maybe it was a good thing?
So...
It was just a little hook-up, right?
It'll be fine...
but make sure no one finds out, right?
That no one else will tell.
Especially not that Chris
you hooked up with, right?
It'll be fine.
Thanks.
For what?
You're a good guy.
TUESDAY, 1:40 P.M.
- Vilde!
- Hi!
Hey...
I have to ask you something.
Yesterday you said Chris hooked up with someone
at the Halloween party.
What do you know about it? Just asking.
No, I just heard he hooked up with someone.
Okay... who said that?
- Or was it Robin who hooked up with someone?
- Robin?
Yeah, now that I think about it, it was Robin.
Chris has a girlfriend.
Yeah, okay.
- Do you like him?
- Huh? No, no!
It would be so perfect if I got together
with William, and you with Chris.
Vilde, seriously?!
It was just a suggestion, if she felt like it...
You can't walk around in that sweater,
thinking you'll be together with William.
Come here.
You see that girl over there?
She has slept with William.
See her over there?
She's also slept with William.
And there's one.
And there.
And one up there.
You can't know
if all those girls slept with William!
- There's a lot of guys on their bus.
- Vilde, it's marked on your sweater.
The one you've slept with
is marked in red, get it?
You're just walking around
like some living trophy now.
You have to forget William!
Give him back the sweater,
and take back your integrity!
Hey...
he's the loser, not you.
I know you're supposed to think that
if a guy doesn't like you,
something's wrong with him, not you.
But how do you think like that?
I always think that
there's something wrong with me.
WEDNESDAY, 6:40 P.M.
Hello?
- Hi.
- Hey.
To Chris Penetrator:
Sorry, low battery,
didn't mean to hang up,
call you afterwards.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean by that?
Hi.
- Hey.
- You good?
Yeah, I'm fine. What about you?
Good. I was reading.
Yeah, what?
Elle.
Are you going to get that, or?
Yeah!
- Hallo?
- You're such a damn stalker!
Hi, mom! I can't talk right now.
I've got someone visiting.
"Mom"?! What kind of sick game are you playing?
- I'll call you afterwards, okay?
- "Okay, my girl! We'll talk later. Kiss, kiss!"
- Okay, bye!
- Hey, wait, one more thing.
- "Have you done your homework?"
- Bye!
- Was that your mom?
- Yeah!
"Someone visiting"?
It's REALLY important
that you shut up about
what happened on
Halloween, ok?
Have you still not told her we're together?
You had the chance to meet my mom,
but you'd rather smoke marijuana
with Ingrid's brother.
So, look who's talking.
- What?
- It's so cute that you call it "marijuana".
I'll keep my mouth shut.
No worries.
What's cute about that,
isn't that what it's called?
Yeah...
- But...
- But?
Only old people call it that.
- Old people?! I'm a bit older than you.
- Yeah...
- A bit smarter.
- No...
- What do you call drugs?
- "Drugs"...
I don't know. We just call it weed or something.
But it's the same...
- Yes.
- ...and it's not good for you.
See, you're really distant now.
Hello? Can you see me?
See how distant I am, can't see you!
I'm a junkie... yeah, then you're an alcoholic,
because you've tried alcohol.
You can't compare those!
- You'd need to drink a lot!
- That's what you're saying!
- Fine, I'm a junkie for trying it a few times.
- A few times?!
- How many times has it really been?
- I don't know.
- Are you awake all night?
- No.
- Can't you stop for my sake?
- Sure, I can do anything for your sake.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But...
THURSDAY, 1:20 P.M.
You can't buy pink Uggs!
- Of course I can!
- Uggs in general.
- Why not?
- They're super comfortable, though.
- They're slippers!
- They look insanely ugly.
I've decided on what I'm
going to say to William.
Say?
- What are you talking about?
- My integrity.
You don't have any. Next subject.
- What are you going to say?
- I'll say that I won't be treated like this.
- Huh?!
- And then, I'll return the sweater.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
We're finally in with the Penetrator guys,
and now you're going to fuck everything up?
Says you, who ruined it for all of us the
first time we were invited to a bus pre-party.
There was a good reason.
Sana, it's good that Vilde will explain to
William that she will not be treated like crap.
She can't tell him! It won't work.
It's better to be completely cool.
It's possible to be cool and speak up.
There he is.
- You're not going to say it now?!
- I am.
- Not now, he's with his friends.
- I don't give a shit who he's with!
- Hi!
- Hi?
I just wanted to say that if you thought
I would walk around like some living trophy,
you're terribly wrong.
Don't play dumb! You know what I mean,
half the girls are walking around--
Sorry, what's your name again?
Vilde.
Okay, Vilde. Take a deep breath.
I think there's been some kind
of misunderstanding here.
It's probably my fault.
But if you think I see you like
some kind of trophy, you're wrong.
Because you're not pretty enough for that.
- What an awesome guy you are!
- Who are you?
I'm so curious as to what happened to you,
to make you have such an inferiority complex
that you have to piss on the feelings
of a tiny first-year girl in order to feel cool?
Were you never validated as a child,
is that it?
Mommy was never proud of your drawings?
Or was it daddy,
who never came to
any of your graduations?
You didn't have hair on your dick
in the 7th grade and got bullied for it?
Whatever it is, you seriously have to get over it
and start behaving like a decent human being.
Stop walking around like a fucking cliché.
FRIDAY, 2:02 P.M.
I have to go to Norwegian class.
- No...
- I have to!
Yeah. But seriously, I really have to go.
I've been late way too many times.
Talk to you later.
- Fucking hell, you were so awesome yesterday.
- Yeah, that was legendary.
- Are you doing okay?
- Yeah, yeah. I'm completely over William.
Good.
Anyway, nobody cares about me and William.
Everyone's talking about that rumor about Chris.
What rumor about Chris?
Chris hooked up with someone at the Halloween
party, his girlfriend found out and went psycho!
But you told me it wasn't Chris!
Chris hooked up with someone
at the party.
I saw it.
You saw it?
Yeah, on the stairs.
On the stairs?
You fucking whore!