- I didn't think she was his type.
- Neither did I.
- When did they get together?
- Last weekend.
Where was that?
Jonas said that she gave
him a blowjob on the toilet.
Since when are you
together after a blowjob?
You're not together after that.
They were already together in
the 10th grade or something.
- Yeah.
- Who is this about?
- Eva, why?
- TEXT FROM WILLHELM
It's so sick that they got together.
You look freaking hot in that shirt.
One of the prettiest girls
in Pepsi Max has a boyfriend.
They fall in the same category
as the Penetrator-boys.
You guys! I have fantastic news.
Are you ready?
- Say it.
- Are you excited?
I have acquired "Brun
og Blid" as a sponsor.
What did you say?
It's Norway's largest
tanning salon chain.
I know what "Brun og Blid" is.
We will not be sponsored by them, no.
Why's that?
Because they contribute
to the most speculative
and sexist marketing in Norway.
Have you even seen their commercials?
It's a tanning salon...
It's difficult to promote it
without showing tanned bodies.
Noora, I worked really hard
to get them to sponsor us.
You're just being really ungrateful.
Can't you see how difficult
it was to persuade them?
So you think we should
promote "Brun og Blid"?
And contribute to a completely
inhumane body pressure?
I don't feel too much
of that body pressure.
I say we milk those sexist
motherfuckers for every penny they have!
OK... Oh my god,
fucking cool. Go for it.
But then I'm not
joining the bus anymore.
Huh? Are you kidding right now?
Noora, oh my god. Just because
things don't go your way?
Now you're being really childish.
It's just because I refuse
to contribute to that
inhumane body pressure.
The logo is this small. Here.
I don't understand how that
will contribute to body pressure.
Yeah well, whatever. I give up.
Should we go as a gå-russ then?
Vilde, it might come
as a shock to you...
But Russebuss is not important to me.
I just wanted to get
to know Eva and Sana.
- Wow, thanks for that!
- No!
You too, Chris.
You know I love you.
This discussion isn't over!
MONDAY, 4:35 PM
Yeah?
- Did you eat my pasta?
- No.
Can you ask Eskild to
turn down the music?
Eskild!
Sorry!
Noora?
Can you lend me 200 Kroner until Monday?
Yeah, OK.
- Hi!
- Hey.
- Do you need help?
- No, never.
Never.
Hey.
- Hello.
- Hello. What's up?
Netflix. Just Netflix...
- Do you have some food?
- Yeah, of course.
I didn't have a chance to eat at home.
Too much guy-on-guy BJ action.
No, what the fuck?
Your parents, or what?
I live in a shared
apartment with roommates.
Ah, OK.
But I have actually seen
my parents in BJ action.
No way! Seriously?
I would have been scarred
for the rest of my life.
What did she reply?
"Come to my house and show me."
Are you kidding? She is stalling.
What should I answer, then?
Who is this?
A 00'er Jonas is involved with.
I haven't even kissed her.
But it's going to happen.
I never want to hook up with a 00'er!
Then why are you chatting with her?
Because she has a good body.
***
OK so...
Jonas is flirting with a girl
and you're helping him?
Eh... yeah.
Wow!
How is that working out for you?
We're friends,
so it works out just fine.
OK...
What the fuck?
- She sent boobs!
- Are you kidding?
No, look!
- Hey, you can't show that to us!
- Why not?
Let me see! Screenshot it!
Fucking hell, they are really nice.
And she's a 00'er?
I bet she took a screenshot
from a magazine or something.
No, I don't think so.
She got it to look like this with
a good black and white filter.
***
I know the tricks. Shit!
Fuck. They are really big!
One is a little higher
up than the other.
Now it's your turn. I'm sorry.
Should I go and send stuff to people?
You should send loads
of dick pics, of course.
I keep it real.
It's not hard to do this.
But it's hard to take screenshots?
Set it as your background!
What school does she go to?
- TUESDAY, 11:40 AM
- We should talk about our sponsors.
Because everyone should feel like
they have a say in the Russebuss.
We are very different girls.
At the same time it's also important
that we are strong and independent.
But we have to have money.
I suggest a Russebuss meeting on Friday.
Then everyone can talk properly
about the image and the concept.
We'll drink wine and
just enjoy ourselves.
It's been so long that it was just us.
For me, we don't really need to do this.
It's not important to me.
I have a party in
Elvebakken on Friday, so...
- With who?
- With Jonas.
I promised I would go with him.
Come on! We're friends, OK?
Why is it so hard to understand
that you can be friends with
your ex? When you're a couple,
it's the same thing as being best
friends. You just also have sex.
We ended the sex part.
That doesn't mean we can't
still be best friends.
Did you hear William beat up
someone from Hansen this weekend?
- Who was it?
- A 98'er. He was properly destroyed.
He ended up in the emergency room.
Oh my god, so cool!
I think William is very sensitive.
He knows what it's like to lose someone.
- I think he's a fuckboy.
- What do you mean by losing someone?
His little sister.
He lost his little sister?
Yeah, didn't you know? She's dead.
A dead little sister. It's so tragic.
- When did this happen?
- A long time ago.
Something like that
really stays with someone.
I like that you're sitting
there looking at me.
It's' so sad for him. I think
that's why he's a fuckboy.
- Because he knows what it's like to lose someone.
- I'm not looking at you.
He doesn't want to lose anyone again.
***
He's really a good guy. I
noticed that during Christmas.
- Right, Eva?
- What?
That he's a really good guy.
Yeah. It seemed like he was really keen.
Why else would he say you were hot?
You still owe me a date. Friday?
I actually don't remember
what he said to me.
Do you?
Didn't he say something like...
- Unfortunately, can't on Friday. Got something important.
- "Vilde,
- I didn't mean what I said back then."
- What's that?
Then he said:
"Whoever gets you, is fucking lucky."
Buss meeting. Russetiden preparation.
Most important thing in the world.
"Every guy that gets
you is so fucking lucky."
"Remember when I said
you weren't good enough? "
That was bullshit. And every guy
that gets you is fucking lucky."
He's totally random though.
He came up to Noora and...
Came up to Noora and then?
Nothing.
Vilde,
it's never going to happen
between me and William.
He's the most unsympathetic,
selfish person I've ever met.
I would never touch him.
And you shouldn't either.
You don't know him like I do.
If you had just heard him at Chrismtas.
How long can we talk about
Christmas? It's March!
Just because he came
over and apologised,
because he behaved like an asshole...
it doesn't mean he's a good person.
And it doesn't mean he's keen on you.
I'm not the one who
said he was keen on me.
It was Eva who said that.
I just don't want you to
get your hopes up and...
It's from William!
"Penetrator party on Friday.
Bring your bus group and come."
Don't we have a bus meeting on Friday?
I thought that wasn't important to you.
I thought it was important to
you to be strong and independent?
Yeah, but I can be strong and
independent at the Penetrator party.
So we'll just drop all our
plans, because a guy calls.
Can't we have a bus meeting first,
and then go to the party afterwards?
That's exactly what we'll do.
"We're coming." Heart... heart?
So then we'll have the
bus meeting and the party,
and then you can go to that
party with your best friend.
_
Eskild!
THURSDAY, 5:21 PM
Do you still need money?
- I need help with something.
- 500 Kroner.
- 200 Kroner.
- 200 Kroner?
200 Kroner!
- 400 Kroner.
- 300!
***
- 350! Last offer.
- 350. Great.
You have to make a move
on one of my friends.
- Yeah?
- Eh, yeah. OK.
Don't you think
I'm gonna set off some gaydars?
No, oh my god. No stress. She
doesn't even know what gay is.
She's so naive.
Yeah great, OK. Whatever.
What do you want me to do?
I'm having a bus party here tomorrow,
and you just walk in randomly.
Is there alcohol for me?
Sure!
- Just be home around 7, OK?
- OK.
Do I have to make out with her?
No, no, no. Oh my god.
She just needs some attention.
Just some compliments and stuff.
Because she's crazy obsessed with a guy
who isn't interested in her.
So that's why I need you
to help her forget him.
OK.
- He'll be forgotten.
- Great!
- For 500 Kroner.
- No! I said 350!
If I make out with her,
we'll say 500 Kroner.
You don't need to make out with her!
For 390 I'll touch her boobs.
350! No making out and no boob touching.
- Just a little attention.
- 350 and boob stroking.
No. 350 and a little attention.
If it goes well, I can
touch her boobs a little.
Oh my god, what the fuck?
It's nothing. Just to know how it feels!
FRIDAY, 7:48 PM
With this here. I
thought something like...
Up here it's classy, but
here it's a little slutty.
- Didn't the bottles break?
- A white top is just stressful.
If you spill something,
it becomes transparent.
- Yes...
- Ah you'd like that, don't you?
No Vilde! Take this. That one was
super pretty. Now you have to stop.
I think I'm going to
sleep with William tonight.
Don't forget a condom.
Are you going to sleep
with Jonas tonight?
- No, we're just friends.
- Where are you? Come home NOW!!
So you guys haven't had
sex after you broke up?
No, I promise.
- Last time we had sex was when we broke up.
- That's when you broke up?
Yeah.
I'm serious, you have
to try that once. Fuck.
The best sex I ever had.
It was really amazing.
Shouldn't you be sad
after you've broken up?
Well yeah, we were.
But that was what made
it so hot. So intense.
- What?
- Are you sure it happened?
That it wasn't a dream or a flashback?
Hey guys, can I ask something?
- Has anyone ever gone down on you?
- No.
Yeah!
Someone went down on me in
Gran Canaria last summer.
- Are you kidding me? How was it?
- It was fucking nice.
I sat there and just...
Then it couldn't have been very...
I'm really scared William
will try to go down on me.
Vilde, there's no Norwegian
guy who will do it.
It's true, while we
suck dick for dear life.
Snapchat from William! He's
wondering when we're coming.
When are you gonna go to Jonas?
We were supposed to call.
I can call him.
That snapchat to Vilde
was directed towards you.
Can't we go in half an hour?
You can't use Vilde this way.
No, oh my god!
Now we're going to talk
about image, concept.
- That's why we're here. Right?
- Yes.
What kind of concept would you like?
Jonas' phone is turned off or something.
- Hi!
- There you are!
I'm having a bus party tonight.
It's nice that you're here.
These are my friends. This
is Eskild. He lives with me.
- Yeah, hi. Eskild.
- Hi.
- Hi. Vilde.
- Hi, Eskild.
Eva, if you could...
I have some tomatoes...
I'll sit here. Hi.
Here.
But eh...
- don't you have some wine?
- Yeah!
- Oh, Chablis! Hmm.
- From 19... eh 2010.
- OK. Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Noora, what should I do with the tomatoes?
- You have really pretty eyes.
You think so?
You have a lot of eye make-up.
It was Eva who did that.
You shouldn't let her do it.
She's not really good at it.
You're not a virgin, right?
No I'm not.
- Can you see it?
- I might be a little direct now...
I can see it from your breasts.
Once you've had sex...
Jonas, what's wrong with your
phone? Why is it turned off?
Call me when you get this.
***
- This wine is good.
- Hello? Music?
I want to put on some
music! Which phone is it?
- Let's dance!
- Yes!
It's Britney, bitch.
It's William!
Hi?
Yeah...
OK...
It's William. He wants to talk to you.
Eh... To me?
Yeah, hello.
I can't stop using Vilde when
you don't answer your phone.
What is it?
We wouldn't have been in this
situation if you had kept your promise.
No. I don't have his number.
Whose? Maybe I have it.
You go on a date with me,
and then I'll stop using Vilde.
OK?
- OK.
- Good!
Let me speak to Vilde.
He wants to talk to you.
Hi!
What a shame.
Yeah, I understand.
Ok. Bye!
There's no Penetrator party.
Chris' parents came home.
Can't we come along to
your Elvebakken party?
Jonas doesn't answer.
He turned off his phone.
Can we at least dance and have a party?
Whose number did he want?
Next Friday. 7:PM. I'll pick you up.
Aren't you gay?
Subtitle by kazekira
resync and corrections by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com