We have merged with the Pepsi-Max.
So we have a bus meeting this week. Vilde?
Why can't you host for once?
I heard you talked to Isak about Mikael.
Oh yeah! He saw a picture
of Mikael on my Facebook.
Okay?
We didn't talk about him or anything.
There is a boy I like.
- Muslim?
- Yeah.
He is funny and smart.
- Good looking?
- Yeah, really handsome.
Like that guy Yousef. Do you know him well?
Why are we talking about Yousef?
Aren't you with William?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T BELIEVE IN ALLAH.
SUNDAY
11:45
- No.
- You have it open.
Take away those teeth.
Take them away!
- Do you love me?
- You don't think I love you?
Meow!
You think I don't love you Vilde? Hey!
- You have the dick of a lion.
- Hah! I have.
I love you so much that we'll be
together for the rest of our lives.
If you liked it, then you
should have put a ring on it.
Come.
You are so quiet today?
I'm a little tired.
- Shall we go?
- We're going to Magnus' home and to fuck.
- Okay...
- Bye, bye.
- Nice to have coffee with you...
- Jump on my back!
Aren't couples in love
just sick gross or what?
Yes.
When are you going to tell me
about that stuff with William?
I guess that would
be now, I suppose.
I couldn't testify against Nico.
Has the trial been up?
It was up in August.
I took the plane to Oslo and
got up and got dressed.
I sat on the streetcar. Then
I went off the streetcar.
Then I walked ten meters and
took the streetcar back again.
Then when I got back to London,
William asked me how it went.
And I lied and said everything went fine.
You should have told us. We
would have gone with you.
Either way, the letter about the
trial being dismissed arrived.
I don't think I've ever seen
anyone so disappointed.
But he has to understand
that it was difficult for you?
Yes he understood, or he said so.
That it was fine, but...
I could see that he was so hurt.
It was like as if everything
with Nico just...
came up to the surface again.
After that he started working
and working, all the time.
And we hardly talked
to each other anymore.
So I felt like he
didn't love me anymore.
So...
One day when he was at work...
I just went back home.
What?
Without saying anything?
But you've talked to
each other after that?
I've tried writing a mail
to him a hundred times,
but every time I think about
sending it, I think...
that perhaps it's better
if we just stay apart.
It has just become so ridiculously
complicated between us,
that perhaps both of us would be
better off with someone else.
You...
My God! If I'm going to think about
him being with someone else,
I'll just be destroyed.
You are so lucky.
That you don't have to think
about all those problems.
Heartbreak and all that.
Maybe I should just
convert to Islam as well?
Don't you think Allah would like me?
I think Allah would love you.
I could just get married and...
I could marry that sweet
buddy of your brother.
Yousef?
TUESDAY
17:13
BUSS STUFF :)
Sara Nørstelien
THANKS FOR YOUR COURAGE ON FRIDAY.
YOU SEEM LIKE A COOL BUS BOSS.
1) HOW DO WE PAY FOR THE BUS?
SHOULD WE USE YOUR ACCOUNT?
CAN DO A SHARED ACCOUNT LATER.
2) YOU SPOKE ABOUT A BUS BOSSES' MEETING.
WHEN WILL IT BE?
YOUSEF: ANYONE MISSING THIS?
IT'S TIME FOR ASR
SOUND MUTED
REMOVE AS FRIEND
ADD AS FRIEND
-
Hello.
Are you doing homework?
Yeah. I...
I have to submit a biology
work in two days.
Biology? Okay.
What are you reading then?
I'm writing about the
human immune system.
Yeah.
Does Elias have guests?
No.
But you never know with these boys.
It's almost like they live here.
They come over at any time.
You.
I have to ask you something.
Do you think Elias has
started drinking alcohol?
- Huh? Why do you think so?
- No, I don't know.
But since Yousef drinks alcohol and...
I'm a little worried.
You don't have to worry mom. I
really don't think Elias drinks.
You don't think so?
No.
No? Okay. I'll just
have to trust you then.
Have you talked more with that
handsome muslim boy then?
No. I haven't.
No.
-
WEDNESDAY
13:37
-
Hello!
What is it?
I've done some research.
Okay?
I know how you can get over William.
What are you doing on Friday?
What are we going to do now?
You'll have to find out and see.
No, I don't like surprises.
Hi!
Did you see my e-mail?
Yes, but I haven't had
the time to answer.
But... Can't you just contact Mari
yourself, regarding payment?
Yes, do you have her mail so I can
send the suggestion for contract?
No...
Noora, do you have it?
I think so. Maybe.
Or just check mine.
- What's your mail then?
- Loglady997
- Password?
- Exper 5.
Huh?
Exper 5.
- Exp...
- Exper.
Exper 5. Haven't you heard...?
How do you write that? E-K-S... or?
Oh my God!
With X, or C or?
Hang on, my God. Don't
judge me for my passwords.
Here. Just look here.
But!
- What's she called? Mari Aspeflaten?
- Yeah.
- Thanks! I'll put you on copy.
- Yes.
Okay. But you'll come along on Friday?
Hello, come on!
My God! You are really excited!
Yeah. But I'm excited for you
getting over William. All right?
- That's why I'm a good friend.
- What are we doing then?
Say it! Say it! Say it!
Will you come if I tell
you what we're doing?
No! Come on! Yes, say
what we are doing!
- Okay, we're going to a cafe.
- Are we going to a cafe?! That's...?
- Which one?
- Now you ask a lot.
- No, I'm just curious.
- Some of it must still be a surprise.
But, what are we going
to do at the cafe?
Just drink coffee and enjoy ourselves?
Or is something happening? Is it...?
It's nothing dangerous. It's just a cafe.
And the rest you'll see.
Oh, have you started rhyming as well?
Yes, that's included!
- I come along. (continues rhyming) No.
- I already said "med" (along/with)
- Ok. - Like, "exper5". What's
that suppose to rhyme with?
How was this thing going again?
We're here for my sake?
Yes, of course we're here for your sake.
Just to check out muslim boys and so?
Aren't you tired of westside boys now?
I think we have to go out,
meet new types of people.
Check that...
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
If you know what I mean.
But you said muslim boys
only use norwegian girls.
Yeah. But then it's a good thing
you're converting to Islam.
Don't turn around now, but...
are those guys looking at us?
How am I going to know that
if I can't turn around?
Oh my God. They are coming over!
- Be cool.
- Be cool? I'm super cool!
- Hello!
- Hi.
Can we sit here?
Yeah!
- Is it ok?
- Yes, take a seat.
- Hi!
- Ali.
- Noora.
- Nice to meet you.
- Sana.
- Jonas. Nice to meet you.
- It was Sana?
- Sana.
- What are you doing then?
- We're drinking tea.
- Chai.
- Enjoying apple.
- It's fucking good.
- It looks fucking good.
You have no idea how good it is.
Or you can imagine?
Yes, it looked really good.
Help yourself.
- Awesome!
- Are you selling tea or what?
- Yeah. I'm selling this tea.
- Oh! I understand now!
- Good choice. Apple tea.
- Totally agree. - Cool
But what do you do besides
drinking tea then?
- What do we do?
- Are you studying?
- Yeah.
- Yes, we do.
- Cool.
- At the University in Oslo.
- Oslo? Same here.
- You're studying there too?
What are you studying?
[UNKNOWN]
We're taking different subjects.
Like some...
Individual courses?
Yeah. Individual courses.
- Shopping for courses?
- Shopping for courses.
What do you do then? Study?
Yes, they study...
Shopping for courses. Then I'll see.
Maybe a year off.
Because the student fund costs, you know.
[UNKNOWN]
- Hello?
- Hi. It's Yousef.
Sorry for calling, but I don't
know what to do with Elias.
What happened?
He's completely drunk and
wants to go home and sleep.
But I don't think that's a good idea.
Where are you?
I can walk you home.
It's ok, you don't have to.
God, there's no problem.
I'll walk you home.
What was Elias exactly drinking?
Vodka.
Bad reaction?
What did you say?
Bad. Reaction.
Relax.
You gotta relax.
You're so tough.
Pass the ball.
Wow, reaction! Or what?
Tough girl, then.
Just give me the ball. You
can't handle the ball.
- You got such bad reaction...
- I can handle balls better than you.
Wow. Wow. What the fuck?
Why don't you believe in Allah?
You know, Even, that guy
we used to hang out with?
I think he is gay.
Because he... he tried to...
kiss Mikael.
And Mikael is quite religious.
So he distanced himself completely.
He was shocked.
So what happened was,
that Even was going to cure
himself by reading the Quran.
He started posting different
verses from the Quran
about those being gay ending up in hell.
You know that he...
tried to kill himself?
So I just feel that Islam,
or religion in general,
creates a lot of anxiety on people.
Even was sick though.
It had nothing to do with religion.
I don't know.
I personally feel I've taken
the best from religion
and thrown away the rest.
And what's the best then?
Things like compassion for others. Be
grateful for everything you receive and,
to help others, to be positive.
Do the best for others and
not just for yourself.
That's all.
But that's exactly what
the rituals in Islam
remind you all the time.
Those values.
By fasting and praying
five times a day.
It gives you focus.
And that's because of the fact that...
one should always remember
what is the most important.
And that is to be a good person.
Don't you think I remember how to
be a good person without praying?
Well.
For me,
I stress through the days,
with hundreds of thoughts in my head
and...
and everything can be totally
chaos in the daily life,
but...
but in the moment I start praying,
everything becomes completely quiet.
And clear.
Because even if all that chaos is
happening in your everyday life,
you remember what really matters.
Everything...
Everything it's ok, because
everything is on a bigger frame,
and has a meaning.
Like...
Do you know for example,
that brains of cockroaches,
have nine different types
of molecules for antibiotics,
that are stronger than any
penicillin we have today?
Cockroaches? Seriously?
Where did that come from?
Because!
It's just that...
Every little part of the
universe is so complex.
Think about that.
Even the brain of a cockroach
has a bigger importance
and meaning on earth.
All the way down to
the smallest details.
And I...
I just can't believe that
all this is a coincidence.
If religion is so good,
why does it divide society?
- Are we two?
- Then we're cool.
- Oh, we are cool.
- We are two as well.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Are you looking into my eyes now?
Let me see. Are you?
I'm not really sure...
- I am looking into your eyes.
- Very good. Okay.
No...
But...
What was I going to say?
-What should I say?
- Sana!
Goodbye, then.
Goodbye.
@Ledgerina