SUNDAY, 3:18 P.M.
Add friend.
Invitation sent
Mom
- Hi!
- Hi, dear.
Are you in Oslo now?
No, my flight from Geneva is canceled,
so I'm stuck here until tomorrow.
- No...
- But I'll be in Oslo tomorrow afternoon.
But, I'm going to the cabin tomorrow.
Oh, yeah, that's true!
Where were you going again?
To Ingrid's cabin,
with Ingrid and Sara.
Oh, how nice! Who will drive you guys?
No, we'll take a bus.
A bus? Can't you wait? If you wait a day,
or go on Tuesday, I can drive you.
But...
I've been looking forward to going to the cabin
for over a month now.
Yeah, I know.
But, I'm coming home on Saturday.
Yeah... on Saturday...
It looks like I'll have to leave again
on Friday night.
Oh...
But... do you have enough money?
Yes.
Yeah.
You know what? I'll wire you a little bit extra,
so you can enjoy yourselves at the cabin trip.
Thanks!
Okay, have a good trip,
and say hi to Ingrid and Sara.
Yeah, thanks, you too! I will.
- Okay, we'll talk.
- We will. Take care!
TUESDAY, 9:04 A.M.
- Sorry, sorry!
- Isak!
- Should we send him home?
- Okay, let's just do it.
♪ Lonely, I'm so lonely ♪
♪ I have nobody, of my own ♪
What time is it really?
Text from Ingrid.
- Ten past nine.
- Ten past nine?!
- Isak, why did you come in so damn early, man?
- I didn't know that you were going to fuck!
WEDNESDAY, 8:32 P.M.
- Play "I'm Yours".
- No!
- You only know gay songs.
- Shut the fuck up! Is that a gay song?
Who is it?
- Jonas?
- Elias.
- Your new boyfriend?
- What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
You ran after him the entire school day,
it's like he's your god.
- Hello?
- "Oh, Elias? I'm so glad to be talking to you!"
"I-I think I love you!
Maybe we can get married in February
"and go on our honeymoon in March
"and live together for the rest of our lives.
And love each other!"
- What's the deal with Jonas and Ingrid?
- Huh?
You heard what I said.
You have to ask Jonas.
Why do you ask?
I saw a notification on his phone.
I know that you know something.
Can't you just say it?
I promise I won't get angry.
And I promise I won't tell Jonas
you said anything.
Are they texting?
Maybe a little.
Okay, talk to you later. Bye!
Ahh, bro!
♪ Well, you done done me
and you bet I felt it ♪
♪ I tried to be chill,
but you're so hot that I melted ♪
♪ I fell right through the cracks ♪
♪ Now I'm trying to get back ♪
♪ Before the cool done run out ♪
♪ I'll be giving it my bestest ♪
THURSDAY, 5:32 P.M.
In which stadium
does the English Cup Final take place?
- Wembley.
- That's correct.
What bone in your body gets broken most often?
Cancel friend request?
Cancel request
Close
- The collarbone.
- Yep.
Who was the first president of the United States?
George Washington.
Okay, Eva. Who was the first
female Prime Minister of Norway?
I'm not joining.
She doesn't know the answer.
- I do, I just don't want to join.
- Just answer, then we won't nag anymore.
- I didn't hear the question.
- Who was Norway's first female Prime Minister?
Erna Solberg.
Fuck you guys!
Why are you so pissed?
I'm not pissed.
I just think Trivial Pursuit is boring.
Okay? What do you want to play then,
since you think it's so boring?
- Nothing. I want to read.
- Come on! You got to want to do something.
Okay.
- I want to play "My ship is loaded with..."
- Let's play it, then.
I'll start.
My ship is loaded with Ingrid.
My ship is loaded with Erna Solberg.
Okay... my ship is loaded with insects.
My ship is loaded with ice cream.
My ship is loaded with--
- What the fuck? What was that?
- Shit. Damn.
- Did you see it?
- No.
- So weird.
- Really strange.
It's...
Hello?
- Hi!
- The fuck?
- Elias!
- Jonas!
- What's up?
- You came!
Of course I came!
When I say I'm coming, I'll do it.
- How did you find the way?
- Embedded GPS in my brain, man.
No, I asked a guy at the parking space up there.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So this is where you guys hang?
Really cool.
Good atmosphere, at least. It'll be a party.
- Where am I sleeping?
- In the inner bedroom, with Isak.
- Am I sleeping with the gay guy?
- Why is everyone calling me gay?
You are gay.
He's kidding. Have a sense of humor.
What? He asked if he could come.
What should I have said?
♪ ...from home, he's no father ♪
♪ He goes home ♪
FRIDAY, 7:04 P.M.
♪ and barely knows his own daughter ♪
♪ But hold your nose
'cause here goes the cold water ♪
♪ His hoes don't want him no more,
he's cold product ♪
♪ They moved on
to the next schmoe who flows ♪
♪ He nose dove and sold nada ♪
♪ So the soap opera
is told and unfolds ♪
♪ I suppose it's old partner,
but the beat goes on ♪
♪ Da da dum da dum da da da da ♪
♪ You better lose yourself
in the music, the moment ♪
♪ You own it,
you better never let it go ♪
♪ You only get one shot,
do not miss your chance to blow ♪
♪ This opportunity comes
once in a lifetime ♪
- That was really awesome.
- Yeah, it's working now.
Do you need help?
- Did you set the table?
- Yes, I did.
- Mmm, smells good! Can I taste?
- Yeah.
That was good.
- We're going out for a smoke.
- A smoke?
- Yeah, a smoke.
- You don't even smoke.
- Come on, it's a party.
- Yeah, it's a party.
- Are you sure you don't need any help?
- No, it's fine.
Food's ready!
Jonas!
Seriously?
- It's not funny.
- It's a little funny.
You can help yourself, can't you?
Why are you so pissed all the time?
I'm pissed because you're
behaving like a jerk.
Jerk? What did I do?
Tell me what I did, then!
You invited people to a cabin trip
that was supposed to be just us.
- Two guys?
- Yes.
And you change personality when Elias is around,
acting all tough guy.
And you're texting with Ingrid
behind my back,
even though you know what
a bitch she's been to me!
Ingrid? I'm not talking to Ingrid
behind your back!
- What did she say I did?
- You think I don't know you text her?
- I was texting her about French.
- About French?
- During autumn break?
- We have homework for after the break.
Okay, if it's about French,
can I read the messages?
- Why would you read my messages?
- You can read my messages!
- I don't want to read your messages.
- Why not?
Do we have to read each others messages
to trust each other?
- Yes!
- That's ridiculous!
Jonas! This is ridiculous!
What the fuck?
Why do you think that I'm talking to Ingrid?
- It's true, right?
- Yeah, about school!
- Can I see your messages, then?
- I already told you it's ridiculous!
Why don't you just trust me?
- She's pissed.
- Yeah, she's damn pissed.
Damn pissed!