[thunder rumbling]
Oh, yes! You got donuts.
I already ate
all the Boston Cream.
Kyle!
This place
gives me the creeps.
Relax. That Popsicle
hasn't moved in 50 years.
[guitar strumming gently]
[fluid bubbling]
[guitar music continues]
[alarm blaring]
[heartbeat thudding]
[beeping]
Is that normal?
No.
Someone's hacking the system.
What?
The containment tank
is destabilizing.
He's waking up.
[alarm blaring]
[weapons powering up]
[heartbeat thudding faster]
[steady beep]
[sighs]
[power crackling]
[grunts]
[yells]
[soldier gasping in fear]
[energy crackles]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[both yelp]
We need more guys.
That is all the guys.
[thunder pealing]
[duck squeaks]
Wait a second.
I thought
we were going tubing.
Hold on, hold on.
Is this a race?
You're going down!
It is my destiny
to claim the throne
of Family Champion, hedgehog.
[laughs] Cute.
Are you sure
you want to challenge
the fastest creature
in the universe?
I mean, that's kind of
my whole brand.
Okay, Tom and Maddie,
count us down.
Right!
Don't worry,
a little sibling rivalry
is healthy.
Me and my brothers used to
do this kind of thing
all the time.
Tom, your brothers are lunatics
and neither of them
were born with the power
to trigger a global
cataclysmic event.
That's a fair point.
Did you hear that, boys?
No cataclysmic events, okay?
Let's keep this
cataclysmic-less.
Ten-four!
Understood,
Lord of the Donuts.
Then on your marks, get set...
go!
And way out in front,
to the surprise
of absolutely no one,
it's the Blue Blur,
the Red-Shoed Rocket,
the one, the only--
[Tails] Come on, Sonic!
Catch up! Yeah!
What in the what, now?
I am also defeating you,
hedgehog!
Seriously?
All right, you know what?
Time to light the afterburners.
Look! It's a bird! It's a plane!
It's Air Hedgehog!
["99 Red Balloons"
by Goldfinger playing]
[laughing]
Yes! I did it! I...
lost?
How is that even possible?
I do not lose.
I am also defeating you,
hedgehog.
Okay, okay, I get it, man.
No need to rub it in.
Come on, Sonic!
Catch up! Yeah!
Wait, what's going on?
[yelps]
Why are you guys acting like...
holograms!
Which means...
I remain the undefeated
speed champion of all time!
Yes!
And the crowd goes wild!
But also, what's going on?
[all] Surprise!
But wait a sec, you guys...
[stammering]
...what is all this?
"Happy Bea Arthur Day"?
Oh, it's
"Happy B-Earth-Day."
Today's the anniversary of
the day you came to Earth, bud.
It's your "Earth Day Birthday."
So the race
was just a distraction,
which I totally didn't fall for,
by the way--
Good try, though--
so you could throw a party
for me?
Today, we honor you, hedgehog.
If it wasn't for you, none of us
would be here right now.
The boys are right, bud.
You know, the day you came
to this planet
is the day all our lives
changed forever.
And we became a family.
[barks]
You guys, I don't...
I don't know what to say.
Except... let's party!
[Tom] All right!
[Sonic] Yeah!
[Knuckles] It's now on
till the break of dawn!
[Tails] Toga! Toga!
Thanks for the surprise party.
It really means a lot to me.
Ah, you deserve it, pal.
[gasps] No way. Is that...
What? [sighing] Dude...
Could you just for once
walk at my speed?
Whoa.
[chuckling] Sonic!
This is your--
Yep. My old cave.
Oh, man.
I can't believe this is where
you lived all those years.
Hey! My state-of-the-art
security system!
[kiais]
[grunts] Still works.
Hey, bud.
What's this?
Wow. You know, I drew that
on my first night on Earth.
I wanted to remember
where I came from.
I still miss her.
You think Longclaw
would be proud of me?
I know she would, pal.
Because even though you lost her
at such a young age,
you didn't let your pain
change who you are...
in here.
Yeah. In my lungs.
Or your heart.
Heart, right.
Yeah, makes more sense.
Not lungs, heart.
That's the thing
about life, Sonic,
it's all about the choices
we make.
You're gonna
make some good ones and,
knowing you,
you're gonna make some bad ones.
But...
as long as you remember
to listen to your heart,
you're gonna
make the right choice
when it matters the most.
Thanks.
I don't know
what I'd do without you.
I'd probably be
a totally different hedgehog.
[horn blares]
[grunts]
2024?
I've been trapped for 50 years?
[people screaming]
[motors revving]
Move, move!
Take positions!
[tires squeal]
Get on the ground now!
We've got you surrounded!
Why won't you leave me alone?
Take him down!
I have dishonored
my marshmallow.
It's really just a question
of temperature and distance.
It's not a competition.
This is so nice.
Peace.
Quiet.
Finally.
Finally!
[helicopter thrumming]
Hey! We're trying to have
a family moment down here!
What did we do?
Or what did they do?
What did you do?
I don't know.
I do a lot of stuff.
Mr. and Mrs. Wachowski.
Aliens.
"Aliens"? Excuse me?
It's not like we're
from different planet--
Oh, yeah, we are.
I guess we are aliens.
Please continue.
I'm Director Rockwell.
There is a very
dangerous situation
unfolding right now
in Tokyo.
Commander Walters
is requesting Team Sonic's
immediate assistance.
"Team Sonic"?
Who picked that name?
Love it!
Ten out of ten, no notes.
Tom and Maddie,
put the s'mores on ice
because Team Sonic
is off to save the day!
Remember,
make good choices!
["Neon"
by ONE OK ROCK playing]
Good evening and welcome
to Tails Air flight 1012.
We're looking at
an on-time arrival into Tokyo.
Okay, Captain, we got
a rogue alien on the loose.
How do we find him?
[explosion booming]
Uh, start with
the giant fireball?
I love it! Let's start
with the giant fireball.
[grunting]
[cackles]
Finally, some action!
Okay, time to gear up.
Titanium handcuffs,
completely indestructible.
I don't need
your silly gizmos, fox.
And you know why?
Because I am...
[all] ...one million
percent muscle.
Yes, good.
You've been listening.
[alert buzzes]
We're over the drop zone.
All right, here we go.
Showtime!
Now, look, we don't know
if it's Godzilla
or Hello Kitty down there,
but as long
as we stick together,
there is nothing
we can't handle.
"Team Sonic" on three.
One, two, three.
[all] Team...
Sonic!
Knuckles!
[groans]
Talk about low-budget flights.
No food or movies?
We're out of here!
["Neon" continues]
[song ends]
[people screaming]
[Knuckles] What happened here?
[Sonic] Looks like GUN
got their butts kicked.
Keep your eyes open.
Tails, anything?
Whoa! These energy readings
are off the charts!
[loud crashing]
[Sonic] Look out!
[Knuckles grunts]
One... million...
percent.
[truck crashes]
[heavy footfalls]
Whoa! Are you guys seeing this?
He looks just like you.
Impossible!
You're a colorful bunch.
Um, excuse me.
Why do you look like me?
I don't look like you.
You look like me!
Why do you look like me?
Hey, you know what?
I'll ask the questions,
new hedgehog!
Who are you?
Why do you look like me?
This is a waste of time.
Walk away,
before you get hurt.
Whoa, whoa, easy, buddy.
We don't want to fight you.
Actually, Sonic,
I would like to fight.
Not now.
[Knuckles growls]
Why don't you stop throwing cars
at us for a second
and come down here to talk?
You jumped
out of a GUN helicopter.
There's nothing
to talk about.
All right, then. Enough!
Knuckles, no!
Let us talk with our fists!
[fist crunching]
[yells]
[grunts]
[grunts sharply]
[both] Knuckles!
Knuckles!
Knuckles, are you okay?
No, not really. Ow!
[Tails] Who is this guy?
He is much more impressive
than the hedgehog
I fought previously.
Dude,
I'm standing right here.
Now, come on!
He can't take us all at once.
[Tails] Ow!
[Knuckles grunts]
[Sonic grunts]
[yelling]
[breathless] Okay,
he took us all at once.
Weakling.
[groans]
Don't try to follow me.
[motor revving]
Sonic, I know that look.
Going after him
is a bad idea.
When has that ever stopped me?
I got to ask,
one hedgehog to another,
who does your highlights?
[growls]
[horn blares]
Hey! Dangerously weaving
through traffic is my thing!
[loud grunt]
Coming through!
[yelps]
Why are you running away?
We were just getting started.
[both shriek]
The more you talk,
the harder
I want to hit you.
[yelling]
Watch out!
Ugh, I'm gonna throw up!
[motor revving]
Yeah, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yah!
[grunting heavily]
[machinery powering on]
[groans] 1.21 gigawatts.
[metal clinking]
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
[Tails] Sonic!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, guys.
And before you ask,
I handcuffed myself
for tactical reasons
that I do not have time
to explain.
You shouldn't have gone off
on your own.
We're supposed to be a team.
Sorry, buddy.
I'm still working
on this teamwork thing.
So now what?
Well, I'm not jumping
out of any more helicopters
until we get some answers
from GUN.
We need somewhere to regroup.
I know just the place.
["Lollipop"
by TEMPURA KIDZ playing]
[all clapping]
Hai, chiizu.
[yelps]
It's an ambush!
You'll never take us alive,
foul beasts!
Calm down, Knuckles.
This is a Chao Garden.
One of the top ten must-see
spots in all of Tokyo!
It's a perfect place
for us to blend in.
Are you Detective Pikachu?
Yes, he is!
[chortles] He does
look like a Pokémon.
"Pika, pika!" [laughs]
Commander Walters!
Sonic.
Thank God you're all okay.
I'm sure you have questions.
Just a big ticked-off
red and black one.
Who was that guy?
Shadow's story
began a lot like yours, Sonic.
But where you found family
and friends on this planet,
Shadow found only pain and loss.
It begins over 50 years ago,
with a meteor crash
in a quiet corner of Oklahoma.
The meteorite contained
a life-form.
The ultimate life-form.
Shadow's power--
his "chaos energy"--
went far beyond
any living creature.
The scientist
who discovered him
believed this power
would usher in a new era
for humanity.
But Shadow's power
proved too dangerous.
A terrible accident
destroyed the lab,
taking human lives with it.
[siren wailing]
The project leader
was blamed for the incident
and imprisoned.
With the program canceled...
[yelps in pain]
...Shadow was a loose end
no one knew how to deal with.
Too dangerous
to be walking free,
too valuable to destroy.
So I had him placed
into stasis...
indefinitely.
Wait a second. If Shadow's
been on ice for 50 years,
someone had to help him escape.
True.
But there's only a few people
in the world
who even know
of Shadow's existence.
[J-pop cover of
"I Want You Back"
by Jackson 5 playing]
[people cheering]
A live show? Yeah!
[drones humming]
Get down!
[people screaming]
[groaning]
Egg drones?
But Robotnik
is supposed to be dead!
Konnichi-what?
[weapons powering up]
[motorbike revving]
[tires squeal]
I'm sorry, we already had
our big motorcycle chase
for the evening.
Commander Walters!
[Knuckles grunts]
[Sonic] Commander Walters,
are you okay?
Sonic...
[painful grunt]
...take this.
[Sonic] What is it?
[Walters] A key...
to the most powerful weapon
GUN has ever built.
You're the only one I trust
to keep it safe.
[exhales weakly]
Commander Walters...
[sirens, vehicles approaching]
[gasps]
[indistinct shouts]
Alpha team, fan out!
Do we have eyes?
Secure the perimeter!
Medevac is en route.
[indistinct radio chatter]
His launch key is missing.
I knew they couldn't be trusted.
[all exclaiming]
[Tails] Why are we
running from GUN?
Aren't we on the same team?
[Sonic] Until we get
more information,
we're not trusting anyone.
Follow me.
Get it... off!
Hold it right there,
Tokyo Drift!
Who are you?
[gasps] It's the Goat Milker!
[mimicking Knuckles]
"It's the Goat Milker!"
Relax.
I'm not here to fight.
Then why are you here?
And why did you free Shadow?
Are you kidding?
The last thing we want
is more super-powered
hedgehogs running around.
The doctor had nothing
to do with it.
And I can prove it.
[car alarm chirps]
Please,
join me in the crab.
[narrator] And now back to...
"La Última Pasión."
I have fallen in love
with another.
[gasps]
But who, Gabriella?
Tell me who!
My twin brother, Pablo?
Pablo!
¡Bastardo!
Buenos días, ¡hermano!
No!
[cackling]
Let that be a lesson
to you, Juan.
[beeping]
Family
is a field
of emotional claymores
that leave you abandoned,
betrayed
and weeping
while you eat cake,
which creates copious amounts
of adipose tissue,
and what some calloused
individuals refer to as...
[sniffs deeply]
...man boobs.
Ha.
[up-tempo Latin jazz playing]
[slapping along
with the congas]
[trilling loudly]
[shrieking]
Doctor,
we have visitors.
Really?
I thought I was having
an anthropomorphic nightmare.
Where the only person
I could trust in the world
showed up with
all my worst enemies,
while I was in a bathrobe,
playing congas
on my big, fat belly!
Sorry, sir.
I don't believe it.
Eggman's alive?
And he's never
looked worse.
[cackling] Well, maybe,
this is what not giving a damn
what you think
I look like looks like.
Sir, right now we have
an even bigger problem.
Oh, come on.
There's an imposter out there
using your technology.
Imposter.
That's impossi-- What?
No.
My sweet mechanized spawn!
Whomever this party-pooping
posse is looking for
has stolen my persona
and the precious babies
from my egg sac.
Well...
I'll soon egg-xact
my revenge.
You see what I did there?
[chuckles]
It's time for the dramatic
soap-opera twist,
where this Pablo
reveals his Juan!
By cross-referencing
the precise coordinates
of each drone's
energy spikes,
I can track my babies
to the imposter's
base of operations,
right about...
there!
Sonic, I hate to say it,
but I think we're both
after the same person.
Hold on, hold on.
You're not suggesting
we team up
with Doctor Ro-Butt-Stink,
are you?
Perhaps the fox is right.
It could be our only chance
to find this mysterious,
more impressive hedgehog.
[groans]
All right, Egghead.
I hate to say it,
but it looks like
we're partners.
On one condition.
Dude, you have serious issues.
Ow!
[gibbering spasm]
Let's...
do this!
["Firestarter"
by The Prodigy playing]
[pained groan]
[door thuds]
[Robotnik grunting]
Suck it in!
[grunting]
[door rattling]
Tinker-tailor?
I need room.
Think Elvis, circa 1976.
But sir, I don't have
the proper materials.
Found some.
Resourceful.
[thunder rumbling]
[faint, indistinct chatter]
Hey! This is a restricted area.
Oh, it's okay.
She's the professor's
granddaughter.
He takes her everywhere.
Welcome to the lab, Maria.
I'm Captain Walters.
Oh, do you know
where my room is?
Yeah, down the hall
and to the right.
Make yourself at home.
But, um,
let's lose the skates,
okay, kiddo?
Okay.
[machinery humming softly]
[fluid bubbling faintly]
[light chuckle]
[chuckles]
[bag rustling]
[pen uncaps]
[laughs]
["End of the Line"
by the Traveling Wilburys
playing]
[delighted shriek]
[squealing]
[gasps]
[yelling]
[whooping]
Look out!
[crashing]
[faint roaring]
[song ends]
[crickets chirping softly]
Wow.
Look at all those stars.
They're like diamonds.
My grandfather says
it can take hundreds of years
for the light of a star
to reach Earth.
And by the time you see it,
the star might not even
exist anymore.
Isn't that crazy?
A light shines,
even though the star is gone.
Yeah, it does.
I wonder which one
you came from, Shadow.
I don't know.
I don't know anything
about my home.
This is your home, Shadow.
Earth.
Maria,
do you think I'm...
dangerous?
What are you talking about?
The way the scientists
look at me,
I can tell they're afraid.
Like I'm the horrible thing
from that movie we watched.
I don't know...
what I am.
You're my friend.
And you can do or be
anything you want.
Not because of your powers,
but because of who you are...
in here.
I don't know what I'd do
without you.
["End of the Line" resumes]
[song ends abruptly]
[dust crackling]
[footfalls]
Professor?
It's good to see you,
Shadow.
I knew you'd come home.
I can't get her out of my head.
The pain...
It's too much.
And that is why
we have to punish them.
Okay, I don't like you
and you don't like me.
Let's get this
over with quickly.
Out of my way, dorkupine.
"Dorkupine"?
Really clever.
[hollow tapping]
This door is six-inch-thick
solid steel
on a pressurized latch.
I'll need a moment to calculate
the molecular density
and invert
the venting mechanics.
[thunderous crash]
[Knuckles] I unlocked it.
[Robotnik] Subtle as always,
fist-for-brains.
Easy, Shadow.
Those are the guests
I've been expecting.
Let's give them
a warm welcome.
[Stone] Whoa.
What is this place?
[Sonic] It looks like
a military base,
but nobody's been here
for years.
I wonder if it's haunted.
Haunted? Nobody said anything
about being haunted.
What's the matter?
You afraid of g-g-g-ghosts?
Nothing scares
an Echidna warrior.
Uh, yeah. Do you remember
what happened last movie night?
[screaming in terror]
[piercing scream]
[all yelling]
Let go, let go, let go!
There is no such thing
as a friendly ghost.
[Sonic]
So which way do we go?
I know! We should split up.
Everyone with hideous,
brightly-colored fur
take the left and the middle.
Stone and I will go right.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm not
letting you out of my sight.
Tails, you and Stone go left.
Knuckles, you take the middle.
Eggman, you and me go right.
By all means.
We could use some
time together.
To work on
your trust issues.
You know what? You're right.
I should be more trusting.
I mean, you've only tried
to kill me twice!
Just a dark, creepy hallway.
Nothing to be afraid of.
You hear that, ghost?
You don't frighten me!
[steam hissing]
[yells]
Get... a... grip.
Boo.
[screams]
I'm just gonna
come right out and say this:
You're adorable.
[chuckles]
Oh, um, thanks.
So, what's it like
being Sonic's assistant?
You have a daily routine?
Paid time off? Benefits?
Oh, I'm not Sonic's assistant.
We're teammates.
He's the leader,
Knuckles is the muscle,
and I'm the gadget guy.
We all have a role to play.
That's what makes the team
so special!
That and the fact
we're best friends.
You are?
Well, yeah.
Just like you and Eggman, right?
Uh... Yeah, eh...
Of course! Yes.
Me and the doctor,
best of friends.
That's definitely
what we are.
[metallic clattering]
[squeaking]
Hmm.
[both screaming]
Whoa. Look at all this stuff.
This was more than
just a military base or a lab.
It was a home.
People lived here.
He had a family.
Is that what I smell?
The stench
of domestic harmony?
You ever wonder what
your life would have been like
if you had a family?
Hmm... No!
Maybe you wouldn't have gone
full supervillain.
I have no parents,
no aunts, no uncles.
And something about my attitude
renders me...
undesirable
to all possible genders.
My future is a cul-de-sac!
The Robotnik name ends...
avec moi.
Yes, I know French.
[shuddering spasm]
Whoa.
Is this where you grew up,
Shadow?
No wonder you're so mad.
This place could really use
a beanbag chair
and some comic books.
What happened here?
[hard grunt]
I'm tired
of giving you warnings!
[grunts, yells]
Where'd you go, hedgehog?
I wasn't finished
trauma dumping.
My darlings!
[inhales, giggles]
My eggy weggies!
[professor] ♪ Memories ♪
♪ Light the corners ♪
♪ Of my mind ♪
♪ Misty watercolor ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ Of the way ♪
♪ We weren't ♪
I...
don't believe it.
Don't you?
It's impossible.
Is it?
It couldn't be.
Couldn't it?
I'm--
Are you?
Imposter!
You stole my babies!
But they know
who their real daddy is...
drone-napper!
[chortling]
Magnificent creations,
my boy.
I borrowed them
to lure you here
and reunite our family.
You see, Ivo...
I'm your grandfather:
Gerald Robotnik.
My... grandfather?
But how? And why?
And who did what with whom?
You hail from an ancestry
of excellence...
tied directly à moi.
Yes, I know French.
You do look like me.
But fatter. And older.
And there's that funny smell.
But the resemblance
is uncanny.
It's as if...
[both]
...we're two characters
in a movie
being played
by the same actor.
But I need real proof!
Ivo!
We have very little time.
But I could field
a couple of queries.
Name the most elegant formula
in mathematics.
Euler's Identity.
E to the I times pi plus one
equals zilch.
European capitals
arranged alphabetically
by the fourth letter.
Riga, Monaco, Sarajevo, Tirana.
The speed of light
divided by
the speed of sound,
the speed of the bus
in the movie Speed.
[mimics adding machine]
17,893.33333...
Rounding up?
17,894 MPH.
And, for all the marbles...
Good. I lost mine.
A rare lung disease,
and the longest word
in the English dictionary.
Um...
[both] Pneumonoultramicroscopic-
silicovolcanoconiosis!
Pap-pap!
In the saggy flesh.
But looking pretty good
for a hundred and ten.
[shuddering grunt]
Oh, Grampy-poo! [laughs]
Where have you been
my entire life?
[moans happily]
[gasps] Wait.
Where have you been...
my entire life?
Locked in
a top-secret prison
for the last 50 years.
Made it kind of hard
to send Christmas cards.
Now...
you're probably wondering
why I brought you here.
You didn't bring me here!
I used my unparalleled intellect
to track you down.
Per the plan
I concocted with
my unparalleled intellect.
You'll see.
I have the answer
to everything.
Come on, kiddo.
[groaning]
Oh, no. Oh, no, no.
Someone tell me
this is some kind of
concussion-induced nightmare.
There's two Eggmen now?
Double your villains,
double your fun!
Two Robotniks
are way worse than one.
Chest bump?
No.
Stone,
why are you tied up?
Do that on your own time.
You sicken me.
You must be
the long-lost grandson.
And you must be
another stinking hedgehog.
So you're the one
behind all this.
The Shadow breakout.
The attack on Walters.
That musty
old-man smell.
How dare you insult me
with your unsolicited
exposition!
Shadow, get the key.
Where is it?
Ha! Good one, Hot Topic.
Do you really think
we'd be that stupid
to bring the key
right to you?
Yep, we're that stupid.
GUN took everything from us.
And now we are going
to take everything from them.
[Gerald] With this.
My masterpiece
of malevolence...
The Eclipse Cannon.
In exchange
for my freedom,
I gave GUN
the most powerful weapon
mankind has ever seen,
capable of delivering
a precision strike
anywhere on Earth.
Our first target:
GUN Headquarters.
But firing a weapon
that powerful
could threaten millions
of innocent lives!
Yeah, tera-bite me.
[cackles]
This is one of two keys required
to launch the Eclipse Cannon.
The other is locked
inside GUN headquarters.
Once we have both,
I will take rightful control
of my weapon.
I'm in.
Holy crab!
[Robotnik]
Spacious and crustaceous.
Thank you so much
for inspiring
this little adventure.
It really worked out
for me.
And you wonder why
I have trust issues!
Shadow, wait! Don't do this.
I know you're hurting,
but don't let that change
who you are inside.
I've spent 50 years
reliving what they did to her.
This is who I am inside.
Uh, nice magic marble.
Real scary.
[yelps] That actually
is real scary!
It's a mini black hole!
It's going to suck in
all the matter in this base!
[all yelling]
Fear not, friends.
Even my teeth are muscles!
[Sonic yelps]
[Knuckles growls]
Sonic, try to reach
one of my rings!
[Sonic] Got one.
Check this out. Trick shot!
[grunts]
Come on.
[Knuckles groans]
[both] Come on!
[yells]
[all yelling]
Yeah! Yes!
[Sonic] Yikes.
Somebody better call
Google Maps.
[rumbling faintly]
I've spent years
trying to cleanse
the cosmos
of that spiny,
blue speed freak.
And you did it...
in one afternoon.
There's nothing
we can't destroy
together, my boy.
Charting route to GUN
Headquarters in London, sirs.
ETA four hours.
As the crab flies.
By all accounts,
we're ahead of schedule.
We should take this time
to get to know
each other better.
Wow. What?
You mean...
spend some
qua-qua-quality time?
You've waited for this
your whole life.
How would you choose
to spend one perfect day
with your new grand pal?
[elbow thuds]
[grunts]
[both screaming]
["Wouldn't It Be Nice"
by the Beach Boys playing]
[bell dinging]
[yelps]
[wincing groan]
[shrieks happily]
Ooh! [chortling]
[rockets whistle and explode]
[song fades out]
[song resumes]
[song ends]
And done!
Masterpiece.
Look at that.
Yay!
It's really been great
having time to ourselves.
Right. Absolutely.
I just feel so...
relaxed, you know?
Clearheaded.
Mmm, look at all these
new interests we found.
I know, so many hobbies.
So many!
After the action and adventure
of the last few years,
well, I could get used to this.
Same.
[deep rumbling]
[Sonic] Tom! Maddie!
We need your help on a super--
Knuckles, do you mind?
Oh! Excuse me.
Tom! Maddie! We need your help
on a super-dangerous
top-secret mission!
Hmm.
Thank God. Yeah, we're in.
Let's go.
Really? You're in?
Just like that?
Yes. It was getting so boring
without you guys here.
Yeah. So...
No offense.
...boring. No, none taken.
I mean, whatever crazy plan
you're cooking up,
the answer's yes.
Yes.
Great. But first things first:
What is that?
Oh! This is...
[in puppet voice]
...Li'l Tom!
[normal voice]
Isn't he great?
I told you
to get rid of that.
It's very creepy.
[puppet voice]
I told him to get rid of you.
[normal voice]
Okay, that's, mmm...
crossing a line there.
You are in so much trouble.
Okay, this is it.
The belly of the beast.
GUN Headquarters in London.
[gasps] Tom, we're finally gonna
get to see London together.
Hey, I told you we'd
get there someday, baby.
Okay. So here's the plan.
I run in superfast,
fly over that water,
no problem,
and right when I get to the--
[shrieks]
What just happened?
Congratulations.
You just got incinerated
by their energy shield.
We'll need to shut it down
by planting a USB drive
in their server room
that will give me full control
over it.
That's what we need you two for.
Couple of badass spies,
that's what we are.
Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
[Tails] Once we
disable the shield,
you'll face the laser hall.
[grunts]
These high-density bad boys
will cut you into tiny pieces.
And cut those pieces
into even tinier pieces!
Once again... [shrieks]
Can't we just get Tom Cruise
to do this?
[Tails] Nope.
Because not even he
could break into... the vault.
[Sonic]
Why is it empty in there?
[Tails]
Because we have no idea
what's on the other side
of that door.
To prevent the vault from ever
being accessed by a ring,
all images and schematics have
been wiped from GUN's database.
So for the last leg
of this heist...
[in puppet voice]
...we're going in blind.
Sorry.
[Maddie] Okay,
I'm just gonna say it.
It sounds like this plan would
work a heck of a lot better
if Sonic used the Master Emerald
to go Golden God mode
to get the key.
No way, Maddie.
The Master Emerald
is too powerful
to ever use again.
We made a promise to each other
to keep it hidden.
In a location
only Knuckles knows.
As guardian
of the Master Emerald,
anyone who tries
to take it away
for any reason...
will become a sworn enemy.
Okay, okay! Sheesh!
No need to get
all growly on me, buddy.
You guys are always telling us
to make good choices.
Well, this is the right choice.
Okay.
I guess
we're going to...
["London Town"
by Mr Eazi playing]
London, baby!
GUN Headquarters
is right there.
Let me go in, get the key
and destroy anyone in my way!
I want revenge.
[Gerald]
Patience, Shadow.
Just let us handle this...
and I promise
you'll have revenge
on a scale you couldn't
possibly imagine.
Come on, Granddaddy-O,
we've got...
dirt to do!
Suits.
Right here, sir.
Stone, babysit the hedgehog.
Keep the crab on a low boil.
It's time
for more family bonding.
Come on, Shadow.
Got fresh avocados in the crab.
We'll make guac.
Revenge guac!
Guys, are you ready for me yet?
I've been waiting here all day.
Sonic,
we literally just started.
Tom, Maddie,
are you in position and ready?
We were born ready.
Let's do this.
[Tails]
Knuckles, how about you?
I have taken my perch
atop the giant clock.
Now, where is this glass
I'm supposed to break?
Actually, Knucks, your job
is to "Break Glass
in Case of Emergency."
Understood.
I will shatter this glass
like the jaw of a vile foe.
In case of emergency.
I will pulverize it like
the skull of a loathsome rival!
Just to be clear,
the "emergency"
is the important part.
The glass will beg for mercy
under the shadow
of my mighty fist!
Guys, remember,
we're a team.
Let's focus.
Please.
[Sonic] You know what?
Let's move on.
All right,
everyone knows what to do.
Tom and Maddie,
you guys plant the USB drive.
I'll disable the traps.
Sonic will snag the launch key.
And Knuckles, you stand by to--
Break glass in case
of emergency.
See? He gets it.
Then we're all set.
Hologram time.
You go first.
Tom, it's me, Rachel!
Can you believe it?
We're both in London together.
Have you met your sister?
Try again.
Unless...
you're not
up for this mission.
Yeah, maybe you want
to be back in Green Hills,
baking sourdough.
Thomas Michael Wachowski!
Gah!
You brought aliens
to my wedding,
punched out my husband
and buried me in an avalanche.
Your day of reckoning
is at hand!
Yeah, that's perfect.
Okay, now for
her better half.
Ho-ho, my name is Randall,
and I am too much to handle!
Welcome to the gun show!
Baby, would you describe me
as jacked, juiced,
or shredded?
I would describe your head
as swollen.
Let's get to work.
Agent Randall Handel.
I'm here to have lunch
with my lovely wife, Rachel.
[desk guard]
I'm sorry, Agent Handel,
this facility's
currently locked down.
Command-level
clearance only.
One minute.
Tails... we have a problem here.
Wow, they must have
tightened security
after Shadow's escape.
I got this.
You must be new here.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Rachel.
Rachel Gonnagetyoufired.
Do you know what GUN
stands for?
Well, 'course. Guardian Units--
[mimics buzzer]
Getting. Ultra. Nasty.
Do you want me...
to get ultra nasty?
Nasty nasty?
No, ma'am.
Okay, then.
Then go ahead and take
those little sad fingers
and start tippity
type-type-typing!
Mm-hmm.
That's right, go on.
Sorry for the inconvenience,
ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
That's what I thought!
My God,
I love being Rachel!
Did it work?
Oh, yeah.
Oh! Ouch!
Director Rockwell seeking
access to the server room.
Just one moment, ma'am.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
It's her. It's the real her!
The incident in Colorado?
We're still assessing.
What do you mean,
we're still assessing?
What do we do?
Quick, change faces!
Okay. Did it work?
Who am I? What's going on?
Why are you looking
at me like that?
What am I doing wrong?
[grunts] Ow!
Aye-aye, Captain!
"Aye-aye, Captain"?
Who are you, Popeye?
I panicked! I was panicking!
Jeez!
Get it together!
Okay, Tails,
what are we looking for?
The security server is
in the 7th row, 23rd cabinet.
Are you guys finished yet?
This is taking forever.
[people exclaiming]
[Sonic] Uh-oh.
Has the time come
to break the glass?
Or at least break something?
All right, hang tight, guys.
Maddie's about
to insert the drive.
Ready?
Three...
two...
one...
Go.
It didn't work.
Did you put it in
the right way?
Try punching it.
Do not try punching it.
Oh!
Take it out
and blow on it.
Yes!
Oh, come on, Tom.
There's absolutely
no scientific evidence
to support--
[machines thrumming]
Never mind. It worked!
Little trick
from the '90s.
I mean, best decade ever.
Right?
I'm shutting down
the outside sensors now.
Yes! Uh...
Hold on. Is...
there supposed to be
another USB drive here?
[Tom] One with a giant
mustache on it?
Oh, no.
I've got two heat signatures
en route to the vault.
Which can only mean...
The Robotniks
have entered the chat.
Wait.
Poppyseed?
Grand-geezer?
¿Dónde está?
I'm right here.
If you weren't family,
I could have gut you
like a pheasant.
I mean, try to keep up.
[narrator] And now back to
"La Última Pasión."
Última Pasión...
can only belong to one.
No.
It can only belong...
to Juan!
Gabriella should kill them both.
She's not a prize to be won.
"Kill this. Murder that."
You need to lighten up, Shadow.
We're about to rule the world.
When we're done...
there won't be
anything left to rule.
That is dark. Even for you.
What are you
and the professor up to?
Hello! What's this?
I knew I saw
an outside signal!
Cheerio!
I guess someone
forgot to flush.
[gasps]
[Stone screaming]
[both panting]
What now, my cunning cohort?
Just a little teamwork!
[yelping]
[wheezing gasp]
Hey...
The lasers...
don't seem to be
penetrating my suit.
They're conforming
to the shape
of my bodacious bod.
Of course.
I designed these suits
to create a field
of laser-bending
thermal distortion.
Wasn't sure it would work
till now.
You're heartless, son.
Hmm!
Rotten to the core.
Mm-hmm.
I'm...
so proud.
So now we can just dance
right through.
That sounds like a challenge.
[convulsive gag]
["Galvanize"
by the Chemical Brothers
playing]
[mouthing along]
♪ My finger is on the button ♪
♪ Push the button ♪
The Robotniks are almost
at the vault!
We're out of time. I'm going.
No, Sonic!
I haven't disabled
the traps yet!
Too late!
Look at me! I'm running
on the wrong side of the road!
Well, I got to take in
the sights.
Paul, John, George,
the other one!
Loud American coming through!
Excuse me. Pardon me.
'Ello, guv'nor!
Which way to Hogwarts?
Hear ye, hear ye!
Sonic the Hedgehog
wants a cuppa tea!
Hold this for me, please.
You're not gonna make it!
I can make it.
[Sonic] I'm gonna make it.
I'm not gonna make it.
I'm not gonna make it!
[Tails yells]
Made it!
Whoo!
Excuse me. Coming through.
No time for autographs.
Got to go, bye!
Our destiny awaits.
Stop right there, Roboscum!
Let's do this!
Copy!
[electronic throbbing]
[both grunting loudly]
Too slow, Eggmen.
Now if you don't mind,
I've got to get that key.
Whoa!
My feet. Why can't I
use my beautiful feet?
Heh-heh!
[Rockwell] Because...
this vault is armed
with variable gravity.
[straining]
No kidding.
[Rockwell] Green goes up...
and red takes you down... hard.
Rockwell, listen to me.
The Robotniks are planning to--
[yelps]
Oh, they're planning on stealing
a second key, just like you are?
Yes, I'm aware.
I called it
the second Commander Walters
was attacked.
So...
thank you
for taking the bait
and falling
right into my trap.
I don't believe this.
[Gerald]
I know, grandson.
A woman in the military!
Let's go.
Go, positions!
Full perimeter.
[weapons powering up]
Robotnik.
Going full spandex, huh?
Who's the fossil?
That's my grandfather,
you dough-eating dimbecile.
Who are they?
A couple of bleeding hearts,
here to rescue
their emotional-support animals.
Enough! It's over.
The only way
you're leaving here
is in handcuffs.
There is no other way out.
You know, there might be
one other way out.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
[Sonic] Hey, big guy,
I think it's time to...
Break glass
in case of emergency!
[roaring]
[grunts]
Ha! Nothing can stop
Team Knuckles!
Open fire!
[yelps] Knuckles,
turn this stuff off!
Hurry!
On it.
Uh-oh.
[all yelling in surprise]
[grunting]
Ha! See how you like it--
[groans]
[yelping]
[both gasp]
[all groaning]
Can you move?
No, not at all.
Tails, can you?
No, I'm stuck.
We might be here a while.
[growls, grunts]
Whoa! Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Where's the key?
Whoa!
What was that?
We might have a problem.
[grunts] No, no, no, no!
[grunting]
[exclaims]
[huffs]
I'm moving.
I'm moving!
You go get it, grandson!
Hey!
Oh, whoa, whoa...
No. No, no!
I'm almost there!
Whoa!
[groaning]
Sonic!
[gasps]
[all yelling, grunting]
[heavy grunt]
[yells]
That was so not worth it!
Ooh!
You okay?
Yeah. You good?
Sonic!
[Tom] Hey.
[groaning]
Sonic, one,
concrete boulder, zero.
[sighing]
Thanks for the save.
Cutting it a little close,
don't you think?
Secure the room!
She's got the key.
I got an idea.
Commander Walters.
Sir.
You're...
Still alive?
I'll die before I let that key
fall into the wrong hands.
Thanks for keeping it safe.
I'll take it from here.
That's an order,
Director Rockwell.
Now, organize
the reinforcements.
Yes, sir.
Guys, guys, I got the key.
I repeat, I got the key.
Now let's get out of here.
Commander Walters.
No, no. No. Wait!
What?
Tom! Everyone's clear!
Come on, let's go!
You. What are you--
Tom!
Tom. Tom, what happened?
Speak to me. Come on.
Come on,
it's gonna be okay.
Please, please, please get up.
Hey, come on, please wake up.
Wake up, wake up, come on.
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
Maria.
What did you do?
What I had to.
Oh, my God. Tom!
Help me up, kid.
[grunting]
Freeze! Don't move!
Any tricks up your sleeve,
Captain Grandtastic?
[soldiers grunting]
[terrified yelp]
We got what we came for.
Great job, Shadow.
We have both keys.
So where's your little
science project?
It's closer than you think,
my boy.
Welcome...
[yelps]
...to my masterpiece!
I must hand it to GUN.
They built her
to my exact specifications.
It's...
remarkable!
Mm-hmm.
Astounding!
Yes.
That's my genius grand-genome!
And I have one more surprise.
It's a new suit!
[giddy squealing]
[excited grunting]
Gee.
[smooching]
[grunting]
♪ I'm a chip
Off the old block ♪
♪ I'm a chip off
The old block! ♪
[ring tone chiming]
What do you want, Stone?
I'm busy.
Doctor, I have a bad feeling
about this.
I don't think your grandfather's
been completely honest with us.
It was something Shadow said.
There's more to their plan.
How dare you!
You have been jealous
of my long-lost grand-Pop-Tart
since the very beginning!
I no longer require
your obsequious groveling.
Consider this your notice
of termination.
Your letter of reference
will be L for Loser.
Of course,
I'll expect you to stay on
until you've been
successfully cloned.
But you and I are done!
Like a blackened
catfish dinner!
Sir, it's too dangerous and
I'm not there to protect you.
I already lost you once! I--
Unsubscribe.
Blocked and reported.
[breath shaking]
I can't lose you again.
[sighs]
Do the honors...
grandson.
Here we go.
[excited chatter]
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[siren wails]
It'll be okay, Sonic.
It'll be okay?
Tom is fighting for his life
and you think it'll be okay?
The fox is simply trying
to comfort you.
Comfort's not
what I need right now.
I need to stop them.
By any means necessary.
Wait, you don't mean--
The Master Emerald.
The Emerald must never be
wielded for vengeance.
Not ever!
We swore a sacred oath.
Don't talk to me about oaths.
Not now!
But you told Tom
using the Emerald
wasn't the right choice.
Well, now it's the only choice.
And if neither of you
have the guts to help me,
then I'll do it alone.
But I thought
the three of us
were a team.
I thought that's what
made us special.
I'm not asking you twice,
Knuckles.
Where is the Master Emerald?
Your heart is being consumed
by anger, hedgehog.
You are in no condition
to make decisions right now.
I know you're upset about Tom.
We all are.
Last chance.
Where... is it?
Don't do this.
Part of our oath
is to trust each other.
And I must abide
by that promise,
even if you have chosen
to break it.
But heed this warning:
The Master Emerald is guarded
by a fearsome warrior.
And to seize
this ultimate power,
you will have to go...
through him.
[exhales deeply]
Okay, Wade...
all comes down to this.
Last few seconds.
Whipple down the ice.
He shoots... he scores!
Wade Whipple
is a champion again!
[cackles]
Oh, hey, Sonic. See my goal?
Pretty sick, right?
I'm here for the Emerald.
Look, Sonic, I'm sorry.
I promised to guard this emerald
with my life.
I will do whatever it takes--
Well, I tried.
[thunder rumbling]
[Wade] Sonic!
Too bright!
[woman] This is an urgent
national emergency broadcast.
A spacecraft designed
by the agency GUN
has been hijacked and launched
out of the River Thames.
[man broadcasting in Japanese]
[man] All residents are urged
to seek immediate shelter.
[Gerald] It's time, Shadow.
Professor, is this really
what Maria would have wanted?
The question isn't
what Maria would have wanted.
It's what do they deserve.
Remember what she meant to us.
Remember what they took from us.
[Gerald] Kids!
We have to go, now!
[Maria panting]
[Gerald] They want to take
Shadow away from us, Maria!
[weapons charging]
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
Those are children.
We've got our orders, Walters!
Stand down!
[gasps]
[muffled rumbling]
[high-pitched whistling]
[groaning]
Huh?
Maria!
[angry roar]
[panting heavily]
Excuse me,
Grand Paso Doble.
What is that thermonuclear
gerbil doing?
[Gerald] Infusing the core...
with chaos energy.
That's my little secret.
The Eclipse Cannon
is about to turn this planet
into a flaming pile
of rubble,
wiping out everything
in a 25,000-mile radius.
Including us.
What?
We can't annihilate
the Earth!
Hmm?
By combining our genius,
we can rule humanity.
Together!
Humanity is a failed experiment.
If anyone should know that,
it's you.
All your life, you've been
rejected by this world.
You have nothing down there.
No one who cares about you.
But I have you now.
We're family.
We have each other.
Oh, Ivo...
you're no Maria.
The moment I lost her,
my family was gone forever!
The only way
to give Maria's life
meaning
is to destroy the world
that took her from me.
So I'm burning it all down!
It's done.
Good work, Shadow.
I'm prepping
the firing sequence.
The weapon will be fully charged
in ten minutes.
It's almost finished, Maria.
You will have justice.
[muffled, distant boom]
What is that?
Is GUN launching
missiles at us?
Impossible.
It's moving too fast.
It's him.
[wind whistling]
[both grunting]
You hurt my family.
This ends now!
Now you know my anger.
The pain I've felt
for 50 years.
And you've made
the same choice I did.
I'm nothing like you!
We'll see.
[both yelling]
Show yourself, coward!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[shouts]
[thunder reverberating]
You were right about one thing.
[straining]
This ends now.
[both grunting]
What's happening?
Where are they?
Up there.
Where?
Higher.
Hmm?
[shocked gagging]
Left yourself open.
Ivo! What are you doing?
Thwarting your evil plan!
[both howling in pain]
Not the mustache!
Agreed.
Let go on three.
One, two, three!
[whiskers flapping]
[beeps]
[mocking]
Oh... a nano-fist.
I haven't seen that
since I hate-watched
Green Lantern in 2011.
I was saving it for Comic-Con.
But now there won't
be a Comic-Con!
[yells]
[both grunting]
[dust settling]
Why are you alone?
Where are your friends?
[straining]
They tried to stop you,
didn't they?
But you came anyway.
Your anger was too much.
What kind of hero
abandons his friends
to pursue revenge?
Abandons his family!
Don't you dare talk
about my family.
And here I thought
you cared for them.
Especially the one...
What's his name?
Tom?
[angry howl]
[Sonic yelling]
[gasps]
[strained panting]
Go ahead. Finish it!
What are you waiting for? Do it!
[grunting]
I'm right here!
You didn't let your pain
change who you are...
in here.
[whimpering sigh]
This is not who I am.
What are you doing?
You won. Take your revenge.
There are no winners
with revenge.
[Maria] Wow.
[voice echoing]
Look at all those stars.
They're like diamonds.
The last time I sat
beneath stars like this...
I was with her.
I've felt this pain for so long.
It's all I know.
When I lost Longclaw...
I felt the same way.
Did your pain eventually
go away?
No.
But in time,
I learned there's something
even more powerful than pain.
The love we felt for each other.
That's what you need
to hold on to, Shadow.
Maria might be gone,
but your love
will always remain.
"The light shines
even though the star is gone."
[cannon rumbling in distance]
This whole mess
is my fault.
I've been so blinded by rage,
I thought...
I had no choice.
You always have a choice.
But making the right one
is never easy.
One more thing I learned
is that when you
really screw something up,
you can't fix it
on your own.
["Live and Learn"
by Crush 40 playing]
Gotta go fast.
Don't tell me you've
got a catchphrase.
That's right, new hedgehog.
And everyone loves it.
I... will... not... try...
[grunting]
...to stop... my...
elders... from...
destroying... the... world!
[screams]
Playtime is over.
There's no going back now.
[wheezing grunts]
Set up defense.
Damn you, autocorrect!
[attacking grunt]
[shouts]
Mantis!
Oh!
[cackles]
Whee!
[hissing growl]
I'm right here,
arach-nerd.
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[cackles]
That's what I call
mantis-scaping.
That's elder abuse!
[exclaims]
[female computer voice]
Alert! Alert! Alert!
Shadow...
I see you've chosen betrayal.
And you were once
so useful to me.
Ready to recycle
some tin cans?
Just try to keep up.
[Robotnik]
Please, Grampsy,
don't do this!
Sorry, kiddo.
Bring Your Grandkid to Work Day
is over.
[device beeping]
[air whistling]
[yelping]
Any last words?
Just one thing...
that I never thought I'd say.
What is it?
"I love you"?
No.
It was something even better.
But I'm not gonna say it
if that's the way
you're gonna be.
Okay. Bye.
[screaming]
[cackling]
[hissing inhale]
[happy grunt]
Grandchildren.
All the fun
and none of the responsibility.
Who said life was pointless?
Huh?
Oh, right. You did.
[growls]
[electricity buzzes]
[screams]
[faint zap]
[Tails, Knuckles cheering]
[Knuckles] Victory!
Say what you want
about my granddad,
he made one
hell of a bug zapper.
[groans softly]
We got to stop that laser!
I knew there was something
I was forgetting.
We're out of time.
The cannon is about to fire!
Where are you?
Oh, you know,
just making friends.
They're all yours.
[laughing]
[Sonic] Follow me!
Now, this might hurt a little!
[all exclaiming]
So this was your plan?
[straining] Yeah...
Would someone mind
shutting down
the giant death ray?
We can't stop the cannon
from firing...
But we can steer it away
from the Earth.
Coming around to starboard.
Aye-aye, Doc.
Here we go.
[Tails grunting]
[Robotnik] It's a little tight.
Definitely not power steering.
Keep... turning.
[straining]
Jump in anytime here, guys!
[all straining]
[steady beeping]
Can't... hold... much... longer.
[all yelling]
[exhausted groan]
[groans]
Yes!
[cheering]
I did it! I did it!
Oh!
Ooh!
Look what you did!
Hey, look down there!
Sonic!
Oh, Knuckles,
please tell me you have a--
Last one.
Let's make it count.
Ready for a little base of ball?
Deep breath.
One... two... three!
[Knuckles grunting]
[yells]
[shocked yell]
Really!
What's happening?
The reactor core is overloading.
It's only a matter of time
before it blows.
So what does that mean
for Earth?
A radioactive atmosphere.
Rain that kills the crops
and melts your flesh.
Other than that...
We're not done here!
You try to stabilize
the reactor.
Buy me some time.
I'll push the station
away from Earth
before it explodes.
This is our last chance
to do the right thing.
[in Spanish]
[female computer voice]
Core integrity failing.
I've got you, Sonic!
[gasps]
[moans]
[straining]
[computer] Initializing
reactor core stabilizers.
This is Doctor Ivo Robotnik,
dedicating my final livestream
to one very special henchman:
Agent Stone.
No, no. Doctor, wait!
If I can't
rule the world...
I might as well save it...
for the one and only person
who ever cared about me.
Don't do this, Doctor, please!
Stone, you were more
than a sycophant to me.
You were...
a syco-friend.
I'll miss your lattes
with steamed Austrian goat milk.
I love the way you make 'em!
So... I guess there's
only one thing left to say.
[mimics robotic servos]
It's been a real drag.
Thanks for nothing.
[birds chirping faintly]
[coughing]
Sonic, look.
Shadow and Robotnik.
They sacrificed
themselves...
to save everyone.
You always have a choice.
Guys, I'm really sorry
for running off like that.
I shouldn't have
left you behind.
The truth is...
you're the best teammates
a hedgehog could ever ask for.
And the best friends.
Can you ever forgive me?
Team Sonic?
[Sonic]
How about just "team"?
Goodbye, Doctor.
[Sonic] Big finish.
[Knuckles] Mmm!
Now that's
what I call teamwork.
Okay! It's ready!
[munching]
[gasps]
Knuckles,
how could you?
Gotta be faster than that!
Give me a break.
Still moving a little slow
over here.
Donut Lord!
Yay!
[pained groan]
Okay, Knuckles, that's...
I am having the love.
[barks]
[Tails] Aww...
Get in here, Ozzy.
It's great
to be back together.
We're stronger than ever.
And nothing is gonna
stand in our way.
Except that one piece
of unfinished business.
And way out in front, to the
surprise of absolutely no one,
it's the Blue Blur!
Often imitated,
never duplicated,
the one, the only...
[yells]
Let's do this!
Yeah! [laughs]
[yells]
All right, boys,
try and keep up.
[all cheering, whooping]
["Run It"
by Jelly Roll playing]
Sonic the Hedgehog
is Family Champion once again!
Tails?
Knuckles?
Okay. Yeah, I overshot
the finish line.
[electronic whirring]
[Sonic] Okay,
so how do I get back?
[weapon powering up]
[beeping]
[Sonic] Pro tip:
If you're gonna take a shot
at the fastest creature
in the universe...
you'd better not miss.
Um... I'm flattered
by the cosplay,
but you got
a few details wrong.
I can't blame you, though.
It's hard to copy perfection.
That's a neat trick.
[Sonic yelps]
What? Who are you?