Ambon, 18 February 2020
"Sonic the Hedgehog"
by ARJUKEN27
So I know what you think
Why is the hedgehog so handsome being chased?
by a madman with a mustache from the civil war
To be honest, it feels like I've run
all my life, is this too much
Am I too fast?
I do, you know what
let's step back
This is the island where I come from
That's all there, beach
sandy, terraced waterfalls
General access to loop de loop
And I don't need to catch a school bus, because of me
can run around the island in less than two seconds
Also no school, me
know, beautiful island right
Hey / I was born with outside power
usual, I was told to keep it a secret
And like other children, me
do the opposite
That's Long Claw, he takes care of me
He was consciously obiwan kenobi,
if Obiwan Kenobi has a beak
Sonic, someone can
saw you / Nobody saw me
I'm too fast, and me
want to bring you this3
Get down
Apparently with great power, followed
with criminals with great strength
And I guide them
right at us
Listen carefully Sonic
You have no strength like
whatever i've seen
And that means someone
will always want
The only thing to stay safe
is to stay hidden
This world is at the end
far from the universe
You should be safe there / I'm not
Want to leave without you / You must
This ring will be your item
the most valuable
If you ever have
found, use one
Never stop running
Now leave
Long Claw
No
I have one car
Hey man! Where's the fire
There are kids living around here
That's kind of funny, sorry
What
Tom, we need you on your way
Maine, there's a gang shot
Just kidding, ducks steal bagels
But they need help
Hi guys
You almost got killed out here, what
You are some kind of adrenaline junkie
It must be hard to be slow all the time
I'll tell you what, today
is your lucky day
Have you ever felt so alive
This is good, you're good
Gosh
Good recovery
Let's make this
our little secret, okay
You have never seen me
I've never been here
So what do you expect?
Small dirty hedgehog
Eat berries struggling to survive
Think again, because I live
my best life on earth
I have a library
And the most advanced security system
Oh no
And if I've ever been found, me
will follow the long claw instructions and
use my ring for
escape to a new planet
The beautiful small world is safe
filled only with mushrooms
Disgusting and smelly mushrooms
Mushroom
Let's not worry about it all
This is Green Hills
The best place on earth
These are my people,
and I dare say
I am a creature
their favorite sky
Then what if they are
didn't know i existed
My favorite person is Lord Donuts
Protector of this city
And defenders of all large creatures
and small / good morning
Hello Daisy Dapne
Lord Donuts lives with Pretzely
He is super good with animals, and
strangely born without a bulge
Ouch, ouch, ouch
There is one person who doesn't like me
I think it's because of the blue devil / me
almost caught him last night
Say hello to Crazy Carl
We are happy to be together
I know you're out there!
I know you are real!
No, I'm not!
The night's stay is my favorite
Please, please, please
Yes, Keanu
You were a national treasure when I found it
yourself / Oh, stop the champ
There is a bomb on the bus / Sudden Quiz
hotshot, classic sentence
Basically we are like family
Although we have not met
You don't think of your isolation
make you a little crazy
Crazy I No, you're wrong
And rule out whose name
'' friend '', deep inside
You're still a bit lonely
Maybe afraid you will
alone forever
Hey
No, no
Down there, come on, come on
Get out of there, get out
from there you are an intruder
Betty as a veterinarian
most respected on green hill
What is the fastest way to
destroy raccoons
What is that
What is like that
I think / Uh-huh, okay
That's rather small, is that bad? Just open it
Dear Thomas, we have reviewed
your proposal to the San Francisco Police Department
And after the review and
background check
We are happy to tell you, you have
selected to join our team
Oh god / Wow
Oh god / bye
Sanfransisco sucks
False
Cistern
You never have doubts, yes / No.
I don't believe this / You did it
What is that
Apartments for rent,
I found it on zilla
I think Ozzy and I can fly there
tomorrow and look at the surroundings
This happened that fast
Ah, that's the craziest thing, you applied
the work, you get the work
Background check
pending back
Don't think I don't know the time
you use neighbor's wifi
Correction, I still use the wifi
Are you sure it's okay with this
Tell Mr. Wachowski
What do you do all the time
I'm in veterinary school
I'm doing a second job to pay
rent and / Jobs to pay spp
You sacrifice for me, me
happy to sacrifice for you
Beib, you sure you're okay with this
I mean there's Wachowski protecting
this city more than 50 years
This is a big change
I'm positive
Time for this person to come out
and prove himself
I like greenhouses, but you know
I want to help you with a problem
Someone will need me in a life situation
or die and I will be there for him
I understand, I'm very proud of you
Thank you
So with a heavy heart I tell you I have
accept a position in the San Francisco police department
Effective immediately
This will be hard for the city
my hometown, and all my friends
But this is something that I am
think I need, to grow
As an officer
And a man
What do you think, pretty cool
Not so bad, right
All I have to do is
Tell everyone who needs donuts
Wow, the match
Very cool
Tonight's score and draw
exactly who you want
With victory at stake, sonic
And from pitcher pitcher
the most terrible
softball ball on Green hill, also sonic
If you win this match you will
will be the most player in green hills
Hit to the left, he's really bad
Oh, I can not
Come on sonic
I did not get it
Wait
Come on
Secure
Oh yes, yes, yes, I did it
You see that, I've done it
I did it
I really am alone
Alone, forever
I'm sure nobody noticed
that giant blue explosion, right?
Hi Wade / Hi Tom, wade
here, what happened
I think the electricity is off / Electric
extinguished, the whole city panicked
What should I do / Okay,
calm down, take a deep breath
Call Gill, see if he can
find a channel that goes out and
Call Jen to see if she can
bring the generator to the station
Call Tim before Gill
Call the team / I will
call you back
Okay, fine, you can take care of this
What is the first thing he is
say to do
Right, calm down
40 minutes ago
The surge of energy turns off electricity
throughout the Pacific Northwest
What do we know / guess
our first is EMP
But electromagnetic waves
has no power like that
Nasa has ruled out attacks
meteor or solar incandescent
The energy department says it's not
power plant malfunctions
Sounds very good to us
in knowing what that is
That could be the beginning of a bigger attack, I think
we have to send regiments 5 and 6 / No, no
This requires a more complicated mind
Someone who understands technology / We send
lab rat / Not lab rat carelessly
Lab rats with teeth
You're not suggesting who I think you are
suggest / I know he's a little weird / Strange / No.
He is horribly terrible
psychology / But he's also brilliant
5 Phd, and lQ cross the line and
he's revolutionary drone technology / You
sure he can overcome this
He has a record of perfect surgery
Remember the coup in Pakistan / No.
Or the algabanistan / lt's rebellion
not even country / Exactly
And you can be grateful
on Robotnik for that
I can't believe you brought that madman
in this case / I don't either, but
We have no choice
Are you in charge?
here / Yes, I do / Not
False I am the authority
His name / Major
You never say
this before, this is top
The world is full of hungry little monkeys
I will clarify it
-
Agent Stone / Doctor says you're basic
I run the sweeping order
10 miles in all directions,
that should be enough
He still sees me funny
Yes / Tell him to stop, or I'll check
its history / If you don't stop seeing a doctor
I'm not deaf
And tell him to
report to me, blah blah blah
Excuse me, listen bro, I don't know what
You realize / I'm sorry, major, what's your name
Bennin / Nobody cares
Nobody cares, listen
Major, nobody cares,
nobody cares who you are
Because no one cares
with your poor achievements
And no matter how much
proud of your mama, now you're level 3
You have completed Charlotte's web
spoiler warning, he died in the end
This is very scary
Ah, my children
See what comes out
from my egg bag
You know what I like about machines
They do as they are told,
they follow their program
They don't need time off
to get drunk with friends
You do as you are told
Stand there, at the end
your personal hole
and watch my machine do your work
You can feel Stone
I can feel it doctor
This is evolution
Stone agent / doctor
You see something
useful in this picture
There is no doctor at all
Of course you don't, your eyes are trained to
find traces of native american wolf shadows
That's amazing / No.
What is extraordinary is
I determine the exact weight
From this creature
And my computer could not find
any match anywhere
In the animal kingdom of the earth
This power outage is not an attack
terrorist and that's not a big foot baby
This person, this is something else
Fully
Switch the search unit to the footprint
That's a small step for humans
One big jump for me
OK, OK, everything's fine
You play baseball, get a little angry, thunder
shot your ass, and now they come for you
Fine, fine, the earth is no longer safe
It's time for plan B, the mushroom world
I have to bring my stuff.
okay, just important stuff,
OK, toothbrush, toothpaste,
hair gel, cute hat
This catalog
My entire comic collection
Leave the backpack
No, of course not, that's stupid
OK, what else
The ring, of course
Here it is, its time,
mushroom planet, here I come
Oh no, they are outside,
I have to go somewhere else
Hi / Hey / What are you doing
Coloring with Jojo and Rachel / Oh,
that sounds fun
There is something interesting here,
we have a power cut
The whole city is darkened
His behavior is like a sign to me, tell me
I have to get out of here / Wade must be crazy / Yes
He doesn't have much to lose
How is your sister She already
convince you to leave me /
No, but he told me to check
your phone for a dating application
Stupid Apps on my phone
Because you're there / You're family
Impossible
The raccoon is back
They are ready for a surprise / You're surprised,
it shouldn't be a tranquilizer gun
They are just hungry, and
also not for bears
Good, I know / Tom / I'm kidding, me
will only use it to scare him
Maybe to death,
okay baby, bye / Tom
I entered, with minimum damage
Here it is, it doesn't work
on earth, never mind
You will safe world, safe world filled with
mushrooms, mushrooms that will be your only friend
That sounds bad, me
can't do this
You have to do this,
There are no other options
Well
SFPD! Background check!
Paws in the air
Miaw
San
Fransico
What
Blue Devil
Donut Lord / You can talk
You do not
You're not here to
kidnapped me, right? You kidnapped me
Okay, that's a fair point, what are you
Why are you hiding in my garage / me
need somewhere safe
And you're the only person I can think of, donut lord / Why
You keep calling me donut lord / Because you talk to donuts
I need that to get out
Fair / Wait, where are all the mushrooms
Why am I still on earth
No, I lost my ring / What
Is this your aircraft carrier
Not in the mood for that / You think
I see, I don't even wear pants
They are coming for me / Who is coming
for you, what does that have to do with me
I don't have time to explain, but
You have to help me / No, I don't
Why / My legs are normally classified
as a deadly weapon, it feels like spaghetti
I need your help, please
This is life or death
Okay, come with me
Uh, hello
Fine, stay here, and don't
noisy / Good plan, great plan
We have worked well together, practically
finish each other's sentences
I hope you are right
Hello there
I can help
Good morning my friend
I'm from the electricity company.
investigating blackouts
If you don't mind, I want to
take some reading at your house
That's right, you're from the electricity company
You must know my friend Spencer,
we play softball together / Spens
He's a good guy
Yes, yes, please come in / OK
Take all the readings
you need, except
Electricity company took
reading from outside the house
They can check it
Also my friend Spencer works
for gas companies
Prefer fressbee, so
You want to tell me why
You think I'm stupid enough to
let you into my house
Sorry, Mr. Wachowski
You better call me Tom
Unless my dentist calls me Tim
He called me that long ago,
it would be strange if I corrected him
Tom, the dentist called Tim
You probably know this whole city has
experienced a power outage
Yep, there's no light, I know that
20 minutes ago, I tracked the anti-pulse, with
a similar sign that caused the damage
Listen, uh, sir. Doctor
Robotics doctor
But my dad calls me Rob
Listen from Robotnik
I'm sure this is very serious, but
has nothing to do with me, you
can ask everyone in the city
Everyone knows me / I know
Maybe one day you
will achieve your goal
get the card
But the truth is
I passed everything you would do
before I was a toddler
I made a formula while you
still spewing formula milk
I was breastfed actually / Good
Rub it on the face of my orphan
Mr. Wachowski, are you familiar
with US code 904 title 10 article 104
No / Whoever
Anyone who tries to help the enemy
The United States will suffer
And I will catch you
And that will be worse
Worse than death
I'm a ball, just a normal ball,
blending with other balls
Shut up sonic / You're the shut up Sonic
I hope they don't scan me with
xray, I have a shameful lunch
Don't be afraid
Over here
Why don't you use the carpet
Yes
Maybe just the ceiling of the house,
nothing can be seen here
This is the problem
I was never wrong
Uh, there's first time
for everything i guess
I think raccoons have the cleanest mouths
of all animals that eat rubbish
look at that
I am right
Not surprised
We try this again
I'll give you five
seconds to tell
where am I Lima?
What are you talking about / Four / Hey
champ, I'm a cop
You threaten the officer / How are you
threatening someone who never existed
Three
Come on, use your brain
You might find it
poor excuse to continue living
And two, one! Wait!
Don't hurt him
This feels excessive
Still behind me
Do not worry, I get
He is exactly where I want him
You can trust we will
deliver the package with this thing
This is a plan
bad, what am I thinking
We gotta get out of here / Oh
don't tell me that
That's all you have, I'm just getting started
Doctor
Are you OK? Yes
I saw a man run out of
Here, I think / You have to stop them
Open your mouth
and say you think you are
must stop them
No, I think maybe I should
check see you're fine
You know what it's hard to be
the smartest person in the world
Good, you got it
Whatever the creature is, that's a task
us to secure it
Neutralize it, find
the source of his strength
And if it's against
We destroy, piece by piece
See what makes it tick
Doctor, optical telephone
Tell me I need a new frame
They know what that is
Oh
Bring the porcupine thorn
Alright guys
You have to talk now, who are you
What are you / I hedgehog, I guess that's clear
And I'm in big trouble
You're in big trouble, you don't hit
Government freaks behind there
You think your problem, I lost
My ring / Ring, what are you talking about / Okay
The ring is how all civilization
sophisticated international travel
And mine above
the sharp one that's only me
look in your tight shirts
So I want you to take me
to San Francisco for me
can get my ring back
and go to the planet mushroom
Mushroom Planet / Yes
Right
Okay buddy, come out / Sorry, what
Listen, this is the worst time
got me in trouble okay
You want me to save
you, I saved you
Now please, go search
your ring, and your mushroom soil
I hope I will wake up
on a hospital bed
And the doctor will tell me, my surgery
was a big success, so goodbye
Okay, bye / bye
Why don't you go / I don't
know where Sanfransisco is / West
West / Straight, you can't
miss it / Good, that's cool
I'm really cool to say
bye now
So, when I fell
in Pacific cold water
I realized a few things
I don't know where I'm going
B salt water smell
C I shouldn't be on this planet
now, but I am there, why
Because you shot me / I know
You shoot me
I heard you first
Just pile / I'm wet
I'm cold there is a fish in my head
And obviously I can't
do this alone
Really you will help
Me / Get in the truck
I think it's my fault, this happened
/ Not all of you
That's all your fault / What
Yes
Travel
What do I do
Well, there will be rules on this trip, number
one do as I say every time
Ready / Please stop it
with mister donut
I have the name Tom
I'm Sonic / Sonic
So you spy on us for years
don't say it's a spy
We just hang out
only I was not invited
And nobody knew I was there / Me
Can not believe, there is every moment
You should be called super observation
Come back and stop it
the car now / what
The biggest rubber ball in the world,
we have to see it / No.
No, this is not a trip
that's fun okay
The government must be your digest,
and catch me, this is serious
You're right, that's bad
cool / I got your stuff
How do we get there?
there, when you arrive
Check what happened
You will see Wade with a glass object
that, what is that, teleportation box
This is a paid telephone
Just do this, just us
Stay in the car, no
anyone saw you
Well
Okay, this is the coolest place in the world
You have to stay there
Remain strong
Hello
Wayne it's me / hi
Someone asked a question
to me, a little scary
Like remind me of Man In Black
But not handsome
What kind of question is that
Question about
Terrorist / I told him
He doesn't know to make a bomb
Wait, listen, this is very important, don't
tell anyone we talk okay
I guess he already knows
Mr. Korosky
I want you to know, people
hit my face
Son
He beat me at the cafe for small wounds
Embarrassing me, in front of the school,
and you know what I'm responding to
I assume you reported to the officer
You know that's unacceptable
I tested world efficiency
Use technology for
solve inefficient efficiency
That's a straw for a year
And I never tried again
To this day
Hey / No you're going to be bullied
I did not come for you sir
Hello / hello
You may / Actually he's closed
Because I know / Thank you
Wait / No
You just sit there / don't bother
Less
Nobody erases my memory here
I won't talk to people like that
This clearly helps you
Sonic
Hello, colleague
Let's go / You want your partner
Glad to see his mustache / Come on get up
If we stay, I promise I won't
take another word on the trip, start
Welcome, what?
that I can serve
Natcho, and beef, lots of it
Hey kids are not allowed here
Hey he's 43 years old actually
Suffer
That's for one
Hey / The one I was born
I take it on the side
Road / Make sure the yellow place
Okay / You're only one
Very good look at this
This is spinning
Wow music
Check is a big night for you
What is the bouquet list?
List of what you are
do in your life
Kick the bucket / I'm not
kicked the bucket too
I have to make my life
Uh, uh
Sonic
There are a lot of things that me
never do
I will not be forever
I just missed my chance
I think this is the place
You live in a short dream
We can at least share what
You will list the bucket with me
Of course why not / You
will not regret this
I am sure
Yes
Is he not much or anything
That's easy
Great
Wow
Yes cheer up / Good romero
I have a good time.
what could be his fault
Uh
We can help you
I don't like types
like you / what type are we
Hipster / I challenge you
Hey you know, we want to
go away / it's ok
No, we go / I know
how to handle this situation
Oh
You were just about to fight with
hedgehogs disguised badly
Who watched a lot of films
action, what are you doing
Give it back
Uh, I guess
Please / Sorry
Oh come on / Hey Dalton right / Come on
Okay, who's next
Who wants it
Stay right there
You
Really
How are you
We must get out of
here / Yes time to go
Extraordinary
I want to do this
See you later
Attention, red light
Oh yes / yes
You're so great / okay
I really like him
Do you see a lot
that, close to the toilet
The floor is very tight
There is no stopping
Rub my list
You know this
Okay / so what do we do now
I watch tv
You have to do this / last
time I've heard
I want every second
And you can do it in this room
Time
Come on
That's how bad you eat
Spicy hot dogs
Check your fur, buddy. Okay
Hey, this is the next thing you should like
Inappropriate / I can tell you
Nobody is just mushrooms and stuff
Let's make it like this
See someone nice
No, don't ever do that again
I like it
I messed this place up
I know we have to go, the earth will
safer / But what if wrong
Maybe I can have a life here
Hey / You have to sleep
You sleep / Don't worry about me,
I will stay awake all night
Enjoy the earth while I can / Sure kid
Same to know
That's him
accused of domestic terrorism
Wachowski is dangerous
And there is information about him
What did he say where he went
Maybe
Maybe not, as you say
Sit agent
Don't understand about
the importance of this meeting
Yes
That's what I call it
good and bad cops
Cheer yourself up
Rate it approx
Fasten the vehicle / Local weather
This should be it
Still in
Here
That's smart sir / Thank you
Help me
So what's on your bucket list / me
Yes everyone has a bucket list right / Yes
You who left earth and
Not clear
Oh don't be sure
Your best friend is a magnet for danger
I mean / I like you
Of course, but we are not best friends
You put me in last night
Okay, that's animal friend. Okay
Embarrassing conversation topic
Bucket list gives
Okay / here's the thing
I always feel
I don't know, like a nanny
than the original police
So I will prove it to myself
At high pressure, move to san
Francis became a street cop
And, why not, look
what i got
Right / You leave Greenhills
Okay / But why
Why did you leave Greenhills
You must understand
small town greenhills
Not small, there are hundreds
people / it's a small town dude
It's a perfect city and people need you
Help me clean, and can call
someone else to do that
Of course they can call
anyone but they don't
They call you
Cup chip stamp
Mayhem
You don't make sense / you come
People about me / Zeroman
will kill you
What is more important
Tell the people you care about
I am indeed
You know what, I'm wrong about you
Not saying, you are more like
stop it
I was forced
Hey, this is perfect and you
leave / Why did you do that
Okay / wait, don't wait
We will do this
Sonic
This is lucky
Yes dear, Sonic is running
Sorry
Don't know see you dance / Yes you dance
That's all you have / Wow
thanks for asking
Sonic
You come / I'll go
I think there's a baby
That's my turn
Hey stop fighting,
keep that stuff / Okay dad
Just get / drive the car
I take care of this
To me, see what we get
Back to my life, today
Move aside
Hey we made it
We don't / Who is this person
Never thought where / my turn
Straight ahead
That's Vin Diesel
Saran
With your body / Hey
Where did you learn from / here
That happens when we speed up
Could not reach it,
bring it closer / What
Closer
Oh you mean this / Yes
Give it to me
That's sweet, let's keep this
We will be very bad
You have that trick right
Move aside
That doesn't sound good / Get rid of it
Remove from the window / Me
turn off / okay pull over
What i got
Closer / That's the way
It's still here
Keep away from me
Sonic
You are ok
Tell him
Do we get him?
Oh no
There are survivors in this city
We are
To the wall
I won't need you
Humans cannot be relied on, and are stupid
But my genes are great
They are everything to me
Your eyes
You are right
No
I contacted the FBI
Don't do it / okay get it
You're all over the news
I'm trying to contact you
Try to trap me / what
JoJo
Now your niece
Betrayed / Are you happy / You're calm
Not calm / Enough
See / No.
Oh, my God
What is plutonium? Yes
Please come / Stop / Me
already told you
He is not good
Catch me Jojo
Gratitude
Every last word
I think you want latte
I like what
Of course I want to be late
Prototype ready
This power is the engine
Finally able to reach its potential
Will be alright
It will be OK
I know Tom, what am I?
look here / She is a hedgehog
He said / He spoke
Jeez / Super fast pulse
Like it's normal for him
I didn't know you had to
help me / I don't know
He looks just
How messed up
Look at his poor feet
I'm here buddy you
will be alright
Jojo
Let go, jojo
Let go / mother / darling
Jojo
I go to the bathroom
He will be fine right
Beat this and wake up soon
Who smells it, what
she is there for cats
Or ditch / No.
I should / I have humans
In my first aid kit
Here it is
Come on buddy
What year are you / buddy?
Hi girl / Calm down
Quiet
May I speak to you please
Stay there / I'm great
Still talking / May we
there is a short time
To know how deep
his control / extraordinary
That's what we call / Thank you
Second
What ig happened / So
You remember the carl crazy talking
then about blue devil
That's it, she's real
What are you doing in
Here What / lt's like
Shoot our blue friend
with your stun gun
I don't mean, this is for
I can't explain it
And this is a little crazy
He has to go to the American building,
I'm sure I can bring him
Matty
Your husband is crazy, use us as
the chance to leave him
So that your feet don't hurt anymore
Really / Yes
Nobody gave me
gift to me before
And check on my bucket list
OK, looks OK
Okay
You said you said people
in trouble right
That's what you do
Blue hedgehog aliens, and
Countless people
Yes / Yes
Okay
I love you, did anyone say
I don't deserve you, you know that
I do not know
So
You should be Tom's best friend
won't stop, about that
I did not see
That is very dirty
Hey / hey / so
You think the younger siblings can
we borrow the car
You must be kidding me
It will be fine / Yes
That's my house
Hear
Sorry
You didn't get hit
Why do we let / I get
here, 5 star please
So here it is / That's it
Wow / What is that / What
is happening now
Oh he goes
Not good, you need a key
Special for the roof
What now
Time for me to abuse it
the power that is trusted by me
We have a jumper on the roof / Think
Montana
Yes it is serious
You just saved our lives
How much longer, me
can't stand it here
Hello there is someone there
Your child is in that bag
No, yes it's a child
but not mine
Not your child
Relax I'm a cop, he is
love it there, buddy
Why I like it here, at
here worse than before
Children
Is anyone there
What did you keep in this bag
A pickle jar
Okay, what are we looking for
Here it is
Okay what is happening now / Now
I have to do
Think about where the ring appeared
and I throw / Just like that
We did it / Yes
Sorry we didn't make it all in
Your bucket list / It's OK
I do what I want most
You both
Very sweet / What / No.
We are not sweet / we are missing children
live by your own rules
Exactly / Really / Yes
and our rules
Includes emotion sensor / If
you said so
Okay then fine
You will go / We must
Go too. Okay
One more thing
I'm sorry I was very rude to you
I know it was a tough decision
to leave me
Get away from something you care about
It must be very painful
Really you want to go
I don't want to go
But I cannot stay
As long as I'm here, me
for dangerous people
I can't do it
I just want you to know
these past two days
It has been two days
the best of my life
I will miss you
I miss you too
Terimakaish / For what
To save my life
Okay, someone left the cellphone
Welcome to
Sanfrancisco, Mr. Wokosky
I enjoy
It's a government man
who tried to kill us
Unsuccessful / Yes, what will you do
It's a flight suit
Designed for my body temperature
Subtract / Oh yeah he's still / The good one
You're fired Thomas
Oh hot talk, I take a lot
Does he have a name or us?
call him severe destruction
Hey watch your mouth
You want to get more
than I gave
Time / Hajar on his face
Amazing / Talk time over
Time to press the button / You
that fly is impressive
Sir is right, let's face it
Never chase me / Confidence
Stupid people change for intelligence
That's not good
Sonic
You can be super fast, and not survive
Maybe it will explode / Yes
Don't worry, I know
What to do
I did not expect this
I didn't expect it, so it doesn't count
Come on
Oh
Hi glad you're on
here / Can I ask for help
Oh he will be born
Genius advice
Do not run
It will get worse if you do
And bad for you / Okay
You want it fast
Come on, quickly
The hard way is indeed
That's illegal anyways
So here it is again, we've been through
very much together
Now you understand why there is a doctor
crazy robot chasing super sonic hedgehog
Want to know what it is / Yes you too
How could it be
Yes ma'am
Yes, here it is
I cannot lose him
Can't beat him, me too
Contact
You are alone there
This is from 7 miracles
You are an extraordinary little creature
It will be fun to bring you
back to the lab, for the procedure
There is the last word
Damn
I must say
to you / it was made possible
You are very selfish
You think you are
Don't know you / Damn
Auto pilot adjust
Why
Why did you waste your life for this
Think that's why I don't have friends
Next thing you know, best friend
and there is a wedding in the city
Like no one
do better
And where are we? Oh yeah
You will die
I'm sorry, Sheriff
Devil Blue
This is the real creature
And not always created by me
Be careful / Tom
I mean to be good here but
Someone must get it
ice, make the body fresh
He is just a funny little alien
He doesn't belong here
That little alien
And more human
You ever
His name is Sonic, this is his house
My friend
He is all yours
We are back,
I think you have something that belongs to me
This is my home
And I don't use to run anymore
I use to protect my friend
Damn / guess what
I did not leave the earth, but you
You know what
I told you I could / We can
This is yours / Thank you very much
There is no pushing anyone out of
building / You know I can't promise that
Pretty good / Thank you
You have to explain this
Donut / No, he's the one
We have things, you get your things
Oh, God
Jojo
We can't go back there
We
It's like we go home
Really
I can't feel it
I checked my bucket list
What I want to do
I checked it
Yes, like that
Everything's good
It was an ordinary day at Greenhills
Let's go
You have never seen
intergalactic battles
Robots and doctors
You were there / Yes
There are more
Mr. and Mrs. Wokosky
Yes
I'm talking about awards
from your government
Keep calm on new accidents
that never happened
I need to fix that / What is that
You will see
Okay
Oh / oh yes
You will see
There is something more
Good / You made it possible
Never end
Um, thank you, we appreciate it
Hey I think we can close
file about robotic people
This disappears
I'm sorry but no
there is that person there
That's right / You've never been connected
With aliens
Want to chat with him
you mean little blue people, no
That again
OK / OK
Thank you / OK
That's very possible
So you want to watch a movie or something
Sorry, night school, you
must return to your cave
It's three o'clock in the afternoon
You know what you become
when you're tired / me, no
You guys are very uncool / Yes we know
Where you going / me
must return to my cave
Oh are you kidding me?
I do not believe
How you
That's all here
Look / You're kidding
Oh how are you
I like it
Alright, back home
Thank you very much
My insanity remains absolute
That's right, Agent Stone
You just start
Do something
Come on it's amazing
What is wrong with you
Here it is
There is no source anymore, there is no supply
There is no way home
Unless people die here
I'm going home at Christmas
Look at this
Be happy