I'm John Dykstra.
Here today with me are Scott Stokdyk
and Anthony LaMolinara.
Anthony was director of animation.
Scott's the visual effects supervisor
for SPI. Imageworks.
And I am the visual effects designer.
This title sequence was done
by Imaginary Forces.
The important part of the relationship
between the people in visual effects...
...and the people who were doing the
title sequence was obviously the web.
We worked with them to come up with
a web that gave the impression...
...of the web that's in the movie,
but keep the stylized quality...
...that our director wanted to have
for the title sequence.
Some of the volumes
that you see here...
...the Spider-Man character, the hand,
the Goblin's face...
...was interpreted from the geometry
that we used for our virtual character.
They simplified it and put it
into the sequence.
They were trying for
something that wasn't real.
They wanted a stylized version
of the web and the characters.
They succeeded.
- So we shared. There you are.
- Yeah, there I am. That's me.
- "Visual effects designed by."
- Yeah.
We shared a couple models,
passed some models over.
I hope we get to do the next one.
- The next set of titles.
- The next opening sequence.
It's interesting, because
it's this sort of period graphic...
...that goes on the front of a movie
that is fairly starkly real.
If we did these as photo-realistic
webs for this whole sequence...
...it would have taken months.
This is the transition from
our stylized web into the real web.
The opening scene of the film.
The background for this
was shot in New York...
...and they overlaid the synthetic web
from the title sequence...
...across the cross-dissolve
to create the opening sequence.
Originally, wasn't it...
...a cross-dissolve behind her head,
where the bus materialized?
There were a couple of different ideas
of introducing the opening sequence...
...introducing Mary Jane,
whom the story is about...
...as is said in the monologue.
But this was the...
This was chosen as the best means
to make that transition...
...because it didn't leave us looking
at her for a huge amount of time.
- Don't even think about it.
- You're so lame, Parker.
That's a good look for Tobey
with those glasses.
And like that.
We shot all of this stuff...
Throughout the film, we used
live-action locations in New York.
In some cases we shot in Los Angeles
to be substituted for New York.
And sometimes we created components
completely synthetically...
...that are added into both locations
in Los Angeles and New York...
...to create our version
of New York City.
- Can we drive around the corner?
- Why?
The entrance is right there.
Dad, this is public school.
I can't show up in a Rolls.
I should trade my car for a Jetta...
Lot of setup here. Lot of exposition.
One of the things
that we're gonna talk about...
Working with Sam was terrific.
He's a very collaborative director.
Using his version of the script...
...the script that he approved
and interpreted to us...
...we started creating the preliminary
visual effects for this movie.
Sam not only welcomed...
...contributions from people
on the crew...
...he encouraged it.
He was the arbiter of all the stuff
used in the film, as the director...
...but everybody got the feeling that
they had a vested interest in this...
...in some very small part
as a filmmaker...
...as well as whatever
their particular job was.
I think that comes through
in the sense of this movie.
I think it trickled on down
through the whole crew.
Our CG supervisors, Ken Hahn,
Peter Nofz and Dan Eaton...
...they at different points had input
into the process, which was nice.
It's unreal.
Getting close to our first
effects shot. Any minute now.
The atomic spider.
One of the things about this story
is it's a period piece.
In the original origin, the character's
bitten by an irradiated spider.
We now know, if you get bitten
by an irradiated spider...
...you'll probably get
radiation poisoning.
But in those days it imbued the
character with superhuman capabilities.
Rather than use a sort of old saw
for this superhero transition...
...Sam brought the story
into a contemporary vein...
...by using the DNA basis.
Genetics, this genome-splicing
capability...
...as the component to cause
the transition from our normal kid...
...to the superhero character,
Spider-Man.
That contemporary science brings
the film into a contemporary sense.
When she describes the characteristics
of all these spiders...
...we think about what Spider-Man
will do with those powers.
It'll be a spider
trapped in a man's body...
...dying to get out.
Over five painstaking years,
Columbia's research facility...
- You gonna talk to her now?
- Oh, no. Come on.
That's part of how
Spider-Man moves.
His molecular structure
has been changed after this bite...
...so that he no longer moves according
to the physical rules we know...
...with human bodies, but something
combined between human and spider.
- Like a Spider-Man?
- Just like that.
One of the things I point out
in the live-action material:
The personality of these characters...
...both Tobey and Willem...
...they are the basis...
...for our hero and our villain.
Their postures, positions
and body language...
...are an important part
of defining them as a character.
Keeping an eye on that, trying to
integrate that into the characters...
...once they are masked
and dressed in costume...
...was a very important part of
making the character seem...
...like he was an extension
of the actor...
...as we have seen him
without the costume.
Here's Tobey getting ready
to take his photo.
You did a lot of photography
a long time ago, didn't you, John?
Oh, yeah. That was me, actually.
I got bitten by a spider.
It bit me in my visual-effects lobe.
Trying to get the girls
by taking their picture.
I did fashion photography when
I was in college. It was terrific.
You do a headsheet.
- There's our first effects shot.
- There you go.
- The beautiful crawling spider.
- That pesky spider.
A close-up is coming up,
which was a lot harder on many levels.
That was a real spider, and...
Stand by.
This guy let the spider crawl
on his hand. It isn't Tobey.
The guy who did the spider shot quit.
This bite is so short.
It was a much longer shot...
...and we just see a little snippet
of the actual bite.
It actually sits on his hand
and grinds into his fangs for a while.
Parker, let's do it.
To get that close-up of that hand
that the close-up spider was on...
- John, you want to talk about that?
- Yes, I'd be pleased to.
First matte painting.
The close-up of the hand was done
with a very special piece of optics...
...designed for photo-microscopy...
...which is microscopic photography.
We used special strobe lights
to illuminate the hand...
...to give us enough brightness to make
the entire hand be in relative focus.
It was recorded at high speed to out
down on the quivering of the hand...
...so we could put
our CG spider on there.
I talked over the guy
landing the glider.
We were just looking
at our first effects.
There's a practical glider,
but we added effects.
We added heat distortion,
thrusters coming out the bottom...
And heat distortion.
One thing that's interesting:
Sam's concept for this movie
was for it to be real.
It's not Metropolis. It's not Gotham.
It's New York...
...right down to the pigeon droppings
and the rust underneath the pipes.
Throughout the film,
he'd ask us to pursue...
...a very "real" effect
in all of these environments.
The toughest thing to do
when we made virtual versions...
...of the characters and the objects
was putting in high-frequency noise.
By that, I mean the dirt and debris...
...that populates our real life.
Dust bunnies under the bed,
stains on the wall...
...the pigeon droppings
on the windowsill.
That's tough for a computer to do
because it's random, a chaotic event.
So although we were successful...
Scott can talk about
the procedures...
...but we had our artists go back in
and add dirt to many sequences...
...to give you the visual cues that
this is real, not computer-generated.
A lot of texture work on this movie.
Many thousand textures.
We figured out there were
62,000 textures painted.
A texture is a...?
It's basically just a color map
that's mapped onto objects...
...and represents its texture,
if you will.
It represents its look...
Like taking the textures
from Tobey's face...
...and laying them on
the model of Tobey's face...
...to achieve the look and try
to make it look realistic.
- The texture is basically a photograph.
- Starts out as a photograph.
A photograph of the surface
you want to reproduce...
...in the computer environment.
The artists add to it...
...and then that photograph
could be shrink-wrapped...
...or vacuum-formed onto the shape,
which we call the geometry...
...of the person or the object
that we're creating.
Since the photograph contains
all of that detail...
...you get that in your
representation.
This is not Tobey Maguire's body.
But he'd love to have it.
It was Tobey's head
mapped onto that body.
It was a big tracking job.
And color-correction job too.
In this recombination lab...
We did some digital color-timing
on many of these sequences.
When you take original photography
and bring it into the computer...
...you have to make adjustments
to the color...
...to make sure when you take it
out of the computer...
...it will look like
the original photography.
This is a nice matte painting.
The OSCORP image.
Done by Ivo,
one of our matte painters.
The image from the computer
needs to cut back into the movie...
...adjacent to original negatives.
Rather than make it significantly
different from the original photography...
...we try and make it match
the original photography...
...so when they do color correction,
everything falls into place.
But in many sequences, especially
with cross-dissolves and fades...
...you have scene-to-scene
color timing that's critical.
So we did an awful lot
of digital color adjustment...
...throughout those montage sequences.
I was wrong before. Ivo,
the head of our matte department...
...painted the daytime
OSCORP lab exterior...
...and Dave Bleisch
painted the nighttime version.
Norman Osborn is put into this thing,
this dramatic moment...
...and he goes, "It's cold!"
when he straps him in.
I think that's pretty interesting.
We're coming up to the green gas
modification shots.
They didn't want to shoot with
toxic green gas, for some reason.
I don't understand it.
So our friends at Digiscope
did a handful of shots...
...maybe 10 to 15 color-correction
shots on the gas.
Started out as white smoke
and got turned into green.
Norman?
One of the things Anthony
talked about earlier was...
...characters going from being
human to superhuman.
One of the things that people
talked about...
...was whether or not we used
motion capture for our characters.
Although I have an opinion,
Anthony's might differ.
I think motion capture's
an interesting technique...
...to get the detail that defines
a person's body language.
Motion capture is essentially a series
of measurement points attached...
...to a person's body.
You have that person
go through a series of moves...
...and then you record those points.
It allows you to then animate a
synthetic version of that character.
When we did our motion capture,
we got great high-frequency detail...
...in terms of defining
a character's personality.
But if you have a character
jump off a three-foot-high box...
...that high-frequency detail
gives away...
...that all he did was jump off a box.
So the animators have to expand
the personality of this leap...
...into something for a 100-foot fall.
Although the motion capture for
high-frequency detail was very good...
...that same detail was a giveaway...
...when we made him
do superhuman things.
That's Tobey's real body, by the way.
Superhuman.
As a result, the principal characters,
Goblin and Spider-Man...
...were key-frame animated...
To use the high-frequency detail...
...we had to do so much adjustment...
...it would take longer to do it that
way than to animate it from the top.
Another thing about motion capture...
...as the technology exists right now,
it is cumbersome.
You have to dress up in a Lycra suit...
...and have these big, reflective balls
stuck all over you.
You can't go outside a 30-by-30 area.
There's a lot of new technology
that's being developed.
Hopefully, it'll be
a little less restrictive...
...in how you capture the data,
and the setup for it.
Not that it'll necessarily influence
our choice of doing motion capture.
I always tell people how pissed off
the gorilla got in Hollow Man...
- ...when we stuck those balls on him.
- And shaved him. Or her.
We missed it. There were two
beautiful wire removals there.
Him flying out, the doctor flying out,
and Willem flying out.
As far as motion capture goes...
...even if, say, a guy from
Cirque du Soleil...
...could swing down
between the buildings...
...the technology's not there
to capture that in that distance.
Yeah, it's too big. When you compress
that action into a small space...
...it looks compressed
into a small space.
So the accuracy of the capture
is also a curse.
If you don't use a real actor you can tell
just because of the way he moves.
Anything Spider-Man would do...
...shooting a web one way,
then changing directions...
The G-force on his body...
...if it didn't rip his arm out,
would rip his whole body in half.
It's impossible for a person to do...
...and therefore impossible
for a real person to fake.
Tobey looking at his hands
is a precursor...
...to the close-up of his hands
that comes up.
Dad, are you all right?
- Dad's been out for a fun night.
- Exactly.
A couple of other things,
just definitions.
One, we decided that the Spider-Man
character wanted to be...
...a mechanism by which
the audience experiences...
...what it's like to swing
between buildings.
At the end of the film,
Sam wanted the audience...
...to feel they had been Spider-Man.
The animators worked with a camera
as well as the character...
...much like a skydiving team works.
The guy doing the performance
is photographed...
...by his partner,
the skydiving photographer.
We're gonna see some webs
in a minute.
Lot of web shots.
One of our guys...
This is a mechanical rig,
where he catches all this stuff.
Yeah. He actually did that.
Pretty good. Take 156.
At any rate...
...we decided that Spider-Man,
when he swung through the city...
...would have his own
cameraman with him.
The cameraman had the same
abilities as Spider-Man...
...and was able to operate the camera.
The cameraman gets better over the
course of the film as does Spider-Man.
He gets more adept
at doing the photography.
That's another way we added
this sense of reality to things.
This is a practical...
The first one's a practical web.
That's a real one, and then this...
That last one's a CG.
The first one was our effects shot.
That's practical, and then...
I can't even tell anymore.
Our guy, Theo,
set up this great web system...
...including the dynamics and shading,
just to be multipurposed.
To work for small webs, and to work
for the large-scale webs he swings on.
This fight scene coming up,
as well as Wirework that's in this...
There is a wire attached,
lifting him up in the air...
...or supporting him so he can
lean back and not lose his balance.
A lot of these shots were speeded up
in certain sections of this shot...
...to give them more force,
like the punch.
John should talk about this.
Well, this is spider sense.
It's made up of all of the components
that you want to see...
...when you think about
what Spider-Man can do.
It's expanded time.
Why don't you talk about the fight?
We took part of the punch and sped
it up so that there's more force...
...and slowed it down at the right
moment so it's not so obvious.
And the one long shot where we see
that arm just glide by him...
...and Tobey sees everything
in slow motion.
That's another idea
of the spider sense.
He's in one temporal realm,
they're all in a different one.
And here, for example,
when he grabs Flash's arm.
It's speeded up, then back
to real speed as he holds it...
...and then it's speeded up again
for the punch.
Which one?
There were so many shots that were
sped up and slowed down.
Both Stan and Bob
liked experimenting with that.
- We tried a little bit of it too.
- All right.
Spider sense, by its very definition,
is time expansion.
Spider-Man slows everything down to
inspect all these potential threats.
The beginning of this, where you saw
the fly being inspected...
...were events that he had
no control over.
His spider sense, which is newly
developed, checked out all this stuff.
It gives you a sense
of his ineptitude.
Next is a sequence where you see
his first experimentation...
...with his newfound powers.
That's the spider's
genetic modification to his wrist.
It's not exactly where
the spinneret ought to be, but...
We figured putting it in
the right place might be a mistake.
There's the big microscopic hair shot.
- This is how he climbs up the wall.
- That was Theo's shot too.
A lot of tight tracking work
to get those to work too.
Here are our first real
digital environment shots, actually.
They're extension shots.
That's a fake alley floor there.
And there.
When we look up on the side,
it's all building extensions.
This was the beginning of
the personality for this camera.
The idea that the camera actually rose
with him, kind of stayed with him.
Keeping the camera with the character,
as opposed to watching him from afar.
Most of this is Wirework.
It's our video-game shots.
We were going to use a stuntman,
but they decided...
...that it was not practical to do.
It was a little too dangerous.
Here's the first webs that he shoots.
He's figuring how
to control his webs...
...and how to dictate where they go.
Up, up and away, web.
So the web, this is Theo's work...
...has a huge range of personalities.
It comes out of his wrist, it's
thin and willowy in some cases.
It's big and strong in others.
It has to spread into an actual
spider web in some cases...
...and in other cases it's a lump
on somebody's face.
An enormous effort went into
defining the web.
If you think about real webs, the
biggest problem is, they're invisible.
If bugs could see the webs,
they wouldn't fly into them.
We knew that, in order to meet
the expectations of an audience...
...who knows of spider webs
as just glints...
...we had to figure out a way to make
the web like a spider web...
...in that it had what we called a
sundog defining it by highlight...
...and keep enough volume
to feel it was strong enough...
...to do whatever it was
we were asking the web to do.
There are a number of practical webs
intercut with our CG ones.
The web had to be flexible
enough to look practical...
...or go away from that
when we needed to.
That last shot where he was swinging
on the web and hits the wall...
We'll see him almost do the same thing
when he's in his homemade spidey suit.
Then he just misses it
at the last moment.
Gotten a little better.
We've got this character arc.
He's not so facile
when he first gains that capability.
Over the course of the film,
he gets better and better.
You see that happen. Also, the way
he is followed through the film...
The camera work also gets
better and better.
So everybody's kind of got this same
learning curve.
I guess you can always hear us.
Everybody shouts.
Your aunt and uncle don't.
When we were shooting this stuff...
...you see these scenes that last
two or three minutes...
...yet it takes an entire night
to shoot this stuff.
This was a situation where
color correction was used.
Over the course of the evening,
we went from dusk to night to dawn.
And it wasn't shot in continuity.
In some cases,
they're taking light out of a scene.
In other cases, they're adding light
to make it all consistent throughout.
A difficult problem
when he was on the roof...
...is that the actual size it needs
to be to see it in the distance...
...is gigantic as opposed to
what it really would be.
Yet I buy it when I see it on screen.
The illusion in the service
of the story.
It's cinemagraphic license,
making the web change size.
Also, depending on the background...
...we had to do different things
if it went over a bright sky.
The whiter specular hits
wouldn't show up as much.
You had to get some dark in there,
and sundogs running down too.
The web had several different states.
It's liquid when shot from his wrist.
As it attached to things,
it did a catalyzation...
...which was a change of state,
like water becoming ice.
When it changed state, there was a
difference to the visual personality.
You can see when it strikes a building
when he swings through the city...
...the web has a transition that occurs
once it's stuck to a surface.
He also seems, through some
psycho-physio process...
...to make the web come out and have
different consistencies.
One time it would be hard as steel,
another it would be elastic...
...and he could pull on it and
pop himself up to a building.
Just like a mutant spider could,
I'm sure.
Absolutely.
Hey, M.J.! Come take a ride
in my new birthday present.
Come on.
I gotta go.
Something I'd like to do in the sequel
is put Tobey's idiosyncrasies...
...into the digital actor.
There's another alleyway.
Lots of alleyways in this movie.
Cool car.
John was talking about the performance
of the digital actor.
In this film, we're almost
working backward.
Usually you work
from the facial expression down...
...as far as the hierarchy
of what gives the expression.
In this case,
there is no facial expression.
Spider-Man maybe has a jaw moving.
Goblin has nothing.
It's a very big challenge...
...to try to let this digital actor...
...emote from body movement.
Goblin is certainly more complex
than Spider-Man...
...with his Shakespearean moves
and psychotic personality...
...that goes from kind to sadistic.
That was a very big challenge,
something we'll develop more next time.
The interesting thing about
the personality of this character...
Sam asked, and maybe
you can give input...
...that we use some of the classic
Spider-Man poses...
...to brand this character
from the comic books.
I know the animators
had that stuff as reference.
Do you have a sense of
how you integrated that stuff?
Certainly, we worked
from all of the comics...
...then tried to figure out what pose
works best in a given situation.
If he's perched,
waiting for something.
In the last swing,
there are a lot of...
...typical key Spider-Man poses.
When his hands are raised
over his head...
...his wrists are arched and
his fingers are in a formation.
That's a good example of these poses.
It comes from the storyboard artist
and animators...
...on up through me, you, Sam...
...and everybody else who's
watching this film on a daily basis.
The other interesting thing...
You talked about Willem Dafoe.
When we started defining what the
Goblin would be like as a character...
...we started with this conveyance,
the Goblin glider.
We built a simulator,
a motion base with a glider attached.
It boiled down to something
like a mechanical bull...
...only you had to stand on it.
It was an ankle-breaker.
We worked with the stunt people
to figure out a way...
...to come up with something
to give them a timing choreography...
...so when it moved,
they'd anticipate it...
...and position themselves to look
as if they're affecting the machine.
Interestingly, we weren't successful
with the stunt people...
...but when Willem Dafoe showed up
and started to define the character...
...they stuck him on the machine,
and within 15 minutes of riding...
...he didn't put new moves in,
he's just reacting to the machine...
...he managed to come up with
these terrific moves for the Goblin.
I don't know how you feel about it,
Anthony, but for me...
...when I saw him on the machine,
I was encouraged...
...as to how well the character
was going to work on the glider.
That was the first experience...
...of seeing the actor
define the character for us...
- ...to bring to the screen.
- Go ahead.
This sequence is interesting
for color correction...
...because their skin tones
were so different.
Ben had a more ruddy,
reddish complexion.
Tobey leaned toward olive tones and
went green, if you weren't careful.
Especially in two-shots, where they're
together. This was tricky.
I remember when Willem came in.
The pumpkin bombs
pop out of the glider...
...and when he had his mask on,
he couldn't see where they came from.
He had to learn how to catch the bombs
just by feel...
...or having his hand
in the right place.
He ended up doing the work
that a stuntman would normally do.
He dedicated himself to creating
body-language personality for Goblin.
He was so studious in terms
of his positions in every situation...
...as to whether or not it was
appropriate for the Goblin.
A lot of effects guys tried to go in
and be extras in the movie.
One guy, Jeff Wolverton,
made it into this match...
...holding a Bone Saw sign.
- Is that him in the bikini?
- Yeah, that's him on the left.
I haven't spotted him, but I'm going
to go frame-by-frame on the DVD.
It's the guy trying to pitch a film.
The thing I didn't realize the first
couple times I saw this movie...
...is that it's Bruce Campbell
in a cameo as the announcer.
Bruce is the hero from Sam's movies.
And you're participating
under your own free will?
Down the hall to the ramp.
May God be with you. Next.
Here's a case where it's
a reverse of the norm.
Usually, they couldn't do what
they needed to do with a stuntman...
...so we did it digitally.
In this sequence...
...they did most everything
with the actor or a stuntman.
Wouldn't you like to have
done Bone Saw CG, though?
That would've been fun.
$3000 will be paid to...
- What's your name, kid?
- The Human Spider.
That's it? That's the best you got?
- Yeah.
- Oh, that sucks.
The sum of $3000 will be paid to...
...the terrifying, the deadly...
There's some web work
coming up in this sequence...
...and it's more of an
elastic-type web.
Anthony mentioned
the different characteristics.
In this sequence, Tobey uses...
...that web as just a very springy
substance to help him do some flips.
Almost like bungee cord.
This is another place, although
they did this actual work on-stage...
...this is another case where
the Cirque du Soleil performers...
...or performances were used.
The idea of the multiple webs
sort of like some of the stuff...
...that they do on multiple bungee
cords in Cirque du Soleil performances.
Cage!
There were some speed up
of some shots in here too.
Some skip-framing,
or different software sometimes...
...to speed it up and make it
look a little smoother.
...Please lock
the cage doors at this time.
This is some kind of mistake.
I didn't sign up for a cage match!
Unlock the thing! Take the chain off!
Hey, freak show!
You're going nowhere.
I got you for three minutes.
Three minutes of playtime.
When we did tests
of our homemade costume...
...we used some of this photography...
...to check how our CG version
costume would light.
We really liked the dramatic
lighting here.
And it made for a good color
comparison kind of check.
Smash him!
One of the things that...
Back to this Green Goblin thing
we were talking about before...
One thing we did to make
the Green Goblin feel...
...as if he were a
contemporary character...
...is the motions of him
on his glider.
Rather than looking like he's
standing on top of a small airplane...
...and flying straight and level...
...we gave him the sense of motion
you get...
...from skateboarding and
surfing and snowboarding.
That kind of finesse that the
characters have in movement...
...you see in sports to bring this
into a contemporary vein as well.
Yeah, the Goblin's glider
is sort of like his pet.
Some kind of pet
that he can call at will...
...and watches out for him,
and comes back to him.
We had to give the feeling
like he controlled it...
...not completely by body movement.
A thought process was going on...
...as if he had to just lean and it
knew where to go, as opposed to...
...just pushing it around by leaning.
It was partially the understanding
of the Goblin and him as one.
- What the hell...?
- Put the money in the bag.
Hurry UP!
Hey! He stole the gate!
Stop that guy!
Stop him! He's got my money!
I like this costume.
It had interesting detail work...
...when we made our CG version.
One of the first things we did
were the shoes...
...which you don't really see here.
But he had these red Nike sneakers
we sort of did on a turntable...
...flying around a screen
to try to balance...
...how the colors and lighting
looked on it.
The interesting thing about
a movie like this...
...because it took two years,
we had to make promises...
...we weren't certain that we could
fulfill at the beginning of this film.
As any film of this scope,
it's a living document.
It has to be able to change
over the course of time.
The homemade costume
was something...
...that evolved over the course
of time.
The homemade costume wasn't
in the first script...
...certainly not as it ended up
being in the film.
And this is something
that we had to embrace.
It was different than
our hero character costume:
It's baggy and floppy and has folds
and the wind affects it.
So it was actually more challenging...
...than the more polished,
finished version of Spider-Man.
Definitely. We had to build
an extra layer, basically...
...on top of our slick costume
and do a cloth simulation.
John Lee did that and had to add in...
...all the effects where he's flying
and get those ripples...
...and the Wind's amplitude
and frequency...
...to just give him a sense of motion.
Multilayers of wrinkles,
wrinkling in there.
You can see on this sweatshirt
how many wrinkles and folds there are.
This is a little thicker
than our costume...
...but those kind of details
really give it realism.
The guys who did the cloth came up
with a garment workers' stamp...
- ...they put on dailies.
- Migrant textile workers of Imageworks.
An interesting thing about
this cloth:
When you make these costumes, you
end up using the same techniques...
...real patternmakers use.
So this cloth you see here was
fitted to the body of the character.
If it doesn't fit right in the chest,
it might come back and take a pleat.
We re-tailor it, basically.
And it's actually tailoring
the way a real tailor works.
That wall crawl is a great shot
by Spencer Cook.
It shows what we came to
for the character's movement.
First we tried suspending
him from a track...
...and let him crawl along the surface,
A stuntman or Tobey.
But there's no way you can
get the correct weight distribution.
You lift one hand,
they've got two feet and one arm...
...the way that pulls on the body,
it didn't look right.
Here's the shot
when he just misses the wall.
The camera follows him.
In one of those shots we had a bus...
...and on top there's lettering.
We put "PT13" on there.
PT13 was just one of our first building
tests. It was an homage to that.
The thing about this fabric
in this sequence...
I think I heard you
talking about this, Anthony.
The fabric enhances
the sense of motion.
The idea that it's fluttering
helps the animators...
...keep a sense of motion
in the character.
The fabric gives an impression
of the wind moving.
It makes the animation...
It complements it.
It makes you aware of
how much clothing...
...is what tells you the kind
of movement a person is making.
There was a huge section of CG
buildings earlier in this sequence.
A lot of work went into it by Ken Hahn,
Francisco, Laurence, Dan Abrams...
...a bunch of really great lighters.
We did a couple of things here.
One of them is this business
of adding New York...
...into Los Angeles and adding
New York into New York.
The buildings you see in some
of these sequences are from L.A...
...and some are from New York.
And there are buildings
that have been added...
...so you're gonna see more of that.
Here's the first animated shot in the
film. This shadow across the ceiling.
- That was the very first shot.
- One of our first finals.
Not that one. That's a live action.
This one.
He's animated, funny enough.
The rolling bear animation.
We did quite a few different
versions of that.
That must have been an
interesting thing to animate.
Indirect animation. You animate the
character and then cast his shadow.
Because you've got to go
by silhouettes.
What looks right from one angle
doesn't look right from another.
Stop that guy!
You had a version of the character
you were using...
...and he was in an impossible pose
to make a feasible-looking shadow.
It wasn't our final
physiquing on the character...
...so his shape wasn't perfect.
You had to manipulate that a bit.
That was some of Koji's
earliest physiquing there.
Part of an eight-month process.
"Physiquing" being the creation
of the model of the character.
Actually, the Goblin and Spider-Man
were set up by two different people...
...and set up in different ways.
Koji's version, Koji Morihiro,
set up Spider-Man.
He approaches it differently...
...than JJ Blumenkrantz
did on Goblin.
One of our guys, Alberto,
helped set up the Goblin system...
...which was based on an underlying
skeleton and muscle system.
The Goblin also had, in addition
to having a skin over Willem's skin...
...it had a hard exoskeleton
that had a little bit of flux in it...
...but basically, like, slid...
...slid up and down
his arms and his chest.
So it had to be a different technique
than our Spider-Man.
The definition of the physical form
of the peoples' bodies...
...also included a muscle system.
So when they flexed,
you could see a change displacement...
...in the forms of their body.
The legs, the contours of their thighs
and chests and arms.
There was also breathing. Anthony had
access to breathing controls.
Those are the kinds of subtle details
that tell the audience...
...that this is a live character,
as opposed to a CG simulation.
A lot of that work was based on
reference footage...
...we took of the actors and stunt
doubles at the start.
We put them through calisthenics
and range-of-motion tests...
...and basically took up days of their
time to get all of that set up work.
But it paid off. I mean, just having
video reference...
...of how the quads flex,
and the deltoids and biceps.
All through the body,
how muscles distort their volumes.
It was really useful.
And it had to be there because when
he's in that custom-made costume...
...that's the only real feeling you get
of this character being alive.
Because the suit is tight,
there's no clothing to flow...
...and give the sense
of movement.
So it's more difficult to bring
the character to life in that costume.
I keep thinking of that shot
in the fire building later...
...where Spencer animated him landing.
It's just such a nice, subtle flex
in his quads on his legs as he lands.
It didn't make the out, but it gave a
sense of the weight of the landing.
When we first started doing the work
on this movie...
...we did a test as a proof of concept.
And we used a model of a body that
came from another environment.
It wasn't the real character, but we
put a Spider-Man costume on him...
...and had him climb up the side
of a set piece, a piece of set wall.
And when we did the test, we shot
the set wall with a camera move...
...with a stuntman crawling
on his belly...
...using a rig we'd designed
to let him slide on the surface.
The mechanical effects guys
put that together.
Then we shot the same camera move
without the character.
Then we took the version of the wall
without the character on it...
...and created a CGI version using
this existing model of this person.
Then Anthony and the guys...
Did Spencer animate that?
- That first test?
- Yeah.
Anyway, so we took this in
and showed it to them.
I don't know who the lighters were.
It was our first...
That was a long time ago.
- I think Greg Anderson was involved.
- So we gave it our best shot.
This was before we'd worked out
how we were going to do this.
We took it in, and the producer,
sort of as a tongue-in-cheek joke...
...told the executives
who were watching the film:
"So here's Tobey
climbing up the wall."
And they ran film.
The executives watched it.
The lights come up,
and they smile and say:
"It's great-looking, but that couldn't
have been Tobey. It's a stuntman."
So they had mistaken the animated,
computer-generated character...
...that animators had put
on the wall...
...and that SPI had lit and composited,
for a real image.
So we knew we had a shot at being
successful when they decided...
...our first test was indistinguishable
from a real human being.
You look back on those tests now...
...and Spider-Man looks nothing like
he does now in terms of his costume...
...and even some
of his body language.
On every movie we do a test on,
you look back...
...and that test looks so different
than the final product.
We were trying to arrive
in these tests...
...at the proper movement for him
to be a mix of man and spider.
That anecdote of Laura Ziskin
watching the screening and saying:
"Wow. You know, this character
looks like a man...
...but, well, like a spider."
Everybody said:
"That's exactly what it is."
And then we knew we had more or less
what we needed to sell this character.
A couple of shots ago, the camera
swinging through the city, shot in L.A.
That was where a couple of us
got a cameo. We were in on Sunday.
On the street corner.
And Sam's there waving.
And Bob, the editor, and you and I.
But you'd never find it on the DVD.
In trying to give this the feeling of
a camera flying through the street...
...there were amplitude
and frequency controls...
...so as the camera accelerated
into the skyscrapers...
...into these canyons,
the camera would shake...
...as if it were being shaken
by wind buffeting.
As it came up, it would slow
down and steady out...
...and then hang in the air
to give the feeling of an operator...
...following along with Spider-Man.
But we should all just give him
One big hug
On this montage sequence they cut in
some of our very early shots...
...from the original teaser trailers
and in the early trailers.
If we tried to follow along with
the character, that didn't work.
You had to let him go away,
then come back to the camera.
And let the character work the frame...
...while depending on
where he was headed.
Work it from bottom left
to upper right, or opposite.
Give this feeling of an operator
behind this camera...
...following this digital actor.
What's he got to hide?
She needs to know
if you want chintz or chenille.
- Whichever's cheaper.
- It's like this.
We double-booked page six.
Macy's and Conway's both have...
I was trying to figure out what was on
that TV. What movie we're showing...
They switched there,
but it was some old horror film.
Some monster, big monster.
Sam loves sneaking little things in.
He would never give away
his secrets.
I'm sure you have to watch it
many times to find that.
Some creature coming out of the water.
Aren't those, like, oil-spill victims?
He doesn't want to be famous?
I'll make him infamous!
The interior of that office
existed in three places.
It was built on the stage once...
...then it was photographed
in a location in downtown L.A.
Then it was rebuilt in another piece
shot yet again on a separate stage.
That sets up the interesting
problem that there was...
...after Goblin comes crashing through
into Jameson's office...
...and then Spider-Man comes down
outside the window...
...and the Goblin knocks him out.
When he falls down
the side of the building...
Because of the lights
for the shots to match...
...we had to do a matte painting
of the building, right?
I'm talking to you! Hey!
Yes, Enrique, okay? I get you!
It better not happen no more.
Don't roll your eyes at me.
The process is interesting.
You shoot all this material...
...and they edit the thing together.
There's times when complete
sequences get left out.
And you end up with a sequence shot...
...for a particular time of day
used at a different time.
Or a shot even where a shot that was
made with the sun in one direction...
...cut with the sun in another
direction, or perhaps the sun gone.
Those are things now, although they've
always been a part of it...
...those are things now
that we are using...
...digital color timing and techniques
to smooth out...
...so they don't create as big
a disconnect for the audience.
The trick is to get people
to not be aware of being in a theatre.
The one thing we would never do
though, is flip a shot.
Are you being facetious?
You're still sensitive about
your Times Square shot they flipped.
The whole process,
every studio, every group...
...every visual effects house
has a different approach...
...to how they're going
to work together.
Even within a certain house,
you'll find that every group...
...certainly every effects designer, is
gonna have a different way of working.
On this, we were all together.
All departments saw dailies together.
And I think that was healthy
because everybody contributes.
It may hurt to hear what they have
to say, but it usually makes it better.
We would separate animation dailies...
...where we were blocking out the shots
with lighting and compositing dailies.
John, Anthony and I, and some
supervisors would sit in all of them.
Peter Parker.
Maybe you'll tell me who she is.
It's interesting,
we've had stuff to say...
...about the first part,
but it hasn't been intense.
I guess it's the same kind
of distribution a lot of films have.
But there was an effort in this to
focus on the people at the beginning...
...to establish these characters
and create empathy...
...before we got too carried away
with the visual theatrics.
If it ended now, you wouldn't
call it an effects film.
It would just be...
No, and I'd still be wondering what
happened at the beginning.
...About photography.
Hello.
Let's go!
This was interesting.
This was a fascinating sequence.
It became evident that the character...
...in this custom-made costume,
when he would be animated...
...the best explanation we could
come up with was that as light...
...arced across his skin, backlight,
it caused him to speed up.
So we went through several speed
changes in that sequence.
It's funny.
All three of us have seen this
several times now.
But shots like those
you're talking about...
...we've seen hundreds
and hundreds of times.
We see them at artists' workstations
when they're first being made.
We see them in dailies on a loop,
maybe 30, 40 times a day.
Then we see them on film,
just looped over and over again.
So we've seen this film many,
many times over.
The little shot where Spider-Man's
on the ground...
...and he's kicking the bank robber...
...and then flips over the top of him.
We went through so many different
versions of this because...
...as in a lot of shots, some shots
we'll see later, it's the same thing.
This character is a superhuman...
...but we still wanted him
to be a thinking character.
So if everything's too
well-choreographed...
...it can have a false look to it.
As if the character weren't thinking
on his feet at that moment.
It can look scripted, as it were.
Contrived.
Interesting thing about this character,
something Sam said consistently:
"I want to know what he's thinking."
When you have a character
who has a face...
...the idea of establishing
his thoughts is much easier...
...than with a character who is only
using his body because he's masked.
That's the interesting thing
about animation in this film.
From my point of view, you have
a sense of what he's thinking...
...just based on the way
his body's moving.
The actors actually dealt with the
same issues as our animators.
Acting with the body
instead of the face.
We both kind of had to come
to our solutions separately.
You can't do this to me.
I started this company.
You know how much I sacrificed?!
Here's Willem Dafoe
in his psycho routine again.
No effects used to enhance his
expressions there.
The character's physicality is part of
what made the Goblin successful.
Not only in the virtual character,
but in the actor himself.
He's never static. There's always
something going on with him.
I know it's an acting issue...
...but Tobey's very quiet as an actor.
He moves his body much less.
All those board members we just saw
we had to make digital versions of...
...to mess with later in this
Times Square sequence.
This was one of the first sequences
we got live-action photography on.
It was the first sequence.
This is where we cut our teeth.
This is where we worked out
how we'd achieve these events.
This is exciting.
I animated that balloon.
That was Anthony's personal animation.
What did that take,
three or four weeks to do, Anthony?
That was the first time.
We did it again.
The tough thing about this sequence
is it's a daylight exterior.
Without getting into specifics,
this was shot in New York.
Portions of it were shot in New York,
portions of it were shot on a stage.
Portions of it were shot in Downey,
portions were computer-generated.
It's not necessarily
the same piece all the time.
When you watch the sequence
you can see...
...that we had to create everything
from very small-scale...
...to very large-scale components
to make this sequence complete.
There's no other way we could do it,
aside from shutting down Times Square.
They talked to us...
We talked to them, excuse me.
We talked to them about shutting down
Times Square for the weekend.
They weren't going for it.
The animation on the balloons
in there is dynamics...
...which is a method of...
...how the energy would flow
through an object...
...if it were animated
or hit with energy.
So in this case, the balloons
are hit with air, or an object.
Dan Kramer did a nice job making these
balloons look natural for their size...
...and the way it would move.
The balloons helped tie
different environments together.
They gave good foreground objects
and bridged the gap...
...between the different photography.
We have our somewhat controversial
sign replacements in this sequence.
One thing the balloon did,
in foreground and middle ground...
If you look at Times Square,
we were on Dick Clark's balcony...
...the one he stands on
during the New Year's celebration.
Then the people were below us.
If you stand and look down,
everything's in the distance.
You don't have much of a sense
of perspective or scale.
Putting the balloons into the sequence
gave us some middle-ground elements...
...which allowed us to show not only
the scale of the environment...
...but also to keep the screen
alive with movement.
Because as the camera moves,
you can see that the balloons...
...give a sense of foreground
and background...
...which you wouldn't have
if it wasn't for them.
These are a series of multi-purpose
pumpkin bombs.
Another CG creation.
I'm sure everybody noticed a couple of
minutes ago the Stan Lee cameos.
Originally he was selling
sunglasses at a stand.
He had a couple funny lines,
but they got cut.
One of his lines was,
"Yeah, they use these in X-Men."
- There's your cameo.
- I ran by in front of the kid.
Shot at the very end of production.
There was a case of the glider
coming back to the Goblin...
...waiting on him for when he needs
to jump back on, like a cowboy's horse.
A lot of these ground shots of Goblin
we used as lighting reference...
...when we were developing our Goblin
CG model, and its lighting model.
There he is.
This was shot by
Pedram Goshtasbpour...
It cuts together with live action,
goes back and forth between the two.
Watch Goblin spin out.
- He stalled.
- Kicking off a wave on a surfboard.
Interestingly, the people in the street
are made of digital characters...
...generated in the computer...
...people from Downey,
who were shot...
I think we had 5000 people one day.
Another day we had 1000,
then it got down to 250.
People got tired of coming.
And the crowds in the streets
are all made up...
...of separate pieces
that are all sewn together...
...to create much more scope
than we actually had to photograph.
This is Peter Nofz's sequence,
as a CG supervisor.
He coordinated the set up of a bunch
of these different systems...
...including our crowd system
and the character setup.
He got a taste of every pipeline.
Our building pipeline,
our painted tile pipeline.
We stitched together photography
that John shot in New York.
It came together.
Just for the sense of description,
when Scott talks about a pipeline...
...it's the process characters and
environments go through to be finished.
Once principle photography is done,
if that's a component of a shot...
...let's say a background plate,
in the case of this New York piece...
...then all of the pieces
begin to come together.
Those pieces may take five weeks
to assemble, or a week to assemble.
We call the length of time
that it takes...
...to go from the beginning components
to its completion a "pipeline."
In some cases the pipeline
is tied to a character.
In other cases, it's tied
to the complexity of the shot.
The last shot in the movie
took six months, I believe.
- Yeah, six to eight months.
- That's not a pure pipeline...
...but it gives you a sense
of how long it takes.
We had to decide what we were actually
going to do fairly early on...
...to get the shots done by the time
the film was in the theatres.
By the time we got
into really finishing...
...or getting close to finishing
the last swing shot...
...everybody wanted to do
more shots like it.
We just knew we didn't have the time
in the schedule to do more.
Well, you use every moment.
I have yet to work on a movie
where we said:
"We're done. We'll take the week off."
You always work until,
as Sam said for this movie...
...I believe he's quoting someone
else but he says:
"They will pry the film
from his cold, dead hands."
That's pretty much the way
these movies always are.
The whole process,
from script to storyboard artists...
...to Sam, and then over to us...
...then going through you, John,
then filtering through other people.
Going from me to the animators, and
then back in the other direction again.
It goes back and forth
through this hierarchy...
...and you arrive at something
until Sam finally agrees upon it.
But everybody has their input
into these things.
And different people input
on many different things.
The lighter can comment
about the animation.
An animator might comment
about the lighting.
It works a little...
- Is that a sore spot?
- No. Not at all.
Anthony and I always argue
a little bit in jest, in dailies.
- But we won't do that now.
- Oh, I'll miss it.
I was gonna say, the pre-visualization
that Anthony was talking about...
...it's different for live-action shots
and an all-CG shot.
For live-action photography,
a lot of it was used to hash out...
...where the camera should be
and what lens would be used...
...and to block out
for the day of the shooting.
In the case of all-CG shots,
it was actually much easier, in a way.
The animators were really blocking out
the shot in that case.
It just went from pre-vis
to finishing animation stages...
...straight into lighting without a
photography section in that path.
We talked about pre-visualization...
...which is the geometry of a set
or a location...
...and simple geometry
of the characters...
...with a virtual camera that can be
positioned to create shots.
We did pre-visualization on shots that
were live-action pieces, as well...
...so that when we showed up on-stage
to do the photography...
...we could tell the director of
photography the focal lengths...
...and the distance from the camera
to the subject.
That was a place to begin.
Pre-visualization isn't cast in stone.
It's always, again, a living document.
But it gave everyone
an exhibit to work with...
...to determine the needs of a shot
on a given day.
It makes you more efficient.
You put more of your money on screen...
...instead of putting the money into
doing fix-its or changing your mind.
Pre-visualization was good.
John Schmidt was great about working
out those things for shoot days.
He also made printouts for them.
He went through a ream of paper
making printouts used for shooting.
Here comes the Goblin.
We worked with the mechanical guys
and the stunts guys.
In many cases, the Goblin was there
on a practical glider.
Sometimes it was Willem on the glider,
sometimes it was a stuntperson.
We had to communicate
on an ongoing basis.
We used the pre-visualization as the
exhibit that we discussed together.
It allowed us to bring the proper tools
for the day's photography...
...as well as the postproduction work
that had to be done in visual effects.
Another shot by Koji Morihiro...
...the guy who actually made the set up
for Spider-Man animation.
Jeff Stern lit that shot.
When I saw that lighting,
it was such a nice golden-hour look.
It influenced how we ended up
on that sequence.
This is a great sequence
to get a feeling...
...for the psychotic behavior
that Goblin has...
...and what I looked to...
...to give different facets of
his behavior in the performance.
Well, to each his own.
I chose my path,
you chose the way of the hero.
This was also the sequence
shot on-stage...
...and we decided that the backing
didn't have the right contrast level.
As a post process, we did some
adjustments on the background.
Put some steam in.
The other interesting thing,
because of dialogue changes...
...we obscured the Goblin's mouth
in some of these shots...
...so the lip-synch wouldn't be off.
We did a lot of editorial tinkering
with this shot...
...during the process of making it.
We went through a lot of different
versions of his performance in this.
When the glider comes in,
he jumps on it and flies away.
In his speech, we tried to get across
in his body what Sam wanted him to say.
We had different versions.
One time, we were repeating
what he was doing to his head.
There's something coming up where
he puts his fingers to his head.
Well, that's cut out.
But he flies away, and gives
this Shakespearean gesture to him.
For characters, the actors,
Willem Dafoe and Tobey Maguire...
...one who's very still,
one who's animated...
...once we put the costumes on...
...the somewhat melodramatic motions
become totally acceptable.
You don't balk at them, because they
replace the business of the guy's face.
It's very interesting that some of the
motions and positions...
...that the characters get into
when they're masked seem extreme...
...but don't seem extreme
in the context of the story.
So how'd it go?
They said I needed acting lessons.
A soap opera told me
I needed acting lessons.
There's a lot of little wire removal
and some composite shots...
...Imageworks didn't do.
We worked with vendors.
CIS, Post Logic, Digiscope
did a lot of the work...
...coming up in the next
rain sequence.
What's interesting
about contemporary filmmaking...
...is it used to be you couldn't
remove wires or posts.
So production had to be very careful
about what they put into a scene.
Although, I'd like to say this
production wasn't bad that way.
On films I've worked on, they've left
the food truck in the background.
Because it was quicker
to shoot the scene...
...and have the truck
removed in postproduction.
And the whole business of wires now,
and posts to support people...
...to make them fly and do other things
is rampant. Every other shot...
...in action sequences...
...often times have support rods,
or tubes...
...or cranes, or people's hands, that
you end up going back to paint out.
It's one of the things digital imagery
has provided to the filmmakers.
You can take eyes from one take
and a mouth from another...
...and paint them together
to make another shot.
Pixel Magic was our
other vendor, I forgot to mention.
Now it doesn't necessarily mean
that you should do that.
We had many
wire removal and fix it shots...
...they all just blend together.
I can't remember where they all are.
Tobey's fighting style
is not martial arts.
It's a cross, as Anthony was calling
it, between human and superhuman.
He throws conventional boxing-type
punches, but he also uses...
...almost Judo-type moves.
It's kind of an interesting mix
of a collage of fighting styles...
...which, I think, gives him
a personality all his own.
I love the shot in that sequence
where he's all wet.
It's just so unmotivated if you look
at this shot out of context.
I felt sorry for Tobey in this shot.
Because I was there
when they shot it...
...it's difficult for me to see it as
romantic. His sinuses were full of water.
He was breathing out of his mouth,
through the wet fabric.
Boy, that spider web
does some interesting stuff.
- You just press a button...
- And up you go.
In those shots, even though
you don't see anything...
...we've done a little extra movement
around and overriding post move...
...to just reframe or add extra
motion into those shots.
And there, this is kind
of the first of our daytime...
...CG buildings in the
background of some shots.
Except for Times Square.
Nice work on the webs where they
waft in the wind after he goes...
...to get back into the window.
That shot came together pretty fast
at the end of the show.
That was a kind of last minute
pull-together shot.
Okay, this fire sequence contains
components shot in New York.
This piece, for instance,
is located in New York, as is that.
Once we go inside, we're on a set...
...that was built once
in a parking lot in Downey...
...then again, to shoot subsequent
components of the shot...
...in a parking lot in Culver City.
It all goes together very nicely.
This is an example of integrating this
character seamlessly into a scene.
I think this is a terrific shot
that is in this sequence...
...which we'll point out.
It was a great transition
between real and digital actors.
That was a great shot by Ken Morris,
coming in the window.
That web, animated by Todd Boyce, was
a web that Sam kept coming back to...
...as a reference of a floating web
where it wafted into the air.
He liked that quality. We tried
to get that in some other shots.
The actors were actually in this set
as it was on fire, wearing Lycra...
...which is flammable. You can imagine
how excited they were about that.
I don't know whether Willem talked
about this or Tobey...
...but it was quite hot on that set.
If you were gonna be on the set...
...you wore a complete firefighters'
uniform, including a respirator.
This is Spencer Cook
in a really beautiful shot...
...where all the elements come together
very well. People thought this...
...was a real actor.
Greg Anderson did a great job lighting
that and Greg Derochie...
...compositing it.
Jeff Lin doing this work,
Torn Gurney doing this work.
Razorbats exploding.
I thought it was a very well
choreographed sequence too.
No one says no to me!
I think the transitions Sam uses
are somewhat dated...
...but they're interesting. It gives
a certain personality to the film.
The flame transitions. There's other
places where he's used wipes...
...and interesting kinds
of fades and things.
Thank you, Mr. Osborn.
We're so glad you could come.
Who is this lovely young lady?
M.J., I'd like you to meet my father...
We worked on this movie
through the transition...
...of the September 11th
disaster in New York.
I was gonna mention it earlier,
we didn't remove...
...the World Trade Centre
from any of our shots.
The only shot that had
the World Trade Centre in it...
...was the one in the trailer.
They chose to not use it because
the Trade Centre was featured...
...so they felt that
that was too painful.
John, when you shot the footage
after September 11th for the top...
...of the buildings in the last swing,
the Twin Towers weren't there.
To make it consistent, Dan Eaton
actually put those towers in there.
And this our famous blood shot.
So this was a bone of contention.
This is a shot Anthony teased me
about looking like ketchup.
I still, to this day,
don't think it looks like ketchup.
I think that the shot wouldn't have
worked unless it looked like ketchup.
Well, I was hoping for some kind of
big conflict. I guess that was quick.
I tease Scott, but it had to be thick.
Real blood would splatter horizontally.
Yeah, I was ready to jab Anthony
and get some blood experiments...
...to really test
what it would look like.
Thank you.
Now then, everybody sit down...
...and we can say grace.
Here we go.
There we are.
So New York City, real New York City
with all the bits and pieces...
We started using a technique
called photogrametry...
...where we were gonna create
large chunks of the city...
...based on multiple-positioned
camera photographs of New York.
It turned out that that technique
didn't provide us enough resolution.
Meaning that the buildings
we created that way...
...didn't have enough detail in them
for the camera to get close to them.
We then decided instead
of doing that...
...to use conventional...
...surveyors' instruments...
...to create a mathematical model
of buildings in much higher detail...
...and use still photographs of the
surfaces of those buildings to be...
...stretched back
onto that geometry.
We had the shape of the building and
we had a picture of the surfaces...
...on the building. We placed
those surfaces onto the building.
It's called mapping.
And as you look at this...
As we continues through this...
...you're gonna see extensive
use of this technique.
We had buildings in the middle ground,
foreground, and in the distance.
Some were in original photography
and some were added in after the fact.
The other weakness
photogrametry had was you tend...
...to get the built
in lighting of the day...
...so it depends on
how overcast it is...
...the sun's angle, what time of day.
You don't have leeway.
Our buildings had to hold up
for different sun angles...
...and different times of day.
So our main texture painter guy,
Carey, ended up taking all the photos.
They painted out a lot of detail that
we'd add back in later with lighting.
Also, paint the edges
so we could tile...
...and reuse some of that photography
to extend buildings.
Talk about the tiles. That's an
important thing that we used.
- The tiles in terms of...
- Just how we did it.
We started out making
this whole building system.
We knew we would have complex
scenes that had a lot of geometry.
We made our buildings
as building blocks.
We used a system that Steve LeVietes
created in Houdini software...
...to easily instance pieces
and assemble them all together.
Also there was a notion that
when we took these photos...
...they had to seam up on the edges.
If you look at real buildings,
there's lots of variation in color...
...and lighting across
these buildings.
Our texture painters had to balance
those out of the textures...
...make them so they could seam up
together and work generically.
The beautiful thing about the
tiles is, you get this hemisphere...
...which functions as a plate.
But a normal plate, you've gotta work
within what the camera has shot.
When you have this hemisphere
of tiles stitched together...
...you can move
the camera all around...
...and create your own camera move
within this background.
Our pan and tile system...
...which was another technique we used
to put behind our CG buildings.
The camera sits in one place.
You take a shot and then tilt up.
Take one to the right and left,
until you have these...
...photos that define or capture
the panorama before you.
If you look at David Hockney's art,
you see some of this kind of tiling.
We did it in a much more precise
fashion, but far less artistic.
It's a lot of single images
which are combined together...
...to create a much larger image
at high resolution.
That allows you to move in closer
and further away and to pan...
...and move up and down
on this big domed projection.
It's a technique that's been
getting more and more...
...in use over the last couple
of years.
Many years ago, you'd have
to assemble it in 3-D and render out.
Nowadays, at Imageworks,
we've got a system...
...where we do it in our last
compositing stage so it's much faster.
One of the interesting things about
visual effects in movies is that...
...you start out with scripts that have
more stuff than you can afford to do.
Using resource as a definition
of time and money.
You always have twice the material
as you have the resource to do.
Throughout the creation of the film,
you have to go back...
...and constantly be on top of deciding
where you'll put the resource.
We knew we had to create a virtual
version of the Spider-Man character...
...a virtual version of the Goblin...
...and a virtual version of
portions of New York...
...to allow us to do the kinds of
camera moves that we wanted...
...because they weren't allowing
anybody to swing through the streets.
So those were our primary
allocations of resource.
Then as the script developed,
as we worked on the movie...
...the story became clearer to us.
We then had to re-evaluate where we
were putting our efforts or resource.
And one of the things that was...
We also knew we had to do the web.
The web was a component
of resource allocation.
But as we continued
through the process...
...we had to re-evaluate
what was being put into the film.
We'd get new sequences they
wanted to make a story point.
Then that sequence would be evaluated,
then abandoned because of expense.
And that was going on
for the live-action stuff as well.
It requires that you be very flexible.
You have to be willing to abandon
a scene that you like that you've...
...spent months developing since
it no longer applies in the story.
That's the hardest thing in doing
visual effects and filmmaking...
...is giving away your "babies,"
so to speak...
...in pursuit of a more
effective storytelling.
You also have to be willing to meet...
...an impossible challenge at the last
moment. When we did this film...
...it wasn't unusual
in the last two or three weeks...
...for the director and editor to
come up with a shot that required...
...some heroic performance.
We talked about one of the shots
earlier which was Spider-Man...
...swinging through buildings
on his way to the fire.
That shot came out
through animation, lighting...
...and compositing in record time.
You have to be light on your feet...
...and willing to pursue the end
goal of the story, first and foremost.
Seems like on every film,
you always promise something...
...that you have no idea
whether or not you can do.
You have to.
And that's generally how new ways
of doing things are created.
What's interesting
is that Sam's very pragmatic.
He chose, in many cases,
to use practical effects...
...meaning mechanical
effects or stunts.
Other filmmakers I've
worked with have defaulted...
...to a digital solution immediately.
He'd explore more traditional methods
extensively before allocating...
...that visual effects resource
to a single shot or a sequence.
And I think that that shows up
in his understanding of this story.
He knows where he wants
to put the money, the resource...
...in terms of the telling
of the story.
Just another note,
there's a sort of different class...
...of shot that's
become more popular recently...
...and that's these product placement
or product replacement shots.
We went through a sequence earlier
where he's shooting at a can.
- Of course, we replaced products.
- Three different kinds of cans.
We went through different
types of cans.
There's a critical phone call shot
coming up where Tobey's on the phone...
...and it was a brand of payphone
nobody wanted to see in the shot.
So we had one of our
vendors take it out.
So there's a lot of attention to those
sort of details that happens nowadays.
I think people must think
that people will want to...
...drink and eat the same
things that Spider-Man does.
- I think so.
- I do.
I personally eat almost every sugared
cereal that has his picture on it.
How do you think
he makes all that web?
You were supposed to be asleep.
You know, you were about 6 years old
when M.J.'s family moved in next door.
When she got out of the car,
and you saw her for the first time...
...you grabbed me and said,
"Aunt May, is that an angel?"
- Did I say that?
- You sure did.
Now it'll get fast and furious.
This last portion of the movie goes
at about 100 miles an hour.
We'll never be able
to talk fast enough.
We should go through all the methods
that we were thinking of.
There's a moment
when he has to jettison...
...himself to the
Queensborough Bridge...
...and he attaches his webs
to the top of these flagpoles...
...pulls himself backward
and then lets go and springs off.
We went through several ideas
on how to get him over there.
From cannons to clock springs, to...
So much of this next
sequence is all virtual sets.
It gave us flexibility
to explore ideas like that.
The thing that's interesting
to me is that...
...we paid very little attention
to physics.
The truth is,
I'm a stickler for physics.
I like to make stuff kind of stay
within the practical world.
That probably is a disadvantage.
Actually, it's probably
a good balance...
...because Sam
and the writers' penchant...
...is for writing stuff that's so
fantastic that you might not buy it.
So I temper that particular tendency
on their part by going:
"Physically, this couldn't happen."
So the sequences that you see here,
swing from one end of the pole...
...to the other. Things that
are practical and that aren't.
But the truth is, it all goes together
in a way where you're not aware of it.
I think that the willing suspension
of disbelief has been achieved here.
In a couple of these shots,
Anthony and I also got little cameos.
- We're people on the ground...
- That's my daughter right there.
That's Chloe.
That was a shot by Brad Booker
of him looking into the tram.
It was a shot done early on
and Sam liked...
...the acting from the Goblin.
Lit by Kevin Hahn. It was one
of our first lighting jobs on Goblin.
This is an integration of all manner
of mechanical effects too.
We photographed explosions
against black so we could...
...combine them in those images.
There are miniatures...
...combined with computer generated
cables and cable cars and people.
This is a real potpourri
of the visual effects techniques.
We shot from the top
of the Queensborough Bridge.
We were gonna climb to the top
of the bridge and photograph...
Here's Anthony's shot of him being
shot to the bridge with the flagpoles.
Chris Williams, Ken Morissey,
Bill Diaz did this great shot of him.
And then James Pam's does the shot
where he comes over the top here.
This is a real great shot in the film.
It was a beautiful shot.
So this is again...
Mechanical effects boys...
...had to provide wind, explosions,
fog, smoke and all kinds of things.
So it's another case where departments
had to collaborate extensively.
We did lots of photography
on Roosevelt Island in New York.
It was exciting to have our own
Roosevelt Island tram car.
We rented it. We could make it go back
and forth, wherever we wanted to.
What pre-visualization
did for us is...
...when you've a sequence where points
of view aren't on the same level...
...you have to establish the camera's
angle relative to the live action.
Pre-visualization allowed us to say:
The camera needs to be 40 feet below
the subject on a 15 millimeter lens.
Those kinds of details allowed us to
photograph our characters...
...in some cases,
against green screen...
...then put them into a photography
of the real bridge or a CGI bridge.
Ken Hahn is the CG
supervisor of this...
...and did a great job pulling together
all the green screen and CG elements...
...and putting up with listening
to me talk about the black levels...
...and different variations
across the images.
This is a difficult area, to keep the
character doing the same thing...
...all the time so there's a continuity
of what he does in the physical world.
You have a temptation to make
the character do something human...
...and you can't
let yourself fall into that.
Just like before when he was shooting
web and going through the bridge.
He comes up, flies over the top
and I had him landing so hard...
...in this big follow through.
Sam said, "He can't do that."
I said, "He has to do that."
I thought about it and he was right.
He's not a person, he's Spider-Man.
As opposed to this,
which a person could easily do.
Lots of pieces went
into this sequence.
The toughest part is you're working
with a large set piece, this bridge.
You get close to the characters, it's
hard to see the bridge and vice versa.
So this was a real tour de force
of editing and design of sequence...
...to integrate the pieces so you
had a sense of the environment...
...but were still close enough to the
characters to read their emotions.
It was interesting to just set up all
the lighting of our virtual sets...
...and matched pieces. Sometimes
it worked, sometimes it didn't.
We just dialed in different fall offs
and bright and dark areas for shots.
Spider-Man, watch out!
Interesting thing about this,
this is our "hulking ruin" sequence.
Spider-Man gets pretty beat up
in this sequence.
We made a full CG version
of Spider-Man completely beat up.
One of our guys
painted beautiful maps.
It's this pristine CG model
that looks fabulous.
And by the end of the cut that
they made, it was no longer in there.
I hope in the sequel, there's
an area where he's beat up...
...pretty similarly to this so we can
use that model. I'm sure we won't.
That was the shot that,
because of the rating system...
He had a mouthful of blood
spewing out...
...and to get the rating down
to PG-13, we had to turn that blood...
...from red to clear to be spit.
We had to take out a bit so it didn't
look like he was spewing a fountain.
This was an interesting solution
with the web.
This is of course a new kind of web...
...but also had to look like the real
web because it was already shot.
Todd Boyce spent a lot of time
weaving that pattern...
...making it match the next shot.
This sequence really got out down.
At one point, it went on for days.
The thing that happens
is these sequences...
...end up being distillations
of much, much larger vintages.
The Razorbats used to be
in this sequence.
There were Razorbats and even another
kind of thing at some point.
In this sequence, there were flocks
of them all over the place.
But again,
I think that the distillation...
...really focuses on the
development of the characters.
That's the saving grace of this
movie. You pay more attention...
...to the people involved
than you do to the...
- Action.
- Action, yeah.
This is definitely an homage to
some of Sam's earlier movies.
Army of Darkness or whatever.
A lot of speed up on this thing.
Did that wall move or no?
- Can't give away all the secrets.
- I'm sorry.
Again the spider sense
comes into play here.
The spider sense thing was a huge
combination of many elements.
It's a beautiful digital blade
that comes out of this.
It comes out of the glider.
It's photography
done on the set, paintwork...
...some CG components
that were generated...
...in three dimensions and painted and
added. The glider is a virtual...
...version of the glider,
a CGI version...
...and that's combined with our...
...actually live actor
in the foreground.
Give me your hand.
For the spider sense shot coming up,
Dan Kramer did a great job...
...because we shot different ideas,
motion control...
...and the end result ended up being
a combination of some of those ideas.
So we had to piece together
different photography in.
Godspeed, Spider-Man.
That shot right there.
We also, actually, had to try
to give a character to the glider...
...to have it and a certain feeling,
as silly as that may sound.
Well, it's back to
your faithful servant, the glider...
...hanging out,
waiting to take care...
...of the threat.
And of course that sequence was cut
down to get into the PG-13 rating.
Some of our work was
cut out of there as well.
I'm sure in the director's cut, the
R-rated version, that'll show up.
What have you done?!
A lot of these shots have to be
leading towards sequels to come.
Setting up some of the situations.
So this is the set-up
before the final shot...
...in which Sam had a small request...
...that the animation
in this last shot...
...be more incredible,
more astounding.
The all time, best animated shot in
history. That was all he asked for.
We went away and tried to do that.
This went through many generations.
But it was interesting to see...
...as we got down I think John
has said before, what is it?
Ninety percent of your time you
spend getting ready for the shot...
...and 10 percent getting it done.
All the camera moves
and the animation.
There were minute adjustments
on these things.
One frame of a change
of a move where the camera...
...would come close to a
building or move.
It really got down to a beautiful shot
that I think is well remembered...
...in great animation
by Peter Giliberti.
Lighting and compositing-wise
it came down to the wire.
Like, our artists Marc Rienzo,
Jeff Stern, Dan Abrams...
...Laurence, Dan Eaton
all these guys in the last week...
...working around the clock,
sleeping under their desks.
It's funny, the president
of our company, Tim Sarnoff...
...had to come and force these guys
to go home and walk them out.
We had people drive them home
so they wouldn't crash.
That's how dedicated
they were to this last shot.
It took about seven months
for this last shot.
When you watch this shot...
...I mean, if you've seen the movie in
a theatre where it's on a big screen...
...it actually succeeds in getting you
to sort of be physically involved...
...in swinging through the city.
In terms of a storytelling component...
...it gives you a sense of what
it's like to be Spider-Man.
Not the irony where he has
to deny the woman of his dreams...
...but where you understand
why he goes forward.
Why he sees some
kind of real future...
...in the business of being responsible
for this power he wields.
It comes along
with some great fun too.
And I think that this shot
embodies all of those things.
It embodies the best of the work
of the visual effects in the movie.
I love you so much, Peter.
All I wanted was to tell her
how much I loved her.
I can't...
You can't what?
Tell you...
...everything.
I mean, there's so much to tell.
Yeah. There's so much to tell.
I want you to know...
...that I will always be there
for you.
I will always be there
to take care of you.
I promise you that.
I will always be your friend.
Only a friend...
...Peter Parker?
That's all I have to give.
Whatever life holds in store for me...
...I will never forget these words:
"With great power
comes great responsibility."
In the performance of the character,
in the beginning...
...he's not sure what move to make,
where to shoot his web...
...how to move around it.
And through the film he develops.
Whereas in this shot, you feel
that he knows where he's going...
...and exactly what he's doing and
he's in control of his movement.
I think a lot of the photography ended
up helping us out in the last shot.
The photography that we got on that
Sunday in downtown L.A. swinging...
...through the cars
and everything built off of that.
And that stuff you got in New York
for the tiles. The sort of...
...golden-hour looking tiles that we
processed and pushed more.
That sort of grounded it and gave us a
base to build our virtual environment.
Also we had good success
with finishing the buildings off...
...and figuring out how to use them
in the lighting...
...environment to make them feel
more real. So when you...
...get to the point of watching...
...what he's doing and what's
happening around him...
...it's very spectacular.
The composition,
the choice of buildings...
...the color compositing.
Even if it were something that were...
...done for real and wasn't put
together as elements...
...it would be
a very successful shot.