[Peter] She looks at me every day.
Mary Jane Watson.
Oh, boy.
If she only knew how I felt about her.
But she can never know.
I made a choice once to live
a life of responsibility,
a life she can never be a part of.
Who am I?
I'm Spider-Man, given a job to do.
And I'm Peter Parker,
and I, too, have a job.
[Aziz] Parker! Parker!
No, no, no, no! Stop! Stop!
[tires screech]
Parker, you're late, man.
Always late, huh?
I'm sorry, Mr. Aziz,
there was a...disturbance.
Disturbance?
Always a disturbance with you.
Come on. Twenty-one minutes ago,
in comes order. Harmattan, Burton & Smith.
Eight extra-large deep-dish pizzas.
In eight minutes, I am defaulting
on Joe's 29-minute guarantee.
Then not only am I receiving
no money for these pizzas,
but I will lose the customer
forever to Pizza Yurt.
Look, you are my only hope, all right?
You have to make it in time.
Peter, you're a nice guy,
but you're just not dependable.
This is your last chance.
You have to go 42 blocks
in seven and one-half minutes,
or your ass is fired.
Go!
[horn beeping]
-[tires screech]
-[horn beeping]
[backfires]
[tires screech]
[man] Hey, what are you, stupid?
[bus horn blares]
[horns honking]
[panting]
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
He stole that guy's pizzas!
[child] My ball! I'm gonna get it!
Yah!
[horn honks]
[child grunts]
Hm.
Hey, you guys, no playing in the streets.
-[both] Yes, Mr. Spider-Man.
-See ya.
-[grunts]
-[onlooker] Way to go, Spidey!
[grunting]
[mellow music playing]
[clattering]
-[grunts softly]
-[clanging]
Pizza time.
[ticking]
You're late.
I'm not paying for those.
[Aziz] Joe's 29-minute guarantee
is a promise, man.
I know to you, Parker,
a promise means nothing,
but to me, it's serious.
It's serious to me too, Mr. Aziz.
You're fired. Go.
-Please, I need this job.
-You're fired.
Look, give me another chance.
[Jameson] You're fired.
-Parker, hello. You're fired.
-Why?
Dogs catching Frisbees?
Pigeons in the park?
A couple of geezers playing chess?
-Boss--
-Not now!
I was thinking maybe the Bugle could show
another side of New York for a change.
We got six minutes to deadline, Jonah.
We need page one.
I don't pay you to be a sensitive artiste.
I pay you because-- Still not now!
I pay you because, for some reason,
that psycho Spider-Man will pose for you.
Spider-Man won't let me take
any more pictures.
-You've turned the whole city against him.
-A fact I'm very proud of.
Now, get your pretty little portfolio off
my desk before I go into a diabetic coma.
[intercom buzzes]
Boss, your wife's on the line.
She lost her checkbook.
-Thanks for the good news.
-Mr. Jameson, please,
isn't there any of these shots
you can use?
-I really need the money.
-Aw. Miss Brant?
-Yes?
-Get me a violin.
Five minutes to deadline, Jonah.
All right, run a picture of a rancid
chicken. Here's the headline:
-"Food Poisoning Scare Sweeps City."
-Some food got poisoned?
-I'm a little nauseous, yeah.
-All right, Mr. Jameson.
It stinks.
Robbie, there's your page one.
"Masked Menace Terrorizes Town."
I told you, he's not a menace.
-And I told you--
-I'll take care of it.
-I'll give you 150.
-300.
That's outrageous!
Done. Give this to the girl.
Thank you, bye-bye.
Hi.
Hey, Pete.
Oh. I don't think this covers the
advance I gave you a couple weeks ago.
-Oh...right.
-Sorry.
Hey. Chin up, okay?
-Oh!
-[student] Watch it, jerk!
Oh, hey. Wow.
Dr. Connors. Sorry.
Where were you headed, Parker?
-To your class.
-My class is over.
See me standing here?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm trying. I… I wanna be here.
Then be here.
[sighs softly]
Look at you, Peter.
Your grades have been steadily declining.
You're late for class.
You always appear exhausted.
Your paper on fusion is still overdue.
I know. I'm planning to write it
on Dr. Otto Octavius.
Planning is not a major
at this university.
Octavius is a friend of mine.
Better do your research, Parker.
Get it done, or I'm failing you.
-[all] Surprise!
-[tooting]
-Well, say something.
-Uh, what's the occasion?
-Really, Peter! It's your birthday.
-"What's the occasion?"
Whether you want to
remember it or not. [chuckles]
He lives in another reality.
Don't you, Pete?
-Hi, M.J.
-Hi.
-Hey, buddy.
-Hey.
Long time, no see.
So, uh, how's the play?
-I read a great review.
-It's going fine. It's going good.
-She's brilliant in it.
-Harry sent me roses.
So where you been, pal?
You don't return my calls.
I've been busy.
Taking pictures of Spider-Man?
How's the bug these days?
The less you see of that man, the better.
Now, let's all go into the other room
and have something to eat, hm?
I'll get the hors d'oeuvres.
-So how are things going at OsCorp?
-Oh, they're great.
I'm head of Special Projects.
We're about to make
a breakthrough on fusion.
Oh, how lovely, Harry.
Your father would be so proud,
rest his soul.
Thank you.
We're actually funding one
of your idols, Pete. Otto Octavius.
-I'm writing a paper on him.
-You want to meet him?
-You'd introduce me?
-You bet.
Octavius is gonna put OsCorp on the map
in a way my father never even dreamed of.
-M.J., could you give me a hand?
-Huh? Oh.
-She's waiting for you, pal.
-What do you mean?
Oh, the way she looks at you
or doesn't look at you,
however you want to look at it.
-I don't have time for girls right now.
-Why, are you dead?
I've been kind of busy.
Taking pictures of your friend?
Could we get off that subject?
I want us to be friends, Harry.
I want us to trust each other.
Then be honest with me.
If you knew who he was, would you tell me?
[sighs]
[clock chiming]
[whispers] May.
-May.
-Oh, what, Ben? Hmm?
Wait. Oh...
-Aunt May.
-Oh, my.
[chuckles] Oh, Peter.
Oh, for a second there,
I thought I was years ago.
[sighs]
Everybody's gone, aren't they?
Did they have a good time?
I'm sure they did.
-You okay?
-Of course.
But you go home.
And be careful.
I don't like that scooter thing
you drive around.
I'm worried about you. You're so...
alone.
And I saw the letter from the bank.
Oh, my. You did?
Oh, well. So?
I'm a little behind.
Everybody is.
Anyway, I don't want
to talk about it anymore.
I'm tired, and you better start back home.
[chuckles] Here, kiddo. Happy birthday.
You need it more than I do.
-No, I-- I can't take that from--
-Yes, you can!
You can take this money from me.
[crying] For God's sake, it's not much.
Now, take it!
And don't you dare leave it here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[sighs heavily] It's just that
I miss your Uncle Ben so much.
Can you believe that it's...
two years next month since he was taken?
I think to myself at times...
were I to face the one responsible
for what happened, I'd...
Oh, I don't know what I'd do.
[sniffles] Oh...
Now...
you better take
the rest of your cake home.
[inhales]
[dog barking]
[Mary Jane] Hey.
Hey. You're still here.
I saw your billboard on Bleecker.
Isn't it funny?
I'm really kind of embarrassed.
Don't be. It's nice.
I get to see you every day now.
I liked seeing you tonight, Peter.
Oh, boy, yeah.
"Oh, boy, yeah" what?
Nothing.
Do you want to say something?
I...
was… [clears throat]
wondering i-if you're still
in the Village.
[sighs softly]
You're such a mystery.
[whispers] Peter.
[whispers] What?
Happy birthday.
I'm seeing somebody now.
You mean, like a boyfriend?
Well...like, I like him.
-[quietly] Uh...
-What?
Nothing. [clears throat]
That's good, you know? Companionship...
Maybe more than that.
More?
[sighs] I don't know.
I'm gonna come see your play
tomorrow night.
You...You're coming?
I'll be there.
Don't disappoint me.
I won't.
[footsteps]
[festive folk music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[landlord] Rent!
[music grows louder]
-Hi.
-What's "hi"? Can I spend it?
-Uh…
-I have a paycheck due this week and--
-You're a month late again.
-Again.
-I promise as soon as--
If promises were crackers,
my daughter would be fat. [chuckles]
I'm really sorry, Mr. Ditkovitch,
you know.
All I got is this 20
for the rest of the week--
Ah! "Sorry" doesn't pay the rent.
And don't try to sneak past me.
I have ears like a cat.
And eyes...like a rodent.
Thanks, Mr. Ditkovitch.
Hi, Pete. Ah! Oh!
[door creaks]
[locks clicking]
[train rumbling outside]
[glasses clinking]
[rumbling fades]
[sighs]
[knocks on door]
Hello?
[grunts]
Rent?
-Doctor? Mr. Osborn's here.
-[Harry] Nobel Prize, Otto.
-Nobel Prize, and we'll all be rich.
-Yeah.
It's not about the prizes, Harry.
-Nah, but you need money. You need OsCorp.
-Who do we have here?
This is my good friend I called you about.
The guy who got me through
high-school science.
-Peter Parker, sir.
-Parker.
-I'm writing a paper on you for--
-Yes, yes, I know what you're doing here,
but I really don't have time
to talk to students right now.
-[clears throat]
-But OsCorp pays the bills so...
That's right. That's why I have
to take off, board meeting,
but my job is done here.
Got you two geniuses together.
Good luck tomorrow, Otto.
Nobel Prize. [chuckles]
We'll see you in Sweden.
Interesting fellow, your friend.
-Well, I won't take much of your time--
-Parker. Now I remember you.
You're Connors' student.
Tells me you're brilliant.
He also tells me you're lazy.
-I'm trying to do better.
-Being brilliant's not enough, young man.
You have to work hard.
Intelligence is not a privilege,
it's a gift,
and you use it for the good of mankind.
[operator] You wanna try back there?
-So...is that it?
-Yes.
My design to initiate and sustain fusion.
Well, I understand you use harmonics
of atomic frequencies.
-Sympathetic frequencies.
-Harmonic reinforcement?
Go on.
An exponential increase in energy output.
A huge amount of energy.
Like a perpetual sun providing
renewable power for the whole world.
Are you sure you could
stabilize the fusion reaction?
Peter, what have we been talking about
for the last hour and a half?
This is my life's work.
I certainly know the consequences
of the slightest miscalculation.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to question you.
Rosie, our new friend thinks
I'm gonna blow up the city.
You can sleep soundly tonight.
Otto's done his homework.
Come to the demonstration tomorrow
and you'll see for yourself.
-You need to sleep soundly tonight, Otto.
-[scoffs]
Did Edison sleep
before he turned on the light?
Did Marconi sleep
before he turned on the radio?
Did Beethoven sleep
before he wrote the "Fifth"?
Did Bernoulli sleep before he found
the curves of quickest descent?
Ah, Rosie, I love this boy.
Peter, tell us about yourself.
-Do you have a girlfriend?
-Uh, well...
I don't really know.
Well, shouldn't you know?
Who would know?
Oh, leave him alone.
Maybe it's a secret love.
Love should never be a secret.
If you keep something as complicated
as love stored up inside,
gonna make you sick.
I finally got lucky in love.
We both did.
But it's hardly perfect.
You have to work at it.
I met him on the college steps
and I knew it wasn't going to be easy.
He was studying science,
and I was studying English literature.
That's right. I was trying
to explain the theory of relativity...
[Rosie] Mm-hmm.
...and Rosie was trying
to explain T.S. Eliot.
[chuckles]
I still don't understand
what he was talking about.
-Oh, come on.
-I'm serious.
T.S. Eliot is more complicated
than advanced science.
But if you want to get a woman
to fall in love with you...
feed her poetry.
Poetry.
Never fails.
[Peter] "A tall and slender maiden
All alone upon a prairie
Brightest green were all her garments
And her hair was like the sunshine
Day by day he gazed upon her--"
[machine buzzes]
[groans]
["Hold On" by Jet playing]
You tried so hard to be someone
That you forgot who you are
You tried to fill some emptiness
Till all you had spilled over...
[Ditkovitch] Rent!
Now everything's so far away...
Where's my money?
[muttering]
[speaking Russian]
You are
Well, all that you wanted
And all that you have don't seem so much
'Cause you'd hold on to...
-You seem jittery tonight.
-Oh.
You never know who's coming.
'Cause you'd hold on to
You'd belong to...
Ladies, five minutes. Five minutes.
[siren blaring]
How'd you do that?
Uh...
Work out, plenty of rest.
You know, eat your green vegetables.
That's what my mom is always saying.
I just never actually believed her.
Come on. Go.
-[tires squealing]
-[horns honking]
Keep it steady.
[crowd yelling]
[all gasping]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[glass tinkles]
It's a web.
Go, Spidey, go!
Whoo!
We got trouble!
-[bullets ricocheting]
-[grunts]
-Oh!
-Ah!
-Whoa!
-[screams]
Argh! Get me down!
[English accent] I am more than content
with what Mr. Moncrieff said.
His voice alone inspires one
with absolute credulity.
Then you think we should forgive them?
[scoffs softly]
Yes.
I mean, no.
[tires squeal]
Hey. Hey. Hey, chief.
If you park there, I'm towing it.
Whatever.
Uh, shoelace.
-[actors speaking indistinctly]
-[audience laughing]
You might wanna...
-Can I help you?
-Yeah, I, uh…
-come to see the show.
-Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
No one will be seated
after the doors are closed.
It helps maintain the illusion.
Uh, Miss Watson, she's a friend of mine.
She asked me to come.
But not to come late.
Well, I have to see this show.
Just let me in,
-I'll stand in the--
-Shh.
-[dialogue continues on stage]
-[audience laughs]
Mm.
[busker plays intro on violin]
[busker plucks strings]
Spider-Man, Spider-Man
Does whatever a spider can
Spins a web any size
Catches thieves just like flies
Look out
Here comes Spider-Man...
[overlapping chatter]
-Sure you don't wanna come tonight?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Okay. Call me.
-I will.
-You were great tonight.
-Thanks.
[man] May I have
an autograph, please, miss?
[laughs] What are you doing here?
[sirens blaring]
-You hungry?
-Starved.
Yah!
[sirens blaring]
Huh? Ah! [yelling]
[grunts]
[groaning]
What was that?
Okay.
[clicking]
[car horns honking]
Huh.
-[elevator bell dings]
-[dog whimpers]
[elevator music plays]
[elevator bell dings]
Cool Spidey outfit.
Thanks.
Where'd you get it?
I-I made it.
Hm.
Looks uncomfortable.
Yeah, it gets kind of itchy.
And it rides up in the crotch
a little bit too.
[clicks button]
[dials phone]
-[ringing tone]
-[clears throat]
[man] The other way, the other way!
[Mary Jane] Hi, it's me.
-Sing your song at the beep.
-[beep]
Hi, M.J. This is Peter.
I was on my way to your show, and...
Well...
I was on my bike...
Uh...
[sighs] Are you there?
I really was planning on it all day.
And...
I know you predicted I'd disappoint you.
Bingo.
It's amazing, isn't it?
How complicated a simple thing...
like...being someplace at 8:00 can become.
[chuckles]
Actually...
-there was this obnoxious usher.
-[sighs]
-Somebody has to talk to that usher, M.J.
-[beep]
[operator] Your time has expired.
Please deposit 50 cents
for the next five minutes.
[dial tone]
[hangs up]
[sighs] I wanna tell you the truth.
Here it is.
I'm Spider-Man.
Weird, huh?
[inhales]
Now you know why I can't be with you.
If my…enemies...
found out about you...
if you got hurt,
I could never forgive myself.
[sighs softly]
I wish I could tell you
how I feel about you.
[sighs]
-Hello, Dave.
-How's it going?
Ladies and gentlemen, my wife Rosie and I
would like to welcome you this afternoon.
But first, before we start,
has anybody lost a large roll
of $20 bills in a rubber band?
-Because we found the rubber band.
-[all laughing]
[laughs] It's a terrible joke.
But thank you for coming.
Today...
you will witness the birth
of a new fusion-based energy source.
Safe, renewable energy
and cheap electricity for everyone.
And now let me introduce my assistants.
These four actuators were developed
and programmed for the sole purpose
of creating successful fusion.
They are impervious to heat and magnetism.
[clicking]
[whirring]
[hums]
[whirring and squishing]
[click]
[all groan]
[whizzing]
[clicking]
These smart arms are controlled
by my brain through a neural link.
Nanowires feed directly
into my cerebellum,
allowing me to use these arms
to control fusion reaction in an
environment no human hand could enter.
Doctor, if the artificial intelligence
in the arms
is as advanced as you suggest, uh,
couldn't that make you vulnerable to them?
How right you are. Which is why
I developed this inhibitor chip
to protect my higher brain function.
It means I maintain control of these arms,
instead of them controlling me.
And now, on to the main event.
Give me the blue light, Rosie.
[switch clicks]
Precious tritium is the fuel
that makes this project go.
There's only 25 pounds of it
on the whole planet.
I'd like to thank Harry Osborn
and OsCorp Industries for providing it.
Happy to pay the bills, Otto.
[energy buzzing]
Ladies and gentlemen...
fasten your seat belts.
[electronic humming and popping]
[energy whirring]
[whirring intensifies]
Doctor, we have
a successful fusion reaction.
[applause]
This is a breakthrough
beyond your father's dreams.
Thank you.
[assistant] We're producing
a thousand-megawatt surplus.
The power of the sun...
in the palm of my hand.
[metal creaking]
[whirring, clicking]
[all gasping]
Keep calm! It's only a spike!
It'll soon stabilize!
[people clamoring]
-Pete.
-[Rosie] Ladies and gentlemen,
please clear the room!
[alarm sounding]
We have a containment breach!
-Huh?
-[energy crackling]
Otto, please get back! [screams]
Shut it off, Otto! Shut it off!
It will stabilize! It's under control!
I'm in charge here! It's my money!
I'm in con--
This doesn't change anything.
-What are you doing?
-Pulling the plug.
-No!
-[grunts]
[gasps]
[glass shattering]
[screams]
Rosie! [yelling]
[beeps]
Huh?
[groaning]
[grunts]
[electricity sputtering]
[panting]
[siren wailing]
[overlapping chatter]
[paramedic] Watch it.
-That was too close.
-If he had more than a drop of tritium,
he could've destroyed the city.
I'm ruined. [breathes heavily]
I have nothing left, except Spider-Man.
-[assistant] He saved your life, sir.
-He humiliated me by touching me.
Mr. Osborn, the press'll be here soon.
I suggest we move on.
What was he doing here, anyway?
[doctor] As you can see,
molten metal penetrated the spinal cavity
and fused the vertebrae
at multiple points,
including the lamina
and the roof of the spinal column.
We won't know the extent of the damage
until we get in there,
so I suggest we cut off
these mechanical arms,
slice up the harness, and if need be,
consider a laminectomy
with posterior spinal fusion
from C-7, T-1 to T-12.
[nurse] We're ready, Doctor.
Anybody here take shop class?
[all laughing]
[heart monitor beeping]
[gasps]
[screams]
[all yelling]
[shrieks]
[grunts]
[yells]
[screaming]
No!
No! No! No-- [screams]
Help me! Help me!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[screams]
[metal scraping]
[yelling]
[panting]
[yells]
[groaning]
[screams]
[saw buzzing]
[screaming]
[screams]
[howls] No!
[horn honks]
[tires screech]
It's all over town, Robbie. Gossip.
Rumors. Panic in the streets.
If we're lucky.
Crazy scientist turns himself
into some kind of a monster.
Four mechanical arms
welded right onto his body.
[chuckles] Guy named Otto Octavius
winds up with eight limbs.
What are the odds?
-Hoffman!
-Yeah?
-What we gonna call this guy?
-Uh... "Dr. Octopus."
-That's crap.
-Oh, uh, "Science Squid"?
-Crap.
-"Dr. Strange."
That's pretty good.
But it's taken.
Wait, wait. I got it.
"Dr. Octopus."
-B-but-- I like it.
-Of course you do.
Dr. Octopus. New villain in town.
"Doc Ock."
-Genius.
-What, are you looking for a raise?
Get out.
Chief, I found Parker.
Where you been?
Why don't you pay your phone bill?
Mad scientist goes berserk
and we don't have pictures!
I heard Spider-Man was there.
Where were you? Photographing squirrels?
-You're fired.
-Chief, the planetarium party.
Oh, right. You're un-fired.
I need you. Come here.
What do you know about high society?
-Oh. Uh, well, I--
-Ah, don't answer that.
My society photographer
got hit in the head by a polo ball.
You're all I got.
Big party for an American hero.
My son, the astronaut.
But could you pay me in advance?
[laughing hysterically]
You serious?
Pay you for what, standing there?
The planetarium, tomorrow night, 8:00.
There's the door.
[gulls cawing]
My Rosie's dead.
My dream is dead.
And these...
monstrous things
should be at the bottom of the river...
along with me.
[tentacle screeches]
Something...
in my head.
Something talking.
The inhibitor chip!
Gone.
[whirs]
Rebuild.
No.
Peter was right.
I miscalculated.
I couldn't have miscalculated.
It was working, wasn't it?
Yes.
We could rebuild.
Enlarge the containment field.
Make it bigger and stronger than ever.
But we need money.
-[whirs]
-Steal it?
No, no, no, I'm not a criminal.
[whirs, chirps]
That's right.
The real crime would be
not to finish what we started.
We'll do it here.
The power of the sun
in the palm of my hand.
Nothing will stand in our way. Nothing!
-[Aunt May] That's the Social Security.
-Yes, I see.
-My Uncle Ben's life insurance.
-Yes.
But I'm afraid it's just not sufficient
to refinance your home.
-Oh, but I'm giving piano lessons again.
-You are?
Ow!
Oh, ow...
Wh--?
W-we appreciate that
you've just opened up a...
a new supersaver account with us today.
But the fact is, you do not
have the assets to justify this loan.
I'm sorry.
Well...
[chuckles]
at least we get the toaster.
Actually, that's only
with a deposit of, uh, 300 or more.
Oh...
Oh, yes, I see.
Okay.
[Peter] Don't worry, we'll figure it out.
[grunting]
[people gasping, screaming]
[gasping]
Peter?
Don't leave me!
Oh, that boy of yours is a real hero.
[guard] Hold it! Put your arms up!
-All of them!
-[grunts]
[guards yell and groan]
[whirring]
Hah!
Here's your change!
[grunts]
[growls]
-[grunts]
-[clicking]
-Oh, no. Come on!
Ah!
Ha!
[grunts]
-Uh-bup-bup!
-Ow!
You're getting on my nerves.
-I have a knack for that.
-Not anymore.
[groaning]
[roars]
Ah?
[grunts]
[people shrieking]
[groans]
[growls]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[tires screech]
-Freeze! Don't move!
-Freeze! Freeze!
[screams]
-Hold your fire.
-Don't follow me.
[Aunt May] Oh!
Wait a second.
[customer] That won't be charged
to my card for seven days?
-[heavy thuds approach]
-Thank you so much.
[screaming]
-Hand her over!
-Of course.
-Easy now.
-[sighing]
-[screams]
-Butterfingers.
[groans]
[grunts]
Oh! Ooh. Oh...
Look out!
[people screaming]
Help me!
-Help me!
-I'm coming!
[whimpering]
Hang on!
[glass shatters]
[shrieks]
Help!
[grunting]
[glass shatters]
[yells]
[wind whistling]
[gasping]
[panting]
Thank you.
[screams]
Aunt May.
You've stuck your webs
in my business for the last time!
Now you'll have this woman's death
on your conscience.
[grunting]
Come on.
-[yells]
-[gasps]
Shame on you.
[growls]
-[yells]
-[grunting]
[wailing]
[screams]
Whoo!
[gunfire]
[bullets ricocheting]
-[Aunt May wails]
-There you go.
[gasping]
Oh, thank you.
Oh, have I been wrong about you.
-We sure showed him.
-What do you mean "we"?
Oh.
[people clamoring]
-Take me with you, Spider-Man!
-No, take me!
[romantic jazz music playing]
[overlapping chatter]
-May I?
-Sure, go ahead.
[guest] Penny, over here!
[Harry] Leave it.
[glass shatters]
-[sighs]
-Hey.
-Might want to take it easy, buddy.
-Why? It's a party.
Wouldn't you be drinking
if you lost a bundle on some crackpot
who you thought was gonna take you
with him to fame and fortune?
Not to mention your friend, the bug.
-Not tonight, Harry.
-Every night.
Until I find him, it's 24/7.
[Jameson] Parker!
Parker! Parker! What, are you deaf?
I called you twice. Think I'm paying you
to sit around and sip champagne?
Here, get a shot of my wife
with the minister here.
Beautiful tie.
Ooh, no, get a shot of us with the D.A.
Oh, beautiful dress.
Ooh, here, get a shot of the mayor
and his girlfriend...
-[room goes quiet]
-Wife.
[presenter] Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
The committee for
the Science Library of New York
is pleased to present our guest of honor.
He's the first man
to play football on the moon.
-[crowd laughs]
-The handsome, the heroic,
the delicious, Captain John Jameson.
[band plays "Stars and Stripes Forever"]
[applause]
[guest] Johnny!
[indistinct conversation]
[band plays smooth jazz]
Hi.
Oh. [scoffs] You.
Listen, I'm sorry.
But there was a disturbance.
I don't know you.
And I can't keep thinking about you.
It's too painful.
-I've been reading poetry lately.
-Whatever that means.
"Day by day
He gazed upon her
Day by day
He sighed with passion
-Day by day--"
-Don't start.
Can I get you a drink?
I'm with John. He'll get me my drink.
John.
By the way,
John has seen my show five times.
Harry has seen it twice.
Aunt May has seen it.
My sick mother got out of bed to see it.
Even my father.
[scoffs] He came backstage to borrow cash.
But my best friend,
who cares so much about me,
can't make an 8:00 curtain.
After all these years...
he's nothing to me but an empty seat.
You know, it pisses me off, your loyalty
to Spider-Man and not to your best friend.
I find him with my father's body,
and you defend him because
he's your bread and butter.
-Hey, take it easy.
-Hey, don't push me.
Don't act like you're my friend.
You stole M.J. from me.
You stole my father's love.
Then you let him die because
you didn't turn in the freak.
-Isn't that right?
-[people gasp]
Huh? Isn't that right? Huh, brother?
[breathes heavily]
[people murmur, whisper]
[John] Ladies and gentlemen,
I just want you all to know that the...
beautiful Miss Mary Jane Watson
has just agreed to marry me.
[crowd coos, applauds]
[guest] What a surprise.
Parker, wake up!
Wake up! Shoot the picture!
[clicking]
-Oh, no. No!
-[clicking]
[grunting]
[groans]
[panting]
[clicking]
Why is this happening to me?
[yells]
[panting]
[grunts]
[groans]
[sighs]
Ah...
You seem very okay to me.
My diagnosis:
It's up here.
[removes gloves]
You say you can't sleep.
Heartbreak? Bad dreams?
T-there is one dream,
where…in my dream...
I'm Spider-Man.
But I'm losing my powers.
I'm climbing a wall, but I keep falling.
Oh.
So you're Spider-Man.
In my dream.
Well, actually, i-it's not even my dream.
It's a friend of mine's dream.
[chuckling] Oh...
Somebody else's dream.
[sighs]
What about this friend?
Why does he climb these walls?
What does he think of himself?
Well, that's the problem. He doesn't...
know what to think.
Gotta make you mad
not to know who you are.
Your soul disappears.
Nothing as bad as uncertainty.
Listen...
maybe you're not supposed to be...
Spider-Man climbing those walls.
That's why you keep falling.
You always have a choice, Peter.
I have a choice.
[thunder crashes]
[Uncle Ben] All the things
you've been thinking about, Peter...
make me sad.
Can't you understand?
I'm in love with Mary Jane.
Peter, all the times
we've talked of honesty,
fairness, justice.
All of those times, I counted on you
to have the courage
to take those dreams
out into the world.
I can't live your dreams anymore.
I want a life of my own.
You've been given a gift, Peter.
With great power,
comes great responsibility.
Take my hand, son.
[crying] No, Uncle Ben.
I'm just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man...
no more.
No more.
[thunder rumbling]
["Raindrops Keep Fallin' On My Head"
by B.J. Thomas playing]
Raindrops keep fallin' on my head
And just like a guy whose feet
are too big for his bed
Nothin' seems to fit
[grunts]
Those raindrops are fallin' on my head
They keep fallin'
So I just did me some talkin' to the sun
And I said I didn't like
the way he got things done
Sleepin' on the job
Those raindrops are fallin' on my head
They keep fallin'
Because I'm free
Nothing's worryin' me
-[crashing]
-[man] Hey!
-You punk!
-Sorry.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
[sirens blaring]
It won't be long
Till happiness
Steps up to greet me
Raindrops keep fallin'...
When the borderline is tau equals zero,
the eigen values are?
Someone, please?
.23 electron volts.
I'm never gonna stop the rain
by complainin'...
Excellent work today, Parker. Keep it up.
Because I'm free
Nothing's worryin'...
Me
[English accent] I'm not wicked, Cousin
Cecily. You mustn't think I'm wicked.
If you are not, then you have
certainly been deceiving us all
in a very inexcusable manner.
I hope you have not been
leading a double life,
pretending to be wicked
and being really good all the time.
That would be hypocrisy.
Oh. Of course I have been rather reckless.
[mouthing]
[prompter whispering] "I am glad."
"I am glad."
Are you glad to hear it?
Uh...
I am glad...to hear it.
In fact, now you mention the subject,
I have been very bad in my own small way.
[sighs] You were so wonderful.
-That was such a great play. I--
-You could've told me you were coming.
I was afraid you'd say, "Don't come."
You look different.
I shined my shoes, pressed my pants,
did my homework.
I do my homework now.
You wanna get some chow mein?
Peter...
I'm getting married.
I always imagined you
getting married on a hilltop.
And who's the groom?
You hadn't decided yet.
[scoffs]
You think just because you saw my play
you can talk me out of getting married?
You once told me you loved me.
I let things get in the way before.
There was something I thought I had to do.
-I don't have to.
-You're too late.
-Will you think about it?
-Think about what?
-Picking up where we left off.
-Where was that? We never got on.
-You can't get off if you don't get on.
-I don't think it's that simple.
Of course you don't,
because you complicate things.
-You don't understand.
-[sighs]
I'm not an empty seat anymore.
I'm different.
Punch me, I bleed.
I have to go.
[sighs]
I'm getting married in a church.
[softly] You are different.
[Jameson] Dear, we agreed
to put on a wedding,
not go into bankruptcy.
Caviar? What, are we inviting the czar?
Get some cheese and crackers,
some of those little cocktail weenies.
Boss, I got a garbage man here who says
he's got something you might wanna see.
Don't tell me you have the head
of an extraterrestrial in there,
'cause if you do,
you're the third guy this week.
-Where the hell did you get that?
-In the garbage.
In the garbage?
He must've given up.
Thrown in the towel.
Abandoned his sad little masquerade.
[laughs] I finally got to him.
The power of the press triumphs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Now, look, uh...
I think I deserve
a little something for this.
-I'll give you 50 bucks.
-I could get more than that on eBay.
All right, 100. Miss Brant, give this man
his money, and throw in a bar of soap.
Your wife is still on that line.
-...about the flowers--
-Flowers! How much?
You spend any more on this thing,
you can pick the daisies off my grave.
Get plastic!
-Gotta go. Big story.
-[hangs up phone]
[chuckles]
[violin plays intro]
[plucking strings]
Spider-Man, Spider-Man
Where have you gone to, Spider-Man?
[whispers indistinctly]
[both giggle]
-[grunting]
-[mugger] Come on, man. Get the money.
Come on, come on.
Ah! Give it!
Help!
Come on.
[Aunt May]
It wasn't fair to have gone like that.
He was a peaceful man.
And it was all my doing.
Aunt May...
you don't have to punish yourself.
Oh, I know I shouldn't.
It's just that…
you wanted to take the subway
and he wanted to drive you.
And if only I had stopped him,
we'd all three of us
be having tea together.
[sighs]
I'm responsible.
For what?
For what happened to Uncle Ben.
But you were at the library.
You were doing your homework.
He drove me to the library,
but I never went in.
What do you mean?
I went someplace else.
Someplace where I thought
I could win some money...
to buy a car, because I wanted to...
impress Mary Jane.
It happened so fast.
I won the money,
and the guy wouldn't pay me.
Then he got robbed.
The thief...
was running towards me.
I could've stopped him, but I wanted...
revenge.
So I let him go.
I let him get away.
[swallows]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
He wanted a car.
He tried to take Uncle Ben's.
Uncle Ben...
said no.
And then he shot him.
Uncle Ben...
was killed that night...
for being the only one
who did the right thing.
[voice breaking] And I...
I held his hand...
when he died.
I've tried to tell you so many times.
[footsteps on stairs]
[door shuts]
[metal creaking]
[electricity crackling]
Just one more little chore.
[thunder crashes]
Where are you?
-I'm leaving for the night, sir.
-Fine.
Your father only obsessed over his work.
Good night, Bernard.
[sighs]
[wind whistling]
[heavy thuds approaching]
[rattling]
[thudding stops]
Ah!
-Hello, Harry.
-Otto.
-What do you want?
-That precious tritium.
But I need more of it this time.
More tritium? Are you crazy?
You'll destroy the city! You're a hack!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop!
All right! Ah!
All right, all right, all right.
All right, put me down.
We'll make you a deal.
Okay.
[grunting]
Kill Spider-Man...
I'll give you all the tritium you need.
On second thought,
bring him to me...alive.
How do I find him?
-Peter Parker.
-Parker?
He takes pictures of Spider-Man
for the Bugle.
Make him tell you where he is.
Have it ready.
-Don't hurt Peter!
-[tentacles screeching]
[woman] Auxilio, fuego!
[flames crackling]
Somebody, help!
[woman] Fire!
Help! My baby's still in there!
Fuego!
[people clamor, scream]
Alicia! The Chens can't find
their daughter. H-have you seen her?
Somebody call the fire department!
Help! Help!
Is anybody in that building?
We think there's a kid
stuck on the second floor.
Hey, where you going?
[panting]
[grunts]
[child screams]
[child crying]
-I'm coming!
-[child coughs]
[grunts]
[groans]
Oh!
[child sobbing]
Ah!
Hah!
[coughs]
[child cries, coughs]
It's okay. It's okay. Come here.
I'm gonna get you out of here. Come on.
Come on.
[coughing]
[girl sobs]
-[Peter grunts]
-[girl screams]
[screaming]
[speaking Mandarin]
[grunting]
[sobbing]
-[peter coughing, choking]
-[girl crying]
-[sirens blaring]
-Mama.
[mother speaks Mandarin]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[coughs]
You got some guts, kid.
Some poor soul got trapped
on the fourth floor.
Never made it out.
Aw...
All right, Billy, let's knock it down
and roll them up.
-Get on out of here.
-[Billy] Let's pick it up!
Let's get all this equipment,
let's go! Let's move it!
Am I not supposed to have what I want?
What I need?
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, uh...
I shouldn't have without...
knocking.
[knocks]
Come in.
-Hi.
Um...
W-would you like a piece
of chocolate cake?
Okay.
And a-a glass of milk?
That would be nice.
Okay.
[cutlery clinking]
Mmm.
-Thank you.
-Mm.
Oh, um...
you got a message.
-It's your aunt.
-Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
What's going on?
Oh, they gave me another few weeks,
but I decided the hell with it.
I'm moving on.
-I found a small apartment.
-Why didn't you tell me?
I'm quite able to take care
of things myself.
And Henry Jackson across the street
is giving me a hand.
And I'm giving him five dollars.
-That's Henry Jackson?
-[chuckling] Yes.
It's funny what happens in two years.
Nine years old, has great ambitions.
Um...listen, about...
my last visit...
Pish-posh, we needn't talk about it.
It's water over the dam
or under the bridge
or wherever you like it, but… [sighs]
But you made a brave move
in telling me the truth.
And I'm proud of you.
And I thank you, and I...
I love you, Peter.
So very, very much.
[sighs]
Hey, where are all my comic books?
Oh! Those dreadful things?
I gave those away.
-I put the pans in the box, Mrs. Parker.
-Thank you, Henry.
-Hi, Peter.
-Hey, Henry. You're getting tall.
Henry, why don't you put
those cookbooks in with the mixer?
Okay.
You take Spider-Man's pictures, right?
[Peter] I used to.
-[Henry] Where is he?
-Henry and I agree.
We don't see his picture
in the paper anymore.
He...
uh...
-quit.
-Why?
-Wanted to try other things.
-He'll be back, right?
I don't know.
You'll never guess who he wants to be.
[chuckling] Spider-Man.
Why?
Well, he knows a hero when he sees one.
Too few characters out there,
flying around like that,
saving old girls like me.
And Lord knows,
kids like Henry need a hero.
Courageous, self-sacrificing people
setting examples for all of us.
Everybody loves a hero.
People line up for them,
cheer them, scream their names.
And years later, they'll tell
how they stood in the rain for hours,
just to get a glimpse of the one who
taught them to hold on a second longer.
I believe there's a hero in all of us...
that keeps us honest...
gives us strength...
makes us noble...
and, finally, allows us to die with pride.
Even though sometimes
we have to be steady and--
and give up the thing we want the most.
Even our dreams.
Spider-Man did that for Henry, and...
he wonders where he's gone.
He needs him.
Do you think you could...
lift that desk and put it
into the garage for me?
But don't strain yourself.
Okay.
Strong focus on what I want.
[panting]
Whoo-hoo!
I'm back!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[indistinct chatter in distance]
My back!
-[joints crunching]
-Oh! My back!
[moaning]
[alarm blaring]
Honey, you sure you don't wanna
invite your friend, the photographer?
Peter Parker?
Oh… Positive.
-Thought he was your pal.
-Peter Parker?
-Yeah.
-Uh, he's just a great big jerk.
Well, the world's full of great big jerks.
You're adorable.
It's just the uniform.
Lean your head back for me.
-Put my head back?
-Yeah. Just do it.
-Just put my head back?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Wow.
I'm back on the moon.
[laughs]
You up there with me?
-Hiya.
-Surprised?
-Very.
-Thanks for coming.
-Everything okay?
-Uh… You might say so.
This is funny. I'm not sure how to begin.
You know how our minds play tricks on us.
Tell me about it.
Well, mine did a real number on me.
Some part of me heard what you
had to say after the show that night,
that you were different,
but I didn't wanna listen.
I was afraid to trust you.
But… I've been thinking about it--
Listen...there's more for me to say.
I...maybe rushed into things.
-I thought--
-Wait a minute.
What are you saying?
I'm saying...
I...
uh...
I thought I could be there
for you, Mary Jane.
But I can't.
My mind was playing tricks too.
Do you love me or not?
I...
don't.
You don't.
Kiss me.
Kiss you?
I need to know something.
Just one kiss.
[tires screeching]
[screaming]
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
[heavy thuds approaching]
[people screaming]
What's happening?
Peter Parker.
And the girlfriend.
What do you want?
[grunting]
I want you to find
your friend, Spider-Man.
Tell him to meet me
at the Westside Tower at 3:00.
I don't know where he is.
Find him.
-[tentacles screech]
-[gasps]
Or I'll peel the flesh off her bones.
-If you lay one finger on her--
-You'll do what?
-[claw clangs]
-[screaming]
[people yelling]
[roars]
[people clamoring]
[panting]
[people screaming and shouting]
Still no word on the whereabouts
of your son's fiancée.
Sorry, Jonah.
It's all my fault.
I drove Spider-Man away.
[Hoffman] He was the only one
who could've stopped Octavius.
Yes.
Spider-Man…was a hero.
I just couldn't see it.
[whooshing]
He was a-- A thief! A criminal!
He stole my suit!
He's a menace to the entire city!
I want that wall-crawling
arachnid prosecuted!
I want him strung up by his web!
I want Spider-Man!
Hah!
Where is she?
Oh, she'll be just fine. Let's talk.
[yells]
[both grunting]
Ah!
[grunts]
[tentacles screech]
[Octavius yells]
[people gasping and screaming]
[both grunting, groaning]
What the hell?
[growls]
[yells]
[both grunting]
[people screaming]
[panting]
[yells]
[tires screech]
[snarls]
-[yelling]
-[screaming]
[growls]
[engine accelerating]
[all screaming]
[all gasping]
You have a train to catch.
Help! Help! Help!
I can't stop it! The brakes are gone!
-It's Spider-Man!
-Oh, my gosh! This is it!
Tell everyone to hang on!
Brace yourselves!
-[grunting]
-[wood smashing]
[yells]
[groaning]
Any more bright ideas?
I got a few.
Yeah!
[grunts]
[web creaking]
Argh!
[gasps]
Better watch out!
[panting]
[groaning]
[yelling]
[webs creaking]
We're slowing down.
[groaning]
[webs snapping]
[gasps]
[yelling]
[people gasping]
[metal squealing]
[people screaming]
[metallic squealing stops]
[sighs]
[webs whizzing]
[passenger 1]
Nice and easy, we'll go down.
Slower, gently.
Is he alive?
He's...
just a kid.
No older than my son.
[gasps]
It's all right.
We found something.
We won't tell nobody.
It's good to have you back, Spider-Man.
[Spider-Man groans]
[people scream]
[tentacle squeals]
-Hyah!
-[all screaming]
He's mine!
You wanna get to him,
you gotta go through me.
And me.
Me too.
Very well. [snarls]
[all screaming]
[all groaning]
[all gasping]
[thunder crashing]
-[metallic clicking]
-Where do you want him?
And the tritium?
-[tentacles hissing]
-[claws clanking]
[grunts]
Yes.
If only I could cause you the pain
that you've caused me.
First, we'll see who's behind the mask.
I can look into your eyes as you die.
[gasping] Pete...
No...
It can't be.
[grunts]
[panting] Harry...
where is she?
Where is he keeping her?
He's got M.J.
No, all he wanted was the tritium.
Tritium?
He's making the machine again.
When that happens,
she'll die along with half of New York.
-Now, where is he?
-Peter...
you killed my father.
There are bigger things happening here
than me and you.
Harry, please, I've got to stop him.
[thunder crashes]
[Mary Jane] Hey!
Hey!
[whistles] I'm talking to you!
You got what you needed for your
little science project. Now let me go!
I can't let you go.
You'd bring the police.
Not that anybody could stop me,
now that Spider-Man's dead.
He's not dead. I don't believe you.
-Believe it.
-[clangs]
[electronic humming, pinging]
-[whispers] Surprise.
-[gasps]
As soon as you get free--
[screams]
I should have known Osborn
wouldn't have the spine to finish you!
Shut it down, Ock.
You're gonna hurt
a lot more people this time.
Well, that's a risk we're willing to take.
-[electricity crackling]
-Well, I'm not.
[grunts]
[yells]
[screams]
[tentacles screech]
[grunting]
[energy buzzing]
[screaming]
Hang on, Mary Jane!
[grunting]
Run!
[panting]
[grunts]
[yells]
-Let's see you scurry out of this.
-[groans]
Argh!
[groaning]
[yells]
[panting]
[electricity crackling]
[buzzing]
Now what?
[tires screeching]
[woman screams]
[tentacle whirs]
[electricity crackles]
Dr. Octavius.
We have to shut it down.
Please tell me how.
Peter Parker.
"Brilliant but lazy."
Look at what's happening.
We must destroy it.
[metal clanking]
I can't destroy it.
[whirring]
-I won't!
-[grunting]
You once spoke to me about intelligence.
That it was a gift to be used
for the good of mankind.
A privilege.
These things have turned you
into something you're not.
-Don't listen to them.
-[tentacles hissing]
It was my dream.
Sometimes to do what's right,
we have to be steady
and give up the thing we want the most.
Even our dreams.
[tentacles click, squeal]
-You're right.
-[tentacle squeals]
-He's right.
-[tentacles screech]
-Listen...
-[tentacles squealing]
Listen to me now.
Listen to me now!
[gasping]
[panting] Now...
tell me how to stop it.
It can't be stopped.
It's self-sustaining now.
-Think!
-Unless...
The river.
Drown it.
I'll do it.
[gasping]
[metal creaking]
No!
[screams]
[grunts]
[panting]
Hi.
[grunts]
This is really heavy.
[metal creaking]
[yells]
M.J...
in case we die...
You do love me.
I do.
Even though you said you didn't.
I will not die a monster.
[grunts]
[yells]
[groaning]
[screams]
I think I always knew...
all this time...
who you really were.
Then you know why we can't be together.
Spider-Man will always have enemies.
I can't let you take that risk.
I will...
always be Spider-Man.
You and I can never be.
[sirens blaring]
[John] Mary Jane!
[grunts]
[wind whistling]
[door opens]
Hello?
[door creaks]
[faint laughter]
[laughter grows louder]
-Who's that?
-[Osborn] Son.
I'm here.
Dad?
-I thought you were--
-No.
I'm alive in you, Harry.
Now it's your turn.
You swore to make Spider-Man pay.
Now make him pay.
But Pete's my best friend.
And I'm your father.
You're weak.
You were always weak.
You'll always be weak
until you take control.
Now you know the truth about Peter.
Be strong, Harry. Avenge me.
[mouths]
-Avenge me!
-No!
[panting]
Wha...?
[glass crackling]
[equipment hissing]
[clicks, hisses]
[bells chiming]
[indistinct chatter]
["The Wedding March" plays on organ]
[people murmuring]
Call Deborah.
[whispers] The--? The caterer?
Tell her not to open the caviar.
[sighs]
["The Wedding March" continues]
Had to do what I had to do.
Mary Jane.
Peter.
I can't survive without you.
You shouldn't be here.
I know you think we can't be together,
but can't you respect me enough
to let me make my own decision?
I know there'll be risks,
but I want to face them with you.
It's wrong that we should
only be half alive...
half of ourselves.
I love you.
So here I am, standing in your doorway.
I've always been standing in your doorway.
Isn't it about time
somebody saved your life?
Well, say something.
Thank you, Mary Jane Watson.
[sirens wailing]
Go get 'em, tiger.
Whoo!
Hoo-hoo!
["Vindicated"
by Dashboard Confessional playing]
Hope dangles on a string
Like slow spinning redemption
Winding in and winding out
The shine of it has caught my eye
And roped me in
So mesmerizing
So hypnotizing
I am captivated
I am vindicated
I am selfish
I am wrong
I am right
I swear I'm right
Swear I knew it all along
And I am flawed
But I am cleaning up so well
I am seeing in me now
The things you swore you saw yourself
So turn up the corners of your lips
Part them and feel my fingertips
Trace the moment
Fall forever
Defense is paper-thin
Just one touch and I'd be in
Too deep now to ever swim
Against the current
So let me slip away
Vindicated
I am selfish
I am wrong
I am right
I swear I'm right
Swear I knew it all along
And I am flawed
But I am cleaning up so well
I am seeing in me now
The things you swore you saw yourself
My hope dangles on a string
Like slow spinning redemption
["Ordinary" by Train playing]
Whose eyes am I behind?
I don't recognize anything that I see
Whose skin is this design?
I don't want this to be the way
that you see me
I don't understand anything anymore
And this web that I'm tied up
Is taking me right up
These walls that I climb up
To get to your story
It's anything but ordinary
And when the world is on its knees
With me it's fine
And when I come to the rescue
I get nothing but left behind
I'm anything but ordinary
Ordinary
["Theme from Spider-Man"
by Michael Bublé playing]
[sirens wailing]
Spider-Man, Spider-Man
Friendly neighborhood Spider-Man
Wealth and fame
He's ignored
Action is his reward
Look out
Here comes the Spider-Man
Spider-Man, Spider-Man
Friendly neighborhood Spider-Man
Wealth and fame
He's ignored
Action is his reward
Look out
Here comes the Spider...
Man!