[Peter] It's me, Peter Parker.
Your friendly neighborhood...
you know.
I've come a long way from being the boy
who was bit by a spider.
Back then, nothing seemed
to go right for me. Now...
Wow, look, it's Spider-Man!
-Super cool!
-Spider-man!
...people really like me.
Hey, stick around. It's gonna start again
in a couple minutes.
-[all] Nah.
-That's okay.
The city is safe and sound.
I guess I've had
something to do with that.
My Uncle Ben would be proud.
I still get to school. Top of my class.
Now, the Hamiltonian shows us
that the energy levels
are perturbed by the electric field.
From the form of this matrix, we can see…?
Miss Stacy?
That only the "m equals zero
quantum states" are affected.
[Connors] Correct. Good work, Miss Stacy.
Parker? You got something to add?
No, sir.
[Peter] And I'm in love
with the girl of my dreams.
Hi. Uh...
Miss Watson left a ticket for me.
Peter Parker.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Thank you. Sorry.
[audience chattering]
Oh. I'm so nervous.
[orchestra playing]
They say that falling in love
Is wonderful
-[mouthing]
-It's wonderful
So they say
[audience applauding]
That's my girlfriend.
And with the moon up above
-[mouthing]
-It's wonderful
It's wonderful
So they tell me
I can't recall who said it
I know I never read it
I only know they tell me
that love is grand
And...
The thing that's known as romance
Is wonderful
Wonderful
In every way
So they say
[audience applauding]
-I thought she was good.
-Yeah.
Harry?
Harry!
I need to talk to you.
Explain things.
Tell it to my father.
Raise him from the dead.
I'm your friend, Harry.
I cared about your father.
M.J.!
-Peter!
-Congrats!
-Was I good?
-Good? You were great.
-You were--
-You said great.
I love my flowers, they're beautiful.
And those are from Harry.
-Was he here tonight?
-Yeah, I ran into him outside.
-What's with you guys anyway?
-It's complicated.
Tell me again. Was I really good?
I was so nervous. My knees were shaking.
-Your knees were fine.
-The applause wasn't very loud.
Yes, it was. Well, it's the acoustics.
It's all about diffusion. It keeps
the sound waves from grouping.
You see, when the sound waves,
they propagate, then it's like an--
You are such a nerd.
[monitor beeping rapidly]
-Wow.
-Ooh.
Did you see that one?
-You know what?
-Mm.
I'd like to sing on-stage
for the rest of my life...
with you in the first row.
I'll be there.
Tell me you love me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I always have.
[engine revs]
-Ready?
-Yep.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[train rumbling nearby]
[light switch clicks]
You can't hide here, Flint.
-I'm just here to see my daughter.
-You are an escaped convict.
The cops are looking for you.
You're not getting near her.
You're nothing but a common thief.
-You maybe even killed a man?
-It wasn't like that.
It wasn't.
I had good reason for what I was doing.
And that's the truth.
You and the truth, sitting in prison,
having three meals a day together.
I live in the presence of great truth...
and that is the truth that you left behind
right there in that bedroom.
[door creaks]
Penny.
I missed you.
I miss you too, Daddy.
I promise I'll make you healthy again.
Whatever it takes, I'll get the money.
[Emma] You get out of here. Now.
[sirens wailing nearby]
I'm not a bad person.
Just had bad luck.
[doorbell rings]
Peter, what is it?
It's M.J.
-I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
-Oh, Peter.
Oh!
The day your Uncle Ben asked me
to marry him, we were so scared.
And excited.
And very young.
And I loved him so fiercely.
-And you said yes, right?
-No.
I wanted to say yes, but I said no.
I wasn't ready. Neither was he.
So we took our time.
Looked forward to it.
Didn't want to run into something
with nothing to count on but love.
A man has to be understanding
and put his wife before himself.
Can you do that, Peter?
Yeah, I think I can.
Then you have my blessing.
Oh. I hope you've considered
a proper proposal.
Your uncle had it all planned.
He took me to the beach one Sunday.
Oh, he was a knockout in his bathing suit.
And I didn't look too bad myself.
We were very good swimmers.
And it was a beautiful day and he said,
"Let's swim to the island."
And at the island,
we found a perfect spot by an old tree
and we lay down and looked up at the sky.
And then he said, "Close your eyes, May."
And I did. And then he said, "Open them."
And I did.
And he was holding this ring.
Dazzling...
in front of me.
I thought it was the sun.
We'd be married 50 years...
come August, if...
So...
I hope you'll make it very special
for Mary Jane.
Do something she'll never forget.
Give her this.
Go on. Take it.
[both grunting]
[screams]
[peter yelling]
-Harry.
-You knew this was coming, Pete.
Listen to me! I didn't kill your father.
He was trying to kill me.
He killed himself.
Shut up!
[car horns honking below]
[gasps]
[glider beeping]
[beeping stops]
[Harry] I'm still here, Peter!
[Harry yells]
[screeches]
Hate those things.
[screeching]
[yelling]
[yells]
[Harry] Oh!
Harry?
Harry.
Harry!
Oh, my God.
[grunting]
Harry!
Come on!
God!
-[nurse 1] Defib.
-[nurse 2] Two hundred.
[doctor] And clear.
[nurse 3] No response.
-Recharge, let's go again.
-[nurse 2] Go ahead.
-Charging.
-[doctor] And clear.
[nurse 3] No response.
[doctor] Let's recharge
and do it one more time. And clear.
Captain Stacy.
-What's this?
-Flint Marko.
The guy we tied
to the Ben Parker homicide.
-What about him?
-He just broke out of Rikers.
-And?
-He's on the run.
He's in the marshlands.
I think we got him.
[snarling]
[whistle blowing]
There he is!
[dogs barking]
[dog whimpers]
[officer] You two, take the west side.
Tommy, take the east.
Where did he go?
[grunting]
[rumbling]
[capacitors powering up]
[electricity crackling]
-Capacitors charged.
-Right.
Donnie,
we got a little fluctuation on one.
There's a change in the silicon mass.
Yeah, it's probably a bird.
It'll fly away when we fire it up.
Initiating demolecularization.
[whirring]
[grunting]
[screaming]
-How is he?
-He's gonna be okay.
But there's been some memory impairment.
Particularly his short-term memory.
Right now he can't remember the accident
or anything that happened to him recently.
Is it permanent?
It could be. Only time will tell.
He's awake if you wanna see him.
Oh. Maybe I should wait.
No, it's fine. Just keep it brief.
I want him to rest.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Hit my head.
Yeah.
Doctor said I was in an accident.
Hit-and-run.
I don't remember much of anything.
My father...
he died, right?
This is all so weird.
Hi. I got here as fast as I could.
-I know that face.
-How you doing?
I don't know.
Last thing I remember, I was fine.
-Somewhere.
-[M.J.] You're still fine.
We love you, Harry.
It feels like...
somehow I've been gone
for a really long time.
And now I'm back home.
It's good to have you back.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have
to ask you guys to scoot, okay?
-Okay.
-All right. Thank you.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Great.
[M.J.] Get some sleep.
-I think he's gonna be fine.
-I think so.
-And you guys seem great.
-Yeah.
You have lovely friends.
My best friends.
I'd give my life for them.
[exhales]
[knock on door]
-Yeah?
-[M.J.] It's me.
Oh! Hey.
-[doorknob jiggling]
-Peter, you know I can't open the door.
It's stuck again?
Just come on and help me.
I'm coming.
-Hey.
-The review.
Oh!
-They hated it. They hated me.
-Well, they can't hate you.
"The young Miss Watson is a pretty girl,
easy on the eyes, but not on the ears.
Her small voice didn't carry
past the first row."
That's ridiculous, I was right there.
You were in the first row.
Yeah, this-- Listen, you were great.
That's a critic. This is something
you're gonna have to get used to.
Believe me, I know.
Spider-Man gets attacked all the time.
This isn't about you. This is about me.
It's about my career.
I know, and I'm just saying
you can't let it bring you down.
You just gotta believe in yourself
and you pull yourself together.
You get right back on the horse and--
Don't give me the horse thing.
Try and understand how I feel.
It's just...
I look at these words...
and it's like my father wrote them.
[dispatcher] All cars.
All cars in the vicinity of 54th
and Sixth Avenue, please report.
Crane out of control,
approach with caution.
"Go get 'em, tiger"?
I'm sorry.
[sirens wailing in distance]
Oh, my God. 7-Adam to Central.
That crane job you sent us on?
It's bigger than we thought.
We're gonna need
a major mobilization right away.
[metal groaning]
Shut it down at the generator! Now!
Okay, Gwen, I've got a secret.
It's my copier.
What is that thing doing in my background?
[screaming]
[people screaming]
[tires screeching]
Captain Stacy, they got some kind of short
up there. They can't shut down the crane.
Get Edison on the phone. Have them
kill the power to the whole block.
Are you all right?
It's coming back.
[metal groaning]
[woman] Oh, no.
[all screaming]
[crowd gasping]
[screaming]
[camera shutter clicking]
-Oh, my God. That's Gwen.
-What?
What's she doing up there?
I don't know, I just saw her last night.
She said she had a modeling gig.
-Who are you?
-It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
And I work at the Daily Bugle.
And I'm dating your daughter.
[gasping]
[screaming]
[Gwen screaming]
[grunting]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank you.
Hey, Spidey, hold on. Bugle needs a photo.
-Thank God you're okay.
-[Gwen] Daddy.
-Hey. I'm the new guy.
-New guy?
-Sweetie. You okay?
-[whimpering]
From now on, I am gonna be
taking shots of you for the Bugle.
So smile. Are you smiling? Just kidding.
-They got a guy.
-Who, Parker?
Um, yeah, look, just between you
and me, guy's kind of an amateur.
Have you noticed his stuff
makes you look a little bloated?
Just--Yeah, a little chunky.
Okay.
But you don't have to worry
about that anymore, buddy.
[Jameson] Dazzle me.
Pow. Zap.
Just a little something the boys
in the Ad Department and I whipped up.
As you know, circulation at
the Bugle's been pretty good.
Though not as good as The New York Times.
Or the Daily News, or the Post,
or several other smaller--
-Get on with it, you moron--!
-[intercom buzzes]
-What?
-[Brant] Your blood pressure.
Your wife told me
to tell you to watch the anger.
You tell my wife--
Thank you.
[Hoffman] So I propose this campaign.
"Daily Bugle." That's obvious.
"It's hip, it's now."
I came up with that one.
"It's wow." That's actually Erickson.
He goes crazy.
We gave him a couple lattes,
he's like, phew!
"And how." That's me again.
[intercom buzzes]
Time to take your pill.
Not that one.
[intercom buzzes]
Drink plenty of water.
Thank you.
Continue.
Betty, Betty, bo-Betty, banana-nana
Fo-fetty
-He's busy.
-Oh, no.
-I'm just here to talk to you, beautiful.
-What's that smell?
That's a little something called
Nice and Easy. What's on you?
It's called Go Away.
Get out! That is the dumbest idea
you've ever had!
-And you have had some doozies!
-Blood pressure.
Hey, where are you going?
-Who are you?
-You hired him last week. Freelance.
-I did? What's that smell?
-It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
-Who? What--?
-Can I just say I really like that shirt?
Here, it's the crane accident.
-Check out the light source.
-He likes my shirt.
-Hey, Betty.
-Hey, Pete. You better get in there.
New guy.
He's trying to sell some Spidey photos.
Oh.
Thanks.
Parker! You're late, maybe too late.
Bruckner here beat you to it.
It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
-But I got you this.
-But he got me this.
Wait, how'd you get that? I didn't see
you there. How'd you get that high?
-Climbed. Nearly fell off a flagpole.
-A flagpole?
-Which one do we use?
-I like Bernstein's.
-It's better.
-Cheaper too.
Congratulations, son, we'll use your shot.
I'll pay you 50 bucks.
All right, J.J., I'm your man. I know
more about what makes a good picture
than any photographer in this town.
See, photography, it's not just about,
no offense, uh, flagpoles or whatever.
It's about lighting. Composition. Drama.
I want a staff job, sir.
I have a girl that I intend to marry
and I guess, I don't know,
I have this stupid little dream
of working with one of the greatest
newspaper editors of our time...
J. Jonah Jameson.
Well, we do have an opening.
Johnson quit, remember?
-You fired him.
-Whatever.
Wait a minute. I know what makes a good
picture and I've been here a long time.
If there's a staff job, Mr. Jameson,
I think I deserve it.
He's right, Jonah. Peter's been with us
for years. He's done a great job.
You want a staff job,
and you want a staff job.
-Anybody care about what I want?
-[Hoffman] I do.
Shut up. Get out.
I want the public to see Spider-Man
for the two-bit criminal he really is.
He's a fake, he's full of stickum.
Catch him in the act.
Spider-Man with his hand in a cookie jar.
Whoever brings me that photo gets a job.
What are you waiting for,
Chinese New Year? Go, go, go.
I'm on it, boss.
You'll never get that shot.
Oh, we'll see.
You know, I guess one person
can make a difference.
Enough said.
Welcome home, Harry.
-Thank God you're all right.
-Thanks, Bernard.
-Bernard.
-Sir.
Got you a little homecoming present.
-[Harry] It's your old ball.
-[Peter] Yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
Hey, we were pretty good
in the back yard, weren't we?
We were terrible. And we tried out
for the varsity team.
-For the cheerleaders.
-Right.
-Hey, do I have any girlfriends?
-I don't know.
You don't?
Hey, Bernard. Do I have any girlfriends?
Not that I know of, sir.
It's a pretty cool pad, huh?
It's okay.
-Looks like I'm not hurting for money.
-No.
Well, maybe I can turn this
no-girlfriend thing around.
[Peter chuckles]
You know, he always appreciated
how you helped me through high school.
Just wish I could remember more about him.
Well, he loved you. That's the main thing.
Hey, let's watch a game in the kitchen.
Get something to eat.
Okay.
Whoa, heads up.
Did you see that?
-Still got the moves.
-Yeah.
[singer] They say...
[piano playing]
And with a moon up above
It's wonderful
So they tell me
[piano stops]
[director] Why are we stopping?
What is she doing here?
[producer] Well,
Gary was supposed to call her agent.
Hi, honey. We tried to reach you.
I'm sorry.
One critic?
[producer] No, all the papers, dear.
Mary Jane, honey, sit down.
Let us explain it to you.
Listen, if you'd like,
we could say you became ill.
[piano playing]
That was so poorly handled.
Yeah.
Let's just rehearse.
[crowd cheering]
[man] All right, Spidey!
-[marching band playing]
-[crowd cheering]
[woman 1] Go, Spidey!
[woman 2] All right!
[woman 3] Yeah, Spidey!
-Spidey!
-Yeah!
[crowd chanting] Spidey! Spidey! Spidey!
Excuse me, miss?
Could I please see that gorgeous smile?
Hi, Eddie. [chuckles]
You're so beautiful.
This is front-page stuff.
Okay, I've gotta practice.
I'll see you later, okay?
-How about tonight?
-Not tonight.
Why not?
What about that amazing,
amazing night that we had?
[laughs]
We had coffee, Eddie.
-[Peter] Hey, beautiful.
-[camera shutter clicking]
One more.
-Everything okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-You're not still mad at me, are you?
-No, Peter, I'm proud of you.
Hey, I'm gonna be
swinging in from over there.
-Oh, yeah?
-So you know where to look.
Give them a good show.
Don't worry about that review.
We're gonna be laughing about it
tomorrow night, I promise.
Yeah.
Isn't that that guy
from that prison break?
[officer] He fits.
Hey, you. Halt!
Cover the back.
-[woman] Hon, be careful.
-[man] Come on, let's go.
[sand spilling]
[yells]
[screams]
-[officer 1] He's in the truck.
-[officer 2] Round the front.
[crowd screaming]
Fire.
[groaning]
[roars]
[car alarms blaring]
People of the city of New York,
I am here today because I fell 62 stories
and someone caught me.
Someone who never asks
for anything in return.
Someone who doesn't even
want us to know who he is.
Hey, M.J.
-Harry.
-Hey.
-Where's Pete?
-Um...
-Taking somebody's picture, I guess.
-Right.
I'm so happy to see you.
You look so good, Harry.
I've never felt better.
It's a weird feeling
not knowing who you are.
Bump on the head, I'm as free as a bird.
-Will you bump me on the head?
-Bop.
Hey, Pete said you're in a play.
You came. You sent me flowers.
I did? I'll come again tonight.
You can't. I was let go.
What happened?
I wasn't very good.
You know, this is embarrassing,
but I once wrote you a play
in high school. Heh.
-You wrote me a play?
-Yeah.
Harry, that's the sweetest thing.
So I ask you: When you're
dropping without a parachute
or your store's being robbed
or your house is on fire,
who is it that breaks your fall,
puts out the flames
and saves your children?
[all] Spider-Man!
They love me.
Then let's hear it for your one and only
-friendly neighborhood Spider-Man.
[all] Spider-man!
-[band playing]
-[crowd cheering]
[Spider-Man]
Hey. What's up? All right. How you doing?
Shazam!
Woo-hoo! Hey, guys.
Spider-Man. Spider-Man.
[Spider-Man] Hey there. Hi.
-Kiss him.
[all] Kiss him. Kiss him. Kiss him.
Go ahead, lay one on me.
-Really?
-Yeah, they'll love it.
-Kiss her.
-Kiss him.
No, Spider-Man, no.
All right.
[crowd cheering and whistling]
Hope Pete's getting a shot of this.
[giggles]
Ack!
-Hey, hey, are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-[woman screaming]
-[crowd clamoring]
Hey, man, we got something on the roof.
[Sandman growls]
[roars]
[guard] Oh!
[yelling]
Jig's up, pal.
I don't wanna hurt you. Leave now.
I guess you haven't heard.
I'm the sheriff around these parts.
Okay.
[both grunting]
Uh-oh.
[car horns honking]
[tires screeching]
[driver] Help!
[crowd chattering]
Where do all these guys come from?
[gasps]
[musicians playing classical music]
[maitre d' speaks French]
[speaking French]
I'm sorry, I don't speak--
But this is a French restaurant, non?
-Oui?
-Ha, ha!
-Name, please?
-Parker, Peter.
[blows whistle]
Ah. Here we are.
Table for two. Parker.
-Parker.
-That is what I said: Parker.
Um, I have a request.
My girlfriend will be coming
and I have this ring.
Ah!
Hello.
Oh, so you want to
pop the question tonight, huh?
Yes, and I wanna do
something very special.
I love it. Romance.
I am French.
When I signal you, if you'd bring
some champagne with the ring--
-In the bottom of her glass?
-Perfect.
[speaks French]
Also, I thought at the same time
if the musicians would play this song...
Their favorite.
And take good care of the ring.
Oui, with my life, monsieur.
[both speak French]
I like you.
[maitre d' chuckles]
Thank you.
[speaks French]
Oh.
Okay, so...
Oh, would you like some champagne?
How'd that get in there? Heh.
Oh, don't cry.
Hi.
Look at you. Wow, beautiful.
Thanks.
This place in your budget?
Oh, well, it's a special occasion.
You're on Broadway.
I don't feel like much of a star tonight.
Well, you are a star.
And you've earned it.
Peter...
you have no idea how I feel right now.
Oh, no, I know exactly how you feel.
Listen, I have been through this.
It happens to me all the time.
I see Spider-Man posters in the window,
kids running around
with me on their sweaters--
Big Halloween item.
I don't know, I guess
I've become something of an icon.
Like yesterday, they kept screaming,
"Spider-Man, Spider-Man."
I don't know, you know,
I mean, I'm thinking to myself:
"I'm just a nerdy kid from Queens.
Do I deserve this?"
-Hi, Pete. [chuckles]
-Hi.
Hi, my parents and I
were just having dinner here.
-Hello. I'm Gwen Stacy.
-Hi.
This is Mary Jane Watson.
Oh! Oh, it's so nice to finally meet you.
Pete talks about you all the time.
Oh?
Gwen is my lab partner
in Dr. Connors' class.
Pete's something of a genius.
I'd be completely lost without him.
Which actually reminds me,
Pete, if you've got a picture
of my kiss with Spider-Man,
could you bring it to class?
I'd really love it. Heh. For my portfolio.
After all, who gets
kissed by Spider-Man, right?
I can't imagine.
Well, it was lovely to meet you.
-Good night.
[snaps fingers]
Oh, she's in my science class.
It's not her best subject.
What?
How come you never mentioned her?
She's your lab partner?
You saved her life?
She thinks you're a genius
and she had her polished
fingernails all over you?
Or didn't you notice?
And she gave Spider-Man
the key to the city.
I'll never forget that.
She's just a girl in my class.
Let me ask you something.
When you kissed her...
who was kissing her?
Spider-Man or Peter?
-What do you mean?
-You know exactly what I mean.
That was our kiss.
Why would you do that?
You must have known how it'd make me feel.
-Do you wanna push me away?
-Push you away?
Why would I wanna push you away?
I love you.
You're my girlfriend.
She's a girl in my class, M.J.
I don't feel very well.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
No, w--
-Where are you going?
-Please, don't follow me.
[musicians playing
"They Say It's Wonderful"]
[maitre d'] Here we are.
[M.J. on message] Hi, it's M.J.
Sing your song at the beep. Beep.
[beep over phone]
Hello. Uh...
I wish you'd pick up the phone.
I don't know what's going on or...
[Peter, over speaker] I don't know
if you got the messages or what.
But, uh...
I just wanna talk to you.
Okay, call me. Bye.
[dial tone]
[phone rings]
-Hello?
-[man] Mr. Parker?
Yeah?
This is Detective Neil Garrett
from the 32nd Precinct.
I'm calling on behalf of Captain Stacy.
He would like you to come down
to the station to speak with him.
[Stacy] Originally, we thought
that this man, Dennis Carradine,
was your husband's killer.
We were wrong.
What?
Turns out Mr. Carradine
was only an accomplice.
The actual killer is still at large.
What are you talking about?
This is the man who killed your husband.
His name is Flint Marko.
He's a small-time crook
who's been in and out of prison.
You got this wrong.
Two days ago he escaped.
Evidently,
he confessed his guilt to a cellmate
and we have a couple of witnesses
who will corroborate the story.
No, wait, son. You don't wanna do this.
[Marko grunts]
No!
Hey, get in! What are you doing?
Would you put these photos away, please?
I'm sorry, Mrs. Parker.
I know this isn't easy,
but, please, be patient with us.
We're doing our job. We will catch him.
No, you're not doing your job.
I watched my uncle die,
and we chased down the wrong man.
Now you're telling me you had suspicions
for two years? Witnesses?
-Why weren't we told about this?
-Settle down.
I have no intention of settling down.
This man killed my uncle,
and he's still out there!
[dispatcher] L-20 Parkway.
All officers in the vicinity,
please report.
We have an abandoned vehicle
and an elderly man
in the middle of the street.
Sorry, Wabash Avenue.
[knock on door]
[M.J.] Peter, it's M.J.
I'm not here about what happened
at dinner. Just please open up.
Aunt May called me.
She told me about what happened.
She's worried about you.
I'm worried about you.
Don't be. I'm fine.
I don't want you to do something stupid.
Like try to find my uncle's killer?
And do something you'll regret.
Like with that other guy.
He had a gun on me. I made a move
and he fell. I told you that.
I'm not accusing you of anything.
[dispatcher] 10-22, auto at 556--
-Will you turn that thing off?
-Crossing 5-6 to 5-7.
[officer] Yeah, Central, this is Car 3-9
responding to your Sixth Avenue call.
Peter, I'm here because I care about you.
And I know that you made a mistake
and that you feel guilty,
but I wanna be here for you.
Okay. I get it. Thank you.
But I'm fine. I--
I don't need your help.
Everybody needs help sometimes, Peter.
Even Spider-Man.
[officer] Ninety X-ray, 98.
[dispatcher 1] Two-four King,
respond to 1031 at 642 Madison Ave.
[dispatcher 2] One-three Thomas,
respond to 1020 at 540 East 107.
Male complainant inside apartment.
May be on first floor.
[dispatcher] Three Henry 10-1 1,
I have a residence. 73818...
[overlapping radio chatter]
[thunder crashing]
[grunts]
[peter gasps]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[Carradine]
Don't hurt me. Just give me a chance!
[Peter] What about my uncle?
Did you give him a chance?
Did you?
[gasps]
[Peter] Where am I?
What is this?
I feel...
Wow.
This feels good.
[grunting]
Whoo!
Yeah!
[car horns honking]
Whoo!
[chuckles]
This is something else.
What do you think?
I've never seen anything like it.
I'm a physicist, not a biologist,
but let me look at it in the morning.
Run some tests.
Can we do that now?
It seems to like you.
-Don't let any of that get on you.
-Why not?
It has the characteristics of a symbiote,
which needs to bond to a host to survive.
And sometimes these things
in nature, when they bind
they can be hard to unbind.
[dispatcher] Bank robbery in progress.
First Eastern Bank at 202 Bismark.
Another sandstorm is reported in the
vicinity. All cars proceed with caution.
Marko.
[groans]
[tires screech]
[grunting]
Whoa.
Buddy, love the new outfit.
This is exactly what I need
to scoop Parker.
Give me some of that web action.
See you, chump.
What the hell?
[sirens wailing]
[train horn blaring nearby]
Flint Marko.
-What do you want from me?
-Remember Ben Parker?
The old man you shot down in cold blood?
What does it matter to you, anyway?
[train horn blares]
Everything!
[Spider-Man yells]
[groans]
[both grunting]
[train horn blares]
[screaming]
It's time to pay, Marko!
[Marko yelling]
[yelling]
[grunting]
Good riddance.
-Rent.
-Not now.
Listen, it's a free country.
It's not rent-free country.
-Leave me alone.
-Give me rent.
You'll get your rent
when you fix this damn door!
That wasn't cool.
He is a good boy.
He must be in some kind of trouble.
Flint Marko,
the man who killed Uncle Ben...
he was killed last night.
Oh, my.
-What happened?
-Spider-Man killed him.
Spider-Man?
I don't understand.
Spider-Man doesn't kill people.
What happened?
I, uh...
He--
He was...
I thought that you'd feel...
He deserved it, didn't he?
I don't think it's for us to say
whether a person deserves to live or die.
But, Aunt May, he killed Uncle Ben.
Uncle Ben meant the world to us.
But he wouldn't want us living one second
with revenge in our hearts.
It's like a poison. It can--
It can take you over.
Before you know it,
turn us into something ugly.
-[woman] He said it was a good idea.
-[man] Yeah.
[phone ringing]
[classical music playing on stereo]
Hello?
[M.J.] Hey, Harry, it's M.J.
Hi.
I need some company.
Are you doing anything? Can I stop by?
Yeah, sure, come on over.
Okay. Are you sure it's okay?
No, I'm not doing anything.
Please, come over.
-Okay, I'll see you soon.
-Great.
Bye.
-Bernard.
-Yes, Mr. Osborn?
We're having a guest.
Can you get some food?
-A guest?
-Yeah, a guest.
-A "guest" guest?
-Will you just get some food?
Right away, sir.
[door opens]
[Ditkovitch clears throat]
Hey, Mr. Ditkovitch.
-An orange?
-No, thanks.
Listen, I'm really sorry
for what happened earlier.
I shouldn't have yelled about that door.
It was nothing to be angry about.
Ah, it's no big deal.
But if you feel that bad about it,
you can buy me pizza sometime.
-Today's good.
-Okay.
-Have problem with the phone?
-No, no. I was just--
Well, I was trying
to figure out what to say.
If it's a woman you're calling,
then you say:
"You're a good woman. I am good man."
Hm?
-[Ursula] Hi, Pete.
-Hi.
-He's calling a woman.
-Are you calling Mary Jane?
-I think that would be so good--
-This is none of your business. Go. Go.
-Call.
-Uh--
-You should call.
-Thanks.
-Bye.
Hi.
-You hungry?
-Yeah.
Come on.
["The Twist" by Chubby Checker
playing on stereo]
-I hope you like peppers.
-I love them.
Come on, baby
Let's do the twist
[turns volume up]
Take me by my little hand
And go like this
Twist, baby
Baby, twist
No. Please.
Yeah, just like this
Come on, little miss
And do the twist
Oh, the butter.
And mama ain't around
Yeah, Daddy's just sleepin'
And Mama ain't around
Beautiful.
Till we tear the house down
Check this out.
Yeah, baby, twist
[M.J.] Oh!
Twist
-Well, we can use that part.
-Um, right.
You've been dreaming.
Nothing like a little self-deception
to get you through the night.
-All right.
-When did you write that?
-Twelfth grade.
-It's intense.
-So you want the part?
-I'd love to be in your play.
It's yours.
You know, there's not even a scar.
Barely.
-Sorry.
-Me too.
-I didn't mean to do that.
-No, it's okay. Please, forgive me.
Mary Jane.
Mary Jane!
-Mary Jane, please.
-I'm sorry.
Just--
[Norman]
You've taken your eye off the ball.
[Norman yells]
Harry.
What have you done?
Avenge me!
-My father, he died, right?
-Yeah.
[Harry] Just wish I could
remember more about him.
[Peter] Well, he loved you.
That's the main thing.
[Harry] I swear on my father's grave,
Spider-Man will pay.
[Norman] Harry.
Remember me?
Yes, Father. I remember.
I was right about her. About Peter.
About everything.
You know what you must do.
Make him suffer.
Make him wish he were dead.
First, we attack his heart!
[phone rings]
[M.J. on message]
Hi, it's me. Sing your song at the beep.
[beeping]
Hey, M.J. It's Peter.
Uh...
I wanna talk to you about last night.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I know you were just there
to help and I, uh...
I don't know. I wanna see you.
[M.J. gasps]
If you want Peter to live,
you're gonna do something for me.
-[Peter] Yeah?
-It's Ursula.
Come in.
-Hi, Pete.
-Hi.
There's a phone call for you.
It's Mary Jane, she called back.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I put the phone on top of the thing.
Thanks. Okay.
-Hey.
-[M.J.] Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad you called.
I've been trying to--
-Can you meet me?
-You bet.
-Now?
-Okay. Where?
At the bridge in the park.
-On my way.
-Okay.
Okay. Hey. I love you.
[line disconnects]
[Peter] You look beautiful.
Peonies.
-You okay?
-No.
There's something
I have to tell you, Pete.
Okay.
It's not working.
You and me.
What?
I don't wanna see you anymore.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I'm lonely.
You aren't there for me.
I can't do this.
-It's over.
-No. Please. Please don't say that.
I know I've been selfish,
but I can do better.
-I can change.
-It's not that simple.
We love each other. I love you.
We have problems.
When people have problems
they work it out. They talk to each other.
-Look, you see?
-Oh...
You know what this is?
-You know what I want for us?
-There's someone else.
I've fallen in love with someone else.
[Harry] Bravo.
She says that she's lonely,
that I'm not there for her.
There's another guy.
[sighs]
Well, how you holding up?
Not good.
Harry, I was gonna propose to her.
Really?
Well, she's been going through
a tough time lately. Career.
I mean, a singing waitress at a jazz club?
It's not exactly what
she had in mind for herself.
Singing waitress? What are you--?
What are you talking about?
Well, she was fired from the show.
Didn't she tell you?
She was fired?
She was fired and she told you?
She didn't tell me?
Well, that's why I asked you here, Pete.
I'm the other guy.
What?
Look, she came to me
one afternoon, troubled.
She needed someone
and I was there for her.
I've always loved her, Pete.
You know that.
It just...
started.
I don't believe this. I don't--
Ahem. I don't believe you.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
[door opens]
-Can I warm you up?
-Yes, please.
How's the pie?
So good.
[truck horn blares]
[thunder crashes]
Would you like a drink?
I'm sorry. What was I thinking?
Bad for the public image, right,
Mr. Key-to-the-City?
What did you do to her?
I did what you failed to do.
I was there for her.
Mary Jane and I, we understand each other.
-She doesn't know what you are.
-Peter, she knows me very well.
And when she kissed me,
it was just like she used to kiss me.
That taste...
Strawberries.
[both grunting]
[blade slices]
How'd you like that, Spidey?
That all you got?
-Stings, doesn't it?
-I protected you in high school.
-Now I'm gonna kick your little ass.
-Ooh!
[both grunt]
Gonna kill me like you killed my father?
I'm done trying to convince you.
You took him from me. He loved me.
No. He despised you.
You were an embarrassment to him.
Oh.
Look at little Goblin Junior. Gonna cry?
[grunts]
[beeping]
[woman]
Spider-Man used to make me feel safe.
Now I'm afraid to walk home from work.
My son thought the world of this guy.
I have a 9-year-old daughter,
loves Spider-Man.
Who's she supposed to look up to now?
[woman] This is the guy
they gave the key to the city to?
I'm gonna put some dirt in your eye.
[man]
Cheers to the new staff photographer.
Hey, I just got lucky.
This is so wonderful for you.
Well, you might wanna tell J.J.
to make a little more wall space.
Wow, good morning.
It's a beautiful day, huh?
What was it you said?
I'll never get that picture?
-There's your hero.
-Huh.
-I never thought he'd really do that.
-See? Right there.
You made a judgment call.
You gotta see it as it is.
It's funny you should say that
because I was looking through
some old photos
and it looks very, uh, similar.
Okay. [chuckles]
Well, I gotta get back to work.
You're trash, Brock.
-Excuse me?
-Your picture's a fake.
Oh, Parker, you are such a boy scout.
When are you gonna give a guy a break?
You want forgiveness? Get religion.
-What's going on here?
-Are you guys all right?
Heh. Yeah. No, we--
We're just horsing around.
Look, I'm begging you.
If you do this, I will lose everything.
There's not a paper in town
that will hire me.
You should've thought of that earlier.
[Robbie] What are you doing, Peter?
[Peter] Show this to your editor.
Tell him to check his source next time.
[Robbie] It's a fake.
Empire State Photographic
Department confirms it.
Pack your things. Get out of my building.
-I was just trying--
-You're fired!
[Robbie] We're gonna
have to print a retraction now.
I haven't printed
a retraction in 20 years!
["People Get Up & Drive Your Funky Soul"
by James Brown playing]
[phone rings]
Hello.
Mr. Parker, Dr. Connors here.
Oh, Dr. Connors. How are you?
[snores]
Quite a specimen you left me, Parker.
Its chemistry is not unlike
the chondritic meteorites of the '70s.
Thanks.
-Mmm. That's good.
-You know what, Parker?
-Parker?
-Get me some milk.
-It amplifies characteristics of its host.
-Mmm.
-Hey, give me another cookie.
-Especially aggression.
-Mm.
-This could be dangerous.
Peter, you didn't keep any, did you?
-You got any with nuts?
-Um...
I have some nuts. I could make some.
-Go make me some.
-Peter?
No, no, no. Course not.
Your shots are so good.
I'd love to shoot you sometime.
Peter Parker! Peter...
Parker! Miss Brant,
that's not the position I hired you for.
Black-suit Spider-Man.
Peter, these are incredible.
-We gotta have these, Jonah.
-I'll pay you the usual rate.
If you want the shots,
I'll take the staff job.
Double the money.
Get on up
Get yourself together
Drive that funky soul
Everybody knows somebody
Who can drive that funky soul
Get up
Get yourself together
And drive your funky soul
Raise up
Get yourself together
And drive that funky soul
Raise up
Get yourself together
And drive that funky soul
Raise up
Penny.
You are really gonna dig this joint.
Do you think I'm--? I'm dressed all right?
Too fancy or too...?
[Peter] Are you kidding me?
You're looking fine, babe.
[Gwen] Heh. Thank you. [chuckles]
[Peter] Love that little giggle.
[band playing "L-O-V-E"]
Hey, keep it open there, pops.
[singer] In love, can make it
Oh, this is so cool. [chuckles]
I have never been to a jazz club before.
Oh, I hope we can get a table.
[whistles]
Find us some shade.
Thanks, hot legs.
Right this way, sir.
Oh, don't you know that love
Was made
Oh, why, thank you.
For me and you
[crowd applauding]
-I am so loving this.
-Oh, me too.
-Isn't that your old girlfriend?
-Yeah.
-Do you wanna go someplace else?
-Oh, no, no. I'll--I'll be okay.
-Mary Jane, show us what you got.
-[man] I'll take that.
[band playing "Fever"]
-I'll be right back.
-All right.
[piano playing]
[M.J.] Peter?
This is for you.
Double-time.
[crowd murmuring]
Thanks.
[crowd cheering]
Now dig on this.
[woman] That is hot.
[crowd] Ooh!
[man 1] Oh!
[man 2] Yeah!
[crowd applauding and cheering]
That was all for her?
[band playing "Stormy Weather"]
I'm so sorry.
-You all right, Mary Jane?
-I'm fine.
Okay.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
You.
-Can I help you, sir?
-No.
Is everything okay here, Paul?
Yeah, is everything okay here, Paul?
-Take him out of here.
-[bouncer] Let's go, sir.
-Take your hand off of me.
-[bouncer] Now.
-Okay.
-Hey, get off. Let go.
-Peter, stop it! Aah.
-Unh!
Who are you?
I don't know.
[church bell tolling]
[thunder crashing]
[thunder rumbling]
It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
I come before you today...
humbled...
and humiliated...
to ask you for one thing.
I want you to kill Peter Parker.
[grunting]
-[bell tolls]
-[screeching]
[bell tolls]
[screaming]
[Peter yelling]
[Peter grunting]
[Peter screaming]
Parker.
[screams]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[retches]
[screeches]
[handle squeaks]
[knocking on door]
[knock on door]
-Hi, Peter.
-Hi.
Hmm.
You don't seem to have changed
the room around very much.
Of course, there's not much
you could do, is there?
When we spoke on the phone
I sensed that something was bothering you
so I thought I'd just come by.
How's Mary Jane?
I don't know.
I never heard from you.
Did you ever propose?
You said...
a husband's gotta
put a wife before himself.
I'm not ready.
But what happened?
You seemed so sure.
Yeah.
I, uh...
[Peter sighs]
I hurt her, Aunt May.
I don't know what to do.
Well, you start
by doing the hardest thing:
You forgive yourself.
I believe in you, Peter.
You're a good person.
And I know you will
find a way to put it right.
In time.
[Marko] End of the line, Spider-Man.
[screeches]
I want him dead too, Flint.
That's why I've been looking for you.
Oh, yeah. I know all about you.
Like the fact that Spider-Man
won't let you help your poor daughter.
It's just--That doesn't seem right to me.
Look, I wanna kill the spider,
you wanna kill the spider.
Together, he doesn't stand a chance.
Interested?
Yeah.
[man] So...
where to?
All New York is holding its breath
as the hostage crisis continues to unfold.
[reporter] Just 30 minutes ago
police came across this startling sight:
A young woman, held hostage in a taxi
suspended 80 stories above the ground
in what appears to be a giant web.
[anchorman] Every attempt by the police
to rescue the hostage
has been thwarted by the Sandman.
[people screaming]
Compounding the danger
is the appearance
of a strange black-suited figure.
Early reports had believed him
to be the black-suited Spider-Man
but he has now been identified
as something entirely different.
[Venom screeches on TV]
The hostage has been identified
as Mary Jane Watson,
an actress recently seen
in a brief stint on Broadway.
We're now going to take you
live to the scene
with Jennifer Dugan. Jennifer?
We're only about a hundred feet
away now, Hal, and--
Wait. There seems to be some
kind of activity in the web.
They seem to be creating
some kind of gigantic lettering.
Apparently, Spider-Man's being
challenged to some sort of confrontation.
And that raises serious questions
about what kind of chance he'd stand
against such overwhelming--
[sighs]
[Peter] Harry?
I need your help.
I can't take them both, not by myself.
You don't deserve my help.
Harry...
she needs us.
Get out.
[Bernard] if I may, sir?
I've seen things in this house
I've never spoken of.
What are you trying to tell me?
The night your father died...
I cleaned his wound.
The blade that pierced his body...
came from his glider.
I know you're trying to defend
your father's honor,
but there's no question
that he died by his own hand.
I loved your father...
as I have loved you, Harry.
As your friends love you.
-[snapping]
-[creaking]
-[gasps]
[creaking]
[creaking stops]
-[snapping]
-[screams]
[crowd gasps]
Look.
[crowd cheering]
[crowd chants]
Spider-Man! Spider-Man! Spider-Man!
He seems to have come out of nowhere
to answer the prayers of the city
just when all hope seemed to be lost.
Peter. They're gonna kill us both.
-I'm gonna get you out of this.
-Watch out.
[Venom screeches]
[grunting]
Hey, Parker.
My God. Eddie.
Ooh, my spider-sense is tingling...
if you know what I'm talking about.
Heh, heh.
[both grunting]
[crowd gasping]
[M.J. screams]
We can find a way to settle this.
You're so right.
I'm thinking humiliation.
Kind of like how you humiliated me.
Do you remember?
Do you remember what you did to me?
-[metal creaking]
-[gasps]
[chuckles]
You made me lose my girl.
Now I'm gonna make you lose yours.
How's that sound, tiger?
[screeching]
[metal creaking]
[gasping]
Hold on, Mary Jane!
[crowd clamoring and screaming]
[Sandman growling]
[M.J. shrieks]
Mary Jane!
[screaming]
[Spider-Man grunting]
[roaring]
[laughs]
It's hard to believe what's happening.
The brutality of it.
I don't know how he can take any more.
This could be a tragic day
for the people of New York.
It could be the end of Spider-Man.
Hm?
[beeping]
[Sandman roaring]
-Awesome.
-Wicked cool.
[screeches]
You came.
Looks like just in the nick of time.
A couple minutes ago
wouldn't have been so bad either.
What are you gonna do?
[Venom screeching]
I may need some help over here.
I'm a little busy right now.
Give me your hand!
[Sandman groaning]
[crowd gasping]
Parker! Parker, where--?
I need a photographer.
Hey, kid, you want a job?
Why would I want a job? I'm just a kid.
-All right, how much for the camera?
-One hundred bucks.
A hundred bucks?
[crowd gasping]
All right, you little crook. Here.
What the--?
Film's extra.
[grunts]
[Spider-Man] Gotcha.
-[snapping]
-[gasps]
Pete, up top!
[screams]
[screaming]
[Spider-Man] Mary Jane!
-This thing got any more?
-Hang on!
To what?
-Go, buddy!
-Got her!
[all cheering]
You okay?
Yeah.
-Good.
-[Harry] Hey, Pete!
[Sandman roaring]
Am I interrupting?
[women shrieking]
[roaring]
[crowd cheering]
[Venom screeches]
[metal squeaks]
[growling and screeching in distance]
[growling continues]
[screeching]
Never wound...
what you can't kill.
Eddie, the suit, you gotta take it off.
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
Ah.
I know what it feels like.
It feels good.
The power. Everything.
But you'll lose yourself.
Let it go.
I like being bad.
It makes me happy.
[screeches]
[poles chiming]
[Venom screaming]
[screeching]
-[bell tolls]
-[screeching]
[Venom screeching]
[blades slashing]
Harry!
[grunting]
[screeching]
[poles chiming]
[yelling]
[screeches]
[screaming]
[wailing]
[screeching]
Peter. What are you doing?
No!
Eddie!
-Harry.
-Mary Jane.
-I'm gonna get help.
-No.
Stay.
[Marko] I didn't want this.
But I had no choice.
We always have a choice.
You had a choice when you killed my uncle.
My daughter was dying.
I needed money.
I was scared.
I told your uncle
all I wanted was the car.
-[Ben] What is it?
-[Marko] I need your car.
He said to me:
"Why don't you just put down
the gun and go home?"
I realize now
he was just trying to help me.
Then I saw my partner
running over with the cash.
And the gun was in my hand.
[gunshot]
[inaudible]
Get in!
[Marko] Did a terrible thing to you...
and I spent a lot of nights
wishing I could take it back.
I'm not asking you to forgive me.
I just want you to understand.
I've done terrible things too.
[crowd cheering below]
[Marko] I didn't choose to be this.
The only thing left of me now...
is my daughter.
I forgive you.
Hey, pal. How you doing?
Been better.
We'll get you through this.
No.
I should never have hurt you...
said those things.
[Harry] None of that matters, Peter.
You're my friend.
Best friend.
Harry.
[Peter] Whatever comes our way...
whatever battle we have raging inside us,
we always have a choice.
My friend Harry taught me that.
He chose to be the best of himself.
It's the choices
that make us who we are...
and we can always choose
to do what's right.
[piano playing "I'm Thru With Love"]
I'm through with love
I'll never fall again
Said adieu to love
Don't ever call again
For I must have you
Or no one
And so I'm through with love
[band playing]
I've locked my heart
I'll keep my feelings there
I have stocked my heart
With icy, frigid air
And I mean to care for no one
["Signal Fire" by Snow Patrol playing]
The perfect words
Never crossed my mind
'Cause there was nothing in there
But you
I felt every ounce of me
Screaming out
But the sound was trapped
Deep in me
All I've wanted
Just sped right past me
But I was rooted fast to the earth
I could be stuck here
For a thousand years
Without your arms to drag me out
There you are
Standing right in front of me
Forced fear falls away
To leave me naked
Hold me close
'Cause I need you
To guide me to safety
No, I don't wanna wait forever
["Move Away" by The Killers playing]
Last time I said I was in control
I had 25 debts and we both know
When you come back now
You'll see my face
I said 25 debts and we both pray
While I move away
Hard times don't come until tomorrow
These eyes don't see
Take your skin off
When you listen to me
Move away
Hard times don't come until tomorrow
These eyes in me
Take your skin off
When you're talkin' to me
["Falling Star" by Jet playing]
Know that I loved you from the start
When we believed in who we are
Don't wish upon a falling star
Love will remind us who we are
I dreamed a dream
So much has changed
Wake
You've been sleeping
You pushed too far
Now you're bleeding
You fell so far
You should have been a star