Hello, my name is Sam Raimi.
I'm the director of Spider-Man,
which you paid too much money to see.
With me is my good friend and
co-producer, Grant Curtis.
And I'm Laura Ziskin, and I'm here at
the Sony Studios with Kirsten Dunst.
We're gonna talk about Spider-Man.
We're at Sony, where we spent...
...most of last year
making the Spider-Man movie.
Kyle Cooper, who did the titles to the
movie, created this logo for Marvel...
...which has gotten an ovation
in the theaters.
The first time we showed the movie,
people clapped for that Marvel logo.
We're recording this from ADR 2
on the Columbia Pictures lot...
...which is next to the scoring stage.
It's a black box.
Do a lot of voice work for pictures.
Grant, what are your thoughts
about this opening title sequence?
Beautiful title sequence designed by
Kyle Cooper and Imaginary Forces.
Very well done.
He worked tirelessly with a great team
of artists creating this. It took months.
Return trips to the editing room, back
into his world, and back to editing room.
A lot of artists and technicians spent
a lot of time crafting this sequence.
We didn't want to show
Spider-Man early in the movie...
...because it was his origin story.
But we wanted to give
the audience a taste of him.
So we tried to design with Kyle
and his team some sequence...
...that would give the audience...
...the flavor of the character
without actually...
...spoiling the big reveal
of Spider-Man before it was due.
I think this is one of the best
title sequences...
...I've ever seen in my entire life,
of any film.
When I first came on the movie,
Sam said the way he likes to work...
...is to have two editors.
They each work individually.
And then he sees both of their cuts and
both of their materials, scene for scene.
And then at the end
of the first cutting process...
...he'll screen the two movies
back to back, the two cuts.
Then, in his words, he then
likes to "mush them together."
I can tell.
I think it's such a smart idea to have
those two different perspectives.
It's a great honor to have a chance
to make Spider-Man...
...and work briefly with Stan Lee.
He's one of my childhood heroes.
He created some of the greatest
fiction characters...
...in American comic book history.
That was my favorite day on the set,
when he came by. That was bizarre.
- What was that like?
- It was just...
You guys were in watching dailies,
and I waited outside for Stan.
He showed up while you guys
were in dailies.
The whole crew had broken for lunch.
And I just showed Stan around
the Times Square set out in Downey.
And it was very bizarre introducing
the creator of Spider-Man...
...to the world of Spider-Man
on the film set.
He just walked around
with a big smile on his face.
He was thoroughly pleased.
- Was it what he had hoped it would be?
- It was, and more.
I mean, he could tell that...
...everybody was putting 100 percent
effort into making his vision...
...and your vision come through
on screen.
He knew it was being
well taken care of.
That's me.
Tell him to stop! Please!
Stop!
Hey! Stop the bus!
Stop! He's been chasing us
since Woodhaven Boulevard.
This was shot in Queens, New York.
On the right is my brother
and his family...
- ...walking, as cameos.
- That was Ivan? Oh, my gosh.
And little Max and Sophie and Kyle.
One of the very first storyboards
that I saw in the movie...
...was the design of the scene
of Peter chasing the bus.
And of the sort of, shall we say,
portly young man eating the doughnut.
It was really fun to see it
come to life because it's exactly...
...as he storyboarded it, brought to life
by these lovely performances...
...and the music and everything.
It's fun.
I came into the movie
in July of...
What year are we in? 2000.
And Sony had already made
a decision to make the film.
They were in the early stages
of preproduction.
Nobody had been...
The movie hadn't been cast yet...
...and the script was in a state of flux.
That was when I came on to it.
Avi Arad, the executive producer,
has been with it for many years.
And it's sort of folklore now
about how long it's taken...
...to bring Spider-Man to the screen.
I guess 18 years or so...
...from when they first made
a decision to try to make the movie.
And we have all sort of only
half-jokingly said...
...it was a good thing
it took this long to get made...
...because the technology
didn't really exist...
...to have Spider-Man do the things
that the fans would expect him to do.
It was exciting to shoot this
at Columbia University in New York.
The light kept changing
when we were shooting.
Caused tremendous amounts
of problems for Don Burgess...
...and the gaffers, grips.
Willem did a wonderful job
in this picture.
He is both warm and intelligent,
sweet in this scene.
That was necessary
because we really needed Peter...
...to look up to the character
of Norman Osborn.
In some ways, Norman was supposed to
be Pete's surrogate father in the piece.
So Willem Dafoe had to have
those qualities.
At the same time, he had to be
incredibly physically adept...
...to be able to ride
that goblin glider...
...in that incredible suit.
It was like riding a mechanical bull
from those bars in the Southwest.
Took an incredible amount
of muscle ability and coordination.
The third thing we needed for that actor
to pull this role off...
...was, he had to have a great deal
of menace to threaten Spider-Man.
Willem pulled all three
of those qualities together...
...and delivered quite well
in his performance.
This scene inside was,
of course, shot...
...months and months
before in a location in Los Angeles.
- Right near USC, right?
- Right. In the Natural History Museum.
This was during night shooting. I was
so tired because we worked all night.
It was split days. This was probably at 2
in the morning when we were doing this.
It was because of the museum...
...and when we could have control of
certain parts of it. We had to be at night.
And these were the days
when we had the spider guy.
- Oh, right.
- Steve Kutcher, who was...
- The spider wrangler.
- ...wrangling the spiders.
Let's go.
...Hunts using reflexes with
nerve-conduction velocity so fast...
I had a great team
of second unit directors...
...who put together a lot
of the pieces of these spiders for me.
Doug Lefter did an excellent job. He was
one of my chief storyboard artists...
...and great second unit directors,
and so was Jeff Lynch.
He shot some of those spiders.
And then we also had John Dykstra...
...who did additional second unit
photography as a director.
Dick Buckley did an excellent
job shooting on this picture.
Delivered some great footage
for that montage...
...of people speaking
about Spider-Man...
...in the second act. He shot a lot
of that stuff. Most of that stuff.
Sam was very fixed on what
the spider would look like...
...that would bite Peter.
And we were shooting in the winter,
and spiders are summer critters.
So the spider wrangler had to go to New
Zealand and Australia to get spiders.
He came in the first day to see us
with this box full of spiders.
And we all sat there slightly repulsed
and slightly mesmerized...
...as he played with his spiders.
Neil did a beautiful job.
And his team created things
like this web.
Did a beautiful job out of monofilament
and, I think, a hot glue gun.
He worked closely with our special
effects house and John Frazier...
...making all those webs.
I think she's so charming,
along with Tobey, in this scene.
They really give a lot of themselves.
He's so afraid to ask.
He knows it's his chance,
and he can't let it pass him by.
Could I take your picture?
I need one with a student in it.
- Sure. Yeah.
- Great.
Where do you want me? Over here?
Yeah, that's great.
Don't make me look ugly.
That's impossible.
Perfect.
- Is that good?
- Great.
That's great.
I didn't really know a ton
about Mary Jane.
I had seen more Gwen Stacy,
for some odd reason.
When I first met Sam, I was just
flipping through the comics.
I saw her and I was like,
"All right, I'm blond. Makes sense."
I didn't know a lot about
Mary Jane and Peter's relationship.
But of course I did lots of research
after I got the role.
A lot of that is the real spider. A black
widow with a "dress" put over it.
A little shell snapped over the abdomen
of the spider...
...so we could paint the shell
without harming the actual spider.
But sometimes that spider is created
with the help of John Dykstra...
...and his incredible CGI team
of artists and technicians.
And I thought they did a great job
matching the real spider.
General Slocum,
good to see you again.
Mr. Balkan, Mr. Fargas.
- Norman.
- Mr. Osborn.
Always a pleasure to have
our board of directors visit.
I want to see the progress report
on human performance enhancers.
Neil Spisak did a lot of research
on putting together this lab.
What his research told him was
these projects come and go...
...so quickly that everything
was gonna be on wheels.
Nothing permanent. Everything
Jerry-rigged and brought in on carts...
...and rolling platforms.
I thought that was so unlike what I had
seen in the movies, and so dead on.
...Our entire staff certifies
the product...
- ...ready for human testing.
- Dr. Stromm?
We need to take the whole line
back to formula.
- Back to formula?
- Dr. Osborn.
I'll be frank with you.
I never supported your program. We
have my predecessor to thank for that.
The general has approved
Quest Aerospace...
...to build a prototype
of their exoskeleton design.
- They test in two weeks.
- And if your performance enhancers...
...have not had a successful
human trial by that date...
...I'm gonna pull your funding.
I'm going to give it to them.
Gentlemen. Ladies.
And the Lord said, "Let there be light."
And voile! There is light.
I love Cliff Robertson.
He's an old-school gentleman.
Great actor, and he's got
a really good soul, that fellow.
He really brought a lot of life
to a part...
...that was just a very simple role.
He infused it with a great deal
of warmth and love...
...and that's what it's all about.
He really made me miss him
when he was gone in the story.
Well, let's look in the paper and see.
There are the want ads.
What do we got here?
Computer...
Computer salesman, computer
engineer, computer analyst.
My Lord, even the computers
need analysts these days.
I'm 68. I'm too old for computers,
and besides, I...
This moment when May says to him...
Comforts him.
He realizes in the performance
that she's right here.
Listen. Watch him listen to her.
We've been down-and-out before.
But somehow, we survive.
Hi, sweetie. You're just...
He really is in the moment. He takes in
what the other actors say...
...and reacts to it in a realistic way.
Rosemary gives him great stuff
to act off of. She was great.
- Did you get some pictures, Peter?
- I gotta crash. Everything's fine.
What's that all about?
We like this scene.
That's the computerized body
on Tobey.
- Don't give away the secrets.
- Same with the buff one. Just joking.
We did have the body double
for Tobey when he was skinny.
- Sam will get mad at me for telling this.
- Oh, well.
He didn't think the guy
was skinny enough.
- He said, "I want somebody skinnier."
- Then his head would look huge.
Our editor,
Bob Murawski did a great job...
...putting this
dream sequence together.
We really didn't have the money left to
do what we wanted to do, so it was cut.
But Bob scrapped together pieces...
...from titles, stock footage...
...that was used in Darkman,
an old picture I worked on with Bob...
...and some new graphics and even
a shot from an old Italian horror picture.
- Which shot was that?
- The eyeball with the spider on it.
I don't know if it's a Lucio Fulci
picture, or some other film.
But that's where that's from.
Let me reschedule, with a proper
medical staff and a volunteer.
- Just give me two weeks.
- Two weeks?
In two weeks we'll have lost
the contract to Quest...
There's so much going on with
John Frazier's mechanical effects.
All the precision timing he's got going
with the computers...
...and this table bed
and the doors shutting.
It's really a beautiful work of art he put
together to make all this look so great.
Oh, that's cold.
We really wanted to get
this green gas, but...
Every time we did a test with the green
smoke, it was terribly toxic.
Every combination we used
with mechanical effects.
Finally, at the last minute,
we had to just use the white...
...I think, liquid nitrogen...
...and then colorize it. Colorize it
as a postproduction effect.
Norman!
Oh, my God.
Norman?
That was a hard surface to light
because it has so many angles of glass.
Kept seeing a lot of reflections.
- This scene makes everybody jump.
- Yes.
- It's scary.
- It is scary.
That looks so good.
Great stunt pulled off by
Jeff Habberstad and his guys...
...going through that window.
This was really fun.
This was something we tested...
...early on with this giant pair
of glasses in front of the camera. Yeah.
Basically Tobey had a large pair
of glasses that he would hold up.
And then the cameraman would
rack focus and go back, blurring it...
...as the lenses came into frame
to pull off the illusion of out of focus.
His eyes being out of focus.
Now something you maybe don't notice,
but look really closely at his wallpaper.
Can you tell what the design is on the
wallpaper? It's little spider webs. Yeah.
I'm fine.
- You can't really tell. But it's there.
- You can't really tell.
Neil Spisak,
who designed the production...
...it's his little secret.
This was all done on a set. The entire
house on the Columbia Pictures lot.
This bedroom.
Okay.
Jeff designed that for us.
Our stunt coordinator.
The distance between the rail and the
wall so Tobey could learn that stunt...
...of running along the wall.
Neil did a great job with their house.
Every time I see this I think I'm
walking in my grandparents' house.
Neil and his art director
really studied the homes...
...in Queens
where this exterior was shot.
And really patterned it precisely
after the interior decors...
...and the ad-on front porch made
into an entry hall, all those details.
The cracking plaster...
The mix of wallpaper and paint...
...from different eras
where the front was added on.
Hi, M.J.
Hey, M.J.
I don't know if you realize this,
but we've been neighbors...
Our prop guy was driving this bus.
Yeah. Martin.
He's a brilliant prop guy, but...
Let's just leave it at that.
I never heard such grinding of gears.
This was actually originally planned
to be a more elaborate scene...
...where he more than just...
Than sticking to the banner.
He was then gonna leap
out of the way of a truck.
But we ended up cutting it
both for budgetary and time purposes.
- It's better subtle, though.
- It worked.
It would've been too much
with him jumping the bus too.
Osborn's mansion was also designed
and shot...
...here on the Columbia Pictures lot
in Culver City.
This interior.
Danny Elf man saw this place
and said, "I want to live there."
I thought, "That's the villain's home.
You don't wanna live there."
He loved the design
of this particular room.
In this room you'll see a wide variety
of masks Karen O'Hara...
...our set decorator,
went to great pains to get.
Some are quite valuable,
and they're all quite beautiful.
They did a really great job
with the background stuff...
...telling the story of his love
of masks and tribal masks.
That's Bill Paxton's dad there.
I love that guy.
- John Paxton.
- He's great. He's in A Simple Plan too.
He argues with Bill about feed,
for the day of the month.
That's right. He's really funny
in that picture.
Not CGI, by the way. That little
catch thing. That's all Tobey.
- That's real.
- Which is pretty impressive.
And they put sticky glue stuff
to stick his hand to the tray too.
- Many takes of those items falling.
- Yeah, yeah, there was.
This was actually a scene that...
We had the scene and what
subsequently transpires...
...but the studio had asked us
to actually cut the tray part.
Because we'd originally had two days
scheduled for the scene.
And then in the, you know,
the vicissitudes of production...
...we had to cut some time.
They wanted us to cut a day.
So we made it that we would
shoot it in one day.
That part was gonna have to go,
but Sam and I really wanted it.
So we said, "Well, we're gonna
do it anyway."
So we did shoot this scene
in one extremely long day.
Remember how long?
It was, like, a 16-hour day.
- But thank God we did it.
- Because people love that.
It's used as a clip whenever
we do publicity. People love that scene.
It's so cute because he's learning
his powers and he saves her.
Parker?
This school was also built by Neil on
a stage here at Columbia. I love this set.
This 1952 school hall.
That sequence of the spidey-sense
was something...
...we began designing
actually kind of late.
We were in production already. The
shot was one of the last things finished.
It wasn't the absolute last.
The absolute last thing finished...
...was the very last shot of the movie.
Which took 18 months from the time
we started talking about it...
It was the last thing that came in.
But this was also... Came in quite late.
John composited all these pieces.
Shot the fist. Shot the background.
He really did an excellent job
putting these effects together for us.
I loved your idea there of showing
Peter's POV while in mid-backstand.
- Looking up at M.J. is a great shot.
- You know who... That was...
...Don Burgess' idea:
"Let's pick up a piece...
...of Peter's point of view."
I thought that was a great idea.
Joe, who plays Flash,
he was an unconventional choice...
...because he didn't look like
the Flash in the comic book.
But we just liked him.
Thought he had a great quality.
Watching Tobey think on screen.
He's got so much going on.
I love, in that sequence, how he's
coming to realize his powers...
...but he doesn't quite know
what's happening.
But he's kind of secretly thrilled.
Once he finally delivers
that knockout punch...
...he's stunned, and he transitions
into, like, "Oh, yeah."
And then this fear starts
to creep over him.
This change is happening to him,
and that sort of overwhelms him...
...and the confusion of that drives him
out. He plays it all silently.
Yeah, he's great.
I want more wall-climbing
in the sequel.
- I know. I love this.
- Climbing is the best part.
I get excited every time.
Like when Uncle Ben is killed, and he's
hopping and climbing. It's so exciting.
It's hot.
I have a funny story, actually...
...about the wall-climbing
that comes later. I'll tell it later.
Tobey was on a treadmill
to do those few runs.
This was a really complicated business,
to get this sequence.
Isn't it sad? It's so much work and
nobody realizes it, for split seconds.
- It's better they don't know.
- But they'll appreciate it on the DVD.
Go, web!
- I love this. This is hilarious.
- This is really cute.
Up, up and away, web.
This is Tobey improvising,
with much encouragement from Sam.
Tobey can be so funny.
He's really funny.
He's really a great Peter Parker.
He's really amazing.
Amazing.
This was hard because it was
the first place where we see the webs.
And among the many challenges
of the movie...
...certainly making something
that looks like a web...
...that a human-sized Spider-Man
could swing from was a big challenge.
And a combination of, obviously,
practical webs and CG.
- This is really funny.
- I know.
I love that the next shot's like,
running home. It's like such a little boy.
Like, "I'm hurt. I'm hurting.
I'm running home."
We painted an image on the wall...
...and we'd had various ideas
for what that should be.
Then Neil came up with this notion...
...that it's for a talk radio...
Drive-time radio show, and it's
the spider on the windshield.
- As Kirsten pointed out.
- Well, no, it just came to me.
I was like, "Oh, my God,
it's brilliant."
- Stop yelling.
- Stop it!
Little known fact:
The woman who plays
Mary Jane's mother is...
...my co-producer
Ian Bryce's wife.
She is also an actress
in her own right.
She loved wearing those leopard... She
got the sleaziest outfits. I loved it.
This scene was shot at 6 a.m.,
the night before I turned 19.
- On Kirsten's birthday.
- It was on my birthday.
We shot in the morning,
which was your birthday.
- And we celebrated.
- I got a cake. But it tasted like...
It was cool.
It was like a breakfast cake.
Like strawberry jam and bagel.
I don't know. It was good.
- We were fighting the sun.
- Yes.
And birds. Listen closely,
you can hear the birds.
- Just on Tobey, though.
- The sunrise birds.
I got to sync mine. You can
see my long underwear in this shot.
And you were wearing
your own coat.
We were gonna shoot the scene
without the coat...
...but it was freezing. And that was
your coat that we all loved.
I think this scene was shot on
Kirsten's 18th birthday. Is that right?
- I think so.
- I remember there was a big cake.
At the end of the night.
Our last night in New York.
Very cold.
It's true. The whole crew had hoods on,
and scarves, gloves and hats, and...
...act...
...on stage.
Really?
She does a beautiful job here opening
up a little window of her soul to Peter.
Maybe the first time M.J.'s ever
really done that to somebody.
Peter, that was first grade.
Well...
...even SO.
Sometimes...
...you know people.
I remember with a lot of the scenes...
In this case...
...Tobey and I had to keep cutting
down the dialogue, cutting it down...
...to just find the minimum
that we could say.
Although David Koepp did a great job
writing it.
And then Alvin Sargent did
a beautiful job polishing it.
When we got there, we just realized...
...less had to be said
to make it work.
That garage back there became
your guys' office between takes.
The next-door garage,
the door would come up...
...and you guys would work out
of the office. Or out of the garage.
I hunch.
We were racing against the sun
this night, I remember.
Mostly because of that last-minute
edit session...
- ...before the performance.
- Yeah.
- Okay, Grant, what kind of car is that?
- It's a Dodge Viper.
Is it really? Not a Viper. I thought
it was a lower-end version.
No, it's not a Viper. It's a Dodge...
Great.
Yeah, thank you.
What is that thing?
It's pretty. Our transportation
coordinator, Randy Peters...
...let me drive it home one night
when we had one in Los Angeles.
I think it's a Dodge Prowler.
- Is that it?
- I think you're right.
It's a brilliant idea of Stan Lee's
originally to have Peter...
...enter a wrestling match where
those colorful costumes are a must...
...to develop the Spider-Man costume.
That was a smart way to have him
originally come up with an outfit.
This was one of the Marvel artists who
we got to do some of the sketches...
...so that the design of the costume
would look like...
...the comic book's
for the comic book aficionados.
Jeff Lynch shot a lot of the drawing
of the costume for me.
And that artist did a lot of the actual
illustration, like you suggested.
Remember, Kirsten, we had this scene
of you dancing in the window.
That was too provocative.
Initially this took place
over a number of days.
So at one point in the scene...
...Peter looks out his window
and Mary Jane's dancing.
I was first dancing in my underwear.
- Then in a leopard thong. Not really.
- We covered you up.
Then I wore pajama pants
because it was a little too much.
- Now I see the spider webs, kind of.
- See the spider webs?
- I love this, when he's lying.
- This is hilarious.
"Okay, thanks." Like such a little boy.
So cute.
- Tobey ad-libbed.
- Cute.
That came out of the scene with her.
- I love that. I love the webs.
- Yeah. That looks cool.
Meanwhile...
Something's bothering him. Maybe
he's too embarrassed to tell me.
Maybe I'm too embarrassed
to ask him.
I just don't know anymore.
I'm going to the library.
See you later.
- Wait, Pete. I'll drive you there, buddy.
- I'll take the train.
No, I need the exercise.
Go on. Go, go.
He needs the exercise.
That's a funny line.
There's the car, Sam.
It's an 88 Oldsmobile Delta.
1973?
It's a, yeah, 1973 Delta 88 Oldsmobile.
Kids, it's currently for sale.
If you'd like to own a piece of
the Spider-Man movie, just contact me.
There's a little problem
with the radiator.
But otherwise I would recommend it
to compliment...
...any connoisseur's
motion-picture-prop movie collection.
No collection is complete without it.
No, you're not supposed
to run away, but...
Pete, you're changing. I went through
exactly the same thing at your age.
No, not exactly.
Peter, these are the years
when a man changes...
...into the man he's gonna become
the rest of his life.
Just be careful who you change into.
This guy Flash Thompson,
he probably deserved what happened.
Cliff made this scene work...
...beautifully. It's one of my favorite
scenes in the picture.
Remember, with great power
comes great responsibility.
Are you afraid I'll become a criminal?
Quit worrying about me, okay?
Something's different.
I'll figure it out.
I kept Cliff up till like 2 in morning the
previous night, recutting this scene.
Trying to make the dialogue play,
rewriting it.
He was exhausted
because it was a 6 a.m. call.
So he had three and a half hours
of sleep.
Yeah, he did a great job that night.
I love that Danny played the theme here
too. It's such an interesting impulse.
He had two themes going,
Peter's theme and Spider-Man's theme.
And they would each derive from
the other. But I love that he played...
...that right there.
This was pretty funny.
That's Bone Saw. That's Randy Savage,
and he's, obviously, a wrestler.
And when he came to audition for us,
I just fell in love with his voice.
Like, amazing, that voice.
Remember when Randy Savage
met with you for the first time on this?
I can't remember our first meeting.
You were asking him
what type of moves...
...he thought
would be good on-screen.
I'll never forget, he grabbed
Ian Bryce, our producer...
...his head, shoved them between his
legs, demonstrated a pile driver on Ian.
I thought he was gonna kill Ian.
Ian's face was turning red,
and Randy just kept working him over.
I felt so sorry for Ian.
There's my buddy, Bruce Campbell.
I love the fact that he would
do this for me. Be in this picture.
I only wish I could've punished him
in some way.
The audience enjoys Bruce's
performances in films relative to...
...the amount of punishment
he endures in the picture.
- Remember that young lady's name?
- Octavia Spencer.
The check-in lady.
Is that who you're asking?
- Yeah, she did a great job.
- She was Francine Maisler's assistant.
Sometimes. She comes in and
helps. She did a really good job for us.
We had footage of those women
beating up that wrestler.
Kicking him in the face and stomach
once he was down.
But we just didn't have time
to incorporate everything in the picture.
I love Bruce's Cadillac medallion
that they put on him.
James Acheson gave him. Yes.
If he can withstand just three minutes
in the cage with Bone Saw McGraw...
...the sum of $3000 will be paid to...
- What's your name, kid?
- The Human Spider.
That's it? That's the best you got?
Bruce is so great.
You probably won't admit to it,
but if you look closely...
...I think I remember who pushed
Spider-Man onto the platform that day.
- I think that's Sam Raimi.
- Just the hand.
I love shoving Spider-Man around.
- No, he got my name wrong.
- Get out there, you moron.
That was our PA, Rhys, who shoved
him out, but that was your hand.
I think I remember who was throwing
the popcorn at Tobey here as well.
- How dare you?
- Yeah, well...
You're not as nice
as everybody says.
Somebody's gotta tell
the truth someday.
- It was a pleasure working with you.
- Yeah. Thank you, sir.
Oh, my legs.
Oh, God. I can't feel my legs.
That's something...
That line came from a real story.
Rob Taperd once was driving from
Detroit, and he had just...
My partner, good friend...
...and he was going past
an automobile accident...
...and they were pulling some guy out,
and that was what he was screaming:
"My legs! Oh, God,
I can't feel my legs."
- As horrible as it was...
- How twisted.
That's why it's in the picture.
Really wanted to give Peter Parker
a taste of what was to come.
This is some kind of mistake.
I didn't sign up for a cage match!
Unlock the thing! Take the chain off!
Mark Andrews, our storyboard artist,
contributed an incredible amount...
...to this whole fight scene. A lot
of the ideas in this scene are his...
...and it's guided by his brilliance
and his great storyboarding.
- Remember Mark?
- Oh, yeah. Great guy. He's an animal.
He could just crank those out.
He had such great ideas too.
A lot of these fighting moves were
developed by Jeff Habberstad...
...and others by Chris, our stuntman.
Chris Daniels did a lot of great work.
Great spidey-pose reference.
He did a lot of homework.
He really knows his Spider-Man poses.
Some of the ideas came
from watching those wrestling videos.
Like beating him up with the chair.
Randy had a lot of input on all this.
Wasn't this one of the first sequences
we filmed...
...with the wrestling arena?
Yes, it was. I remember they had a big
press conference...
- ...and it took place in this arena.
- Yeah.
Right, Ian scheduled it early.
We had to film it to make way for the
balcony sequence in Times Square.
It was filmed on the same stage.
We had to film here and get out.
All of those guys in the crowd did
an incredible job, all the extras.
They put so much energy
into the screaming and the jumping.
I could tell they loved Spider-Man.
That's why they were there.
We got a better performances...
...than usual
because they're such fans of the comic.
Cash Oshman was the extras casting
director and he did a good job...
...of giving us a lot of great people.
A hundred bucks?
The ad said $3000.
I like Neil's set in this room
and the hallway, and the sound job.
They work to tell the story that this is
some subterranean area of the arena.
Which is a hard thing to communicate.
The promoter is played
by Larry Joshua...
...one of my favorite character actors.
This is such a pivotal scene, and so
much right out of the comic book...
...and something we felt
we had to really do in a way...
- ...that fans would recognize it.
- Right.
It's obviously the scene
upon which the whole story turns.
He's got my money!
Thanks.
What the hell's the matter with you?
You let him go!
Look at the rake to this ceiling.
That's what I was referring to...
...when I mentioned Neil designed this
to seem like...
...it was underneath the stadium.
I love Tobey's face here.
He's a sinner.
He's let pride and anger rule.
You won't see that look
anywhere else in the picture.
He's full of himself, feels his own
bitter justice has been served.
The guy deserved it.
It's a sin he'll end up paying for
the rest of his life.
- What happened?
- Someone got hurt.
- Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Stay back.
- Stay back!
- That's my uncle!
- What happened?
- Carjacker. He's been shot.
We just called the paramedics.
They're on their way.
Uncle Ben?
Cliff Robertson was a real sport
in shooting this.
It's probably 3:00 in the morning,
it was freezing cold...
...and we'd say,
"Get Cliff on the ground."
He'd just throw himself right
down on the cold concrete.
No screaming for a furni-pad
or any of that nonsense.
He'd throw himself down and
wait for the camera crew to set up.
He's a real professional.
It was written originally
that Cliff was already expired...
...when Tobey's character
came up to him.
It was his idea. He said,
"Why don't we just have me alive...
...to make contact with Peter
one last time?" It's a great idea.
That alley he just ran in was the same
alley that he climbed up the wall in.
We shot one in the day
and this at night, obviously.
Downtown Los Angeles.
- I love this.
- I have a funny story about this.
We did a test of CG Spidey
climbing up the wall...
...which was a very early iteration
of this scene right here.
I took the test, I called Amy Pascal
and John Calley and I said:
"We put Tobey in the suit and we
tested him climbing up.
We put a wall on its side
and tested him climbing up the wall."
We were in pre-production. I was
trying to get more money for the movie.
I called them into the screening room
and they came down and watched it.
It was CG, but I said it was Tobey
in the suit. They went nuts.
They said, "Oh, my God, it's amazing!
He looks so incredible"
Then we laughed.
This was a composite of Tobey's real
face put into the CGI Spider-Man.
That was a very tricky move.
I enjoy watching him struggling with
swinging. He's never done it before.
I love the subtlety that you
and John Dykstra put together in here...
...of him twisting and turning
on one of these shots...
...showing him struggling
with his gift and curse.
Arthur Coburn, was insistent,
one of my editors...
...that we had to track his progression,
as far as his development of grace.
He had to be as awkward as possible
in this early sequence to sell it.
- And I thought that was a great idea.
- Yeah, it was.
I shot this sequence
with our second unit...
...director of photography,
Chris Faloona.
He did a lot of great second unit work
for us. Chris is a garner.
So happy to be going with him.
This is a beautiful set built by Neil.
It's supposed to be the interior
of the abandoned part...
...of the New York
Port Authority Building.
Where the old ferry
used to arrive every day.
Who's there?
Don't hurt me. Give me a chance.
Give me a chance!
What about my uncle?
Did you give him a chance? Did you?
Answer me!
Stop that guy!
- Great moment.
- It's very powerful.
Again, this moment
is so much a trigger...
...and so integral to what made
the whole story work in the comic book.
There's this whole notion that
Spider-Man doesn't ever kill anybody.
But he has to be responsible for this
guy's death, so the guy actually trips.
But the whole, sort of,
ethic of Spider-Man is...
- ...he defends people, but he doesn't...
- Kill them.
Even, of course, with the Goblin,
who's responsible for his own death.
He just has a lot of good luck
in that way.
This was an image that we loved.
Which was also an early image
Sam had...
...of Peter on one of the eagles
in the Chrysler Building.
If you know New York, you'll know that
skyline is something that we made up...
...which was something we did often
in the movie.
We took architecture that we liked and
manipulated it in the CG world.
So you know it's New York,
but no street is exactly photo-real.
That's why I...
New York has never been shot this way.
It's so inventive and beautiful
and romantic, in a way...
...when he swings through the city.
- Good evening.
- General. Good to see you.
Our exoskeleton's got
real firepower, general.
Well, if it does what you say it can,
I'll sign that contract tomorrow.
- He's clear, let's go!
- You're confident about this test?
Absolutely.
Captain Curtis is our top pilot.
Now, what about
your commitment to OSCORP?
This entire sequence...
...starting with that "Quest Aerospace"
stenciled on the crate...
...all the way through the explosions of
the bunkers was shot by John Dykstra...
...my second unit director.
We are picking up
an unidentified object, closing fast.
- Your favorite transition is coming.
- Yeah.
- That's really fun.
- It's so cool. I love it.
"Chess!"
Sam just makes this such a great...
We have some action, then you come to
the more humanistic things.
It's just so great how he balances
all of that out.
The audience is never scared...
...because right after comes
a happy thing or sweet thing.
It's just a great mixture of action
to the story line.
It just blends very nicely.
Peter, the science award.
That's terrific.
Yeah.
I don't know if I should tell this.
This scene was shot on the Sony lot
in front of the executive building...
...because we only had half a day
to shoot the scene...
...so we didn't have time
to go to a location.
So we dressed up the front
of the building...
...and wouldn't let the executives
get into their office on that morning.
I love it. Now when I walk
on the Sony lot, it's like:
"That was our school in Spider-Man."
It'll always be there.
It makes for a great tour spot
on the Sony tour.
That's true.
Can I fix you something?
No, thanks.
- I love Rosemary.
- She's amazing.
Yeah, she's amazing.
She's so beautiful, I think.
She's magnificent-looking.
She's funny, because she really didn't
know anything about Spider-Man.
She worked with Sam on The Gift.
I knew her through mutual friends
but had never worked with her.
She had no idea
what she was getting into.
Now she goes places and
she's recognized as Aunt May.
- She has a whole new following.
- That's so funny. Fan following, yeah.
- This is a great scene.
- Yeah.
I remember right before
the camera rolled, I told Tobey:
"Your name is not gonna be
above the title."
I missed him a lot today.
I know.
I miss him too.
But he was there.
I can't help thinking about
the last thing I said to him.
He tried to tell me something important,
and I threw it in his face.
You loved him...
...and he loved you.
He never doubted
the man you'd grow into.
How you were meant for great things.
You won't disappoint him.
I love Danny's score right here.
It really takes you into the moment.
With great power
comes great responsibility.
Remember that, Pete. Remember that.
That shot was shot with an Earl Wiggins
cam in Downtown L.A...
...with a New York background.
Great shot.
Doug Lefter shot this scene for me,
the whole robbery.
These snippets were shot by
Dick Buckley, second unit director.
I love that dog.
We called her "the dog walker."
These guys I actually found
on a construction site.
We were shooting the scene in front
of the library with Uncle Ben...
...and we were trying to get
real faces, great faces.
I found these guys
in this construction site.
They couldn't believe it. "What do you
mean? We're gonna be in a movie?"
It's always better to get real people.
Guy with eight hands.
Lucy Lawless, a friend of Sam's.
- This guy I love.
- Yeah, he was funny.
Doesn't he look like Owen Wilson?
- Kind of?
- A little bit.
- He doesn't have Owen's great nose.
- No.
"Who is Spider-Man?"
He's a criminal, that's who he is.
- I love him. He's so good.
- He's fantastic.
J.K. had worked with Sam in The Gift...
...and he came to see us in New York
and it was like meeting you.
It was like, "This guy has to play
this part." Born to play the part.
Once we got the hair...
It's the thing about hair.
Once we got the hair, he was Jameson.
And Sam's brother's in this scene also.
Like the Delta 88 and Bruce Campbell,
Ted Raimi is in all Sam Raimi movies.
He's hilarious.
- There's Sam's brother.
- There's Ted.
- We sold out four printings.
- Sold out?
Every COPY-
Tomorrow, Spider-Man, page one,
with a decent picture.
- Conway to page 7.
- That's a problem.
Page eight, give him 10 percent off.
Five percent.
- That can't be done.
- Get out!
- He's so good.
- Sam loves to work with him.
It's such a big brother-little brother
relationship. He likes to torture him.
He makes him do 12 takes.
He's really kind of sadistic.
He doesn't want to be famous?
I'll make him infamous!
There's a famous New York extra,
radio man, that goes sneaking by there.
- Do you remember him?
- Sure do. Radio man. He's a classic.
He was in For Love of the Game
but he found the cutting room floor.
But he did a great job for us
in that one too.
Begging for a job. How about you?
Every time I see these two together,
they make a connection for me.
She gives a bit of herself in everything
she does. She's very generous.
I just got off a job.
She's great at playing layers
and levels of things.
She's so embarrassed.
Doesn't want Peter to know.
I see she's not a very good liar
in this scene.
Excuse me, Miss Watson?
Busted.
Yes, Enrique! Okay? I get you.
It better not happen no more.
Pete even feels worse than she does
about the whole thing.
He's very empathetic.
- There's the button.
- "Try my cream pie."
It's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
- Makes me want to go to New York.
- Yeah. That was a beautiful day too.
We're going out. Didn't he tell you?
Oh, yeah. Right.
I think he'd hate the idea...
There's paparazzi guys too.
Tobey pisses off the paparazzi guys.
They're nicer to me.
- Do they go away when you tell them?
- They're just, like, nicer to me.
The more you act like,
"Don't take my picture," the more...
- Just wave and they go away.
- Give them a moment.
But Tobey likes messing with them
a little bit more.
They were in his eye line.
They stayed out of mine...
...but throughout his eye line they were
always taking his pictures and stuff.
I'll come by and have some of your
Moondance coffee someday.
- And I won't tell Harry.
- No, don't tell Harry.
I won't.
I won't tell Harry.
I love that location,
it's right across from NYU.
It was an amazing apartment,
where the exterior was shot.
- This was a set that Neil designed.
- Yeah, this is an amazing apartment.
Where do you get this apartment
in New York? I'd love to live here.
Daddy got it for him. Daddy.
They even have a nice balcony.
I remember when we worked
on this set...
...Tobey had a lot of good notes
for myself and Neil Spisak...
...about the reality of the size of the
loft that these two would really have.
And the style of the furnishings.
He had a more realistic take and guided
us from a character point of view...
...which is so important
in making a picture...
...to listen to actors and believe they
have the best take on who they are...
...and what they know about
their world, to listen to that.
See I love this intrigue,
this set up of the triangle.
Sam had said, even early on...
"mat he wanted 'Ms 90210 or Melrose
Place... I don't watch those shows.
Very soap Opera-Y-
He wanted these, kind of,
teenage relationships...
...to be moving in a parallel line
with the superhero story.
- I believe it. I see that kind of behavior.
- There's tension.
Yeah. Seems really real to me.
Hello.
Let's go! Move it!
Watch the street!
That was me in the suit
during this fight scene.
- That was you? You're very acrobatic.
- You know...
You're multi-talented.
I saw Bring It On.
I know you can do those jumps.
Cheese!
Neil Spisak and his team came up
with these pictures.
They're very difficult because
Spider-Man can't be doing any...
...of the things in reality
that are needed in these pictures.
We can't do it with an actor.
So we had to stage backgrounds
and separate foreground elements...
...and do a lot of composites
and then clean up in a digital state.
It was a big deal to come up with
those pictures Peter supposedly took.
Give you 300.
That's the standard freelance fee.
There's a slight old-fashioned quality
to the whole film.
It feels like a '50s comic book,
even with what we wear.
I told Jim I really wanted to wear
a trench coat in the film...
...because it signified for me that classic
"girl-in-the-comic-book" kind of look.
I'm pleased about that, that what
we captured looks like a comic book.
Yeah, and it has an old-school
feel to it, the movie, a little bit.
I was so happy that Elizabeth Banks
took the job of Betty Brant...
...in the reception area here.
With a talented actress like that...
...I was able to have these actors
make a moment...
...when there was really
nothing there.
Bill Nunn did a great job
as Robbie Robertson, as well.
I'm Peter Parker.
I'm a photographer.
Yes. I can see that.
He strikes out everywhere.
Yeah, he strikes out, but at
the same time, I see on his face...
...that as lame as he is, he's actually
achieved one of his dreams.
- So he feels a sense of fulfillment.
- Yeah.
In short, ladies and gentlemen
of the board...
...costs are down, revenues are up...
Neil designed this set
on the Warner Bros. lot.
It's one of his best accomplishments,
it's really beautifully detailed.
He created depressions...
...in the walls where
he'd hide these fluorescent tubes.
Quite beautiful, giving it a lot of
dimensionality.
They don't want a power struggle
with entrenched management.
The deal is off if you come with it.
The board expects your resignation
in 30 days.
You can't do this to me.
I started this company.
You know how much I sacrificed?!
- Oh, Max. Please.
- Norman, the board is unanimous.
We're announcing the sale
after the World Unity Festival.
I'm sorry.
You're out, Norman.
There's the Goblin theme.
Welcome to OSCORP Industries
Unity Day Festival.
What a complicated shot that is there.
You've got Downey,
you've got New York background plates.
You've got pieces shot
on the stages here at Sony.
Very complex. It took us a long time
to design that shot.
And a lot of these shots here
in the Times Square sequence.
Neil did a great job with Don Burgess
and John Dykstra and his team...
...just seamlessly tying
a lot of locations together.
Don Burgess had a difficult job in
shooting all these different elements...
- ...to fit together, lighting-wise.
- Yeah.
That is obviously a stage shot here...
...but the last shot of Parker
was shot on the streets of Downey.
He had a lot of New York photography
and it all had to blend seamlessly.
Remember this drama
of trying to find the dress?
- I love that dress.
- Yeah, it's good.
It makes sense too, because
it's not an expensive dress, you know.
Great choice.
M.J., would you do me a favor?
I forgot my drink inside.
I also like that line where he says:
"Why didn't you wear the black dress?
My father loves black."
It is a funny line.
- Have you seen my father around?
- Well, I'm not sure if he's coming.
This was, without question, the most
complicated thing we did in the movie.
Even more complicated than the end.
We would have these meetings.
We would have these weekly
or bi-weekly, or sometimes daily...
...what we called
"Times Square meetings."
Starting from when we made
the decision...
...to set this scene in Times Square.
The logistics of how to do it
and how to get the shots.
The building where you guys are on
the balcony is a building Neil made up.
It doesn't really exist in Times Square,
but we had to fit it in geographically.
And there were plates that were shot
for this stuff up in the sky.
And then there was a gigantic set
built in Downey.
So even though
it's a five-minute sequence...
...in terms of the resources
and the shooting time...
...we probably shot, between the set
and the location, three weeks maybe.
- Close to a month.
- It was a big deal.
There was Stan Lee.
There's Stan Lee.
- Laura's daughter is coming in soon.
- My daughter. The stuntman who fell...
...was a guy who played Spider-Man
on the TV show.
Remember that?
Here we go, Kirsten.
Here starts the screaming match.
Hold your ears.
"Oh, God!"
I kept telling Sam...
I love that shot.
Girls in movies who scream
really annoy me.
At the end, I got a little annoyed
by my screaming.
At the end of the movie.
I love that.
That's one of my favorite things.
The pumpkin bomb was kind of fun
because the Goblin was full of...
- There's my daughter.
- Yeah. Hi, Julie.
The Goblin has this bag of tricks...
...and when we were sitting
and thinking about it:
"What would a pumpkin bomb look like?
Who would think of such a thing?"
This kid's stupid. I know he's
in shock, but move, already!
Wouldn't your mother go in
and move you?
- She couldn't get to him.
- Oh, yeah, whatever.
- Hold it!
- I surrender.
Willem demanded to do
all his own fighting.
He felt that the character
had to be consistent...
...and that it would show if he
let stuntmen do his work.
It wouldn't sell.
Not that the quality would be poor,
but it wouldn't be the same character...
...that he'd created and seen through
from beginning to end.
In this strafing run,
this is him on the glider right there.
That's right, that behind shot.
Shot by Max Kleven.
It's really a good... Well-designed
glider gag that Max came up with...
...hanging off of the camera car,
on a Ubangi on wires.
It worked beautifully.
The storyboard artists, mostly Doug
Lefter, did a great job designing all this.
He had help from Neil Spisak
and the production department...
...with balloons and the set.
Also,
Jeff Lynch and Dave Stephan...
...contributed a tremendous amount
to this.
But my hat's off to Doug.
He's such a great visualist.
This sequence is complicated.
Andrew Jimenez really added a lot
with his skills...
...working this whole sequence out.
Karen Goulekas contributed quite a bit
on the picture.
John Dykstra and the animation team
made each and every shot come to life.
But it couldn't have been put together
unless we had Bob Murawski...
...who worked the pieces as the editor
and made them all come together.
That was a great swinging shot
by our stuntman.
Jeff Habberstad put together this shot
over the blue sky over the ocean...
...because there're no
green screens that big.
They shot that out at the ocean.
It's a beautiful swing.
Neil Spisak really came up with a
beautifully romantic location here...
...for the moment between
Peter and Mary Jane.
He did his homework. Many
New Yorkers don't know this exists...
...on top of the Rockefeller Center
roof garden.
It is such a beautiful place up there,
with the church in the background.
Starting to swing a little better.
I love when he swings off and yells.
It's like the high of public service.
You've done your best to help others
and that's what he's celebrating.
That's really why it's so effective.
And he runs along that building.
I love that moment.
The fellas in the animation department
came up with that.
I think it was Anthony,
our animation director.
And what do you mean,
incredible?
All right. I'm sorry. Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs...
Alvin Sargent wrote that scene.
It's one of my favorites.
So funny, with James Franco
on the phone with M.J.
You just imagine, obviously,
the other side of the conversation.
And then, after being dumped on...
...he hangs up the phone and he says,
"She's just a little rattled."
What else would he be thinking?
I didn't.
I'm gonna get some rest.
I'm gonna stay up for a while.
What was that thing?
I don't know.
Whatever it is,
somebody has to stop it.
That moment was important to me...
...because it was Peter Parker stepping
up to the responsibility of Spider-Man.
Somebody there?
Somebody.
Who said that?
This sequence with Willem takes you
to depths of the insanity...
...that his character is starting
to plummet down into.
I love the device you came up with...
...with the mirror showing
his two different personalities...
...and interacting with his
two different personalities.
You know, that was in the script.
It was all made to work...
...just only through Willem Dafoe's
performance.
Did you think it was coincidence?
So many good things,
all happening for you.
All for you. Norman.
What do you want?
To say what you won't.
To do what you can't.
To remove those in your way.
The board members.
You killed them.
We killed them.
We?
Remember?
Your little accident...
It's this lesson you learn
all the time...
...about how much you need
to communicate, for the story...
...what's going on, and how much
an actor brings to the storytelling.
Initially written, it was a three
and a half page scene, or something.
And the revelation as we went along
in the process was...
...you could get everything you had
to get from a storytelling standpoint...
...as well as the emotional stuff
that was going on with the character...
...much more economically.
Spider-Man. And the Green Goblin.
The Green Goblin. You like that?
Made it up myself.
- These weirdos all got to have a name.
- Mr. Jameson, Spider...
- Hoffman!
- Yeah?
Copyright the name "Green Goblin."
I want a quarter every time it's said.
How about "Green Meanie"?
Spider-Man wasn't attacking the city.
That's slander.
It is not. I resent that.
Slander is spoken.
In print, it's libel.
You don't trust anybody.
I trust my barber.
What are you, his lawyer? Get out.
Let him sue. Get rich like a normal
person. That's what made this country...
I remember shooting that scene with
the cigar flying back into the window.
Usually it missed the table, sometimes
it landed in J.K.'s lap, burning him.
It's a dangerous scene, to have
that hot thing flying in from behind.
One of my favorites to shoot.
You are useless.
Jane Alexander did such a great job
with his hair.
It's so J. Jonah Jameson. He's great.
...let Mom and Dad
talk for a minute.
Sleep...
Wake up, little spider. Wake up.
No, you're not dead yet.
Just paralyzed...
...temporarily.
You're an amazing creature,
Spider-Man.
You and I are not so different.
I'm not like you. You're a murderer.
Well, to each his own.
I chose my path,
you chose the way of the hero.
And they found you amusing
for a while, the people of this city.
But the one thing they love
more than a hero...
...is to see a hero fail,
fall, die trying.
In spite of everything you've done for
them, eventually, they will hate you.
Why bother?
- Because it's right.
- Here's the real truth.
There are eight million people
in this city.
This whole notion of trying to see,
at least see the eyes...
...even though we couldn't see
any of Tobey's features...
The genius of what Sam did
in the end of the movie was find a way...
...to reveal Tobey's face
in the final scenes.
Because as you can see,
looking at this...
...you're limited in how you can act
behind those masks.
Or we could destroy.
Cause the deaths of countless
innocents in selfish battle...
...again and again and again until
we're both dead. Is that what you want?
Great animation from the fellas at SPI.
I love him leaping on that glider.
He seems like he's gotta balance
himself for a brief moment.
He gotta grab a hold of the front of
the glider to stabilize himself.
- Seems very real to me.
- Yeah.
In spite of everything you've done for
them, eventually, they will hate you.
This was also shot
on the Warner Bros. back lot.
How was your audition?
The sound man gave me
an ugly choice. He said:
"You can have oars in the background,
or you can have your sound."
Horrible thing to say.
They made so much noise going over
those wet city streets, those cabs.
Motion picture cabs are always
in terrible shape.
Loud engines, terribly in need
of a tune up.
This is my favorite scene between
the two of them. I really, really enjoy it.
I'd like a cheeseburger.
Alvin Sargent wrote this.
Did a beautiful job with it too.
He did a great job.
Come with us.
No, thanks. How's it going with...?
Never mind.
That's none of my business.
It's not?
Why so interested?
Avi Arad had a great idea during
this scene.
He said, "Maybe this is the point
where she can finally say 'Tiger."'
Which is what all the fans know is one
of Mary Jane's favorite taglines.
I don't know.
So Kirsten then said, "Why don't I say it
just as I leave, at the very end?"
So together, they satisfied that one
of one thousand fan requirements.
It's a great little punctuation mark.
Hey, check it out, man.
Come on, man.
This scene was further torturing
of Kirsten...
...in very, very cold weather
and freezing cold water.
This wasn't a fun scene.
Although I did like
to do my little butt-kicking.
You did.
See, the sidewalks are higher
on the back lot...
...so the water floods in the street.
You're up to water on your ankle.
This was tough because we were
all bundled up in front of heaters...
- ...and you were out there for hours.
- Freezing my booty off.
And trying to be romantic
at the same time.
When we were doing the close-up
dialogue without the looping...
...I was screaming at him.
I was like, "You're amazing!"
Because we couldn't hear each other
because the rain was so loud.
There was a secret door built
into the side of that wall...
...so that Tobey could escape into it and
the stuntman could then come down.
Although, this is Tobey here.
But the first time you saw Spider-Man
descend was the stuntman.
Does she know or doesn't she?
You have that moment
where maybe you know it's him?
Here? No. That's at the end.
But when he says,
"I was in the neighborhood."
No? That's what I always think
because he said to you earlier on:
"I was in the neighborhood."
No, I don't think M.J.'s that bright.
Or Kirsten.
No, no, I just...
I wouldn't give anything away there.
There was this wonderful image
in the comic book of him...
...with his, you know,
mask half off like that.
It was something that Sam had
in his head very early on...
...to have this upside-down kiss
which is so...
I know it was painful, but it really
is his signature moment of the movie.
Our mixers, Greg Russell and Kevin
O'Connell did a great job mixing this.
This scene, they handled
just beautifully, like the old movies.
They let the rain all drop away,
brought up Danny Elf man's score.
They let the audience soar
with the emotion of the thing...
...pushing away the reality
of the moment.
Let me in! My baby's in there!
This was a great piece
of location work in New York.
I was very impressed
that they let us...
...blaze that building
as large as we needed to.
We owe a great debt
to the city of New York for that.
John Fedynich, he was our New York
location manager.
He did a lot of great work securing
the permits and permission to do that.
When he swings into that window,
the one piece of animation I love...
...is when the animator lets his web
get caught in the updraft of the heat.
And it just floats upward in a moment,
right before the cut.
It really captured
the lightness of the web.
- It's okay. Your baby's fine.
- Oh, my baby!
God bless you, Spider-Man.
The blanket has no dirt
on it or anything.
Now, come on, you guys.
Oh, my God, there's somebody
still up there!
I'm going.
- I'll be here when you get back.
- Not coming back, chief.
Go! GO!
This scene that John Frazier and his
team of fire experts put together...
...I was really impressed by.
The amount of fire.
The fact that they pulled it off
so safely was incredible.
I'm gonna get you out of here!
Initially, we thought the suits
were flammable.
We did all of this experimenting
with fire retardant. Scary.
That's so scary, that...
The action in this sequence
is amazing, I think.
Like a moth to the flame.
What about my generous proposal?
Are you in or are you out?
It's you who's out, Gobby.
Out of your mind.
That's such a cheese line,
but really cute.
"It's you who's out, Gobby.
Out of your mind."
That's one of my favorite piece of
animation. The fluidity of movement.
They really captured the awkwardness
of the human form...
...and its grace at the same time.
I was always impressed by it.
I love the weapons, though.
This was another challenge.
We'd had this notion about
what Sam called "razorbats."
You know, the pumpkin bomb turns into
these flying boomerang-knife things.
Scary.
Great sound design in here as well.
Steve Flick did a great job in putting
these sounds together...
...with his team of effects cutters.
- M.J., will you stop goofing around?
- Harry, relax.
He's here.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Aunt May. I'm sorry I'm late.
Work was murder.
I picked up a fruitcake.
Thank you, Mr. Osborn.
We're so glad you could come.
Who is this lovely young lady?
I'd like you to meet my father.
Dad, this is Mary Jane Watson.
I've been looking forward
to meeting you.
- Happy Thanksgiving, sir.
- Now, where is Peter?
He'd better have remembered
that cranberry sauce.
Oh, that's weird.
I didn't know he was here.
Peter?
The Spider-Man mask wasn't made
to come off so easily.
James Acheson had to design one
just for that shot...
...that could be pulled off in an instant.
He knew it would never hold up
to scrutiny...
...so he made certain exactly what the
shot would be and designed it for that.
- Bit of a slob, isn't he?
- All brilliant men are.
- We actually put Tobey up there.
- You did?
You bet.
One of my favorite shots coming up
here. He looks up. He's not there.
We come back down, he's already
a step ahead of us, furious about it.
- Hey, everyone.
- Oh, Peter!
Sorry I'm late,
it's a jungle out there.
Had to beat an old lady with a stick
to get these cranberries.
Thank you.
Now then, everybody sit down...
...and we can say grace.
Parker.
I remember the turkey in this scene
had been sitting around for two days.
Put off this terrible,
rotting, horrible odor.
People had to pretend that it
was a delicious-looking thing.
In fact, it was nauseating.
Created an awful stench
that turned your stomach.
Why, Peter, you're bleeding.
I stepped off a curb and got clipped
by one of those bike messengers.
Well, let me see.
Oh, my goodness.
- That looks awful.
- No, it's nothing.
I'll get the first-aid kit.
Then we'll say grace.
This is the boys' first Thanksgiving
here, and we'll do things properly.
How did you say that happened?
Bike messenger.
Knocked me down.
- If you'll excuse me, I've got to go.
- Why?
Something has come to my attention.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine, just fine.
This sequence is
such good moviemaking.
It's so entertaining,
such good, concise storytelling.
It's such a pivotal moment
in the movie...
...where everything comes together
and all the conflicts are...
All the rest of the movie
is set in motion.
Your mother was beautiful too.
They're all beautiful.
Until they're snarling after your trust
fund like a pack of ravening wolves.
You're wrong about her, Dad.
A word to the not-so-wise
about your little girlfriend:
Do what you need to with her,
then broom her fast.
In that moment with Mary Jane Watson,
I love where Kirsten is hurt...
...then she pulls it together
and you see some anger come out.
And then she decides she's not
gonna take it and she stands up.
Shut up about stuff
you don't understand!
I love watching her go through
those moments. That thought process.
Spider-Man is all but invincible.
But Parker, we can destroy him.
I can't.
Betrayal must not be countenanced.
Parker must be educated.
What do I do?
Instruct him in the matters
of loss and pain.
Make him suffer.
Make him wish he were dead.
Yes?
And then grant his wish.
But how?
The cunning warrior attacks
neither body nor mind.
Tell me how!
The heart, Osborn.
First, we attack his heart.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses...
...as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us...
Rosemary was a real sport
to go through this...
...tremendous physical challenge,
being thrown about that room.
With the fans hitting her hard and all
the debris flying about around her.
I thought the CGI artist
did a great job...
...taking John Frazier's
explosion on set...
...composting it with her, then creating
CG debris elements that flew past her...
...that really put her
in an explosion sandwich...
...and sold the fact
that she was there.
You have to leave.
- What happened?
- Those eyes!
Those horrible yellow eyes!
The thing about the eyes, that scene
was the first day we had the suit...
...and we didn't have eyes
for the mask.
We'd never seen them.
We were shooting the scene, and we
were literally running back and forth...
...to the truck figuring out
how opaque should they be, how yellow.
And those eyes,
when we first did them...
...to get them to look right on camera,
you couldn't see through them.
This was originally three shots.
Don Burgess,
when we were shooting it...
...had the idea to put it all together
as one, which was a good idea.
It was Parker, the hands, the picture,
another angle of Parker, and his aunt.
Maybe it was five or six shots.
He put it all together with one move.
It turned out to be
the best thing for it...
...because it had a grace in it
that cutting would have broken up.
- Will she be okay?
- She'll be fine.
She's been sleeping all day.
- Thanks for coming.
- Of course.
How are you?
You okay about the other night?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just felt bad
about leaving Aunt May.
- Have you talked to Harry?
- He called me.
I haven't called him back.
The fact is...
- ...I'm in love with somebody else.
- You are?
Alvin Sargent did such a beautiful job
writing this speech by Peter.
It's so heartfelt
and it really gives you a glimpse...
...into the depths of his soul
and his feelings for her.
Trust me.
It's funny.
He's saved my life twice,
and I've never even seen his face.
- Oh. Him.
- You're laughing at me.
No, I understand.
He is extremely cool.
But do you think it's true, all the
terrible things they say about him?
No, no. Not Spider-Man,
not a chance in the world.
I know him a little bit.
I'm sort of his unofficial
photographer.
- Has he mentioned me?
- Yeah.
What'd he say?
I said...
He asked me what I thought about you.
One of my girlfriends
who saw this scene said:
"This is the speech every girl wants
a boy to make to her."
This is one of the many moments when
what we saw in that room in Berlin...
...is what happened in this scene
that made it worked so great.
- Yeah, Tobey was easy to work off of.
- Yeah.
Everything feels not quite normal.
Both Arthur Coburn and Bob Murawski
did a great job with this picture.
One of Bob's talents,
which you see in this scene...
...is his sense of performance
and take selections.
He really has a great talent
to be able...
...to be able to go in and watch all
the performances again and again...
...and choose what I think
is the best of the best.
That really plays in the moment...
...and cut them against each other.
It's as if you've...
...reached the unreachable.
His style of dress
is another thing entirely.
You said that?
Well, something like that.
That was Harry's first day on the set.
For some reason
he came in with black hair.
It was the weirdest thing.
We'd already figured out he was gonna
match his hair color to Willem Dafoe's.
He steps in to shoot,
and he's got black hair.
It gets a laugh in the theater,
this scene.
He's like, "Dad? Is that you?"
It's the most ridiculous...
But the laugh altogether
is such a signature of the character.
That's one of my funniest moments
in the picture.
He comes in and hears the rantings
and ravings of his father.
It's based on, for me...
I would come home and hear my mother
upstairs saying things...
...that she should have said to others,
but didn't have the guts. "Mom?"
He's loved her since the 4th grade.
He pretends like he doesn't, but
there's no one Peter cares for more.
I'm so sorry.
I haven't always been there for you,
Havel?
You're busy.
This was filmed in a great location
in L.A.
It was a huge mansion up
in the Hollywood Hills.
That's right. And Neil Spisak demanded
that we not shoot here.
He'd learned that they had shot
a scene from Batman here.
He demanded that I not photograph it
any way similar to Batman.
He made sure to decorate it
a very different way.
But I don't think anyone knows that.
At least they didn't until this moment,
when you happened to tell the viewers.
Bob came up with the idea
of putting that scare in at that moment.
- Actually, it may have been Paul's idea.
- Paul Hart, assistant editor.
Paul's idea to put a good scare,
jolt moment in there.
He did it as a joke.
Like many things...
...I realize some of the assistant's jokes
were better than my editor's great ideas.
So we took that...
...and Bob transformed it
into a full-fledged scare.
You were supposed to be asleep.
You know, you were about 6 years old
when M.J.'s family moved in next door.
And when she got out of the car,
and you saw her for the first time...
This was a great scene
that David Koepp wrote.
Reminds us of Peter's warmth
for Mary Jane ever since he was a child.
Helps set up the ending of the piece.
When he finally walks away from her.
You're reminded
just how much she means to him.
- She's still his girl.
- Well, isn't that up to her?
- She doesn't really know who I am.
- Because you won't let her.
You're so mysterious all the time.
Tell me, would it be so dangerous...
...to let Mary Jane know
how much you care?
Everybody else knows.
I'll be right back.
But...
Come on, pick up.
- Hey, M.J.
- Hi. Sing your song at the beep.
M.J., it's Peter. You there?
Hello? You there?
I'm just calling to check up on you.
Will you call me when you get in?
All right, well...
Don't...
Don't go up any dark alleys.
Hello?
That laugh.
Such a great cackle.
Where is she?
We actually played around with a lot
of different locations for this ending.
We knew we wanted to be up high.
That seemed like a requirement of the
storytelling. The Goblin who flies...
...and Spider-Man who swings,
and all that.
Then it hit us that
the 59th Street Bridge was the place.
Little did we know how difficult
it would be to execute.
Like the Times Square sequence...
...we couldn't actually go up there
and shoot on top of that bridge.
When we screened the movie
for the studio for the first time...
...they watched a sequence of M.J. on
the bridge, but there was no bridge.
And Spider-Man rescued her...
...but for half of the sequence,
there was no Spider-Man.
And we were trying to say:
"No, no, trust us. It's gonna be okay."
Goblin, what have you done?
I read about 400 kids
for those 10 kids in the tram.
I know you did. You were
in the casting room with them forever.
I spent about four days...
...with 9-year-olds screaming
at me and crying for me.
It was painful.
But they all did a great job...
...and it's really tough. They go
through a lot of emotions there.
Spider-Man!
For all the amount of hanging and
dropping I did, it doesn't look painful.
- It doesn't? It looks like that to me.
- Really? I did a lot?
But I was up there
for two weeks straight doing stuff.
Yeah, you were hanging and falling,
hanging and falling.
When you auditioned, Sam said:
"Are you in good shape?"
You made a muscle.
- You don't have a lot of muscle.
- I don't have any. I'm like, "Yeah, Sam.
Sure, whatever you want."
This bridge sequence is one of
the hardest scenes that I've ever done.
To think about how
the real bridge worked...
...and blocking the characters
on the real structure...
...verses the set pieces Neil
and his team built on stages...
...verses the CGI bridge
that had to be made...
...and the cheats that had to be made...
...relative to the real bridge
and the set pieces.
The under-bridge sets that went with
it. There was so much to keep in mind.
- It got very difficult, I remember.
- More so than Times Square sequence?
For me, it was, because I couldn't
walk the bridge.
These places didn't exist so that you
could scout and know personally.
A lot of it had to be kept in the mind
or just done through photographs.
So much dimensionality to it.
People moving from point A to point B.
I don't just mean left and right
or backwards and forward...
...but up and down.
Under, over, around the bridge.
You have to have a sense of it
in your mind to make the scene work.
So it was a real brain twister.
And always trying to keep in mind
where you are geographically...
...compared to Manhattan
and Roosevelt Island...
...to keep the continuity correct.
That's right.
Dan Sweetman,
a great storyboard artist...
...came in the second half of editing
and helped me re-work this sequence...
...based on original work that
Jeff Lynch, storyboard artist, had done.
Actually, before that,
based on work that I'd done...
...with another storyboard artist,
Mark Andrews.
Everybody really contributed
to this sequence.
Along with all the people
at Sony Pictures Imageworks.
Contributed incredible amount
under John Dykstra's supervision.
That's some more great animation
right there.
What's the groaning cow there?
That's the sound of strain on the...
Slowed down to 72 frames a second...
...the sound of thousands of pounds
of torque on this steel cable.
Tobey's brothers are in the tram too,
one of them was.
And John Dykstra,
visual effects supervisor...
...his daughter was one
of the tram kids.
John (Sally's stepson is one of the
tram kids. Everybody got in the act.
I got something for your ass!
You mess with Spidey,
you mess with New York!
You mess with one of us,
you mess with all of us.
Took a long time to reset
and do those shots.
All the prop guys and crew members
running around picking up rubber pipes.
A rubber chicken
was slipped in there.
But it took a long time
to reload all the New Yorkers...
- ...with objects to pelt Willem with.
- Yeah.
It's tough. You've got 150 extras that
you've treated badly for two days...
...then you give them objects to throw
at you. It's a dangerous job.
This was a set constructed
by Neil and his team...
...that we referred to
as the "hulking ruin."
A lot of beautiful
design work done in here.
Misery, misery, misery.
That's what you've chosen.
And this, to a large degree,
actually exists.
It's an old abandoned
smallpox hospital on Roosevelt Island.
But Neil did take his cue...
...from the actual hospital
that's there. It's interesting.
I thought the mixers did
a beautiful job in here.
Tobey did a great job looping too.
He had to come up
with 16 different ways to grunt.
Yeah, he did.
Peter Menzies came up with the web...
...Peter uses to stop the Goblin
the last second.
He was my second unit director
of photography just for this sequence.
You've spun your last web, Spider-Man.
Had you not been so selfish,
your girlfriend's death...
...would have been quick
and painless.
But now that you've really
pissed me off...
...I'm gonna finish her
nice and slow.
Sam came in one day and said,
"I want him to have a trident."
I don't know where that came from.
- With electric prods on the end.
- Right.
Get him, Spidey.
Your will is stronger than his.
Kick his buttocks.
Kim Kahana did great stunt here.
We let this wall fall down on him.
Willem did do almost all of his own
stunts, but that one was done by Kim.
Sam, I'm curious, is that arm coming out
of the rubble a wink to Evil Dead?
No, it's just a tribute to those old
Universal horror pictures.
The monster awakens.
The guys at A.D.I.,
Amalgamated Dynamics...
...did a great job with Willem's mask
right there, letting us beat it up.
- They really did.
- Yeah.
Mr. Osborn.
Thank God for you.
Great work on Spider-Man's costume
in various stages.
We had meetings about getting him
to the stage where you see him here.
And a lot of great work done
by Jim Acheson and Lisa Tomczeszyn...
...and his team of artists over there
in costume shop.
Jim had a mockup of the Spider-Man
outfit on a dummy he kept in a truck.
He'd follow me around,
location to location...
...lifting the truck's tailgate, saying:
"How about this, Sam?"
He'd take a razorblade to it and slice
away more pieces and more pieces.
He really worked long
and hard on that.
- The battle-ravaged Spider-Man look.
- Yeah.
It was difficult because
the whole costume works on tension...
...as Jim painstakingly told me
again and again.
You could only remove certain pieces
and still have it hold together properly.
Yeah, for the rain sequence,
you had to ruin one of our costumes...
...to make the head removable
and peeled up like that, and build...
...a special helmet.
This shot of Willem coming up
was actually shot later. This one.
He was already on another show.
He had to wear a wig.
He's more like the David Bowie
of Green Goblins.
Don't tell Harry.
The reason we re-did that shot
because we wanted him to say:
- "Don't tell Harry."
- Yeah.
Rather than it being an act of kindness
that Peter performs not tell Harry...
...we wanted him to fulfill
the last wish of Norman Osborn...
...this man who had been
the surrogate father to him.
So that he'd have an obligation,
a friendship...
...to perform these last acts,
to keep this dark secret.
Remember?
This was our first day in New York.
It was so cold and so windy.
Again, we had one day to shoot
this critical end scene in the movie.
But it was literally...
It must have been like 20 degrees.
I know what it's like
to lose a father.
The fellow playing the priest
kept asking me for a line.
I said, "I can't give it to you.
You're just a background player."
He had 10 different ideas of how
he could have a speaking part in this.
I swear on my father's grave,
Spider-Man will pay.
I really like James Franco's
performance in this scene.
I feel he's becoming his father.
Finally walking to that car that he was
so embarrassed of in the first scene.
He's very understated.
He's just brilliant in this last part.
You can feel the evil brewing
inside him, and the hatred.
That's a great shot.
He's almost walking to his destiny.
No matter what I do...
...no matter how hard I try...
...the ones I love will always
be the ones who pay.
You must miss him so much.
It's been so hard without him.
There's something
I've been wanting to tell you.
When I was up there...
...and I thought I was gonna die...
...there was only one person
who I was thinking of.
And it wasn't who I thought it'd be.
There's many questions
when you go to shoot a scene.
I remember Tobey and Kirsten,
they brought so much to this scene.
But one question was, they weren't
sure we should do the kiss at the end.
I really appreciate them going for it,
giving it a shot.
Because it turned out...
And you never know it at the time...
...but it wouldn't have even worked
without it.
We developed a great deal of trust
throughout the making of the movie.
They were willing to try things.
They learn to trust you...
...that if it doesn't work,
you won't keep it in the picture.
Laura was a big advocate of it too.
I thank her for that. Our producer.
I love you.
You had a great collaboration
with these two. They're gifted...
...well beyond their years.
Tobey did this scene.
Tobey screen-tested for the job.
He did a version of this scene
which was the thing...
The studio executives were in tears
when they saw it.
That's when they said they knew he
was the perfect choice for the movie.
You can't what?
Tell you...
...everything.
I mean, there's so much to tell.
Yeah. There's so much to tell.
Sam, if you were 19,
would you walk away?
I can't remember
what it was like being 19.
I will always be there
to take care of you.
I promise you that.
I will always be your friend.
Only a friend...
...Peter Parker?
That's all I have to give.
This scene was a great combination...
...of David Koepp, Alvin Sargent,
great input from the producers...
...and, of course, the actors.
Laura did a lot of great work
on that scene.
I will never forget these words...
As I watch him at the end here,
I really feel he has matured...
...grown into the person
that his uncle thought he could be.
Who am I?
I'm Spider-Man.
This is the shot...
This shot was actually...
...literally conceived 18 months
before we delivered the movie.
They started working on the shot
and it was the last thing...
...that came into the last shot.
It went into the film
just as we were finishing the dub.
- It's an absolutely amazing shot.
- Yeah, it is.
This is Sam Raimi, on behalf
of the cast and crew and everybody...
...thank you for watching the movie
with us.