Hi, guys. Um, I am Tom Holland.
I'm joined today by Tobey Maguire
and Andrew Garfield.
We just wanted to take a moment
to say a massive thank you
for all of your continued love
and support for this film.
While we were making this film,
I think I can speak on behalf of all of us
that we knew that we had our hands
on something really special.
But I don't think
we could ever have imagined
it would have been received
as well as it has been.
So thank you so much.
We are just incredibly grateful
that you guys are here for it.
Thank you to everybody
for supporting this movie.
I got to show up with these guys
and have a beautiful experience.
-Andrew, we have something to tell you.
-What?
It's important to both of us
that you know this. Okay?
-We love you.
About time. I've been waiting months.
I've been waiting months
since that day in Atlanta.
-I had it in here.
-Yeah.
It took every part of me not to say that.
This was worth the wait,
and I will wait for you guys
for centuries.
[Kiernan on TV] We come to you
now with revelations
about last week's attack in London.
An anonymous source provided this video.
It shows Quentin Beck, aka Mysterio,
moments before his death.
You may find this video disturbing.
[Mysterio] I managed to send the Elemental
back through the rift,
but I don't think
I'm gonna make it off this bridge alive.
Spider-Man attacked me.
He has an army of drones,
Stark technology.
He's saying he's the only one who's
gonna be the new Iron Man. No one else.
[Edith] Are you sure you want
to commence the drone attack?
There will be significant casualties.
[Spider-Man] Do it. Execute them all.
[explosions booming]
[Kiernan] This shocking video
was released earlier today
on the controversial news website
TheDailyBugle.net.
[Jameson on TV] There you have it, folks:
Conclusive proof
that Spider-Man was responsible
for the brutal murder of Mysterio,
an interdimensional warrior
who gave his life to protect our planet
and who will, no doubt, go down in history
as the greatest superhero of all time.
But that's not all, folks.
Here's the real blockbuster.
Brace yourselves.
You might wanna sit down.
[Mysterio] Spider-Man's real--
Spider-Man's real name is--
Spider-Man's name is Peter Parker.
-[Spider-Man] What the f--?
-[horn honks]
That's right, folks. Peter Parker.
A 17-year-old high school delinquent...
-[man 1] She knows him.
-Are you Spider-Man's girlfriend?
[Jameson] ...is, in fact...
-...the vile vigilante villain Spider-Man.
-[man 2] Yo, it's him.
-[Spider-Man] Whoa, whoa.
-Please don't touch her.
-You're just a kid?
[woman 1] You murdered Mysterio?
-You helped him?
-[Spider-Man] I didn't--
-Come on, kid, let me see your face.
-[crowd clamouring]
-He hit me. Spider-Man hit me.
-Come on.
He hit me.
[Jameson] All this time, people looked up
to this boy and called him a hero.
Well, I'll tell you what I call him,
public enemy number one!
[gasping] I told you
I never wanted to do this ever again!
MJ, I'm so sorry, but I can't see anything
with your hand in my--
[MJ] Sorry. Where are we gonna go?
-[Spider-Man] I don't know. Your house?
-No!
My dad will kill you.
What? You said your dad really liked me.
Yeah, well, not anymore.
-[gasping]
-[cell phone buzzes]
-[Spider-Man] Dude.
-[Ned] Dude.
-Dude!
Dude!
[Spider-Man gasps] I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
-[MJ] No, not really. Uh--
-[man] Yo, Peter!
[Talking Heads' "I Zimbra" playing]
[crowd clamouring]
We should go. We should go. Come on.
-You said you don't want to swing.
-You should just swing me.
-Okay. We can take the subway.
-Okay.
[screaming]
[Flash] No.
Look out!
That was so much worse. Okay. It's okay.
-[Spider-Man] Are you okay?
-[MJ] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, I'm so sorry.
[MJ whimpering]
[MJ] Okay.
Okay.
[Spider-Man] I'm sorry.
I just feel so dumb.
I didn't realise you were miserable.
No, it was really fun, right?
That's why they call it a fling.
-And we flung.
-It was fun. I could've been more fun.
-We'll hang out again.
-Like, when do you think?
[thud]
-I should see what that is.
-No, no, no.
-[Happy] It's what I do. Peter?
-He's always coming and going.
-[MJ] Peter?
-[Peter] Oh! Oh, no.
-[MJ] Oh, God.
-[Peter] Oh, no.
-I don't know what to do.
-[MJ] Peter?
-Oh--
-I didn't see anything.
[Peter] Um, this isn't what it looks like.
-No, no, no, May.
-Practise safe--
Oh, hey. You must be MJ!
-Yeah. Nice to meet you.
-[May] So nice to meet you.
-Wait, have you been crying?
-We broke up.
-Oh. Oh! Uh...
-[man outside] Hey, Spider-Man!
Thank you. I didn't know you broke up.
I thought you were in love, May.
Can we talk about this in the kitchen?
[Happy] I should probably leave.
I thought you guys were
such a handsome couple.
-It's really about boundaries.
-[intercom buzzing]
-Let me answer the door.
-Let's go in here.
-Is that the door?
-Hey. Is it true?
-[Happy] I was gonna go, but...
-[MJ] Not now.
[May] I didn't know you were
so awkward about sex, Peter.
-This has nothing to do with sex.
-[intercom buzzing]
[Happy] If you wanna go over it again.
I mean-- What's that sound?
[Peter] Uh...
-[woman outside] Hey, Spider-Man!
-[Peter] Oh, my God.
I mean, I'm happy to rehash it
if you want to.
[May] You take care of your side,
I'll take care of mine.
-[cell phones chiming]
-[May] What is up with this phone?
Will you get off your phones
for five minutes?
I just wanna talk to you
about your relationship, okay?
[MJ] Peter?
[helicopters whirring on TV]
-What?
-[May gasps]
-[May] Is that--?
-[Happy] Is that here?
Um...
[helicopters whirring]
[horns honking]
-[man 1] Yo, Peter Parker!
-[man 2] Yo, Peter!
Maybe it's not such a big deal.
[Jameson] Spider-Menace!
Governments around the world
launch investigations
into the murderer known as Spider-Man,
aka Peter Parker,
aka the web-headed war criminal
who, for years, has been terrorizing
the decent citizens of New York.
Well, now this city and the world see him
for what he truly is.
New details from last week's
devastating attack in London have emerged.
For more, we go now
to Joint Intelligence headquarters.
[reporter] Authorities,
just a short while ago, confirmed
that the deadly drones used
in the London attack
were designed by Stark Industries.
-[banging on door]
-[man 2] Federal agents! Open up!
Federal agents? You stay here.
[Cleary] Department of Damage Control.
We have a warrant
for the arrest of Peter Parker.
-You know the Fourth Amendment?
-[Cleary] Sure.
-Unreasonable search and seizure?
-Get in here, guys. Let's go.
[cameras clicking]
I didn't kill Quentin Beck.
The drones did, okay?
-The drones that are yours.
-No.
Nick Fury was there the entire time.
He can explain everything.
Nick Fury has been off-planet
for the last year.
-What?
-[MJ] Peter! Hey.
MJ! Uh-- They have nothing
to do with this, sir.
[both] Don't say anything
without a lawyer.
I want a lawyer.
-Ms Jones-Watson.
-Jones. I don't go by Watson.
-Ms Jones, why do you want a lawyer if--?
-If I have nothing to hide?
Exactly. Unless--
-I'm actually guilty of something?
-Uh-huh.
I'm very aware of your tactics
and my rights.
Just answer my questions.
I've seen your file.
You're a smart young woman
with a bright future ahead of her.
Why would you risk it all
by getting involved
with a vigilante like Peter Parker?
Washington Monument,
Venice Grand Canal,
Tower Bridge!
You know,
if I didn't know any better, Peter,
it's kind of like
your enemy is national landmarks.
[door opens]
[Cleary] So sorry to keep you waiting.
-Can we get Ned a snack?
-Absolutely.
-He's been waiting.
-I got you.
Dude, I'm so sorry about that.
-I'm not supposed to say anything to you.
-Not even a thing.
I just have one question.
When MJ told you Peter was Spider-Man--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-What's up?
-I knew way before MJ did.
-I was Spider-Man's "guy in the chair."
-I know about those.
-Dude, half my guys are guys in the chair.
-Exactly.
You would know.
I literally helped him find the Vulture.
-I didn't know that.
-I helped him hack a suit once
and helped him get to space.
So in Spider-Man's illegal vigilantism,
you were his main accomplice.
I would like to have
my words stricken from the record.
So if you did your job, I wouldn't have
to be on the boat saving people's lives.
I climbed up the side
of the Washington Monument.
Okay, now we're getting to some facts.
Tell me everything you know
about the Night Monkey.
Here's the funny thing about the law.
It's usually not open
to random self-interest interpretation.
Though you and I both know that hasn't
stopped people like you from trying.
So with all due respect,
and I mean that very insincerely,
unless you have
some real specific charges to throw at us,
legally, you can't hold us here.
Sounds like someone
who's been through the system before.
I've been arrested at a couple
of protests. I'm a real career criminal.
You should lawyer up.
Child endangerment's a nasty rap.
Excuse me?
A boy was entrusted to you,
and as his legal guardian,
essentially his mother,
you not only allowed him
to endanger himself, you encouraged it.
Who does that?
I wanna see Peter right now.
[Kiernan on TV] Stark Industries
was caught in the web
of the Spider-Man/Mysterio
controversy today,
when federal agents opened
an investigation
into missing Stark technology.
Agents wanna know
exactly what was taken...
-At least they used a good picture.
-What is happening?
[cane thuds]
[clears throat] That's great.
Thank you.
I have some good news, Peter.
I don't believe any of the charges
against you are gonna stick.
-Wait, seriously?
-Oh.
-I knew it.
-Nice.
Mr Murdock, thank you.
-Thank you.
-That's amazing.
-You're welcome.
-[Happy] Perfect.
-[Matt] However, Mr Hogan...
-Yes?
...the feds are investigating
that missing technology.
I understand your loyalty
to Mr Stark and his legacy,
but if you were involved--
-If I was?
-I advise securing a lawyer.
I need a lawyer because I'm--?
I thought he was--
You said there's no charge.
I could say under advisement of counsel,
I refuse to answer
the question respectfully
because the answer can incriminate me--
It's in Goodfellas.
What's the thing they say in Goodfellas?
I know that's what you think. Calm down.
Let's hear what he has to say. Matt?
You're gonna need a really good lawyer.
You may have dodged your legal troubles,
but things will get much worse.
There is still the court
of public opinion.
[man outside] Murderer! Mysterio forever!
How did you just do that?
I'm a really good lawyer.
We'll need a safer place to live.
[dramatic music playing]
[alarm blaring]
Oh. Aah!
How do we--? How do we--?
-[alarm stops]
-[computer] Alarm system deactivated.
It looks nice. And this is safe.
Welcome to the spiritual oasis.
You like Donkey Kong Jr.?
-[man 1] Hey, man, move!
-[man 2] Stop! Thief!
Move out of the way!
Hey, move, move!
Stop that guy!
Look out!
Stop!
[web thwips]
Oh, my God.
Hey!
Whoa, what are you doing?
You can't do this anymore.
-He's a thief.
-You're a child.
Show some respect.
He's not a child. He's 14 years old.
-I'm not--
-I had a job when I was 14.
-My son is 14. He's a moron.
-Guys, I am not 14 years old.
He's not equipped
to make these kinds of decisions.
It's true. Teenagers' brains
aren't fully developed yet.
-He can't even rent a car.
-[man 3] He doesn't need a car.
-He's been to space.
-Thank you.
How do you know they aren't
working together and in cahoots?
Me and this guy? I don't know this guy.
[woman 1] We don't know
what's in that bag.
We've been in cahoots the whole time.
-[man 4] Murderer!
-Ugh!
Mysterio forever!
-[newscast music plays on radio]
-Ugh!
[host on radio] Nicky, from Jersey City,
you're on the line.
[man on radio] Hi. I'm not saying
I don't want to honour the Avengers,
but, you know, not doing it this way.
Putting the Captain America shield
on the Statue of Liberty?
Nah, that will look ridiculous.
Leave the Statue of Liberty alone.
[Peter] Oh, Happy.
-[MJ] Did you send in your applications?
-I finished my MIT one.
-You?
-Same.
Can you imagine
if we both got in? And Ned?
Yeah, but we'd have to get scholarships
so we could actually go.
You got the scores and the grades.
You think I'm being too pragmatic.
No, no, no. Well...
Kind of. It's okay.
It's one of my favourite things about you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What are your other favourite things?
-Your relentless optimism.
-I'm a glass-half-full kind of gal.
-I really like how you're a people person.
-I love people.
-I love them so much.
-You like sports.
I think the Mets are gonna go
all the way this year.
-Really?
-What's that noise?
-[Happy snoring]
-[whispering] Oh.
It's-- It's Happy. Look.
Gave his room to May,
so he's sleeping down here.
[sighs]
I have a weird question. Um...
Does any part of you
feel relieved about this?
[in normal voice]
Ever since I got bit by that spider...
I've only had one week
where my life has felt normal.
Or kind of normal, I guess.
And...
that was when you found out.
Because then everyone that was in my life
that I wanted to know knew.
And it was perfect.
But now everybody knows and...
I am the most famous person
in the entire world.
And I'm still broke.
I'm...
excited to see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Me too.
[Happy] Wrap it up.
You both like each other.
We get it. Hang up.
There's no new ground being broken.
I need my eight hours.
-Have you been listening this whole time?
-Hi, Happy.
Uh, not by choice.
-MJ says hi.
-Hello.
It's back to school, folks.
And in their infinite wisdom,
Mayor Dingus and the city clown-cil
are welcoming back the town's
most notorious costumed killer--
Peter Parker.
Go get them, tiger!
Or should I say "spider"?
[reporter 1] The crowd has continued
to grow here all morning long
at the Midtown School of Science...
[reporter 2] The crowd seems evenly
divided between supporters of Spider-Man
and protestors.
[man 1] MJ!
MJ! MJ! We love you!
MJ, are you gonna have his spider-babies?
Back up. Back up. Back up!
[man 1]
MJ, you know he's a murderer, right?
[boy] Peter, do a TikTok with me.
[man 2] Mysterio forever!
[man 3] Do a flip!
-Hey, let's see you and MJ kiss!
-[Ned] Back off.
Who are you?
-Ned Leeds. Spider-Man's best friend.
-I'm Peter Parker's best friend.
You come at my boy,
you come at Flash Thompson.
If you wanna read
about our inspiring friendship,
you can in my new book, Flashpoint.
One spider, two hearts,
a million crazy-ass memories.
Check it out.
-[metal detector whirrs]
-[cell phone chiming]
-Go.
-No, I gotta wait--
-[guard] No. Go.
-I'll see you inside, okay?
Keep watching Midtown News all year
as we bring you up-close
and personal coverage
of Peter fighting his biggest battle yet:
College admissions.
Peter,
we would love to welcome you
back to Midtown High,
where we shape heroes.
-Uh-huh.
-Or murderers.
-Stop it.
-Huh?
-It's an honour to serve you, sir.
-It's not.
Mysterio was right.
-Stop. That's all.
-Mysterio was right.
Some students put this together for you.
-No, you did that.
-[Harrington] I helped a little bit.
[Wilson] And I tried to stop you
so many times, but you powered through.
-He did all of that.
-Did a great job.
I hope you have time to check it out.
Feel free to walk
or swing through the hallway.
Or crawl on the ceiling
to avoid everybody.
-We all know you can do it.
-I'm just gonna...
-I know what you did.
-Stop. You're embarrassing yourself.
He's a conspiracy theorist.
[dramatic music playing]
[cameras clicking]
We were lab partners. Did you know that?
[Wilson] Climb it!
Climb it! Climb it! Climb it!
[class continues chanting]
[chanting stops]
Look at that sticky bastard go.
[female student] Freak!
[Flash] I'm where he gets
all his best ideas.
That's why he calls me his Spidey mentor.
Peter! Good to see you, bud!
I'll see you later!
[clamouring]
Oh, my God, he's so cute!
[Betty] What's it like
being Spider-Man's teacher?
[Harrington] Well, Peter's always been
more than a student to me.
He's been more like a son.
Who's also my little brother.
[Betty] So, what do you think about
these crazy Mysterio conspiracy theories
that are spreading online?
There's a conspiracy theory that
Justin Timberlake was in NSYNC
at one time.
And then you look it up,
and, oh, he was in NSYNC.
My ex-wife, for example,
she's been spending a lot of time online.
And, you know,
the Internet is a wild place
that really beckons people like her
who are a little lost
and kind of have forgotten
where they came from and who they are
and that they love someone very much.
Sometimes you just forget these things
and you end up in a subreddit,
believing in Mysterio.
Sorry, what was your question?
[Betty] So you never noticed he had
extraordinary athletic abilities?
I mean, it's a science school,
so two push-ups is
extraordinary athletic abilities.
In your book, you revealed
that the name "Spider-Man" was your idea.
Were there any others that you tossed
around before settling on "Spider-Man"?
Yeah, uh, there were a few.
You know, "Arachnokid." "The Bitten."
When I think about it, there were times
that he was sticking to the wall,
or he had this stuff coming out
of his wrist.
But I didn't really
think much of it. I just...
I've been doing this a long time.
It's just a lot of kids.
I noticed that in your book
I'm not mentioned once.
No. No, I'm pretty sure you are. Uh...
I mean, you're...
Whoa, there are pictures in this?
If that spider had bitten me,
we'd be talking about
a different Spider-Man right now.
I think I would have maybe had
a different style costume.
Maybe something with flared legs, maybe.
As sexy as possible.
So, what is an appropriate text to send
to an ex-girlfriend
in the middle of the night?
You look great, by the way.
Thank you. You look as beautiful as ever.
[clears throat]
[Betty] What do you say
to the people who claim
that you're not really friends
with Peter Parker?
You know, it hurts.
Because...
You know, I...
Tell me:
If the spider that gave you
your powers were here right now,
what would you say?
Would you say, "Thanks"?
Or, "Thanks for nothing"?
I would say "Thanks."
"For nothing"?
You can catch the rest
of my exclusive interview
with Peter Parker today at lunch,
only on MNN.
Up next, Lady Liberty is getting
a makeover,
and some of Midtown High's
very own artists share
their ideas of what she should look like.
We'll be right back
after this important message
from Principal Morita
about cafeteria safety.
[Peter] Can we just stay up here all day?
-It is so crazy down there.
-[MJ] This one's good.
"Some suggest that Parker's powers
include the male spider's ability
to hypnotise females,
which he used to seduce Jones-Watson
into his cult of personality."
Stop. Stop.
Yes, my Spider-Lord.
[Ned] Finally, some privacy.
It is so crazy down there.
So I was thinking...
when we get into MIT,
we should live together.
-Yeah, for sure.
-[MJ] Yeah, I'd love that.
-This is gonna be us.
-Yes. Minus the Frisbee and the smiling.
[Peter] MIT's obviously the dream,
but if we match up our backup schools,
then either way, we'll be in Boston.
New school, new town.
I can Spider-Man there.
-They have crime in Boston, right?
-Yes.
-Wicked crime.
-[Peter] It'll be like a fresh start.
What's up?
I don't know.
I just feel like, if you don't--
If you expect disappointment,
then you can never really
get disappointed.
Come on.
Be a fresh start.
And we'll all be together.
Yeah. No, you're right. Fresh start.
[Peter] Yeah.
Fresh start.
[whimsical music playing]
First one's here!
It's okay. It's a backup.
Peter.
No?
Last one.
MIT?!
Uh-- Okay.
[bell jingles]
-Okay.
-Whew.
-[MJ] Ready?
-[man] Jones,
I told you to take down
the Halloween decorations.
-Actually, that was Sasha, so--
-[man] Enough attitude. Just do it.
On it.
Feel like I'm gonna puke.
Don't, because he will
just make me clean it.
This is our only shot.
It's here or nowhere.
-Hey. Come on.
-Okay. You ready?
-[both] Yeah.
-[MJ] Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
[pensive music playing]
No.
No. You?
"In light of recent controversy,
we are unable to consider
your application at this time."
This is so not fair.
I mean, this is so not fair.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You guys definitely didn't do
anything wrong.
Expect disappointment
and you will never get disappointed.
[bell jingles]
♪ No sleep till ♪
♪ Bom, bom, tsk, bom, bom ♪
♪ Boston! ♪
You didn't get in?
Yeah, because we're actually friends
with Spider-Man.
Uh, yeah. I better get going.
There's a mixer for new admissions and--
-[bell jingles]
-Sorry, guys.
[man] Jones, what are you doing?
Get back to work.
[MJ] Yeah, I'm coming.
Know what?
I wouldn't change a thing I did.
[Ned] Me neither.
Although I do need
to show this letter to my parents.
[melancholy music playing]
[pensive music playing]
[clears throat]
Um, hi.
Hi?
I'm, uh--
[Wong] The most famous person
in the world. I know.
Wong. Try not to slip.
We don't have liability insurance.
-Is all this for a holiday party?
-No.
One of the rotunda gateways
connects to Siberia.
-A blizzard blasted through.
-[air whooshes]
Because someone forgot
to cast a monthly maintenance spell
to keep the seals tight.
That's right, he did, because he forgot
I now have higher duties.
Higher duties?
The Sorcerer Supreme has higher duties.
Wait, I thought
you were the Sorcerer Supreme.
No, he got it on a technicality
'cause I blipped for five years.
-Oh. Congratulations.
-If I'd been here, then--
You'd burn the place down.
You two, no one said stop shovelling.
So, Peter, to what do I owe the pleasure?
Right. Um, I'm really sorry
to bother you, sir.
Please. We saved half
the universe together.
-Think we're beyond you calling me "sir."
-Okay, uh, Stephen.
That feels weird, but I'll allow it.
Uh...
When, um...
When Mysterio revealed my identity,
my entire life got screwed up,
and I was wondering--
I don't know if this would actually work,
but I was wondering if...
maybe you could go back in time
and make it so he never did?
Peter, we tampered
with the stability of space-time
to resurrect countless lives.
You wanna do it again now
just 'cause yours got messy?
It's not about me.
This is really hurting a lot of people.
My aunt May, Happy,
my best friend, my girlfriend,
their futures are ruined
just because they know me,
and they've done nothing wrong.
I am so sorry...
but even if I wanted to...
I don't have the Time Stone anymore.
That's right.
I'm really sorry if I wasted your time.
-You didn't.
-[Peter] Just forget about it.
[Wong] Oh, he will.
He's very good at forgetting things.
Wong, you've actually generated
a good idea.
What?
The Runes of Kof-Kol.
The Runes of Kof-Kol?
It's just a standard spell of forgetting.
Won't turn back time, but people will
forget you were ever Spider-Man.
-Seriously?
-No, not seriously.
That spell travels the dark borders
between known and unknown reality.
It's too dangerous.
We've used it for a lot less.
Do you remember
the full-moon party at Kamar-Taj?
-No.
-Exactly.
[dramatic music playing]
Come on, Wong.
Hasn't he been through enough?
Just leave me out of this.
Fine.
So, what is this place?
The Sanctum's built at the intersection
of cosmic energy currents.
We weren't the first to seek them out.
Some of these walls
are thousands of years old.
And they shot an episode
of The Equalizer here in the '80s.
Well, I, um...
really appreciate you
doing this for me, sir.
[Strange] Don't mention it.
And don't call me "sir."
Right. Sorry.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Nice knowing you, Spider-Man.
Wait, excuse me?
The entire world's about to forget
that Peter Parker is Spider-Man.
-Including me.
-Everyone?
-Uh, can't some people still know?
-That's not how the spell works.
And it's very difficult and dangerous
to change it mid-casting.
So my girlfriend's gonna
forget everything?
Is she even gonna be my girlfriend?
Was she your girlfriend
just 'cause you were Spider-Man?
-I don't know. I really hope not.
-All right, fine.
Everyone's gonna forget
you're Spider-Man except your girlfriend.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God, Ned. Ned.
What is a Ned?
He's my best friend,
so it's important to me that Ned knows.
Okay, let's not change
the parameters of this spell any more
-while I'm casting it.
-Okay, I'm done.
I swear, I'm done. I'm done.
-Ah, but my aunt May should really know.
-Peter, stop tampering with the spell.
When she found out I was Spider-Man,
it was really messy.
I don't think
I could go through that again.
-So my aunt May?
-Yes.
Oh. Thank you. Happy?
No, I'm annoyed.
No, it's a nickname. Harold "Happy" Hogan.
He used to work with Tony Stark,
but then he was...
Would you just stop talking?
[yells]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
Basically, everyone that knew
I was Spider-Man before should still know!
[yells]
[yelling]
-Did it work?
-No.
You changed my spell six times.
-Five times.
-You changed my spell.
You don't do that! I told you.
And that is why.
That spell was out of control.
If I hadn't shut it down,
something catastrophic
could have happened.
-Stephen, listen, I am so--
-Call me "sir."
Sorry, sir.
[sighs] After everything
we've been through,
somehow I always forget you're just a kid.
Look, Parker, the problem is not Mysterio.
It's you trying
to live two different lives.
And the longer you do that,
the more dangerous it becomes.
Believe me.
I'm so sorry about you
and your friends not getting into college,
but if they rejected you and you tried
to convince them to reconsider,
there's nothing else you can do.
When you say "convince them,"
-you mean, I could have called them?
-Yeah.
I could do that?
You haven't called the...?
I got their letter. I assumed that was--
I'm sorry.
Are you telling me
that you didn't even think
to plead your case with them first
before you asked me
to brainwash the entire world?
When you put it like that...
Come on, pick up, pick up.
Dude, what? I'm busy.
Flash, where's the MIT mixer?
-Why?
-Because I need to talk to someone.
I'm trying to get Ned and MJ
a second chance at getting in.
What's in it for me?
I'm risking a lot just talking to you.
Okay, I will, um...
pick you up and swing you
to school for one week?
For a month.
-For a week.
-Two weeks.
-Flash, please. Help me.
-You know what I want.
Okay, I'll tell everyone
you're my best friend.
-Flash, please, help me.
-Cool.
There's the assistant vice chancellor.
You can plead your case with her.
-Okay, perfect. Where is she?
-She left.
-To go where?
-To the airport.
[dramatic music playing]
-[suit AI] Stark network unavailable.
-[Spider-Man groans]
Facial recognition unavailable.
[helicopter whirring]
[sighs]
Hi.
Yeah, I can see you.
[horns honking]
-[barking]
-Oh, my God!
-[toddler] That's Peter Parker.
-Mom.
-Mom, look.
-[toddler] Mommy.
[girl] No, it's Peter Parker.
[man] Hey!
Okay.
Yeah.
Hi. I'm Peter Parker.
-You do know you're in the street, right?
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
I really needed to talk to you and I know
you're on your way to the airport.
MJ Watson and Ned Leeds are
the two smartest people I've ever met,
and I'm the dumbest person
because I let them help me,
but if I didn't, millions would've died,
so please don't let MIT be dumb like me.
MIT is dumb?
No, I'm saying, don't let MIT be dumb.
I mean, like the dumber version of me
that wouldn't have let them help.
-You didn't rehearse that, did you, Peter?
-[horn honks]
Basically, what I'm trying to--
[pensive music playing]
Why are you running?
[crowd screaming]
Oh, my God.
Uh, ma'am, you should get out of the car.
Everybody get off the bridge!
The door's locked.
Door's-- Hey!
[menacing music playing]
Hello, Peter.
[Spider-Man] Hi? Do we--? Do I know you?
What have you done with my machine?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What machine?
The power of the sun
in the palm of my hand.
It's gone.
Listen, if you stop smashing cars,
we can work together
and I can help you find your machine.
You want to play games?
[woman 1 screams]
Catch!
[dramatic music playing]
[yells]
[Spider-Man] It's okay.
You're safe. Get out of here.
You think
your fancy new suit's gonna save you?
[woman 2 screams]
Should've killed your little girlfriend
when I had the chance.
[Spider-Man] What did you just say?
Looks like we got competition.
[assistant vice chancellor] Peter! Help!
[Spider-Man] Don't worry, ma'am!
I'm coming!
[assistant vice chancellor] Peter! [gasps]
[whimpers]
[Spider-Man] Ma'am, just stay calm.
Just take a deep breath.
-Are you okay?
-No!
[Spider-Man] I promise,
I've got this all under control.
-Whoa!
-[suit AI] Suit compromised.
Nanotechnology.
Ah, you've outdone yourself, Peter.
I underestimated you.
But now you die.
[groaning]
You're not Peter Parker.
[grunts] I am so confused right now.
What's happening?
[suit AI] New device detected.
Pairing new device.
You don't listen to him. You listen to me.
[chuckles]
Hey.
[screams]
Whoa! [laughs]
Hey. Hey!
Listen to me.
No, not him. Me!
Ma'am, you okay?
-You can still make your flight.
-[assistant vice chancellor] Peter.
You're a hero.
No. Well, I'm--
No, I'm--
I'm gonna talk to Admissions
about your friends.
And I'm gonna talk to them about you.
But, ma'am, this isn't about me.
I am going to talk to them
about your friends and you.
-Okay?
-Really?
And if you keep your noses clean,
maybe you'll have a fair shot.
Here. Get out of the way.
Let me get that man.
Hey. You. I see you. Come here!
That was not okay.
Unbelievable.
[Peter] Who are--?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Until you stop trying to kill me,
I'm in control, buddy,
of this whole tentacle situation
you got going on here, okay?
Now, who are you? What is going--?
[metal clinking]
[whirrs]
No.
[laughing]
Osborn?
-Doctor--?
-[roaring]
[Peter gasping]
[screams]
Be careful what you wish for, Parker.
Let me out of here!
Can you please explain to me
what is going on?
That little spell that you botched
where you wanted everyone
to forget that Peter Parker's Spider-Man,
it started pulling in everyone
who knows Peter Parker's Spider-Man
from every universe into this one.
-From every universe?
-Who are you? And where am I?
I think it's better we don't engage
with them because, frankly,
the multiverse is a concept
about which we know frighteningly little.
The multiverse is real?
[sighs] This shouldn't be possible.
-I thought you stopped the spell.
-No, I contained it.
It would appear
a few of them squeaked through.
After you left,
I detected an otherworldly presence.
I pursued it into the sewers,
where I found that...
slimy, green son of a gun.
Spell? As in magic?
What is this, a birthday party?
Who is this clown? What is this madness?
Watch this. Do you know
a Peter Parker who's Spider-Man?
-Yes.
-Is that him?
-No.
-See?
Here's what we gotta do.
I don't know how many visitors we've got--
I saw another one on the bridge.
He was like a flying green elf.
He sounds jolly. Start with him.
I need you to capture them,
bring them here while I figure out
how to get them back
before they destroy the fabric of reality,
or worse, Wong finds out.
Uh, Doctor Strange?
[Strange] What?
My friends and I just got
a second chance to get into MIT,
and if the school sees me
fighting these crazy monsters--
-Hey, watch your mouth.
-I'm sorry, but--
Are you seriously
still talking about college?
Whoa-- [grunts]
-Hey, what did you just do?
-This.
[Peter] Hey, you can't just-- Oh!
[Peter groans]
-How did you do that?
-Lots of birthday parties.
[thumping]
Whoa!
Hey.
Whoa.
One shot, send them here, move on.
You're welcome.
-Get to work.
-Sir?
[sighs] Now what?
This is my mess,
and I swear that I'll fix it,
but I'm gonna need help.
Whoa.
I can't believe
I'm in the Sanctum Sanctorum.
Neither can I.
So how did you know
you were a man of magic?
Because my nana says
that we have it in our family,
-and I get these tinglings in my hands--
-Talk to your physician.
-[MJ] Peter.
-[Peter] Hey.
-Hey. Hey.
-[MJ] Hey. Hey.
Sorry for dragging you into this.
-Help me find these guys.
-You don't have to apologise, okay?
You got us
a second shot at MIT. It's fine.
So how did the bad guys get here?
[Strange] We screwed up a spell
trying to get you into college.
-You did it with magic?
-I thought it was the MIT lady you saved.
Uh, no, that was after.
Let's just focus on the good news, okay?
No, let's just focus on the bad news.
As of now, you have detected
zero multiversal trespassers,
so get on your phones,
scour the Internet, and...
Scooby-Doo this shit.
[MJ chuckles]
You're telling us what to do, even though
it was your spell that got screwed up,
meaning that all this is your mess.
I know a couple of magic words myself,
starting with the word "please."
Please Scooby-Doo this shit.
You can work in the undercroft.
The undercroft?
[dryer rumbling]
Badass.
[dryer alarm buzzes]
Oh...
-About this whole spell thing--
-It's totally okay.
-Really?
-Yeah. I mean, I get it.
You were just trying
to fix things, and so...
Maybe just run it by us next time,
you know?
That way, when you're thinking,
"I'm about to do something
that could break the universe,"
we could, like, help you
workshop something or...
brainstorm ideas.
Deal.
Ned?
Oh, dude, I don't care.
It's seriously not a big deal. Um--
Oh!
A torture rack.
[clangs]
That is a Pilates machine.
-That is--
-The crypt.
Okay, so we get the rest of the guys,
you zap them,
Doctor Magic will send them back,
and when we get into MIT,
round of stale doughnuts, my treat.
Let's catch some multiverse men.
Hey! Who the hell are these two?
-My friends. This is MJ. And this is Ned.
-Hey.
Hello.
-Uh, sorry, what was your name again?
-Dr Otto Octavius.
Seriously, what's your actual name?
Oh, is that a dinosaur?
[Bobby Pickett's "Monster Mash" playing]
♪ I was working in the lab, late one night
When my eyes beheld an eerie sight ♪
♪ For my monster from his slab
Began to rise ♪
♪ And suddenly to my surprise ♪
-♪ He did the mash ♪
-♪ He did the monster mash ♪
-♪ The monster mash ♪
-♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
-♪ He did the mash ♪
-♪ It caught on in a flash ♪
-♪ He did the monster mash ♪
♪ From my laboratory in the castle east ♪
♪ To the master bedroom
Where the vampires feast ♪
♪ The ghouls all came
From their humble abodes ♪
♪ To get a jolt from my electrodes ♪
-♪ They did the mash ♪
-♪ They did the monster mash ♪
-♪ The monster mash ♪
-♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪♪
What?
[whispers] What are you looking at?
[May over phone] If the paint
won't come off, I'll get it out.
No, no, no, May.
We gotta find these guys first.
Finish your mission and then come by.
We're having a canned-food drive.
-[Peter] That could work.
-[Ned] I got one!
-I gotta go.
-Okay.
I mean, you can take
the guy out of the chair,
but you can't take
the chair out of the guy.
-What'd you find?
-There's a...
A disturbance near a military
research facility outside of the city,
and witnesses say that they saw
a monster flying through the air.
It's gotta be the guy
I saw on the bridge.
[Doc Ock] That's impossible.
You know him, don't you?
On the bridge, you said his name.
Norman Osborn.
Brilliant scientist. Military research.
But he was greedy, misguided.
-[Peter] What happened to him?
-We tire of your questions, boy!
Okay. Um...
-I gotta go. Where am I going?
-It can't be him.
Why?
Because Norman Osborn died years ago.
So either we saw someone else...
or you're flying out
into the darkness to fight a ghost.
[ominous music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Keep an eye out on the trees.
We don't know where this guy is.
I genuinely don't know
how you do this without throwing up.
[music stops]
-[whispering] Did you see that?
-[MJ over comm] Um...
-No.
-[Ned over comm] It's really dark.
Okay, okay, okay.
[Ned] What's happening?
[MJ] Peter, what is it?
Are you getting the tingle thing?
Is the tingle happening?
Is your tingle tingling?
[eerie music playing]
-Are you guys seeing this?
-[MJ] Yeah.
-[Ned] Osborn?
-No. He was green. This guy's blue.
[in normal voice] Uh, you wouldn't happen
to be from another universe, would you?
[MJ] What's he doing?
-I don't know. Looks like he's charging.
-I don't like this. Just web him.
[both exclaim]
Go left! Left, dude, left!
Left! Go! Left! Yes!
What are you talking about? Right.
Go to the right! Right! Right!
-He means right. Don't listen to him.
-[Spider-Man] This is not helping!
Oh, no, no, no.
What happened? Peter? Peter.
[groans]
[gasping]
[Spider-Man] Whoa!
Peter, it's me, Flint Marko. You remember?
-Uh, I'm Peter, but I'm not your Peter.
-What do you mean, you're not my Peter?
-What the hell is going on?
-I'll explain, but first, can you help me?
-Okay.
-You try to surround him,
and I'll pull the plug.
All right, let's go!
[Sandman] I can't hold him much longer.
[Spider-Man] I got it, I got it!
[grunting]
Different Peter. Weird.
-Thanks. Sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
I got my body back.
[Peter] Hey. Um...
This is gonna sound really crazy,
but, uh, this isn't your universe.
-Another universe?
-Uh-huh.
-What?
-That's what I was feeling.
The power, it's different.
I like it.
-Easy, buddy.
-It's actually my fault that you're here.
Like, the universe or the woods?
I hate the woods.
I meant the universe, sir.
So, what, y'all just gonna stand here
and act like I ain't butt-ass naked?
-I am.
-Uh, no, no. Uh--
I, uh...
[gasping]
What was that?
What did you just do to him?
-No. It's okay.
-Did you kill him?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I can explain everything. Trust me.
-Please, just trust me.
-I don't trust you. I don't know you.
Ugh. What is this?
You picked the wrong side.
[Lizard laughing]
Connors?
Wait. You know this creature?
[Electro] No, no, no.
Not a creature. A man.
Whoa. The same universes.
Dr Curt Connors. He was a scientist
at Oscorp when I worked there.
A brilliant scientist.
Until he turned himself into a lizard.
Then he tried to turn
the whole city into lizards.
-It was crazy.
-It wasn't crazy, Max.
It was the next step in human evolution.
-The dinosaur can talk. Right.
-Lizard.
What happened to you?
Last I recall, you had bad teeth,
glasses and a comb-over.
Did you get a makeover?
You know I can give you a real makeover.
Let me guess, into a lizard?
-Exactly.
-Would you two just shut up?
-Where are we?
-It's complicated.
-A wizard's dungeon.
-Wizard's dungeon?
There's no real way to sugar-coat that.
It's literally the dungeon of a wizard.
You can keep your magic.
I want a taste of that energy I just felt.
[cell phone buzzes]
-Oh, Peter, hey.
-Did those guys come through yet?
There should be an electric guy
and a sand guy.
Yeah, they're all here and locked up.
Perfect. I'm gonna just stay here
and try and fix some of this damage
so they don't blame it on me again.
-Okay.
-But, hey, I, uh...
I couldn't do any of this without you,
so thank you.
Of course.
Hey, ask him
if this is like a tree monster
or like a scientist
that turned into a tree.
[Electro] It's just a tree, man.
Just a tree.
[eerie music playing]
[Green Goblin]
Coward. We have a new world to conquer.
You make me sick.
Leave me alone, please.
Hiding in the shadows.
Hiding from who you truly are.
-No.
-You can't escape yourself.
[Green Goblin laughing maniacally]
[cell phone buzzing]
-Hey, May.
-[May over phone] Hey, Peter. I'm at work,
and, um, one of the guys
you're looking for just walked in.
[suspenseful music playing]
May? Where's May? Thank you.
May.
Ah. Hey, here he is.
Norman, this is my nephew.
Norman Osborn? I thought that you were--
I saw Spider-Man in an ad for this place.
And I thought he could help me.
But you're not him.
Wait, so you want Spider-Man's help?
He just wandered in.
I didn't know where else to go.
Someone's living in my house.
Oscorp doesn't exist.
My son...
[melancholy music playing]
Sometimes I'm not myself.
-I'm... someone else.
-Mm-hm.
And every time he's in control,
I can't remember.
-Who's in control?
-And now I'm here--
-[May] Who's in control?
-I don't know what's going on.
-Okay, it's okay.
-And I don't-- Doesn't make sense.
He's lost.
And I don't mean just in the cosmos.
I mean in his mind.
Are they all like this?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
They all have their own mental
or physical issues.
Oh, well, he needs help,
and maybe they all do.
Wait, you don't mean--?
No, May, this isn't my problem.
Peter, not your problem?
Hmm?
May, their chance of getting help is
way better back where they came from.
Sending them home, that's the best thing
that we can do for them.
For them? Or for yourself?
Look around you. This is what we do.
-We help people.
-This is what's best for them.
Trust me.
[newscast music playing]
I'm now joined by supervisor Walter Burke,
who was at the scene
of tonight's disturbance.
Mr Burke, you're saying
you saw Spider-Man, with your own eyes,
destroying multiple power lines?
Uh... Yes. Yes, sir, he did.
There you have it, folks.
Firsthand, from an unimpeachable witness,
the Teen Terror attacking
our electrical grid.
-Yeah, he was talking to the Dirt Man.
-Beg your pardon?
Yeah, he was talking to the Dirt Man
before they worked together
to make the Power Monster disappear
with what appeared to be a sparkle web.
All right. Yep. Thank you very much.
Well, that, uh... [clears throat]
We'll have to circle back
and confirm this, folks.
I'll talk to my producer to see if we can
find out what's in Mr Burke's thermos.
But the fact remains,
Spider-Man is a menace.
We'll be right back after a brief word
from Daily Bugle Supplements.
The only other daily fix you need.
[man] And we're out.
What?
I got eyes on him.
-He's with his aunt and some guy.
-You sure?
-They're just leaving the shelter.
-Okay. Don't lose him.
Thanks, May. Hope to see you again.
Hey. He trusts you. So do I.
Thanks for cleaning my suit.
See you later.
-Guys, this is Mr Osborn.
-Hey, it's "doctor."
Sorry. Dr Osborn, these are my friends.
This is Ned and MJ.
-Mary Jane?
-It's Michelle Jones, actually.
Fascinating.
Do you think there are other Ned Leedses?
[sombre music playing]
Octavius?
Osborn?
What happened to you?
What happened to--?
-You're the walking corpse.
-What do you mean?
You died, Norman.
Years ago.
You're insane.
God, I love it here.
What are you talking about?
He's standing right there.
-He's not--
-[Sandman] Dead.
They both died, fighting Spider-Man.
It was all over the news.
Green Goblin, impaled
by the glider you flew around on.
And a couple of years later, you, Doc Ock,
-drowned in the river with your machine.
-Nonsense.
Spider-Man was trying to stop
my fusion reactor, so I stopped him.
I had him by the throat, and then I...
And then I was here.
[Electro] Ah, please.
Let me tell you something.
I was whupping Spider-Man's ass.
He'll tell you.
And then he caused an overload.
I was stuck in the grid, absorbing data.
I was about to turn
into pure energy, and then...
And then, uh...
And then-- Oh, shit.
-I was about to die.
-Max, do you know? Do I die?
-Oh, great. You caught another one.
-No, wait, Strange.
He's not dangerous.
It's okay. Um...
What is that?
[Strange] It's an ancient relic.
The Macchina di Kadavus.
I've trapped your corrupted spell inside,
and once I finish the proper ritual,
it'll reverse the spell and send
these guys back to their universes.
And then what? We perish?
No. No, thanks. I'll pass on that.
Let me out of here. Peter!
Strange, we can't send them back. Not yet.
Why?
-Well, some of these guys are gonna die.
-[Strange] Parker.
It's their fate.
Come on, have a heart.
In the grand calculus of the multiverse,
their sacrifice means infinitely more
than their lives.
I'm sorry, kid.
If they die, they die.
[suspenseful music playing]
Peter!
Don't.
-What are you doing?
-Peter, you gotta go. Go!
-Okay.
-Get out of here.
This is why I never had kids.
-Give me the box.
-No.
Whoa!
[yells]
Oh, my God, I'm dead.
You're not dead, you've just been
separated from your physical form.
My physical-- What?
How are you doing that?
-I have no idea.
-You should not be able to do that.
This feels amazing.
One of the coolest things
that's happened to me,
but don't ever do that again.
[dramatic music playing]
Hey! Get off of me!
[grunting]
[over speakers] ♪ ...la, la, la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly ♪
♪ Fa, la, la, la, la, la, la-- ♪
[yells]
[sighs]
What is this place?
The Mirror Dimension,
where I'm in control.
[train horn blares]
Strange, stop!
Can we just talk about this?
Parker, don't you realise
that in the multiverse,
there are an infinite number of people
who know Peter Parker is Spider-Man?
And if that spell gets loose,
they're all coming here.
[Spider-Man] I know, I get it,
but we can't just send them home to die.
It's their fate.
You can't change that any more
than you could change who they are.
What if we could?
What if we could change their fate?
Whoa. What are you doing?
I'm not giving you the-- Whoa!
[yells]
[yelling]
Give me that back!
Wait a minute.
Is that an Archimedean Spiral?
The dimension is just geometry?
You're great at geometry.
You can do geometry.
Square the radius. Divide by pi.
-Plot points along the curve.
-[Strange] It's over, Parker.
I'll come pick you up when it's done.
Hey, Strange.
You know what's cooler than magic?
[Dr Strange groans]
-Math.
-Don't do this.
-Ow.
-I'm sorry, sir, but...
I have to try.
-What happened?
-I had a fight with Strange and I won.
-[Ned] What?
-I stole his ring thing.
Whoa.
I was swinging, and then I went
through this massive mirror thing,
-and then I was back--
-Where is he?
He's trapped,
but I'm not sure for how long.
You could have left us to die.
Why didn't you?
'Cause that's not who he is.
I think I can help you guys.
If I can fix what happened to you,
then when you go back,
things will be different,
and you might not die fighting Spider-Man.
-[Electro] What do you mean?
-Our technology is advanced--
I can help you. You know,
I'm something of a scientist myself.
Octavius knows what I can do.
Fix? You mean like a dog?
I refuse.
I can't promise you guys anything,
but at least this way,
you get to go home and have a chance.
A second chance.
Isn't that worth trying?
Trust me, Peter,
when you try to fix people,
there are always consequences.
You don't have to come.
I also didn't know that you could talk.
But if you stay here...
[sighs] you'll have to deal
with the wizard.
Ah. So we go along or die.
Not much of a choice, is it?
I just wanna go home.
I, myself, don't wanna be killed,
especially by a guy dressed
like Dungeons &amp; Dragons,
so, what's your plan?
I have it all under control.
[whispering]
What are we gonna do about this thing?
Uh, we need to find
somewhere safe for it, right?
-[in normal voice] You gotta take it.
-Wait, what?
If something bad happens,
you just push this and then it's over.
We're not gonna leave you.
You can't. It's dangerous.
-You have done enough.
-We're in this together.
I know we're in this together, Ned,
but I can't do this if you're in danger.
Okay? So for me, MJ,
please just take this.
-Please.
-Fine.
-[Peter] Thank you.
-But, Peter,
if I don't hear from you,
I'm pressing the button.
-Sure.
-Okay. And I will do it.
Yeah, we all believe you, Michelle.
No way that's his girlfriend. No way.
-She'll do it.
-Absolutely, she will.
-Okay. See you later.
-Be safe.
-[Peter] You too.
-Okay.
[both] Whoa.
Okay.
-Be careful, okay?
-Yeah. You too.
[dramatic music playing]
So, uh...
who's coming with me?
Well, I'm in.
But if this goes sideways...
I'm gonna fry you from the inside out.
My client has nothing to do
with the missing technology.
He's a law-abiding citizen.
He has nothing to hide.
That's right.
[cell phone buzzing]
[dramatic music playing]
-Where's Connors?
-[May] He wants to stay in the truck.
-[Peter] Okay.
-[man] Mr Hogan, is something wrong?
[whispers] Happy.
Stop sweating.
How do you do that?
-Yeah?
-I feel bad using Happy's place like this.
No, no, no. He'll get over it.
[reporter on TV] New Yorkers oppose
the Statue of Liberty renovation...
Oh, sorry.
So this is your plan, Peter? Hmm?
No lab, no facilities?
Just performing miracles
in a condominium? Hmm?
What, you gonna cook us some cures
and some frozen burritos in a microwave?
-I could go for a burrito.
-He's gonna kill us all.
Well, let's hope not.
-You're up first, Doc.
-What?
Hey, I told you, I don't need fixing.
I don't need fixing!
Especially by a teenager using scraps
from a bachelor's junk drawer.
Nah, nah, nah.
He got something back there.
I can feel it. That weird energy.
-What the hell is that?
-It's a fabricator.
It can analyse, design,
construct basically anything.
I thought that was
the tanning bed Happy broke.
Look at that.
He's gonna kill us all.
Oh!
What's going on there?
[Peter] So the chip in the back of Doc's
neck was designed to protect his brain
from the AI system that's controlling
these tentacles, but if you look here...
the chip is fried.
So rather than him being
in control of the tentacles,
the tentacles are now in control of him.
Which, I guess, explains why
he is so miserable all the time.
But, if you look here,
if I can introduce self--
Self-healing composite circuitry.
Exactly. So, theoretically,
I mean, if this were to work,
he would go back to the way he was.
Thirsty?
Well, yes, I am thirsty.
Fresh water or salt?
You know, because you're an octopus.
What?
Fresh water it is.
Look at this place.
-And all the possibilities.
-What, this condo?
Yeah, yeah, the condo.
I love the whole open floor plan. No.
Nah, man, I'm talking about the world.
I kind of like who I am here.
And all that power back there...
I could be so much more.
So why'd you come along?
I have a daughter, and I want to see her.
But he's not gonna send anyone home
till he's finished
his little science project back there.
You trust him?
I don't trust anyone.
-How'd you end up like that, anyway?
-Oh.
The place where I worked at,
they were experimenting with electricity
created by living organisms, and then...
I fell into a vat of electric eels.
You're kidding.
I fell into a supercollider.
Damn.
Gotta be careful where you fall.
Remarkable.
The technology and you.
When all this is over,
if you need a job and you're willing
to commute to another universe...
It worked. That totally worked!
-I got it. I did it. Will you send him up?
-[May] Here we go.
-Sorry.
-[May] Hold on, Doc.
Oh, will these humiliations never cease?
You, keep your science-fair project
away from me!
It'll work. Have faith.
Says the reckless fool
who turned himself into a monster.
[Peter] Please stop moving your head.
-Hold still.
-Don't you dare. [grunting]
[groans] I swear, when I get out of this,
we're gonna rip you a new--
[powers down]
Doc?
-Dr Octav--
-[panting]
It's so quiet.
Those voices inside my head...
I'd almost forgotten.
[poignant music playing]
Otto.
Yes. Norman.
It's me.
Would you look at that?
I'm grateful, dear boy. Truly.
Yeah, you're welcome.
How can I help?
[Peter on voicemail]
This is Peter. Leave a message.
[beep plays on voicemail]
Yeah, Peter, this is Happy.
I accessed my doorbell camera.
Who are those guys, huh? Is that a cyborg?
You bring a cyborg
with robot legs into my house?
Was one of the guys made of mud?
What's going on? Call me.
[Octavius] How does it feel, Norman?
You're about to become whole again.
No more darker half.
Just you.
[Osborn] Just me.
[Peter] Okay. Um...
It just goes right here. This...
[device beeps]
That should be drawing power now.
I'll come back in a second to check on it,
but keep an eye on the lights.
When they're all green,
the electricity in your body's dissipated.
Well, not all of the electricity. You need
electricity for your brain to function.
Your nervous system is...
I'm not really sure
why I'm explaining electricity to you.
-Hmm. Yeah, can I ask you a question?
-Sure.
Are these your Legos?
[computer beeps]
Uh, I gotta go. I'll be back.
[sighs]
-Something feels off.
-[Sandman] What do you mean?
-I don't like this.
-Leave it alone.
The sooner you guys get through this,
the sooner we go home.
[device beeps]
[tyres screech]
-Well, where is he?
-He's inside.
And yet here we are, outside.
Did you not hear me say, "Don't lose him"?
I want incriminating footage
of Spider-Man.
I called Damage Control.
They're on their way.
And so it begins.
[Jameson]
Place is about to be swarming with cops.
[tense music playing]
[creaking in distance]
[both in distorted voices] Peter?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
May?
[in distorted voice] What is it, Peter?
[Sandman in distorted voice]
What's happening?
Why are you looking at me like that?
[pulse pounding]
[in normal voice] That's some neat trick,
that sense of yours.
-[in normal voice] Norman?
-Norman's on sabbatical, honey.
-[in normal voice] The hell?
-The Goblin.
"No more darker half"? Did you really
think that I'd let that happen?
That I'd let you take away my power
just because you're blind
-to what true power can bring you?
-You don't know me.
Don't I?
I saw how she trapped you,
fighting her holy moral mission.
We don't need you to save us.
We don't need to be fixed.
These are not curses.
[device beeps]
They're gifts.
-Norman, no.
-[Green Goblin] Quiet, lapdog.
-You don't know what you're talking about.
-I've watched you
from deep behind Norman's cowardly eyes.
Struggling to have everything you want
while the world tries to make you choose.
[device beeps]
Gods don't have to choose.
We take.
May, run.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
-What have you done?
-I liked you better before.
[yells]
Up here! He's up there.
It's the guy from the bridge.
[suspenseful music playing]
[roars]
Did you see that?
[yells]
No, you don't!
Strong enough to have it all.
Too weak to take it!
[cackles]
[groaning]
Now I got you.
I told you, there'd be consequences!
[choking]
Your weakness, Peter, is morality.
It's choking you. Can't you feel it?
[yells]
[growls]
It didn't work.
-[Peter coughs]
-Norman was right.
He got it from you,
that pathetic sickness.
You tried to fix me.
May, go.
Now I'm gonna fix you.
May, run, please.
-[May yells]
-[Peter] May!
Peter, Peter, Peter.
No good deed goes unpunished.
You can thank me later.
No!
[May coughing]
[groaning]
-May?
-[May] Peter.
[Peter] May, May, I'm here.
[Peter coughing]
[groans]
May.
May, I'm here.
-Are you okay? What happened?
-Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
[gasping]
It's okay. We're okay, right?
Yeah. Knocked on my ass.
-Yeah, me too.
-That's all.
[winces] I think I broke my ribs.
-This is all my fault, May.
-No.
I should have let Strange send them back.
You did the right thing.
They would have been killed.
It's not my responsibility, May.
Oh.
What Norman said?
My moral mission? No.
-No, May--
-Peter, you listen to me.
You have a gift.
You have power.
And with great power,
there must also come
great responsibility. Hmm?
I know.
Let's get the...out of here.
Okay, let's go.
[May] Let me just catch my...
[indistinct radio chatter]
-What happened? Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
Yeah, you're okay. What happened?
Just have to...
catch my breath.
Okay, well, catch your breath.
I'm right here.
We're gonna take our time.
You catch your breath
and then we'll take you to a doctor, okay?
[May breathing raggedly]
[sombre music playing]
[sirens wailing in distance]
Are you okay?
Somebody help!
I need an ambulance, please! Somebody?
-What happened?
-Nothing happened.
You're okay, you're okay.
Let me just-- Let me catch my breath.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
You're okay.
It's just me and you.
May?
Will you look at me, please?
May.
What are you doing, May?
Please, will you just wake up
and talk to me? Please?
[officer 1] Get out of the car now! Move!
Get off, get off, get off me.
Peter!
-Run!
-It's just me and you, okay?
It's just me and you, okay?
Oh, May, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so, so sorry. I love you.
[officer 1]
Parker, come out with your hands up!
[officer 2] Come out right now,
or we will open fire!
Run!
[officer 3] All right, let's go, let's go!
Move in!
[Jameson on TV] Tragedy.
[melancholy music playing]
What else can I call it?
What more need be said?
The damage, the destruction.
You saw it with your own eyes.
When will people wake up and realise
that everywhere Spider-Man goes,
chaos and calamity ensue?
Everything Spider-Man touches
comes to ruin.
And we, the innocents,
are left to pick up the pieces.
J. Jonah Jameson reporting.
Good night, and God help us all.
[reporter on TV] We are told
that multiple people have been injured,
and we can confirm
at least one person has been killed.
Still nothing?
No.
[sighs]
I'm gonna press it.
-What? No, he--
-I know he told me to wait...
-but I'm gonna do it.
-I just wish--
I just wish we could see him.
-Ned?
-Yeah?
-Do that again.
-Yeah.
I just wish we could see him.
Okay.
I just wish we could see Peter.
-[gasps]
-Whoa.
-[speaking Tagalog]
-Lola, you're right. I am magic.
Is that him?
-Yeah, yeah, it has to be.
-Peter. Peter!
-Hey, Peter! Yeah.
-[MJ] Peter!
[suspenseful music playing]
[MJ &amp; Ned] Whoa.
[screaming]
Hi. Hi.
No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay. I'm a nice guy.
Okay.
-Who the hell are you?
-I'm Peter Parker.
-That's not possible.
-I am Spider-Man, in my world.
But then yesterday, I was--
I was just here.
Wow.
String theory, multidimensional reality...
and matter displacement.
All real?
-Yeah.
I knew it.
This has to be because of the spell.
The spell? Like magic spell?
-Uh, there's no spell. No.
-No spell.
-Magic's real here too?
-I mean--
-Shut up, Ned. Shut up.
-No, it's not real.
-There's magicians, but there's no--
-Stop talking.
Stop. Stop.
-Prove it.
-Prove what?
-That you're Peter Parker.
-I don't carry an ID with me, you know?
Kind of defeats
the whole anonymous superhero thing.
-Why'd you do that?
-To see if you have the tingle thing.
I have the tingle thing,
just not for bread.
Can you not throw the bread again?
You're a deeply mistrusting person...
and I respect it.
Crawl around.
-Crawl around?
-[MJ] Yes.
-No.
-Yes, crawl around.
-Why do I need to?
-[MJ] This is not enough.
-This is plenty.
-No, it's not.
-Yes, it is. It is.
-No, it's not. Nuh-uh.
-How do I stick to the ceiling?
-[MJ] Do it.
Ned. [speaking Tagalog]
My lola's asking
if you could just get the cobweb there.
-Since you're, like, up there.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
We--
We good?
For now.
So I opened the wrong portal
to the wrong Peter Parker.
I guess you keep doing it
until we find the real one.
-Ouch.
-No offence.
-[Ned] Okay.
-Okay. You got it.
Find Peter Parker.
-What's the thing on his hand?
-Shh.
Find Peter Parker.
Find Peter Parker!
[suspenseful music playing]
Great, it's just some random guy.
Hello.
Um, I hope it's okay,
I just came through this, uh...
Oh. It just closed.
You're Peter?
Yeah. Peter Parker.
I've seen you two--
Hi.
Wait. He's-- He's not your friend.
Huh.
Wait. So you're Spider-Man too?
Why didn't you just say that?
I generally don't go around
advertising it.
Kind of defeats
the whole anonymous superhero thing.
-I just said that.
-That's what he just said.
[speaking Tagalog]
My lola's asking if you could clean up
the webs you just shot.
-Oh, sorry, Lola.
-Yes, of course.
I'm going to bed.
-[Ned] Night, Lola.
-[MJ] Good night, Ned's lola.
[Peter 2]
Uh, this might seem kind of weird,
but I've been trying to find
your friend ever since I got here.
I just have this sense...
that he needs my help.
Our help.
He does.
We don't know where he is.
And, um, honestly,
right now we're all he really has left.
Well, uh, is there someplace
that he might go
that has meaning to him?
Like a place where he would go to just--?
Get away from everything?
For me, it was the top
of the Chrysler Building.
Empire State.
-It's just a-- It's a better view.
-That is a sweet view.
Yes.
Yeah. I think
I know exactly where that would be.
[melancholy music playing]
[crying]
[MJ] I'm sorry.
Peter, there's...
There's some people here.
What?
Hey, wait, wait! Whoa.
What...?
Sorry...
about May.
Yeah. Sorry.
I got some understanding
of what it is you're--
No, please don't tell me
that you know what I'm going through.
-Okay.
-She's gone.
And it's all my fault.
She died for nothing.
I'll do what I should have done
in the first place.
-[Peter 2] Peter--
-Please don't.
You don't belong here. Either of you.
So I'm sending you home.
Those other guys are
from your worlds, right?
So you deal with it.
If they die, if you kill them...
that's on you.
It's not my problem.
I don't care anymore.
I'm done.
I'm really sorry
that I dragged you into this.
But you have to go home now.
Good luck.
[Peter 2] My uncle Ben was killed.
It was my fault.
I lost...
I lost Gwen, my, um...
She was my MJ.
I couldn't save her.
I'm never gonna be able
to forgive myself for that.
But I carried on, tried to, um...
Tried to keep going,
tried to keep being...
the friendly neighbourhood Spider-Man
'cause I know that's
what she would've wanted.
But at some point,
I just stopped pulling my punches.
[melancholy music playing]
I got rageful.
I got bitter.
I just don't want you to end up like me.
[Peter 2] The night Ben died...
I hunted down the man
who I thought did it.
I wanted him dead.
I got what I wanted.
It didn't make it better.
It took me a long time...
to learn to get through that darkness.
I wanna kill him.
I wanna tear him apart.
I can still hear her voice in my head.
Even after she was hurt,
she said to me
that we did the right thing.
She told me that with great power...
Comes great responsibility.
Wait, what? How do you know that?
Uncle Ben said it.
The day he died.
Maybe she didn't die for nothing, Peter.
[heroic music playing]
[Peter] Okay, so Connors,
Marko, Dillon and, um...
I think that I can repair
the devices for Dillon and Marko,
but the others....
Oh, I got Connors.
I've cured him once, so no big deal.
-What? It's no big deal.
-Great.
Yeah, that's great.
I think I can make an antiserum
for Dr Osborn.
Been thinking about it a long time.
Gotta cure all of them. Right?
Right.
That's what we do.
[MJ] Psst.
What?
Just three yous.
[Ned] Um...
So... do you have a best friend too?
I did.
You did?
He died in my arms...
after he tried to kill me.
It was heart-breaking.
Dude.
-Hey.
-Will you run a diagnostic?
Yeah.
Hey, you okay?
-Uh, yeah, I'm fine. Are you okay?
-Mm-hm.
You don't deserve this.
-I've ruined your life. I ruined it.
-No. No, no, no.
Look at me. I'm here.
Not going anywhere.
We'll get through this
and we'll get through it together.
Okay?
-Okay.
Thank you.
You have someone?
No.
[sighs] I got no time
for Peter Parker stuff, you know?
-Do you?
-Uh...
That's a little complicated.
I understand.
I guess it's just not
in the cards for guys like us.
Well, I wouldn't give up.
Took a while but we made it work.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Me and... MJ.
My MJ. Uh...
It gets confusing here.
[laughs] Yeah.
-Peter!
-[in unison] Yeah?
-[in unison] Oh, sorry, did you mean...?
-"Peter" Peter.
-We're all called Peter.
-We're all Peter.
-Peter Parker?
-Same again. We're all Peter Parker.
-The computer.
-Oh.
-Oh, I'm ready.
-[Peter 3] Yeah. Me too.
Okay, so now, all we gotta do is lure
these guys someplace, right?
Try to cure them
while they try to kill us,
and then send them home.
-Using a magic box.
-Well, that's the plan.
Are you gonna go into battle
dressed as a cool youth pastor,
or do you got your suit?
Good.
-Here's your web cartridges.
-Ah, thanks, man.
What's that for?
It's my web fluid.
It's for my web shooters. Why?
Whoa!
-That came out of you.
-Yeah.
-You can't do that, huh?
-No.
How on earth does that even--?
We're getting side-tracked.
This is where we'll do this, okay?
It's isolated, so no one should get hurt.
We draw them there with the box.
It's the one thing they all want.
All we have to do is figure out
how to get there.
-We could portal there.
-What?
-I'm magic now.
-Yeah, he's right. He can.
-Yeah, we saw.
-Yeah, he is.
-Wait, really?
-I got Doctor Strange magic.
-No way.
-[Ned] Yeah.
I promise you, I won't turn
into a supervillain and try to kill you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Um... here goes nothing.
What's that thing you always say?
-Expect disappointment and--
-No, no, no.
We're gonna kick some ass.
Okay.
Cure. Cure some ass.
Cure that ass.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jameson on TV] Ladies and gentlemen,
the Bugle tip line has
just received a call
from none other
than the fugitive known as Spider-Man,
fresh from his rampage in Queens.
So, Peter Parker, what pernicious
propaganda are you peddling?
-[Peter] Just the truth. Truth is...
-[Jameson] Oh, sure.
-that this is all my fault.
-[Jameson scoffs]
I accidentally brought
those dangerous people here.
Well, he admits it.
And if those people are watching...
just know that I did try to help you.
I could have killed you...
at any given moment, but I didn't.
'Cause my Aunt May taught me
that everyone deserves a second chance.
-That's why I'm here.
-Where is "here," exactly?
A place that represents second chances.
[dramatic music playing]
[Jameson] The Statue of Liberty?
Good God, folks.
He's about to destroy
another national landmark.
World, if you're watching...
[Jameson] Believe me,
the world is watching.
...wish me luck.
Your friendly neighbourhood Spider-Man
could use some.
Okay, it could be any minute now.
[Peter 2] Yep, almost done.
[Peter 3] You know, Max was,
like, the sweetest guy ever
before he fell into...
-a pool of electric eels.
-That'll do it.
All the things I wished
I could have done differently.
Now to have a second chance.
Yeah.
Mm. Oh, there it goes.
You okay?
Oh, it's my back.
It's kind of stiff
from all the swinging, I guess.
-Yeah. No, I got a middle-back thing too.
-Really?
[Peter 3] Yeah. You want me to crack it?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-That'd be great.
-All right.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
-Yep. That's good.
-[bones crack]
-How is it?
-Wow.
-That's good. That's better.
-Right? Yeah.
Wow.
This is so cool. I always wanted brothers.
We should do this again,
like, all hang out.
[Peter 2] It's nice.
We should maybe, you know, focus on...
On not getting killed tonight.
Yeah. For sure. That's a good idea.
I'll just grab your number
at the end of the battle.
You got it.
So you, like,
make your own web fluid in your body?
I'd rather not talk about this.
-I don't mean to--
-But are you teasing me?
No, no, no. He's not teasing you.
It's just that we can't do that,
so we're curious as to how
your web situation works, that's all.
If it's personal, I don't wanna pry,
but I think it's cool.
I-- I wish I could tell you,
but it's, like, I don't do it.
Like I don't do breathing.
-Like, breathing just happens.
-Whoa.
It's just, like, when it releases,
it's like a clean release.
Can I ask something?
-Yeah.
-Is it like:
When you think it, it webs?
That's a good way to put it.
Because if I press...
I have to have a mechanism.
-Right.
-But for you, is it like, "Web"?
And then it webs?
Uh, not even conscious at this point.
It's just like riding a bike.
Does it just come out of your wrists,
or does it come out of anywhere else?
Only-- Only the wrists.
Never had a web block?
I run out of webs all the time.
-I have to make my own in a lab.
-[Peter 2] Right. That's--
-It's a hassle compared to what you got.
-Sounds like a hassle.
But I did. You said that,
I was like, "Oh. I had a web block."
-Whoa. Why?
-Existential-crisis stuff.
Pfft. Yeah. Don't get me started on that.
I'm not sure what to say.
It's just a natural thing.
It just happens.
I don't know.
It's so cool, man.
-Like, I wanna see the holes.
-[Peter] Hey.
What are some of the craziest villains
that you guys have fought?
-Seems you've met some of them.
-That's a good question.
Yeah, I fought an alien
made out of black goo once.
Oh, no way. I fought an alien too.
-On Earth and in space.
-Oh.
-He was purple.
-I wanna fight an alien.
I'm still, like, that you fought
an alien in space.
I'm always simultaneously,
like, completely stunned
by the fantastical nature of these things,
and it's also just like,
"Yeah. Okay. Yeah."
Yeah, it's Monday. Yeah.
I mean--
I'm lame compared-- I fought
a Russian guy in a rhinoceros machine.
That's cool.
Not as-- No, it's not.
Can we rewind it back
to the "I'm lame" part?
'Cause you are not.
Thanks. I appreciate that.
I'm not saying I am--
But it's just the self-talk.
Maybe we should...
-Listen, I--
-[Peter 2] 'Cause you're amazing.
Just to take it in for a minute.
-[Peter 3] Yeah, I can take it in.
-You are amazing.
-I can. Thank you.
-You are amazing. Will you say it?
I needed to hear that. Thank you.
[thunder rumbling in distance]
All right, guys, focus up. You feel that?
Yeah.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Electro] What's up, Peter?
How you like the new-new?
Look, you give it to me,
I'm gonna destroy it. [chuckles]
But I'll let you live.
Don't make me a murderer, Peter.
[Spider-Man] Okay, guys, here he comes.
[Spider-Man 3] Hey, Max!
I missed you, man. Ho!
[Spider-Man] All right, MJ, heads up!
Got it! Close it.
[Ned grunting]
-Ned, it's not closing.
-Yeah, I know.
-Why isn't it closing?
-I don't know.
-Did you close it before? No?
-I mean, I've opened some.
[roars]
Max, Max, Max. Can we talk for a second?
-Just you and me, just talk?
-Look who showed up.
My old friend Spider-Man.
I'm trying to save you.
That's all I've wanted.
-You're not trying to save me.
-I am.
You ain't even the shit no more.
-Oh.
-Don't worry about me. I'll save myself.
-Burn up!
-[grunts] Oh!
Well, I got his attention. Now what?
[Spider-Man 2] Okay, great.
Uh, just FYI, lizard guy's here too.
Guys, comm check. Hello?
-[Spider-Man 3] I need Max's cure!
-Yeah. I'm on it.
[Spider-Man 2]
Peter, I need the Lizard cure.
[grunts] Okay, okay.
Where's the box, Peter?
-Flint, we could help everyone.
-I don't care!
[yells]
Sorry!
Ugh. Gross!
[Electro] Sad to tell you, Sandman,
nobody's going home.
[yells]
Oh! What the hell is going on out there?
I keep yelling at you, Peter 2!
-But I thought you were Peter 2.
-What? I'm not Peter 2.
Stop arguing, both of you!
Listen to Peter 1.
-We're clearly not very good at this.
-I know, I know. We suck.
-I don't know how to work as a team.
-Me neither.
I do. I've been in a team, okay?
I don't wanna brag, but I will.
I was in the Avengers.
-The Avengers?
-Yeah.
-That's great.
-Thank you.
What is that?
You don't have the Avengers?
Is that a band? Are you in a band?
No, I'm not in a band.
The Avengers is Earth's mightiest--
-How's this helping?
-It's not important.
All we gotta do is focus,
trust your tingle,
and coordinate our attacks.
Yes. Okay. Let's pick one target.
-Right.
-We take them off the board one at a time.
-You got it. Okay, Peter 1, Peter 2.
-Peter 2.
-Peter 3.
-Let's do this. Ready?
-[Peter 3] Wait, wait!
I love you guys.
[both] Thank you.
-All right, let's do this.
-Let's go.
[heroic music playing]
[all whooping]
[Spider-Man] Okay, Spider-Mans.
Sandman's first.
-I'm gonna lead him inside the statue.
-I'll meet you at the top.
-[Lizard] Come on!
-[Spider-Man 3] Hey!
-Hey, Dr Connors.
-Hello, Peter.
Peter 1!
I got it!
[yells]
[Spider-Man 2]
Flint, we're trying to help you!
Guys, I'm at the top!
I need the cure! [grunting]
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
[grunting] Just wait your turn, doc!
I'll be right back.
[panting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Peter 2] It's okay, Flint.
We're gonna get you home.
You just stay right here.
[Spider-Man 3] How do we stop him?
I've never seen him this powerful.
[Spider-Man] It's the arc reactor.
We gotta get it off him.
You're not gonna take this from me.
That's not gonna work.
[Spider-Man] We gotta do this up close.
Peter 2, go right.
Peter 3, go left. On me.
[Electro] Yeah!
[screaming]
[MJ] Um...
[Ned] I'm trying to close it.
I can't help that it's not working.
It's fine. You'll do it again.
We'll keep trying.
-All right, we got this. Shh.
-Focus and close the portal.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
And that is a lizard and we should go!
[both shouting]
Run!
Come on! Come on, this way!
Quick, quick, quick!
[Spider-Man] Connors, stop!
[laughing] Yeah.
[groans]
Leave them. They're mine.
I don't need your help.
I got it just fine.
Dr Octavius, no.
What are you doing?
Get it off of me.
[dramatic music playing]
There you go.
[growling]
[Spider-Man] MJ!
Whoa.
-We gotta hide this thing.
-Oh, right.
-Nice, Ned!
-Yeah!
[MJ] Oh.
Where is he?
-[Ned] No!
-[MJ] Wait, wait, wait.
Before you do anything, Mister--
Doctor Strange, Peter's plan is working.
-What plan?
-He's curing them.
Dr Connors?
Welcome back, sir.
Well, I'll be damned.
Did you just open a portal?
Yes, sir, I did.
Hmm.
Max? Max?
-Don't worry. I'm all tapped out.
-Are you sure about that?
Back to being a nobody.
-You were never a nobody, Max.
-Yes, I was.
You didn't see me. [chuckles]
-Can I tell you something, though?
-[Peter 3] Yeah.
You got a nice face. You're just a kid.
-Eh.
-You're from Queens.
You got that suit.
You help a lot of poor people.
I just thought you was gonna be Black.
-Oh, man, I'm sorry.
-Don't apologise.
There's gotta be a Black Spider-Man
somewhere out there.
Goddamn eels.
The power of the sun.
-[Spider-Man 2] In the palm of your hand.
-Peter?
Otto.
Oh, it's good to see you, dear boy.
It's good to see you.
You're all grown up.
How are you?
Trying to do better.
[portal roars]
-Strange, wait, we're so close.
-Skip it!
I've been dangling
over the Grand Canyon for 12 hours.
[Peter] I know, I know, I know.
I, uh-- Um...
I'm sorry about that, sir. I mean...
-You went to the Grand Canyon?
-He could have used your help.
[Peter] It's okay.
These are my new friends.
This is Peter Parker, Peter Parker.
Spider-Man, Spider-Man.
-They're mes from other universes.
-Oh.
They're here to help.
This is the wizard I told you about.
I am really impressed that you've managed
to give them all a second chance, kid.
But this has to end. Now.
[Green Goblin]
Can the Spider-Man come out to play?
[suspenseful music playing]
Strange, no!
[MJ screaming]
[Green Goblin cackling]
[inaudible dialogue]
[gasping]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
[grunting]
[screams]
-[heroic music playing]
-Whoa.
Thank you, Mr Cape, sir.
[MJ] Ned?
-Ned!
-Hey!
[panting]
MJ!
Peter?
-[Peter] Ned!
-[MJ] Peter!
Hey!
-[Peter] Are you okay?
-We're okay!
Poor Peter.
Too weak to send me home to die.
No.
I just wanna kill you myself.
Attaboy.
[whistles]
[yells]
[grim music playing]
-[blade pierces flesh]
-[grunts]
[Green Goblin] She was there...
because of you.
I may have struck the blow,
but you...
[chuckles]
You are the one that killed her.
[Green Goblin cackling]
[sombre music playing]
Peter.
What have I done?
-It's you.
-[Peter 3] You okay?
Uh... Yeah, I'm good.
I've been stabbed before.
-Oh, good, good, good.
-Hey.
-Oh, man.
-Hey, nice catch.
Nice throw.
[sky rumbling]
-What? Is that happening, or am I dying?
-[Peter 3] Yeah, no, that's happening.
-That's real.
-[Peter 2] Are there people in the sky?
-I gotta go.
-Yeah. I got it. You okay?
[Peter] What's happening?
They're starting to come through.
I can't stop them.
There's gotta be something we could do.
Can't you just cast the spell again?
The original way, before I screwed it up.
[Strange] We're too late for that.
They're here.
They're here because of you.
What if everyone forgot who I was?
What?
They're coming here because of me, right?
Because I'm Peter Parker?
So cast a new spell.
But this time, make everyone forget
who Peter Parker is.
Make everyone forget...
-me.
-No.
-But it would work, right?
-Yeah, it would work.
But you gotta understand
that would mean that everyone
who knows and loves you, we...
We'd have no memory of you.
It would be as though you never existed.
I know.
Do it.
You better go and say your goodbyes.
You don't have long.
-Thank you, sir.
-Call me Stephen.
Thank you, Stephen.
Yeah. Still feels weird.
I'll see you around.
So long, kid.
Hey. Uh...
I think this is it.
I think you're about to go home.
-Okay.
-All right.
Look, I, uh...
Thank you.
I just wanna-- I want you to--
I wanna tell you that--
I don't know how to say this. I--
-Peter.
-I want you to know that I...
You know. It's what we do.
Yeah, it's what we do. Um...
Right, I gotta find Ned and MJ. I--
Uh... [grunts]
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
-I guess I'll see you.
-[Peter 3] See you.
Bye.
-Oh.
-You're in so much pain, huh?
-I am.
-Yeah.
[MJ] Oh, you're okay. [exhales]
So proud of you.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, we're okay.
-Oh, my God, you're bleeding.
-I'm fine. I'm okay.
-You sure?
-I'm fine, I promise.
-Okay, okay.
-[MJ] I promise.
Good.
Um, we should go, right?
Yeah. You're gonna forget who I am.
-What?
-Forget? What are you talking about?
It's okay. I'm gonna come and find you,
and I'll explain everything.
I'll make you remember me.
And it'll be like none of this
ever happened. Okay?
But what if that doesn't work?
What if that doesn't work?
What if we can't remember you?
I don't wanna do that.
-I don't wanna do that.
-[Peter] I know. MJ, I know.
There's not something we can do?
We can't come up with a plan?
There's always something we can do.
There's nothing we can do.
But it'll be okay.
You promise?
Yeah, I promise.
[poignant music playing]
I'll come find you, okay?
I know you will.
-Okay.
-[Peter] Okay.
You better.
If you don't, I'll just figure it out.
I've done it before, I can do it again.
I promise, I'll fix this.
I really hate magic.
Yeah. Me too.
I love you.
-I love--
-Just wait.
Wait and tell me when you see me again.
Sure.
[sky rumbling]
[stirring music playing]
[mouths] I love you.
[Jameson] It's been a few weeks
since the fiasco on the Statue of Liberty,
and Spider-Man's cultists
continue to contend
that the vile vigilante is a hero.
If he were a hero, he'd unmask himself
and tell us who he really is
because only a coward
conceals his identity.
Only a coward hides his true intentions.
Rest assured, ladies and gentlemen,
this reporter will uncover
those intentions, come hell or high water.
Hi. My name is Peter Parker.
You don't know me, but I... Uh...
Hi, my name is Peter Parker,
and you don't know me, but you--
Okay, come on.
[bell jingles]
-[MJ] No way. [chuckles]
-[man] Hard to believe, isn't it?
-[bell jingles]
-Hey.
One sec. Can I help you?
Hi. Um...
My name is Peter Parker, and I...
would like a coffee, please.
Okay, no problem, Peter Parker.
Doughnut for my fellow Engineer.
-[Ned] Whoa. Wait, what?
-MIT, they're the Engineers. The mascot.
Oh, right, right, right.
I should probably know that.
-Look at you with the school spirit.
-Tell anybody, I will deny it.
Oh, okay.
[poignant music playing]
Peter Parker? Peter Parker.
Your coffee.
-Right. Thank you.
-[MJ] Mm-hm.
Um...
Are you excited for MIT?
Oh, right. Yeah. Uh...
Yeah, I am excited, which is weird
'cause I don't really
get excited about things.
I kind of expect disappointment.
'Cause then you'll never
actually be disappointed.
Right?
Uh...
Yeah. Right.
I don't know, it kind of feels different
this time for some reason.
Right. Um...
-What I was--
-[cash register beeps]
You okay?
It doesn't really hurt anymore.
Is there anything else?
No.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'll, uh, see you around.
[bell jingles]
[melancholy music playing]
How'd you know her?
Through Spider-Man.
You?
Same.
I lost a good friend a while back.
Felt like this.
Hurts 'cause they're gone
and then it hurts all over again
because you remember
what they stood for
and you wonder, "Is all that gone too?"
No, it's not gone.
Everyone that she helped...
they'll keep it going.
You really think so?
I know it.
-Take care of yourself, okay?
-Yeah. Nice to meet you.
[man] Rent is due on the first
of the month. Don't be late.
[poignant music playing]
[woman over radio] Four-three-Edward,
do you need EMS assist?
[man over radio] Negative, Central.
We're gonna need a car tow.
[heroic music playing]
[grunts]
[De La Soul's "The Magic Number" playing]
♪ Three, that's the magic number ♪
♪ Yes, it is ♪
-♪ It's the magic number ♪
-♪ Three ♪
♪ Somewhere
In this hip-hop soul community ♪
♪ Was born three
Mase, Dove and me ♪
-♪ And that's the magic number ♪
-♪ What does it all mean? ♪
♪ Difficult preachin'
Is Posdnuos' pleasure ♪
♪ Pleasure and preachin'
Starts in the heart ♪
♪ Something that stimulates my music
In the measure ♪
♪ Measure in the music
Raised in three parts ♪
♪ Casually see
But don't do like the Soul ♪
♪ Seein' and doin'
Are actions for monkeys ♪
♪ Doin' hip-hop hustle, no rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ Unless your name's Brewster
'Cause Brewster's a Punk ♪
♪ Parents let go
There's magic in the air ♪
♪ Criticising rap
Shows you're out of order ♪
♪ Stop, look and listen
To the phrase, Fred Astaires ♪
♪ Don't get offended
While Mase do-si-dos your daughter ♪
♪ Tri-camera rolls
Since our music's now set ♪
♪ Fly rhymes are stored
On a DAISY production ♪
♪ Stands for "da inner sound, y'all"
Y'all can bet ♪
♪ The action's not a trick
But sure enough a function ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be a DJ
Everybody wants to be an emcee ♪
♪ No more, no less
And you don't have to guess ♪
♪ De La Soul posse consists of three ♪
-♪ And that's the magic number ♪
-♪ Three ♪
♪ This here piece of the pie ♪
♪ Is not dessert
But the course that we dine ♪
♪ And three out of every darn time
The effect is "Mm" ♪
♪ When a daisy grows in your mind
Showing true position ♪
♪ This here piece is kissin'
The part of the pie that's missin' ♪
♪ When that negative number
Fills up your casualty ♪
-♪ Three ♪
-♪ Maybe you can subtract it ♪
♪ You can call it your lucky partner ♪
♪ Maybe you can call it your adjective ♪
♪ But odd as it may be
Without my 1 and 2, where would there be ♪
♪ My three: Mase, Pos and me ♪
-♪ And that's the magic number ♪
-♪ What does it all mean? ♪
♪ Focus is formed by flaunts to the soul ♪
♪ Souls who flaunt styles
Gain praises by pounds ♪
♪ Common are speakers
Who honour the scroll ♪
♪ Scrolls written daily
Creates a new sound ♪
♪ Listeners, listen
'Cause this here is wisdom ♪
♪ Wisdom of a Speaker, a Dove and a Plug ♪
♪ Set aside a legal substance
To feed them ♪
♪ For now get them high
Off this dialect drug ♪
♪ Time is a factor
So it's time that counts ♪
♪ Count not the negative actions of one ♪
♪ Speakers of soul
Say it's time to shout ♪
♪ Three forms the soul to a positive sum ♪
♪ Dance to this fix
And flex every muscle ♪
♪ Space can be filled
If you rise like my lumber ♪
♪ Advance to the tune
But don't do the hustle ♪
♪ Shake, rattle, roll to my magic number ♪
♪ Now, you may try to subtract it
But it just won't go away ♪
-♪ Three times one? ♪
-♪ What is it? ♪
-♪ One times three times one ♪
-♪ Three times one ♪
-♪ What is it? ♪
♪ Three, three, three ♪
♪ That's a magic number ♪
Okay.
Okay, I think I got this.
You're saying that this whole place here,
it's just tons of...
superpeople.
[Venom]
And he has been saying it for hours.
All right, tell me again.
I'm sorry. I'm an idiot.
There was a billionaire,
he had a tin suit and he could fly, right?
Okay, and there was
a really angry green man.
-Hulk.
[Venom] And you thought
Lethal Protector was a shit name.
Yeah, because it is.
Now tell me again about
your purple alien that loves stones.
'Cause I'll tell you what, man,
aliens do not love stones.
-Eddie, don't start.
-They don't.
Know what aliens love? Eating brains.
Because that's what they do. All right?
Señor, he made my family disappear.
For five years.
Five years?
That's a long time.
Maybe I...
Maybe I should go to New York
and speak to this...
Spider-Man.
Eddie, we are drunk.
[hiccups]
-Let's go skinny-dip!
-I don't think we should skinny-dip.
You have to pay the bill.
What is happening? No!
-No, we just got here! No, not again!
-Oh...
And there he goes.
Without paying the bill, no tips, nothing.
[man] Seniors, don't forget to schedule
your graduation photo pickup.
-[air horn blares]
-Cafeteria safety is no joke.
Respect the signs,
or pay the consequences.
This has been a message
from the Cafeteria Safety Council.
[Betty] And now, Betty's Corner,
with Betty Brant.
It seems like only yesterday
that we were just starting the adventure
that we call high school.
And what an adventure it's been.
We learned new things.
We travelled the world.
We fell in love.
We almost died. Multiple times.
We made friendships
that will last forever.
Also, some of us disappeared
for five years and then reappeared.
But the less we talk about that,
the better.
What's important is that we made it.
And as we look out on to an exciting
and uncertain future, just remember:
The memories we've made here
at Midtown High
are the ones that we will cherish forever.
That's Midtown News for today,
and for one last time,
this has been Betty Brant.
Signing off.
Happy graduation! Go Tigers! [whoops]