Hey, you reached Jim.
I'm probably doing something incredible
right now, and I can't...
It's like... It's like I feel
what the shadow monster's feeling.
See what he's seeing.
Like in the Upside Down?
Some of him is there.
But some of him is here, too.
- Here, like, in this house?
- In this house and...
in me.
It's like... It's like he's reaching
into Hawkins more and more.
And the more he spreads,
the more connected to him I feel.
And the more you see these now-memories.
At first I just felt it
in the back of my head.
I didn't even really know it was there.
It's like when you have a dream
and you can't remember it
unless you think really hard.
It was like that.
But know it's like...
Now I remember. I remember all the time.
Maybe...
- Maybe that's good.
- Good?
Just think about it, Will.
You're like a spy now. A superspy.
Spying on the shadow monster.
If you know what he's seeing
and feeling...
maybe that's how we can stop him.
Maybe all of this
is happening for a reason.
- You really think so?
- Yeah. Yeah, I really do.
What if he figures out
we're spying on him?
- What if he spies back?
- He won't.
How do you know?
We won't let him.
Ugh!
- Hey.
- Hey. Did you get 'em?
Yeah.
We'd like a... uh, a room.
We got those.
You want a single or a double?
Double.
Nance...
- Uh, on or off?
- Hmm.
- What?
- Nothing. Just...
déjà vu.
Yeah.
Don't you think it's weird?
What?
How we only seem to hang out
when the world's about to end?
It's not going to end.
Feels like it.
Still have yours?
- Yeah.
- Mmm...
Yeah, mine's bigger.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
What happened?
What do you mean?
To us?
After everything, you just...
disappeared.
Yeah, Will needed me.
And Steve...
I waited.
Yeah, like, only a month.
I want them off.
Will, what's wrong?
Mom?
- Mom?
- Yeah?
- I saw him.
- You saw who, baby?
Hopper.
I think he's in trouble.
I think he's going to die.
Shit!
- That's enough, Erica.
- Uh-uh.
- Dad?
- Mmm-hmm?
When Mom's mad at you,
how do you make her not mad?
Hmm. That's a great question.
How do you, hon?
First, I apologize.
Then, I get your mother
whatever she wants.
Even when she's wrong?
She's never wrong, son.
That's right.
- Not hungry?
- Not really.
Where you goin'?
To hang out with Dustin.
Sorry.
Mews!
Mewsy!
Dusty, baby, you're sure
she's not in your room?
Uh-huh.
If you'd like to make a call...
Thank you so much,
Mr. McCorkle. Thank you so much.
You are a true lifesaver.
All right, this was great.
Thank you. All right. Have a good one.
Bye-bye, now. All right. You, too.
All right, great news.
They found her?
No. But they saw her wandering
around Loch Nora.
How did the poor baby
get all the way out there?
I don't know. Lost, I guess.
But they're gonna look for her.
And I'll stay here,
just in case they call again.
And you're gonna go help look? Yeah? Yeah?
Give me hug.
Give me a hug. Go get her.
- You're gonna find her.
- Okay.
- We can find her.
I love you.
- I love you.
- All right, go.
All right.
All right, Dart. Breakfast time.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Come on. Come on, I know you're hungry.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Shit!
I'm sorry. You ate my cat.
All right. I think this is it.
Five-one-five Larrabee, right?
Yes.
Five-fifteen.
All right, "Five-fifteen." Sure.
Thank you.
Hey.
You apologize to your mama, yeah? Huh?
Must be scared half to death.
How long's it been?
Long time.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Go away! I'm not interested!
Look, I don't want your Thin Mints,
all right, kid?
- Thin Mints?
- Or your religious mumbo jumbo.
Whatever you're selling,
I ain't buying, okay?
I want to see Mama.
Name a way you occupy your time
when you're having a boring day at work.
- Drink coffee.
- "Drink coffee," said Mike.
Yeah! Five answers will beat it, Lynn.
Visit with other employees.
- "Visit with other employees."
- Rainbow.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Mama?
Breathe. Sunflower.
Rainbow.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Mama, can you hear me?
Four-fifty. Breathe.
Sunflower.
Rainbow.
Mama? It's me...
Jane.
I'm here now.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow. Four-fifty.
Breathe. Sunflower.
- What's wrong with Mama?
- Rainbow.
Four-fifty.
Are you positive
this is the right place?
"3833." Yeah.
All right.
Look at the camera.
- The camera.
- What camera?
Not the loudspeaker.
Above you, to the right.
Nancy Wheeler. Jonathan Byers.
You two are a long way from home.
Well...
I hope you didn't come all this way
to tell me about the bear
in the Harrington kid's backyard.
I've heard that one already.
Take a look. Go ahead, don't be shy.
I followed up on 200 tips,
most bogus, but that's how
these things always go, okay?
I know every last step
Barbara took that day,
every last person she talked to.
The answer to what happened
to your friend, it's up here somewhere.
I assure you that.
I just gotta connect the right dots.
Timeline's wrong.
I'm sorry?
Your timeline is wrong.
And the girl with the buzzed hair,
she's not Russian. She's from Hawkins Lab.
Her name was Eleven.
You might wanna sit down for this.
If you're not out in an hour...
- Walking home. Yeah, yeah, I know.
- Hey! Watch the attitude, shitbird.
Sorry about that, Road Warrior.
What happened?
Short circuit in the motherboard.
A real bummer.
But fret not. I got another machine
up and running in the back.
Hold these.
You better get me that date now, Sinclair.
I told you I would.
And keep things PG in here, all right?
What is this shit, stalker?
Sorry. I just needed a safe place.
A safe place to what? Be creepy?
Listen. I'm gonna tell you the truth
about everything that happened last year.
But if anyone finds out,
you could be arrested.
Possibly killed.
- Killed?
- I need to know.
Do you accept the risk?
- Oh, my God! This... this is so stupid.
- Do you accept the risk?
Yeah.
Sure. Fine.
I accept the risk.
Let's hear it.
Last year...
Will didn't get lost in the woods.
He got lost somewhere else.
Hey, is this where you saw him?
Is this where you saw Hopper?
I think so. Yeah.
Okay.
Here!
Okay, so... so Hopper is here?
Yeah. Now we just need to find out
where here is, right?
Right.
Did he say anything?
I mean, before he left?
Uh, some... something about vines?
Hopper.
Surprise. I would've called,
but you said not to clog up the line.
You know, I... We're fine,
we don't need anything.
When I was sick as a kid,
and I was sick all the time as a kid,
nothing made me feel better
than focusing on these brain teasers.
Those are great. Ah...
I could teach him how to play.
You know, he's sleeping.
Okay.
I could wait with you?
Listen, it's just not a good time.
But, um, you know what?
I'll call you, okay?
Thank you.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Well, have him call me. They don't call me
Bob the Brain for nothing.
Bob!
That's my name.
Huh.
Hmm.
- You drew all these yourself?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Why, exactly?
- I... I told you the rules.
- No questions, okay?
- Yeah.
We... we just need you
to help us figure out what...
Bob? Bob?
Over here.
Where... where this is.
That's the objective. Find the X.
Yeah? What's at the X? Pirate treasure?
Bob, no questions.
Okay.
Let me talk to you for a second.
Hang on, guys.
Joyce, you can talk to me.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
What's the problem, exactly?
What's the problem?
Joyce, Will doesn't look well.
You don't look well.
What's going on?
Nothing. Nothing.
Is this an episode?
Is this one of Will's episodes?
No. No! No.
I'm sorry. I just... I don't...
see how any of this is good for Will,
or for you.
And even if I wanted to play along,
I mean, how could I figure anything out
if I don't understand
the context of the game?
- Or...
- What?
- What is it?
- I know that shape.
It's Lovers' Lake.
It's Lovers' Lake. I get it.
Okay, I get. That's Lake Jordan.
And if that's Lake Jordan,
then you can probably find...
Yeah, that's, uh, Sattler's quarry.
And if you just follow it naturally...
it moves to...
the Eno River.
And there it is.
That's the Eno, do you see it?
Okay, so the lines aren't roads.
But they act like roads.
And they act like roads 'cause when you
follow 'em, you'll see...
they don't go over water.
And that's the giveaway.
That's the giveaway. Ha!
Don't you get it? It's not a puzzle,
it's a map.
It's a map of Hawkins.
Right, Will?
Does anybody copy?
Look, if anybody copies,
this is Jim Hopper, Hawkins' Chief...
Guys, this is Dustin again.
Does anyone copy? This is a code red.
I repeat, a code red!
I really need someone to pick up here.
Hopper's MIA, and I've got a code red.
Code red!
All right, it's Dustin again.
Seriously, I have a code red.
Could you please shut up?
Erica? Erica, is Lucas there?
- Where is he?
- Don't know. Don't care.
Is he with Mike?
Like I said,
I don't know and I don't care.
Please tell him it's super important.
Please tell him that I have a code...
Code red?
- Yep, code red. Exactly.
- Mmm-hmm.
I got a code for you instead.
It's called code shut-your-mouth.
Erica?
I just need a little help
understanding, sweetie, okay?
Can you tell me where you came from?
Where you've been all this time?
A policeman and a woman
came looking for you last year.
Did they find you?
She won't get better...
will she?
They don't think so, no.
But she's not in any pain.
She's just stuck, they think.
Like in a dream.
A long dream.
A good dream?
I hope so.
Is it the same dream?
We don't know.
Sometimes she says different words.
But usually those.
She always believed
that you were out there.
that you'd come home one day.
Home?
Yeah, home.
Pretty.
I can get you a real bed,
and you can stay here with me
if you want.
How's that sound?
I wanna help you, but to really do that,
I need you to talk to me, okay?
Doesn't have to be now.
Doesn't have to be today.
But when you're ready.
Okay?
Okay.
Oh, yeah, that.
That happens sometimes.
Old house, bad wiring...
Or if you ask
my crazy aunt Shirley, it's...
haunted.
Sweetie, really, it's just the wiring.
No.
It's Mama.
Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
I don't understand.
Four-fifty.
She knows I'm here.
She wants to talk.
Rainbow.
All right.
All right. I'm 3.6 inches,
what do you got?
I'm not sure. Mrs. Byers?
Hold on.
- Twenty-one feet, four inches.
- What about Tippecanoe to Danford Creek?
Danford?
Where's Danford?
Dining room.
Sixteen feet, ten inches.
What about Danford to Jordan?
Oh, come on.
This has gotta be enough.
It's not. It's... it's really not.
Okay. Can't you figure it out?
Well, it's hard.
The ratio isn't exactly one-to-one.
I mean, if you're twisting my arm,
and you are twisting my arm,
I would say that the X is...
maybe a half mile southeast of Danford?
Thank you. Thank you.
What? Are we... we really going?
I don't know, Cath.
Maybe if it was Margaret Thatcher,
that'd be another story.
Just a second, Cath.
Ted, can you get that please?
Sorry.
I got it.
Your line has been busy
for over two hours, Mr. Wheeler.
- Do you realize this?
- Oh, I do realize.
- Is Mike home?
- No.
No? Well, where the hell is he?
Karen, where's our son?
Will's!
- Will's.
- No one's picking up there.
Nancy. What about Nancy?
Karen, where's Nancy?
- Ally's!
- Ally's.
Our children don't live here anymore.
You didn't know that?
- Seriously?
- Am I done here?
Son of a bitch. You're really no help
at all, you know that?
Hey! Language.
Listen...
I've been thinking...
I love you. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry? What the hell am I sorry for?
Steve.
Are those for Mr. or Mrs. Wheeler?
- No.
- Good.
- Hey. What the hell? Hey!
- Nancy isn't home.
- Where is she?
- Doesn't matter.
We have bigger problems
than your love life.
Do you still have that bat?
- Bat? What bat?
- The one with the nails?
- Why?
- I'll explain it on the way.
- Now?
- Now!
Son of a bitch!
Wait. Wait. No, no! No! No!
And that was the last
we ever saw of her.
After that, she was just gone.
I can't believe it's been that long.
Feels like yesterday.
Yeah. I mean, I bet.
- Wow.
- It's crazy.
I know.
It's crazy, but...
I really liked it.
- Liked it?
- Yeah.
- Well, I mean, I had a few issues.
- Issues?
I felt it was a little derivative
in parts.
What are you talking about?
I just wish it had
a little more originality.
- That's all.
- You don't believe me?
Lucas, come on, seriously?
How gullible do you think I am?
Why would I make this up?
I don't know. To impress me or something?
Or you're just, like, insane.
I tell you all of this.
I mean, top-secret stuff.
Risking my life.
And this is how you react?
Risking your life?
- Oh, so this is funny to you?
- Yeah. I mean...
kind of funny.
Stupid, but funny.
Where are you going?
Story time's over, isn't it?
What's wrong with you?
I gave you what you wanted.
I wanted to be a part of the group,
not a part of some joke.
It's not a joke.
You did a good job, okay?
You can go tell the others
I believed your lies
if it gets you experience points
or whatever.
We have a lot of rules in our party,
but the most important is,
"Friends don't lie."
Never ever. No matter what.
Is that right?
Then how do you explain this?
I had to do that. To protect you.
To protect me from who, exactly?
The big bad government baddies
from Hawkins Lab?
Lower your voice.
Maybe it was to protect me from
the Demogorgon from another dimension?
- Max, I'm serious, shut up!
- Oh, no, no!
You know what it was?
It was Eleven. The girl...
Stop talking.
You're going to get us killed.
Do you understand?
You're serious?
I really wish I wasn't.
Prove it.
I can't.
So what? I'm supposed to just trust you?
Yes.
Shit. I gotta go. Um...
Don't follow me out. Okay?
Do you believe me?
The hell I tell you?
I'm not late.
You know what I'm talking about.
Oh, Lucas?
So he has a name now, huh?
It's a small town, okay?
We weren't hanging out.
Hmm. Well, you know
what happens when you lie.
I'm not lying.
What if they try to replicate that?
The more attention we bring to ourselves,
the more people like the Hollands
who know the truth,
the more likely that scenario becomes.
You see why I have to stop
the truth from spreading, too.
Just the same as those weeds there.
By whatever means necessary.
So, is it enough?
The tape recording, is it enough?
Is it incriminating?
- What are you doing?
- Thinking.
With vodka?
It's a central nervous system depressant.
So yes, with vodka.
Music? Really?
Yes. It helps me...
What? Think?
How long is this gonna take?
Longer if you keep talking.
Is the tape incriminating or not?
It's a simple question.
There's nothing simple about it.
Nothing simple about anything
you've told me.
You don't believe us, do you?
I believe you, but that's not the problem.
You don't need me to believe you.
You need them to believe you.
- Them?
- Them.
With a capital "T."
Your priest, your postman, your teacher,
the world at large.
They won't believe any of this.
That's why we made the tape.
Oh. That's easy to bury. Easy.
He admits it. You heard it.
He admits culpability.
You're being naive, Nancy!
Those people...
They're not wired like me and you, okay?
They don't spend their lives trying to get
a look at what's behind the curtain.
They like the curtain.
It provides them stability,
comfort, definition.
This...
this would open the curtain,
and open the curtain
behind that curtain, okay?
So the minute someone
with an ounce of authority calls bullshit,
everyone will nod their heads and say,
"See? Ha! I knew it! It was bullshit."
That is, if you even get
their attention at all.
You're saying we did all of this
for nothing?
I'm saying, I'm thinking.
Ooh!
This is ridiculous.
- That's it. That's it!
- What's it?
It's just too strong. Too strong.
Better.
Perfect.
We water it down.
- Precisely.
- Wait. What?
Your story. We moderate it.
Just like this drink here.
We make it more tolerable.
Perhaps Barbara was exposed
to some dangerous toxins.
A leak from the lab.
Like Three Mile Island or something.
Something scary but familiar.
Close enough that it hits the man
right where it hurts.
And those assholes that killed Barb...
They'll go down.
All right, what are we looking at?
This was some of the soil
we took yesterday.
Okay. So what is your concern?
Well, we didn't find
any signs of contamination.
Uh, nothing hazardous
other than some pesticides.
Well, it's a farm.
Right, right. Exactly. But...
Like this?
Yes.
It's okay if I sit here, right?
And I won't mess it up
or anything?
- No.
- Okay.
If you talk to Terry, will you tell her
that I love her very much?
And that I'm sorry that I didn't believe...
- Stop talking.
- Okay, sorry.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty.
Breathe.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
- Mama?
- Sunflower. Rainbow.
- Mama, it's me...
Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Four-fifty.
- Jane.
Breathe. Sunflower.
I'm here now.
Four-fifty.
Breathe. Sunflower. Rainbow.
I'm home.
No.
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
- Oh, my baby!
- What do I do?
- Mama, what do I do? Help me!
- Breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe, all right?
They're on their way.
- They're on their way, okay?
- Okay.
Stay with us, darling. Stay with us.
Hey, there.
Jane?
- Where's Jane?
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
No, I saw her.
- No, no, she wasn't breathing.
- She was crying.
- No.
- I heard it. He was there.
- Who was there?
- He took her.
Don't take it out! Terry!
- Terry!
- No! No!
Please don't!
Three to the right.
Four to the left.
Ma'am, can I see your badge?
Stay back. Stay back!
Jane? Jane?
Jane... No!
No! No! She's my child! No!
She's my child!
No! No.
No.
No. No. No.
Ah!
Four-fifty.
Breathe. They're on their way.
Stay with us, darling.
Sunflower.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Rainbow. Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
Sunflower. Rainbow.
Jane... No!
- Four-fifty.
- Breathe.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
- Sunflower. Rainbow.
- Breathe.
- Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty. Sunflower. Rainbow.
Sunflower. Rainbow.
Three to the right. Four to the left.
Four-fifty. Breathe. Sunflower.
There's nothing. There's nothing here.
- Are... Are we close?
- We're in the vicinity.
What's that mean, the vicinity?
It means we're close.
I don't know. It's not precise.
But we did all that work.
I told you, the scale ratio is not
exactly one-to-one. We needed to take...
- Turn right.
- What?
- I saw him.
- Where?
Not here. In my now-memories.
- In your what?
- Turn right!
Are you okay?
Superspy.
What's Jim doing here? Joyce?
- Boys, I need you to stay here.
- No. Mom, Mom, Mom, it's not safe.
That's why I need you to stay here!
Stay here!
Hopper!
Hey, be careful.
Just going down the hole.
Vines.
Give me that.
- The shovel?
- Yes, give me the shovel.
I need you to help me
get down there.
- Joyce, what are you talking about?
- Bob! Now!
Hopper!
- Joyce, what is going on? Where are we?
- Bob, are you okay?
Tunnels. Is this Will's map?
Hopper!
Are we in Will's map?
Hopper! Hopper!
We're in Will's map.
Hopper!
We're actually inside of Will's map.
How did he know all this?
Bob!
Over here!
It's his.
He's gotta be this way.
Come on.
Hopper!
Do you see anything?
I mean, in your now-memories?
Hopper!
What?
This is...
Oh! It's his arm.
It's choking him.
Knife.
- Knife?
- It's over there.
Okay.
Hands!
Cut it...
Bastard!
Oh, my God.
Hopper, are you okay?
- Joyce.
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Hey, Bob.
- Hey, Jim.
Oh, God!
Go! Go! Go! Clear the area!
- Go!
- Wait.
Move, now!
Will? Will, you okay?
Will, what's wrong?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::