Out.
Everyone out.
Let's go! Move it!
What are you all waiting for?
Move!
Let's go!
What is wrong with
your American friend?
He has lost his spirit to live.
And he is not my friend.
He is American after all.
Big talk, but weak inside.
Tell him to eat.
Or he endangers us all.
We have a big fight ahead of us.
What are you talking about? Fight?
I have been in this place one week.
My first night,
I saw six men enter this room.
Six.
Just like us.
They came out
happy and fat, faces smothered in grease.
But when night fell,
they were thrown into that pit out there.
But not alone.
You heard those roars, yes?
That is a monster.
Not from this world.
Thirty seconds it took! Thirty seconds...
And all six men…
You speak no sense.
If they plan to kill us tonight,
why waste this food on us?
They want us strong.
So we can fight it.
To test its strength.
To train this monster for war.
But last week, the men got their weapons...
then scattered like fools.
We stick together...
Perhaps we stand a chance!
Perhaps we live to see another day.
Till tomorrow!
Come on, come on, come on. Translate!
How do you know this?
Stop talking.
Be silent!
I said go!
Come on, go!
I said to be silent!
You do that again...
we shoot you on the spot.
Fools.