[SIRENS WAILING FAINTLY]
[SIRENS INTENSIFY]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Where is he?
[JASON BREATHING SHAKILY]
[HORRIFIC MUSICAL STINGER PLAYS]
POWELL: Where was Eddie
when that happened?
[INHALES DEEPLY] Wha...
Wait, what?
Eddie.
Where was Eddie when you saw this?
- He... He was in the...
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
...in the boat, like I said.
POWELL: Right.
OFFICER: Right. Right.
But then, uh... [CLICKS TONGUE]
...who lifted Patrick out the water?
What...
You're not listening to me.
- Why aren't you listening to me?
- Jason, we are listening.
No, you're not. You're not.
Eddie, he's...
Eddie is a vessel.
Just a vessel.
A vessel?
For Satan.
He's made a pact with the devil.
Now he has his powers.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't believe me.
We're just, uh,
processing all of this, that's all. Okay?
CALLAHAN: Yeah.
How do you expect to stop the devil
if you don't believe he's real?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE PUTTERING]
[WATER GURGLING]
[JARRING MUSICAL STINGER PLAYS]
[THEME SONG PLAYING]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [RATTLING]
- [DISTANT YELLING, GRUNTING]
[SINISTER MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[YELLING AND GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING AUDIO DISTORTION]
- I can make it stop.
- [GASPING]
I can make the pain end.
Where's the girl?
[WEAKLY] I told you.
I don't...
I don't... I don't know.
There are two proposed explanations
for what is happening.
Explanation one,
an invisible boogeyman
from another dimension
is slaughtering these kids.
Explanation two,
Dr. Brenner's special little pet
has gone rogue again
and he and his lackeys
are now seeking to cover it up.
Perhaps in the hopes
of selling their pet to the Soviets.
Now,
which explanation sounds plausible to you?
Hmm?
[SOBS] I don't know.
There's still a chance
to redeem yourself, Mr. Wallace.
Where is she?
[SUSPENSEFUL AUDIO DISTORTION]
No! [WALLACE STRUGGLING]
No! No!
[GRUNTING]
No!
[DOOR SLAM ECHOES]
[EXHALES]
BRENNER: Do you know what happens
when someone has a stroke?
The blood supply to the brain is cut off.
It scrambles the signals in the brain
to the point where the mind
can forget how to do things.
To eat. To speak.
To walk.
When you were attacked last year,
I believe that your signals
were scrambled in much the same way.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
But just as a stroke victim
can learn to walk again,
I believe you, too,
can return to your full power.
Your abilities are still in here.
You just need to remember.
[BEEPING]
Everything that took place in my lab
was captured on videotape.
Every success and every failure.
It's important for you
to not just see your past,
but to fully re-experience it.
In doing so, I believe we can
repair your broken signals.
As we saw tonight,
that process has already begun.
[PLAYER WHIRRING]
If this all happened,
why don't I remember?
Because you do not want to.
Our brains have
a defense mechanism in place
to protect it from bad memories.
From trauma.
You buried these memories long ago.
ELEVEN: Papa.
When I was in there,
I saw something.
[EERIE DISTORTED AUDIO]
There was blood.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
So much blood.
That was another memory,
a... a more powerful one,
invading from your subconscious.
You have demons, Eleven.
You have demons in your past.
That is why we must proceed carefully.
One step at a time,
one memory at a time.
- [MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- If we go too fast,
I'm afraid you could
become lost in the darkness.
[TANK DOOR WHIRRING]
And if you are lost...
so are we all.
[DISCONCERTING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC FADES]
- [TOOLS WHIRRING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
WORKER: Oh.
Hey, Eric. I'm taking five.
You just took five.
Yeah, well, tell Milo
to take it easy on the onions next time.
[LAUGHS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO]
ROBIN: Not to be a wimp,
but can I sit in the car?
'Cause this is gonna
totally and royally suck.
It'll be fine.
I can't stand to see
those dull eyes of Eddie's break again.
I really, really can't.
At least he can drink himself
into feeling better.
That's what my mom does.
ROBIN: Why don't we give it a trial?
"Hey, Eddie.
Uh, good news first this time."
"We got you some Dustin-approved junk food
and that six-pack you requested."
"Oh yeah, and we found Vecna."
"Bad news is that he's in that other,
darker, much scarier dimension,
and the gate's closed,
so we have no way of getting to him."
"He's entirely shut off to us,
so basically you're screwed."
"And, no, I know
you were already screwed,
but now you're doubly, triply screwed."
Wait. Maybe we don't put it like that.
"We're one step closer to finding Vecna."
That's what we say.
That's what's important.
See, Robin? Positive spin
can make all the difference.
Uh-huh.
Oh shit.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
POWELL: Nothing to see.
- Just step back a little.
- [CROWD CLAMORING]
All right?
- This way.
- POWELL: As many of you know,
the Roane County line received a call
- a little after midnight...
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
...reporting a homicide here on the lake.
Officer Callahan here and myself
arrived first on the scene.
We made our way
to the shore of Lover's Lake,
about ten yards from that house
you see behind me.
It was there that we found the victim,
an 18-year-old senior from Hawkins High,
Patrick McKinney.
His limbs...
- Oh my God.
- ...his body, it was disfigured...
What are we even doing?
I mean, where is the FBI?
- There was an eyewitness on the scene...
- That's what I want to know.
We got a serial killer on the loose.
We have also identified
a person of interest.
Eddie Munson.
We encourage anyone with information
- to please come forward.
- Oh man.
- [REPORTERS CLAMORING]
- This is not good. Really not good.
POWELL: You've got a lot of questions,
and I'm going to answer as many as I can.
Two o'clock at town hall,
where anyone from the Hawkins community
is welcome. But right now,
I've got work to do,
and I appreciate your understanding.
REPORTER: Is Eddie still in Hawkins?
EDDIE: [ON RADIO] Dustin, can you hear me? Wheeler?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Eddie. Holy shit.
Are you okay?
Nah, man.
Pretty... Pretty goddamn far from okay.
- Where is he?
- Where are you?
- Skull Rock. Do you know it?
- Uh, yeah.
- That's near Cornwallis and...
- Garrett, yeah. I know where that is.
Hold tight. We're coming. We're coming.
[ARGYLE GRUNTS]
I can't feel my butt.
Can't feel my butt.
Can you guys feel your butts?
WILL: I can feel my butt.
Everyone needs to be
on their best behavior, okay?
ARGYLE: Why are you looking at me
when you say that?
- JONATHAN: I didn't.
- MIKE: They're just really religious.
Yeah, and I'm super spiritual, dude.
Yeah, I think they're spiritual too.
Just in a different way.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
MIKE: Oh. Hey.
Is Suzie here?
[SHRIEKS]
- Ow!
- [SHRIEKS]
[CHILDREN CLAMORING]
CHILD: Away, you starveling!
You elf-skin! You dried neat's tongue!
This is my kind of party.
I've been bitten.
Help! Help!
- Beautiful performance.
- JONATHAN: Excuse me.
Uh, hey, we're looking for Suzie.
[SNAPS ANGRILY]
[EMPHATICALLY] Can you not see
that we are filming?
DIRECTOR: Come on.
All right, stay in it, Tabitha.
Stay in it.
Hi, we're looking for Suzie.
Don't know, don't care.
That's too much salt, Peter.
Father's kidneys! Father's kidneys!
[BREAKER TRIPS]
WOMAN: Cornelius!
How many times do I have to tell you?
That is not a toy.
- [CORNELIUS GRUNTS]
- Come on.
You make another escape,
- I'm getting Father.
- [HISSES]
[TIMER WINDS, DINGS]
Who the hell are you?
Argyle.
Uh, and you are?
Eden.
- Like the garden.
- JONATHAN: Wow.
- We're looking for Suzie.
- Do you know where she is?
Third floor, second door on your left.
You make sure to give that selfish
four-eyed shit a nice little shove for me.
[SPLUTTERING] Absolutely.
Eden, I...
I will shove her for you. I will...
I will do anything for you.
[SIGHS] Well, great, she's not here.
[WINDOW CREAKING]
[CLATTERING]
"Give her a shove."
- MIKE: Suzie!
- Yeah?
Who the heck are you?
And what are you doing in my room?
- Sorry, that's... that's fair.
- No, listen.
- We're Dustin's friends.
- MIKE: Yeah.
We really need your help.
[BRAVE, PLUCKY CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[MURRAY SHIVERING]
You said an hour.
MURRAY: I underestimated.
JOYCE: I thought you were dead.
Might as well be.
We are truly in hell if hell froze over.
[MURRAY PANTING]
There's nothing south,
but two miles north I saw some smoke.
Could be a town, a house.
Maybe somebody there knows
where we can find this prison.
The top-secret prison.
Really?
Right.
[PANTING] Any luck with our friend?
What do you think?
[MURRAY CHUCKLES]
Hey!
Dipshit!
We're outta here. Last chance.
- Where's the prison?
- [JOYCE SIGHS]
I told you.
Yuri will help you for the right price.
I told you, we're wasting our time.
- Half.
- What?
- You heard me, you stubborn bastard.
Half the reward.
Twenty thousand.
- Thirty thousand.
- Twenty-two.
Twenty-five.
All right.
[YURI LAUGHS]
Looks like we got ourselves
a moron!
[MURRAY LAUGHS]
You thought I was serious?
He thought I was serious.
[IMITATING YURI] I got you!
I got you good!
[LAUGHING]
There's only one thing you get
if you take this deal.
You get to live.
You are not killer.
Oh, you're right.
He's not a killer.
No.
Thing is, we don't need to kill you.
We can just leave you here.
Because there's nothing for miles
- and no one will find you.
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
MURRAY: No human, at least.
- I saw tracks.
- Tracks.
MURRAY: In the woods, Yuri.
- Bears.
Who knew you could see your own future?
Shall we fly out of here, little bird?
Uh, da, da.
Bye-bye, Yuri.
[MURRAY LAUGHING]
Wait.
You should go east, not north.
My warehouse is there.
Supplies, guns, truck.
We will need to reach prison by nightfall
if you hope to save your friend.
That is, if he's not already dead.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[YURI LAUGHS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[IN RUSSIAN] Out.
Everyone out.
- [GUN COCKS]
- Let's go! Move it!
[IN ENGLISH] This is it, American.
I hope you're ready.
[IN RUSSIAN] What are you all waiting for?
Move!
Let's go!
[GRANDIOSE RUSSIAN OPERA PLAYING]
[IN ENGLISH] Am I dreaming, American?
Or is this real? [LAUGHING]
[LIPS SMACKING WETLY]
[IN RUSSIAN] What is wrong
with your American friend?
He has lost his spirit to live.
- [CHUCKLES]
- And he is not my friend.
[IN ENGLISH] Isn't that right, Cursed One?
You have lost your spirit to live.
Yeah. Yeah, something like that.
[CUP CLATTERS LOUDLY]
No...
[HOPPER CLATTERS]
[LAUGHING]
ANTONOV: [IN RUSSIAN] He is American after all.
Big talk, but weak inside.
Tell him to eat.
Or he endangers us all.
We have a big fight ahead of us.
What are you talking about? Fight?
I have been in this place one week.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
My first night,
I saw six men enter this room.
Six.
Just like us.
They came out
happy and fat, faces smothered in grease.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
But when night fell,
they were thrown into that pit out there.
But not alone.
You heard those roars, yes?
That is a monster.
- Not from this world.
- [INTENSE STINGER PLAYS]
[HOPPER GRUNTING]
Thirty seconds it took! Thirty seconds...
And all six men...
You speak no sense.
If they plan to kill us tonight,
why waste this food on us?
They want us strong.
So we can fight it.
To test its strength.
To train this monster for war.
But last week, the men got their weapons...
then scattered like fools.
We stick together...
Perhaps we stand a chance!
Perhaps we live to see another day.
ALL: Till tomorrow!
[MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
[IN ENGLISH] Let me guess.
This...
...it's about nine feet tall?
Thin, white skin?
No face?
No eyes?
[IN RUSSIAN]
Come on, come on, come on. Translate!
[TRANSLATES INTO RUSSIAN]
[EERIE, FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
How do you know this?
[IN ENGLISH] 'Cause I've seen one.
[ANTONOV TRANSLATES]
And I've fought one.
And all your theories about it,
they're all wrong.
[ANTONOV TRANSLATES]
You know why they feed
captive predators live prey?
[ANTONOV TRANSLATES]
Because if they don't, the predator
gets bored and it stops eating.
[ANTONOV TRANSLATES]
It needs the thrill of the hunt.
We're not here to train this monster
with swords and axes.
[ANTONOV TRANSLATES]
We're here to entertain it.
And this food...
this food isn't to make us strong.
It's to, uh, make us plump.
[CLATTERING]
So we're full of the nutrients and protein
that a growing monster might need.
[TRANSLATES INTO RUSSIAN]
HOPPER: So eat up, boys.
Enjoy.
This is your last meal.
[TRANSLATES INTO RUSSIAN]
[OMINOUS MUSIC SWELLS]
[CHIP CLATTERING]
[SIGHS]
[FRUSTRATED GRUNT]
Which number are you aiming for?
Three.
You know,
sometimes
it's helpful to take a step away
for a moment.
Let the mind clear.
[SIGHS]
[CHIP CLATTERING]
ORDERLY: Determined, aren't we?
- You know...
- [SIGHS]
...you remind me of someone.
Someone I used to know really well.
Can you guess who that is?
One?
- Papa said that he doesn't...
- Exist? I know.
[CAMERA WHIRRING]
[WHISPERS] But can I tell you a secret?
Sometimes,
Papa doesn't tell the truth.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
I spent years with One.
Right here.
In this very room.
Where is he?
Maybe we'll save that story
for another day.
It doesn't have a happy ending,
I'm afraid.
But he was a lot like you.
Everything was hard for him.
Then, out of nowhere,
he walked in here and it was like
something had changed.
And I asked him what's different,
and he said...
he said he had figured it out.
He had found his strength
in a memory from his past.
Something that made him sad.
But also angry.
Do you
maybe have a memory like that?
Do you remember the day
a strange woman came to see you?
This would've been
when Eight was still here.
[CHILDREN LAUGH]
The woman,
she was calling a name to you.
[MUFFLED] Jane. No! No!
No! Jane!
That
was your mother.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Mama is dead.
She died making me.
And who told you that?
Papa.
Who doesn't always tell the truth.
This place...
and the people here...
are not what you think.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Good morning, children.
- CHILDREN: Good morning, Papa.
I've got something very special
planned for you today.
Are you ready?
Yes, Papa.
Good.
Seventeen, would you open the door?
- Yes, Papa.
- Off you go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
After you.
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
We should've just told her the truth.
And risk everything?
No.
She'll find out soon enough.
STEVE: Dude, I'm telling you,
you're taking us the wrong way.
It's north. I'm positive.
I checked the map.
You do realize Skull Rock,
it's a super popular make-out spot?
Yeah. So?
Yeah, well, it wasn't popular
until I made it popular.
All right? I practically invented it.
- We're heading in the wrong direction.
- Steve.
- Where are you going? Steve!
- Stop whining. Let's go. Trust me.
MAX: Okay, so apparently
we're going this way now?
I swear to God, if they get us lost...
Hey.
You okay?
Uh, yeah.
I'm fine. Just...
thinking about Patrick. You know?
Yeah.
I mean, it's... it's like,
why him?
But then, I remember this one day,
he... he came to practice with a black eye.
He said he fell, but clearly he was lying.
It's like everyone Vecna targets
has something in their life.
- Something that's...
- Hurting them.
Haunting them.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah.
I... I didn't really know Patrick,
so it was easy to just
look the other way, I guess.
But I did know you.
And I'm sorry I wasn't there.
It's not your fault.
- No.
- I disappeared.
No, no, you didn't.
I just didn't look hard enough.
Okay?
But I see you now.
I see you.
[SCOFFS]
Oh my God, they're so adorable.
I just wanna squeeze 'em, you know?
If I'm permitted to see a silver lining
in this end-of-the-world doom and gloom,
it would be the rekindling of old flames
that never should've been snuffed out.
I didn't mean that as a hint or anything.
Right.
But if I did mean it as a hint,
would that be so terrible?
To wish for happiness for my friends?
[SCOFFS] You think I'm not happy?
I... I'm sure you are.
It's just, the other day,
I mentioned Jonathan
and you flinched
or winced or something like...
I didn't flinch or wince.
- Okay.
- Jonathan and I are fine.
- Got it.
- We're good.
Right.
It's just...
[NANCY SIGHS]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
He was supposed to be here for the break,
and then he backed out at the last minute
for some vague, mumbly Jonathan reason.
And, to be honest, I'm not that surprised
because I've been
feeling him pulling away.
And I don't know
if it's because we're 2,000 miles away
or if he met someone new or what.
And now I can't find out why
because apparently he's blown up
his family's house phone or something.
So, yeah, if... if the mention of his name
caused a slight muscle spasm on my face,
that's... probably why.
Seems like a perfectly reasonable reason
to flinch, wince, or something.
You said, "the happiness of your friends."
So does that make us friends?
As in, officially?
Uh, yeah. I... I mean, right?
Right.
STEVE: Oh, boom!
Bada bing, bada boom.
There she is, Henderson.
Skull Rock.
In your face, man.
In your stupid, cocky little face.
Doesn't make sense.
Yeah, yeah. Even with it staring you
in the face, you can't admit it.
Can't admit you're wrong, you butthead.
EDDIE: I concur.
You, Dustin Henderson, are a...
total butthead.
Jesus, we thought you were a goner.
Yeah, me too, man.
Me too.
How long have you known
Eddie was killing these kids?
It was his trailer
where Chrissy was killed,
and you expect us to believe
he was made a suspect just this morning?
The truth is we've been
following several leads,
and, yes, Eddie Munson was one of them.
And we are now doing everything
in our power to find him.
[ALL CLAMORING]
POWELL: In the meantime, for your safety,
we will be enforcing a strict curfew.
- What?
- That's your solution?
- Hide from him?
- We're already doing that.
It's been days. Days!
So you tell me why
he's not behind bars right now.
I understand you all are upset,
but I promise you,
we will find him.
JASON: No.
[CROWD FALLS SILENT]
You won't.
Jason?
Son, how about
we talk about this in private?
Why? So you can keep me quiet?
So you can keep the truth from coming out?
I don't know about the rest of you,
but I can't bear to listen
to any more excuses and lies.
- That's enough.
- I agree, I've had enough!
[SCATTERED YELLING]
In fact, I think we've all had enough.
[APPLAUSE]
[MICROPHONE FEEDBACK]
Last night...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Last night, I saw things,
things I can't explain.
Things the police don't wanna believe.
And things that
I don't wanna believe myself.
But I know what I saw. I know.
And I've come to accept an awful truth.
- These murders are ritualistic sacrifices.
- [CROWD GASPING]
We've all heard how satanic cults
are spreading through our country
like some... some disease.
And Eddie Munson
is the leader of one of these cults.
A cult that operates here in Hawkins.
The mall fire.
All those unexplained deaths
over the years.
Some people say our town is cursed.
They just don't know why.
Now... Now we do.
Now we know.
They call themselves Hellfire.
That's bullshit!
The Hellfire isn't a cult.
It's a club for nerds.
- MRS. SINCLAIR: Erica!
- Just the facts.
JASON: A club.
A club. A harmless club.
That's what they want you to think.
But it's a lie.
A lie designed to conceal the truth.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
And now this cult
is protecting its leader, Eddie.
Hiding him.
Allowing him to... to continue his rampage.
Last night, I became overcome
with this feeling of... of hopelessness.
Then I remembered Romans 12:21.
"Do not be overcome by evil."
"But overcome evil with good."
And God knows there's good in this town.
So much good. It's in this room!
It's in this room, right here, right now.
So I came here today, humbly,
to ask for your help.
To join me in this fight.
Let us cast out this evil
and save Hawkins together.
[CROWD MURMURS QUIETLY]
[CROWD SHIFTS UNEASILY]
What are y'all just sitting around for?
You heard the kid.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
POWELL: Hey.
I want you all to hear me
loud and clear on this.
Anyone interfering with this investigation
will be arrested.
Hey! Hey!
We will be implementing a curfew.
If you are not in your house after sunset
with the doors locked,
you'll be written up.
And it's gonna go
on your permanent record.
SUZIE: Okay, that is a lot to process.
I mean, that might be seriously
the craziest thing I've ever heard.
I know, it's hard to believe.
But it's true. All true.
I dial in to this computer
and find a location,
and at this location is the Nina Project?
Exactly.
And the Nina Project
is the code name for a video game?
No, it's not just a video game.
It's a video game console.
It's basically America's answer
to Nintendo.
Americantendo.
That's a stupid name.
You're right, it is a stupid name,
but, Suzie, it's 16-bit.
Sixteen-bit?
- Why have I never heard of it?
- Because it's top secret.
- That's why we're doing this.
- Yeah, right. It's for the promotion.
The first people to find
the secret location receive a...
- Americantendo?
- Uh, an Americantendo.
So you drove 3,000 miles
over your spring break
so I can help you get
a new video game console
no one has ever heard of?
ALL: Yes.
[SCOFFS]
- But it's not for us. It's for Dustin.
- Right.
Exactly. It's for Dustin.
For Dustin's birthday, which is...
In two months, three days, five hours.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- I don't know what you're doing,
but I am not spending
my entire day babysitting.
- Pull your damn weight.
- Language!
Oh no, am I gonna burn in hell now?
You tell her, Eden.
- Out of my room.
- Don't touch me, you little shit!
- [SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
- Okay, so can you help?
I would do anything for Dustybun,
but I'm afraid there's been
an unfortunate development.
After changing Dusty's grade,
I was wracked with the most awful guilt.
Suzie, I am incredibly disappointed.
Father could see my soul was tortured,
and he wrenched a confession out of me.
I wanted to help him.
Not only was I breaking the law,
I was dating an agnostic.
An agnostic!
- I've never seen Father so angry.
- ...starting today.
He needed me.
- Naturally...
- Father, no!
...after learning the terrible truth,
he confiscated my computer.
And Father is not one to change his mind.
I'm as likely to see it again
as I am my poor Dustybun.
Where is it?
His study.
He uses it for work now.
And Father's always working,
and his door is, like, permanently locked.
- [WILL SCOFFS]
- I'm really sorry.
Truly.
But it looks like you came
all the way here for nothing.
- [BREAKER POWERING DOWN]
- EDEN: Cornelius!
- [CORNELIUS SHRIEKS]
- [BREAKER POWERING UP]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Unless...
Unless?
There might be a way.
But we're gonna need help.
And I mean a lot of help.
All right.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys?
Are you down here?
[PANTS] They should've been back by now.
They should be back.
- What time was the movie?
- Uh, four hours ago.
Hate to break it to you, Mrs. Wheeler,
but they lied to you.
- ♪ Liar, liar, pants on fire ♪
- Holly.
We don't think they're actually involved
with Eddie, do we?
I think at this point,
anything's possible.
- Our children are not murderers, Ted.
- Don't put words in my mouth.
See, she does that, twists my words.
- You're calling the theater?
- [KEYPAD BEEPING]
- [INHALES] The police.
- [LINE RINGING]
When I got to the shore,
I tried calling you guys, but, uh...
my walkie was busted, man.
Drenched.
So, uh, I did the thing
that I do now, apparently.
I ran. [CHUCKLES]
Do you know what time this was?
The attack?
Yeah, no, I... I know
exactly what time it was.
My walkie wasn't the only thing
that got soaked.
- 9:27.
- Same time our flashlights went kablooey.
Which means what, exactly?
That that surge of energy
was Vecna attacking Patrick.
ROBIN: Well, we're one step closer.
We know how Vecna attacks.
And where he attacks from.
So now we just need to sneak into
his lair in the Upside Down
and drive a stake through his heart.
If he has a heart.
A stake? Is he like a vamp?
Is he a vampire?
- It was a metaphor.
- A bullet should work on him, right?
I say we chop his head off.
All of the above,
but we can't do any of that
- 'til we find a way into the Upside Down.
- We need El to get her powers back.
Everything was way easier.
We had this girl. She had superpowers.
Superpowers. Yeah, you mentioned her.
Hey, uh, Henderson's not,
uh, cursed, is he?
STEVE: Cursed? No, no. He's fine.
- [MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mental? Absolutely.
Boom! [ECHOES]
Bada... bada... boom.
I was right.
Skull Rock was north.
- Seriously? You're serious?
- Mm-hmm.
- This is Skull Rock. Okay?
You're totally, absolutely,
100% wrong. Right now.
Yes.
And no.
Oh my God.
This worked correctly
when we left the Wheelers'.
Correct when we got in the car on Curly.
But it started to slip
the further east we went.
Now it's way off.
When I was leading us here,
I wasn't wrong.
The compass was.
So you're using faulty equipment.
You're still wrong.
Except it isn't faulty.
Lucas, remember what can affect a compass?
- An electromagnetic field.
- Yep.
Sorry. I must've skipped that class.
In the presence
of a stronger electromagnetic field,
the needle will deflect
towards that power.
So either there's some
super big magnet around here, or...
There's a gate.
But we're nowhere near the lab.
But what if, somehow,
there's another gate?
A gate that we don't know about.
It'd have to be smaller.
Way less powerful.
- Snack-size gate.
- How? Why?
No idea. All I know is that something
is causing this disturbance,
and the last time we've seen
anything like it, it was a gate.
And I hope it is
because then we'd have a way to Vecna.
And a shot at freeing Max from this curse.
STEVE: Where are you going?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Eddie's still a wanted man.
We can't just go hike in the woods.
This little steel capsule might be the key
to saving both Max and Eddie.
What say you, Eddie the Banished?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC TRAILS OFF]
I say you're asking me
to follow you into Mordor,
which, if I'm totally straight with you,
I think is a really bad idea.
But, uh, the Shire...
the Shire is burning.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
So Mordor it is.
What is Mordor?
Get your stuff, dude. Let's go.
[MUSIC FADES]
BRENNER: Today,
we are going to play a game.
The rules of the game are quite simple.
Stay in your circle.
If you leave your circle,
you lose.
The last person standing in their circle
will get to spend
an extra hour of free time
in the rainbow room.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BRENNER CHUCKLES]
Now, even though we are going to be
competing against one another...
Two.
Six.
...I don't want you to approach this
any differently than one of our tests.
Yeah?
Now, this is very important.
If you allow anger or emotion
to invade your thoughts,
you will fail.
I promise.
Do you understand?
CHILDREN: Yes, Papa.
Good.
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [TOES CRACK]
[EXHALES]
Begin.
[TWO INHALES]
[ENERGY THRUMMING]
[THRUMMING INTENSIFIES]
- [GRUNTS]
- [CLATTERING]
[EXHALES]
Very good, Two.
Number Six,
please,
take a seat by the door.
[INHALES]
Five.
[PULSATING INDUSTRIAL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENERGY THRUMMING]
- Ah!
- [BONES CRACKING]
- [INTENSE AUDIO DISTORTION]
[CONTESTANTS GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
- [INTENSE AUDIO DISTORTION]
- [SHRIEKS]
Eleven.
[EXHALES]
[INDUSTRIAL MUSIC PULSES, FADES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Good luck.
Begin.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[BOTH STRAINING]
[GROANS]
[THUD ECHOES]
ORDERLY: He'd found his strength
in a memory from his past.
Something that made him sad,
but also angry.
Do you have a memory like that?
[MUFFLED] Jane. No! No!
No!
[ELEVEN YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
- [MUSIC SUBSIDES]
- [TWO GROANS]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
BRENNER: Well, well.
It looks like we have a new winner.
[TRIUMPHANT SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
YURI: I present you... Kyrzran.
You see that gray steeple over there?
That is Yuri's warehouse.
JOYCE: Looks like a church.
Let's see what miracles it holds, yes?
Oh. [TUTS]
Someone has been in my peanut butter.
Very popular, as I say, eh? [CHUCKLES]
Weapons.
Where are the weapons?
- Oh Jesus.
- Hey. Not in a church.
You like all this?
Wait until you see my flamethrower.
We don't have time for show-and-tell.
We need to get going.
She's always this bossy?
You heard her.
[GUN COCKS]
Keys, map.
[GUN CLICKS]
Let's go.
YURI: So, prison is here.
Between these two mountains.
Approximately two-hour drive.
I don't see anything.
Because it's not on the map,
but it is there.
How do we know
you're not leading us into some trap?
Because I do not need to.
You want to break into
deadliest prison in all motherland.
[CHUCKLES] It is suicide.
Who said anything about breaking in?
Oh. You just expect to knock?
"Oh hello, let me in.
I'm friendly American with a big beard."
[WHEEZING LAUGHTER]
Something like that, actually, yes.
MURRAY: You were planning
to turn us over to the warden.
Today, if I'm not mistaken.
Ah, I see now.
I bring you in as prisoners
and then set you free inside walls.
It is risky, crazy,
you will still probably die,
yet I like it.
But for this to work, Yuri cannot be tied.
Hey, it's hard to turn over prisoners
when I'm a prisoner myself.
Hey, I think the warden
might find that suspicious.
Which is why, from here on out,
you're gonna be Murray.
And I'm gonna be Yuri.
I don't follow.
Don't worry.
It's a silent role.
[CHUCKLES] Ah!
[METAL SWOOSHING]
You want to make a fool of yourself,
go ahead.
But to bring down these men,
leaving them with no hope,
what is the purpose of that?
I tell them truth.
You feed their delusion.
Not delusions. Hope.
I believe we can fight.
I believe we can win.
I have a son, Mikhail.
I cannot leave this world with him
believing his father is a traitor.
I need to get back to him,
and I will get back to him.
- Is he slow?
- What?
Mikhail, your son.
Is... Is he slow? Is he stupid?
[IN RUSSIAN] Stop talking.
[IN ENGLISH]
No, he's very smart. Top of his class.
[IN RUSSIAN] Be silent!
[IN ENGLISH] Then you're not his father.
[IN RUSSIAN] I said go!
[IN ENGLISH] You are drunk, American.
I would stop speaking
unless you wish to die sooner.
I can. It doesn't matter.
I know I'm gonna die today.
But guess what?
I know who I am and what I've done,
unlike you and these men,
who can't face the truth.
That you're the reason
why we're in here. You're gonna die.
[IN RUSSIAN] Come on, go!
[IN ENGLISH] Your son is not your son...
[IN RUSSIAN] I said to be silent!
- [IN ENGLISH]...and your wife...
- [PRISONERS CLAMORING]
Come on! Come on!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[PRISON SIRENS WAILING]
[GRUNT ECHOING]
[COUGHS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[HOPPER COUGHS]
[IN RUSSIAN] You do that again...
we shoot you on the spot.
- Fools.
- [HOPPER GRUNTS]
- [IN ENGLISH] You happy now, American?
- [COUGHS]
Was that worth it?
- [ANTONOV GRUNTS, GROANS]
- [HOPPER EXHALES]
We call it a Demogorgon.
I don't know how they got it here
or what they're doing with it, but...
everything I said about it's true.
Except it has one weakness.
[DRAMATIC SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
Fire.
Hates fire.
So I figure, if we want a shot
at killing this thing,
we need some fuel.
And I need something to light it with.
So you asked me if it was worth it?
To answer your question... [BLOWS]
...yeah, I think it was worth it.
- [CHUCKLES] You son of a bitch.
- [HOPPER LAUGHS]
You son of a bitch.
Don't make me laugh.
My ribs are broken. Don't make me laugh.
[RAUCOUS LAUGHTER]
[HOPPER GROANS]
[MUSIC SUBSIDES]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[BREAKER POWERING DOWN]
[GRUMBLES]
Cornelius?
[DOOR OPENS]
- Cornelius?
- [CORNELIUS SHRIEKS]
Cornelius!
[CORNELIUS YELLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
- Wait, where's Argyle?
- Shit, I don't know.
And three, two...
- Oh my God.
- [COMPUTER WHIRRING]
Way to go, Cornelius.
- [CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KEYPAD BEEPING]
Away, you mouldy rogue! Away!
And we're in.
Holy sh... heck.
Oh holy heck. You did it.
Hold your applause.
I don't see an address.
"Office." Try "office."
[COMPUTER TRILLING]
What is all this?
- Tanner, Tatum, out of the way!
- [TANNER AND TATUM GIGGLE]
[ELECTRICITY SPARKS]
- [THWIP]
- Cornelius.
- [HISSES]
- [FIRE CRACKLES]
[YELLS]
- [COMPUTER TRILLING]
- Maybe it's hidden in the code?
- What you just said makes no sense.
- Hold your butts. I'll trace the IP.
The... The I-what?
SUZIE: The internet protocol address.
It's a unique numerical label
given to all information technology
connected to the Internet.
- What's the Internet?
- Don't worry about it.
It's just gonna change the world.
What's happening now?
I'm running the IP
through a geolocation software.
Basically a form of data mining.
[EXTINGUISHER GUSHING]
[TABITHA GURGLING]
Tabitha!
Tabitha?
Tabitha. Oh no. [WHIMPERS]
And cut!
Incredible. Just incredible.
And, Father, your terror.
It looked genuine.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC CRESCENDOS]
SUZIE: Bingo.
ALL: Nevada?
Can you print this?
No, my skills end at IP geolocation.
[PRINTER WHIRRING]
You were being sarcastic.
Yeah.
These kids are gonna
drive me to the loony bin.
Hi, Father. You look like you need a nap.
Slow down!
[MIKE PANTING]
Dustin's right.
You're a certified genius.
I think we just spooked a skunk.
["PASS THE DUTCHIE" PLAYING]
♪ Pass the Dutchie
'Pon the left-hand side... ♪
Yo.
My dudes.
Any luck?
♪ Give me the music
Make me jump and prance ♪
- [RAUCOUS ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TRUCK PASSENGERS WHOOPING]
You see that, Chief? Openly mocking us.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
A bunch of angry, armed vigilantes
are out hunting kids,
openly defying us,
and you want me to stay calm.
Stay calm. Yeah.
OFFICER: [ON RADIO] Hey, Chief, you copy?
Yeah, I copy.
Found their station wagon
hidden up by Skull Rock.
No sign of them though.
- Skull Rock?
- POWELL: Yeah.
- Isn't that a make-out spot?
- And a stone's throw from Lover's Lake.
The hell they wanna go back there for?
One way to find out.
Hold tight. On our way.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIREN WAILING]
Something's happening.
Dustin? Can you slow down? Dustin?
I think we're getting close.
Watch your step, big guy.
STEVE: Oh man.
- You gotta be shitting me.
- Yeah.
- I thought these woods were familiar.
- ROBIN: Lover's Lake.
DUSTIN: This is confounding.
There's a gate in Lover's Lake?
Whenever the Demogorgon attacked,
it always left an opening.
Maybe Vecna's the same way.
Yeah, only one way to find out.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Easy. I... I said easy, man.
- EDDIE: Sorry, dude.
- Here you go.
- Yeah, I'm just gonna do that.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, that works too.
Good, you got her.
- Wheeler.
- Thanks.
Hey, hey, hey, you trying to sink us?
This thing holds three people tops, okay?
It's better this way, okay?
You guys stay here with Max.
- Keep an eye out for trouble.
- You keep an eye out.
- It's my goddamn theory.
- You heard Nance.
- Who put her in charge?
- I did.
Compass.
Hey, there you go.
DUSTIN: Ow.
You said three.
[WHISPERS] Sorry.
Bedtime at nine, kiddos.
Miss you already!
[CHIP CLATTERING]
[SIGHS]
- [CLATTERING STOPS]
- [SIGHS]
[DISTANT SCREAMING]
BOY: Please!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISTANT SCREAMING, STRUGGLING]
- BOY: Please, please...
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[BOY STRAINING, YELLING]
[BODY SCREECHING]
[ELEVEN PANTS]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
TWO: You shouldn't be
wandering the halls.
[MENACING STINGER PLAYS]
GIRL: It's against the rules.
TWO: And not safe.
You shamed me today.
- [ELEVEN PANTS] I'm sorry.
- I didn't wanna hurt you.
You are weak
and pathetic.
I was holding back.
And then you do that before everyone?
Before Papa?
- [INHALES] No.
- [DRAMATIC STINGER PLAYS]
[ELEVEN GRUNTS]
[ELEVEN SOBS]
[LABORED BREATHING]
How'd that feel?
Did you like that?
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYING]
See a light?
I don't.
Something must've happened to the power.
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
- [INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHILDREN GRUNTING]
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
ELEVEN: Stop it! No! [SCREAMS]
No!
- [GRUNTS]
- [UNSETTLING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[ELEVEN WHIMPERS, SIGHS]
Tell Papa we did this,
we will kill you.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SOBS]
[BULLIES LAUGHING]
GIRL: Aw, feeling a little dizzy there?
Poor baby.
[CHUCKLES]
[DISEMBODIED DISTANT SCREAM]
[UNSETTLING RATTLING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
[PANTING]
[UNSETTLING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
BRENNER: What have you done?
What have you done?
- [HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
- OWENS: Okay, easy. Deep breaths.
Take deep breaths.
You did well, Eleven.
You did very well.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
- [EERIE STINGER PLAYS]
- [ELEVEN PANTING]
I know what happened now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I killed them, didn't I, Papa?
[UNSETTLING AUDIO DISTORTION]
I killed them all.
Okay. Shh.
[SOBS] I killed them all.
[OMINOUS MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC SUBSIDES]
[ROBIN EXHALES]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down.
Slow down, guys.
[NANCY GRUNTS]
[COMPASS FLICKING]
- Whoa.
- Wait, wait, wait.
They're stopping.
What are they stopping for?
Guys, what's going on?
Come on, talk to me.
What's going on?
Uh, Dustin, your compass has gone
from wonky to wonky with a capital "aah!"
Steve, what are you doing?
Somebody's gotta go down
and check this out.
Unless one of you three can top
being a Hawkins High swim co-captain
and a certified lifeguard
for three years, then...
it's gotta be me.
No complaints, all right?
Hey, I'm not complaining.
I do not wanna go down there.
LUCAS: Ugh.
- When'd Steve get so hairy?
- Right?
I keep telling him
he needs to tame that jungle,
but he claims the ladies dig it.
MAX: Let me see.
LUCAS: What?
Hey.
Good luck.
Thanks.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
ROBIN: Gross.
- [STEVE BREATHING STEADILY]
- NANCY: Steve?
Be careful.
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC SUBSIDES]
You guys realize,
if there's a gate down there,
it's technically a water gate.
[OWL HOOTING]
Watergate.
[CHUCKLES]
Where we at, Wheeler?
- Closing in on a minute.
- ROBIN: Okay.
[ROBIN EXCLAIMS]
Come on, Steve. Come on.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
- OFFICER: Down by the water!
- Shit. Down!
Shit. Shit.
OFFICER: It was on this shoreline.
[MUSIC SUBSIDES]
[EERIE SOUNDS EMANATING FROM FISSURE]
[WATER GURGLING]
[FISSURE GURGLING]
[JARRING STINGER PLAYS]
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
[EDDIE CLEARS THROAT]
[WATER GUSHES LOUDLY]
Oh Christ!
I found it.
- You found it?
- I found it. Yeah. I found it.
- [STEVE PANTING]
- Dustin, you are a goddamn Einstein.
- Steve found the gate...
- [SIREN WAILING]
- MAX: Cops.
- Shit, shit, shit.
We can't let 'em find Eddie.
Stay with me.
Hey, officers!
- Max!
- Over here! I found the killer! This way!
- Shit.
- Go!
It's pretty wild.
It's more a snack-size gate
than the mama gate,
but still, it's pretty damn big.
[ALL CLAMORING]
[ALL YELLING]
Steve!
- Steve! Steve!
- EDDIE: No! No!
- What the hell was that, man?
- Nancy, really, what happened?
EDDIE: Jesus!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STEVE STRAINS]
[YELLS, GRUNTS]
[CREATURE YAPPING]
OFFICER: Stop!
Get back here, you little rats!
[GRUNTS]
Wait, wait, wait.
- You're not going in there, are you?
- Just wait here.
- No, Nancy!
- Nancy!
EDDIE: Goddamn it!
[SCREAMING]
Dustin! Shit.
Hey there.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing? She said wait.
Yeah, I heard her.
She's in charge.
Are you kidding me?
I made that shit up.
Don't you go. Don't you...
Goddamn it...
Son of a bitch!
Oh, this is so stupid.
This is so stupid.
This is so stupid. Shit! Shit! Shit!
[PANTING]
[CREATURES SNARLING, BAYING]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CREATURE SNARLING]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[CREATURE SQUAWKING]
[TENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[SHRIEKING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[CHOKING, STRUGGLING]
[CREATURE CHITTERING]
[STRAINING]
[CREATURE CHITTERS]
[CREATURES BITING WETLY]
- [STEVE SCREAMS]
- [CHITTERING CONTINUES]
[SCREAMING ECHOES]
- [THUNDER RUMBLES]
- [SINISTER MUSIC DIMINISHES]
[RASPY AUDIO DISTORTIONS]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
[MENACING INDUSTRIAL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TRAILS]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44