[PEACEFUL BIRDSONG]
[DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[WHEELS RATTLING]
[DOG BARKS]
[BIRDSONG]
[NEWSPAPER THUDS]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
[TIMER WINDS, TICKS]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
[TIMER DINGS]
[RAZOR SCRAPES]
[DOORS GRINDING]
[FABRIC STRETCHING]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPINNING TOPS RATTLING]
[CHIP CLACKING]
[BALL RATTLING]
That's your favorite, isn't it?
[BRENNER SIGHS]
How are you feeling today?
Okay.
Are you up for some more lessons?
[DOOR CLANGING]
Afternoon, Dr. Brenner.
Dr. Ellis.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Okay.
What do you see?
[FAINT BUZZING]
[SHARP SCREECHING]
Don't force it.
Let it come to you.
Just like we practiced.
- It's...
- [SHARP SCREECH]
...a yellow circle.
The sun.
Very good. Very good.
All right. Now, let's see...
Okay.
[CRAYON CLATTERS]
Now what do you see?
A...
cow?
It's supposed to be a dog.
It looks like a cow.
[CHUCKLES]
It does, doesn't it?
I never was much of an artist.
All right. Let's try something
a little bit more challenging.
Is that all right with you?
I want you to find Dr. Ellis.
Can you do that?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Have you found her?
[ECHOING] Yes.
What's she doing?
Lessons with Six in his room.
What kind of lessons?
Six is trying to move a block.
- A red block.
- [DEVICE WHIRRING]
Can you hear what they're saying?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
Something's wrong.
If you've lost the visual, just let it go.
Try to reorient.
[SHRILL SCREAM]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
They're screaming.
Why are they screaming?
[INTENSE MUSICAL FLOURISH]
Ten?
[ALARM KLAXON WAILING]
- Peter, Alec, what's going on out there?
- [MAN]Sir, we've got a situation.
[GUNSHOT]
[TEN] Six and Dr. Ellis...
Dead.
They're both dead.
- [BANGING ON DOOR]
- [SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSICAL FLOURISH]
[DISTORTED SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BRENNER GRUNTING]
- [ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[SHOCKED GASP]
[GRUNTING]
[SHRILL SCREAMING]
[MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [DOOR SLAMS]
[DISTORTED MUSICAL FLOURISHES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What have you done?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
["CALIFORNIA DREAMIN'"
BY THE MAMAS &AMP; THE PAPAS PLAYING]
[ELEVEN]Dear Mike,
Today is day 185.
[CHUCKLES]Feels more like ten years.
Joyce says time is funny like that.
Emotions can make it
speed up or slow down.
We are all time travelers
if you think about it.
For example, this week is going very fast.
I think because I am so busy.
I have to make something
called a visual aid.
I hope Mrs. Gracey will give me an A.
[JOYCE] I can send you
a previous edition as a loaner
to see if you like the product
before committing to purchasing it...
[ELEVEN]Some exciting news.
Joyce got an amazing new job.
She gets to work at home.
Yeah, I'm... I'm not a robot.
You do realize that, don't you?
[ELEVEN]She says she loves the "freedom."
Prick.
[ELEVEN]Will is painting a lot,
but he... he won't show me
what he's working on.
Maybe it is for a girl.
I think there is someone he likes,
because he has been acting
weird.
[WATER BUBBLES]
Jonathan is acting weird also.
- I think he is just nervous about college.
- [JONATHAN COUGHING]
He is still waiting for his big letter.
- [BLOWING]
- I hope he and Nancy get to go together.
Damn it.
But I don't know how he'll get to college
because his car is still broken.
- [VAN HORN HONKING]
- [BRAKES SCREECHING]
[ELEVEN]His funny friend Argyle
has been taking us to school.
His hair is longer than mine.
And he and Jonathan
like to smoke smelly plants together.
Jonathan says the plants are super safe
because they come from the earth,
but to not tell Joyce.
[ELEVEN CHUCKLES]Me?
I am twice as happy now.
You were right. It just takes time.
[ARGYLE] All right.
Hold on to your butts, brochachos.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[ELEVEN]I think I have finally adapted.
Slow down!
- ♪ California dreamin' ♪
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
♪ Stopped into a church... ♪
[ELEVEN]At first,
I missed all the spring flowers,
but now I find it pretty here too.
- ♪ Well, I got down on my knees ♪
- ♪ Got down on my knees ♪
- ♪ And I pretend to pray ♪
- ♪ I pretend to pray... ♪
[ELEVEN]I even like school now.
I am still best at math,
but my grammar is getting good now also.
♪ California dreamin' ♪
- [SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
- ♪ California dreamin' ♪
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
[ELEVEN]It helps
that everyone is so nice here.
I have made lots of friends.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Even so, I am ready for spring break,
mostly because I get to see you.
I am so excited to see you,
it is hard to breathe.
Are you excited too?
I think you will love it here like me.
I think we will have
the best spring break ever.
- [SPITBALL SQUELCHES]
- ♪ All the leaves are brown ♪
[GIRL LAUGHS]
♪ And the sky is gray ♪
- ♪ I've been for a walk ♪
- ♪ I've been for a walk... ♪
[ELEVEN]I hope my spelling
was better this time.
Miss you.
Love, El.
[DOOR CLATTERS]
- The hell are you doing? It's ten after.
- Oh, shit. Shit!
Thirty seconds
or I'm leaving without you, okay?
Thirty seconds.
Okay, I have to find my pants.
[ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Michael, I know your D&amp;D club is tonight.
- Hellfire.
Why don't you call it
the High School Dropout Club?
- I want you home no later than 9:00.
- I'll try.
- No trying. You need to go to bed early.
- Why?
- It's a 6:30 flight, Michael.
- Yeah, I know, but...
No buts. Nine or no California.
And no sweetie pie.
[NANCY] Mike!
Let's go.
Jesus. How am I gonna survive
a whole week without you guys?
[DOOR OPENS]
Nine.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Remind me, when do they become
reasonable human beings again?
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[SUZIE]That's a negative, Dustybun.
Son of a bitch.
Try "Tigers86."
"Tigers86." Copy that.
[COMPUTER TRILLING]
Jiminy crickets, Dusty. I'm in.
Holy shit.
[POUNDING AT DOOR]
What's going on in there?
You're gonna be late.
Don't come in! I'm naked!
I'm running out of time here.
Just hold your horsies, Dustybun.
Do you see it?
Yeah, I see it.
Yikes, Dusty.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
I will repent later.
Then there's Heidi tomorrow night,
but the problem with Heidi
is that she's going
out of state for college.
Do I wanna start another relationship
that has no point other than sex?
I mean, I don't know.
Does that make sense to you?
- Robin, are you listening?
- Uh, yes.
- What did I just say?
- Something about sex with Linda.
No, I'm talking about Heidi.
- Cut me some slack, please.
- Well...
Your love life
is one of labyrinthine complexity.
It is 7:00 in the morning,
we have the stupid pep rally,
and I woke up looking like a corpse.
You're worried about a pep rally?
Expect me to believe that?
- Yeah? So?
- So we both know what this is about.
- Not buying that. This is about Vickie.
- Absolutely not.
- It is. You know what else?
- I don't care...
You gotta stop pretending to be
someone else when you're around her.
You just gotta be yourself.
You're literally quoting me to me.
You do realize that.
Maybe you need to listen to yourself.
Ever think about that?
I listened. Look at me.
Boom. Back in business.
- It's not the same thing. Okay?
- Well...
You ask out a girl and she says no.
Big deal. Nothing happens.
Maybe your ego's a little bruised.
I ask out the wrong girl,
and bam, I'm a town pariah.
I'd buy that, except Vickie
is definitely not the wrong girl.
We just don't know that, do we?
She returnedFast Times
paused at 53 minutes, 5 seconds.
Know who pausesFast Times
at 53 minutes, 5 seconds?
- People who like boobies, Robin.
- Ew!
- Gross. Don't say boobies.
- Boobies.
Not a big deal, okay?
I like boobies. You like boobies.
Vickie likes boobies. Definitely.
["OBJECT OF MY DESIRE"
BY STARPOINT PLAYING]
It's boobies.
♪ On and on and on and on ♪
♪ Jump! ♪
- [TEACHER] To the gym, everyone.
- Hey, wait up!
[TEACHER] Pep rally! Pep rally!
Kyle, good to see you. [LAUGHS]
Hey, Josh.
To the gym, everyone. To the gym.
Go support your Tigers! Go, Tigers!
To the gym! Hi, Amber.
Max! Max!
[SONG VOLUME DECREASES]
Where were you yesterday?
Oh, yeah. Sorry, I forgot it was Thursday.
I'd like to see you today.
Come straight after lunch, okay?
[MARCHING BAND DRUM PLAYING]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[MARCHING BAND PLAYING]
Look, I'm not saying
that my girlfriend is better than yours.
It's just that Suzie's,
like, a certified genius.
You do realize El
saved the world twice, right?
And yet you still have a C in Spanish.
[ANNOUNCER]
And let's hear it for your Tigers!
Whoo!
[MARCHING BAND DRUM PLAYING]
Good morning, Hawkins High!
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
First off... Hey.
First off, I'd like to thank
each and every one of you.
Without your support, we wouldn't be here.
Give yourselves a big hand.
[CHEERING]
[MICROPHONE FEEDBACK WHINES]
[PLAYER] And of course, of course,
I have to give a special shout-out
to the best
and the prettiest fans of all time,
the Tiger Cheer Squad.
[STUDENT] Yeah!
Chrissy...
Chrissy, I love you, babe.
[CROWD] Aww!
You know...
I think I can
speak for all of us when I say
it's been a tough year for Hawkins.
So much loss.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
And sometimes I wonder,
"How much loss can one community take?"
In dark days like this,
we need something to believe in.
So, last night,
when we were down by ten points at half
to Christian Academy,
I looked at my team,
and I said,
"Think of Jack."
"Think of Melissa."
"Think of Heather."
"Think of Billy."
"Think about our heroic police chief,
Jim Hopper."
"Think about every one of our friends
who perished in that fire."
"What did they die for?"
"For us to lose
to some... some crap school?"
- "No."
- [CROWD] No!
"For us to return home
with our heads hung low in defeat?"
- "No!"
- No!
"No."
"Let's win this game."
"Let's win this game for them."
And that's exactly what we did!
[ALL CHEERING]
[HOPEFUL MUSIC BUILDING]
We embarrassed those candy-asses
in their own house,
and now tonight, tonight,
we're gonna bring home
the championship trophy!
Let's go!
Tonight?
- How is that possible?
- [MAX] They call it a tournament.
You win one game, you go on
until there's only one team left.
I don't get the big deal.
Just talk to Eddie.
Get him to move Hellfire to another night.
"Just talk to Eddie."
Why don't you justtalk to your coach
and get him to move the game?
- I think that's a great idea, Mike.
- Thank you, Dustin.
- This is the championship game.
- And this is the end of Eddie's campaign.
A semester of adventuring
has led to this moment, and we need you.
Yeah, and the Tigers don't.
You've been on the bench all year.
- That's not the point.
- Please, arrive at the point.
If I get in good with these guys,
I'll be in the popular crowd,
and then you guys will be too.
Has it ever occurred to you
that we don't want to be popular?
You wanna be stuck with the nerds
and freaks for three more years?
We arenerds and freaks.
But maybe we don't have to be.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Look, I'm tired of being bullied.
I'm tired of girls laughing at us.
I'm tired of feeling like a loser.
We came to high school
wanting things to be different. Right?
So now we have that chance.
I skip tonight, that's all out the window.
So I'm asking you guys,
as a friend,
just talk to Eddie.
Get him to move Hellfire.
Come to my game.
Please.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Shit.
[DOG BARKING]
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[OMINOUS MUSICAL FLOURISH]
[JOYCE]Mrs. Ergenbright,
let me ask you something.
- [MRS. ERGENBRIGHT]Mm-hmm.
- Have you ever wished
you could have the answer to any question,
right at your fingertips?
Oh, gosh.
[CHUCKLES] Yes. It's just like those...
those big fancy books you see on TV.
- Oh, yes, they're lovely.
- [DOORBELL RINGS]
Yeah, just imagine, you'd never
have to go to the library again.
Or, hey, think of the money
that you'll save on gas alone.
- Oh, good point.
- Anything?
Nothing.
Acceptance letters tend to come
end of week to make you sweat.
Well, I'm sweating.
- It's coming, Mrs. Byers. Don't you worry.
- I always worry. Thanks.
Oh, gosh. Did I lose you? Hello?
No, sorry. Carol? Can I call you Carol?
- Of... Of course.
- Great. So, what are we thinking?
Could do volumes A through C,
or we could do the... the whole alphabet.
Well, uh, remind me how much money...
I can't remember...
Carol, uh, can I call you back?
Oh, sure.
[OMINOUS MUSIC SWELLS]
[UNSETTLING RUSSIAN FOLK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGERS SINGING IN RUSSIAN]
[FOLK MUSIC HALTS]
[GIRL]After learning to speak,
she traveled the world
to spread her message,
and along the way,
changed how the world perceived
those like her with disabilities.
And that is why I have chosen
Helen Keller as my hero.
[TEACHER] That was wonderful, Angela.
Truly wonderful.
- What an inspiring story.
- [ANGELA CHUCKLES]
Okay. Now let's see
who has to follow that.
Jane.
[LIGHT, SCATTERED CLAPPING]
Hi.
For my hero,
I...
I chose my dad.
And for my visual aid,
I made a "direyama" of our cabin.
More like diarrhea.
[CLASS LAUGHING]
[TEACHER] Quiet, everyone.
Let's be respectful.
[LAUGHTER SUBSIDES]
This is my dad.
His name is Hopper.
He made the best Eggos,
and... [CHUCKLES]
...we liked to watch Miami Viceon Fridays.
This is Mr. Fibbly.
- He is a squirrel.
- [SNORTS DERISIVELY]
- [SCATTERED LAUGHTER]
- [STUDENT] What?
And this is the alarm that my dad made.
I... I was never scared because...
beca... because...
Uh, Angela, let's save questions
until the end of Jane's presentation.
Yeah. Sorry.
I'm just, like, confused.
I thought this was
a presentation about a historical hero.
My dad was in the newspaper.
Your local paper?
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
I just don't think that's
what Mrs. Gracey meant by historical.
This is supposed to be
about famous people.
My dad is famous.
He... He saved lots of lives.
In a mall fire.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
He was a hero for people.
And he was my hero too.
That's not what I'm saying at all,
but it's okay.
I am so sorry, Mrs. Gracey.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
I just wanted clarity
on the rules of the assignment.
Well, technically, you are correct,
but Jane has decided to do her father.
So,
please, continue
with your presentation, Jane.
[UNSETTLING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
El, it wasn't that bad.
Friends don't lie.
I'm not lying.
El.
Come on.
["RUNNING UP THAT HILL"
BY KATE BUSH PLAYING]
- ♪ It didn't hurt me ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Do you wanna feel how it feels? ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ If I only could
I'd make a deal with God ♪
♪ And I'd get him to swap our places ♪
♪ Be running up that road ♪
♪ Be running up that hill ♪
♪ Be running up that building ♪
♪ Say if I only could ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Tell me we both matter, don't we? ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ If only I could ♪
♪ I'd make a deal with God ♪
♪ And I'd get him to swap our places ♪
♪ Be running up that road ♪
♪ Be running up that hill ♪
♪ Be running up that building ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ Say, if only I could ♪
[MUFFLED] Can you remove
your headphones, please?
[SONG STOPS]
Sorry.
A C in English and a C-minus in Spanish.
Yeah.
Well, that's not normal for you.
If you say so.
How's your mom holding up?
She's fine.
I mean, she hates our new place,
which is, like...
Yeah, it's terrible, but...
she's fine.
Is she still drinking?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Like, yeah, a little, but...
Well, she's working two jobs.
So, it's not easy.
It must not be easy for you either
with your stepdad gone.
It's kind of better, honestly.
Better how?
He was an asshole.
So, there's less
assholery.
Are you sleeping better?
Yeah, fine.
No more headaches?
Nightmares?
[SCREAMING]
[ECHOING] Billy!
[GRUNTS]
Nope.
Max?
What you've been through,
what you're still going through,
it's a lot for anyone.
And it's okay to not be okay.
But I can only help you
if you're truthful,
if you open up to me.
Yeah, I... I know.
I'm... I'm being open.
[EXHALES]
I'm being open.
Max, hey.
Are you stalking me or something?
Oh, no, I... I just wanted to give you this.
- What is this?
- A ticket to the game.
I know you never want to go to my games,
but this one is kind of a big deal.
A big deal?
Lucas, you really care about this?
Yeah, I... I do. Maybe you should
find something you care about too.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Uh... [EXHALES]
You're just...
It's... It's like
you're not even here anymore.
you're a ghost or something.
A ghost?
Really?
Max,
I know something's wrong.
Yeah, right.
Something must be wrong with me
because I broke up with you.
No.
No, that... that's not what I meant.
Lucas, look,
people just change, okay?
That's it.
I've changed.
It's that simple.
Good luck.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[MAX BREATHING SHAKILY]
[PILLS RATTLE]
[GIRL COUGHING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIRL RETCHING]
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah... Yes, I'm...
I'm fine.
Okay, um...
You're sure?
Please, just go away.
- [TOILET FLUSHES]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[POUNDING AT DOOR]
Are you deaf? I said go away.
[WOMAN] Chrissy?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom?
[WOMAN] You ready
to try on the dress again?
I loosened the back a little for you.
[MENACING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[WET SQUELCHING]
[CHRISSY'S MOM'S VOICE]
Chrissy! Did you hear me?
Open the goddamn door, Chrissy...
[VOICE DISTORTING] ...or I'm gonna gut you
like the fat pig that you are.
[SCREAMING] Go away! Go away! Go away!
- Did you hear me?
- Go away!
Go away! Go away! Go away! Go away!
[DISTORTED VOICE] Can you hear me?
[CHRISSY PANTING]
["I WAS A TEENAGE WEREWOLF"
BY THE CRAMPS PLAYING]
[DEEP VOICE]
"The Devil has come to America."
"Dungeons and Dragons,
at first regarded as
a harmless game of make-believe,
now has both parents
and psychologists concerned."
"Studies have linked violent behavior
to the game,
saying it promotes satanic worship,
ritual sacrifice,
sodomy,
suicide,
and even...
murder."
[LAUGHING]
Shit, he seems really revved up today.
He's always revved up.
We'll just act casual.
- Casual.
Right, okay.
Totally.
Society has to blame something.
- We're an easy target.
- Exactly.
We're the freaks
because we like to play a fantasy game.
But as long as you're into band
or science...
[SNEERINGLY] ...or parties
or a game where you toss balls
into laundry baskets...
- [STUDENT] Loser!
- You want something, freak?
[SPLUTTERS]
[EDDIE CHUCKLES]
Prick.
It's forced conforming.
That's what's... [SHOUTS]
...killing the kids!
[GROUP CHUCKLING]
That's the real monster.
So, uh, speaking of monsters,
uh,
Lucas has to do his, uh,
balls-in-laundry-baskets game.
So... [DUSTIN CHUCKLES]
...he's not gonna be able to make it
to Hellfire tonight.
And I know there's no way we can beat
your sadistic campaign without him.
So, me and Mike,
we were talking,
shooting the shit,
and we were thinking
that maybe we might...
Postpone.
- Postpone? Can't just drop this on us!
- Over my dead body.
- Shut up!
- [GROANS]
You saying Sinclair's
been taken in by the dark side?
- Uh, something like that.
- Something like that?
Jesus Christ.
And rather than find a sub for him,
you want... you want to postpone
"The Cult of Vecna"?
I... I don't want to postpone it.
We don't want to postpone it.
It's just that, you know, most of the subs
will be at the championship game.
- Oh, it's the championship game?
- Yeah.
Can I level with you?
Jeff graduates this year.
Gareth's got, what? A year and a half?
Me, I am army-crawling my way
toward a D in Ms. O'Donnell's.
If I don't blow her final,
I'm gonna walk that stage next month,
I'm gonna look Principal Higgins
dead in the eye,
I'm gonna flip him the bird,
I'm gonna snatch that diploma.
- I'm gonna run like hell outta here.
- [DUSTIN LAUGHS]
- Didn't you say that last year?
- And the year before?
Yeah, yeah, and I was full of shit.
This year's different.
This year is my year.
I can feel it.
'86, baby.
- [BOYS CHUCKLE]
- You know what that means?
It means you boys
are the future of Hellfire.
I knew it the moment I saw you.
You sat on that table
right over there, looking like...
looking like two little lost sheep.
You were wearing a Weird Al T-shirt,
which I thought was brave.
Thank you.
Mike, you were wearing whatever shit
your mommy bought you from goddamn Gap.
[ALL LAUGHING]
And we showed you
that school didn't have to be
the worst years of your lives, right?
- No.
- Okay, no, no.
Well, I'm here to tell you
that there are other little lost sheepies
out there who need help.
Who need you.
And all you guys gotta do
is get your Bo-Peeps on
and go and find one.
[PHONE RINGS]
Where the hell have you been?
I have karate
from 1:00 to 3:00 on Fridays.
[JAUNTY, UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
So let me see if I have this right.
You received a doll in the mail.
- Yes.
- And it's creepy.
Oh, yes.
And you believe it's from Russia, huh?
- I know it is.
- Hmm.
The... The stamps on the package have
that hammer with that hook thingamajig.
- Sickle.
- Whatever.
Sounds like it came from Russia.
Wow, I am so glad I called you.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Should I be worried?
I would be.
Ah!
Could be a threat.
After all,
you did sabotage their U.S. operation
and killed about two dozen comrades.
But how would they know my name?
If it's the KGB, Joyce,
and they wanna find out
who you are, they will.
Wait, can you undress her?
- What?
- The creepy doll.
Can you remove her dress?
I don't...
Okay.
[JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING OVER PHONE]
Jesus.
What?
She has nipples.
[EXCLAIMS]
Yeah!
Okay, now,
do you see anything taped to her?
Wires or a bug or something?
I don't know. It's... It's cracked.
Cracked?
Yeah, like, the porcelain's cracked
and they tried to glue it back together.
Okay, okay. Uh, do you have rope
and something heavy?
What for?
Smashing.
[JAUNTY MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
What do you think, Byers?
I call it a weeder.
You get it, man? Like a feeder?
Weeder?
Clever.
Hey, where are you going, man?
Look, I'm just trying
to turn that frown upside down, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, come on, man.
What, are you gonna be
moping around all break or what?
- I'm not moping.
- You're moping.
- Really?
- Mopey Dick.
Wow, wow, that's clever.
Is this because your girl is ditching you?
What? Nancy's not ditching me.
Oh, so she's coming now?
No.
Ah, so she's ditching you.
Dude, no, she's not ditching me.
She has to work.
Who the hell works over spring break?
Nancy. Nancy does.
Maybe I'm missing something, but why can't
Jonathan come down here for break?
- Because.
- Because why?
Because a lot of reasons.
Curious.
Um, do you mind
if I take a crack at this, Candace?
Um, go ahead. All yours.
You said there's lots of reasons
he's not coming. Such as?
- Why are you being so nosy?
- Call it journalistic instinct.
[SIGHS] Okay, well, there's no story here,
if that's what you're after.
His mom works,
so he has to watch over his brother.
On top of that,
he's not early decision like me,
so he's waiting on his acceptance letter,
and he wants to be there when it comes.
Which I totally get.
Okay.
Um, I don't. It just...
...doesn't make any sense, dude.
Okay, let me sift through this mess.
Nancy is the supposed love of your life.
In fact, you're so smitten
that you have this grand plan
to go to some fancy-schmancy college,
AKA money pit, together?
And yet he's so nervous
about this acceptance letter,
he doesn't have time to visit
the most desired girl in Hawkins?
That doesn't pass the smell test.
In fact, it stinks to high heaven.
Whoo!
Look, you're a good boy, okay?
You've been a good boy, man.
And I think it's way past due you give
that right hand of yours a vacation
and get you
some well-deserved hanky-panky.
Okay, first of all, Fred, I'm going to try
to forget that you said any of that.
- It's...
- Gross, dude.
- It's natural.
- You don't understand Nancy.
He's not like you.
He's caring and compassionate and...
...incredibly ambitious. She's never done
a single thing halfway in her life.
He's so protective
over the people that he loves.
If she takes on
the editor of the school paper,
she's gonna make that
the best paper that ever existed.
And he'll never back down
from what's right, what's moral.
No matter the pressure,
no matter the personal cost...
- That's why I love her.
- That's why I love him.
- Everything between us is...
- Perfect.
Eh, I'm still rooting for my alt.
- [MIKE] Nancy!
- [DOOR BANGS]
[DOOR HINGES CREAK]
Nancy, hey.
Um, do you wanna join Hellfire tonight?
[SEETHES]
Just move your date this one time.
Come on.
What, to hang out with you
and Eddie "the freak" Munson?
Uh, yeah, I'll pass.
You're just jealous
'cause I have another older male friend.
Ew. Ugh. Whatever.
Besides, I mean, I really dig this girl.
I think that she could...
Who knows, she could be the one.
Oh, I got some customers.
Call you back. Bye.
- No, you can't. I'm at...
- [DISCONNECT TONE DRONES]
...school.
["PLAY WITH ME" BY EXTREME PLAYING]
[WRESTLERS GRUNTING]
So you fight with dice?
Yes, but these aren't your normal dice.
They have up to 20 sides.
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[WRESTLERS GRUNTING, EXCLAIMING]
If I play,
do I get one of those cool T-shirts?
- [LAUGHS] Yes.
- Really?
Everyone gets a T-shirt.
We make 'em ourselves, and if you...
You're being sarcastic.
You being sarcastic?
♪ Do you wanna... ♪
She was being sarcastic.
Mom says the game promotes
Satanism and animal cruelty.
That's just bullshit media propaganda.
60 Minutes begs to differ.
- No.
No.
[SONG STOPS]
[PANTING] I hate high school.
[DUSTIN GRUNTS]
So, screw it.
Screw what?
Screw high school.
What? What? Dustin, where are you going?
Just trust me!
Come on, just talk to me.
[MIKE] Tell me things!
- Wear a helmet!
- [MIKE] What are you talking about?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRD CAWING]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[UNSETTLING AMBIENT AUDIO]
[ANIMAL CALLING OUT]
Hello?
[CLOCK CHIMING]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[CLOCK BELL CHIMES]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
- [CHIMES LOUDLY]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [SPIDERS SCUTTLING]
Whoa, hey, hey, hey.
Sorry. [CHUCKLES]
Didn't mean to scare you.
You okay?
[BOX CLATTERS]
There's, uh...
There's nothing to worry about. Okay?
No one ever comes out here.
We're safe.
I promise.
So, how does this work exactly?
Oh, just like any other old sale,
except, uh, cash only,
and, uh, for obvious reasons,
no receipts.
I'll do you a half ounce for, uh... 20.
What do you say?
Plenty of bang for your buck.
Should last a while.
- [GASPS]
- [SCURRYING]
Hey, uh, we don't need to do this.
Just give me the word and I'll walk away.
- Okay?
- It's not that. I don't want you to go.
It's just...
Do you ever feel like
you're losing your mind?
Um,
you know, just... on a daily basis.
I feel like I'm losing my mind right now
doing a drug deal with Chrissy Cunningham,
the queen of Hawkins High.
You know,
this isn't the first time that we've, um...
hung out.
No?
You don't remember?
I'm sorry. I...
That's okay.
[GASPS]
I wouldn't remember me either, Chrissy.
Honestly, do I have stuff in my hair?
[CHUCKLES]
You don't remember me?
I'm sorry. [CHUCKLES]
Middle school, talent show.
You were doing this cheer thing.
You know, the... the thing you do.
It was pretty cool, actually.
And I...
- I was with my band.
- Corroded Coffin.
- Corro... You do remember.
- Oh my God! Yes, of course.
With a name like that, how could I forget?
I dunno. You're a freak.
No, you just...
- You looked so...
- Different?
Yeah. Well, uh, my hair was buzzed,
and I didn't have
these sweet old tatties yet.
- You played guitar, right?
- Uh-huh.
Still do. Still do.
You should come see us.
Uh, we play at The Hideout on Tuesdays.
It's pretty cool.
We... We actually get a crowd
of about five drunks.
[LAUGHS]
It's not exactly the Garden,
but you gotta start somewhere, right? So...
You know,
you're not what I thought you'd be like.
- Mean and scary?
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, I actually kinda thought
you'd be kinda mean and scary too.
Me?
Terrifying.
Uh, so,
in other good news,
flattery works with me, so...
Twenty-five percent discount for the half.
Fifteen bucks.
You're robbing me blind here, you know.
Do you have anything
maybe
stronger?
Nice job, Kate.
Excellent work, Paul. Nice improvement.
Very disappointing, Jane.
Let's talk after break.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[ELEVEN GRUNTS]
- [CROWD] Oh!
- [ANGELA] Oh my God.
[LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY] I am so sorry.
I hope Mr. Fibbly's okay. [CHUCKLES]
[BULLIES CHUCKLING]
[CROWD MURMURS]
[BOY LAUGHING]
Whoops!
[ANGELA] Oh my God.
[BULLIES LAUGHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS]
Angela!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[CROWD MURMURS, LAUGHS]
Holy shit!
What the hell was that?
[CROWD LAUGHING]
[MRS. GRACEY] Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, what's going on here?
What's going on? Jane?
- Jane.
- [LAUGHTER SUBSIDES]
Did someone do this?
I tripped.
It was just an accident.
[SIGHS] All right, Angela.
You come with me.
- [CROWD] Ooh!
- What? Why?
Let's go.
I didn't do anything.
Tell her, Jane. Tell her!
[ANGELA GRUNTS]
Shit. El. El.
Shit.
El...
I'm sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
It... It's not that bad.
We'll fix it together, okay?
Okay? Shit.
[WILL SIGHS]
[MATERIAL STRETCHING]
[JOYCE GRUNTING]
[CLANG]
Come on, kids.
Don't stare.
Oh, hi. [CHUCKLES]
[CHILD] Mommy, what's she doing?
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Was this really necessary?
If that porcelain belly
is pregnant with an explosive device,
you will soon be thanking me.
And remember, you are not
lowering this bucket. You are...
Releasing it. Got it.
We want to make sure
that we destroy that doll
with as much force as possible.
Yep. Got it.
One more thing.
Joyce. Are you there?
Talk to me! Joyce! Joyce!
Joyce! Joyce! Joyce!
- Joyce!
- Yeah?
[MUSIC HALTS]
What happened?
It broke.
Do you see a bug?
Anything with wires?
Or anything that... that doesn't look like
the insides of a doll.
Anything like that?
Joyce! Joyce!
Where'd you go? Where'd you go now?
Why are you not answering me again?
Joyce!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh my...
[MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
[AIR HORN BLOWS]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- [MARCHING BAND PLAYING]
[CHEERLEADERS] Let's go, Tigers!
Does it bother you that, like,
we might win a championship
right after you graduated?
Yeah, that's an interesting point.
Thank you so much
for bringing that up, Brenda.
[BAND STOPS]
Everyone now please rise
for our national anthem.
Singing for us tonight,
we have a very special guest.
All the way from Nashville,
our very own Tammy Thompson!
[ALL CHEERING]
- [INAUDIBLE]
- [STUDENT 1] Go, Tammy!
[STUDENT 2] We love you, Tammy!
- [OFF-KEY]♪ O say, can you see ♪
- [MICROPHONE FEEDBACK WHINES]
♪ By the dawn's early light... ♪
[WHISPERS] Told you.
Muppet.
Okay, she does sound like a Muppet.
Oh my God, totally.
She sounds like Kermit.
I was thinking
it was more like Miss Piggy.
[SNORTS]
I used to think she sounded good
'cause I had this massive crush...
Sorry?
Um, we... we took
a... a massively hard class together.
We were... We were
in Mrs. Click's class together.
Yeah. [CHUCKLES DRYLY]
Uh...
- Sorry, were you asking me a question?
- No. [CHUCKLES]
Oh, okay.
♪ ...ramparts we watched ♪
Wow. She sounds amazing, doesn't she?
♪ And the rocket's red glare ♪
♪ The bombs bursting in air ♪
♪ Gave proof through the night ♪
♪ That our flag was still there ♪
♪ O say, does that star-spangled... ♪
[ELECTRIC GUITAR RENDITION PLAYING]
[SONG CRESCENDOS]
Absolutely not.
You asked for a sub. We delivered.
This is Hellfire Club.
Not Babysitting Club.
I'm 11, you long-haired freak.
My, my, the child speaks.
[CHUCKLING]
So, what's your name, child?
Erica Sinclair.
[CHUCKLES]
So this is Sinclair's infamous sister.
- He's sharp.
- [LAUGHING]
[BOTH STOP LAUGHING]
What's your class and level?
Level one dwarf?
[LAUGHTER]
My name is Lady Applejack.
And I'm a chaotic good
half-elf rogue, level 14.
I will sneak behind
any monster you throw my way
and stab them in the back
with my poison-soaked kukri.
And I'll smile as I watch them die
a slow, agonizing death.
So, we gonna do this,
or we gonna keep chitchatting
like this is your mommy's book club?
Welcome to Hellfire.
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[CHEERLEADERS] Push 'em back, defense!
Push 'em back...
[CHEERING]
Hey! Yo, you gotta stay on 'em.
Stay on 'em! Let's go! Go!
Looks like my headline has a shot.
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [EDDIE] The hooded cultists chant,
"Hail Lord Vecna."
They turn to you,
remove their hoods.
You recognize most of them from Makbar.
But there is one you do not recognize,
his skin shriveled,
desiccated.
And something else.
He is not only missing his left arm,
but his left eye!
[ALL CLAMORING]
No! No!
- Vecna's dead.
- He was killed by Kas.
So it was thought, my friends.
So it was thought.
But Vecna lives.
["DETROIT ROCK CITY" BY KISS PLAYING]
[REFEREE BLOWS WHISTLE]
- [CROWD BOOS]
- Yo, what the hell was that?
What the hell was that?
That's not me, that's him.
[EDDIE]You are scared.
You're tired. You are injured.
Do you flee Vecna and his cultists?
Or stand your ground and fight?
Come on.
- Sinclair, you're in.
- Huh?
You're in. Son, let's go!
[BUZZER BUZZES]
I say we fight.
To the death.
[ALL CHANTING] To the death! To the death!
To the death! To the death!
To the death!
♪ Detroit rock city ♪
♪ Get up
Everybody's gonna move their feet ♪
♪ Get down
Everybody's gonna leave their seat ♪
♪ Getting late... ♪
[DICE CLATTERING]
[ALL] Yeah!
♪ Ten o'clock
And I know I gotta hit the road ♪
[DICE CLATTER DRAMATICALLY]
♪ First I drink, then I smoke... ♪
- No!
- [CROWD] Defense! Defense!
♪ Try to make the midnight show ♪
♪ Get up
Everybody's gonna move their feet... ♪
Shoot it!
[WHOOPING]
Yes!
Come on!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[EDDIE CACKLES]
Time-out. Time-out.
[SONG FADES]
Time-out! Time-out!
Guys, I hate to say this,
but we've got to flee.
- I concur.
- Didn't we just agree "to the death"?
That wasn't literal.
Vecna just decimated us.
We can't kill him with two players.
You too? He only has 15 hit points left.
Don't be pussies.
Pussies? Really?
'Cause we're not delusional?
- Delusional? How about not cowards?
- [EDDIE] Hey!
If I may interject,
gentlemen, Lady Applejack.
Whilst I respect the passion,
you'd be wise to take
Gareth the Great's concern to heart.
There is no shame in running.
Don't try to be heroes.
Not today, 'kay?
One sec.
What do you think?
How many hit points
do you and Applejack have left?
[BOTH] Twelve.
[COACH] Here, on inbound,
they're gonna try and take away Jason
and double-team him.
That is gonna free up Patrick.
Wait, no. You gotta let me take the shot.
It's risky as hell.
But you're the ones on the battlefield.
So it's your call.
- What do you say, Lady Applejack?
- You really gotta ask?
Screw it.
Let's kill the son of a bitch.
Winners find a way to win.
Let me find a way.
The chances of success are 20-to-1.
Never tell me the odds.
Just get me the ball. Get me the ball.
Give me the D20.
[INDISTINCT CHANTING]
[DICE RATTLING]
[DRAMATIC CLATTERING]
[DISTORTED] That's a miss!
- No!
- Shit! Shit!
[TIMER TICKS]
[DISTORTED, SLOW RATTLING]
- Please!
- Come on!
[BRIGHT, EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUZZER BUZZES]
Please!
Come on!
[CROWD ROARS]
- Crit hit!
- Yeah!
What? What?
[UPBEAT SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
That's why we play.
[DUSTIN] Yes! Yes!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[ALL CHANTING] Lucas! Lucas! Lucas! Lucas!
[CARS HONKING]
That's you, baby! That's you! [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, man.
Hey, Jed, you comin'?
Oh, yeah. Party at Benny's, boys!
Yeah!
[HELLFIRE CLUB CHEERING]
Yes!
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Lucas. Come on, man.
[MAN 1]After a tragic year for our town,
the Tigers have brought home
the conference title
for the first time in 22 years.
[MAN 2]And what a great game
it was, Allen,
ending with a dramatic buzzer-beater
from benchwarmer Lucas Sinclair.
He must be feeling
on top of the world right...
[DOG BARKING]
[SIGHS] All right, all right, I hear you.
[TV PLAYING FAINTLY]
- [WOMAN ON TV]It'll be 3.07.
- [MAN]Yeah.
But this is your old friend Billy talking.
You know, just... just a little favor.
And I don't think...
- [WOMAN]No. I don't wanna do that stuff.
- [MAX SIGHS]
Not for you, not for anybody.
- I'm trying to be normal, Billy.
- [CANS CLATTERING]
[TV CONTINUES FAINTLY]
[DOG CONTINUES BARKING]
I'm coming. I'm coming.
- Here you go. Good boy.
- [CAR APPROACHING]
- [CAR STEREO PLAYING LOUD ROCK MUSIC]
- [DOG WHIMPERS]
[STEREO STOPS]
[ENGINE REVS, STOPS]
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VAN DOOR CREAKING]
[EDDIE] This is, uh, my castle.
[DOOR OPENING]
- [BARKS]
- Okay. All right.
One more. That's it though, right?
Good boy.
Sorry for the mess.
Uh, the maid took the week off.
You, um...
You live here alone?
With my uncle.
But, uh, he works nights at the plant.
Bringing home the big bucks.
How long does it take?
Sorry?
The Special K. How long to kick in?
Oh, uh, well,
it depends if you snort it or not.
Uh, if you do,
then, uh, yeah.
It'll, uh, kick in pretty quick.
Oh, shit.
- You're sure you have it?
- No, no, I got it.
Um, somewhere.
Uh...
Sorry I'm late, sweetheart.
- [STRUMS NOTES]
- You're beautiful.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
[LOUD CHIMING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Eddie? Did you find it?
Eddie?
- [SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING]
- Mom?
Just loosening this up for you,
sweetheart.
You're going to look...
[VOICE DISTORTS] ...absolutely beautiful.
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
[WHIMPERS]
[CHRISSY'S MOM] Chrissy!
- No!
- [DISTORTED] Chrissy, open the door!
- No! [SCREAMS]
- Let go! Let go!
Chrissy!
[EERIE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Dad.
Dad! Dad?
- [SCREAMS]
- [MUFFLED MOANING]
Gotcha.
Found it.
Peaceful bliss, just moments away.
Chrissy?
Chrissy.
Hello?
Hey, Chrissy, wake up.
Hey. Hello?
Chrissy. Hello?
Hey, Chrissy.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[DISTORTED VOICE] Chrissy?
[WET SQUELCHING]
[CREATURE GURGLES]
[DESPERATE, MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[SCUTTLING]
[DISTORTED VOICE] Chrissy.
No! [GROANS]
[SCREAMING] Help! Help!
Somebody, help me!
Time to wake up. Hello? Can you hear me?
Wake up, Chrissy.
Chrissy, wake up!
I don't like this, Chrissy! Wake up!
Help!
[DISTORTED VOICE] Chrissy.
- [CHRISSY PANTING]
- [CREATURE GROANS]
No.
[CREATURE GURGLES]
[MENACING, GUTTURAL GROWLING]
[CHRISSY WHIMPERS]
Chrissy! Chrissy! Chrissy!
Chrissy, wake up now! Chrissy!
- Don't cry, Chrissy.
- [CHRISSY WHIMPERING]
It's time
for your suffering...
to end.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Chrissy!
What...
[CREATURE GROANS]
Jesus Christ!
[BONES CRACKING]
- [BONES SNAPPING]
- [CREATURE GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
[WET SQUELCH]
[EERIE PERCUSSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]