[INSECTS CHIRRUPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
ARGYLE: Shit! Oh, shit!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
- MIKE: God.
- JONATHAN: Keep pressure on it.
- It's not slowing.
- Keep putting pressure on it.
- More pressure. Get the napkins.
- MIKE: Come on.
- WILL: More napkins.
- MIKE: Shit.
- It's not slowing.
- Argyle! Get us to St. Mary's.
I don't think praying's
gonna help that dude.
- No, you idiot! St. Mary's Hospital.
- HARMON: No, no.
- What?
- [WEAKLY] No hospital.
- We're gonna get you to the hospital.
- You need to warn...
[GURGLES] ...O... Owens.
- Owens, okay.
- HARMON: The girl.
She... She's in danger.
Okay, how... how do we find Owens?
[WEAKLY] Nina. Nina.
- Nina. Who's Nina?
- WILL: Come on. A pen.
- JONATHAN: Okay.
- MIKE: Shit.
- Here's the number.
- Number. Number.
- MIKE: He wants to write something.
- We can call this Nina?
MIKE: Grab a magazine or something.
Will, get something.
- He's really bleeding a lot.
- WILL: Right here.
- Come on. Hey.
- MIKE: Write the number.
Hey! Look at me!
- Hey! Come on!
- MIKE: Hold on!
- Oh, shit.
- JONATHAN: Hey!
ARGYLE: Hey, yo, yo. Wait, wait, wait.
Why is it so quiet back there, huh?
- Yo, is he dead? Jesus, man.
- [INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
- Talk to me! Shit!
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
We should get off the road.
Argyle, Ar... Argyle, get off the road, now!
Shit, he's dead, isn't he?
- This is real bad.
- JONATHAN: What are you doing?
ALL: Get off the road!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[ITEMS CLATTERING, CLINKING]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DISCOMFORTING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[LABORED WHEEZING]
Listen.
- I know she was just here.
- [LABORED INHALE]
And if you wanna live...
you're gonna tell me where she is.
[DISCOMFORTING SYNTH MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[INDISTINCT RUMBLING]
[VEHICLE JOLTS, RUSTLES]
Apologies for the bumpy ride, kiddo.
I would've paved the road, but...
kinda ruins the whole
"top secret location" thing.
Did you get some rest?
A little.
Good.
I have a feeling you're gonna need it.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC GROWS MORE TENSE]
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [BIRD TWEETING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[CAR MANEUVERING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DOOR CHIMES, BUZZES]
[DOOR SLAM ECHOES]
[SHUTTER GRINDING]
OWENS: Oop.
Okay. Here we go.
[ELEVATOR LOCK CLICKS]
You didn't really think
we were working out of a shed, did you?
[CURIOUS SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR RUMBLING]
[CURIOUS SYNTH MUSIC CONTINUES]
You built all this?
Well, more gave it a face-lift.
Do you know what an ICBM is?
It stands for
intercontinental ballistic missile.
It's a... a fancy bomb.
We used to store them in these silos,
but we haven't used this one in years.
In fact, there...
there's no bomb here at all.
It's just a big ol' empty space.
So we repurposed it to hold something
much more powerful than a missile:
you.
- Anne, Tracy. Morning.
- Morning, doc.
WOMAN: Morning.
You'll have to forgive the staring.
You're a bit of a celebrity down here.
- I am?
- Oh yeah. You kidding?
You... You're bigger than Madonna to them.
They've all given up their lives,
their jobs, their families
to come work on this program,
'cause they believe in the cause.
They believe in you.
[DOOR BUZZES LOUDLY]
[CURIOUS SYNTH MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay. Yeah.
We call her Nina.
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [MACHINERY GUSHING]
What is it?
MAN: If we told you,
it would ruin the surprise.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS]
Hello, Eleven.
[ELEVEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
I know.
You're frightened of me.
Perhaps, in our time apart,
you may have even grown to hate me.
But all I've ever wanted to do
is to help you.
And right now,
I think you very much need my help.
Your gifts have been stolen.
I believe I know why.
And I believe I know how to get them back.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let us work together again.
You and I.
Daughter
and Papa.
Papa!
[ELEVEN GROANS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
- [SNARLS]
- [SCREAMS]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALARM KLAXON WAILING]
AGENT: Yeah, I got her.
[GASPS]
Why don't you go back inside?
Play nice for the doctor, hmm?
ELEVEN: No!
[ECHOING] No!
The more you move,
- the more this is gonna hurt.
- No! No! No!
[INJECTOR HISSES]
Leave her.
- [GASPS] No.
- I'm... I'm sorry, Eleven.
This is not how I wanted things to begin.
[DELICATE, UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
But everything's going to be all right.
[ECHOING] You're home now.
You're home.
[OMINOUS SYNTH PULSES]
[DOOR GEARS RUMBLING, WHIRRING]
[DOOR SLAM ECHOES]
[INTRO THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
[WIND RUSHING]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[IN RUSSIAN] Enough!
[MAN PANTS]
He is not yours to kill.
Fools.
[IN ENGLISH] What I tell you, American?
- [HOPPER PANTS]
- No run.
You don't listen.
Now is going to be much pain.
Much.
[BLOW LANDS, ECHOES]
[BODY SCRAPING]
[DOOR CLATTERS, SCREECHES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOG BARKING]
[LIGHTS BUZZING]
[UNSETTLING CHORD PLAYING]
[HOPPER COUGHING, PANTING]
- [GATE SLAMS]
- [LOCK CLICKING]
ANTONOV: It could be worse, American.
At least you have company.
[HOPPER PANTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your eyes don't deceive you.
I'm a prisoner now.
Like you.
Yuri, the smuggler, he betrayed me.
Betrayed us.
[ANTONOV GRUNTS]
[IN RUSSIAN] The pig's in trouble now.
[IN ENGLISH] You said we could trust him!
You swore to me!
Because I believed we could.
You think this is what I planned?
I have lost everything. Everything!
We both knew the risks. Both of us.
[IN RUSSIAN] Do us all a favor. Finish him!
[IN ENGLISH] We gambled today,
and we lost.
We lost.
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
PRISONER: [IN RUSSIAN] Finish him!
[TENSE MUSIC FADES]
[GRUNTS, SPITS]
[ANTONOV GRUNTS, PANTS]
[IN ENGLISH] Joyce.
What about Joyce?
[DISTRESSING MUSIC BUILDS]
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [YURI WHISTLING POORLY]
[TOOL RATTLING]
- [PLANE ENGINE SQUEAKS]
- [WHISTLING STOPS]
[CLANGING]
- [ENGINE SPLUTTERS]
- [YURI CHUCKLES]
[IN RUSSIAN] There you are, my girl!
Mwah!
[GRUNTS]
[IN ENGLISH] Why the long faces?
Are you not excited for your journey
across the Iron Curtain?
Yuri, I have a family.
I have three kids waiting for me.
Did you know?
Peanut butter is banned in motherland.
I buy for dollar-thirty here,
sell for $20 there.
Your mother must be very proud.
My mother is dead.
Dead...
tired of living like a bum!
[YURI CHORTLES]
You see?
Yuri has family too.
And with money I earn from selling you,
I will buy her a new house.
I will buy my daughter
a pony.
Whatever they desire from now on,
they will have.
And, yes, for that,
my mother will be very, very proud.
["TRAVELIN' MAN" BY RICKY NELSON PLAYING]
♪ I'm a travelin' man
And I've made a lot of stops... ♪
Hold tight.
This is not American Airlines.
Is going to get bit choppy.
[ENGINE REVS]
♪ ...at least one lovely girl ♪
♪ I've a pretty señorita waiting for me ♪
♪ Down in old Mexico ♪
♪ If you're ever in Alaska, stop and see ♪
♪ My cute little Eskimo ♪
[SONG CONTINUES OVER RADIO]
- ♪ Oh, my sweet Fraulein ♪
- [FAINT CLATTERING]
♪ Down in Berlin town... ♪
[CLATTERING CONTINUES]
When'd Rick get out of jail?
♪ And my China doll
Down in old Hong Kong ♪
Justice system's a goddamn joke.
[DRAWER CLATTERS]
Nope.
Yeah. [SNORTS]
You'll do.
[FLAMES WHOOSH]
[FOOD PLOPS WETLY]
Hey, Dustin, this is Eddie the Banished.
- You there?
- [RADIO CLICKS]
[STATIC]
EDDIE: Dustin, can you hear me?
Dustin?
Earth to Dustin.
Hey, it's Nancy.
Wheeler! Hey.
Um, I'm gonna need a food delivery,
like, really soon, unless you want me
going out into the world.
No. No, no, no. Don't do that.
Stay where you are,
and we'll be there as soon as we can.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Listen, um... can you pick me up a six-pack?
I know, it's stupid as shit,
drinking right now,
but a cold beer
would really calm my jangled nerves.
Hey, I'm gonna have to call you back.
No, don't you da... Wheeler? Wheeler?
- Dustin!
- DUSTIN: Mm.
- Wake up.
- What?
Aren't you supposed to be on Max watch?
Yep. Yep, yep, yep.
- Sorry.
- Then where is she?
She's right there. A second ago.
I swear, I just dozed off for...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
...an hour.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS, SUBSIDES]
KAREN: Morning, guys.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, everything's okay.
I think it's so sweet that you guys
are sticking together like this.
Could try sticking together
at a different house for a change.
You know you're welcome anytime.
DUSTIN: Totally. You're like family.
- May I?
- Absolutely.
Yeah, why not?
Take us for all we're worth.
[CHEEKILY] Okay.
["RUNNING UP THAT HILL" PLAYING OVER MAX'S HEADPHONES]
♪ You wanna feel how it feels? ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ You wanna know ♪
[TAPE DECK CLICKS]
Hey.
You okay?
Just couldn't sleep.
People kept blasting music in my ears,
for some reason.
[CHUCKLES]
But Holly let me borrow
some of her crayons.
- We've been having fun, right, Holly?
- Mm-hmm.
[EERIE MUSIC]
Is this what you saw last night?
I mean, it's supposed to be.
I thought it'd be easier to draw it out
than to explain it, but...
not so much.
Is that...?
MAX: It was like they were on display.
And then there was
this red fog everywhere.
It was like a dream.
A nightmare.
You think Vecna's
just trying to scare you?
With Billy? Yeah.
But when I made it here...
I dunno, something was different.
He seemed surprised, almost.
Like he didn't want me there.
Maybe you infiltrated his mind.
He invaded your mind, right?
Is it that big a leap to suggest
you somehow wound up in his?
Like Freddie Krueger's boiler room.
Freddie Krueger?
He's a super burned-up dude
with razors for fingers.
- And he kills you in your dreams.
- Seriously?
Sorry. It's a movie.
It's not real.
Just... think about it.
What if you somehow
unlocked a backdoor to Vecna's world?
Like, maybe the answer
we're looking for is
somewhere in this
incredibly vague drawing.
- God, we need Will.
- MAX: No shit.
But I tried them again this morning,
and it's the same busy signal.
Is this a window?
Yeah.
NANCY: Stained glass with roses.
Yeah. See? I'm not so terrible after all.
Yeah, well, it helps
that I've seen it before.
[RATTLING]
[DELICATE, EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's pieces of a house.
Not just any house.
[CHILLING STINGER PLAYS]
It's Victor Creel's house.
Where you going?
Waking the others.
Sorry, fuel for the road.
Thanks, Mr. Wheeler!
[LOUD RUSTLING ECHOES]
[ELEVEN BREATHES UNSTEADILY]
[INHALES]
[UNSETTLING AUDIO DISTORTION]
No.
[MENACING STINGER PLAYS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BREATHING ECHOES]
[SOBS] No.
[CHILDREN'S LAUGHTER ECHOES]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERA LENS WHIRS]
[ECHOING, INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
[CHILLING STINGER PLAYS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES]
[ELEVEN BREATHES HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT VOICE CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
ORDERLY: Well, well.
Look who finally decided to join us.
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
Where am I?
I guess you're still not quite awake, huh?
Am I in Hawkins?
[ELECTRICITY BUZZES]
[EERIE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC FADES]
ORDERLY: Well, well.
Look who finally decided to join us.
[DISCONCERTING AUDIO DISTORTION]
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
Don't go too far, sleepyhead.
Lessons begin promptly at 10:00.
[JARRING STINGER PLAYS]
[ELEVEN GASPS, BREATHES SHAKILY]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DISTRESSING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISTRESSING MUSIC BUILDS]
ORDERLY: Well, well.
Look who finally decided to join us.
[OMINOUS STINGER PLAYS]
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
[MUSIC SWELLS, STOPS]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
Heart rate's now 120 BPM.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
- She's rejecting it. [SIGHS]
- BRENNER: Give her time.
No, no, no. We shouldn't have
just thrown her in like this.
- She's gonna drown in there.
- BRENNER: No.
No, she is going to swim.
[MACHINE WHIRRING INTENSELY]
ARGYLE: Oh man.
[ARGYLE GRUNTING, GROANING]
Okay. This is not the way
it's supposed to go, okay?
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
Okay, this is so messed up.
This is so messed up!
Okay. Dude's probably got,
like, a family, kids, you know.
All that shit.
We gotta go to the cops with this.
Lay it all on 'em. Your superpowered
girlfriend, bad government dudes,
- Upside Down dimension planet thing...
- No.
But... But listen!
The bad government dudes are after
your super girlfriend, right? Right? Okay.
So maybe cops can help us
find out where she is.
They're gonna kill her.
- If they kill her, they're gonna kill us.
- Hey!
They might kill us before they kill her.
- I dunno, man.
- Argyle!
- Don't know what order they wanna go.
- Listen! Hey!
- Eeny meeny miny moe...
- Argyle!
- Listen!
- What?
Look, I think we can
figure this out, okay?
We just gotta open our minds.
Open our minds?
That's an open grave in front of me, man!
- Open my mind? What are you talking about?
- Listen. Hey, dude! Hey!
Just relax, okay?
- Yeah.
- Why don't you just go to the van...
[PANTING] ...and do your thing, huh?
- Purple Palm Tree Delight.
- Right.
- [ARGYLE CHUCKLES]
It's all worn off.
It's just worn off.
I'm all emotional.
- You're emotional.
- [CHUCKLES] Okay.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
- I'm sorry.
- You're fine.
- Jonathan.
- Yeah?
More weed? Is that really a good idea now?
Got a better idea to keep him calm?
Let's just get this done.
[TENDER, EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
WILL: You can't let him get to you.
He's stoned out of his mind.
Doesn't know what he's talking about.
MIKE: That doesn't mean he's wrong.
I mean, if that guy would've lived
one more second, one more second,
then w... we would know where she is.
Wh... Why didn't he just say the number?
I should've explained myself.
Maybe Eleven would've taken me with her
and things would be different, but...
- No.
- I didn't... I didn't know what to say.
Sometimes I think it's just scary
to open up like that.
To say how you really feel.
Especially to people
you care about the most.
Because, what if...
what if they don't like the truth?
[TENDER MUSIC CONTINUES]
ARGYLE: Does anybody know
the dead dude's name?
- What?
- The dead dude.
I'm making him a headstone.
You do realize we spent all morning
hiding the body.
Well, I'll just write, uh,
"Here Lies Unknown Hero Agent Man."
Yeah. "Saved Argyle, Jonathan,
Will, and Mike from certain death."
You... You're gonna write our names
on the pizza box?
They're pretty common names.
Okay, dude. Uh, do your thing.
Jesus Christ. [SIGHS]
Come on, man.
That's his pen.
What?
Unknown Hero Agent Man,
that's the pen he gave me
right before he died.
ARGYLE: Piece of shit.
Why would he give me a pen
that didn't work?
[ARGYLE SCRIBBLING WITH PEN]
[INQUISITIVE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCRIBBLING CONTINUES]
ARGYLE: Come on.
Hey, man, I'm using that.
What are you doing?
Something fell outta that pen, man.
Wh... What is it?
It's the number.
We've had it this whole time.
We got his digits, man?
[WET PLOP]
[SQUELCHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER IN RUSSIAN]
[SIGHS]
[IN RUSSIAN] Did I tell you
it's okay to break?
Over there, there is a hand.
A HAND!
Are we animals?
- [DRAMATIC MUSICAL FLOURISH]
- [METAL SWISHING]
ANTONOV: Psst!
Hey, Ivan. Ivan!
- [CLANGING]
- Stop calling my name.
You trying to get me in trouble?
I don't know what they've told you,
but it is all lies.
I'm here by mistake!
I'm sorry. I cannot help you.
I can make you rich.
See this American?
He comes from money.
Old money.
[IN ENGLISH] Tell him, American.
Tell him how you will make him rich.
You're a real help, American,
you know that?
A real help.
Hey.
[CLAPS HANDS]
You want to die here?
You want to die? Is that it?
That's what we've been brought here to do.
So, that is it? You give up, then?
[EXHALES]
What about your woman, huh?
She's captured, yes, but still alive.
We can still save her.
[CLICKS TONGUE] "Save her."
That is amusing to you?
You don't get it, do you?
You don't get it.
The closer I get with Joyce,
the more danger she's in.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
You're not thinking straight, American.
No, I think I am.
For the first time in my life,
I think I'm thinking straight.
I used to think I was cursed.
Ever since I was 18.
Got some letter of induction in the mail.
Uncle Sam wants me
to go fight some war in the jungle.
Charlie's moving south like a plague
'cause of commie bastards like you, and...
You know, I'm happy enough to go.
Prove to my old man
I'm not the piece of shit he thinks I am.
I get over there, I must test well,
and they put me in the Chemical Corps.
There I am. I'm just... a kid, you know.
I'm 18 years old, 8,000 miles away,
and I'm mixing up
these... 55-gallon drums of Agent Orange.
With just these kitchen gloves, you know?
We used to clean out
these buffalo turbines after a run
and just be inhaling the stuff.
No masks, nothing.
"It's not chemical warfare.
It's just herbicide to kill plants."
"Harmless." That's what they told us.
Then I got back to real life,
and these guys I worked with,
the ones that made it back,
they started trying
to get back to normal, you know?
Having families.
And then things started going wrong.
Kids born stillborn. Dead in the womb.
Crooked spines, eyes popped out.
The horror...
followed us, clung to us.
My wife Diane, she wanted a baby.
[SIGHS]
I did too.
We had a baby, and she was, um...
she was born healthy.
She was perfect, you know. Sara.
And then she died.
WOMAN: Blood pressure's dropping.
HOPPER: It wasn't an easy death. She...
suffered.
[MUFFLED WAILING]
I knew the risks, but I, um...
I hid them.
And then Diane left me.
She didn't blame me. Not with words.
After that, I was just...
I just hid myself in drugs and alcohol.
And then people
started coming into my life.
This girl El, and Joyce just happened,
and I told myself they needed me.
But that wasn't true.
That's a lie. They didn't need me.
I needed them.
You were right, what you said last night.
I knew the risks,
breaking out of here, but I did it anyway.
The minute I sent for Joyce,
the minute I sent for her,
I sentenced her to death.
Just like I did with Sara.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Everyone I love, I hurt.
See, I was wrong this whole time.
I wasn't cursed.
I am the curse.
[DISTANT, SHRILL SNARLING]
[SNARLING CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING, TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I've heard rumors of a monster.
From America.
I don't know
if what you say is true, American,
if you're truly a cursed man,
but you're right about one thing.
We are going to die in here.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[KNOCKING ECHOES LOUDLY]
[DOOR HINGE CREAKS]
Can I help you?
We need to look around.
[TENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[DEVICE TRILLING, CHIRPING ELECTRONICALLY]
[TRILLING, CHIRPING INCREASES IN SPEED]
[OMINOUS STINGER PLAYS]
WAYNE: Yep.
I think it's some kind of leak.
I haven't had a chance to fix it
with everything going on.
Pack your things. We're moving you.
[SIGHS]
[DISQUIETING SYNTH MUSIC BUILDS]
WOMAN: The devil is here.
I can feel his presence...
growing stronger each day.
But I know Chrissy's in heaven now,
looking down at us, smiling.
[SCATTERED SOBBING]
Happy to see all the lives
she touched and brightened.
But I also know she's frustrated.
Angry.
That the monster
that did this to her is still out there.
Still.
Hurting others.
[GROWING MUFFLED]
How can he live, while my angel is gone?
- I know God has a plan...
- [CLOCK CHIMES]
[EULOGY CONTINUES, MUFFLED]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
[SOBS] Lord, I've prayed.
And I just do not understand it.
[SOBS]
[ECHOING] I see no reason.
I see no reason.
JASON: So I finally
got ahold of Cappelletti.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Photos for the '86 yearbook.
Hot damn.
ANDY: Sinclair?
Goddamn traitor.
Only reason he'd lead us to a dead end.
The Hellfire Club.
- They're hiding Eddie.
- Maybe we should bring this to the cops.
The cops who think
Chrissy's a drug dealer?
Who are letting this... this psycho
go around killing people?
I'm just saying,
what if this cult is doing shit to us?
- Doing what?
- They already know we're after them.
- What if they cursed us or some shit?
- Patrick thinks he's cursed.
- [ALL CHUCKLING]
- JASON: Hey!
None of this is funny.
Look, I don't believe
in that supernatural crap, all right?
But this cult is dangerous.
We have to be smart about this.
I made a list.
Everywhere these freaks have been seen.
We divide and conquer.
Check 'em out one by one. Smoke 'em out.
We should add Reefer Rick's house to this.
What?
Reefer Rick.
He's Eddie's supplier.
He's supposed to be in prison,
but someone spotted him back in his house.
Now my parents are freaking out and shit.
It's probably nothing.
I don't know.
No, that's good. That's good.
No stones unturned.
[TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[EERIE, UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[OMINOUS STINGER PLAYS]
Yeah, that's not creepy.
- [WOOD SNAPS]
- [NAIL CLINKS]
What exactly are we supposed to be
looking for in this shithole?
NANCY: We're not sure.
We just know this house
is important to Vecna.
Because Max saw it
in Vecna's red soup mind world?
- Basically.
- Great.
Maybe it holds a clue to where Vecna is.
Why he's back. Why he killed the Creels.
And how to stop him
before he comes back for Max.
We don't think he's in here,
do we?
Guess we'll find out.
Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR THUDS]
VECNA: Max.
What are you doing in here,
Max?
[DOORKNOB RATTLES]
It's locked.
Should I knock, see if anybody's home?
ROBIN: No need.
I found a key.
- [WINDOW SHATTERS]
- [GLASS RATTLES]
- [TENSE, EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOOR SCREECHES]
[WHISTLES]
LUCAS: Looks like someone
forgot to pay their electric bill.
Where'd everyone get those?
Do you need to be told everything?
You're not a child.
- Thank you.
- Huh.
Back pocket.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
NANCY: They just left everything.
I guess a triple homicide
isn't good for resale value.
MAX: Hey, guys?
You all see that, right?
- DUSTIN: Yeah.
- STEVE: Yeah.
Is this what you saw?
In your visions?
[CHIME ECHOES]
I mean, it's... just a clock.
Right?
Like a normal old clock.
Why is this wizard obsessed with clocks?
Maybe he's, like,
a clockmaker or something?
I think you cracked the case, Steve.
NANCY: All I know is
the answers are here.
Somewhere.
Okay, everyone stay in groups of two.
Robin, upstairs.
Come on. Let's go.
[STEVE SIGHS HEAVILY]
- Was that a sigh?
- No, I did not sigh.
- Why'd you sigh?
- I didn't sigh. Just come on, dude.
- I heard you.
- W... We're just always partners, okay?
DUSTIN: You have a problem with that?
STEVE: It'd just be nice
to, I don't know, mix it up a bit.
- DUSTIN: I'm boring you? Is that it?
- No, the opposite...
- [ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
- [MUSIC BUILDS TO CLIMAX]
[YURI GRUNTS]
[LID CLATTERS]
Ah.
Hey, Yuri.
Yuri, I need to take a piss here.
Just give it up. He can't hear you.
I really do have to go, Joyce.
This isn't some ploy to escape.
[MURRAY SIGHS]
- He can't hear.
- What?
[JARS RATTLING]
Joyce, what are you doing?
[JOYCE GRUNTS]
- Joyce! Joyce!
- [GRUNTS]
- Joyce!
- My leg is too short.
Can you grab that shard with your foot?
Perhaps, you know,
we should talk this through first.
What is there to talk through?
- We cut our binds, break free.
- [DETERMINED MUSIC PLAYS]
Yes, okay. Then what?
- Then you take him out.
- Take him out?
You know karate.
You said you were a black belt.
We're 10,000 feet in the air, Joyce.
I take him, who flies this plane?
All right, so don't knock him out.
Just get his gun
and make him turn us around.
Get his gun. Just like that, huh?
- Is black not the highest color?
- Yes.
- It's just...
- Just what?
I've never fought
in a real-world scenario, okay?
I've only sparred with the other students.
How old?
It doesn't go younger than 13.
Thirteen?
But Jeremiah is 16.
Almost. His birthday is next month.
And... And Jeremiah is a ferocious fighter.
Lightning fast. Very skilled.
And I beat him.
That one time.
And certainly Yuri is not
trained or skilled like Jeremiah.
So, yes.
Yes, you're right.
I can defeat Yuri.
Absolutely.
Thank you for talking it through.
I feel much better now.
[MURRAY LAUGHS] Yeah.
[JOYCE SCOFFS]
[PLANE ENGINE WHOOSHING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVEN PANTING]
[EERIE VOCALIZATIONS]
[MISCHIEVOUS LAUGHTER]
[ELEVEN INHALES SHARPLY]
[ELEVEN GROANS]
[FRUSTRATED SOBBING]
No.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS, STOPS]
[GASPS, PANTS]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [CHIP CLATTERING]
ORDERLY: Well, well.
Look who finally decided to join us.
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
[LOW, MENACING MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop this!
Let me out!
[PANTING]
[MENACING STINGER PLAYS]
[SIGHS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
BRENNER: In 1786,
Nicolas Dalayrac
wrote an opera called Nina.
["QUAND LE BIEN-AIMÉ REVIENDRA" BY DALAYRAC PLAYING]
[WHISPERS] Papa.
It's the story about a young woman
whose lover was killed in a duel.
Nina was so traumatized
that she buried the memory.
It was as if it never happened.
Every day, she would return
to the train station
to await her lover's return.
A return that would never be.
If only Nina could know the truth.
This... This isn't real.
BRENNER: No.
But it once was.
A memory.
BRENNER: Very good.
How?
Never mind how.
ELEVEN: Let me out.
I want out!
BRENNER: I'm sorry, Eleven.
You'll have to find your own way out.
Leave your train station.
Stop waiting.
Focus.
Listen.
Remember.
I don't understand.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[YELLING] I don't understand!
[ELEVEN'S VOICE ECHOING]
Well, well.
[ARIA STOPS]
Look who finally decided to join us.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
BRENNER: Focus.
Listen.
Remember. [ECHOING]
ORDERLY: Well, well.
Look who finally decided to join us.
Someone's a sleepyhead this morning.
[YOUNG ELEVEN AND ELEVEN, OVERLAID]
I'm sorry. Am I... in trouble?
[GASPS]
ORDERLY: Trouble?
No.
No, why do you think that?
You're just missing out on all the fun.
Training starts any minute.
Okay.
Hey.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
You're going to do great today.
I just know it.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Good morning, children.
- ALL: Good morning, Papa.
How are we feeling today?
ALL: Good, Papa.
Good.
Number Twelve.
Would you be so kind and open the door?
TWELVE: Yes, Papa.
Please, follow me.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING RHYTHMICALLY]
- How's she doing?
- Very well.
She's swimming now.
Good. 'Cause I just
got off the phone with Stinson.
[SIGHS] We don't have much time.
Well then,
she'll just have to swim faster.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
- MIKE: There's one. Argyle, slow down.
- ARGYLE: There's one what?
- Slow down.
- ARGYLE: Stop barking orders.
MIKE: Argyle! Slow down!
- ARGYLE: Whoa!
- MIKE: Christ!
- 202-968-6161.
- [DIAL TONE BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE TRILLS]
Is it ringing?
No, it's just making
a bunch of weird noises.
WILL: Busy?
- MIKE: Listen to this.
- [MODEM DIAL-UP SOUNDS]
That remind you of anything?
WarGames.
JONATHAN: What?
Oh my God, we're not calling a phone.
We're calling a computer.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know if Nina's a computer
like Joshua or Owens' lab,
but Unknown Hero Agent Man
gave us access to it for a reason.
We just need to find the computer.
We find Owens, then warn him.
Then we warn Eleven.
I just need a hacker.
The only hacker that I know lives...
in Utah.
- Wait, Utah?
- Salt Lake City, to be specific.
Oh my God.
What? Why "Oh my God"?
♪ Turn around ♪
- ♪ Look at what you see ♪
- Oh no.
NeverEnding Story.
That scared the shit out of me.
The Nothing, man?
That's some proper existential shit, dude.
- [YO-YO WHIRRING]
- You can't be serious.
If we take the I-15 north,
we'll get there by morning.
Oh, you're serious.
I know it sounds insane,
but Suzie saved the world last year.
Maybe she can save it again.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC TURNS MENACING, SWELLS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[OBJECT CLATTERING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC STINGER PLAYS]
Shit. Shit.
Looks like Rick's had company.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's him.
EDDIE: Hey, Dustin.
You there?
It's Eddie. You remember me, right?
Hey, if anyone's there, I really think
I might be in a bit of trouble here.
Okay? Wheeler?
Anybody?!
STEVE: Hey, uh, Henderson?
Yeah?
Could you maybe, uh,
clarify what sort of clues
we're supposed to be looking for here?
[IN BRITISH ACCENT]
"The world is full of obvious things
which nobody by any chance ever observes."
[IN REGULAR VOICE] Sherlock Holmes.
[DUSTIN SCOFFS]
That's great.
Thanks. That's great.
Really helpful.
Sherlock...
[CHILLING STINGER PLAYS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[HIGH-PITCHED AUDIO DISTORTION]
[DISTORTION CONTINUES, STOPS]
[MENACING MUSIC BUILDS]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
NANCY: Whoa, whoa.
- NANCY: What's wrong?
- There was a spider.
- What?
- It's a black widow.
- Okay.
- Don't go in there.
Oh, oh.
- Wait, just...
- What?
- Something? Shit. Okay.
- Wait. Stop moving.
- Stop. I just... I got it. I got it.
- Thank you.
If there's a spider,
you're never gonna find it
till it lays eggs
and the babies spill out.
- What's wrong with you?
- [ROBIN CHUCKLES]
Robin, seriously.
She's got problems.
- Tell me about it.
- It's cool you two are friends now.
Maybe after we find Vecna, kill him,
save the world and stuff,
maybe we can all go out.
You know? Me, you, Robin,
Jonathan, when he's back.
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
It's not like we're dating.
Me and Robin. Not like we're dating.
- She told you? That we're not?
- Yes. She made that very clear.
Platonic with a capital P.
STEVE: Yep. Thank you.
I mean...
I would date her. It's just...
She's... We're just...
Never mind. We're friends.
- Just friends.
- Right. Right.
[TENDER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay. All better.
Great. Thanks.
[CHUCKLES] Well...
Great. Um...
Guess we should, uh,
get back to the investigation.
"The obvious things
are not what people observe."
Or... "Do... Don't observe."
Or...
Sherlock Holmes.
What?
["RUNNING UP THAT HILL" PLAYING FAINTLY OVER HEADPHONES]
[TAPE DECK CLICKS OFF]
[TAPE REWINDS]
I wish we had a longer loop.
Forty-six minutes isn't bad.
I think there are bigger concerns.
Like...
What if, by listening to this
over and over, I get sick of it,
and suddenly it's not my favorite anymore?
Will it still work? Or will Kate Bush,
like, lose her magic power or something?
Kate Bush? Never.
You're a Kate Bush fan?
Uh, yeah. Now I am.
- Really?
- Yeah, mega-fan.
She... She saved your life.
Besides, we're hot on this creep's trail.
We're gonna find Vecna
and kill him before he even thinks about
messing with you again. All right?
In fact, I bet if we hit these suckers
in the right combo,
we might just open a door
to his secret lair.
[PLAYS DISCORDANT NOTES]
Voilà. [LAUGHS]
You're such a dork.
I thought you were, like,
one of the cool kids now.
I'm not cool?
[LAUGHS]
[TENDER, EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I've really missed that.
Missed what?
Your laugh.
[TAPE DECK CLICKS]
All done.
Work your magic, Kate.
["RUNNING UP THAT HILL" PLAYING FAINTLY OVER HEADPHONES]
[LOW THRUMMING]
I promise I'm gonna stop asking this, but...
[MUSIC TURNS DISCORDANT]
...you're seeing that, right?
Yeah.
[MUSIC TURNS MENACING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
♪ Feel how it feels ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Do you want to know... ♪
Look.
["RUNNING UP THAT HILL" CONTINUES FAINTLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDS]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[BULBS POPPING]
[CHILD STRAINING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
Stop.
[BULB SIZZLES]
Very good, Two.
Very good.
Now,
which brave soul
would like to follow that?
Hmm?
- Hmm?
- [CHILDREN CLAMORING] Me. Me. Me.
[ALL REPEATING] Me. Me. Me. Me. Me. Me.
Eleven?
[CHILDREN FALL SILENT]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[EERIE AUDIO DISTORTION]
Remember to stay focused.
Find the energy.
Feel it.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANTING, WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[OTHER SUBJECTS LAUGHING]
Why does he waste so much time with her?
Hey.
Quiet.
[ELEVEN EXHALES DEEPLY]
[WHISPERS] They're laughing.
At you.
They think you're weak.
Show them, Eleven.
Show them.
[RESOLUTE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENERGY THRUMMING]
Good.
Now make it move.
[ELEVEN BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
Waste of time.
[EXHALE ECHOES]
[OMINOUS STINGER PLAYS]
[SCREAMING ECHOES FAINTLY]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[DISCOMFORTING AUDIO DISTORTION]
[MONITOR BEEPING]
- What is happening?
- WOMAN: She's going into arrest.
Okay, that's enough. Pull her out.
[ECHOING] Pull her out!
[CHAOTIC, INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS, FADES]
[AIRCRAFT WHIRRING]
[YELPS]
Naughty, naughty bird.
Did you fall out of your nest?
Where do you think you are going?
Come on.
Be a good girl now
and get back to your place.
Or what? Are you gonna shoot me?
I... I don't think the KGB would like that.
You're right, I cannot kill you.
But KGB didn't specify
condition you must arrive in.
You are fragile cargo.
You can still break.
MURRAY: Not if I break you first.
[RAPID, CONFIDENT SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
My fingers are like arrows.
My arms, like iron.
My feet, like spears.
Resist,
and I will end you.
But turn this plane around,
and I will spare your life.
[WHEEZY LAUGHTER]
[YURI LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLES]
- Kiai!
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING, STRUGGLING]
[BOTH CONTINUE GRUNTING, STRUGGLING]
[JOYCE GRUNTING]
[MURRAY EXCLAIMS]
- Ah! Kiai!
- [CLATTERING]
- [JOYCE STRAINS]
- [MURRAY GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
- [EXCLAIMS]
[SCREAMS]
[AIRCRAFT WHIRRING]
- [JOYCE GRUNTS]
- [YURI WHIMPERS]
[AIRCRAFT WHIRRING]
[BOTH GRUNTING, STRUGGLING]
- [GUN COCKS]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
[JOYCE SHOUTING] Let him go!
- Let him go!
- [CONSOLE BEEPING]
[JOYCE SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[CONFIDENT MUSIC PULSING]
My fingers are like arrows.
My arms, like iron!
My feet, like spears! [ECHOING]
Kiai!
- [GONG RINGS]
- [EXHALING]
What did you do?
What?
I said, "Don't knock him out."
[DRAMATIC STINGER PLAYS]
[CONSOLE BEEPING]
- I thought you didn't know how to fly!
- I don't!
[ENGINE SPLUTTERS, RUMBLES]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Pull up! Pull up!
I am pulling up!
[BOTH CONTINUE YELLING]
[CLATTERING]
- [MURRAY SCREAMS]
- [JOYCE SCREAMS]
[SNAPPING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[CRASH RUMBLING, FADING]
[SINISTER MUSIC BUILDS SLOWLY]
[OWL HOOTING]
It's like the Christmas lights.
The Christmas lights?
Yeah, when Will was in the Upside Down,
the lights... came to life.
Vecna's here.
In this house.
LUCAS: Just on the other side.
I think he just left the room.
Did he hear us?
Can he see us?
Headphones.
Wait, wait.
Everyone, turn off your flashlights
and spread out.
We're not gonna be able to see
if we turn off our flash... lights.
- ["RUNNING UP THAT HILL" PLAYING FAINTLY]
- Jesus Christ.
[SNARL ECHOES]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES TO BUILD]
ROBIN: I got him!
Got him!
I got him.
[ENERGY THRUMMING]
I... I had him.
Oh, whoa.
Oh, I think he's moving.
He's moving. He's moving.
[SINISTER MUSIC BUILDS]
Shit.
I lost him.
No, you didn't.
It's an attic. Of course it's an attic.
Hold up, guys.
What if he's leading us into a trap?
Guys, guys.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit, shit.
[EDDIE PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
Dude, he's not here, seriously.
Shut up and keep looking.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dustin?
Please. Are... Are you there?
Never mind.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
- [JOLTING STINGER PLAYS]
- Come with me.
[DOOR CLATTERING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WATER RIPPLES]
Holy shit.
Hey, freak!
- Where do you think you're going?
- Shit.
[TENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
- Come on!
- [ENGINE SPLUTTERS]
- [EDDIE, EMPHATICALLY] Just come on...
- You scared of some water? Let's go!
- ...you piece of shit!
- [ENGINE SPLUTTERS]
Come on. Gotta help me out here, man.
Come on.
Come on, you piece of shit!
- [ENGINE REVS]
- Come on!
EDDIE: Goddamn it!
Nope? Okay. All right. Okay.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Shit. Shit.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Flashlights.
Okay, what's happening?
[EERIE, DELICATE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENTACLES SQUELCHING WETLY]
[UNSETTLING VOCALIZATIONS]
[TENSE MUSIC BUILDS]
[CLOCK CHIMING]
Hey, stay back, man! Stay back!
Stay back!
Come on. We almost have him.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
Hey, Patrick.
Patrick!
[VECNA SNARLS]
[CLOCK CHIMING]
Patrick.
Hey, Patrick.
Patrick!
[UNSETTLING STINGER PLAYS]
[ELDRITCH MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[BONES CRACKING]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[GASPS, PANTS]
[BONES CRACKING]
[ELDRITCH MUSIC SWELLS]
[MOANS]
- [GASPS]
- [MONITOR BEEPING]
- Air.
- [ELEVEN PANTING]
Get her some air, for Christ's sake.
It's okay. It will take time to adjust.
But you're safe now, hmm?
[MEDICAL MONITOR BEEPING]
- [ELEVEN SHRIEKS]
- [BRENNER GRUNTS]
[DARK, INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PANTING]
Giving us quite the workout.
You really wanna do this again?
- No! No! No!
- [ENERGY THRUMMING]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAM ECHOES, FADES]
[EMOTIONAL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASP ECHOES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BRENNER ECHOES] Remarkable.
[SINISTER TONES PLAY]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Stay away.
I said, stay away!
[ELEVEN'S VOICE ECHOING]
You didn't think it would be that easy,
did you?
I don't understand.
I do.
[DOOR BUZZING]
[DOOR WHIRRING]
Papa?
Daughter.
["QUAND LE BIEN-AIMÉ REVIENDRA" BY DALAYRAC PLAYING]
[DOOR WHIRRING, SLAMS]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
["QUAND LE BIEN-AIMÉ REVIENDRA" CONTINUES]
["QUAND LE BIEN-AIMÉ REVIENDRA" ENDS]
- Original SUB by hadilan - subscene.com -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44