[JONATHAN] Nancy!
[PANTING] Nancy!
Come on, come on.
Nancy!
Where are you?
[NANCY ECHOING] Jonathan! Jonathan!
Jonathan!
Jonathan, I'm right here!
Nancy!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[NANCY] Jonathan, where are you?
Jonathan! [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Jonathan!
Jonathan, I'm right...
I'm right here!
- [FAINTLY] Where are you?
- [PANTING]
- I'm right here!
- [NANCY] Jonathan!
I'm right here! Nancy!
- Just follow my voice!
- [PANTING] Jonathan!
[JONATHAN IN DISTANCE]
Follow my voice, Nancy, I'm right here!
Nancy!
- [GROWLING]
- [GASPS]
Nancy!
[PANTING]
- [GROWLING CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SQUELCHING]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Nancy?
Nancy.
[JONATHAN IN DISTANCE] Nancy!
Follow my voice!
[MONSTER GROWLING]
Nancy?
[JONATHAN GASPS]
- [NANCY] Jonathan!
- Nancy!
- [NANCY STRAINING]
- [JONATHAN GRUNTING]
[NANCY SOBBING]
[JONATHAN PANTING] I got you.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[POP SONG PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
I just don't understand
why we're coming out here.
- She obviously doesn't wanna talk to you.
- That's... that's not it.
Oh, really? Because no girl
would ever blow off King Steve.
She was acting weird.
I mean, something was wrong.
So what? [SCOFFS]
Like, you're worried about her?
- What?
- Aw, you are.
- Aw, Steve has a heart.
- Would you just... Stop.
- Oh, Stevey's in love.
- Would you just shut up?
- Who knew?
- Shut up!
[CHUCKLING] Jeez.
- [CAROL] Damn. Sorry.
- [TOMMY CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS] So this is it, huh?
Princess' castle.
[STEVE] I'll just be a minute.
[JOYCE] Look, we gotta
go through this again.
- I told you everything that I saw.
- Oh, gosh. Tell me again.
- Upstairs or downstairs?
- Upstairs.
There was a laboratory.
It was where they must do experiments
or something, and then there was...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
There was this kid's room.
- How do you know it was a kid's room?
- More like a prison.
So why would you think
it was a kid's room, then?
Because, I told you,
the size of the bed, there was a drawing,
there was a stuffed animal...
[STAMMERS] You didn't say
there was a drawing.
Yeah, there was a drawing of a...
an adult and a child.
- It said "Eleven" on it.
- Was it good?
It was a kid's drawing, Joyce.
It was stick figures.
[SIGHS]
Wasn't Will.
Earl...
The night that Benny died,
Earl said he saw some kid
with a shaved head with Benny.
Now, I pressed him,
he said it might be Will, but maybe...
Wait... Maybe, it wasn't?
Look... this woman, Terry Ives,
she claims to have lost
her daughter, Jane.
She sued Brenner,
she sued the government...
Now, the claims came to nothing,
but what if...
I mean,
what if this whole time I've been...
I've been looking for Will...
I've been chasing after some other kid?
- [JONATHAN GASPS]
- [MONSTER GROWLING]
- [GROWLING]
- [GASPS]
[JONATHAN] Nancy!
[MONSTER GROWLS]
Better?
Yeah.
Is this okay?
Uh, I found it in the closet.
I can go home.
[STAMMERS] I just figured...
Yeah, no.
I... [STAMMERS]
- I don't wanna be alone.
- [SIGHS]
- Do you?
- No. Uh... no.
[SIGHS]
Can you just come up here?
Yeah.
- Do you want the lights off, or...
- [SOFTLY] On.
[SOFTLY] Yeah.
You know, it...
it can't get us in here.
We don't know that.
Uh, yeah, it's Ives.
Terry Ives. That's with a "Y."
Yeah, I got a pen.
Hang on.
Mmm-hmm.
Great, thanks.
I really appreciate this, Frank.
Say hi to the boys for me, too, would you?
Did you get it?
- I got it.
- Okay.
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
[PAGES RUSTLING]
Oh...
Hey.
[NANCY] Hey.
[GRUNTS] Couldn't sleep?
Every time I close my eyes, I just...
keep seeing that... thing.
Wherever I was, that place...
I think that it lives there.
It was feeding there.
Feeding on that deer.
That means that if...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
if Will and Barbara...
Hey.
My mom said she talked to Will.
If he's alive,
there's a chance Barbara is, too.
That means that she's trapped...
in that place.
We have to find it again.
You wanna go back out there?
Maybe we don't have to.
When I saw it,
it was feeding on that deer.
- Meaning it's... it's a predator, right?
- Right.
And it seems to hunt at night, like a...
a lion or a coyote.
But it doesn't hunt in packs like them.
It's always alone, like...
like a bear.
And remember at Steve's,
when Barb cut herself?
- And then, last night, the deer...
- Hmm, it was bleeding, too.
One sec.
Sharks can detect blood
in one part per million.
That's one drop of blood in a million,
and they can smell it
from a quarter mile away.
So you're saying it can detect blood?
[SOFTLY] It's just a theory.
We could test it.
But if it works...
At least we'll know it's coming.
- [DOOR KNOB RATTLES]
- [BOTH GASP]
- [NANCY SIGHS]
- [KAREN] Honey, are you up?
Yeah, I'm... I'm getting dressed.
[KAREN] I, uh, made
some blueberry pancakes.
I'll be down in a second.
- [FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
- [SIGHING]
[JONATHAN SIGHING]
- [SIGHS]
- Your mom doesn't knock?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hi. Scott Clarke?
- Uh, yes.
The same Scott Clarke
who teaches science and AV
- at Hawkins Middle?
- The very same.
Oh, wonderful.
...and we're making a newsletter,
which we'll send out monthly.
It'll showcase all the latest equipment,
as well as how-to articles,
which the kids write themselves.
Oh, that's neat.
What we're really trying to do here,
Mr. Clarke...
Uh, please, call me Scott.
Scott.
What we're trying to do here, Scott,
is to connect kids from all over the state
and give them
the support and encouragement
to pursue careers in technology.
We feel these are the kinds of kids
that are going to make Indiana proud.
I agree, yes.
Completely.
So, you know any kids
you think might wanna participate?
Oh, I have a few in mind.
[MIKE SIGHS] I just...
I can't believe she didn't come back.
- [DUSTIN] She's gotta be close.
- She said it wasn't safe.
She just messed up the compasses
because she wanted to protect us.
- She didn't betray us.
- Mike, calm down.
I shouldn't have yelled at her.
I never should've done that.
- Mike, this isn't your fault.
- Yeah, it's Lucas'.
It wasn't his fault, either.
- It wasn't his fault?
- No.
So you're saying
he wasn't way out of line?
- Totally, but so were you!
- What?
- And so was Eleven.
- Oh, give me a break!
No, Mike, you give me a break!
All three of you were being
a bunch of little assholes!
I was the only reasonable one.
But the bottom line is...
you pushed first.
And you know the rule.
You draw first blood...
No! No way!
I'm not shaking his hand.
- You're shaking his hand!
- No, I'm not.
This isn't a discussion.
This is the rule of law.
Obey or be banished from the party.
Do you wanna be banished?
- No.
- Good.
Where are we going?
Where do you think?
We're going to get Lucas.
And then we're gonna find Eleven.
[DOOR OPENS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Today is a very special day.
Do you know why?
Because today, we make history.
Today, we make contact.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[SIGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[KAREN] Here you go.
Ah... yum.
Okay.
Now, sweetie, swallow the pancake.
Where is Nancy?
I thought she was coming down.
[SIGHS] She is.
Uh, she was.
I don't know.
- Nancy, what's taking so long?
- [MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY]
Nancy?
- [DOOR KNOB RATTLES]
- [SIGHS] Nancy, come on.
- [SIGHS]
- [MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nan...
[DOORBELL RINGS]
What do you want?
[SIGHS] I drew first blood, so...
Okay, I'll shake.
On one condition.
We forget the weirdo
and go straight to the gate.
- Then the deal's off.
- Fine!
- [DUSTIN] No, no, not fine!
Guys, seriously?
Do you even remember
what happened on the Bloodstone Pass?
[SIGHS] We couldn't agree on what path
to take, so we split up the party
and those trolls took us out one by one.
And it all went to shit.
And we were all disabled!
So we stick together, no matter what!
Yeah, I agree. But this is the party,
right here in this room.
- El is one of us now.
- Um, no, she's not. Not even close!
Never will be.
She's a liar, a traitor...
She was just trying to keep us safe!
She didn't mean to hurt you.
It was an accident!
An accident?
All right, accident or not...
- admit it, it was a little awesome.
- Awesome?
Yeah, she threw you in the air
with her mind!
I could have been killed!
Which is exactly why we need her.
She's a weapon!
Do you seriously wanna fight
the Demogorgon with your wrist rocket?
That's like R2-D2
going to fight Darth Vader.
We're no use to Will if we're dead.
If you two wanna waste your time
looking for a traitor, go ahead,
'cause I'm not spending my time
on her anymore. No way!
I'm going to the gate.
I'm gonna find Will.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON PA]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[DR. BRENNER]It's okay, Eleven.
Don't be frightened.
These are all friends.
They're just here to watch.
Don't focus on them.
Stay in here, like before.
Yes, Papa.
Now, remember.
Whatever it is, it can't hurt you.
Not from here.
So there's nothing to be frightened of.
It's reaching out to you...
'cause it wants you.
Hmm?
It's calling you...
so don't turn away from it this time.
I want you to find it.
Understand?
Yes.
[MAN]Are you lost?
Is your mom here?
Your dad?
Mouth breather.
- What should we do?
- Uh...
Call the police.
Excuse me. Young lady!
You know you have to pay for those!
- Hey! Stop right...
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
- Please.
- [WOMAN GRUNTS]
[STAMMERS] You have to pay for those!
Stop right there!
Thief! Thief!
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
- [CLAMORING]
Can I help you?
Hi, we're looking for Terry Ives.
Does she live here?
- Who's asking?
- The Hawkins chief of police.
And you want to talk to my sister?
Well, if your sister's Terry Ives,
then, yeah, we do.
Okay, well, you can come in,
but if you want Terry
to tell you anything,
you're about five years too late.
[TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY]
Terry, you have some visitors.
Hello.
My name's Joyce Byers.
Uh, this is Hopper.
We drove over from Hawkins.
Um, you see, uh, my son...
he's been missing for almost a week now,
and, um, we were wondering
if we could talk to you
about your daughter, Jane?
If there's anything that you could tell us
about when she was taken...
What was your relationship
with Dr. Brenner?
You guys keep in touch?
This is, uh... this is him.
[STAMMERING] This is Will.
Uh, you may have seen him on...
on the news.
- Uh...
- What's wrong with her?
I told you, you're wasting your time.
[DUSTIN] This is weird without Lucas.
- He should've shaken my hand.
- He's just jealous.
What are you talking about?
[SIGHS] Sometimes, your total
obliviousness just blows my mind.
He's your best friend, right?
- Yeah... I mean, I don't know.
- It's fine. I get it.
I didn't get here until the fourth grade.
He had the advantage of living next door.
But none of that matters.
What matters
is that he is your best friend.
And then this girl shows up
and starts living in your basement,
and all you ever want to do
is pay attention to her.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is. And you know it.
And he knows it.
But no one ever says anything
until you both start punching
and yelling at each other
like goblins
with intelligence scores of zero.
- Now everything's weird.
- He's not my best friend.
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah, right.
- [SIGHS] I mean, he is, but so are you.
- And so is Will.
- Can't have more than one best friend.
- Says who?
- Says logic.
Well, I call bull on your logic,
because you're my best friend, too.
Okay.
[PANTING]
Whoa.
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- [DUSTIN] You don't think...
[PANTING] Uh... definitely.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING ON TV]
[HOST ON TV]Are you ready?
[BECKY] She was a part of some study
in college.
- MK Ultra?
- Yeah, that's the one.
[EXHALES] Was, uh, started in the '50s.
By the time Terry got involved,
it was supposed to be ramping down,
but the drugs just got crazier.
Messed her up good.
This was the CIA that ran this?
You and Terry would've gotten along.
"The Man," with a big capital "M."
[SIGHING] They'd pay... you know,
a couple hundred bucks
to people like my sister,
give 'em drugs, psychedelics.
LSD, mostly.
And then they'd strip her naked
and put her in these isolation tanks.
- Isolation tanks?
- [BECKY] Yeah.
These big bathtubs, basically,
filled with salt water,
so you can float around in there.
You lose any sense of, uh...
sense and feel nothing, see nothing.
They wanted to expand
the boundaries of the mind.
Real hippie crap.
I... I mean, it's not like they were
forcing her to do any of this stuff.
The thing is, though, is that
she didn't know
she was pregnant at the time.
Jane.
[SIGHS]
Do you have any pictures of her?
I don't think you guys understand.
Terry miscarried in the third trimester.
She keeps all of this up.
Been doing it for 12 years.
[SIGHS]
Terry, uh, pretends like Jane is real,
- like she's gonna come home someday.
- [LULLABY PLAYS FROM MOBILE]
Says she's special.
Born with "abilities."
Abilities?
[BONES CRACKING]
You read any Stephen King?
- [HISSES]
- [BEEPING]
[STAMMERS]
[CHUCKLES]
You guys look scared, actually.
[CHUCKLES] I mean, it's all make-believe.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What... what kind of abilities?
Telepathy, telekinesis...
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
You know, shit you can do with your mind.
That's why the big, bad Man
stole Jane away.
[YELLING] Papa!
Her baby's a weapon,
off fighting the commies.
You know, the doctors all say
it's a coping mechanism.
You know, to deal with the guilt.
Do you think there is any chance
she could be telling the truth?
[STAMMERING] About having had the kid.
There is no birth certificate,
nothing from the hospital.
Doctors and nurses
all confirm that she miscarried.
Yeah, but that could've been covered up.
Right?
Like I said, you and Terry
would've gotten along.
Oh, man.
[GRUNTS]
[CLATTERING]
And I'll have four boxes of the .38s.
What you kids doin' with all this?
Um...
- Monster hunting.
- Huh. [SCOFFS]
[CASH REGISTER DINGS]
"Monster hunting"?
You know, last week...
I was shopping for a new top
I thought Steve might like.
It took me and Barb all weekend.
It seemed like life or death, you know?
And... and now...
You're shopping for bear traps
with Jonathan Byers.
Yeah.
What's the weirdest part?
Me or the bear trap?
You.
It's definitely you.
[CHUCKLES]
- [CAR HORN HONKING]
- [REED] Hey, Nance!
Can't wait to see your movie. [LAUGHS]
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
What?
Hey! Where are you going?
- [PANTING]
- Nancy, wait!
[WHIMPERS]
Nancy!
[MAN 1] I can't believe it.
[MAN 2] These kids!
- [JONATHAN] Jesus.
- [SIGHS]
Wow.
- [SPRAY CAN HISSING]
- [TOMMY LAUGHING]
[JONATHAN] Wait!
[CAROL] Tommy,
you write like a three-year-old.
[TOMMY] Shut up!
[NICOLE] I didn't know you could spell.
[TOMMY SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[LAUGHTER]
Aw, hey there, princess!
[TOMMY] Uh-oh! She looks upset.
[CAROL] Oh!
[TOMMY] Damn!
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with you?
I was worried about you.
I can't believe that I was
actually worried about you. [SCOFFS]
- What are you talking about?
- I wouldn't lie if I were you.
You don't want to be known
as the lying slut now, do you?
Speak of the devil.
Hi.
You came by last night?
Ding! Ding! Ding!
Does she get a prize?
Look, I don't know what you think you saw,
but it wasn't like that.
What, you just let him into your room
to... study?
Or for another
pervy photo session? [LAUGHS]
- We were just...
- [STEVE] You were just what?
Finish that sentence.
Finish the sentence.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCOFFS] Go to hell, Nancy.
Come on, Nancy, let's just leave.
You know what, Byers?
I'm actually kind of impressed.
I always took you for a queer,
but I guess you're just
a little screw-up like your father.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that house is full of screw-ups.
You know, I guess I shouldn't
really be surprised.
A bunch of screw-ups in your family.
- Jonathan, leave it.
- I mean, your mom...
I'm not even surprised
what happened to your brother.
[NANCY] Steve, shut up!
I'm sorry I have to be
the one to tell you,
but the Byers, their family,
it's a disgrace to the entire...
[GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
- [JONATHAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [GRUNTS]
- [NANCY] Steve!
- [TOMMY] Oh!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [NANCY] Steve.
- [GROANS]
Stop! Steve!
Knock it off, you guys!
- [CAROL] Get off of him, seriously!
- Kick his ass, man!
- [CAROL] Get off! Stop!
- [BOTH CONTINUE GRUNTING]
- Get in there, he's going to hurt himself!
- Easy, easy!
Hey. Hey! Get out of here!
Get out of here! Get out of here!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Jonathan, stop!
Stop! You're going to hurt him!
- Jonathan, stop!
- [SIRENS WAILING]
[TOMMY] Cops!
[NANCY] Guys... Jonathan, get off of him!
- Stop it!
- [TOMMY] Cops! Come on!
- Stop it! Come on!
- Cops!
- You have to stop!
- Just go, Carol!
- [NANCY] Stop it!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
Hey, he's had enough, man!
I said he's had enough!
- Kids! All right!
- Stop it!
[INDISTINCT CLAMORING]
[CALLAHAN] Oh! My nose!
[POWELL] Calm him down!
- [GRUNTING]
- Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hey! Hey, uh-uh. Uh-uh.
Come here, little guys! Come here!
- [JONATHAN] Get off!
- I got this one!
[CALLAHAN] Get back here!
Get back here, you little punks!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING ON TV]
[MAN ON TV]
Good gift for a college student...
[CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[HOPPER] Well, thank you for your time.
We appreciate it.
[BECKY] Hmm, yeah,
I'm sorry I couldn't be of more help.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Good luck.
- [HOPPER] Thank you.
[SIGHING]
Hey...
[SOFTLY] What?
We're gonna find him.
Yeah, like Terry found her daughter?
We're close.
[BREATH TREMBLING] Twelve years?
Twelve years she's been looking for her...
And then she shows up
at Benny's five nights ago,
which means we've got a chance.
You know what I would give?
For a chance?
[CALLAHAN OVER RADIO]
Hey, Chief, you there?
- Hey, Chief?
- Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, a fight broke out here and...
- Cal, I don't have time for this.
- It's Jonathan Byers.
You haven't seen Joyce, have you?
Do you think we'll be out of here soon?
You, yes. Him, no.
He assaulted a police officer.
- [ICE CUBES CLATTER]
- Well, how long are you gonna keep him?
You and your boyfriend
have big plans, do you?
[CHUCKLES] He's not my boyfriend.
I think you better tell him that.
What?
Only love makes you that crazy,
sweetheart.
And that damn stupid.
[SIGHS]
Found some ice.
Thanks.
[SNIFFS]
[SIGHS]
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
[SIGHS]
[DUSTIN SHOUTING IN THE DISTANCE] El!
[MIKE SHOUTING] Eleven!
- Eleven! El!
- El!
Eleven!
[PANTING]
- Hey, stop. Do you hear that?
- What?
El!
El?
Hey, there, Frogface.
Toothless.
Shit! Run, Mike!
- What?
- Run! Come on!
[TROY] You're dead, Wheeler.
[DUSTIN] Move, Mike!
Mike, come on, run!
[BEEPING]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
[BEEPING INTENSIFIES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PANTING]
[GROANS] Cramp!
- Just keep going!
- [GRUNTS]
Keep going!
Shit!
- Stay back!
- Don't come any closer!
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCOFFS] Nice throw, numbnuts.
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
- [GASPS]
- Get off! Get off me!
Let him go! Let him go!
- Stay back, or I cut him!
- What do you want?
I want to know how you did it!
- How I did what?
- [DUSTIN WHIMPERS]
I know you did something to me.
Some nerdy science shit
to make me do that.
You mean piss your pants?
Our friend has superpowers,
and she squeezed your tiny bladder
with her mind.
- Shut up!
- [GROANING]
I think I should save Toothless here
a trip to the dentist.
Help him lose the rest of his baby teeth.
Let him go.
Let him go!
I'll let him go, sure.
- But first... it's your turn.
- [PANTING]
My turn for what?
Wet yourself.
- What?
- Jump...
or Toothless here
gets an early trip to the dentist.
[DUSTIN] Stop! No!
[GASPING]
I'll cut him right now!
[WHIMPERING]
All right, just hold on!
Hold on!
Mike, don't do it.
I don't need my baby teeth, Mike!
Mike, seriously, don't!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DUSTIN] Mike, don't do it!
Seriously, don't do it, man!
Seriously, don't!
Troy, I don't think
this is a good idea, man.
[DUSTIN] Mike, don't!
- Dentist's office opens in five...
- [DUSTIN PANTING]
Four! Three!
- Two!
- Mike!
[TROY] One!
- [MIKE SCREAMS]
- [GASPS]
Holy shit.
[MIKE GASPING]
[WHIMPERING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[GRUNTS]
- [BONE CRACKS]
- [SCREAMING]
[TROY] She broke my arm! My arm!
Go.
[TROY] Let's get out of here! Let's go!
[JAMES] Go!
Yeah, that's right!
You better run!
She's our friend and she's crazy!
You come back here and she'll kill you!
You hear me?
She'll kill you, you sons of bitches!
[ECHOING] She'll kill you, you hear me?
[TICKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WATER TRICKLING]
[MONSTER GROWLING]
[GROWLING]
- [ROARS]
- [SCREAMING]
[LOUD BANGING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[MIKE] El, are you okay?
El?
[SOBBING] Mike... I'm sorry.
Sorry? What are you sorry for?
The gate...
I opened it.
I'm the monster.
No. No, El, you're not the monster.
You saved me.
Do you understand?
I have eyes on 'em now.
They're heading home.
[ENGINE STARTING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]