What was that?
(IN RUSSIAN)
I told them they should have sex.
They have not had sex?
No.
And why all this?
If I just turn the keys,
it's like turning off a car.
But then the car still works, does it not?
Yes.
And do you want the car to still work
or do you want it to explode?
I want the car to explode.
Good. Then do this.
Just make sure you are nowhere near it
when it does. It is not pretty.
Turns people into dust.
And then...
It's over.
And I become an American citizen
and join in the fun, yes?
Who said you had to be an American
to join the fun?
It doesn't getmore American
than this, my friend.
Fatty foods, ugly decadence,
rigged games...
They are rigged, these games?
Yes.
They do not look rigged.
That's just it, my dear Alexei.
They have been designed
to present the illusion of fairness!
But it's all a scam, a trick,
to put your money
in the rich man's pocket.
That, my dear friend, is...
America.
But, hey...
knock yourself out.
Where are you going?
To get us the closest thing to food
I can find.
Look!
It's not rigged!
It's not rigged.
Traitor.
Keep pressure on it.
I'll get you help.
I'll get help.
Heading to "Big Top."
Northeast side of the fair.
Vasilev, are you there? Vasilev? Answer!
Comrade!
Get off me!
On the lower level...
We've found the children.
They are still in the mall. Lower level.
Keep all entrances locked down.
I repeat...
Everyone, get over here.
I found them.
What the hell?