I have a question.
What if I don't want to answer?
Have you always been a coward?
Yuri Ismaylov
is many things, you traitor.
But he is…
No coward.
If that is so,
why do you continue to stall?
What do I owe these Americans?
Nothing!
This isn't just about America, smuggler.
They have warned us
of a great evil in the world.
An evil that does not rest,
that does not respect borders.
After it has consumed
everything in their land,
it will come for us.
For our families.
For our Motherland.
You saw it with your own eyes.
You know it to be true.
And yet you continue to play tricks!
I was told the Peanut Butter Smuggler
was once a great man.
Before he lost his way to drink and cards.
That he led his men to victory
over the Chinese in Damansky.
Is it true?
It is true.
That hero, where is he now?
Because I do not see him.
What happened here?