What's going on there?
Get the power back on!
Tell him that the prisoners
are contained...
and that you're working on the power.
Tell him!
And that door there, where does it lead?
To... to cell block two...
No cell blocks!
I need a safe way out of here.
Lower your weapons.
Lower your weapons!
Don't shoot!
Stop!
You can't go in there!
It's dangerous!
[ROARING]
Son of a bitch!
You Neanderthal...
If I get a whiff of any
funny business, smuggler...
I will not hesitate to kill you.
In fact... I am just looking for a reason.
Understand?
Are you a parrot, cop?
You keep repeating the same thing.
Yes, hello, miss.
I'd like to place a call to
the United States. A very sick relative.
Correct. Yes... The number is...