Get him out. Go! Go!
God! Hold on, sweetie!
I'm right here. Just hold on.
- Vitals?
- Heart rate 220. Temperature's 106.
Will, where does it hurt?
All over.
She says he feels like he's burning.
Check for burns.
I don't see anything.
- Where does it hurt the most, Will?
- Everywhere! Everywhere!
Wait a sec. How big?
First it was like that.
Now he's like this.
I swear to God, man,
it's just some little lizard, okay?
- It's not a lizard.
- How do you know?
- How do I know if it's not?
- How do you know it's not just a lizard?
Because his face opened up
and he ate my cat.
I don't hear shit.
He's in there.
All right, listen, kid. I swear, if this
is some sort of Halloween prank,
- you're dead.
- It's not.
- All right?
- It's not a prank.
Get it out of my face.
You got a key for this thing?
Let me see that.
He must be further down there.
I'll stay up here
in case he tries to escape.
Steve?
Steve, what's going on down there?
Get down here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
No way.
That thing, it...
it did something to him.
Okay. And these now-memories,
as you call them,
how long has he been experiencing them?
I told you, since Thursday.
Since I found him in the field.
And why wasn't he brought in?
I have been bringing him in,
and what have you done?
Nothing. Nothing!
These are new symptoms, Joyce.
No. No, he has been telling you
over and over that something's wrong,
and you said it was all in his head.
You said, "Be patient."
Those were your words.
I understand that you're upset,
okay? I get it.
I would be, too, if I were in your shoes.
But we are all in the same boat here,
and I just need you to try...
What? Stay calm? Trust you?
No, I want him transferred
to a real hospital.
Well, you know that's not possible.
He really will get
the best treatment here, Mrs. Byers.
The very best.
And what are you
treating him for, exactly?
Can anyone tell me what's wrong with him?
Can a single person in this room
tell me what is wrong with my boy?
What is wrong with my boy?
You see why I have
to stop the truth from spreading, too.
Just the same as those weeds there.
By whatever means necessary.
Whoo-hoo!
- To taking down the man.
Commie bastards sure know how
to make a spirit. Am I right?
- Oh, no, no, no. We... we can't.
- Yeah, no. No, I've got to drive.
Drive? What, tonight?
Our parents...
Would be proud
if they knew what you were up to.
Just tell 'em you're at Tammy's
or Dawn's or whoever's,
and take my guest room.
- I mean, do... do you want to stay?
- Well, it is pretty late.
Okay. Uh...
Could I use the sofa?
Okay, I'm confused.
What's going on here? A lovers' quarrel?
- No, no. I mean, we're just friends.
- Friends.
You've told me a lot of shockers today,
but that, that is the first lie.
- It's not a lie.
- No?
You're young, attractive.
You've got chemistry, history,
plus the real shit, shared trauma.
Trust issues, am I right?
Something to do with your dad.
- What? No, I mean, my dad's...
- An asshole.
Hmm. It is a curse to see so clearly.
You, you're harder to read.
Probably, like everyone,
afraid of what would happen if you
accepted yourself for who you really are
and retreated back to the safety of...
- Name? Name?
- Steve.
Oh. Steve. We like Steve.
Yes.
- But we don't love Steve.
- What?
No, we... I mean, I do.
There it is, ladies and germs,
the second lie of the evening.
So, how'd I do?
My goodness.
You two are adorable, aren't you?
Listen...
...there's a pull-out sofa in my study
if you want it.
But if I were you,
I'd cut the bullshit
and share the damn bed.
Afraid.
Trust issues?
Trust issues.
Retreat?
I don't retreat.
Trust issues? I do not...
Oh. Hey.
Hey.
I just, uh...
I... I just wanted to say that...
Oh, no, don't... I mean... He's so drunk.
- Wasted.
- Yeah.
I mean, what? He knows us for a couple
of hours, and he's got us all figured out?
Exactly.
God. Okay, yeah. I feel...
I'm glad we feel the same way.
Yeah. Yeah, it's fine.
Uh...
So, uh, good night, I guess.
Yeah, um, good night.
Oh, He-Man, thank you for saving my life.
What strong muscles you have.
- I knew it.
- Hey! They're in love!
No, actually, they're not.
They don't even exist on the same planet.
Aren't you too old
to be playing with toys?
That... that's not the point.
The point is to stay out of my room.
Then tell your little nerdy friend
to shut his mouth.
What are you talking about?
"Code red, Lucas. Code red. Code red."
Bunch of nerds.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Dustin!
This is Lucas. Do you copy? Dustin?
- Well, well, well, look who it is.
- Sorry, man.
My stupid sister turned it off.
Well, when you were having
sister problems, Dart grew again,
he escaped, and I'm pretty sure
he's a baby Demogorgon.
- Wait. What?
- I'll explain later.
- Meet me and Steve at the old junkyard.
- Steve?
And bring your binoculars
and wrist rocket.
Steve Harrington?
All right, let's go.
Just be there, stat. Over and out.
All right, cowboy, good news.
We're giving you the green light.
How you feeling?
Never better.
All right, well, got a present for ya.
- The hell is that?
- Uh, something you should see.
Watch your step.
All living organisms develop
defense mechanisms against attack.
They adapt. They find some way to survive.
Oh, my God.
It's pretty impressive, isn't it?
It's been spreading,
growing beneath us like some cancer.
- Why aren't you burning it?
- There's a complication.
They made me sign,
like, a thousand documents.
I mean...
we all had to. We had to.
I mean, I lost track at a certain point.
They're gonna make you
do the same. I'm sure.
Yeah. Well, hey, whatever.
What kind of documents?
Uh, confidentiality,
and there were these official forms
saying, like, nothing ever happened,
which is why...
Will got lost in the woods.
Yeah.
Man, I always thought stuff like this
happened in movies and comic books.
Certainly not in Hawkins,
and certainly not to someone like you.
- Or you.
- Yeah.
Bob Newby, superhero.
You cold?
Uh, just a little jitters, I guess.
Hey, don't you start worrying about me.
- Okay.
- Okay? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
It's not like you didn't warn me.
"This is not a normal family."
- Isn't that what you said?
- Yeah.
You weren't kidding.
It kinda makes my idea of moving to Maine
sound a little less crazy, right?
Oh, it... it's not crazy at all.
Mom?
Hey.
Is there a doctor? We need a doctor!
- Sweetie, how you feeling? You okay?
- Okay, they're on their way.
Hey.
- Who is that?
- What?
- It's me, big guy. It's Bob.
Are you a...
doctor?
No. No, it's just me. Just... just Bob.
So, Jonathan, how was the pull-out?
Uh, sorry?
The sofa.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it was good.
I bet.
Oops.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we just, um...
We just had some fun girl time.
- Will you be back for dinner?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah, I'll be home real soon.
- Say hey to Ally for me.
Okay. All right.
I love you, too, Mom. Bye.
She said Mike's at your brother's house.
They just had a sleepover. So...
Oh, okay.
Do you wanna try again?
No. No, it's fine. They're probably
just at the matinée or something.
Yeah, I'm sure.
For your travels.
And to water it down.
Got it.
Thank you for everything.
Don't thank me yet.
Just keep your eyes on the papers, hmm?
And if you need to reach me again...
don't.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
- Max, are you getting that or what?
- Okay!
Swear to God, Max!
What are you doing here?
- I have proof.
- What?
Proof that what I told you was real.
But we have to hurry.
What kind of proof?
Who the hell were you talking to?
Mormons.
Mormons?
Talkative ones.
Come on, hop on.
Hurry.
This better be good, stalker.
Do you know your name?
Will.
- Your full name?
- William Byers.
Do you know... Do you know who I am?
A doctor.
Have we met before?
- I don't remember.
- Hmm.
You don't remember me?
Okay.
How about, uh... How about this guy here?
Know who that is?
It's all right. Take your time.
That's my friend.
Mike.
What about me, kid? You remember me?
They tell me you helped save me
last night. You remember that?
Do you remember anything about last night?
About what happened?
I remember they hurt me.
You mean the doctors?
No. The soldiers.
The soldiers hurt you?
They shouldn't have done that.
It upset him.
You say, "Upset him." Is that him?
Okay. Okay, I wanna try something.
It's gonna seem a little odd at first,
but I think it's really gonna help us
understand what's going on.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Now, Will, I want you to just let us know
if you feel anything. Okay?
- Do you feel anything?
- Little sting.
It stings? Where?
My chest.
- Okay, son.
- Sweetie...
- How about now?
- It... it burns.
Ah!
- It burns.
- Where?
Everywhere.
That's enough. That's enough!
Stop! You heard her! That's enough!
That's it! We're done!
Okay.
Sweetie... Sweetie. It's okay.
Our best guess right now
is it's some kind of virus
which is causing
this neurological disorder.
Now, when... when a typical virus
attaches itself to its host...
...it duplicates, right? It spreads,
essentially hijacking the host.
A virus is alive. It has an intelligence.
That's not... That's not unusual.
What is so unusual here,
this virus... the infected hosts
seem to be communicating.
It has some sort of a hive intelligence,
and it's connecting all the hosts.
The good news is a virus can be cured.
We... we're gonna continue to run tests.
We're gonna see what we find.
What happens
when he can't remember anything?
When there's
nothing else there?
What happens when my boy is gone?
All right,
so let me get this straight.
You kept something
you knew was probably dangerous
in order to impress a girl who...
who you just met?
All right,
that's grossly oversimplifying things.
I mean, why would a girl
like some nasty slug anyway?
An interdimensional slug?
Because it's awesome.
Well, even if she thought it was cool,
which she didn't, I... I just...
I don't know. I just feel like
you're trying way too hard.
Well, not everyone can have
your perfect hair, all right?
It's not about the hair, man.
The key with girls is just...
just acting like you don't care.
- Even if you do?
- Yeah, exactly. It drives them nuts.
- Then what?
- You just wait until, uh...
- until you feel it.
- Feel what?
It's like before it's gonna storm,
you know?
You can't see it,
but you can feel it, like this, uh...
electricity, you know?
Oh, like in the electromagnetic field
when the clouds in the atmosphere...
No, no, no, no, no.
Like a... Like a sexual electricity.
Oh.
You feel that and then you make your move.
So that's when you kiss her?
- No, whoa, whoa. Slow down, Romeo.
- Sorry.
Sure, okay, some girls, yeah,
they want you to be aggressive.
You know, strong, hot and heavy, like a...
- I don't know, like a lion.
- Mmm.
But others, you gotta be slow,
you gotta be stealthy, like a...
like a ninja.
What type is Nancy?
Nancy's different.
She's different than the other girls.
Yeah, she seems pretty special, I guess.
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
But this girl's special, too, you know.
It's just, like, something about her.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
You're not falling in love with this girl,
are you?
Uh, no. No.
- Okay, good. Don't.
- I won't.
She's only gonna break your heart,
and you're way too young for that shit.
Fabergé.
What?
It's Fabergé Organics.
Use the shampoo and conditioner,
and when your hair's damp...
It's not wet, okay?
- When it's damp...
- Damp.
You do four puffs
of the Farrah Fawcett spray.
- Farrah Fawcett spray?
- Yeah, Farrah Fawcett.
You tell anyone I just told you that
and your ass is grass.
You're dead, Henderson. Do you understand?
Yup.
Okay.
- Farrah Fawcett, really?
- I mean, she's hot.
Yeah.
Hey, it's, uh...
It's me.
I know that I've been
gone too long, and, uh...
It's... I just, I want you to know
that it's not about you
and it's not about our fight.
Okay?
Something came up, and I will...
I will explain it all when I see you.
I just... I want you to know
that I'm not mad.
I'm just sorry.
About everything.
I...
I don't want you to get hurt at all.
And I don't wanna lose you.
Just make sure you heat up
some real food. Not just Eggos.
And I want you to eat all the peas,
even if they're mushy and gross. And...
I will be home soon.
This is him last week.
And there are the hippocampal
abnormalities we had discussed.
Nothing out of line with what we've seen
from others suffering
from post-traumatic stress. But...
this is Will from last night.
And as you can see,
there are now abnormalities
in the limbic and paralimbic areas.
And this...
is from an hour ago.
- I don't hear any suggestions.
- We have bigger problems than the boy.
- Do we?
- We can't keep delaying the burn.
You're talking about putting...
putting a Band-Aid on this.
- Right now, a Band-Aid is the best option.
- It's our only option.
- And if it kills the boy?
- Then quite frankly, Sam, it kills him.
Say that to me again.
The rate this is spreading,
he'll be lost by the end of the day.
What we do or don't do
won't change the outcome.
We have to start the burn.
Where you going?
I'm going to think.
What the hell is taking so long?
Hey... doctors take forever, always.
Just try and relax. Just be patient.
You know, I just...
Let me through. Let me through!
- You know we can't do that.
- I need to talk to...
- He'll be with you shortly.
- You said that an hour ago.
Will.
Will? Will?
What's wrong? Are you hurting again?
Uh...
I saw something.
In your now-memories?
The shadow monster.
I think I know how to stop him.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this will do.
This will do just fine.
Good call, dude.
I said medium-well!
Who's that?
You told her?
- So what?
- "So what?"
- You wanted to tell her, too.
- But I didn't, all right?
We agreed not to tell her
and to look for Dart.
- Who you conveniently found.
- Are you suggesting that I'm lying?
I'm saying you have
a creepy little bond with him.
Yeah, that was before
he turned into a Demogorgon.
- And you haven't heard from Mike?
- No.
- Or Will?
- Hopper?
- No! No one is around.
Why do you think
I'm with Steve Harrington?
- Something's...
- Wrong. I agree.
Which is why we need
as much help as we can get.
She didn't believe me anyway.
You probably didn't tell it right.
That must be it.
So, we good?
Hey! Dickheads! How come the only one
helping me out is this random girl?
We lose light in 40 minutes. Let's go.
Let's go, I said!
- All right, asshole! God!
- Okay! Stupid.
What...
What is all of this?
I don't know.
Mom?
Will?
I don't shoot Polaroid.
- What?
- It's not mine.
Someone else has been here.
Sam, this is ludicrous.
- Just give him a moment, okay?
- We don't have time...
Hey, jackass, why don't you
do us all a favor and shut up, okay?
That's it.
That's what? What... what's there, Will?
I don't know.
I just know
he doesn't want me to see there.
I think it's important.
Let's see if this kid's a wizard
or schizo, Doc.
First door on your right, gentlemen.
- I'm guessing a ten.
- Let's not overdo it now.
I read four.
Moving in.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
So you really fought
one of these things before?
And you're, like, totally,
100% sure it wasn't a bear?
Shit. Don't be an idiot. Okay?
It wasn't a bear.
Why are you even here
if you don't believe us?
Just go home.
Geesh. Someone's cranky.
Past your bedtime?
That's good. Just show her you don't care.
I don't.
Why are you winking, Steve? Stop.
- It's kinda awesome.
- Huh?
The fog, I mean.
Looks like the ocean.
- You miss it?
- What?
The ocean. The waves? California?
- Hawkins seems pretty lame, I bet.
- No, no, no, it's not that. It's just...
My dad's still there. So...
- Why?
- It's this legal term called "divorce."
See, when two married people
don't love each other anymore...
Yeah.
My mom and my stepdad,
they wanted a fresh start away from him.
As if... As if he was the problem,
which is total bull.
And things...
are just worse now.
My stepbrother's always been a dick,
but now he's just angry...
all the time and...
Well, he can't take it out
on my mom, so...
So he takes it out on you?
I don't even know
why I'm telling you this.
It's just... I know that I can be
a jerk like him sometimes,
and I do not want to be like him. Ever.
I guess I'm angry, too, and...
I'm sorry.
Jesus! What's wrong with me?
Hey. You're nothing
like your brother, okay?
You're cool and different.
And you're super smart.
And you're, like, totally tubular.
- Nobody actually says that, you know.
- Well, I do now.
And it makes you seem really cool.
I like talking with you, Mad Max.
And I like talking with you, stalker.
- You see him?
- No.
Lucas, what's going on?
Hold on!
I've got eyes! Ten o'clock!
Ten o'clock!
There.
- What's he doing?
- I don't know.
- Wait. You sure that's not a dog?
- What?
He's not taking the bait.
Why is he not taking the bait?
Maybe he's not hungry?
Maybe he's sick of cow.
Steve? Steve, what are you doing?
Steve?
Just get ready.
Come on, buddy.
- What's he doing?
- Expanding the menu.
Come on, buddy.
Come on. Dinner time.
Human tastes better than cat, I promise.
He's insane.
He's awesome.
Steve, watch out!
A little busy here!
Three o'clock! Three o'clock!
Steve!
Steve! Abort! Abort!
- Steve, run!
- Steve, hurry!
Steve, run!
Shit!
Are they rabid or something?
They can't get in! They can't!
Shit!
Is anyone there? Mike? Will? God! Anyone!
We're at the old junkyard,
and we are going to die!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
You want some? Come get this!
Jeez.
What happened?
I don't know.
- Steve scared 'em off?
- No.
No way.
They're going somewhere.
- Almost there, ladies.
- Roger.
All right, stay frosty, boys.
- Wait. That's where I was.
- What?
It's that damn graveyard.
Sir, there's nothing here.
Looks like your kid's full of shit, Doc.
Got some kind of fog
moving in now.
I'm sorry.
What? What do you mean, sweetie?
He made me do it.
Who? Who made you do what?
I told you.
They upset him.
They shouldn't have done that.
They shouldn't have upset him.
The spy.
The spy!
We've got movement.
You've got company, fellas.
Whoa, whoa!
I need to get through! It's a trap!
It's a trap! I need to warn them.
It's a trap!
I can't see shit!
Where are they? Where are they?
They're right on you!
- Wait, what?
- What was that?
Will, sweets, talk to me.
You got to help me understand.
It's too late.
You should go now.
They're almost here.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::