Why are you staring at me?
Huh? I am asking you!
Move, bastard!
Crazy American.
Hey! Get back! Get back!
Get back!
Broken…
Cannot work.
Stay there.
Where is the American?!
Watch your back, American...
Where do you think you're going, American?
Stand.
Stand up!
Hands.
Hands!
Tool shed!
It came from the tool shed!
Open up!
Open the door!
Keep pushing! Hurry!
RUN!
There!
We can't let him get to the tree line!
Antonov, phone for you.
You realize we just had an escape?
They say it's urgent.
Enzo. It is Yuri.
Why are you calling me here? Are you mad?
I know. I am very sorry. I just felt
you should know that there has been...
...a slight change in plans.
What? What has happened?
I just got off the phone
with your warden.
A very productive call.
It turns out, escaped prisoners
are worth quite a bit of money.
So Yuri thinks, why not keep
the forty grand and make extra money?
That wasn't the deal.
But it is a better
deal for Yuri, yes?
And you know what is worth
even more than escaped prisoner?
Corrupt guards.
What have you done?!
And worth most of all...
Americans...
...wanted by the KGB.
Goodbye, Enzo.