O STREE COME TOMORROW.
Prakash.
Prakash!
O STREE COME TOMORROW.
The heart's completely open
With no hook or button
No button
Dreams are larger than life
And a mind that cares for no one
Cares for no one
My dreams are too
Big to fit in this city
Bigger than the city
I can fix your pain
With just a smile
I am the tailor of the heart
Like a bird soaring in the skies
Hey...
I am the tailor of the heart
Like a bird soaring in the skies
He comes closer to me and gaze
And his magic makes me amaze
Stitch me a beautiful dress, darling
Which makes me look more charming
I am the tailor of the heart
Like a bird soaring in the skies
Uncle, you start this charade
in every festival, don't you?
Vicky, there's still time.
But, this is no ordinary ink.
These are crushed bones of a bat
mixed with the urine of a white crow.
That's how this ink is prepared.
Uncle, sell these stories
to those who like reading Aesop's fables.
We're the modern generation.
The entire city believes
in this ignorance.
Vicky, any house that has
this ink outside their house
-will always be safe from Stree.
-I see...
Have you ever heard that the
Ambani's daughter was possessed?
Or the Tatas or Birla's were haunted.
I know she will come.
Loosen your pockets
and let me finish writing.
Uncle, don't forget
to write on our wall too.
And listen, write it in bold.
Otherwise, she might not
read it and come right in.
Yes, I will.
Your mouth will end
up like that someday, aunty.
Close the gate, mister.
Or the cow will barge in.
I am the watchman as well.
So you finally found some
time to come home.
What's the matter?
You should also come with me
from tomorrow.
I don't need to.
The sewing machine gives
me all the exercise I need.
And, you don't need this either.
Or soon you'll be hanging in a hanger.
-Was that a joke?
-And you're trying to be wise.
I'm already observing a fast
for the next four days.
And, you're making me waste my energy.
-Another fast?
-Focus on your job.
Soon the ladies will queue up.
I've told you before
stop taking alteration work.
Loosen the petticoat, tighten my blouse.
We'll only accept orders
for stitching new clothes.
Brand new clothes only.
Only?
And what will you do for
the rest of the year, son?
Ring the bell?
Daddy, explaining you is impossible.
Listen.
Listen...
You should spend some time
learning how to run the shop.
Otherwise, if someday your dad passes away
then you won't be able
to run the show alone.
Even if Death comes himself
to collect your soul, you won't die.
Even when your fingers will become frail,
you'll still be altering lady's dresses.
Son, soon you'll be following
in my footsteps.
Daddy, I wasn't born
to alter lady's dresses.
Then what are you destined for, Son?
I don't know yet, Dad.
But I will know pretty soon.
-Let them in.
-How are you, brother Vicky?
Stitch a dress for me.
Take down sister-in-law's measurements.
Step back a little.
Length;48, Shoulder; 14.5.
-Take off the shawl, sister-in-law.
-Yes.
Arm-hole;16, Wrist;
7, Chest; 38, waist; 42.
Turn around, sister-in-law.
Hip;44, Neck:10
Deep or Medium?
No, not deep.
Keep it medium.
Deep is better, sister-in-law.
It's in fashion these days.
You'll look nice.
I am telling you, my son
is the tailor-incarnation of God.
Do you want it tighter?
The shoulder on this dress...
But this idiot doesn't
respect his own talent.
What is this boy, Khan sir? What is he?
I've stitched thousands of clothes.
But the way his fingers
moves on the machine
feels like God's fingers are
moving on the machine.
The way he handles the scissors sounds
like Goddess Saraswati playing Veena.
When he puts a thread in the needle,
I can hear conches resonating in my ears.
I am sure it's some
connection from his past life.
I am the tailor of the Heart
Like a bird soaring in the skies
I'll be back in 10 minutes, Dad.
Break time.
I am the tailor of the Heart
Hi.
-Hi...
-Is your name Vicky?
Yes.
I saw you last year at the festival.
Okay...
I've heard a lot about you.
I don't live here, but I come
every year during the festival.
I see... okay.
-Can you stitch a dress for me?
-Okay.
-How long?
-Two weeks.
Can't you do it earlier?
How about 10 days?
I want it on the last day of the festival.
To wear it during the
auspicious veneration.
Vicky, please.
Give it earlier.
It's okay.
I'll get it done by someone else.
Thank you.
Two days?
-Two days.
-Thank you so much.
My measurements.
Take off the jacket.
Turn around.
Turn.
Again.
-Done.
-Ohh...
Thank you.
I'll be visiting the
temple in the evening.
Good.
-For the evening veneration.
-Very good.
Visiting the temple!
Okay.
One.
Saw?
She doesn't even look at you, and
you can already hear wedding bells.
And you're Mister know-it-all, aren't you?
Whenever I pass through her lane,
she always looks at me.
No, she doesn't, she stares at you.
Are you all right?
Will you say something? What happened?
-Love at first eye-sight.
-First eye-sight.
Love at first sight.
We both attended the English
Speaking course together.
Don't try to be Shakespeare.
Who is the girl?
The same girl who attended
the festival last year.
The one with brown eyes.
-One with the long hair.
-Yeah...
The one you bragged about last year?
I wasn't bragging.
She came out of nowhere
like a cool breeze.
Took my hand and said...
"Vicky, please!"
She held your hand.
Bullshit.
-And she even said please?
-Yes.
-He is lying and you believe him.
-Swear on my sewing machine.
She held your hand and said,
Vicky, please.
"Vicky, please!"
Vicky, please!
That's what I am saying, Vicky, please.
You have no emotions at all.
Give me your hand.
"Vicky, please!"
Now that's emotion.
But why you?
She wants me to stitch a dress.
Stitch a dress.
I have a readymade dress shop.
Who gets dresses stitched nowadays.
You idiot, stitched dresses
have a different charisma.
And love is never readymade.
It's always tailor-made.
Right.
"Vicky, please!"
Bro, put it on my tab.
Jealous.
She held this hand.
Smell it.
Sunflower.
I think you should start
planning your wedding.
Even I can hear wedding bells, Janna.
Hey, snap out of your dream world.
Today is the first day of the festival.
Lokesh is throwing a
party at his uncle's home.
So we're going to have
a ball for the next four nights.
Nobody be late.
Meaning party all night and,
in the morning--
Full tight.
-Right.
-But that's in the morning.
Just tell me why do you throw tantrums
I can follow you around
Like your crazy lover
I feel a little shy to convey
But, I want to sleep in your arms
I've been telling
you since the February second
Darling, step out of Chanderi for me
Come over to my mansion
You guys go ahead, I'll join you later.
-What are you planning to do out here?
-My heart's a little restless.
I guess I'll just sit here and pray.
What's wrong with you, Vicky? Why
are you feeling so religious today?
That dancer from Bhopal
must have arrived too.
I've been waiting for a year to see her.
-Let's go...
-Janna, you just go.
-I'll come later--
-Hold on.
He's going to see that girl.
One who said "Vicky Please".
And he's making excuses to us.
Is sister-in-law coming?
Then we'll wait too.
-What?
-No one's coming.
-I'll get the offerings for you.
-What offerings.
Stop making excuses, Vicky.
Remember, females have been
the reason for the downfall of men.
What?
It was a woman who disrupted
Vishwamitra's penance.
And I am not Vishwamitra.
And I am not looking for a boon.
I am not standing on one leg and waiting
for some Meneka to disrupt my penance.
-What do you think?
-You explain to him.
He's talking nonsense.
-Take him with you, Janna.
-This is not about any girl.
Let's go, Bittu.
-Go on.
-Come soon.
-Come on.
-I'm coming.
-You too.
-Janna...
-Go on.
-Why did you say yes?
-Hi.
-Hello.
-I thought you didn't understand.
No, I understood,
but it takes me a little time to...
I mean I've very little experience in...
I... I--
-Do you have a problem in speaking?
-No. Why?
Because if you do, it can be treated.
No, no, I can speak pretty well.
Peacock. Peacock is our National bird.
Peacock has a long and sharp beak.
The Peacock is around 1.5 feet tall.
The Peacock is a beautiful bird.
The Peacock's feather has many colors.
Some people believe when the female
peacock drinks the male peacock's tears
then a baby peacock is born.
When the Peacock dances
during the monsoons
people are enchanted to see the sight.
Just like I was
enchanted when I saw you...
Sorry.
By the way,
you're looking really nice tonight.
Even you're looking... alright.
Thank you.
-You're late. The veneration is over.
-Is it?
-Yes.
-I didn't realize I was late.
It's the ambiance.
But I will inform you before
the veneration starts tomorrow.
I will call you.
Store your number in this.
I don't carry a mobile.
You don't.
Okay.
If I... or anyone else wants to talk
or call you then how do they do that?
I don't know about others,
but if you want to talk then...
Then?
Just think about me. And I'll come over.
Fine, I will do that.
Letter.
"To Vicky." For me?
No. Read it in the morning,
after you get freshened up.
After...
Okay. Thank you.
By the way, it's quite late, isn't it?
It's dark everywhere.
I wait for this darkness.
Okay...
FIRST NIGHT
What's the point of owning
a bike if you can't afford fuel?
Do you have any problem with the petrol?
It always gets over.
Forget the petrol.
Think about Vicky.
Stop fighting, Bittu.
It was his good luck,
that he found a girl.
But he could've introduced us.
Why didn't he do that?
I think there is no
girl in the first place.
And if there is one,
then there's something wrong with her.
What was that sound?
What sound?
I've been speaking all this time.
What sound did you hear?
-There, I heard it again.
-What?
-Brother Rudra.
-Hello.
Hello, brother Rudra.
-Are you two in your right mind?
-Yes, we are.
-Where are you two going at this hour?
-Why?
-What happened?
-The festival has begun.
She will be out
hunting for the next four days.
Who?
Her.
Stree.
Stop scaring him, brother Rudra.
I am not scaring him, just warning you.
Look, our city is the
only place in this world
where no man steps out alone
during these days of the festival.
She abducts male,
leaving only his clothes behind.
Only his clothes.
It's just that I like you two,
you two are like family
that's why I was telling you, otherwise...
Brother Rudra, please tell us.
Form a triangle. Come here.
-What is that?
-Beer.
All right. I have mine.
Yes.
There are certain rules
for escape the wrath of Stree.
Rule no. 1.
Under no circumstances, and I mean
none... don't step out of the house alone.
And only those men are safe, who have
written outside their house
-O Stree Come tomorrow.
-Come tomorrow.
Rule no. 2.
If in case you've to step out, then don't
try to be a lion, be a wolf instead.
-Wolf?
-Why?
-Travel in packs, not alone.
-I see.
Rule no. 3.
If you ever come across the Stree
then she will first call out your name.
Hello, Tom-Dick-Harry.
What do you do?
Take off your slippers,
hold it in your hand, and?
-Run!
-No!
No running.
Keep walking.
-What to do?
-Keep walking.
Then she will call you again.
This time with more passion.
And what do you do?
Keep walking.
Then she will call out to you again,
for the third time.
With an enchanting, alluring voice.
Like an angel.
Embrace me now because this
night may not come again.
That's the kind of emotions you'll feel.
Your breathing will get faster,
your heart will start pounding.
Bedroom will be the only thing
on your mind.
And what do you do?
-Keep walking.
-No.
No man could ever resist the Stree
when she calls out for the third time.
You will start losing
control over yourself.
And as soon as you turn around...
Gone!
But brother Rudra, there must be some way.
Yes.
Rule no. 4.
And the most important thing to
remember if you want to escape the Stree.
At any point...
Yes, Shama.
What?
You're coming into my life.
I am coming right over.
Brother Rudra.
You didn't finish the 4th rule.
Keep walking! Keep walking! Keep walking!
Don't make a noise.
-Wait a minute.
-No! Keep walking! Keep walking!
Bittu.
-Janna, look.
-What?
Someone's out there.
Bittu. Wait.
Stop.
Bittu.
Stop Bittu, for your mother's sake.
-Why are you running?
-Because you're running.
-Come on.
-Come.
-What was that?
-I haven't the slightest clue.
Don't tell Vicky anything.
or he'll make fun of us.
Do you understand or not?
Do you understand?
Where were you two?
What happened?
-Huh!
-Nothing.
What?
Oh, my silly beloved
Snap out of your illusion
Stop being afraid
Stop making gestures from a distance
Open the door to your heart wide apart
And say it out loud
Don't be scared
Tell me what's your plan for tonight
I want to see the lightning tonight
Start a fire in my heart
If you come with us, baby and
Shake your hips
Shake it
Cross your eyes with us
Shake your hips
Shake it
Cross your eyes with us
Take my heart, sweetheart
Take my life
But just
Just shake your hips for me
Take my heart, sweetheart
Take my life
But just
Just shake your hips for me
Shake it
Cross your eyes
Cross your eyes with us
These beautiful sights
The stars in the sky
The season of spring that's arrived
It's all for you my love
My love
And my joys
Take anything you want, sweetheart
These beautiful sights
The stars in the sky
The season of spring that's arrived
Is all for you my love
My love
And my joys
Take anything you want, sweetheart
I want to be struck by lightning
Start a fire in my heart
If you come with us, baby and
Shake your hips
Shake it
Cross your eyes
Cross your eyes with us
Shake your hips
Shake it
Cross your eyes with us
Shake your hips
Shake it
Cross your eyes with us
Bye.
Shake it
Go on.
Go.
Come on in. Come in.
She's my girlfriend.
I called her over for "friendship".
Come in.
This kind of friendship isn't
allowed in here.
Wasn't it enough that we called a dancer?
Uncle will never approve of this.
Just go out and start the generator, okay?
Why didn't you inform me earlier
that there are going to be more people?
Don't worry, darling.
I've already reserved
a room for us upstairs.
No one's going to disturb us.
Just you and me.
All alone in a room.
Well, if I had known, I would've
brought my friends along.
And even your friends could've
snuggled in with them in a room.
Naughty.
Go upstairs.
Narender.
Shake it
Come on.
-Do you have protection?
-Protection?
No protection, no friendship.
Oh, protection!
Take away my heart baby
Hello. Who is it?
Janna, do you have protection?
Protection.
No, I don't carry one.
Let's ask one of the guys.
-Guys, is anyone carrying protection?
-No, I don't have one.
Come on, quickly.
Hurry up.
Light's back...
I got the stuff.
Why have you turned off the lights?
I like the lights on.
Because now I've protection.
This thing is older than my grandfather.
This is of cheap quality.
Yes.
Narender.
-What happened?
-There...
-What?
-Outside the window.
-Someone dragged him out of the window.
Narender?
I came into the room and
someone dragged him outside.
Stay here. You go check.
Narender.
Clothes.
Clothes?
Narender's clothes.
Only his clothes.
Stree took him.
This is Stree's doing.
Whenever she takes any man,
she leaves his clothes behind.
But I don't understand one thing.
How did Stree get inside?
I don't know.
I wrote "O Stree come tomorrow" on the
wall so that we can party peacefully.
Someone erased it.
I think that someone
intentionally erased it.
Who peed on the wall?
Who was it? Huh?
Speak up now.
-Vicky?
-You did it.
No, it wasn't me.
Oh really? Then who did this?
Right, you went out
in the middle of the dance.
You peed on the wall.
Yes, I did.
It didn't say no peeing here. Get lost.
Why did you have to pee
there of all the places?
My pee, my will,
I can pee anywhere I want.
We lost a friend because of you.
He's a junkie.
He must be high and wandering around.
We won't hear anything against our friend.
-You made him disappear.
-I didn't do anything.
You made him disappear.
You peed on the wall.
Just a second.
Stop! Stop! Stop, guys! Stop!
What's the point of beating up Janna?
Your friend's missing, go look for him.
Stop ranting Stree.
It's pretty late.
Daddy must be waiting for me.
Even I didn't tell my
mom that I'm coming here.
Fine, let's come back tomorrow.
STREE COME TOMORROW.
GET RID OF STREE IN JUST Rs. 150.
Letter.
Here's the letter.
Brother, some madam's here to see you.
Who is it? Tell her to come later.
It's her.
Take a look for yourself.
Idiot!
-Did you tell her that I am at home?
-I did, brother
Come here.
What are you doing here?
-I want my money.
-What money?
My charge for the friendship.
Your friend didn't pay
me for the friendship.
So? So you're going to pay me.
Why will I pay?
I see... you pee on the
wall and I won't get my money.
Has the government put a ban on my pee?
I can pee anywhere I want.
Pay up quietly.
I heard that the
friendship never happened.
We were halfway through.
Please sister, I don't have money.
I don't have money--
Look here, stop making excuses.
Otherwise, I will come here
with my friends and make a scene.
Calm down.
And, your father won't like it.
-I have heard a lot about him.
-How much do I pay, sister?
She's collecting donation.
I think 3000 will be fine.
-Take some lessons from him.
-Jai Mata Di.
So mister, are you going to stand
like this or put something on.
Take care of your son.
He's bustling with energy.
Son, I'm going to share a
really important experience of life.
Youth is a weird phase.
The body bustles with vitality.
A tank full of energy.
And this energy craves to come out.
But this body is puzzled
about what to do or not to do.
And this restlessness
provokes it to have
friendship with the opposite sex.
Dad, I hope you know
what friendship means here.
Friendship.
Son, I was born in this town before you.
I've had a lot of friendship
back in my days.
-You had friendships.
-I did.
Yes, but once I met your mother
she completely changed my point of view.
The union of a male and a female...
-Listen to me.
-Go on.
The union of a male and a female is pure.
It's auspicious.
Like the union of Heaven and Earth.
The confluence of Shiv and Shakti.
But why are you telling me all this?
I telling you so that
you don't pay for friendship.
When did I pay for friendship?
And what about her?
Dad, she wasn't here for me.
-I didn't pay for friendship--
-Listen to me first.
My advice to you is that you must
wait for a companion
with whom you can enjoy this
process for the rest of your life.
And learn to control this energy
bustling in your body till then.
And if you can't, then...
Then what?
Then be self-reliant.
-Cater to your needs.
-Meaning?
Meaning... yourself.
How, daddy?
I mean...
-I mean...
-Loss of words?
-Come on. Go out.
-Listen...
Come on. Go out.
Energy.
Where is my energy?
My dear Vicky.
If she's started with "My dear"
then she will end it with "with love".
-Okay.
-"My dear Vicky, how are you?"
What a stupid question?
She just met yesterday and
today she's asking how you are.
Keep reading.
"To be honest, I was
really happy to meet you.
After talking to you I felt like we've
known each other for a long time.
Since I've retreated"--
"Returned."
Sorry, "Since I've returned
I feel like meeting you again.
And this time when we meet,
my dear Vicky
can you bring these things for me?
PTO.
A quarter brandy.
Half a kilo of mutton.
A kilo of charred glass.
Thornapple flower, Hair of a cat"
-And...
-And?
"A tail of a lizard"
"Thanking you, with love."
With love. Told you...
What is this stupid stuff?
Who asks to get stuff like these?
-Also she drinks.
-What if she drinks?
-Sister-in-law is cool.
-That's not the point.
She wants you to get the tail of a lizard.
And you're a tailor,
not the ancestor of lizards.
You're prepared for an impossible
mission because she asked you.
Janna has been asking you to
stitch a shirt for him. But did you?
I have been asking you
let's go to Goa. But did you?
Trying to be a hero for the girl.
You say something.
What now?
-She's asked so politely...
-So?
Then I must get it.
-What?
-It's very simple.
Guys always do what
girls tell them to. That's it.
Shahjahan built the Taj Mahal for love.
And our brother is
chasing cats and lizards.
Whoever imagined love would
fall to such levels in 500 years.
Tell me something, don't
you think something is wrong?
Right and wrong are just
a point of view, Bittu.
Don't try to be wise.
I am telling you,
I have a bad feeling about this.
Something is wrong about this girl.
Got it...
Got it.
Come on, now hurry up.
That Stree already
took one male last night.
We must return home before
she comes out for a hunt.
Don't hurry. Why are you so scared?
You can't handle one woman, and
now you're scared of another.
Hello. Janna, meet me right now.
Vicky!
Vicky! Hi.
Hello. Sorry, I was too engrossed
in listening to music.
What do you listen to?
English.
Wow!
-Akon.
-Who?
Akon.
Wanna be my Chammak Challo.
-The guy's like Kumar Sanu of his country.
-I see.
-You don't know?
-No.
I see.
You missed the veneration again.
I guess I don't get
along with God too well.
Right. Right.
I...
I brought this offering for you.
I'm fasting today.
Even offerings are not allowed?
I see.
Doesn't matter. Whether you
eat or me, it's the same.
By the way, we can go inside.
I know the priest.
I can arrange for a
special veneration for you.
And even make a donation
of 11 rupees in your name.
-Your name--
-Did you get the items on the list?
Yes.
I got everything you asked for.
You didn't tell me which brand
of brandy, so I got every brand.
But it's better this way.
You can try every brand, for variety.
And, I couldn't find a
cat with completely white hair.
She had mixed colors.
But what will you
do with all these things?
Are you going to ask everything right now?
Let's go to some other place.
-At this hour?
-Yes.
Okay.
But where?
Let's go. I know a spot.
Fair you're so fair
Like the moonlight that's falling on earth
Bad very bad
The world's intentions are very bad
I hope no one casts an evil eye on you
This thought keeps scaring me all day
this thought keeps scaring me all day
This silky dress that you've worn tonight
When you smile all
My sorrows get alleviated
I hope no one casts an evil eye on you
This thought keeps scaring me all day
-Vicky's gone tonight.
-Where?
Focus on my meaning.
I pondered over this a lot.
And the verdict I've
reached is pretty dangerous.
What is your verdict?
You were a genius at school,
then how are you so slow in real life?
I go to the depth of every
matter and weigh it properly.
My dear Pacific Ocean.
Why aren't your depths
showing you what I can see?
This girl
appears once in a year
like an endangered species.
And always during the festival.
And do you know who else
shows up during the festival?
Who?
Stree!
Mister, open your mind
Has anyone else seen her except for Vicky?
No.
And what does she ask him
to get in her first love letter?
-Cat hair, lizard leg--
-Tail.
It's one and the same.
Who asks to get stuff like this?
He's not picking up.
-Mister, turn off your phone.
-You shut your mouth.
And fill fuel worth 50 rupees.
50 again.
Why don't you ever put more?
Why don't you try telling my father that?
You try calling him.
He's gone to meet her, I am telling you.
Our friend is in trouble, understand.
Stree has laid a trap.
And our made in love friend,
is heading straight for it.
He is actually cutting the calls.
Why do people become blind in love?
How would I know?
Blind following is a bad thing.
You can be anyone you want,
but not a blind follower.
Where do you think the new couple
have gone to get cozy?
The lake.
SECOND NIGHT
How do you know about this place?
And why did we come here?
Because it's dark out here.
And no one comes here.
Dark?
He isn't here either.
Where could he be?
I am telling you,
we'll only find his clothes today.
Your clothes are very nice.
Where did you buy them?
I designed them myself.
People call me the Manish
Malhotra of Chanderi.
Isn't it too tight?
It's just my body.
How do you open it?
-Listen.
-Yeah?
-Shall we leave?
-Why?
-Are you scared too?
-No.
I am not scared of any ghosts or spirits.
But how long are we going
to waste our time on a selfish guy?
But he's our friend.
-Bittu.
-Wait.
So what else do you stitch at your shop?
Just skirts and long dresses,
or anything else?
Actually, we make everything.
Completely ladies fashion.
Skirts, tops, traditional dresses,
tunics. Midis, minis.
Short dresses, long dresses,
kaftans, fringe, party dresses.
Mirror work,
stonework, designer panty, nightfall.
Nighty fall.
That's it.
When will you give me my dress?
It completely slipped off my mind.
-I troubled you a lot, didn't I?
-Of course not.
It was no trouble at all.
And anything for you.
I should have taken
your measurements that day.
I thought you did.
Normally I am good at this,
but in your case, I goofed up.
So take it now.
But I don't have my measuring tape.
Can't you take my measurement without it?
I can, but...
Can I?
Take it.
-Should I?
-Take it.
Okay, I will.
Hello.
-Where are you?
-Hello.
-Bittu.
-Yes.
I am missing my mom.
Shall we go back?
You're right.
-Parents are more important than friends.
-You're right.
Let's go back.
What happened?
Let me check.
-What?
-I think we're out of petrol.
I told you, didn't I?
Tell me, is your father a menial labor?
You own a big shop in the city.
From Manish Malhotra to Manish Behl.
What is this?
Whether you fill 50 rupees
petrol at a time or fill your tank.
It's still the same.
The petrol pump is close-by. Push.
It's your bike, isn't it? You push.
Why should I?
-I've been pushing it since we were kids.
-What's wrong with you?
That Stree is wandering around the city.
And we're stuck in the middle of nowhere.
And you want to know what's wrong?
Mom clearly said that
I should come back soon.
If I don't hurry up,
she will lock the doors and sleep.
What now? Push!
Mummy!
Hello.
Where are you?
Madam.
Where are you going?
I knew it, selfish rascal.
What's wrong with you today?
I am your friend, not your slave.
First I go to your house so that you
can tuck yourself under the blanket.
-And then I go home all alone.
-But we do that all the time.
-Not today.
-Fine, let it be.
I've been listening to
your nonsense for a long time.
-Go on.
-Fine, you don't have to.
-Get going.
-Weird guy.
-I hope Stree abducts you.
-Same to you.
Son!
No!
If you ever come across the Stree,
this is what you do?
Janna...
No.
Don't turn around.
Keep walking.
Janna...
And the most important thing to
do if you want to escape from Stree.
At any point...
Mummy!
No... No... No!
Janna...
Janna. My Janna.
I curse that Stree.
Janna never even touched a girl in life.
And now she must be sitting on top on him.
I told him a thousand times not to hang
around with these worthless friends.
Janna could've had a good job.
But these rascal friends spoiled him.
Lord, give him strength.
Give my son strength.
I know you went to meet her.
Stop getting jealous of my love life.
Think about Janna.
Did anything weird happen?
Weird how?
Anything at all, when you were with her?
What did you two do?
Why?
Just tell me.
We went to the temple.
Then to the river banks.
We were just sitting and chatting,
and then she disappeared.
And didn't return.
I knew it.
-I knew it, Vicky.
-What?
-That your girlfriend is a ghost.
-What do you mean ghost?
Janna and I were coming to save you.
-And she took Janna instead.
-What nonsense!
Snap out of your dream world, Romeo.
Why does your girlfriend show up
only during the festival,
and then disappear?
She asks you to get ingredients
for black magic in her love letter.
Have you ever seen her feet?
Are they straight or crooked?
Did you ask her name?
Do you know her phone number?
Has anyone seen her except for you?
Because I haven't.
But...
Oh, fuck!
I just don't understand this.
How does she enter the temple?
Are these ghosts atheists?
Aren't they scared?
She never enters the temple,
always stays out.
She doesn't take the offerings either.
Vicky, I am feeling sad for you
for the first time.
Because, of all the things in the world,
you fell for a witch.
Go and ask your Stree,
where is Janna.
I miss him.
One more thing.
Don't tell her that
Bittu told you all this.
Otherwise, she might abduct me too.
Warning! Warning! Warning!
An important piece of warning
for all the people in the city.
Stree is out hunting
and the men are in threat.
The method to save yourself
from Stree is written in this paper.
Remember it.
-Show me.
-No, it's not for you.
You're safe.
If you ever run into Stree
then there's just one way to escape
Under no circumstance will you...
Hello! Hello!
How do you know so much about the Stree?
I know everything.
Triple BA, Double MA,
literarian, musician, teacher.
I have all these degrees.
I spent my childhood amongst crocodiles.
Rudra Book Depot.
But why do we write
"O Stree Come tomorrow"?
We can write something else.
Like, "Stree, never come back again".
As long as it's working, let it continue.
And by the way,
if we ever have an unwanted guest
we don't say
"Get lost and don't come back".
We say politely "Come back tomorrow".
I've heard that the Stree sleeps
with her prey before killing him.
That's the system
with female scorpions too.
She swallows the male
scorpion which she mates with.
Listen wise guy, please don't share
your knowledge with us.
Leave all that aside.
Tell us what's the solution to it.
My wife says that I should
wear a sari when I step out.
Please don't spread such rumors.
Or soon we'll see everyone
in our city draped in sari.
"My beloved's arrived" type.
No, no.
How does she know everyone's name?
Because all our databases
are linked to her.
-I see.
-Shut up, idiot.
You see, two youngsters
have already been abducted.
Be alert.
Poor guy was abducted from the town
square. He was such a healthy boy.
Wasn't he your friend too, Vicky?
But not anymore. Not anymore.
-Keep the glass down.
-What?
Trying to be over smart. Huh!
Get lost.
He's still alive. My friend isn't dead.
Brother.
Sir. Sir.
Brother Vicky, you are amazing.
You stitched this dress in 31 minutes.
Sir.
-What happened?
-No, it's nothing.
No, I haven't done anything.
I didn't do anything.
Don't kill me, Stree. Don't kill me.
What happened?
-Don't kill me, Stree. Don't kill me.
-Vicky, what's wrong?
What happened?
It's nothing.
You look like you saw a ghost.
Ghost. No... ghost. Nothing like that.
-Are you all right, Vicky?
-Yes, I am okay.
I am all right.
-Is it ready?
-Yes, it is.
-Thank you.
-It's all right.
Shall we go out somewhere?
Out?
I'll take you to another
one of my favorite spots.
No! This is my favorite place.
-Let's sit here.
-Okay.
There's magic in your hands.
And even in my feet.
I can turn it around like this.
Can you turn your feet around too?
-Is there a problem?
-No. What problem?
There is no problem.
Can I ask you a question
for my personal knowledge?
Do you believe in ghosts and spirits?
I've heard that a woman
wanders in this city at night.
Called Stree.
She is a witch.
She abducts males.
Strips them.
I know she must have a good reason.
No one is born as a witch, Right.
I understand.
My friend Janna, has disappeared as well.
He's a very nice guy.
People say that Stree took him.
Have you seen Janna?
Can I ask you a question?
Its personal,
but don't take it personally.
Are you...
I mean not intentionally.
Are you... Stree?
I just asked.
I don't have a problem.
I was just confirming.
If you're a ghost...
I mean you are what you are.
If it's anything like that,
please tell me now.
I'll just be prepared mentally.
That's all.
Uncle.
Do you see that girl standing there?
-What girl?
-That one...
That...
You should listen
to your friends sometimes.
But how can a beautiful
woman like her be Stree?
Was she beautiful?
Sorry.
Think about Janna.
What condition will he be in?
Lying somewhere naked in this cold.
What now?
We'll have to find someone who's
an expert in such absurd folklores.
You came to the right place.
I know everything.
-Doesn't get me high.
-Then why do you drink?
In Shama's memory, that's why.
Leave Shama aside.
-And tell us what you know about Stree.
-I am doing research on Ms. Stree.
And like they say, the fruits
of hard work is always sweet.
-And I got one too.
-Sweet fruit?
No. Book.
-Book?
-Just a minute.
Here you go.
Oh, KS.
Ka Su...
-Are you researching on this?
-Not that.
This one. This is it.
This is Chanderi Puran.
Chanderi has its own manuscript.
Our city is older than you think.
The spot where you're sitting.
If we dig beneath it,
you'll find the Harappa Civilization.
Right here. Harappa.
Exactly under this spot.
So look, Chanderi Puran
written by Shankar Shashtri.
Here we go.
Many years ago.
Many years ago there used to be
a beautiful and attractive courtesan.
Every male in the city
would dream about her.
Finally, she found a man
who loved soul and not her body.
True love.
And talk about your generation.
Love at first sight.
Then your place or mine.
What direction is this
generation heading to?
Brother Rudra. Don't be a dad.
-Please read ahead.
-Yes.
They both decided to get married.
But the other people
couldn't tolerate their joy.
And before their wedding night, the
jealous people murdered both of them.
Since then she has been
wandering in this city.
Looking for her love,
and complete her wedding night.
And this can only happen when
she will find her lost love again.
Such insolent people.
They can't tolerate someone's happiness.
Every female has the
right to find her true love.
Brother Rudra.
We can have this debate later.
First, tell us if there's
a method to stop Stree?
There is just one way to get rid of Stree.
-Yeah
-Turn the page.
-Okay.
The city's main business was silk.
People had such high
scarcity for education
that they actually believed
that the moon sun's brother.
The main caste in the...
How come Shastri turn
up in south from the west.
After page 66 there is page 80.
Where are the rest of the pages?
This is why I don't let anyone in.
Children tear pages from
the book and make paper boats.
-How will we save Janna now?
-Wait a minute.
I've seen this place.
-You have?
-Yes.
-Where?
-Above the hill.
-We should go there.
-Then let's go.
-We might find something here.
-Yes.
-Go. Go on you two.
-What do you mean?
-You must come along too.
-Me?
-Brother Rudra, you have done research.
-Of course.
I see Wait a minute.
Let me take this along.
Shama, I am going.
THIRD NIGHT
We'll run out of petrol.
-How much further, Vicky?
-Just a little further.
Stop! Stop.
What? I am allergic to dust. Come on.
It's so dark around here.
-What if she abducts me forcefully?
-She is a woman, not a man.
Women don't use force
against your will, like men.
She will ask for your permission first.
Hello Mr. Tom-Dick-or-Harry.
And if you turn around.
Then she will think it's a yes.
Yes, means yes.
Then she will take you away.
So under no circumstance
will you turn around.
-No turning around.
-Let's go.
Janna.
What are you doing?
Brother Rudra. Give me the alcohol.
Alcohol.
Why?
This is not a time for a drink.
No. For power.
No power.
Okay, give me.
Save some for me.
You're worried about the alcohol.
You go that way.
Brother Rudra, you search upstairs.
-Why?
-And I will look here.
-Let's stay together.
-We don't have time for that.
Hail Goddess! Hail Goddess!
Mom always told me to learn
the Hanuman Chalisa.
Now I regret.
Sorry, mom.
Oh my god!
God, please save me.
Snake! Snake! Snake! Snake!
Run.
Mummy!
Brother Rudra! Where are you going?
I was just warming up.
-I saw her.
-Did you?
Brother Rudra!
Janna.
Vicky...
Stree, it's me. Vicky.
Remember I stitched your dress.
I am here for Janna, he's a very nice guy.
In fact, he calls you sister-in-law.
Vicky...
I stitched your dress in 31 minutes,
Stree, and you want to abduct me.
You hurt me.
I won't turn around.
-Vicky...
-I can't hear you at all.
I'll not turn back.
I'll not turn around.
Daddy.
Vicky!
-Are you okay?
Yes, I am fine.
Is she gone?
Don't know.
Don't know?
But at least there is a relief.
You're not Stree.
You know, like in the morning...
Sorry.
Shall we go back?
-But Vicky is still inside.
-Bittu.
Vicky, where were you?
Did you see Janna?
No!
Run brother Rudra.
He's fallen prey as well.
That's not her.
-She is not Stree.
-You are lying.
That's the girl.
The letter... Remember?
The dress.
"Vicky Please!"
That's her.
I swear she risked
her own life to save mine.
You two would've...
Been amazed.
She flung her dagger at the witch.
If we had posted that video on Youtube,
it would've been an instant hit.
#daggergirl.
But what is she doing here?
How does she know we're here?
Your friend is not
the only one who's missing.
Many people go missing every year.
I've been coming here for the
past three years during the festival.
So that I can get rid of her for good.
Just like the others,
I've lost someone too.
I know he will never come back.
But still.
You can share your sorrow with me.
It will lighten your burden.
-No
-No? Okay.
By the way, where did you learn this art?
I had to wander around for it.
I went to ascetics, and tantric.
Tantra, magic, hypnosis, and spells from
the red book. I learned everything.
I've had only one mission
for the past three years.
Defeating Stree.
I tried everything I knew.
But it wasn't enough.
I thought I was ready.
I thought that I would
defeat her this time.
You see, ma'am. I've done
extensive research on this subject.
Research.
I have books on magic spells, hypnosis,
and other art forms in my library.
You can come over if you need any help.
Even we have a shop for lady's fashion.
Best in town.
If you need anything at any time,
just let me know.
And anyway it's always
better than stitched clothes.
I don't like readymade.
Shall we?
What happened?
Janna. My Janna is back.
My son is back.
My son, where were you?
-Where were you...
-His clothes will tear.
He's lost so much weight.
Forgive me, son. Forgive me.
You really are his friend.
-I said such bad things.
-It's all right.
-It's okay, aunty.
-Janna, it's your mom, son.
I want to go sleep.
He wants to sleep.
-Yes son, let's go.
-Come on.
-Please send my coat back.
-Okay, aunty.
Bye, Janna.
Aunty. Aunty.
She took my husband.
She took my son too.
She took him too.
She took my husband.
My husband too.
But, how did so many people disappear?
Someone has erased the ink.
Janna, look what Stree did.
She abducted a dozen men.
And she's also erased the ink. Janna.
You...
Janna.
Janna...
Why are you sitting like that, Janna?
And your palms...
Janna.
I am your mother. Listen to your mom, son.
Janna, spare your friends at least.
Listen to me, I am already 70% damaged.
Janna. We're humans, not kites.
Janna.
Vicky, look at Janna's hand.
He erased the ink.
-Divert his attention?
-Me?
Go.
-Janna.
-Someone get a blanket.
Janna.
Janna. Janna, stop.
Janna...
It's Vicky.
Janna.
Quiet!
Or else I will slap you. Quiet!
Janna. What are you doing?
It's Vicky.
Bittu! Bittu!
Come on.
This is the only solution left.
Wear sari and bangles like women do.
Your solutions were not effective at all.
That Stree took 20 men.
Yes, Shama.
Yes, I know. I am coming.
I am coming.
We want our youngsters back.
Whoever brings the missing men back
will be rewarded Rs.10,000 for every man.
Understand?
This city wants freedom.
Freedom.
Everybody knows that
Stree is a thief.
Let's all unite.
And drive Stree away.
You give us men.
GET RID OF STREE IN JUST Rs. 250.
We'll give you freedom.
It's the smoke coming on my face.
-Bittu, get me out.
-Wait.
Don't listen to him, today.
David has turned into Goliath today.
How can someone beat up your own friend?
We cannot waste any more time.
Janna is completely under her control.
We must do something
before the festival ends.
You're experienced in this field,
suggest something.
If we can find out more about Stree,
then I can come up with something.
But from where?
-We found a book at his shop.
-Library.
We found a book in his library.
But the pages were missing.
What if we find the
guy who wrote that book
then he would know what
was written on those pages.
-Yes.
-Yes?
-Do you know that guy?
-I know everything.
-Everything?
-Is he alive?
He lives in Emergency.
ICU!
Emergency.
Which book are you talking about?
Respected Mr. Shastri.
You wrote the history
of our city in a book.
Chanderi Puran, remember?
The book was launched
in my Rudra Book Depot.
You used to sell eroticas back then.
Mr. Shashtri,
that Stree abducted our friend.
She abducted many more men too.
Can we get them back?
Stree.
Please, Mr. Shashtri.
We request.
Did the emergency end?
We've been banging
our heads against a wall.
This man doesn't remember anything.
Yes, Emergency is over.
No-no-no.
Mr. Shashtri, we're talking about Stree.
-Stree.
-Like "Stree come back tomorrow".
Stree.
What is a woman?
She has no stature compared to men.
What?
She should always stay within her limits.
Never step out of the house.
Her job is to keep her husband happy,
and bear children.
And if she crosses her limit,
then burn her alive at the cross.
-He has no solution.
-Such vile thoughts.
We just wasted our time with him.
What kind of a writer is he?
Is this what he writes?
What about Janna now?
He's too strong to control.
-Let's think.
-He's got such a filthy mind.
It's not me.
The people of this city
have a filthy mind.
They used that Stree
as long as they wanted.
And then they got rid of her.
And that man who gave her respect,
they took him away as well.
They will all die.
Everyone.
As long as there's even one male
in this city, she won't rest.
Just one. One man can douse this fire.
-Who is he?
-How does he look?
Wheatish color, long nose.
And treats himself like a king.
Born in the arms of the oak tree.
The prince of his family.
Love reflects in his eyes.
A true artist.
He's the true protector of this city.
A prostitute's son who's a bachelor.
Courtesan's son who's a bachelor.
A courtesan's son who's a bachelor.
-Let's find that guy.
-Come let's go
Wheatish color, long nose.
And treats himself like a king.
Born in the arms of the oak tree.
The prince of his family.
Vicky. Weren't you born
at your grandma's house?
And there was an oak tree
behind her house.
-Yes.
-So?
And you're the only son.
-A Prince.
-Very good.
Wheatish color, long nose.
And treats himself like a king.
-He has wheatish color.
-And a long nose.
And, you always think of yourself
as a king.
Love reflects in his eyes.
And a true artist.
There's love in your eyes.
And Stree saw that,
which is why she didn't abduct him.
There's love in my eyes?
-Stree can see it, not her.
-And you're an artist as well.
Aren't you getting carried away now?
What artist?
Vicky is the best ladies tailor
in the neighboring three districts.
-Exactly.
-This is a good coincidence.
But we must find someone
who has all five qualities.
And what about the fifth quality?
courtesan's son?
How will find him?
Courtesan means that right? That...
No one told him.
Nobody.
Everyone knows, but you don't know?
What?
-What?
-Look...
There's nothing to feel bad about.
Some mothers are school teachers,
some are government officers.
Some make pickles.
-Your mother was that...
-What?
That.
What?
Courtesan!
I will kill you right now.
I thought you never meant
it when you called me a bastard.
You...
This is absurd.
Do you have any sense?
Vicky. it's true.
Janna, I will break your head.
Vicky. Don't look at me.
Should I believe what he says?
My mother was not a courtesan.
-Listen!
-No.
Vicky!
We've found the protector of the city.
He will deal with Stree.
-You mean Stree.
-Yes. Stree.
One more.
Brother Vicky, mom's asking
when will you return her blouse.
Dad.
What were you lecturing me about energy?
You've done a lot of friendship
when you were young, right?
Tell me something.
Did you do friendship with mom,
or marry her?
Blouse petticoat.
Who was she?
Why didn't you tell me?
You kept lying to me.
Daddy, I won't drink again. Swear on mom.
Swear on my dad, okay. Sorry.
Eat.
You could've told me this once.
That's all.
Eat.
I talked to daddy.
And I thought how does it matter.
She was my mother after all.
Maybe my father's someone else too.
But I know only one father.
The guy who stands at the
shop with the measuring tape.
And who thinks that my talent
is the greatest talent in the world.
But this city...
Everyone knew about me,
but they never made fun of me.
Otherwise, people like to gossip.
I always knew that I wasn't
meant for altering dresses.
But I didn't know that
I was born to save these people.
Lord chose a really unique mission for me.
"Born in the arms of the oak tree."
"The sole prince"
"The son of a courtesan who's a bachelor."
If I really am the son of a courtesan
then I will save this city.
Along with Janna, I will save everyone!
Bittu gather everyone.
What do we know about the Stree?
-She is scary.
-Ferocious.
No! She can read.
Have you ever heard about
a ghost or spirit who can read?
Right.
Meaning we're up against
an educated witch.
She is the new generation witch.
Point no. 2.
She comes every year during
the festival, to abduct men.
But if you write outside your
house "O Stree, come back tomorrow".
Then she reads it and thinks
"Oh okay. Rest today,
and I'll come back tomorrow".
Meaning she listens.
That means she is obedient.
No. 3.
She is very stupid.
Next night she comes back again.
Reads the same line again and thinks
"Oh shit, now I'll have
to come back tomorrow again".
"This is cheating."
And she goes back home.
Poor thing doesn't understand
that these people are s...
...fooling her.
-She has a low IQ level.
-Exactly.
And we're much smarter than her.
-Thank you.
-And, if we get serious
then we can easily
get rid of this witch forever.
-Then let's get serious.
-Correct. Let's get serious.
But what are we going to do?
Wedding night.
But brother Rudra,
aren't you too old for that?
Not me. No!
According to Mr. Shashtri's book
Stree wants her wedding
night which was left incomplete.
Yes. So?
And if you're the protector of this city
then you must fulfill her wish.
What are you saying?
Have you lost your mind?
-No.
-What are you saying?
My father never even let
me watch a wedding night on TV
how can I do it with a witch?
Yes.
I am the protector, shouldn't
I prepare for a battle or something.
The battle begins after the wedding night.
Brother Rudra...
You mean, me and that witch...
We just have to use it as bait.
We must lead her to you, that's all.
Remember? She saw love in your eyes.
-Yes.
-And then?
Then leave it to me.
She is very strong in her dueling.
But I know how to overpower
her when she is out of her house.
But where will we call her?
Right here, in Vicky's Palace.
Best place.
Hurry up.
Stree is out hunting today.
Don't step out of the
house and lock the door.
-Okay.
-Come back soon.
I feel scared alone.
-I'll be back soon.
Keep the doors closed.
Vicky, you're looking really handsome.
-Now wear this cap.
-No, no.
-I said wear it.
-No, no, caps. You'll ruin my hair.
-But the groom has to wear...
-I don't want to...
Wear it.
Dad had such vivid
dreams about my wedding.
Who knew that I'll be
marrying a witch some day.
Don't worry.
You're getting a chance
to save the entire city.
Not everyone gets this opportunity.
-Don't be scared.
-Don't you want to save Janna?
Don't you want to bring him back again?
What is the plan? What do we do?
Stree will definitely come here
after reading the message on the wall.
When she looks into your eyes,
don't look away.
Instead look into her eyes.
I know a spell.
That spell will render her powerless.
And then we must drive
this dagger through her heart.
Dagger? How can I...
We're waiting inside. Don't be scared.
-Let's go.
-Listen...
Will your spell work?
-90 percent
-What percent?
Maybe 99% percent.
Meaning there is a 1% chance I'll be dead.
-Daddy...
-Let's go.
Listen.
I am going.
Don't worry, okay.
Don't forget you are Vicky.
The guy who can spend
a night with a witch.
In case I don't come back,
don't come looking for me.
And... look after my dad.
THE LAST NIGHT
O Stree come back tomorrow.
O Stree there are no men here.
O STREE COME HERE.
I think it's her.
She isn't coming inside.
Is she suspicious?
Stree is smarter than you thought.
-Janna.
Janna. Listen to me. Janna.
-Leave him.
Janna.
Vicky.
-Janna!
-Janna.
Vicky is missing.
Vicky.
-Vicky isn't here.
-Isn't he?
Where could he be?
Meaning Stree was here
and she took her lover.
Don't say that.
All our arrangements, the wedding
night preparations, didn't work.
Where did your sister take him?
-Vicky just sent a message, on WhatsApp.
-What?
He just shared his location.
Stree.
Where are you, Stree?
Stree, I...
Okay. Fine. I am sitting here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I am sitting right here.
This is the same place.
I guess she took him to the bedroom.
And she won't let him go until
she spends her wedding night.
Oh, God.
Stree... I am ready.
Come to this bed.
We'll spend our wedding night.
I am getting ready.
I'm taking it off.
Do I have to take my pants off too?
Fine, I'll take it off.
I am ready now. Come on.
Sorry. Sorry...
Sorry, Stree. I understand
that you've no interest in all this.
I respect you.
I'll even wear my clothes back.
See, I am wearing them back.
Don't kill me, Stree.
I misunderstood you.
Vicky!
Janna.
What happened? Is she dead?
She is just powerless at the moment.
But we must finish her
before she gets her powers back.
Where are your clothes?
Sorry, I...
I thought in order to save the city,
I will have to sleep with her.
But you know what,
I don't think she wants any of it.
Here you go.
You must pierce her
heart with this dagger.
And cut off her braid.
Braid? How did her braid get in all this?
And, how will I do this?
You do it, please.
I would've done it if I could.
You will have to do it.
You're the protector of the city. Come on.
Yes, I know I am the protector,
but I am a tailor, not a killer.
-Kill her before she wakes up again.
-Take it. Come on.
Yes.
Do we have to kill her?
Poor thing is lying down so comfortably.
This is exactly how the
people of this city treated her.
And we're doing the same.
So what's the difference
between us and them?
She must be having a reason.
She is trying to find her true love.
Let her go, please.
There must be another way.
Like lizard's tail, cockroach soup.
Then cut off her braid.
This will make her powerless.
And, she won't die either.
Okay.
No, no, no.
Find the dagger.
Vicky, look into her eyes.
Vicky, open your eyes.
She won't do anything
if you look in her eyes.
It's not working.
She is hungry for love.
Look into her eyes with love.
Love.
Love...
More love, Vicky.
I am shitting in my pants,
and you want more feelings.
Quiet!
What is all this yelling for?
This is no way to take revenge.
I am the protector of the city,
so show some respect.
Always screaming.
Vicky. Here.
Vicky. Throw the braid away.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Dagger.
Sit up.
Get up.
Sit up straight.
-I think she's gone. Isn't it?
-Yes.
She kept attacking her.
But I snuck up behind
her and cut off her braid.
Then she disappeared.
And didn't come back.
But is the Stree dead or not?
Tell me.
Meaning she will come
back again next year.
-She's only hungry for one thing.
-No. it's two.
What?
Love and respect,
which this city never gave her.
And that was this city's biggest mistake.
And we were going to
repeat the same mistake.
And if this city gives her
the respect, which she never received.
Then she might leave the city.
These brave men together
have protected the city
and we will never
forget their contribution.
All the youngsters who went missing
in the last two days have returned.
Are you listening?
-There she is.
-Stop. Stop.
Sister-in-law.
The flower. The flower.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
Everyone was looking for you.
You wore the dress.
Does it fit well?
You took my measurements so well.
This is for you.
I could've never fought
against the Stree without you.
Thank you.
You are very nice, Vicky.
I wish we had met you before, then
we could have a friendship.
Can we have a friendship?
You mean friends, or...
Yes. Isn't that what friendship means?
No.
There's another meaning
for friendship in our town.
What if I want to talk to you,
or meet you?
I don't even have your number.
Just think of me.
Do you have to go?
Please wait for a few more days.
Please.
Vicky, please!
Name?
You didn't tell me your name...
This is my first time where he's smitten
by love but doesn't know her name.
Maybe this is true love.
Vicky, please.
For the past three years,
I had only one motive.
Defeating Stree.
I tried everything I knew,
but it wasn't enough.
There's always a method
to control any power.
Just cut off her braid.
She will become powerless, and won't die.
I would've done it long ago if I could.
You're the protector of the city,
you have to do it.
ONE YEAR LATER.
O STREE PROTECT US.
Music.
Everyone's talking about you
They all know that you're an angel
You're hard to get
Your poor beloved's been waiting
All I know is there's a cave
but the cave's hard to open
No matter what I do,
but you're never impressed
Your beloved's been wandering around
I've played all the shots
And have been in a tight spot
But haven't yet hit the jackpot
But you'll get it, You'll get it
You'll get it
I'll get it too
The miracle's going to happen
You'll get it, You'll get it
You'll get it
Someday we'll all get it
Be patient my friend
I warned you before
She will come draped in a sari
Draped in a sari
And come for your
Heart, Your heart
She comes alone
When she comes along
Just meet me
Meet me in my dreams
Meet me completely decked up
Don't you worry my dear
Because
You'll get it, You'll get it
You'll get it
I'll get it too
The miracle's going to happen
You'll get it, You'll get it
You'll get it
Someday we'll all get it
Be patient my friend