Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Attention everyone!
The Mahapooja
festivities begin today.
The veneration of the Mahapooja
will be carried out by female devotees,
as it was done last time.
And the men are requested
to use a rattle
to entertain themselves
as well as the children.
All the women are requested
to wear red saris
and assemble in the temple courtyard.
"She'd visit during the grand
veneration festivities, it's true,"
"Go for it, DJ!"
"She'd visit during the grand
veneration festivities, it's true,"
"Yeah, she'd visit during the grand
"In the lonely streets,"
"She'd call out to men from behind."
"Yeah, she'd visit during the grand
veneration festivities, it's true,"
"With her voice so mesmerizing,
she'd steal their hearts,"
"Yeah, she'd visit during the grand
veneration festivities, it's true,"
"And, and, and..."
"And if anyone dared
to turn around and look,"
"She would strip him bare,"
- Oh no!
- Oh God! - What are you saying?
"She would strip him bare,
And take him away fast."
"She'd visit during the grand
veneration festivities, it's true,"
"So in Chanderi,
the men used to not step out of the house,"
"English lyrics, huh?"
"Brother Rudra!"
"And those who went out,
they dressed in a sari and blouse."
"It was hard to get rid of Stree,"
"That's why everyone
wrote outside their homes -"
"O Stree, come tomorrow,"
"No, don't come today,"
"Then came the protector of Chanderi,
mighty and bold,"
"He risked it all, made his move,"
"He looked into Stree's eyes,
with affection so true,"
"With love..."
"Stree's strength was in her braid,"
In her braid!
And the protector chopped it off too,"
"Chopped off!"
"He chopped off that braid
and saved all the men,"
"And gave Stree - "
"The love and respect she deserved."
Brother Rudra?
Looks like someone had a little
too much to drink last night, hmm?
Barfing and all?
Knowledge.
Just getting some knowledge out
of my system.
You know, when you've got too much knowledge it overflows,
you've got to find a way to let it all out.
What brings you here?
Oh, I just came by to drop off
this old letter for you.
I found it
when I was cleaning up the place.
Wow, that's pretty quick service, Postman.
A letter that was received
during the Pooja,
is being delivered during
the Mahapooja?
Who sent it?
I was kind of curious myself about
who would bother sending you a letter--
- Hmm, maybe it's a love letter?
- Why do you say that?
Well, look at it! It's got all these drawings
of red flowers and vines on it.
And there's some writing in Urdu, too.
You can't read Urdu, huh?
Unknowledgeable man.
Private and confidential.
For Mr. Rudra's eyes only.
Sounds like it's from Shama.
Come on, open it up, let's take a look!
Why don't you read it?
Nah, I can't read Urdu.
You shouldn't be reading
other people's love letters anyway.
Don't get so excited.
Still delivering letters
in the digital age of emails!
You're going to be out
of a job before you know it, buddy.
Better get moving.
That's the trouble with small towns,
everyone's nosy and wants
to read everyone else's mail.
Trollers.
Huh?
Vicky?
Hi.
Vicky!
Hi!
You? Is that really you?
Yep, it's me.
I thought you were just...
It's been so long.
I've missed you.
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
Right, right, right!
You...
You are still wearing the same old dress.
Yes.
No worries,
I can make you a new one.
In just 31 minutes flat.
But my measurements have changed.
You can take them again if you want.
Perfect.
Nah, I always mess it up
when it comes to you.
Alright, then just do it without
a measuring tape.
- Can I really do that?
- Go for it.
Okay, I'll give that a shot then.
Did you have a little shot
of rum before coming here?
I've never seen you...
Can you see me now?
Or do you need another smack
to wake you up?
Getting a little handsy there
to take my measurements, huh?
You're trying to stitch me
a new blouse?
You would've kissed me
if I hadn't stopped you.
Well, I...
What's going on here, Vicky?
- So I...
- Oh Chanderi's Forlorn Lover!
Keep daydreaming like this
and you'll be curing your own nightfall problems!
You dress up and sit here waiting for her,
but she's not coming back.
That unfaithful woman
was just an illusion.
- Alright, that's enough, Brother Rudra.
- Yeah, enough already.
She vanished into thin air
from a moving bus!
I'm telling you, I won't tolerate
you saying a single bad word about her.
Anyway, what brings you here this morning?
Why am I here?
Oh right, to show you this.
Take a look.
- Chanderi Puran?
- Yep,
some torn pages from the Chanderi Puran.
Someone sent them to me
in the mail a couple of months ago.
The postman just delivered them today.
Stree was a prostitute.
She had a lover.
We already knew that part.
But we didn't know this.
The letter also included something else.
He is coming back.
Yes.
Who is coming back?
That's the million-dollar question,
isn't it?
We don't know who exactly is coming back.
- He is coming back?
- We have no idea
who tore these pages,
why they did it,
or why they are sending them to me now.
There has to be some secret
agenda behind this.
Maybe someone's trying to warn us.
- Brother Rudra?
- Hmm?
This chapter is done, okay?
You need to find something better
to do with your time.
And do me a favor - brush
your teeth in the mornings.
Don't come here smelling like that.
He is coming back.
Listen, son,
have you ever thought about your future?
The girls here have become quite modern.
One by one, they're leaving town
and moving to the big cities.
I know, Daddy.
They are doing it for their own good.
So what am I supposed to do?
What if there isn't
a single girl left for you?
If there aren't any left, then so be it.
It doesn't make a difference to me.
What are you saying?
Of course, it makes a difference to you.
Stop! Listen up.
It should make a difference to you!
Have a seat.
- I'm running late, Daddy.
- I told you to sit down.
Remember I told you a young person's body
bustles with vitality?
Yeah, like a tank full of energy
or something.
Exactly!
It's craving to come out, right?
Yeah,
but you taught me to be self-reliant.
There's a limit to that as well.
Just get to the point.
A virgin oil is healthy,
but a virgin man is not.
You're being too cool about this, Daddy.
- I'm leaving, I'm late.
- Just hear me out.
Do you want to get married or not?
I don't want to. So?
Then there's only one option left.
What?
Take this.
Go and do it.
Go and do what?
Friendship.
- Daddy!
- Yes!
You never know,
perhaps that will bring about a change?
You are committing a sin here.
I'm fasting,
and you're sitting here
saying these wrong things to me.
There's nothing wrong with it.
- But I'm not like that.
- But...
You keep enjoying your unhealthy habits
in your virgin oil.
Hey!
Look, I know you won't go
for the friendship thing.
So, I'll just keep the cash.
Say thanks to Uncle.
Want a burger?
Sure.
Nah, I'm fasting.
It's the girls who fast for the boys,
not the other way around!
He's fasting, he says!
You used to fast until just
a few months ago.
I didn't fast for Chitti,
I did it to stay slim and trim.
- I see.
- Considering your situation,
I'd suggest you do
the Akshay Ekadashi fast.
Why?
To get freedom from that unrequited
love you have for that witch.
Like hell, he's in love!
- What?
- That so-called girlfriend of yours,
the one you've bought 40 teddy bears
for in the last four months -
you used my money for that.
- I'm not giving them back.
- Give them back.
Nope, not happening.
- I won't.
Give me my money back!
This money is mine.
It was your money, but now it's mine.
- I won't give it back.
- Give them back. Hurry up.
Vicky, please.
First ask nicely, with some love.
Is this what you call love?
Hmm.
Forget it.
You should beg for it.
That suits you better.
Vicky, pleaseeeee!
I need to buy a gift for Chitti.
- Pleaseeeee!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Alright, alright.
But first, promise
you'll never call her a witch again.
I won't, I promise.
Apologize.
Sorry.
Apologize to her.
She's here?
Say it from the bottom of your heart,
and she'll hear you.
Okay.
Sorry, witch, I didn't...
Sorry, plain simple sorry.
Thank you.
Now I can get her
a teddy bear this month too.
Hey, your little Miss Katrina is here.
Bits!
Burger?
- Ugh.
- Ew, man.
- No.
- You'll start bloating up again.
Your tummy will stick out,
and you'll make me stand
in front of you in all the pictures.
Nah, Bits.
The frontal is not my best angle.
No, I wasn't having it.
Brother Vicky was having it.
Remember, I'm doing "intimate" fasting?
Hey Vicky!
Yes, it's mine.
How is it going?
Where have you been these days?
Why don't you go come for a jog anymore?
Because he's still stuck
in his unrequited love.
Oh no.
Come on, Vicky,
forget about her already.
You can have anyone you want.
What?
Trust me, you're so handsome and talented.
- Aw, come on now...
- Leave Chanderi.
Get out of this place.
- Remember my friends...
- Yeah.
Shardha, Nikku, and Gauri?
They left the town without
even telling anyone.
Okay.
- You should leave too.
- Leave.
You are right.
I think you should leave too.
What or who do you have here anyway?
I'm here!
Ready-made, top-to-toe.
And I take such good care of her.
I've brought you your protein shake too.
You can have it.
It's Monday today.
We have to do that tonight, right?
Yes, we do.
- Okay, I'm running late, so...
- Okay.
Bye, Vicky.
- Bye.
- Come for a jog, okay?
- Bye, Bits.
- Bye.
Bits.
Short for Bittu.
Thank goodness your name isn't Tittu.
"Come down, Come down."
"Lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-love..."
"Give it to me, give it to me."
Soft Chitti, warm Chitti,
little ball of fur.
Happy Chitti, sleepy Chitti,
purr purr purr.
- Bits, sing it nicely.
- Yes?
Nicely? Okay.
Soft Chitti,
Warm Chitti,
Little ball of fur.
Happy Chitti,
Sleepy Chitti,
Purr purr purr.
Looks like you're not in the mood for it.
- Nah, I am.
- Nah, it's cool.
I'll call Prathamesh.
Why would you call him?
He puts me to sleep so nicely.
No need, I'll put you to sleep.
Don't do that.
Alright, I'll sing, I'll sing it well.
Soft Chitti,
Warm Chitti,
Little ball of fur.
"Lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-love..."
"Give it to me, give it to me.
Give it! Give it! Give it!"
Happy Chitti,
Sleepy Chitti,
Purr...
"Come down, Come down."
Someone's looking a bit tired, huh?
If you hadn't told me to
"come down, come down",
I wouldn't have come down.
- Really?
- Yeah.
No need to brag.
I know you sang her a lullaby.
She has trouble sleeping.
She can't fall asleep until
I sing her a lullaby.
I'm telling you this
because we're friends.
Our body bustles with vitality.
Did you see someone out there?
Let's get going
before someone overhears us.
Start the engine!
No!
Mummy! Please! Momma!
- Chitti!
Upstairs! I heard her scream upstairs!
- Uncle, we should go upstairs and check on Chitti.
- What happened?
What's this commotion about?
- What was that?
- Chitti!
Chitti!
Where is Chitti?
- Chitti!
- Where is Chitti!
What the hell just happened?
Chitti!
The car's trashed too.
- Come on!
- Let's go!
What happened?
- That's Bittu!
- Come on, let's go guys.
Who did this?
Did anyone see anything?
Did she run off to Delhi?
She didn't need to break
the wall for that.
She could've just taken the bus.
I've got a bad feeling about this, Vicky.
What happened, Bittu?
Did you see anything?
- Let's go downstairs and look for her.
- Yeah. Let's go.
O dear lord, I earnestly pray,
please keep the evil away.
Chitti!
- Chitti!
- Hello, Aunty.
- What's wrong?
- What happened?
- Chitti's missing.
- Chitti!
Brother Rudra?
- Come here.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Brother Rudra?
- What are you doing here?
Look at this.
It's a huge footprint.
Looks like a Dinosaur's.
So a dinosaur kidnapped Chitti?
Come on,
how can a Jurassic creature be
in a place without even a jogger's park?
- You are right. But then...?
- Whose footprint is this?
It...
It belongs to a demon.
A demon?
Monster! Ogre! Beast!
Bakasura, Banasura,
Bhasmasur, Narakasura, Talasur...
You can find books
on these legendary beings at my store,
with a 5% discount.
Brother Rudra,
can you promote your store later?
First, let's figure
out where Chitti went!
She didn't go anywhere.
He took her.
Who?
A headless guy.
He had no head.
I saw him.
He went this way.
Where? Here?
This way?
He took her through the wall.
Shut up, pothead.
Enough of this nonsense.
Don't believe a word this pothead says,
just keep looking for the girl.
I'm sure she's at her friend's place.
Chitti's ice cream printed sock!
Chitti!
Why are you yelling
her name like that, huh?
Chitti is my love.
If it had been my turn
to help her sleep today,
then I would have saved her.
Vicky...
Ms. Stree?
Ms. Stree? It's me, Vicky.
I thought you'd left for good,
but looks like you are back.
Vicky...
Ms. Stree, we...
we're on the same team now, aren't we?
We are friends now.
Sorry about cutting your braid.
Massage your head with warm oil
and it'll grow back in no time.
Ms. Stree, I'm going to turn around now.
Don't take off my clothes, please.
We're friends, remember?
Friends.
Ms. Stree?
What's wrong?
Brother Rudra, why did you ditch
that footprint thing and follow me here?
It's me, not your brother Rudra.
You didn't have your daily dose
of rum earlier or what?
Vicky, it's me.
Wait a second.
Bittu?
Daddy?
Badri?
Whoever you are, just give me
a whack and get this over with.
Wake me up.
Go on, slap me.
Hit me.
Huh?
You...?
You...
You're really back!
You're back!
You're back! You're back! You're back!
I thought about you
from the bottom of my heart.
But you took your sweet time to return.
You know the names
they call you behind your back?
What?
They call you an illusion,
a witch, an ogress
and say you're an unfaithful lover
who rejected my love,
and now I'll seek my revenge.
That's not all.
You know what they say about me?
They call me Chanderi's Forlorn Lover,
the Ruined Lover Boy,
Weirdo Vicky, Roadside Romeo,
Love Me No More,
Crazy in Love,
the Latest Loser, Crazy Lover,
the Heartbroken Prince
with unrequited love,
Kabir Singh, the Dry Virgin.
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
And you're still the same too.
Speaking of change,
did you change the bus back then?
The conductor said
you just disappeared from the bus, so...
- Everyone has been...
- Can we discuss this stuff later, Vicky?
First,
I need to tell you something important,
that's why I got you here alone.
Alright, tell me.
I know who took that girl.
Which girl?
Chitti?
Not just Chitti,
I know who took all the girls.
Who?
The one who killed that prostitute
and turned her into Stree.
That's why
he only came back after Stree left.
He laid low until now.
Who is that little girl?
Chitti disappeared.
Then Vicky went missing too.
I'll be damned.
Brother Rudra,
what if they ran away together?
Never doubt a friend.
But look at the timing.
Brother Rudra,
where's the Chithi?
Huh? Chitti is here?
No, Chitti's not here.
You had it.
I had Chitti with me?
Yeah, remember you brought
it up to the rooftop.
The rooftop?
Yeah, he brought it there,
opened it, showed it to me,
- and then took it with him.
- What?
Oh, I see.
He's talking about the Chithi.
I'm talking about Chitti too.
And I'm talking about the Chithi.
- No, no...
- Why are you talking about Chitti?
Why wouldn't I talk about the Chithi?
Do you have some copyright
over it or what?
Chitti belongs to me,
so of course I'll talk about her.
He's talking about the Chithi.
That's what I'm saying!
- Chitti is mine, why won't I talk about her?
- How can that Chithi belong to you?
- It belongs to him, he has it.
- How can Chitti belong to you?
He's talking about the Chithi!
Chithi - the letter!
"You've got mail!"
Letter, mail, correspondence, missive.
And you're talking about
"I'm your fair lady, get me bangles baby!"
Oh, I see.
T-T-I and T-H-I
- Okay, got it.
- Got it.
I had it. I had received it.
- T-T-I and T-H-I
- I see.
- Give me a second.
- Okay.
What did you think?
I thought that...
I'm not interested in singing lullabies
to your step-girlfriend.
She's not my step-girlfriend!
I just got too emotional, man!
Alright, don't cry. Don't cry.
This is the Chithi, the letter.
We wouldn't have an issue if you were
more familiar with the Hindi alphabets.
It contains the secret
that will tell us who took Chitti.
Then read it quickly.
- May I?
- Brother Rudra,
see what's written in it.
Stree's murderers -
Chandarbhan and the sinful
village council members.
Chandarbhan was the village chief
of Chanderi.
Powerful as a bull, tall as a camel,
and proud like Ravana.
He was a womanizer and a drunk.
Though I'd say drinking
isn't always a bad thing.
Some drink to drown their sorrows,
others to forget about ex-lovers.
As long as it's in moderation...
Brother Rudra,
could you please continue reading?
Yes, of course.
Dushashana was his ideal.
Disrobing women was his hobby for real.
For them, women's duty was to clean up,
keep the family fed,
And warm their beds whenever they said.
Chandarbhan and his friends loved
to watch a prostitute dance.
When that prostitute tried to tie a knot,
these sinners
first slit her lover's throat
and then right in front
of their little girl,
they burnt both of them at one spot.
Then that prostitute came back as Stree,
no wonder,
and she beheaded Chandarbhan
and his friends
and buried them six feet under.
Those headless bodies
still lay buried somewhere.
Oh damn!
Remember the wall at Chitti's place?
Didn't have a head.
Even the pothead said...
What else does it say, Brother Rudra?
Please read.
Give me a minute.
Those headless bodies
still lay buried somewhere,
but nobody knows exactly where.
Men used to spend their days eating
carom seeds and lazing around in bed.
- Carom seeds?
- They considered massages
as exercise and pigeons
cradling as an art.
Carom seeds, massages, pigeons?
Looks like the author lost his mind.
The author is trying
to say that after Stree left,
that headless monster returned
and started taking those girls away.
Yes.
And we all thought our innocent girls
were just skipping town.
You have become quite sharp in my company.
- Thank you.
- Hold on a minute.
How do you know that?
Well...
Well, she told me.
Vicky, please.
She is back, I swear.
Brother Rudra, he's daydreaming again.
- I'm not daydreaming, dummy.
- Really?
If she in fact told you that,
then ask her where he took my Chitti!
In all the excitement,
I forgot to ask her that.
But I'll ask her next time I meet her.
There's nothing to be excited
about in that.
No, in fact, I'm sad.
Chitti...
"You call for me,"
"And I'll come without a care,"
"I won't be late, I swear,"
You made this in just one day?
Not a whole day - just a few hours,
actually.
You are an amazing artist.
Thank you.
"I'll stop breathing,"
"But my word I'll keep,"
"I was, I am,
and yours I'll always be,"
Even ages seem like moments,
o' my love so true,"
"This is how special your love is
for me and you,"
"I was, I am,
and yours I'll always be,"
"You promised long ago, "
"And now you've returned,"
"I'm grateful you're here
for my heart has yearned,"
"You're welcome,"
"You're always welcome here,"
"Come and promise
you'll never again disappear,"
"It is true love,
that never ends, trust me"
"I was, I am,
and yours I'll always be,"
"You promised long ago, "
"And now you've returned,"
"I'm grateful you're here
for my heart has yearned,"
"You're welcome,"
"You're always welcome here,"
"Come and promise
you'll never again disappear,"
- Vicky!
- She bit me!
Hurry up!
- Vicky!
- Vicky! Vicky!
- My finger!
What happened, Vicky?
What's wrong?
- Love bite.
- Love bite!
Brother Rudra!
Where are you going? Come here.
- Love bite! Love bite!
- What is it?
- Love bite!
- Where is it?
Love bite!
A love bite on a finger?
Where's the love bite?
What?
Well, I got a little carried away so...
She bit me.
Who?
My girl.
Sounds like a repeat performance.
- No! I swear on Daddy!
- Then what?
Candles were burning everywhere,
flowers were raining down.
I was flying around like Superman.
Okay, so then where did the flowers
and candles go?
Where are the candles?
Looks like she packed everything up
and left, huh?
I'm sure you must have asked her
where that monster took Chitti, right?
So where did he take her?
Vicky,
honestly, stop daydreaming.
This is no fantasy. It's true.
It's true love.
And where can we find
this true love of yours?
Bittu,
there's a realm beyond right and wrong.
That's where you'll find her.
There's an asylum just
a few blocks from that realm.
That's where we'll find you
in a couple of days!
Idiot!
Hey!
Bittu...
Vicky.
Right.
Vicky,
I say this because I'm older and wiser.
What you saw and felt
was just an illusion.
It's not real.
How many more whacks will it take
for you to get that?
Vicky,
we're counting on you
to help us find Chitti.
Come on!
Bittu?
- No, please don't cry.
- Let me go, Vicky.
If you have so much faith in me,
I won't let you down.
I'm Vicky, after all.
I've found a way to get Chitti back
from that headless monster.
What's the plan?
To defeat this headless monster,
we'll have to call Stree back.
Have you lost your mind?
"We'll have to call Stree back," he says.
Chanderi got rid
of Stree with great difficulty.
All her power was in her braid
that you had cut off.
So what's the point of calling her then?
Stree can't help us.
She can.
Because she is Stree.
Even without her braid, she's powerful.
She doesn't need the braid to be strong.
So then...
But how will we call her back?
We know someone
who can lead us to Stree.
Anybody home?
What are you staring at?
Jana! Jana! Jana!
I missed you guys so much!
Cut the drama.
We called you so many times.
Sorry, guys.
I used to have seizures.
People thought I was cursed.
So Mom sent me here
and made me delete all contacts.
She made me block your numbers too.
You forget your friends for a woman?
She's my mother, dude.
Sorry.
Jana...
It's time to be a good friend to us now.
Okay?
Only you can find her now.
Who?
Her!
Her effect still lingers inside you,
correct?
You still get seizures, right?
Yes?
Yes.
- Did you hear that?
- What sound?
- No.
- Are you lying to us?
- Are you enjoying in private?
- No, man.
- Who is it?
- A special friend, huh? Friendship?
- No...
- Introduce us, too.
Vicky, please. Vicky, please.
No, dude.
- Tinted room!
- Hear me out...
- Vicky! Here's his lady...
- Hear me out... Don't go in there!
- Your special friend, huh?
- Don't go in there!
- It's my uncle's room. Listen...
- Your special friend!
Bhask--
I told you not to go in there.
He took off.
Why don't you ever listen to me?
- You used to be such a scaredy-cat.
- Yes.
How did you end up with
a dangerous dog like that as a pet?
Change, Vicky.
Change is the only constant in this world.
I'm not the same old Jana you knew.
- I'm a changed guy now. For real.
- Don't get all Einstein on us, dude.
Let's talk about why we're here.
What did you want to discuss?
- Well, you see...
- Listen, Jana,
you need to come back to Chanderi with us.
Why?
We need to find Stree.
Has he lost it?
Nah, I have not.
You should do it for Chanderi.
Who in their right mind
would jump into a deadly well?
You got to come with us!
Let's get going.
I need to study for the IAS exam,
got to take care of him.
- To hell with your studies and your dog!
- Did you hear that?
- Bittu! Jana!
- What?
- He's just blowing smoke.
- Yeah, he talks without thinking. Idiot.
- No, we don't need to find Stree.
- Then?
You have a part to play in Stree's play.
- Which play?
The one Brother Rudra's putting on?
- The one where Jana has to be in?
- Yup,
you got to be in Brother Rudra's play.
- Yes.
- You have an important role in it.
- Yes
- "A special experience."
- Wow.
- For real?
- Yup.
When do I start packing my bags?
Let's go right now.
"You made a promise but it was a lie,"
It's in the back. Check there.
- "I waited all night in the fields"
- What's up?
"but you never came by."
"I waited all night in the fields
but you never came by."
- Mummy!
- Jana!
- Jana's back! You look great.
- That's enough.
- How have you been?
- I'm doing alright.
- Why'd you come back from Delhi?
- Because of Vicky and Bittu.
- Vicky and Bittu?
- Greetings, Aunty.
- Greetings, Bittu!
"With no blanket to warm me
in the middle of the night,"
"You said you'd be there
but you never came by."
"I waited all night in the fields
Oh, Jana,
I'm so glad to see you back here.
You still look the same,
like a little cricket.
Thank you, Brother Rudra.
- Cricket!
Come on, have a seat.
No, not here, go sit over there.
Alright, tell me when do I get
my big moment in the play?
What play?
Your play.
My play?
Actually, we brought you here
for an important job.
What important job?
Look,
there's no need to be scared.
Chanderi's in trouble again.
A dangerous and powerful headless monster
has kidnapped Bittu's step-girlfriend.
No way.
Impossible.
Unbelievable.
I couldn't believe it
at first either, Jana.
But it's the truth.
I can accept a headless monster,
but how am I supposed to believe
that Bittu has a girlfriend?
It's a miracle.
Miracles do happen in this world.
Did they even do the "friendship"?
He goes for "friendship",
but just sings her lullabies and leaves.
I'd love to hear that lullaby.
Soft Chitti, warm Chitti,
little ball of fur.
- Someone stop him.
- Forget about it. Stop.
The point is,
that this dangerous headless monster
took his girlfriend.
Yes.
We need Stree's help to get her back.
And Stree is like a sister to you.
So you'll help us find her.
- No way! Absolutely not!
- We love you.
- Jana!
- I'm not going to help find anyone!
No, Brother Rudra, you don't get it.
I have to study for the IAS exams.
- I'm heading back to Delhi.
- Jana!
- Yes?
Look me in the eyes.
- Can you see the truth in them?
- Nah.
Come on, Jana, you can see the truth.
Okay, maybe a little bit.
You don't have to do much.
Disha Batani. That's it.
Who is she now?
Who's who?
- You just mentioned her.
- Hey! Step side! Move it!
You need to guide us
in the right direction.
No, no, no.
Jana, Stree's effect still lingers in you.
Just tell us where to find her
and we'll handle the rest.
She'll end up handling all of us instead.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Have I ever let anything
bad happen to you?
You put a frog in my pants
when we were in 5th grade.
Have you forgotten that?
After that?
In 10th grade,
you guys locked me
in the ladies' room and ran off.
After that?
You had me hang upside down
in college to steal a kite.
Where the heck was that kite anyway?
- After that?
After that?
Nothing.
You didn't do anything else after that.
We always step out at night.
And I have to lie to my mom.
So what? We are friends, right?
By the way Vicky, you didn't have to lie,
you know?
You committed a sin.
Slow down, Brother Rudra.
Ugh,
and now we're back
at this inauspicious place again.
You know what, why don't we just come
back here in the morning instead?
- Nah,
- Let's go.
Stree's a nocturnal creature.
She's only going to come out at night.
- Okay.
- Brother Rudra, can I say something?
Come on, Jana,
you've got to save your sister-in-law.
Why do I have to be the one
to do this, though?
She is your younger sister-in-law
after all!
Because there's literally
no one else who can, that's why.
- Alright, let's go.
- Where are we going?
- Let's go.
Why do I have to lead the way?
- Just go on, lead the way.
- What?
- I said, lead the way.
- Why should I have to lead the way?
Just go on, get moving.
Go, call your sister. Call her.
- How do I call her?
- Call her.
Hey Sister?
Stree, my darling sister?
Hello?
Look who's here, Sister.
Call her nicely!
Yes, call her.
"Sister, my darling sister!"
"Sister! My sweet-sweet sister!"
Sister...?
Nah, she ain't coming.
She's not going to show up like this.
Stree only comes when men are all alone.
Bittu? Brother Rudra?
Can you two come over here for a second?
- Come on.
- No.
- This is an adult conversation.
- Okay, you got to step back for this one.
- Okay.
- But I'm an adult too, you know!
We'll fill you in on it later.
He's absolutely right.
We have to leave him alone if we want Stree
to actually show up and kidnap him.
But what if he scares himself to death?
Nah, he'll be fine.
He's right.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
So, what were you all talking about, huh?
Hey, check it out! A rainbow!
- Where?
- Oh, look at that leaf, it's so green!
Where's the rainbow?
No, there's no rainbow here, silly.
Vicky!
Seriously,
this isn't the time for hide-and-seek!
Vicky didn't come with us?
Go check and see where he is.
- Vicky?
- You go check on him.
Bittu?
You have the torch. You go check on him.
But I have really bad eyesight, you know.
- You have bad eyesight?
- Yeah.
- Okay, we'll do it together then.
- Sounds good.
Hey, what was that noise?
What noise?
The noise you just made.
No, I didn't.
Where'd that come from?
I heard it too.
Bloody rascals! Left me stranded!
Lied to me about the rainbow!
Vicky! Vicky! Vicky!
Jana!
- Jana!
Hair! Hair! Hair!
- Hair?
- Hair! It touched me.
Wait a second,
you said there was
a rainbow out there, right?
Where exactly was it?
There was one out there, right?
Whose bright idea was it, anyway?
- Bittu?
- Nah, it was all Vicky's idea.
Brother Rudra, I told you this plan
of yours is not looking too good.
Honestly, I didn't expect this from you,
Brother Rudra.
Alright, I'll apologize on his behalf.
Listen up, guys,
I know where we can find Ms. Stree.
Then why didn't you tell us sooner?
- I just got the script.
- Okay.
There's a spot around here with
a bunch of statues.
- Okay.
- We have to find that place.
Okay.
But not alone.
- But we stick together, right?
- No splitting up.
Form a square.
- Form a square.
- Do I have to turn around?
Let's have each other's backs,
and form a square.
- Just like we used to do when we were kids.
- I know, I know.
- Which way do we have to go? That way?
- No!
- Move anti-clockwise.
- Vicky, give us some direction.
- That way.
- Okay.
- That way. Okay.
Easy, Brother Rudra.
Don't rush it.
Slow down, I'm an old man!
- You're not that old!
- O' Stree...
Ms. Stree,
I've got some friends here with me.
I am Vicky.
We'd like to have a word with you.
Ms. Stree?
Over here.
- Come stand over here.
- Okay.
And she'll call you from behind.
- Why are we doing this again?
- Oh,
I remember seeing this statue
in the Chanderi Puran.
Did you find out
who sent you those torn pages?
It must've been Mr. Shastri, right?
Mr. Shastri passed away ages ago.
- Huh?
- Oh no.
Jana,
you need to think about Stree--
Huh?
- Jana!
Look, over there! Over there!
Oh no!
- Jana!
How did he get stuck up there?
Jana! Come on down, Jana!
- Jana!
- Get down from there!
- He's passed out!
- Huh? Looks like he's got cataract!
- He's unconscious, look at him!
- Stree must've hung him up there.
- Oh no.
We're sorry, Ms. Stree.
Please forgive us.
- We apologize.
- Please let our friend go.
- Okay.
- Ms. Stree, please!
Jana!
- Jana!
- Open your eyes, Jana.
Hey Jana...
Jana?
Jana? Jana? Wake up. Get up.
- Jana?
- Say something.
Wake up, Jana!
Brother Rudra, please do something.
Jana...
Say something, Jana.
- He's gone.
- Huh?
He's gone.
Have you lost your mind?
He's not gone!
Jana!
Get up, Jana!
Come on, Jana, get up!
Open your eyes, Jana! Jana!
You don't have to find Stree, Jana!
Come on, get up, Jana!
Come on, get up, Jana! Please, Jana!
We'll plan a trip to Goa,
we'll go to Goa together...
Jana...
Jana, get up!
Come on, Jana!
Jana! Wake up!
He's not going to wake up.
- Jana...
Jana...
Run!
This way, Jana! This way!
This way! We need to go this way!
Jana is alive!
Jana! Jana! Jana! Jana!
You are alive! You are alive!
You are alive, Jana!
- He is safe!
- We thought you were dead!
I even gave you a French kiss.
Thank goodness!
- We don't have time for this, let's go!
- What for?
- He's coming!
- Who?
HE!!!!
RUN!!!
- Run!
- Hurry up! Start the bike.
Hurry up, guys!
- Come on, Brother Rudra!
- Let's go, guys! Hurry up!
- Quick, Bittu!
- Yeah, yeah.
- What's wrong?
- I think we're running out of gas!
How much did you buy?
Worth 50 bucks.
That's hardly enough for a burp!
You cheapskate!
It's not his fault, Vicky!
It's his dad's fault.
Don't drag my dad into this.
So what do you want us to do?
Drag your bike in this situation!
- Jana, start pushing.
- Push it.
Yeah, push it.
Let's go, guys.
- Jana...
- Hurry up! Hurry up!
Let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go. Hurry up.
Did you actually see something out there,
or are you just messing with me for kicks and giggles?
Trust me,
there was definitely someone out there.
Let's just head back home quickly.
- Let's go.
- Not home, the fair.
Let's head to the fair instead.
Step on it, Bittu! What's wrong?
What the heck
is that thing behind us, Vicky?
Look back there.
What?
What is?
VICKY!
Jana! Jana! Behind you!
What?
Ouch! He bit me!
I can't balance.
I'm about to die and you're worried
about the stupid balance!
We're going to fall!
Let me go! Shoo, let me go!
Jana, use your elbow!
Hit him with your elbow!
Mummy! Help me!
Mummy! Brother Rudra!
- Here, take this.
- Brother Rudra!
This is no time to be drinking!
Throw it at him!
- Okay, fine.
- Throw it at him!
I'll throw it at him.
Take that, you monster!
- What do I do now?
- Burn him!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Dear Lord, I earnestly pray,
please keep all the evil away!
Burn him!
Fire!
Brother Rudra! We did it!
Vicky! Bittu! Look out!
What's he doing?
NOOO!
Someone's head is stuck in the wheel!
Stop, Brother Rudra! Wait up!
Run, Vicky! Run!
- It's on fire! It's on fire! It's on fire!
- Vicky, don't look behind!
Run, my brother!
Stop the bike! Stop the bike!
Stop, stop, stop,
where are you going?
- Go, go, go!
- Don't look behind.
Hurry up.
This way.
- Turn right.
- Yes, turn right.
I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry!
- Jana!
Stree, my sister, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I came back.
I shouldn't have come back.
I'm such an idiot.
I'm a fool.
- I'm so stupid.
- No.
No, I'm the stupid one. I'm so stupid.
Why do I always get myself into trouble?
First the Stree, then the wolf,
and now the head.
What wolf?
You came back for your sister-in-law.
You came back to save her.
Who Sister-in-law? Whose Sister-in-law?
- To hell with this sister-in-law!
- No, no, no.
A sister-in-law should be treated
just like a mother.
- No, I have only one mother.
- Relax.
- Everything's going to be fine, Jana.
There's nothing to be afraid of, okay?
- No one is going to trouble you, Jana, okay?
- No way.
We're not going to take you anywhere.
What?
- What's wrong?
- What's going on?
He's coming back.
Who?
HIM!
I told you--
Vicky?
Vicky? Vicky!
You guys left me and ran away again!
What do we do now?
What?
- How do we get home?
- What?
How do we get home?!
- Don't shout!
- Don't yell!
- Let's use the elephant.
- Huh?
We'll use this elephant.
Wrong way.
- Right.
- No, go left!
Keep it down.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Keep it down.
- What are you doing?
- What happened?
We have to go left.
Our left or your left?
Turn that off.
Stop that.
Go.
Go see what that is.
- What happened?
- What is it?
It's the...
Vicky... check it out.
I'll check it out! I'll go check it out!
Nobody is here.
He was just standing right there!
I swear on my mom!
- He's there!
- Scaring us for no reason...
Bow down! Bow down! Bow down!
Vicky!
Brother Rudra, he has Vicky!
He picked him up like a ragdoll!
- Hold him.
- Let's get him down.
- Glory to the Goddess!
- Pull him down. Pull him down.
No, no, no Vicky! Don't go out there!
- Don't go out there! No, no, no Vicky!
- Where did he go?
Where did he go?
Has he left?
Vicky! Vicky!
Jana...
Take it easy, take it easy.
- Come on, get up.
- He left.
Are you hurt?
- Greetings. Are you okay?
- Thank you for saving us.
OH NOOO!!
Mummy!
Mummy!!!!
Are you okay?
Mummy!
He totally smashed it.
What's that thing exactly?
A Deadly Corpse.
A Messenger of Death.
And you, ma'am,
really gave the headless monster a run for his money
with this magical braid of yours.
Nice work.
Is this braid hers?
- That...?
- Yes,
this is Stree's braid
- that I've been using to boost my powers.
- Oh!
That's how you were able to twirl
it like helicopter blades last night.
But seriously, Sister,
thanks for last night.
What?
- Thank you, Sister.
- Sister?
Yeah.
Now that she saved your life,
she's your sister, huh?
He calls you a witch behind your back.
And this guy addressing you as 'ma'am'
calls you an illusion,
an unfaithful lover, and whatnot.
He says that.
My apologies, ma'am.
You just disappeared from the bus.
We hadn't heard anything about you
for so long, that's why...
I went to study.
Hear that? She went to study.
To study black magic.
To study Black Magic.
Why'd you get mixed up in Black Magic
and the Red Book stuff?
That doesn't fit your personality at all.
Anyway, it's time to settle down in life.
Vicky, now's not the time
to think about all that.
We need to focus on this headless monster.
- We have to figure out how to stop him.
- Yes, you're right.
Only you can stop him.
You've even taken a course on black magic.
And with your magical braid...
No, my powers are nothing compared to his.
Last night, you saw how
he picked me up like a ragdoll
and threw me away.
His powers are at their peak
during the Mahapooja festivities.
We'll have to stop him
before the very last day, or else...
Or else what?
We'll be facing a disaster.
Argh, you deserve hell
for what you did!
What kind of friends are you?
What's wrong? What happened?
Vicky,
my brother,
I haven't slept since last night.
- Why?
- As soon as I shut my eyelids,
I see images from that place.
Which place?
That place? What place?
- THAT place!
- Where?
- That place!
- What happened?
Where?
- Nah, he means the place you know.
He just came back from Delhi,
didn't he, Aunty?
So he is having visions of that place.
The Red Fort, Ring Road, GB Road...
If that's the only stuff he's seeing,
Why is he so paranoid?
- He didn't sleep a wink last night.
- What's making you lose it, man?
Can you help me get some shut-eye?
Why would she help you sleep?
Don't make me whack you.
- What the hell is going on with my son?
- Listen, listen, listen!
Have you got any castor oil on hand?
Just grab it and dab some on his eyes.
- That will make his vision go away.
- Mummy!
- But...
- You're doomed, all of you!
- I mean...
- What kind of friends are you?
My son was a model student,
studying in Delhi.
- He would have become an IAS officer!
- Aunty...
- But you dragged him here
and who knows where you took
him that he is so scared.
He was up all night.
- What the heck?
- Give us two minutes, Aunty. Calm down.
Take a seat.
Sit here.
Sit.
Thank you.
Now tell us,
what did you see?
I saw the place
that the headless monster came from.
What's out there?
It was a very scary place, Brother.
That day, I didn't actually die.
I ended up going there.
It was just darkness all around.
There weren't any leaves
on the trees at all.
Everything looked all dried up
and withered.
And the rocks were hanging upside down.
And there was lava, lots of lava.
Excuse me, Sister? I'm Jana.
Chitti!
Who shaved your head?
Chitti's bald!
Bald?
They shaved her head, man!
Aw, my Chitti had such amazing silky hair.
I just got her this fancy shampoo
worth 2500 bucks, what a waste!
Why'd you have to buy her such
an expensive shampoo anyway?
Come on, Brother Rudra,
love is love, you know.
I can't even imagine
how Chitti must look without hair, it's crazy.
Stop crying, you big baby.
You're Bittu, not Sneha Kakkar, alright?
What's his problem with my Chitti,
huh Vicky?
- What's his issue with her?
- It's not just Chitti,
he's got issues with all the modern girls
whose thoughts are liberal.
Hmm.
Most of the girls
who went missing from our town
were quite modern, you know.
Correct.
Yeah.
Pooja, Poonam, Radhika.
They had a different way of thinking.
- Kavita was a taekwondo champion, right?
- Yes.
Nikki used to go to work.
Yeah.
And Vidhi had a love marriage
with a guy from another caste.
- Intercaste marriage, huh?
- Yes.
- Oh.
- Chitti was like them too,
she had so many dreams.
Not "had", she still HAS dreams.
Remember, he said he saw them alive?
They're bald, but they're alive.
- Yes, Brother.
- Thank God.
If I close my eyes,
I'll see them again,
but I won't do that.
Perfect.
Alright, then from today,
you're our Sanjay for that hellish place.
Sanjay Dutt, you mean?
- Hey, Sanju!
- Sanju!
Were you really trying for the IAS, huh?
I've been at it for two years.
That's another issue, I guess,
that I can't seem to clear it.
No, I mean the Sanjay
from the Mahabharata,
the one who helped
Dhritarashtra see the war
through his divine vision!
Nah, I don't want to show
anyone any divine vision.
I just want to sleep.
Please, help me out.
This is no time to sleep, Jana.
It's time to wake up, got it?
And Brother Rudra,
it's time to wake everyone up as well.
When we used to write "O Stree,
come tomorrow" on the wall,
she would never show up.
Should we try "O Purush,
come tomorrow" now?
Sister, Stree read it
because she's a woman.
Do men ever read instructions?
They pee exactly
where it's explicitly written not to pee.
But this man is after
the modern girls, right?
And we're just very simple people.
Do you watch TV?
- Yes.
- Listen to music?
- Are you on social media?
- Yeah.
- Do you use WhatsApp?
- Post your pics online?
- Yes.
Well, you're all on the list then.
But why's he even here, huh?
To pay his taxes.
- What?
- Yes.
He is a departed ancestor of Chanderi.
He is back to reestablish his reign.
Oh, I see.
We call upon the Ancestor of Chanderi!
We call upon the powerful Headless!
We are here to pay homage to you.
Please come accept the water
we offer you
and forgive us.
And free this town from your wrath.
Brother Vicky,
its neckline's a bit too low, fix it up.
How's this?
Nah, higher.
Better?
Will do.
- Hey! This is a limit.
- We can fight about it later.
- What's up, Sushma?
- The back's too deep,
add some extra cloth there,
in the sleeves and waist.
But I made this Kareena Kapoor
style blouse just for you!
Like the one from "Bole Chudiyan".
Fashion's not more important than my life.
Cover up all the exposed areas quickly.
Like how Nirupa Roy wears them?
Same to same.
And I also have...
Yes--
Sister?
Come with me.
Greetings, Sister.
To hell with your greetings.
Get up.
I don't do this stuff.
I have never done "friendship".
Who'd do "friendship" with you anyway?
- Get up.
- I'm coming, I'm coming.
- Come with me without a fuss.
- Sister!
- Get him on the scooter.
- Where? Huh?
- Get him on the scooter, quick!
- On this.
I feel sandwiched. Can I drive it?
Look at him, having a blast.
Let him have his fun.
When else is he going to get
to have a good time, huh?
Why are you dragging me into
these sketchy-looking ruins?
Just come with me,
I'll explain everything.
Wait a second, is this where you live?
Let's talk outside, Sister. Please...
- Come on.
- Sister--
Aunt Suneeta?
Sister-in-law Anju? Neelam?
What's going on?
Why did you call me here?
Because you messed up our lives.
Who? Me?
- Yes.
- Yes, you.
What did I do?
I was just altering some clothes.
Why did you have to make
Stree leave Chanderi?
Oh, that!
Well,
Ms. Stree would've kidnapped everyone,
- so I was trying to save everyone's life.
- Not everyone,
just the men.
- Yeah.
All the men were like tamed cats,
and we women had so much freedom.
Then you made Stree leave
and that headless jerk took her place.
Sorry, but I didn't know
he'd show up after Stree left.
It's his own deal,
I can't do anything about it.
Look, you have to fight
that headless monster
and get our freedom back.
- Yeah, you're right.
- You'll have to do it.
- Who? Me?
- Yes, you.
You have to get rid
of that monster for us.
Have you been hitting the weed or what?
- Huh?
- Hey!
Have you even seen him?
You can't even see him
unless you crane your neck.
You know how massive he is?
How huge?
Do you have any idea how huge he is?
Imagine Aamir Khan standing
on top of Mr. Bachchan,
he'd only reach that monster's waist.
- Oh God.
- Oh no.
And he's got no head attached.
He just holds it in his hand.
And it keeps yelling all day.
How am I supposed to fight him
with this weak body of mine?
He'll crush me like a bug and eat me.
Then you'll be looking for Vicky forever.
Just get someone else
to do the alterations.
Vicky, my son,
just like you made Stree leave,
you have to get rid
of this headless monster too.
Aunty...
We're counting on you.
- Please, don't beg.
- Only you can save us from him, son.
- Yes, Brother Vicky.
- Yes.
Long live Brother Vicky!
Long live the protector of Chanderi!
- Long live Brother Vicky!
- Hey! No!
Long live Brother Vicky!
Long live the protector of Chanderi!
I think the women are right on this one,
Vicky.
It's time for you to do or die.
You want me dead or what?
Vicky,
you should think about fighting
that monster instead of running away.
Huh?
Fight him?
Come on, how can I fight him?
Even you couldn't fight him
with that braid thing.
You forget what Mr. Shastri said?
In his eyes, love shines.
Right.
A true artist defined.
Vicky,
you're the protector of this town.
Bingo! She's right.
Every superhero has special powers.
Like Arjuna never missed his mark.
Like Bheem had his insane strength.
Your strength is in your eyes,
the love in them.
Trust yourself.
If you could stop Stree,
you can beat this headless monster as well.
Look him in the eyes
and stab him
with this dagger right in the chest.
- That's it?
- That's it.
No way, no way!
How can I beat him?
What's wrong with these women?
Who do they think I am?
I'm just a tailor, not some superhero.
I've seen him.
- I can't do it.
- You can do it.
- No way, no way.
- You can do it, Vicky. You can.
She's right.
Only you can save Chanderi, Vicky.
- But...
- Yes.
You know,
I haven't slept well
since Chitti disappeared.
You can do it.
Nah.
Vicky...
But how do we get this headless
monster to show up?
Well, he was a womanizer.
He likes booze and dance shows.
So, we'll organize a dance show.
But the problem is,
who would agree to dance there?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's a huge issue.
No local girl would dare dance there.
They are all terrified.
I know a dancer.
She's not from Chanderi, an outsider.
Not her. Someone else.
- Who?
- But...
why would an outsider
risk her life for us?
Not for you.
Then?
For me.
- For you?!
- "Love is crazy and wonderful at the same time."
- Stop, stop, stop.
Perfect.
Come with me. Don't be scared.
Who's this dancer
that Brother Rudra knows, huh?
I would like to meet your boss.
And who do we have here?
He doesn't like to brag about himself.
Tell my flame her moth seeks her.
Wait here.
- Brother Rudra?
- Hmm?
You dyed your beard, I see.
And you put on some fancy
'David-On' perfume too.
Nice.
"The flame tells the moth,"
"Go away, please,"
"You'll burn like me,"
"Don't come here, please."
He doesn't listen for he desires to burn.
Aw, you haven't changed a bit,
my innocent prince.
The same goes for you,
my beauty queen.
What have you been up to, Rudra?
Well, you loved books
so I decided
to surround myself with books.
So, what are you now a junk collector?
Books and emotions
both have the same fate
for those who don't know
their true worth consider it junk.
Jana? Bittu?
Go.
- Where?
To jump into the well
and drown in shame.
Let's go.
I am here to ask for a favor, Shama.
You can ask for my life.
I want you to do a dance performance
in Chanderi, please.
So, you are indeed here
to ask for my life.
You have my word, Shama,
no harm will come to you.
Ms. Shama, please?
Do this for me?
Fine.
Gone are the days when the moth
would die for the flame,
This flame will put her life at risk
for the moth today and change the game.
- Amazing.
- Well said.
Go tell everyone in Chanderi.
Won't you come along?
No, I'll come with her.
- This is not right, Brother Rudra.
- Okay, perfect.
- Let's go.
- But...
Thank you.
"Just marvel from afar,
for you can't touch this star."
"For you can't touch this star."
She has come for real.
My Shama.
"Give your arms a rest, my love."
"Behold this beauty with your
eyes tonight requests your dove."
"Take my life if you so desire,
my darling."
"For my ruin is certain tonight,
my sweetheart."
"Take my life if you so desire,
my darling."
"For my ruin is certain tonight,
my sweetheart."
Vicky, where is she?
She must be stuck somewhere,
that poor thing.
Damn it.
"My darling,
try to see the delicacy of the scene."
"You cannot purchase
a lady's consent I mean."
"Don't feel so proud,"
"My love,"
See if you can figure out
if that headless monster is around.
I'm not sure if I can manage that,
to be honest.
- Give it a try, at least give it a shot.
- Alright, I'll give it a go.
"--eyes tonight requests your dove."
Brother Rudra,
he's somewhere nearby. He's close by.
"Take my life if you so desire,
my darling."
Vicky!
"For my ruin is certain tonight,
my sweetheart."
"Take my life if you so desire,
my darling."
"For my ruin is--"
What happened?
Why's the power out?
Vicky! Bittu!
Brother Rudra! What do we do?
Quick, hide Ms. Shama!
Okay.
Surround her. Surround her.
Surround her, hurry!
Hey!
- He's here. He's here.
- Hide.
Bittu?
Yeah?
Make sure Ms. Shama stays protected,
alright?
Okay.
Be careful, Vicky.
Vicky...
Vicky's going over there.
He's walking towards him.
He'll be fine.
He's the protector of this town.
Vicky, my friend...
Daddy...
'Look him in the eyes'
'and stab him
with this dagger right in the chest.'
Where are you?
We'll have to do something,
Brother Rudra.
There's nothing we can do.
Whatever needs to be done,
Vicky will take care of it.
Vicky...
Where...
where's your head?
You were supposed to look into my eyes.
You should leave.
I'll kill you.
You need to leave.
I'll really kill you.
I'm the protector of Chanderi.
You...
Brother Rudra, Vicky...!
Brother Rudra, let me go!
No, no, no!
Help!
Momma!
Let me go.
I have no reason to live anymore.
He took Shama away.
Don't say that, Brother Rudra.
Oh God!
No!
Brother Rudra!
- Go.
- Are you okay?
Vicky...?
Get up, get up.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
I...I don't know.
I was about to stab him
with the dagger...
Okay.
Then he brought his head forward
and everything got foggy.
I know, I saw.
Bittu? Where's Bittu?
- Bittu!
Why aren't you answering our calls?
What are you doing here?
I've had a realization
and my eyes have been opened.
No, your eyes have changed.
You should change too.
Or else...
Or else what?
What will you do?
Or you'll get beaten up
just like this drum.
That headless monster seems
to have them under his control.
Yes.
No, your eyes seem to be fine.
He has divine powers.
Opposing him
is like trying to throw sand over the sun.
That poor guy lost his head.
He lost his head.
Yet he's protecting our culture.
The headless man is here!
All the females should stay home.
The headless man can show up
anywhere anytime.
All the females should stay home.
The headless man can show up
anywhere anytime.
Vicky...
You?
Are you okay?
Where have you been all this time?
Where did you disappear
to at the last moment?
That monster has like over
a hundred men acting just like him.
And he took Ms. Shama with him too.
Now you show up here.
Where were you?
Why didn't you come there?
I... I was trying to get
to where that headless monster came from.
Why?
I thought I'd try and free
all the girls while he was busy here.
But I couldn't get in there.
You are lying, aren't you?
Trust me.
How do I trust you?
I really don't know much about you.
I don't even know your name
or where you live.
You just come and go as you please.
I have no idea about your family
or what they do.
Are you a mountain person
or a beach person?
Vegetarian or non-vegetarian?
What's your past?
Why did you take Stree's braid?
Why did you disappear from the bus?
I'm clueless about all of it.
But you seem to know everything about me.
You know I'm Vicky, I live with my dad,
I don't have a mom,
I'm a ladies tailor and I studied home science.
I love the mountains and I love you--
I am a crazy fool.
Look, Vicky,
I want to tell you everything about myself.
I've tried many times but couldn't.
Now is your chance, so tell me.
There's no better time than right now.
I'm all ears.
You won't be able to hear it.
Whatever relationship we have,
it'll end the day I tell you the truth.
Relationship?
What relationship do we even have, anyway?
It's like a firefly and light,
a flower and dew,
a deer and musk -
a bond between souls.
It's beyond your understanding.
It's beyond time itself.
Woah, beyond time?
Vicky...
Vicky!
- What is it?
- Come down, quick!
Coming!
- I'll die. I'll die.
- What are you doing?
- Take care of yourself...
- What is it? What's wrong?
- What happened?
- Look at his condition.
You...
You decided to show up today?
- Where have you been, Sister?
- Jana...
- Do you know what happened yesterday?
We had a heart-to-heart chat.
It's not her fault.
Brother Rudra, what's wrong?
Are you having a stroke?
- No... no.
- Are you feeling okay?
- What happened?
- I'm disturbed,
really disturbed.
There's like a volcano
of emotions inside me.
I feel so guilty and ashamed.
Shama...
No.
I had promised her
no harm would come to her.
- And I'll keep that promise.
- Okay.
Even if the moth has
to sacrifice himself today,
he will reignite the flame.
- Don't say that.
- Don't get all dramatic on us, Brother Rudra.
Show him what you came here for.
What? I had come to show him my pain.
Did you forget about that document?
He's impossible.
- What is this?
- This...
I got a link that might help us solve
the headless monster's puzzle.
Have a look at this.
The person who sent the warning
knew the monster would
show up after Stree left.
He might have more information
on that headless monster.
He might also know
how to get to where the monster lives.
Well, whatever you need to find out,
you better hurry.
Otherwise, this monster's going
to set Chanderi back 200 years.
Brother Rudra, I asked you
to find out who sent that letter.
I couldn't find that out,
but I found out where it was from.
Look at this stamp.
- Give them the...
- Here.
- Men--
- Mental Asylum, Bhopal.
Give me your hair!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
Baldy is pulling my hair!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Give me your hair!
Chanderi?
Is anyone from Chanderi out here?
No, nothing.
Protect your hair.
Anyone?
Is anyone from Chanderi out here?
He is coming.
- He is coming?
- He is coming.
Stand up, show respect and be alert.
King of kings,
Emperor of emperors,
The defender and decider of the faith,
King of India the Great,
Get locked up before it's too late,
Husband to Mumtaz Mahal,
Builder of the Taj Mahal,
For now and forever
Shah Jahan is blessing us
with his presence!
Let's get started.
Hey!
He's from Udaybhan's family.
Look at him.
Minister!
Your Highness.
What's the update
on Taj Mahal's construction?
There's a shortage of marbles,
Your Highness.
You need to hurry.
My wife's soul will keep "roaming"
till we don't finish its construction.
Astrologer,
tell me - whose body does
my wife's soul possess these days?
In him, Your Highness.
- What are you doing, Brother Rudra?
- Her soul is in him.
- Vicky?
- Yes, it's in him.
Come on.
No, it's not.
It's not.
What is he looking at?
Mumtaz,
couldn't you find anyone better
than this mushroom of a person?
What's wrong with your taste?
Well, I had COVID, you know.
Good Lord!
Come here, I'll give you the vaccine!
- What will you give me?
- Go.
- Go, go, go.
- Go on.
Come here.
Not there, sit on my lap.
That's where you'll get it.
- He's going to give me a vaccine.
- Just take it, man.
How are you, my Momo?
Momo?
I guess that's Mumtaz's pet name.
Tell me,
where did you go leaving me all alone?
Chanderi.
She went to Chanderi,
I mean, I went to Chanderi.
That place is in big trouble.
The headless monster
has started causing havoc then?
You knew about it?
Dismissed!
Leave.
Please leave.
Everyone, please leave.
Yes.
Let's go.
Where are you going, Momo?
You stay here.
Don't you dare!
Don't you dare call me Momo
or kiss me anywhere!
You wretched woman!
Calm down, Your Highness.
Calm down.
I'm just saying
the Iss Mahal will cost a fortune.
Why not build a public toilet instead?
A public toilet made of marble?
That's just weird.
People will come and pee
all over our symbol of love.
Ugh, gross.
Do you love me, my dear?
Yes, I do.
Then tell me,
what do you know
about that headless monster?
That headless monster
is an ancestor of mine.
I have his foul blood in my veins.
That's why you tore those pages
from the Chanderi Puran.
But I sent them back with a warning.
- He will come back.
- Yes.
He will come back.
But you didn't tell us
how to deal with this monster
when he comes back.
You just left us to fend for ourselves
with just a warning.
Your Highness,
you gave us the warning,
didn't you? So tell us,
how can we defeat this headless monster.
My Queen, I would've gone myself,
to defeat him but
I keep slipping off elephants these days
because of balancing issues.
Listen,
that monster has kidnapped girls
from our town,
including Chitti and our Shama.
Hey... She's mine.
- My Shama.
- Yeah, yeah, his Shama.
He kidnapped her right
in front of everyone.
He's even messed with the minds
of every single man in Chanderi.
They've all gone completely bonkers.
If you know anything that can help us,
please tell us.
Otherwise, our whole town
of Chanderi is doomed.
Please, my darling.
You have to help us,
for the sake of our love!
In a realm that dwells
in the shadows of the town.
He can be dealt with only
in his home ground.
Neither by a human nor an animal,
it can be reached.
Neither by a man nor a woman
it can be breached,
To enter in you have
to be an equal part of each.
But he won't stop nor will his havoc
Until he does not get what he wants -
A sacrifice!
Sacrifice who?
Sacrifice a female.
Sacrifice Stree!
But if Ms. Stree's not there,
then who's he going sacrifice?
He's got a whole bunch
of females with him -
He's got my Shama, Chitti,
and other females too.
- Oh shit!
- Oh no!
Today's the last day
of the Mahapooja festivities.
If we don't do something today,
he's going sacrifice all those women.
We have to find a way to get into
his house, no matter what it takes.
So what do we know about
this headless monster?
That it doesn't have a head.
Nice work.
Let's make him an IAS officer right away!
- Thank you, Brother Rudra.
- Shut up.
What a useless person.
He can influence people.
He's changed everyone's minds.
He has influenced them.
What do you mean?
So this headless monster
is basically an influencer.
He wants to grow his followers.
His powers are in his body,
but it's controlled by the head.
So if we separate the head from the body,
the head will be left helpless.
Then we can quietly go
and chop it off.
No, not we, Brother, you have to do it.
You're the protector of this town.
Yes, right.
But that's only possible if we reach
the hellish place where he lives.
And nobody can go there.
Neither humans nor animals.
Hey, I've got another idea!
Plan B.
We haven't even made Plan A yet
and you're already onto Plan B?
No, Vicky, what I meant was...
- Stop.
- Stop it.
Remember what he said.
Neither by a man nor a woman
can it be breached,
To enter, you have to have
equal parts of each.
Neither by a man nor a woman
can it be breached,
To enter,
you have to have equal parts of each.
Hey...
You have to have equal parts of each.
Let's send Jana then.
What do you mean, Vicky?
Are you saying I'm half man
and half woman?
- Is that what you're trying to say?
- No, no, no,
I've seen Jana when he was a kid.
What did you see?
What did you see, Brother Rudra?
I have a lot of respect for you.
That's no way to talk to me.
I came all the way
from Delhi just for you guys.
I even died for three minutes.
That loafer kept calling me Momo,
but you didn't stop him.
- Jana!
- Sister, did you hear what he's saying?
What?
You still have Stree's
lingering effect in you.
So you have a small
Feminine part inside you. That's why...
You're saying I have female
parts inside me!
Why don't you just say
you want me to die?!
SILENCE!
Half man, half woman,
I think he was talking
about Ardhanarishvara.
I see.
Oh, Ardhanarishvara,
the union of Lord Shiva and Shakti.
Neither a female nor a male can break
the reign of the headless monster.
For that, a man and a woman
will have to become one.
But how?
Leave that to me.
You just think about cutting off his head.
In one strike.
One strike?
May I have your kind attention, please!
The upcoming Mahapooja's veneration
will be conducted solely by men.
Women are kindly requested
to remain at home for this event.
Perfect.
Now you look like a real prince indeed.
Vicky?
Where are you all going,
leaving me by myself?
You came here to save those girls,
didn't you?
- You won't be able to save them.
- Hey...
It's just not possible.
- Go on.
- Go.
Watch your step.
Hey Bittu...
- Cut it out, Bittu.
- Hey!
- No.
- Walk properly.
Why did we even bring him along?
Remember we had brought you
along even when you were growling?
- Yeah.
- He's our friend.
And anyway,
we need one of his men with us.
Why is that?
What if we need to give
and take something?
- Yes.
- Give and take what?
And Jana,
if we take too long to get back then...
Then what? Kill him?
No, no, no!
Just handle it as you see fit.
- Okay, fine.
- You'll die! You'll die!
Brother Rudra, make him on the bed.
Just make him sit there.
You've lost all your manners, Bittu.
- What are you going to do, huh?
- Quiet.
Don't worry about him, Vicky.
Brother, when you go in,
no matter what happens,
don't be scared.
I've got your back.
And I've got a Plan B.
Spell out B for me, will you?
B?
- Yeah, B...
- B...
- Vicky!
- Yeah?
- We need to hurry.
- Right.
I'm ready. I'm ready.
Brother Rudra...
- Here.
- Yes.
Go and be victorious.
Be the force with you.
Just let Shama know
I came here with you.
- Yeah, I'll let her know. I'll let her know.
- Vicky...
Vicky...
- Stop.
- Okay, now tell me what we need to do.
We have to go through this wall.
- This wall?
- Hmm.
But we didn't bring a drill with us.
- So how are we going get through it?
- We'll manage.
We'll have to become one
to cross that wall.
- Huh?
- Yes.
Here? In front of everyone?
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay, okay, okay.
What does she mean by "become one"?
Well...
I got it. I got it.
Can you guys...
Come here, Vicky.
Yes, I'm ready.
Hey, you can't watch.
I'm ready.
Get closer.
Even closer.
Even closer?
Closer.
She possessed him!
She has taken over my brother's body!
Mystical powers! Mystical powers!
She has taken over Vicky's body!
She is taking my brother away,
Brother Rudra!
She is taking my brother through
the wall, Brother Rudra!
- Mystical powers!
- Vicky!
Brother Rudra?
Where did he go, Brother Rudra?
She has mystical powers.
Did you break your nose?
Hello?
Are you really inside me?
This is the first time
I've had such close contact with someone.
What were you doing?
I was just...
Nothing.
Sorry.
But how did you even
pull off this miracle?
You entered my body,
then we crossed the wall,
and now you stepped out.
Shh, Vicky.
Don't worry, I'm here with you.
It's so dark in here.
Let's wait right here. He'll come.
Let's go.
Oh, damn! What is this place?
I'm sure no one in the Chanderi Tourist Department
knows about this place.
It could really boost tourism
in Chanderi--
Did you see that?
It's... molten lava.
Over there.
Aren't those the missing girls
from Chanderi?
Go...
and save those women.
Okay.
Come on, let's go save them.
Not me.
Just you.
And why not you?
Vicky, the headless monster
doesn't want to sacrifice those girls.
He wants to sacrifice me.
What?
He wants to sacrifice you?
No,
that headless monster wants
Ms. Stree's sacrifice, not yours.
For him, I'm Stree,
because I have her braid.
Then let's chop that braid off
and give it to him.
Let's deal with this headless
monster first, otherwise.
Like hell, he wants to sacrifice you!
Hey, headless monster!
No one can do anything.
He's very powerful.
This is the only way to stop him.
This is why I came here.
And your purpose
is much greater than this.
You still don't know the powers you have.
I don't want any powers.
I WANT YOU!
I'm not going to leave you.
I won't let you sacrifice yourself.
I'm not going anywhere.
Vicky,
you're a protector.
Don't be so selfish when it comes to love.
- Go. We don't have much time.
- Yes, I am selfish.
I'm selfish.
I'm not going to let you go.
I... I'm going to sit right here.
Let him come, I'll handle him.
I won't let you sacrifice yourself.
I'm not leaving.
I'm not going anywhere.
Vicky, please?
For my sake?
This is cheating.
She is going to sacrifice herself.
- Who?!
- The one who says Vicky please.
She left my brother.
VICKY!
No, I'm alright. I'm alright!
I'm alright!
Be careful.
My vision's all blurry from the tears.
I'm okay...
Daddy...
WATCH OUT, VICKY!
- What happened?!
- He made it. He's safe.
What happened?
He was about to fall into the lava,
but he got through it.
Let's go.
Let's go, hurry up.
Ms. Shama?
Hey, Ms. Shama?
Ms. Shama, it's me, Vicky.
Remember,
I danced with you the other day?
"Behold this beauty
with your eyes tonight, my dove."
Is Shama alright?
Yeah, she's fine.
She's just a little bald, that's it.
She's not hurt, is she?
Brother Rudra,
you don't want me to see anything else?
Do you really just want me
to keep looking at Shama?
- No, no, look at everything happening out there.
- Okay.
Chitti!
Chitti, it's me, Vicky.
Come on, let's go.
Soft Chitti, warm Chitti,
little ball of fur.
Happy Chitti, something Chitti,
Burr, burr, burr...
Statue over!
Hey! What's going on?
Hey, these girls--
You freaky head!
We did it! We won!
Just wait and watch,
he is going to destroy them.
- Shut it.
- Shut up.
You enemy.
You okay?
- Okay?
- Yes.
Okay?
You want me to give you mouth-to-mouth?
Why did you come here?
No point sacrificing yourself.
Your Bluetooth's hooked up to those girls.
They would have died too
if you'd done that.
That's why I chopped
that head off in one go.
You should've seen it!
You missed it.
What?
Huh?!
I may be wearing a skirt,
but I'm no girl, you creepy head!
Glory to the Goddess!
YES!!!
Oh no, Brother Rudra!
The heads just keep multiplying
when you chop them off.
Keep that braid swirling.
Keep it swirling.
Looks like the braid
and dagger don't work on them.
Huh? So what do we do now?
Look over there.
A sword?
Who left a sword here?
Hey!
Looks like it's the one Stree used
to behead him.
Then maybe that's what will kill him.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Go get it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey freaky head!
If you want to live,
let the girl go.
Vicky, they're already dead!
Yeah, I mean let the girl go!
If you think you're man enough,
come fight me.
Huh?
Damn it!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on out or else!
Shame on you, man!
Time out! Time out! I'm taking it out.
Give me a minute, give me a minute.
From deep down, Vicky.
What?
Put your whole heart
into trying to pull it out!
"From the bottom of your heart,
I want you to come on out."
Don't sing the song! Put your heart into
it and try to get it out!
I tried! I just can't get it out!
Wait a second.
Daddy! Daddy!
I was just joking when I challenged you!
I was just kidding!
VICKY!
We have to do something or he'll kill them!
Please, Brother Rudra!
I told you I have a Plan B!
Very good, Bhasky! Very good!
Are you okay?
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Did... did you see that?
Where the heck did
that shape-shifting dog come from?
He's not a shape-shifting dog,
he's a wolf.
A wolf?!
MOTHER!!!!
- What's happening?!
- It's the epic battle, Brother Rudra!
THE EPIC BATTLE!
We're going to win!
We will win!
Yes!
No, don't.
If the Stree chapter ends,
so does the world.
No.
It's not over till it's over, Vicky.
You're the only one
who can pull that sword out.
- Just you.
- No.
No, I can't do it.
You have to recognize your powers.
Recognize the honesty
and simplicity in your heart.
That's your power.
Put your heart into trying
to pull it out, Vicky!
Go, give it a shot.
GO!
Hey!
Ms. Stree!!!
We won!
We did it! She took him down!
She slayed him!
It's me, Vicky.
Go, Mother.
Bittu!
Oh, Bittu is fine!
You are back to your usual self, Bittu!
Thanks to you, Bittu is back!
You know, I jumped
- and chopped his head off in one go.
- Yes, we saw that.
- And then, Ms. Stree grabbed him by his head
- Yes.
and tossed him into the lava,
just like that.
We were all there watching it happen.
Tell me something,
when will Shama be back from there?
And what about Chitti? Where's Chitti?
Aw, my dear lover boys...
Look, there they come -
Shama, Chitti, and all the other women.
"Through your deeds,
righteousness is shown,"
"With discipline, courage is known,"
"In success or failure, stay the same,
with a balanced heart and steady aim."
Yes,
I'm Stree's daughter.
But she wanted to kill you.
She doesn't recognize me
in this form.
In her eyes,
her daughter is still the little girl
who was crying as she was killed.
When she was killed?
But that was like forever ago.
It's part of our scriptures.
Vicky...
Vicky, all I ever wanted was to help
my mother's soul find salvation.
And you were the only one
who could make that happen.
That's why I reached out to you
and befriended you.
From helping Stree find salvation
to slaying that headless monster -
it all happened because of you.
Because of me?
I don't get it.
You...
Why didn't you tell me
about all this earlier?
How could I have, Vicky?
How could I tell you that I...?
That you...?
That I am what everyone thinks I am.
What do you mean?
An illusion,
a shadow.
You...
You are a ghost?
But aren't you way too pretty
to be a ghost?
And your feet too...
So everything we had was all just a lie?
No, it wasn't a lie.
It's a relationship,
that will always remain.
It's a bond
that one soul shares with another.
Soul...
Please, don't leave.
I'll adjust to the fact
that you're a ghost.
Dad will understand too.
He...
Please, don't go.
I have to go.
I don't even know your name.
Huh?
Seriously?
Yes.
Oh, it's nice.
We'll cross paths again, Vicky.
Remember,
we are already one.
I am wherever you are.
Take care.
And make sure to eat on time...
whatever it is you guys eat.
Huh?
Oh shit!
She's gone!
Hey...
Vicky...
Sorry, we're late.
Sorry, Brother. Really sorry.
Where is she?
- She's gone.
- Huh?
Oh no, I didn't even get to say goodbye.
Gone again?
Did you at least ask
for her name this time?
Yes.
So what did she say it was?
- What?
- He's trying to remember.
Tell us, Vicky. Come on, spill it.
What happened, Vicky?
He knows but he's not telling us.
Bhasky!
Janardhan!
Where are you?
JD!
- Where were you?
- Where were you hiding?
Here, try these on.
Ugh, gross.
Whose raggedy clothes did you steal?
These are mine.
You'll look good in them.
You wear Munni's underwear?!
You pervert!
And what the heck was that, man?
How did that creature
even end up in Chanderi?
It's a long story,
I'll tell you later.
Let's go home now.
I'll pack and then
we'll hit the road to Delhi.
- Brother, you rock my clothes.
- You can't go to Delhi.
Why not?
It's dangerous out there.
Why, because of the pollution?
Something much worse.
He sinks his fangs into this vein
and sucks the blood out.
Look JD, I'm a wolf,
I can handle myself in any situation.
But if he gets you...
He'll slurp up my blood like a soda.
Hundred percent.
You are right.
You should go to Delhi
and give me a buzz if you need anything.
I need you.
I really need you for something.
I'm always there for you, bro. Always.
You know that chick with the big eyes
and the long braid?
Set me up with her.
Hey, my friend already has
a thing with her.
The one in the frock?
I bet she would ditch him for me.
Bhasky, you're a wolf,
but don't act like a creepy animal.
Okay, what about just an intro?
She is powerful, and so am I.
Together, we'd be a power couple.
Blegh! Let me go, you rascal.
You've changed, Bhasky.
At least tell me where she lives,
what she's into,
- what she eats, and what she's looking for.
- Disgusting.
Let me at least make a move.
Your buddy won't be able to handle her.
Come on man, you're a wolf!
- Stop behaving like a dirty rabbit!
- Trust me, he won't be able to handle her.
- I want her! I really want her!
- She is not going to come back.
She was unfaithful.
She was an illusion.
"You made a promise but it was a lie,"
"I waited all night in the fields
but you never came by."
"With no blanket to warm me
in the middle of the night,"
"You said you'd be there
but you never came by."
"I waited all night in the fields
"All dressed up
I was ready to leave that day,"
"But my mother glared and made me stay."
"She questioned,
"Where are you going, you little brat?"
"Maidens don't roam fields
and that's a fact!"
"She said boys who ask girls to meet
in the fields,"
"They never marry those girls
and their love never seals."
"I spent the night in the fields waiting,
but you never came by,"
"My youth is fading fast while
waiting here for you,"
No, my dear, in love.
Yes.
"My youth is fading fast while
waiting here for you,"
"I never wooed another girl
for I thought I had you."
You've said it three times already,
now move on.
"I spent the night in the fields waiting
but you never came by."
"You said you'd be there
"I spent the night in the fields waiting
but you never came by."