So, you wanna be a sugar baby.
And why not?
Since the dawn of time,
older men have
wanted younger women.
It's only natural
that we would wanna
take advantage of that, right?
The key is to always
leave them wanting more.
And guess what?
They always want more.
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it.
You're gonna have
to sleep with some guys
who aren't your usual type.
But I mean, let's be honest,
we've all done a lot worse
for a lot less.
I got you that bag
you asked for.
As long as the perks are good
and you can stomach it,
who cares?
Secure the bag.
And do not be fooled
by social media.
I might make it look easy,
but it's a lot of hard work.
You're gonna have
to kiss a lot of frogs.
So, why do it?
Because of him.
The whale.
That one client
who can actually afford
to make all
of your dreams a reality.
The whale's one true kink
is to spoil.
And we all just wanna
be spoiled, don't we?
So for just $9.99,
I can teach you how to come up
with the perfect arrangement.
It'll all be included
in my online class
called "How to Sugar."
And you can visit the link in
my bio for more information.
And of course, don't forget to
follow me on FanZen @MissMarie.
I'm always looking to collab.
Bitch,
you would not believe my day.
I got lectured by
a 12-year-old I was tutoring
about the realities
of making it in Hollywood.
Apparently, I don't have it.
Then, their dad had the nerve
to explain to me
that if I keep wasting my money
on expensive smoothies,
I'll never own a home.
It's like, "Sir, maybe I buy
$17 smoothies to dull the pain
because I know I'll never be
able to afford real estate."
- Is that--
- Yes.
I didn't know
Chanel did Afterpay.
It was a gift from a daddy.
Well, a former daddy.
By the way, Chanel retains
its value as well as Hermès.
You could make bank off of this.
Sometimes I forget that
you grew up around all this.
Well, growing up rich
and being rich
are two very different things.
I think my mom is the only woman
who left her marriage
with less than she went in with.
My dad is such a bastard.
Speaking of which,
it's almost
my biannual pilgrimage
to beg him
to keep supporting me.
Well, all else fails,
you can always resort
to selling pics
of your feet on the internet.
Oh, come on.
Are we not better
than feet pics?
No one is better than feet pics.
I'm telling you,
content is the new frontier.
I'm actually looking to get
some girl-on-girl collabs
going for my FanZen page.
I've heard the tips are insane.
Like what I would make
in a month of sugaring,
I can make in just a few hours.
Well, I wish you
the very best of luck with that.
If you'll excuse me,
I need to get back
to trapping all of my Sims
in an underground bunker.
-Sounds urgent.
-Right.
-You got it?
-Yeah.
-Ooh.
-Okay.
So many awesome pics
to work with.
Hopefully our make-out vids
does well on your page.
They do really well on mine.
Do you mind if I AirDrop our
content to myself real quick?
Yeah, go for it.
-Oh.
-Oh, you can ignore those.
You sure?
Someone named Jeff
seems super thirsty.
You don't have a boyfriend,
do you?
God, no. It's just
a potential sugar daddy.
Are you on Seeking Ties?
Yeah, been there
and done that.
You know, sugaring
kind of has a shelf life.
Once I turned 27, I swear,
those men
could smell 30 approaching.
How old are you, 27?
Um, yeah, just about.
Yeah, but I've been 27
for a few years now.
You know, you don't need men
to make bank, right?
I like sugaring.
It comes easy to me
and I've always been good at it.
I hate men. Like, a lot.
So full-service sex work
is pretty much a no-go
for me at this point.
And for what?
A pair of Louis Vuittons?
A designer bag
they gave their wife
and hope
she doesn't notice it's gone?
No, thanks.
You see these earrings? Fake.
You know what's real?
My 401k.
Everything I make
goes towards my future.
You wanna make money,
like, real money,
you start taking
your online profiles seriously.
-Here, let me see your page.
-Okay.
Oh.
Well, MissMarie,
it's no wonder you hate FanZen.
You're doing everything wrong.
Fuck. Okay.
Okay, you're posting locked
content to the home screen
instead of DMing it
directly to your fans.
The home page is
strictly designed to tease.
The DMs are
for the naughty shit.
The fans wanna think
that you're getting naked
for them and them only.
Also, your spelling and grammar
is too on point.
You have to spell
shit wrong on purpose.
The dumber and drunker
they think you are,
the more likely they are
to buy your content.
Wow, that's so dark.
-I didn't realize how much
strategy goes into this.
-Mm-hmm.
It's like--
They make it seem like
you start posting your nudes
and boom, you're a millionaire.
Yeah, well, there's a reason
they call it "sex work"
and not "sex fun."
God,
I would be so good at this.
Sorry, I'm not
ignoring you guys.
I'm just deep in a Reddit k-hole
about dickdoms
conspiracy theories.
- They don't actually dominate dicks?
-  -Oh,
it's actually
really fucked up.
-Yeah.
-Okay, like,
so there are
these two iconic femdoms
who went, like, mega viral.
Yeah, like,
the kind of viral you dream of
and then, out of the blue,
they break up.
No one knows why.
Becca Leaves is on some
British reality show now.
And wayhorny587 makes
a compelling point
about the other one.
ChloeLamore has gone missing.
All of her socials have been
a ghost town for the past month.
Can't tell if I'm on the wrong
side of the internet
or if you guys are.
Well, it was nice
to meet you, Lucky.
I gotta scoot.
I have acting class.
Look, I don't do
this for everyone,
but you could
and you should be
making way more.
I'm going on
a content trip tomorrow
with some girls from FanZen.
We dress like sluts,
take a bunch of pics,
make a ton of TikToks.
You should totally come.
-What's the catch?
-No catch.
Well, it's only in Big Bear,
not Cancún, like we hoped.
But we're gonna have a masseuse,
a private chef,
and Ozempic shot.
-I'm in.
-Awesome!
Oh, shit, I'm gonna be late
for my Al-Anon meeting.
I'll text you
the address for pickup.
Get excited, bitch.
Welcome to your life
beyond the patriarchy.
- Bye.
We're manifesting a whale.
We're manifesting
that he's gonna be hot.
It's gonna be great.
Yeah. It's gonna be great.
We're making connections.
You have the pussy,
so you have the power.
So, what are you looking for?
Um, well, looking for?
Well, I was married
for a long time.
Now I'm divorced.
I think, you know,
dating's pretty complicated.
I guess what I want is difficult
to explain on a first date.
Let me guess.
You wanna dom the shit
out of a filthy little slut.
Yeah. Okay.
Probably a lot of guys
say that, do they, yeah?
But also, I--you know,
I do want a connection.
I wanna, you know,
get to know you a little bit.
What you like and what you do
with your free time.
You don't get to know me yet.
It's $200 to pass GO.
Okay.
I like to cum.
I like art, okay?
Oh, that's a coincidence.
I like art, too.
-What's your favorite piece?
-It's a Renoir.
It's called Dance in the City.
It's in Paris.
I saw it there a bunch of times.
Do you go to Paris a lot?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, I have to.
I have to go there for work.
H-have you been?
- Let's go to Paris.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'll see you in Paris.
-I like you, Marie.
-I like you, too, Jeff.
I think you are the one
that I've been looking for.
And I don't like to waste time,
so I would like you
to move in with me.
We just met.
We'll do it on
a trial basis, perhaps.
You just come for a week and...
you know,
we'll take it from there.
Name your price.
-$30,000.
-Okay, done.
I'll give you half up front
and then half
at the end of the week.
-What do you say?
-You really think I can't tell
when I'm getting scammed?
I've seen guys
like you before, okay, Jeff?
You're nothing
but a splendid daddy
in a borrowed Armani suit.
Actually, it's Bottega,
and I'm not like
any guy you've ever met.
You'll see.
Have a great day, beautiful.
Hey, babe.
I just wanted to let you know
that I kissed a girl
and I liked it.
You don't want to miss this.
Hi. Who are you?
Ghost.
-This the new girl?
-Hi, babe.
We're so happy you're coming.
Isn't she fab?
Ghost can get your bag.
Uh, I thought
this was a girls' trip.
-I'm Kendall.
-I'm Jess.
It's so nice to meet you.
Um, I guess what I meant,
I didn't know that there were
gonna be men on the trip--
No, these aren't men.
These are just the guys,
you know?
Ghost shoots us, and Harry,
he's actually
our personal chef and masseuse.
I also run
the management company.
Yeah, we're all repped by
the same FanZen agency.
Didn't Lucky
mention that to you?
But they help us so much
for a small fee.
How small?
-40%.
-40%?
Yeah,
but you'll be making so much
money, you won't even notice.
Babe, is she gonna be a problem?
'Cause I don't like problems.
Lucky, I don't even
know these guys.
Marie, who cares?
Just--you met them already.
They're not some
creepy old-ass sugar daddies.
They're just our boyfriends.
Yeah, who you give almost
half the money you earn to.
No, only Lucky's boyfriend
gets a cut.
The rest of the guys
work for us.
Come on,
it's gonna be super fun.
I stuck my neck out for you.
Don't embarrass me, okay?
Let's go.
-Babe, are you good?
-Um, yeah.
My mom just texted me
and my uncle's in the hospital,
so I actually don't think
I can go on the trip.
- Really?
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
Wait, Marie,
what about your bag?
Pleasure to see you again.
You're shaking like a leaf.
What did you get up to tonight?
Here.
All right.
I'm just glad you're here.
So you've really been
thinking about me?
Uh, well, you know,
I've been pretty preoccupied
with work, but...
Yes, I must admit,
I've been thinking
about you constantly.
about you, too.
I missed you.
Does that mean that
you've reconsidered my offer?
Yes, but I have
some requirements.
I've never done
anything like this before.
Name them.
We do a trial run to make sure
that this relationship
is mutually beneficial.
So I'll move in here
for the week
for $30,000, like we discussed.
And then...
And then?
If it works,
I wanna be set up for life.
I won't see any other
daddies besides you,
and I don't wanna have to worry
about anything ever again.
You drive a pretty hard bargain.
Deal.
And what about you?
Now that you have me,
what do you wanna do with me?
I would like it to feel like
a real relationship.
I mean, before we get
to all the other stuff,
I would like to get to know you
a little bit, if that's okay.
Sure.
What kind of music
do you listen to?
I don't really have a favorite.
What about you, Daddy?
Well, I'm a pretty
typical Gen X-er.
I like my grunge.
Favorite artist,
probably Elliott Smith.
-Hmm.
-What about hobbies?
Being fabulous, of course.
Look, I know--
I know what this is,
and I'm not trying
to make it anything else.
But...
could you be real with me?
Well, when I was in high school,
I really loved
working with oil paints.
-Nice. Why'd you quit?
-I don't know.
I guess art school
is, like, stupid expensive,
and it wasn't
gonna be my career, so...
I just kind of felt like,
what's the point?
-I think you should start again.
-Maybe.
You didn't ask
if I was any good.
I don't have to. I know you are.
So when do you want our week
together to actually start?
Um, does now
sound like a good time?
I don't have anything with me.
Come here.
I wanna show you something.
I tried to think of everything
that you would need,
and what you would want.
-Yeah.
-And you can have it all.
I mean, I'm hoping that
you don't wanna leave, but...
So what do you say?
Okay.
Okay?
Just wait here for a second.
I'll be right back.
Yes, bitch!
Use this man
like your own personal ATM!
He offered me 30 grand to
move in with him for the week.
I'm currently staring
at a closet
full of designer clothes
that he bought just for me.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
Uh, when did you meet this guy?
- Like, yesterday?
- Maybe.
What happened to my friend
that loved this for me?
Look, I know
how much finding a guy like this
means to you, Marie,
but do you actually know
anything about this guy?
I don't know
what you want me to say, Eddy.
Unlike you,
I don't have rich parents,
so this is what I need to do.
That's a low fucking blow.
Yeah, I have a safety net,
but everything comes at a cost.
Hey, Marie.
Can you come in here?
- Is that him?
- Yeah.
-He's in the bathroom.
-Is that his fetish?
Spoiling you and then taking
a giant, smelly shit?
I bet he wants
to show it to you.
Oh, there's always a catch
with the handsome and rich.
You know, that's why
I like my men ugly and poor.
-There are no surprises.
-Okay, well, this has been
really, really helpful,
but I have to go.
Hey.
You, uh, seem
a little stressed out,
so I thought it might
be nice for you just
to relax and have a bath.
Are you sure this isn't just
a cheap ploy to see me naked?
Oh, you're gonna be naked?
How does that feel?
Look at me.
Tell me how it feels.
Yes, please.
It feels really, really good.
You like this? Use your words.
Oh, my God.
Please, can I have more?
You are not allowed to cum
until Daddy tells you.
Okay.
Please, daddy, can I cum?
Please. Please, can I cum?
-No. You'll have to beg me.
-Please.
Please. Please.
I'll do anything.
-I'll do anything.
-You'll do anything?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay, cum for daddy.
It's okay. It's fine.
It's just about you.
Mm-hmm.
I guess. Sure.
Depends on, you know.
Yeah.
Say it again?
- Making yourself at home?
- Oh. Oh, fuck.
Oh, no, sorry about that.
Oh, let me see.
I had this happen to me
a few months ago.
You put it in a bowl of rice.
Leave it in there
for a couple of days
and it's like new.
Okay.
Okay, Marie,
you got the run of the place.
Except for one room.
Didn't anyone ever tell you
curiosity killed the cat?
-What's in the room?
-Oh, nothing. Boring stuff.
Birth certificates,
files, taxes.
- It's actually a sex dungeon.
- Okay.
Well, will you show me
if I'm extra good?
I'm counting on it.
Look, I got a couple of calls
I gotta finish up
and then I'm all yours.
Why don't you go for a swim?
It's a gorgeous day.
Perfect timing, beautiful.
- You cook.
- Yeah.
Does that surprise you?
-Just impressed.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Cheers.
It's delicious.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Yes.
What gets you off
about all this?
Well, my therapist says
that I like the control
that comes
with dominating people.
What about you?
Well, I'd actually argue
that the submissive
controls the situation.
We're the ones
who set the boundaries,
express our limits,
we use the safe word.
Hmm.
Have you ever thought about it?
Dominating somebody?
Once or twice in passing,
but I don't think
it's really my thing.
The only times
I've topped were with women.
Do you think that you would like
to be a little more
dominant with me?
Get on your knees.
Quickly.
Did I say you could touch me?
No, ma'am.
Every time you disobey me,
you'll be punished.
Tell me you understand.
I understand.
Good.
Kiss my feet.
Now kiss my ankle.
Did I say you could go up
any higher?
-No.
-You're my little slut now.
-But, uh--
-You're Daddy's good girl,
right?
-Mm-hmm.
-You wanted to hit Daddy,
didn't you?
If Daddy wanted to hit you,
what do you say to me?
-Thank you, Daddy.
-Yeah.
Where were you?
Oh, I just, uh,
had to take a call.
Come on, baby. Sleep.
Hmm.
Marie?
I was gonna surprise you.
You know, I was up
half the night doing this.
-Last night?
-Yeah.
I even had to lug out
an old Persian rug.
Where are you going?
I saw you carrying
the rug, and I thought...
I don't know what I thought.
Oh. Yeah, okay.
Your mind went to a sinister
place because I pay you
to live with me and fuck me,
and you thought, what,
I'm up in the middle
of the night killing people?
I'm really sorry, Jeff,
I--it was stupid.
Um, anyway, here's that.
That's fixed.
I--I'm gonna go get dressed.
Hey, Marie.
Sorry about
how we ended things,
but please call me, okay?
Oh, uh,
and that dickdoms girl
I was telling you about?
She just posted
for the first time in a month.
Anyway, I'm glad your guy
isn't an axe murderer,
but drop me a pin, okay?
ChloeLamore has gone missing.
All of her socials have been
a ghost town
for the past month.
Your mind went to
a sinister place because I pay
you to live with me and fuck me
and you thought, what,
I'm up in the middle
of the night killing people?
Oh, fuck!
Honey, I'm home!
Oh.
Sorry.
That's my fault.
I can buy you a new one.
I kind of thought I'd see you
in that cute little number
that you were in earlier.
Where'd the baby go?
Want me to punish her?
No, my uncle, actually, he fell.
So, he's in the hospital.
I have to go.
Is he gonna be okay?
I don't know,
that's why I have to go.
You're coming back,
though, right?
'Cause I'm really
enjoying our time together.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Sure, I'll--
I'll definitely come back.
I just--I need to go
'cause my mom's a wreck, so...
Okay, I hate seeing you go,
but love watching you leave.
Oh, sorry.
I had this new electronic lock
installed last month
and sometimes I forget.
Okay.
Oh, Marie.
You didn't say "please."
Bread, Jeff, okay?
I'm using the safe word.
Please, bread, I need to go.
I really need to leave
and my uncle needs me.
He's--he just needs me.
You don't have an uncle, Marie.
Your mom's Anita Glover.
She lives at 357 Westburg Lane,
Shingle Springs, California.
She has two sisters:
Marie, who you're named after,
and Jessica.
Neither of them ever married.
And your father
was an only child.
It's--it's not that
I'm mad that you lied to me.
It's that I'm disappointed
you told such a bad lie.
You're smarter than that.
That's why I picked you.
Good girl.
How you feeling?
Like I smashed my head
on some stairs.
Take a seat.
Rest a little bit.
Dinner's almost ready.
Take a seat!
Would you like a drink, baby?
Oh, what am I talking about?
You probably
shouldn't drink anything,
not after you hit your head.
What were you thinking?
What are you gonna do to me?
Do you, um...
like the dress?
I picked it out myself.
What's in that room, Jeff?
I'm gonna bring us out a meal
here, and we're gonna sit down,
and we're gonna eat it together,
and then I'm gonna
run you a bath.
Does that sound good?
Does it?
It would mean a lot to me
if we could just start over.
Have fun.
For the rest of the time
that we have together, okay?
-Hmm.
-Good.
Good girl.
I was gonna ask you--
What are you doing?
Um, I was just gonna have
a sip of your drink,
because you made it
look so good.
Hey.
Did you hit your head
and forget your manners?
Is that it?
Please let me have a sip
of your yummy drink.
Please? Please who?
Please, Daddy.
Hmm.
That's good.
That's very good.
You're getting
the idea now, okay?
Submission, it gets rewarded.
Here.
Hmm.
Oh, boy.
Hey, tell me.
What is it that you think is in
that room?
I don't know,
and it's scaring me.
You're scaring me, Jeff.
Is that where
you're gonna put me?
And lock me away
until I'm nothing?
Is that where you put Chloe?
Chloe?
What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
You are so pretty.
You're alive.
Yeah, what?
No, no, no, what are you doing?
No, uh-uh, uh-uh.
Jeff would not like that.
We have to get out of here.
This could be our only chance.
And I think we could
probably fight him off
if we do it together.
What are you talking about?
I like it in here.
What?
Babe, this place
is like Disney World.
Didn't you see all the clothes?
But we're trapped here.
I know. Isn't it great?
I was going to introduce you
when your week was up,
but now that you've met, maybe
we can have some fun together.
Marie, this is Chloe.
Chloe, Marie.
It's so, so nice
to meet you, babe.
Chloe, you have been locked up
in here for three days.
Let's take a lap
around the house.
Thank you, Daddy.
What do you have
to say for yourself?
- I was--I was just--
- Trying to leave?
Let this be
your official warning.
If you ever disobey me again,
you will be locked in here
as punishment.
Chloe, hey.
You've been such a sweet girl.
Would you like to have dinner
with me tonight?
-Does that sound nice?
-Yes, Daddy.
Marie has been
disobeying orders,
so she's gonna
spend the night here...
all alone.
Marie.
Jeff fell asleep while we were
picking the movie to watch.
Well, I thought
you might be hungry,
so I made you something.
I didn't poison it.
Thanks.
I'm surprised
he didn't chain you to the bed.
You know
the nicer you are to him,
the more freedom he gives you?
Obviously you haven't explored
the true crime genre.
Haven't you heard of
Elizabeth Smart?
I think I blew her brother
in the fifth grade.
Wow. There I was in fifth grade
making friendship bracelets
and learning
how to speak gibberish.
Finally. Something
we have in common.
I know this is gonna
sound crazy, but...
I feel like you're someone
I'm gonna know
for the rest of my life.
Oh, yeah?
And how long do you think
that'll be?
Look, I know
you're scared, but...
we're really gonna
have the best time together.
You're delusional.
Come here.
I wanna tell you something.
Closer.
You're not the first person
to tell me that.
I have to go, but...
do me a favor, explore the room.
I really think you're gonna
like what you find.
See ya.
What the fuck
have I gotten myself into?
Good morning, sunshine.
Okay, so, I begged Jeff
to let us play
hide and seek together outside,
so you could get some fresh air.
-We're let outside?
-Yeah.
Come on, put this on, okay?
'Cause he's already
started counting.
Hide and seek?
Isn't that
a little infantilizing?
Tell me you didn't
have a childhood
without telling me you
didn't have a childhood.
-Where do the stairs go?
-To the pool.
Okay, so the trick is
to keep moving
to all the places
that he's already looked.
Where should we go first?
How far down
do you think the street is?
I have no idea.
But that's against the rules.
Okay, he's probably
already started counting to 100.
We've got to go.
Come on, quicker.
-All right.
-You've got long legs.
Use them.
One, two, three.
Here I come.
Quick! Quicker.
Come on. Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Come on, move your arms.
-Found you.
-Oh! Dang it!
You failed 'cause
you're stuck together.
It's easier to hide
when you're alone.
Yes, Daddy.
Yes.
Yes, who?
Daddy.
Okay, so Jeff may have won
today's games,
but there's always tomorrow.
And now that there's two of us,
I think that we have
a really good chance
of outsmarting him.
Yeah, 'cause
that's what I'm upset about.
That we lost at hide-and-seek.
Look...
...I hate to be
the one to say this,
but your vibes are just, like...
really terrible right now.
Dance with me?
You're not one of those
perennially happy people,
are you?
God, no.
I hate those people.
I was still on killing myself
before Jeff came along.
-What?
-Nothing.
I would just assume
someone like you,
internet fame, plenty of money,
certainly wouldn't need
the help of a man.
You've seen dickdoms?
Well, first of all,
I don't need the help
from anybody.
And second of all,
it's easier to fuck men
than it is
to be in love with women.
Amen, sister.
How do you think
I ended up here?
I guess that's something else
that we have in common.
It just feels really good
to completely surrender.
And he's really good at it
if you give him a chance.
Hey, a real dom
wouldn't trap a submissive
against their will.
We're not trapped.
We're finally free.
I really wish
that you could see that.
They know you're missing.
Your fans are searching for you.
I know.
That's why Jeff
posts for my account,
so they can all chill out.
Those people don't care
if I live or die.
I'm just an object
for them to consume.
And Jeff gets that, he sees me.
I see you.
And I care.
Oh, God, you're good at that.
I know you're just my type.
Don't let me stop the fun.
You girls keep
doing what you're doing.
Chloe, kiss her back.
Yes, Daddy.
Maria, look at me.
Chloe, take off Maria's shirt.
What did you just say there?
I told her
to say thank you to you, Daddy.
Well?
Thank you.
What the fuck?
Chloe, punish her.
Get down on your knees, brat.
Arms.
Harder.
She doesn't deserve
to play with us,
does she, Daddy?
No, she doesn't.
Did it turn you on watching us
dance like that, Daddy?
Yes, it did.
Do you wanna be kissed
like that, Daddy?
Yes, I do.
I have an idea.
How about we go upstairs
and Maria stays down here
and thinks about
what she's done?
Yeah.
Hey, girls.
Marie!
Look what Daddy got us.
For you.
Excuse me, I have to go
bring Daddy his breakfast.
What about these?
Come on.
-You'd look so good in them.
-I'm not wearing those.
I think we should put this one
on, 'cause then we can match.
-That is so not me.
-Nope, you're putting it on.
I don't care.
You don't like anything else.
Take it. Shoo.
Yeah.
Do you like our outfits, Daddy?
Yeah--Uh, no.
Get out of here. I'm working.
Wow.
You're, like, really good.
I'm all right.
You know, no one's
ever painted me before.
Well, I'm not finished yet.
I still have to add
a lot of detail.
You know, when we were
doodling in your notebook
the other night,
I noticed that you have
a really great drawing style.
I mean, they're just doodles.
It's nothing like this.
It's not that hard.
Will you show me?
-How to paint?
-Yeah.
Of course.
You start with a blank canvas.
And then...
you add paint.
It's easy.
Have you always drawn?
No.
I only started drawing
when I got here.
You got to do something
to pass the time in there.
You know, other than masturbate.
Of course.
So you really like
being locked up in there?
Yes.
It's nice
to have time to myself.
It's a place
where no one can get to me.
I just don't get it.
Don't you miss your old life?
What do I miss?
The parasocial online hellscape,
the climate apocalypse anxiety?
What's your obsession
with getting out of here?
What does the outside world
have to offer you?
Okay, yeah, the outside world
is totally fucked,
but this is not normal.
Jeff is, like, a sick person.
Just not a bad guy.
He's just a guy.
He doesn't like to be told no.
But what guy does?
Okay, so you wanna
grip the brush loosely
between your fingers,
and then you just
add just the right
amount of pressure.
And there you go.
You're on your way
to a masterpiece.
I can tell.
How long have you been painting?
My mom taught me to paint
when I was a kid,
so I guess that long.
Okay, so you have a good
relationship with your mom.
What about your dad?
Okay, so you wanna know about
my relationship with my dad?
You're gonna make a point
that I became a sugar baby
because I have a shitty
relationship with my father?
I mean, my dad's my best friend,
and I stomp on men's balls
on the Internet for funsies.
So?
I have a great relationship
with my dad. Okay?
I like sugaring because
it can be lucrative
and because
I can always leave the situation
whenever I want to.
Or... at least
I thought I could.
I don't really get involved
with people romantically.
I don't get attached
because there's no point.
People are selfish. Okay?
Everyone is selfish.
And they're just gonna
leave me once
they're done with me anyway.
So you have a habit of leaving
and I have a habit of staying.
How's that gonna
work out for us?
You painted me.
Can I paint you?
I would love
to see that, actually.
We just have to let the canvas
dry a little bit.
You meant paint me
in a literal sense.
Are we done with our lesson?
You know, if you stayed,
I'd never leave you.
It's getting late.
We should really shower and
get in bed before Jeff notices.
I give up.
-What do you mean?
-I mean, this is your last day.
Done everything I could for you,
and clearly you're not happy.
Yeah. Good.
You... are free to go.
-I'm free. I could just
walk right out the door.
-Mm-hmm.
Money's already been
added to your account.
-And Chloe?
-You can have your freedom
and the money,
or you could stay here
with me and Chloe,
but you can't have both of them.
And the window on
that decision is closing.
I'll go. I'll go. Okay.
-Okay.
-But can I at least
just say goodbye to Chloe?
Please.
Please, Daddy.
Can I say goodbye? Please?
Okay, yeah.
I'll give you 90 seconds.
1 second longer
and I'm locking the door again.
That's it?
You're leaving?
I don't wanna leave you,
but I can't stay here.
Come with me, please.
I told you that I like it here.
Why can't you just stay?
I'll never forget you.
I'm hard to forget.
Since you're going out,
do you mind
taking that with you?
You're gonna have to
make some kind of pledge.
I'll do anything to stay.
Please, Daddy.
-Please let me stay.
-I don't have time for this.
Okay. All right, you can stay.
But tell me...
tell me that you need me.
I need you.
-You do.
-Uh-huh.
Tell me you love me.
I love you.
Okay. All right.
Go put on a bikini.
- I have my guest coming over.
- Oh, and, uh...
Just let me be mad at you
for a little longer.
Okay?
Fine.
Not exactly, my friends.
Welcome aboard. Welcome aboard.
- Oh, lovely.
- Half the size of yours.
Good to see you again, man.
Took an IQ test.
- Oh, you did?
- Oh, yeah.
Off the skids?
What's up, man? Good, good.
It was my note, wasn't it?
It was a very compelling doodle.
Has he ever
had friends over before?
No, this is the first time.
For fuck's sake.
Yuck.
I'm gonna get a drink.
-Do you want anything?
-Surprise me.
We'll do what
we did to them last time.
This is gonna be easy.
No one's looking for...
-What is it?
-Follow me.
Oh, man. Oh, man.
That's exactly right.
It's exactly the thing.
'Cause today's a celebration.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm so happy for you, man.
-I am, yeah.
-Thank you. Means a lot.
Yeah. You take care.
Girls.
What's the matter?
You're right. Okay?
Jeff's just bad.
-He's a bad guy.
-What did he do to you?
It's not what he did to me.
It's what he did to us. Open it.
Ew. He's been filming us?
What a fucking creep.
He hasn't only been filming us,
he's been uploading it too.
This is a FanZen page.
Jeff has his own
creator account.
"Two hot lesbians paint each
other's tits in art studio."
"Daddy fingers
young sugar baby in bathtub"?
These have, like,
a million views.
Yeah, and he's been
blurring his face, too.
-Fucker.
-No, not the bunny!
Oh.
Fuckity fuck shit.
What are we gonna do?
-Chloe.
-Motherfucker.
Babe.
Hey, there you are.
I'm looking everywhere
for you two troublemakers.
What's that?
Why don't you tell us, Jeff?
It's just a security camera.
You gave me Humper
as a fucking gift, Jeff.
- Well--
- Well, you know what?
It's done. We're done.
What the fuck are you
talking about? What?
- You're going to let us leave right now.
-  -What?
What did Marie tell you?
Chloe, what is--
Stop. No, you can't go home.
Sorry, not yet.
Haven't you made
enough money off of us?
"Hot lesbians paint each other's
tits in art studio"?
Where's my laptop?
I know you guys have it,
so I'll let you go
if you tell me where it is.
Why don't you go fuck yourself?
Fucking shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Chloe. Give me the laptop
and I'll let Marie go, okay?
-I won't hurt her.
-Don't give it to him, Chloe.
Shut the fuck up,
you stupid fucking bitch.
Don't. Just run, Chloe.
I won't hurt her again
if you give me the laptop. Okay?
Okay, fine.
Just--just take it.
Marie?
-Hi.
-How long was I out?
It's almost evening.
Jeff sucks.
Levi was an early adopter
of this philosophy.
Well, you should've just
stuck with your instincts
and not come back.
Well, my instincts
were a little bit distracted
with the whole
you still being here thing.
Where's the laptop?
I gave it back to him.
Well, there goes our leverage.
Fuck.
You came back for me?
You know, your "what's so great
about the outside world"
argument was actually
pretty compelling.
Seeing as we're
now probably on the
getting-sold-into-sex-slavery
train,
that point is now moot.
You like me.
Don't we have bigger things
to worry about right now?
-Like how the fuck
we're gonna get out of here?
-Together?
-Yes, together.
-Okay. You don't just like me.
You, like, love me.
Can we please
talk about this later?
No. Come on, just say it.
You're, like, the best
person ever. So just say it.
It's so easy. It's just,
like, three little words.
Just three. Just say it.
Please, please. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
Yeah, just like that.
Just like that.
Yeah. Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
I'm going to cum.
I love you.
We need to get
the fuck out of here.
Wait here.
What? You could've left anytime?
I never had a reason to.
-Now I do.
-How do you even know
how to pick a lock?
A fraternity puts you
in handcuffs once,
you never let that shit
happen to you again.
-Baby, baby.
-Yeah?
When we get out of here,
we're both gonna go to therapy,
okay? So much therapy.
-Okay.
-So what's the plan?
- Who is he talking to?
-  -Well, you wanna drink something?
Oh, God,
it's one of his friends.
So, what you been up to?
Tell me that.
- I just--
- Just hanging out?
You find the phone
and I'll distract them.
-Hold on.
-Gross.
- I'll be in the living room.
-Meet me back in the foyer.
-Marie.
-Eddy.
How do you know my dad?
Okay, phones away.
That's it, just, uh, father
and son time now as they say.
Dad, what the actual
fuck is going on?
-He's the sugar daddy?
-I need help.
I should fucking say you do.
You know that I am begging him
for table scraps
and he's giving you
30 grand to look pretty?
I swear I didn't know.
I just need you to help me
get out of here right now.
Ugh!
You sick fuck!
Fucking bitch.
I should've known you'd
be fucking trouble. Fuck!
How'd you get out
the fucking cell?
-I didn't break us out.
-I did.
Have you lost
your fucking mind?
You were right, Jeff.
We're doomed
if we stay together.
Fuck that.
Dad. Unlock the fucking door.
I'm trying to leave.
Holy shit.
You're Chloe Lamore.
Now what?
What's your second plan?
You got anyone?
You got one plan B.?
-Fuck.
-Hey, Daddy.
Fuck.
Chloe, we gotta get
out of here. Okay?
-What happened to Eddy?
-Find him. Hurry.
-Hey.
-Chloe, get the fuck
out of here.
- Not without you.
- Chloe.
I'm tired of being the nice guy.
You scared?
You think I'm gonna kill you?
I'm not gonna kill you.
But I am gonna break you.
I'm gonna have all that
fiery spirit just for me.
Take the only thought
in your little head.
You're gonna be pleasing me.
No money involved.
Any last words?
Behind you.
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't
take this to the cops.
- You okay?
-  -What are you talking about?
These fucking bitches
are blackmailing me.
Blackmailing our family.
It's your word against theirs.
So who should I believe?
The dynamic
gold digging duo or you?
What do you want?
You want a condo?
A condo by the beach? Whatever.
You know, Dad...
Family is really important
to me.
Eddy, he's dangerous.
Family is everything to me, Dad.
When you left me and Mom...
Marie became my family.
No!
Don't do this, bitch, you--
You hit me for it.
- He's out!
- Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Should we call 911?
'Cause he looks,
like, super fucked up.
No.
Ambulance means cops
and cops means questions.
Yeah, but we have
evidence that pretty much
exonerates us, right?
-Right?
-My dad would do anything
to avoid prison.
-Anything.
-Marie.
No one's going to jail.
No one's calling the cops.
I have an idea.
Knock, knock.
How you feeling today?
I, uh...
Really glad to see you.
I just--
I just wanted to
apologize to you.
For any pain
that I might have caused.
You know, it sounds
really silly, but, um,
I was thinking maybe
after all this is over that,
you know, like,
we could be friends.
You know...
-We have enough friends, Jeff.
-Fuck.
Um...
...guys, I can't.
I don't know how you did this.
Very brave.
But I don't have the strength
to just take much more of this.
So, I'm worried. I'm worried
I might hurt myself.
What are you gonna do?
Asphyxiate on a stuffed animal?
Guess he could strangle
himself with the sheets.
But if you die,
the house goes to Eddy, right?
So, killing yourself
would actually be really
helpful for us.
That would clear up a
lot of red tape.
You're so silly, Daddy.
You're probably just cranky
'cause you haven't eaten
since yesterday.
That's because he was a bad boy.
Are you ready to be
a good boy for us, Jeff?
You get a treat.
Some cheese for the rat?
No?
Okay, suit yourself.
You're so hot when
you're being all dommy.
See you tomorrow, Jeff.
- Baby.
- Wait! Wha--what--
What kind of--
what kind of cheese?
Ladies, I just uploaded
that video we took yesterday
and it's already
banked two grand.
People love feet. I told you.
Who wants a paloma to celebrate?
-Me.
-Me with ice.
I'll get it.
Oh, sorry, I didn't realize
anyone was home.
Hey, is the guy who lived here--
Did he move?
-I haven't seen him in a while.
-Oh, Daddy hasn't
been feeling well.
Oh, okay.
Well,
hope your dad feels better.