Subtitled & Corrected by::: Ashy Ash Montana.
Special thanks to: Joker
Chow time!
It's time!
Floyd, step up to the door.
Dinner time.
Only my friends call me Floyd.
You ain't got no friends, Floyd.
What's that?
That is called loaf.
A loaf!
It's got a little bit of pasghetti in there.
Toenails.
Rat shit.
Everything a growing fella needs, like you.
- Come hear. Can I tell you something? Can I tell a secret?
- Yeah.
One day...
Somehow, Someway,
I'm gonna get outta here.
And I'm gonna rain down on you,
like the Holy Ghost.
Man, you just threatened a staff number.
Yeah?
Yeah, you have.
Do something.
Let's have some fun.
Open a goddamn gate!
Come on guys. Don't waste my time.
Sector C! Pat attention!
Boss is on deck!
Open!
Bravo 14, Open perimeter fence.
Stay Back!
If she moves, fire her up, all right?
You gonna come down from there or what?
Look at you.
You know the rules, hotness.
You gotta keep off these bars.
- What, these bars?
- Yeah. Those bars.
Oh, my good.
You are really in bad shape upstairs, lady!
Can you come in here and tell me that?
Or are you too scared?
Come on, I'm bored.
I'm bored, play with me.
You put five of my guards in the hospital, honey.
No one's gonna play with you.
You sleep on the ground.
I sleep where I want, when I want, with who I want.
Oh man. I love you.
Alpha one...
hit her
Come on man. You're 66 foot four.
She's a tiny little girl.
You got a choice tonight.
What we got here?
We got chocolate, strawberry or vanilla.
My job is to keep you alive until you die.
Do you understand that?
Spring break!
That is just a whole lot of pretty in a whole lot of crazy.
The world changed when Superman
flew across the sky.
And it changed again when he didn't.
Remember.
And that is why I'm here.
Subtitled & Corrected by::: Ali99
Join our Telegram channel: @SubElites.
Hello Amanda.
We lose a national hero...
but you sit there looking like the cat that ate the canary.
I've eaten a lot of canaries.
It's taken some work.
But I finally have them.
The worst of the worst.
There's rumors, Amanda...
Some of them have abilities.
The rumors are right.
You know what a problem with a metahuman is?
The human part.
We got lucky with Superman.
He shared our values.
The next Superman might not.
You're playing with fire, Amanda.
I'm fighting fire with fire.
You are not going to pitch us that Task Force X project of yours again, are you?
Yes.
But this time, you're gonna listen.
Floyd Lawton, AKA Deadshot.
He is the most wanted hitman in the world.
Let's say he has an elite clientele.
- What?
- Hey Angelo.
This is the exterminator you called for your rat problem.
My account's looking a little thin.
No one gets paid until what needs to get done, gets done.
Nope. That's not the rules.
No money, No honey.
Wow! Here is your boy right now.
With about 20 of his new best friends.
I'm still seeing zeroes over here, Angie.
Listen. Stop being cute and do your job!
They're taking him outta the car now.
In about 30 seconds, your window is gonna close forever.
Okay, Okay, Okay. Relax.
There was an accounting error.
We sent it.
Now double it for being an dickhead.
You got 10 seconds.
- We're not the kind of people you play with.
- Did you threaten me?
This dude's gonna get a sore throat.
From all the singing he's about to do.
You son of a bitch.
Pleasure doing business with you, Angie.
But everyone has a weakness.
And a weakness can be leveraged.
His is an 11-year-old honor student in Gotham city.
His daughter.
So we watched her and waited.
You should talk to Mama more.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
Mama stays in bed a lot.
Yeah. She's still going out at night?
Dad, it's okay, I can take care of her.
I know how to make pancakes now.
Hey babe, That's beautiful.
She's supposed to be taking care of you.
That's how that's supposed to work.
I want you to come and live with me.
All right? I came into some resources. I'mma get us spot.
It's gonna be nice, all right?
Mama says I can't live with you because you kill people.
That's not true, That's a lie. She is lying to you.
Daddy...
I know you do bad things.
Don't worry. I still love you.
Come on.
And you caught him?
Not me.
I just gave an anonymous tip the right guy in the Gotham city.
I'mma figure this out.
All right?
It's over, Headshot.
I do not want to do this
in front of your daughter.
- Daddy, please.
- Zoe, move!
Please daddy. Don't do it.
Please.
Don't do it.
All right.
Love you, daddy.
So now we have the man who never misses.
Where'd you put him?
Let's just say. I put him in a hole and threw away the hole.
Harley Quinn.
Before she ran off and joined the circus...
She was known as Dr. Harleen Quinzel.
A psychiatrist at Arkham Asylum.
She was assigned to The Clown himself.
Dr. Quinzel.
You know, I lived for these moments with you.
What do you get?
I got you a kitty.
So thoughtful.
She thought she was curing him ...
But, She was falling in love.
There is something you could do
for me...
Doctor.
Anything. I mean, yeah.
I need a machine gun.
A Machine gun?
Talk about a workplace romance gone wrong.
Get off me!
What do we have here?
What are you gonna do?
You gonna kill me Mr.J?
What?
Oh, I'm not gonna kill ya
I'm just gonna hurt ya...
really, really bad.
You think so?
Well, I can take it.
They became the king and the queen of Gotham city.
And god help anyone who disrespected the queen.
- We finally meet.
- He ain't shake hands.
But sit down and have a drink.
Hey, J.
On behalf of everybody, welcome back.
I wanted to come by and
personally say thank you.
You're making me good money.
I'm making you good money.
Are you sweet talkin' me?
I love this guy.
He's so intense!
You're lucky man.
You got a bad bitch.
Oh, that she is.
The fire in my loins.
The itch in my pants.
The one, the only,
the infamous Harley Quinn!
Oh, come to Daddy.
Puddin"!
Listen! You are my gift to this handsome hunka hunka!
You belong to him now.
You're cute!
You want me?
I'm all yours.
I don't want no beef.
You don't want no beef?
You don't want ..
Why, what's wrong? ( Dont't wanna beef?)
You don't like me?
Fine. Don't waste my time then.
This is your lady.
Look, are you enjoying yourself?
No.
- That's your lady, Joker!
- That's right!
You, J!
And, That was just the beginning.
Come on, Puddin". Do it!
Oh...
- We have got company.
- Batsy, Batsy, Batsy.
She is crazier than him.
And more fearless.
Stupid Bat, You're ruining date night!
Puddin...
Puddin", I can't swimmmmm!
And the Bat got her, too.
She's in the same hole as Deadshot.
And then there's the Aussie.
Digger Harkness.
Or as the tabloids call him: Capitan Boomerang.
We're gonna be rich.
Yeah, you and me, mate.
Go and get the car.
He robbed every bank in Australia. At least once.
Then he came to America for a fresh target set.
Doesn't work well with others.
No honor among thieves, ha?
But he tangled with a metahuman and,
lived to tell about it.
And have you heard of the pyro kinetic homeboy?
How'd you catch him?
We did not. He surrendered.
Chato Santana. On the street they call him El Diablo.
This LA gangbanger thought
he was the king of the world ...
until he lost his queen.
Gets jumped in prison riot and
incinerates half the yard.
The security video is incredible.
Oh, Jesus.
- What the hell is that?
- His name is Waylon Jones.
KC, dinner.
Open it up, B.
Evolution took a step backwards with this one.
Give me that, Smitty.
Where you at?
They call him Killer Croc.
He looked like a monster.
So they treated him like a monster.
Then he became a monster.
He was chased out of Gotham by the bat.
Went searching for sanctuary elsewhere.
He never found it.
I saved the best for last.
- The witch.
- A witch?
I'm talking a flying, spell-casting,
making-shit-disappear witch.
A sorceress from another dimension.
Another world.
Archaeologist doctor June Moone ...
Wondered into the wrong cave.
June...
She opened something she shouldn't have ...
releasing a metahuman more powerful
than any we've encountered.
The Enchantress.
She inhabits Dr.Moone's body now.
Where is this witch?
In my pocket.
Now tell him why she won't turn you into a frog.
Some say the witch has
a secret buried heart...
and whoever finds it, can control the witch.
So we searched the cave where she turned up ...
and we found her heart.
That thing's her heart?
She is vulnerable without it.
You want to put our national security in the hands of...
witches, gangbangers, and crocodiles?
- Don't forget about the Joker's girlfriend.
- These are villains Amanda.
What makes you think you can control them?
Because getting people to act
against their own self-interests...
for the national security of the U.S is what I do for a living.
You take the finest special forces officer
this nation has ever produced...
Colonel Rick Flag.
Help me.
I assigned him to watch Dr.Moone,
and just as I hoped ...
it got personal.
Are you gonna kiss me or not?
I have the witch's heart.
And Dr.Moone has his.
Now he'll follow my orders as Holy Writ.
In a world of flying men and monsters...
this is the only way to protect our country.
What if Superman had decided to fly down,
rip off the roof of the White House...
and grab the president of the US right out of the Overall office?
Who would've stopped him?
We got contingency plans
for nukes in North Korea...
anthrax in our mail. We got fluoride in our water.
But what happens if
the next Superman...
becomes a terrorist?
Amanda Waller has a plan.
Amanda?
I want to build a team of some very bad people
who I think can do some good.
Like fight a next war,
defeat the next Superman.
Not on my watch.
You're not putting those monsters
back out on the street in our name.
General, we run them covertly non-attributed.
Strictly need to know.
And if they get caught,
we throw them under [???]
The next war will be fought
with these meta humans. Ours or Theirs.
We're not the only ones kicking up rocks looking for them.
You know we can't control these people.
June, Be strong!
Dr.Moone.
Enchantress.
Meet the Enchantress.
Everything we know about her,
is in your briefing packs.
She's walked this earth
for a very long time...
and will likely be here
when we're long gone.
This meeting is... is now a magic show?
Magic or not, this girl can do
some pretty incredible things.
Go get it, girl.
How about a little something from
the weapons ministry vault in Tehran?
We've been chasing these plans for years.
Please don't touch me.
Thank you. We'd like Dr.Moone back.
Enchantress.
Please, Please.
I'm sorry. I can'... I can't do that again.
I can'...
Flag, get her out of here.
I move to...
authorize Amanda Waller to establish
"Task Force X" under the Argus program.
All right.
Thank you Mr. Chairman.
Welcome to Belle Reve, special security barracks.
How you doing man?
Why don't you kiss her ass?
She is in charge.
Welcome, ma'am.
How are you?
I'm here to assist you in anyway.
Where are they?
Are you the Devil?
Maybe.
Ain't you scared?
Why'd they put you down here?
I asked.
You. Ese
Hola, amigo.
Put that burrito down.
You got visitors, man.
What's up? Hey, you want some of this?
Then come down here.
That ain't me.
That wasn't you?
Nah, they say it's me, but that ain't me.
That guy's gone.
He's dead.
And yet, here you are.
Ma'am.
Let me try to talk to him.
You wanna die in here buddy?
You got a real shot at
walking at the block again.
Have a nice cold beer, a nice meal.
A Women.
Look, man...
You ain't the first to ask,
and you ain't gonna be the last.
Ask what?
I'm a man. Okay?
I ain't no weapon.
I'mmna die in peace before
I raise my fists again.
I've caused enough harm.
All right, unlock him.
What?
You heard me.
You know what this man can do?
I'm here to find out.
Lose the restraints.
OK.
What is this?
Cheerleading tryouts?
Let's go. Let's see what you can do.
They say you never missed a shot.
Prove it.
Now you got one in the chamber.
What you gonna do with it?
- Hhhh... Hey.
- Shit.
Give me the word, boss.
I'll drop him.
Everybody calm down.
Griggs, tell your men to stand down.
Tell them: "Put it down".
Stand down.
Colonel, for the record, this is exactly
what I was concerned about.
What's for dinner?
Ames, if this man shoots me...
I want you to kill him...
And I want you to go and clear my browser history.
See...
the firing pin is filed down, right?
Mag full of dummy rounds.
If I pull the trigger, nothing happens.
You're absolutely right.
Why would we give a loaded weapon
to an infamous hitman?
Go ahead, pull the trigger. Empty it.
Don't empty nothing.
You don't even know this lady.
I've known you, like, nine months.
Remember when I brought you that cookie?
That was real cookie.
What?
Y'all Jokers must be crazy.
All right.
Now you know what you're buyin'.
Let me tell you the price. First...
I want outta here.
Second, I want full custody of my daughter.
All right?
And her mom can have, like...
supervised visits. But, her boyfriend can't come.
Darnell can't come.
- Darnell's out.
- He's out.
Third, y'all gonna pay for my daughter's whole education.
Best schools.
And then I want her to go to college.
Like Harvard. Or Yale.
- So Ivy league.
- Ivy league, yeah.
One of them big joints, you know?
And if she can't cut it...
and her grades start slipping, I need you to
white-people that thing. You know how y'all do.
- Oh yeah.
- You know, right? Ok.
Now that's my price.
But I'm concerned...
'cause I don't see
nobody writing shit down.
You're in no position
to make any demands.
Oh. I'm sorry.
You thought I was talking to you.
No, errand boy.
I'm talking to your boss.
That's my price, sweetie.
You know what it is.
You notice these are criminals?
They're psychotic antisocial freaks.
It makes no sense.
Let me hit the Tier One units
and I'll build you...
a team of pipe hitters who'll do
anything you can dream up.
I mean, you need real soldiers.
Not these scumbags.
In WW2, the US Navy made a deal with he mafia...
to protect its ships on the waterfront.
This ain't WW2.
It's WW3.
What are you really up to?
It's a "need-to-know", and, all you
need to know is you work for me.
That can change with a phone call.
I have friends, too. You know.
There you go. Call'em.
But without you minding
her, your lady friend stays
here strapped to a board
in a drug-induced coma.
They warned me about you.
I didn't believe the stories.
Nobody does.
Where is she?
It's complex. This is not just her.
Everybody's disappeared.
This new law,
where if you're a bad enough, bad guy
they stamp "Terrorist" on your jacket.
They send you to this swamp in Louisiana.
A black site.
That's where she is.
So what are we doni'?
Bring the car around.
We're going for a drive.
Lester! Lester!
Hit me one more time!
Come on, Man.
You gotta call upstairs and tell them
to float me another 10k.
- Boss wants to see you.
- You know who I am?
Good job, Man.
He's killin' it.
Come on Man. Why am I here?
All right! Yeah! I'm down.
I get it! All right?
I've had run of bad decks.
Not my fault.
All right?
Dude, this is real.
I had to stop these guys from burning down
your house with your kids in it.
But, you're lucky.
Maybe. Why do you think so?
You. Slick, what's up?
Griggs. You are ...?
You might wanna keep your mouth shut.
Can I go, man?
What the hell's going on, man?
This is crazy.
All of that chitchat's gonna get you hurt.
My God!!!
I could tell you meant that.
Yeah.
You're gonna be my friend.
Enchantress.
- Log time of death. 16:20
- June?
- Let's get her down to the morgue.
June?
June.
What did you do?
OK.
Sister.
Brother.
Pus, it could be the routing number.
Wanna go for drinks?
Brother I have freed you.
Where are we?
The same world only much later.
What happened?
The humans turned against us.
But they worshipped us?
We were gods to them.
Now they worship machines.
So I will build a machine.
That will destroy them all.
Build your strength.
Feed on them.
And wait for me to return.
Enchantress.
God damn it!
June! June!
June! I'm sorry.
She went somewhere.
If you have to choose between her or me...
stop her.
Promise me you'll stop her.
Even if it kills me.
Sir!
Sir, You okay?
Can you breathe?
Did you take anything?
This is 21. Send medical to my location.
I'm a physician.
Roger. Bringing medical to your location.
No pulse. Starting compressions.
Sir.
Midway city is under attack.
It's a non-human entity.
I think you know what to do, sir.
Activate Task Force X...
and get Amanda Waller and her whole circus on scene ASAP.
(ASAP = as soon as possible)
Sir.
We're gonna live with Task Force X. Pull'em.
Prisoners, get down on your knees. Now!
Down on your knees! Hands in the air!
Turn around.
Hands up high!
Hey, I'm cooperating. All right?
- This is me being cool.
- Take her.
Do not fire that goddamn weapon!
Damn it!
Open the gate!
Everybody, line up for extraction.
Let's go! Let's move, move!
Yeah! Open the door! Let's go!
Hit him!
Hurry up, before he smokes us!
Where you at?
Is that the new guy?
What is that?
- Who are you?
- Standby. Arming device.
Who are you? I don't know who you are.
Device armed.
Hey... I'm talking to you.
Injection Successful.
Location verified.
Anybody who touches me is dead.
Anybody who...
lady.
Injection Successful.
- Hey! Miss? What was that?
- Location verified.
Next!
Oh, you deaf. You one of them deaf hoes.
Come on.
Shut up, and get it done.
Listen, you're being transferred.
I don't know where you're going.
It's from Mr. J.
You gonna tell him I took care of you?
You're so screwed.
What do you mean by that?
Get off me! Get off me!
Harley, what do you mean by that?
Harley!!!
Hey, I got a delivery.
I have a gift basket for Dr.Van Criss.
You're not on the access list.
I can't let you in. Sorry.
Cool if I leave it with you?
I'm way behind today.
Thank you. You're a good man.
Open up.
Just please, do whatever they say.
Do whatever they say. Just do it.
This look neat.
Light it up! Light it up! Light it up!
He's right above us.
This is a mistake.
Rick, I can't do this.
- I can't d...
- Listen... Listen.
There is no other way.
Just get it done.
Enchantress.
Flag, talk to me.
What' going on down there?
Amanda, she is bolted.
Say it again?
She is bolted.
Shit!
Brother help me.
Before she kills me.
Where's your heart?
I will take it back.
Untill then you will share your power.
Now help me build my weapon.
It's time to wipe them out.
Go!
Worldwide military is on alert.
Our weapons are ineffective.
I thought this was contained!
Guys. I need all three of you follow me please.
Anybody with blood.
This is the worst day of my life.
All evacuees must report
to a FEMA representative.
What's going on in that city?
Those assholes here yet?
Yeah. They're here.
Alpha, Bravo team, on me.
What the hell, Flag?
Unlock'em.
Hi, boys! Harley Quinn.
How do you do?
Haaah?
What was that?
I should kill everyone and escape?
Sorry. The voices.
I'm kidding. Jeez!
That's not what they really said.
What do we got here?
12 pounds of shit in a 10-pound sack.
Welcome to party, Capitan Boomerang.
Hey, hey, hey... What's going on, man?
Calm down.
Hey, one minute I'm playing Mahjong with me nanna...
then this red streak hits me outta nowhere.
Shut up! You were caught robbing a diamond exchange.
I was not.
Here comes Slipknot...
the man who climb anything. Wonderful.
Have a good time, scumbag.
Straighten up!
She had a mouth.
Listen up!
In your necks...
injection you got,
it's a nanite explosive.
As the size of a rice grain...
but it's powerful as a hand grenade.
You disobey me, you die.
You try to escape, you die.
You otherwise irritate or vex me, and guess what?
You die.
I'm known to be quite vexing.
I'm just forewarning you.
Lady, shut up!
This is the deal.
You're going somewhere very bad...
to do something that'll get you killed.
But until that happens...
you're my problem.
So was that like a pep talk?
Yeah. That was a pep talk.
There's your shit.
Grab what you need for a fight.
We're wheels up in 10.
You might wanna work on
your team motivation thing.
- You heard of Phil Jackson?
- Yeah.
He's like a gold standard. OK?
Triangle, bitch. Study
(Kind of strategy for effective attacking in basketball)
What?
Won't fit anymore?
Too much junk in the trunk?
Nah. Every time I put this on, somebody dies.
And?
I like putting it on.
Goody.
Somethin' tells me a whole lotta
people are about to die.
Yeah. It's us.
We're being led to our deaths.
Speak for yourself mate.
Hey, what's that crop on your face?
Does it wash off?
Hey, if you like a girl, can you
light her cigarette with your pinkie?
Because that would be real classy.
Hey, y'all might wanna leave old boy alone.
He could torch this whole joint.
Ain't right, ese?
Ain't got nothing to worry about from me.
I'm cool, homie.
Behold the voice of god.
For those of you who
don't know me officially ...
My Name is Amanda Waller.
There's an active terrorist event in Midway City.
I want you to enter the city,
rescue HVT-1 and get them to safety.
I'm sorry.
For those of us who don't speak good guy,
what is HVT-1?
The only person that matters in the city...
the one person you can't kill.
Complete the mission, you get
time off your prison sentence.
Fail the mission, you die.
Anything happens to Colonel Flag ...
I'll kill every single one of you.
Remember, I'm watching.
I see everything.
There's your pep talk.
Compared to your shit, she killed it.
So that's it?
What, we some kind of Suicide Squad?
I'll notify your next of kin.
Alpha, Bravo team, Mount up!
Your' late.
I was busy.
Please have mercy.
Where was the mercy for my husband?
I didn't kill him.
But you watched.
Criminals deserve no mercy.
This is Katana.
She's got my back.
She can cut all of you in half
with one sword stroke...
Just like mowing the lawn.
I would advise not getting killed by her.
Her sword traps the souls of its victims.
Harley Quinn.
Nice to meet ya.
Love your perfume.
What is that? The stench of death?
- Should I kill them?
- Easy cowgirl.
Ain't that kind of mission.
Have a seat..
She seems nice.
I'm coming for you.
Look at that pretty lights!
Are you guys seein' this?
What happened?
Terror attack.
Dirty bombs, bad guys
shooting up the place with AKs.
You know, usual shit.
Right.
Yeah, you're a bad liar.
I don't know if they told you...
but I'm a hitman. I'm not a fireman.
I don't save people.
Anything for a dollar, right?
You know the dark places, too.
Don't act like you don't.
I'm a soldier!
And you're a serial killer
who takes credit cards.
When the shooting starts...
and it will,
you'll cut and run.
Six-one is going down.
Six-one is going down hard.
Stand by. Drop the ramp.
What a ride!
We're okay. We're okay.
Assets are undamaged.
Mind games.
What's that?
- All this bomb in the neck crap.
That ain't real, mate.
See. They're trying to trap us
with our own minds. Right?
But you look around, we're free, brah.
How do you know this?
Just trust me. I know, all right?
It's a con.
Now I'm going.
Because I got a life to live.
Question is, are you coming?
Yeah! Smart!
Hold your fire.
Sorry. It's what I do.
Damn it.
Now that's a killer app!
Okay. You wanna keep playing...
the Hollywood Squares version of
"I'll Blow your freaking Head Off?"
Are you next?
You tripping, homie.
You next, Deadshot?
You just threatened me?
Oh, yeah.
He just threatened me.
Move.
You got a boyfriend?
I'm gonna kill him.
Well, you better make it quick
'cause he's gonna kill all of us one by one.
I'm gonna drop him. The sword lady.
Five or seven of these SEALs.
After that, I'm gonna need some help.
You down?
Always. What about
the shit in our necks?
Your friend's gonna
help us out with that, right?
You're my friend, too.
Stay evil, doll face, Spread the word.
I'm standing by for follow on tasking.
C2, what is the operational load of the PLS?
Boss, we got people up here.
I'm on my way.
Shit!
Amanda, we have hostiles up ahead.
Flag. Get out of there.
We're not here to fight them.
We know that doesn't work.
Copy that.
We're diverting.
Bump out second two squad two blocks east.
We'll pass through you...
continue north.
Take Bravo two blocks east.
We'll leapfrog through you
once you're in position.
Copy that.
Hey. I like these odds, mate.
You just say the word.
Yeah.
Come on.
Hold that thought.
Rick, why do they look like that?
Just stay cool.
The hell are they?
You cut run.
I'll blow your head off.
Hit'em!
Hey.
Get off me!
Get off me! Son of a...
Flag!
- Good riddance.
- Harley.
He dies. We die.
- Thanks.
- Shut up.
Backblast, clear!
Pinky.
That's how I cut and run.
Hey.
Hey. Come on.
What? I saw it move.
See? It flinched.
I think.
Hey. You were some help. Princess.
It's better this way.
Trust me.
Oh, yeah you're the fire bloke. Eh?
Yeah, I was. Yeah.
Right. Yeah. Hey.
Well. Look at here.
It's fire.
Wants to explain this?
If I told you, would you believe me?
- What are they?
- I don't know.
That's bullshit.
This guy had a 3000$ watch.
Is that a Person?
It was.
Now it's not.
Hey, don't.
What?
We got a job to do.
Keep movin'.
Get your boys moving.
Let's go.
Waller, we are moving toward the objective.
Contacting Bravo. You got the visual?
Stand by.
Anything on the squadron?
No ma'am.
Code7 I need your sensors
in those coordinates.
Flag, it's a negative.
[???], but we've lost them.
Seriously?
What the hell is wrong with you people?
We're bad guys.
It's what we do.
Take a knee.
Our body's at the top of that building.
We get up there...
Pull them out of
the vault they're hiding in.
Helos extract us off the roof.
- It's miller times.
- Check.
Waller?
We're about to enter the building.
Get that chopper ready.
What do say we get this over with?
What the hell? Deadshot.
Fall back.
You mind if we tag along?
Look like we have a spot of luck. Eh?
Be a walk in the park.
Easy peasy.
Don't make me shoot you.
God damn it. Harley!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
I am coming to my lady...
Hey, guys!
Come on. Let's go.
Ma'am. I got motion detectors
going off on the secure floors.
Flag...
- They're all around you.
- Hold.
Use extreme caution.
I don't like this, Flag.
I don't like it either.
Pussy.
I will knock your ass out.
I do not care that you're a girl.
They're after Flag again.
Get off me.
Circle up. Circle around him.
Let me fight!
You die. We die.
Clear! Everyone move out.
- Where you been, homie?
- This ain't my fight!
You know what? You don't stand for shit.
You ain't about shit!
Don't touch me, man!
- Don't touch you? What you gonna do?
- Don't touch me!
I'm touching you! I'm touching you!
- Do something. Do something!
- Don't touch me!
- You wanna see something?
- Yes, I wanna see...
- Yes I wanna see something.
I was just trying to get you there.
Phil Jackson. We good, right?
I knew you'd come through.
That shit crazy.
Clear.
I gotta work on my cardio.
Question.
Would you die for me?
Yes.
That's too easy.
Would you ...?
Would you live for me?
Yes.
Careful.
Do not say this oath thoughtlessly.
Desire becomes surrender.
Surrender becomes power.
Do you want this?
I do.
Say it.
Say it. Say it.
Pretty, pretty, pretty...
Please.
God, you're so...
Good.
Relax.
Just me.
You ever been in love?
Nah. Never.
Bullshit.
You don't kill as many people as
I've killed and still sleep like a kitten.
If you feel shit like love.
Another textbook sociopath.
Clear.
All right, secure the roof.
Sweep for shooters
so we can bring in our aviation assets.
Going to the roof.
Wait here.
Please.
I don't wanna gave this dude
a heart attack okay?
He's embarrassed of us.
Hey, Flag.
This dude better cure cancer
after all of this shit.
You ready? Let's go.
You wouldn't have made it without them.
We got lucky. I don't do luck.
I do planning and precision.
Admit it, rick. I was right.
Yeah, I told you to get on the damn truck.
Why'd you say?
I was studying your girlfriend.
She takes an average person...
A yoga mom an elderly retiree
and she turns them into a soldier.
Who can take a headshot and still fight.
It's an instant army.
How'd she do it. Flag?
How'd she game the system...
With you watching her every move?
I'll accept the consequences.
I am your consequence.
You might need to be careful.
They think we're rescuing Nelson Mandela.
I can take care of myself.
- Shut it down, wipe the drivers.
- Yes, ma'am.
Copy that.
Hey, man I know you can't hear me
'cause you're trapped...
In your temple of
soldierly self-righteousness...
But a two-faced dude like you
wouldn't survive a second on the street.
Oh, says the guy who shoots people for money.
My cards is on the table, man.
It got done. Didn't it?
Damn. That is just...
A mean lady.
Yeah. You get used to it.
And I'm the bad guy?
That's gangsta.
What?
They weren't cleared
for any of this any of it.
Hey. I'm not judging.
I've buried a lot of mistakes, too.
No way.
Let's go home.
Yeah. Let's go home.
That sounds good.
You guys wanna go home?
Or you wanna go back to prison?
I'm not going back to prison.
What I'm saying is...
We kill the pair of 'em now
before they kill us.
I got this.
You all made it this far.
Don't get high-spirited on me
and run a good thing.
I like her.
Savior one-zero,
this is Ground Element.
how copy?
Savior one-zero, the LZ's clear.
Boss, they're not talking to me.
Our bird's been jacked.
Light it up!
What? I got hickey or something?
Professor, could you pick up the pace?
Now!
Harley!
Hello, baby.
Kill her!
Her nanite's disarmed!
Come on, baby.
Deadshot...
Shoot that woman right now!
She ain't do shit to me.
You're a hitman. Right?
I got a contract.
Kill Harley Quinn.
Do it your freedom
and your kid.
Now she dead.
I missed.
Good one, mate.
It's Waller.
Savior one-zero's been hijaked.
Shoot it down.
Rager that ma'am.
Going hot.
Puddin'!
You got all dressed up for me?
You know I'd do anything for you.
By the way...
I've got some grape soda on ice,
and a bear skin rug waitin'.
Yeah?
Boss, we got a problem.
- This bird is baked.
- No.
Okay, honey. It's me and you.
Let's do it.
Target destroyed, ma'am.
Thank you. Now get me off this roof.
Yes, ma'am. We are inbound.
The Joker and Harley Quinn are no more.
You couldn't save her.
Roger. I see ya.
Watch your step. Ma'am.
Stand by. I'll send another helo!
Waller's down.
It's over.
Ops just confirmed.
She's down. 1k west.
Let's go get her.
The mission's not over.
Nah. It is for me.
We had a deal.
Without Waller, you got nothing.
Hey, guys. I'm back!
I missed you all so much.
We're glad you could make it.
Hey, craziness.
Bring me my sister's heart.
With my heart returned,
I can finish my weapon.
Now tell me how to
destroy your armies.
Do your worst, bitch!
So let me guess.
We're going to the swirling
wing of trash in the sky.
You know, 'cause why wouldn't we?
When does this end, Flag?
Load up.
We're in for a fight.
You tell everybody everything.
Or me and you are gonna go right now.
Three days ago,
a non-human entity appeared in the subway station.
Waller, we're almost there.
So Waller sent me and
a woman with incredibles abilities.
Enchantress.
A witch.
See, nobody could get near this thing...
but the witch could.
Bombs ready.
Set for two seconds. You just
press the button and drop it.
Needless to say the whole thing was a bad idea.
She bolted!
Shit!
Brother help me.
And that's how she escaped from Waller.
So now you know.
You can just kill me right now...
but I'm going to have a drink.
Hey! Deadshot, I need your help.
No, sir. You need a miracle.
Here's to honor among thieves
I'm not a thief.
Oh.She's not a thief.
Well, we almost pulled it off...
Despite what everybody thought.
Worst part of it is, they're gonna
blame us for the whole thing.
And they can't have people
knowing the truth.
We're the patsies.
The cover-up.
Don't forget, we're the bad guys.
For about two sweet seconds...
I had hope.
You had hope huh?
Hope don't stop the wheel
from turning, my brother.
You preaching?
It's coming back around for you.
How many people you killed, man?
You don't ask nobody
no question like that, ese.
You ain't ever whacked down no women.
No kids.
I don't kill women and children.
I do.
See, I was born with the Devil's gift.
I kept it hidden most of my life, but...
The older I got, the stronger I got.
So I started using it.
For business, you know.
The more power on the street I got...
The more firepower I got.
Like that shit went hand in hand.
You know? One was feeding the other.
Ain't nobody tell me no.
Except my old lady.
You know, she used to pray for me.
You're welcome.
Even when I didn't want it.
God didn't give me this.
Why should he take it away?
Hey.
This is our home.
You put that back where you found it.
I'm taking my kids to my Mom's.
You ain't taking my kids nowhere!
See when I get mad, I lose
control you know, I just...
I don't know what I do...
till it's done.
And the kids?
He killed them.
Didn't you?
Own that shit.
Own it.
What'd you think was
gonna happen? Huh?
Hey Harley, Come on.
What you were just...
Thinking you can have a happy family...
And coach little leagues
and make car payments?
Normal's a setting on the dryer.
People like us, we don't get normal!
Why is it always a knife fight…
every single time you open your mouth?
You know, outside you're amazing.
But inside, you're ugly.
We all are.
We all are!
Except for him.
He's ugly on the outside, too.
Not me, shorty.
I'm beautiful.
Yeah, you are.
We don't want you here.
You get to the part in that binder
saying I was sleeping with her?
Yeah.
I never been with a witch before.
What's that like?
Apparently that's why the creatures
chase him all the time.
'Cause the witch is scared of him.
The only woman I ever cared about...
is trapped inside that monster.
If I don't stop the witch, it's over.
Everything is over.
Everything.
You're free to go.
Your daughter writes you everyday.
Every single day.
You had these the whole time?
You had letters from my daughter the whole time?
I'm gonna get you there.
And you're gonna end this.
I'm gonna carry your ass if I have to.
'Cause this shit is gonna be
like a chapter in the Bible.
Everybody's gonna know what we did.
And my daughter is
gonna know that her daddy…
is not a piece of shit.
I'll come.
What?
You got something better to do?
Come on!
Pussies.
We think that thing's a weapon.
Here. Lower.
We gotta take out the big one.
I left a big ass demo charge
down there in that subway.
There's a flooded tunnel...
Leads right underneath that building.
SEALs, they can recover the charge,
swim underneath that things feet.
We get in its face and distract
the hell out of that son of a bitch.
So the swimmers can blow the bomb.
That's how we take it out.
I'm going with ya.
We got this.
I'm not asking bro.
I live underground.
Y'all are just tourist.
My dear husband if I die in battle.
We will be together.
The man who killed her husband
used that sword.
His souls trapped inside of it.
She talks to him.
Hey. Well...
You know what they say
about the crazy ones.
Huh?
Let's do this.
You gonna fight with us?
What if I lose control?
Then maybe we'll have a chance.
Duck in.
Hey, everyone can see
all this trippy magic stuff right?
Yeah why?
I'm off my meds.
That's your old lady huh?
Yeah.
Well, you need to handle this shit, alll right?
Get up there, smack on her ass,
tell her: " knock this shit off".
I do not think that'd be wise.
I'm gonna draw out the big one.
My boys will detonate the bomb underneath him.
You know, we should
get a drink sometimes.
I've been waiting for you all night.
Step out of the shadows.
I won't bite.
What the hell? Grab her.
Why are you here?
Because the soldier led you?
And all for Waller?
Why do you serve those who cage you?
I am your ally.
And I know what you want.
Exactly what you want.
Baby. Baby.
Baby. It's just a nightmare.
It's just a bad dream.
I'm here.
Miss me?
I'll put the kids to sleep
and then we can kick in?
Yeah?
I can't change what I did. And neither can you!
He married me.
It's not real.
I killed the Bat.
No homie, you don't want that.
What? I want that.
- She's trying to play games with you man. It's not real!
- He's right.
It's not real.
How long have you been able to see?
My whole life.
You can't have them.
These are my people right here.
But it is our time.
The sun is setting and the magic rises.
The met humans are a sign of change.
Lady...
You are EVIL!
Brother.
Make them bow to me.
Oh wow!
Uh-oh!
Who's this?
It's gonna be bad!
We should run.
GQ, come in. We're in position.
We gotta get him in that corner
That's where the bomb will be.
I'll do it! I'll get him there.
I lost one family.
I ain't gonaa lose one another.
Look, think it through...
I got this.
Let me show you what I really am.
Over here!
Go!
Rick, in position. Standing by.
Diablo, drive him into the corner!
Get him mate.
- Come on.
Yeah, do it.
Diablo, get clear
Get out of there!
Blow it!
Blow it.
Now GQ, now.
NO!
Everybody down!
Now you're screwed.
Brother!
You next.
My spell is complete.
Once you and armies are gone,
my darkness will spread across this world.
And it would be mine to rule.
That was our main satellite uplink.
How did this witch even know how to target this thing?
It's a secret facility.
You got a move here, Flag?
We gotta cut her heart out.
While we're fighting...
that thing is laying waste to the whole damn world.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Hey.
Look out look out!
Sorry.
Flag!
Enough!
Of all who have faced me...
you have earned mercy.
For the last time...
join me...
or die.
I'm not much of a joiner...
but maybe we should.
Hey.
She's trying to take over the world.
So?
What's the world ever
done for us anyway?
It hates us.
Hey Harley!
Hey lady?
I lost my Puddin'.
But you can get him back, right?
I can, my dear.
Anything you want.
You promise?
Yes. Child.
You need only Bow...
and serve beneath my feet.
I like what you're sellin' lady.
There's only one teeny problem.
You messed with my friends.
Her heart's out!
We can ends this.
Hey, Croc!
Harley!
Please Daddy, Don't do it.
The only way for us to be together
is if you don't pull the trigger.
Daddy I love you.
Please don't do this.
That was a great shot man.
Hey, I don't do hugs. I'm not a hugger.
I'm not a hugger. All right?
Let me join my brother.
Katana, no!
Give me that.
You bring June back.
You bring her back.
She's not coming back.
I'll crush this.
Do you hear me?
You bring June back or I'll crush this!
Go ahead.
You don't have the balls.
Hey, Flag.
June!
She's gone.
I though killed you.
I thought I killed you.
Y'all don't mind.
I got me a sewer to crawl back into.
Yeah, and I got some business
to handle back in Gotham.
I'm going to hotwire a car
Need a ride?
You are not driving.
Why not?
How are you not dead?
We just saved the world.
A "thank you" would be nice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, we did all of this
and we don't get shit?
Ten years off you prison sentences.
Nah. That's not enough.
I'm seeing my daughter.
That can be arranged.
Ant other requests?
An espresso machine.
BET.
Ten years off a triple life sentence?
Darling, I'm walking out of here
a free man..
Or we're to start having some real fun.
Why don't have some fun?
You're trying to figure out this length.
That's the hypotenuse.
So you have to know this angle.
Okay. So, if you're up here...
like an a building...
And you shoot a man down here
an the street...
That's how far the bullet actually goes?
Yeah. That's... that's right!
Tou are so smart, Right.
The hypotenuse, good one.
So that would make you
have to know the angle...
Between the building and the sidewalk.
You got to know that angle.
No, I mean, in real life...
You have variables.
You know. You got rifling twist.
You got chamber pressure.
You got bullet weight.
Some shots you'll even have to take
the curvature of the earth in with the...
It's time.
Wind effect.
You know, there's a lot variables...
In the street.
I gotta go.
Are you coming back?
Yeah.
I'm working it out. All right?
You know, promised my friends
that I would just, you know, go...
Without killing them all.
Bring in it.
I love you. Daddy.
I love you.
Hey! Let me out!
Let me out of here right now!
Hey! You feel that? Yeah.
Let me out of here. Darling, please.
Please, I'm begging you. Seriously.
Listen to me. Have you got a car?
Because I'm a brilliant driver.
Come on!
Puddin"!
Let's go home.
Our channel ID: @SubElites.
My E-mail address: aliakbar_1022@yahoo.com
My Telegram ID: @Aliakbar99.
Listen, I can keep a secret, OK?
What do you want?
People have asked questions
about Midway City.
The kind of people can get the answers,
And if they can get those answers, [???]
Consider yourself under my protection. If you deliver.
Why, Mr. Wayne?
It likes to make friends.
It's the difference between us.
You believe in friendship.
I believe in the leverage.
Goodnight.
You look tired.
You should stop working at nights.
You should shout it down,
or my friends and I will for you.