Alright! Lights out!
Here's to honor
among thieves.
We almost pulled it off.
Despite what
everybody thought.
They're gonna blame us for the whole thing.
We're the patsies.
Don't forget ... we're the bad guys.
We've all heard the stories of Samson leveling a temple with a single push.
Or the Philistine weapon of mass-destruction named Goliath.
The next war will be fought with these meta-humans.
Ours ... or theirs.
I wanna assemble a task-force of the most dangerous people on the planet.
Y'all jokers must be crazy!
This is the deal.
You're going somewhere very bad.
Look at the pretty lights!
To do something that'll get you killed.
You might wanna work on your team-motivation-thing.
You ever heard of Phil Jackson? (Yeah) He's like the gold-standard.
Okay? Triangle, bitch.
Joker:
What?
Captain Boomerang:
Aaah, you're the fire-bloke, eh? Well, looky here. Fire. Ooooooh!
I can't wait to show you my toys.
We're going to the swirling ring of trash in the sky.
A walk in the park. Eezy-peezy.
Don't make me shoot you.
They're so intense!
Hey, guys!
Made by MovieTrailerSubs.