Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Chow time!
It's time!
Floyd, step up to
the door. Dinner time.
Only my friends call me Floyd.
You ain't got no friends, Floyd.
What's that?
That is called loaf.
A loaf.
It's got a little bit
of pasghetti in there.
Toenails.
Rat shit.
Everything a growing
fella needs, like you.
Come here. Can I tell you
something? Can I tell you a secret?
Yeah.
One day...
Somehow, some way,
I'm gonna get outta here.
And I'm gonna rain down
on you like the holy ghost.
Man, you just threatened
a staff member.
Yeah?
Yeah, you have.
Do something.
Let's have some fun.
Whoop his ass!
Open the goddamn gate!
Come on, guys.
Don't waste my time.
Sector C! Pull your heads out
of your ass! The boss is on deck!
Open it!
Bravo 14 open perimeter fence.
Stay back.
If she moves, fire
her up, all right?
You gonna come down
from there or what?
Yeah. Look at you.
You know the rules, hotness.
You gotta keep off these bars.
- What, these bars?
- Yeah. Those bars.
Oh, my god.
You are really in bad
shape upstairs, lady!
Gonna come in
here and tell me that?
Or are you too scared?
Come on, I'm bored.
I'm bored. Play with me.
You put five of my guards
in the hospital, honey.
No one's gonna play with you.
You sleep on the ground.
I sleep where I want, when
I want, with who I want.
Oh, man. I love you.
Alpha one.
Hit her.
Come on, man. You're six
foot four. She's a tiny little girl.
You got a choice
tonight. What we got here?
We got chocolates,
strawberry or vanilla.
My job is to keep you alive until
you die. Do you understand that?
Spring break!
That is just a whole lot of
pretty in a whole lot of crazy.
The world changed when
Superman flew across the sky.
And then it changed
again when he didn't.
Remember.
And that is why I'm here.
Suicide squad.
Hello, Amanda.
We lose a national hero...
But you sit there looking
like the cat that ate the canary.
I've eaten a lot of canaries.
It's taken some work.
But I finally have them.
The worst of the worst.
There's rumors, Amanda that...
some of them have abilities.
The rumors are right.
You know what the problem
with a metahuman is?
The human part.
We got lucky with Superman.
He shared our values.
The next Superman might not.
You're playing
with fire, Amanda.
I'm fighting fire with fire.
You are not gonna pitch us that Task
Force X project of yours again, are you?
Yes.
But this time,
you're gonna listen.
Floyd Lawton, aka Deadshot.
Deadshot
Family — Daughter, ex-wife
He's the most wanted
hitman in the world.
Let's say he has
an elite clientele.
What?
Hey, Angelo.
This is the exterminator you
called for your rat problem.
My account's
looking a little thin.
No one gets paid until what
needs to get done gets done.
Nope. That's not the
rules. No money, no honey.
Whoa, here is
your boy right now.
With about 20 of
his new best friends.
I'm still seeing zeroes
over here, Angie.
Listen. Stop being
cute and do your job!
Oh. They're taking
him outta the car now.
In about 30 seconds, your
window is gonna close forever.
Okay, okay, okay. Relax.
There was an accounting error.
We sent it.
Now double it for
being a dickhead.
You got 10 seconds.
We're not the kind of
people you play with.
Did you just... Did
you threaten me?
This dude's gonna get a sore throat
from all the singing he's about to do.
You son of a bitch.
Pleasure doing
business with you, Angie.
But everyone has a weakness.
And a weakness can be leveraged.
His is an 11-year-old
honor student in Gotham city.
His daughter.
So we watched her and waited.
You should talk to mama more.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Mama stays in bed a lot.
Yeah. She's still
going out at night?
Dad, it's okay.
I can take care of her.
I know how to make pancakes now.
Hey babe, that's beautiful.
She's supposed to be
taking care of you, you know.
That's how that's
supposed to work.
I want you to come live with me.
All right? I came into some
resources. I'm gonna get us a spot.
It's gonna be nice, all right?
Mama says I can't live with
you because you kill people.
That's not true. That's
a lie. She's lying to you.
Daddy...
I know you do bad things.
Don't worry. I still love you.
Come on.
And you caught him?
Not me.
I just gave an anonymous tip
to the right guy in Gotham city.
I'mma figure this out.
All right?
It's over, Deadshot.
I don't want to do this
in front of your daughter.
Daddy, please.
Zoe, move!
Please Daddy. Don't do it.
Please.
Don't do it.
All right.
I love you, Daddy.
So now we have the
man who never misses.
Where'd you put him?
Let's just say. I put him in a
hole and threw away the hole.
Harley Quinn.
Accomplice to the
murder of Robin
ARKHAM
Before she ran off
and joined the circus...
she was known as
Dr. Harleen Quinzel.
A psychiatrist at Arkham asylum.
She was assigned
to the clown himself.
Dr. Quinzel.
You know, I live for
these moments with you.
What do you got?
I got you a kitty.
So thoughtful.
She thought she
was curing him...
but she was falling in love.
There is something you
could do for me, doctor.
Anything. I mean, yeah.
I need a machine gun.
A machine gun?
Talk about a workplace
romance gone wrong.
Get off me! Get...!
What do we have here?
I did everything you
said. I helped you.
You helped me by erasing my mind
what in memories I had!
Now,
you left me in a black
hole of rage and confusion.
Am I not the medicine
you practice, Dr. Quinzel?
What are you gonna do?
You gonna kill me, Mr. J?
What?
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm just gonna hurt ya...
really, really bad.
You think so?
Well, I can take it.
I wouldn't want you to break
those perfect porcelain cap teeth
when the juice hits your brain.
La la. La la la.
They became the king
and queen of Gotham city.
And god help anyone who
disrespected the queen.
We finally meet.
He don't shake hands.
But sit down and have a drink.
Hey, J.
On behalf of everybody,
welcome back.
I wanted to come by and
personally say thank you.
You making me good money.
I'm making you good money.
Are you sweet talking me?
Ha. Ha. Ha.
I love this guy.
He's so intense!
You're lucky man.
You got a bad bitch.
Oh, that she is.
The fire in my loins.
The itch in my crotch.
The one, the only, the
infamous Harley Quinn!
Oh, come to Daddy.
- Puddin'!
- Oh yeah.
Listen..
You are my gift to this
handsome hunka hunka!
You belong to him now.
Well.
You're cute!
You want me?
I'm all yours.
I don't want no beef.
You don't want no beef?
- Why, what's wrong? You don't like me?
- You don't want no beef?
Fine. Don't waste my time then.
This is your lady.
Look...
Are you enjoying yourself?
No.
That's your lady, Joker.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Yo, J.
And that was just the beginning.
Come on, puddin'. Do it!
Oh...
We have got company.
Batsy, Batsy, Batsy.
She's crazier than him.
And more fearless.
Stupid bat, you're
ruining date night!
Puddin'.
Puddin', I can't swim!
But the bat got her, too.
She's in the same
hole as Deadshot.
And then there's the Aussie.
Digger Harkness.
Or as the tabloids call
him. Captain Boomerang.
Captain Boomerang
Fetishes — Pink unicorns
We're gonna be rich.
Yeah, you and me, mate.
Go and get the car.
He robbed every bank
in Australia at least once.
Then he came to America
for a fresh target set.
Doesn't work well with others.
No honor among thieves, eh?
But he tangled with a
metahuman and lived to tell about it.
And have you heard of
the pyro kinetic homeboy?
How'd you catch him?
We didn't. He surrendered.
Chato Santana.
On the streets they
call him El Diablo.
This LA gangbanger thought
he was the king of the world...
until he lost his queen.
Gets jumped in a prison riot
and incinerates half the yard.
The security
video is incredible.
Oh, Jesus.
- What the hell is that?
- His name is Waylon Jones.
Evolution took a step
backwards with this one.
Yo, K.C! It's supper.
Go ahead, open that up, B.
Got something real
nice for you today, boy.
Hey boss, is it true he
chewed the dude's hand off?
Look at that, right
there, vulcanized rubber.
Give me that, Smitty.
Where you at?
Don't make me get you.
They call him Killer Croc.
There you are, are you hungry?
You want some food?
Go ahead, feed the man.
What are you in
the mood for tonight?
I got a double cheese burger,
onion rings, a little coleslaw.
Or a giant skinless goat?
He looked like a monster.
So they treated
him like a monster.
Then he became a monster.
He was chased out
of Gotham by the Bat.
Went searching for
sanctuary elsewhere.
He never found it.
I saved the best for last.
The Witch.
A witch?
I'm talking a flying, spell-casting,
making-shit-disappear witch.
A sorceress from another
dimension. Another world.
Archaeologist Dr. June Moone...
wondered into the wrong cave.
June...
She opened something
she shouldn't have...
releasing a metahuman more
powerful than any we've encountered.
The enchantress.
Enchantress aka Dr. June Moone
she inhabits
Dr. Moone's body now.
Where is this witch?
In my pocket.
Now tell him why she
won't turn you into a frog.
Some say the witch has
a secret buried heart...
and whoever finds it
can control the witch.
So we searched the cave
where she turned up...
and we found her heart.
- That thing's her heart?
- Mmm.
She's vulnerable without it.
You want to put our national
security in the hands of...
witches, gangbangers,
and crocodiles?
Don't forget about
the Joker's girlfriend.
These are villains, Amanda.
What makes you think
you can control them?
Because getting people to act
against their own self-interests...
for the national security of the
United States is what I do for a living.
You take the finest special forces
officer this nation has ever produced...
Colonel Rick Flag.
Help me.
I assigned him to watch
Dr. Moone, and just as I hoped...
it got personal.
Are you gonna kiss me or not?
I have the witch's heart.
And Dr. Moone has his.
Now he'll follow my
orders as holy writ.
In a world of flying
men and monsters...
this is the only way
to protect our country.
The Pentagon — Washington DC
What if Superman had decided to fly down,
rip off the roof of the White House...
and grab the President of the United
States right out of the overall office?
Who would've stopped him?
We got contingency plans
for nukes in North Korea...
Anthrax in our mail. We
got fluoride in our water.
But what happens if
the next Superman...
becomes a terrorist?
Amanda Waller
has a plan. Amanda.
I wanna build a team of some very
bad people who I think can do some good.
Like fight the next war,
defeat the next Superman.
Not on my watch.
You're not putting those monsters
back out on the street in our name.
General, we run them covertly
non-attributed. Strictly need to know.
And if they get caught, we
throw them under the bus.
The next war will be fought
with these metahumans.
Ours, or theirs.
We're not the only ones
kicking up rocks looking for them.
You know we can't
control these people.
June, be strong.
Dr. Moone.
Enchantress.
Meet the enchantress.
Everything we know about
her, is in your briefing packs.
She's walked this
earth for a very long time
and will likely be here
when we're long gone.
This meeting is-is
now a magic show?
Magic or not, this girl can do
some pretty incredible things.
Go get it, girl.
How about a little something from
the Weapons ministry vault in Tehran?
We've been chasing
these plans for years.
Please don't touch me.
Thank you. We'd
like Dr. Moone back.
Enchantress.
Please. Please.
I'm sorry. I can't-I
can't do that again.
Flag, get her out of here.
I move to...
authorize Amanda Waller to establish
Task Force X under the Argus program.
All right.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
I know you do bad things.
Don't worry. I still love you.
Welcome to Belle Reve,
special security barracks.
How you doing, man?
Why don't you kiss her
ass? She's in charge.
Welcome, ma'am. How are you?
I'm here to assist
you in anyway.
Where are they?
Are you the devil?
Maybe.
Ain't you scared?
Why'd they put you down here?
I asked.
Open that gate.
Yo, ese.
Hola, amigo.
Put that burrito down.
You got visitors, man.
What's up? Hey, you
want some of this?
Come down here.
That ain't me.
That wasn't you?
Nah, they say it's
me, but that ain't me.
That guy's gone.
He's dead.
And yet, here you are.
Ma'am.
Let me try to talk to him.
You wanna die in here, buddy?
You got a real shot at
walking at the block again.
Have a nice cold
beer, a nice meal.
A women.
Look, man...
You ain't the first to ask, and
you ain't gonna be the last.
Ask what?
I'm a man, okay?
I ain't no weapon.
I'mmna die in peace
before I raise my fists again.
I've caused enough harm.
Bye.
All right, unlock him.
What?
You heard me.
You know what this man can do?
I'm here to find out.
Lose the restraints.
Thank you.
What? This uh...
cheerleading tryouts?
Let's go. Let's see
what you can do.
They say you
never missed a shot.
Prove it.
Now you got one in the chamber.
What cha' gonna do with it?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey!
- Shit!
- Drop it.
Give me the word,
boss. I'll drop him.
Everybody calm down.
Griggs, tell your
men to stand down.
Tell them to put it down.
Stand down!
Colonel, for the record, this is
exactly what I was concerned about!
What's for dinner?
Ames, if this man shoots me...
I want you to kill him...
And I want you to go
clear my browser history.
See...
The firing pin is
filed down, right?
Mag full of dummy rounds.
If I pull the trigger,
nothing happens.
You're absolutely right.
Why would we give a loaded
weapon to an infamous hitman?
Go ahead, pull
the trigger. Empty it.
Don't empty nothing. You
don't even know this lady.
I've known you,
like, nine months.
Remember when I brought you
that cookie? That was a real cookie.
Aw, shit.
What?
Shit.
Oops.
Oh...
Y'all jokers must be crazy.
All right. Now you
know what you're buying.
Let me tell you
the price. First...
I want outta here.
Second, I want full
custody of my daughter.
All right?
And her mom can have
like... supervised visits.
But her stank ass
boyfriend can't come.
Darnell can't come.
- Darnell's out.
- He's out.
Third, y'all gonna pay for my
daughter's whole education.
Best schools.
And then I want
her to go to college
like Harvard or Yale.
- Ivy league.
- Ivy league, yeah.
- One of them big joints, you know?
- Mm-hm.
And if she can't cut it, and
her grades start slipping,
- I need you to white-people that thing.
- Mm-hm.
- You know how y'all do.
- Oh yeah.
You know, right? Okay.
Now that's my price.
But I'm concerned, 'cause I
don't see nobody writing shit down.
You're in no position
to make any demands.
Oh. I'm sorry.
You thought I
was talking to you.
No, errand boy.
I'm talking to your boss.
That's my price, sweetie.
You know what it is.
You notice these
are criminals? Mm.
They're psychotic antisocial
freaks. It makes no sense.
Let me hit the tier one
units and I'll build you
a team of pipe hitters who'll
do anything you can dream up.
I mean, you need real
soldiers. Not these scumbags.
In World War 2, the US Navy
made a deal with the mafia
to protect it's ships
on the waterfront.
This ain't World War 2.
It's World War 3.
What are you really up to?
It's a "need to know", and, all you
need to know is you work for me.
That can change
with a phone call.
I have friends too, you know.
There you go. Call'em.
But without you minding
her, your lady friend stays here
strapped to a board in
a drug-induced coma.
They warned me about you.
My dumbass didn't
believe the stories.
Nobody does.
Where is she?
It's complex.
This is not just her.
Everybody's disappeared.
There's this new law, where if
you're a bad enough bad guy,
they stamp "terrorist"
on your jacket.
They send you to this
swamp in Louisiana.
A black site.
That's where she is.
So what do we do?
Bring the car around.
We're going for a drive.
Lester. Lester. Hit
me one more time!
And... Come on, man!
You gotta call upstairs and
tell them to float me another 10k.
- You got it?
- Hey.
- Boss wants to see you.
- You know who I am?
Good job, man.
He's killing it.
Come on, man. Why am I here?
All right! Yeah! I'm
down. I get it, all right?
I've had a run of bad decks.
Not my fault.
All right?
Dude, this is real.
I had to stop these guys
from burning down your house
with your kids in it.
But, you're lucky.
Yeah, maybe. Why-why
do you think so?
Yo, slick. What's up?
Griggs. You are?
You might wanna
keep your mouth shut.
Can I go, man? What
the hell's going on, man?
This is crazy.
Blah, blah-blah, blah-blah,
blah-blah, blah-blah.
All of that chitchat
is gonna get you hurt.
Oh! My god.
I could tell you meant that.
Yeah.
You're gonna be my friend.
Enchantress.
Log time of death, 16:20
June?
- Let's get her down to the morgue.
- June?
June?
June.
What did you do?
Shhh.
Okay.
Sister.
Brother.
Plus, it could be
the routing number.
Wanna go for drinks?
I got this.
Enchantress.
God damn it!
June... June!
June, I'm sorry.
June.
She... she went somewhere.
If you have to choose
between her or me...
Stop her.
Promise me you'll stop her.
Even if it kills me.
Sir?
Sir, you okay?
Can you breathe?
Did you take anything?
This is 21. Send
medical to my location.
I'm a physician.
Roger. Bringing
medical to your location.
No pulse. Starting compressions.
Sir.
Midway City is under attack.
It's a non-human entity.
I think you know
what to do, sir.
Activate Task Force X
and get Amanda Waller
and her whole
circus on scene asap.
Yes, sir.
We're goin' live with
Task Force X. Pull 'em.
Prisoners, get down
on your knees. Now!
Down on your knees!
Hands in the air! Turn around.
Hands up high!
Hey, I'm cooperating. All right?
- This is me being cool.
- Take her.
Do not fire that goddamn weapon!
Damn it!
Open the gate!
Everybody, line
up for extraction.
Let's go! Let's move, move!
Yeah! Open the door! Let's go!
- Alright. Go! Go!
- Move it! Move it!
Hit him!
Hurry up, before he smokes us!
Where you at?
Whoa!
Is that the new guy?
What is that?
- Who are you?
- Standby, arming device.
Who are you? I don't
know who you are.
- Device armed.
- Hey.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Injection successful.
Location verified.
Anybody who touches me is dead.
Anybody who tou... ahh!
Lady.
- Injection successful.
- Hey.
- Hey! Miss? What was that?
- Location verified.
- Oh.
- Next!
Oh, you deaf. You
one of them deaf hoes.
- Oh.
- All right, all right. Come on.
Shut up, and get it done.
Weeee.
Listen, you're being transferred.
I don't know where you're going.
It's from Mr. J.
You gonna tell him
I took care of you?
You're so screwed.
What do you mean by that?
Get off me! Get off me!
Harley, what do
you mean by that?
Harley!
Hey, I got a delivery. I have
a gift basket for Dr. Van Criss.
You're not on the access
list. I can't let you in. Sorry.
Hey, cool. Can I
leave it with you?
I'm way behind today.
Thank you. You're a good man.
Open up.
Just please, do
whatever they say.
Do whatever they
say. Just do it.
This look neat.
Light it up! Light
it up! Light it up!
He's right above us.
This is a mistake.
Rick, I can't do this.
- I can't...
- Listen. Listen.
There's no other way.
Just get it done.
Enchantress.
Flag, talk to me. What'
going on down there?
Amanda, she bolted.
Say it again?
She bolted!
Shit!
Go!
Worldwide military is on alert.
Our weapons are ineffective.
I thought this was contained!
Pull everyone back
to the evacuation zone.
Guys, I need all three
of you, follow me please.
Anybody a universal donor?
Anybody with blood.
Bring those two over here.
Blunt trauma, right forehead!
This is the worst
day of my life.
All evacuees must report
to a FEMA representative.
What's going on in that city?
Those assholes here yet?
Yeah, they're here.
Alpha, bravo team, on me.
What the hell, Flag?
Unlock 'em.
Hi, boys! Harley Quinn.
How do you do?
Huh?
What was that?
I should kill everyone
and escape?
Sorry.
The voices.
I'm kidding. Jeez.
That's not what
they really said.
What do we got here?
12 pounds of shit
in a 10-pound sack.
Welcome to the party,
Captain Boomerang.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey...
What's going on, man?
Calm down.
Hey, one minute I'm playing
Mahjong with me Nanna...
then this red streak
hits me outta nowhere.
Shut up! You were caught
robbing a diamond exchange.
I was not.
Here comes slipknot...
The man who could
climb anything. Wonderful.
Have a good time, scumbag.
Straighten up.
She had a mouth.
Listen up!
In your necks...
Injection you got,
it's a nanite explosive.
It's the size of a rice grain but
it's powerful as a hand grenade.
You disobey me, you die.
You try to escape, you die.
You otherwise irritate or
vex me, and guess what?
You die.
I'm known to be quite vexing.
I'm just forewarning you.
Lady, shut up!
This is the deal.
You're going
somewhere very bad...
to do something
that'll get you killed.
But until that happens...
You're my problem.
So was that like a pep talk?
Yeah. That was a pep talk.
There's your shit.
Grab what you need for a
fight. We're wheels up in 10.
You might wanna work on
your team motivation thing.
- You heard of Phil Jackson?
- Yeah.
He's like the gold
standard, okay?
Triangle, bitch. Study
what?
Yo, get out of here.
Won't fit anymore?
Too much junk in the trunk?
Nah.
Every time I put this
on, somebody dies.
And?
I like putting it on.
Goody.
Something tells me a whole
lotta people are about to die.
Yeah, it's us.
We're being led to our deaths.
Speak for yourself, mate.
Hey, what's that crop on
your face? Does it wash off?
Hey, if you like a girl, can you
light her cigarette with your pinkie?
Because that
would be real classy.
Hey, y'all might wanna
leave old boy alone.
He could torch this whole joint.
Ain't that right, ese?
Ain't got nothing to
worry about from me.
I'm cool, homie.
Behold the voice of god.
For those of you who
don't know me officially...
My name is Amanda Waller.
There's an active terrorist
event in Midway City.
I want you to enter the city,
rescue HVT-1 and get them to safety.
I'm sorry.
For those of us who don't
speak good guy, what is HVT-1?
The only person that
matters in the city,
the one person you can't kill.
Complete the mission, you
get time off your prison sentence.
Fail the mission, you die.
Anything happens
to colonel Flag,
I'll kill every
single one of you.
Remember, I'm watching.
I see everything.
There's your pep talk.
Compared to your
shit, she killed it.
So that's it?
What, we some kind
of suicide squad?
I'll notify your next of kin.
Alpha, bravo team. Mount up!
Your' late.
I was busy.
I beg you.
Please have mercy.
This is Katana.
She's got my back.
She can cut all of you in
half with one sword stroke...
Just like mowing the lawn.
I would advise not
getting killed by her.
Her sword traps the
souls of its victims.
Harley Quinn.
Nice to meet you.
Love your perfume.
What is that? The
stench of death?
Whoa. Easy, cowgirl.
Ain't that kind of
mission. Have a seat.
She seems nice.
I'm coming for you.
Shhh...
Hey.
Is he suppose to
be green like that?
Oh. Party foul.
Not cool.
Ooo. Look at that pretty lights!
Are you guys seeing this?
What happened?
Terror attack.
Dirty bombs, bad guys
shooting up the place with AKs.
You know, usual shit.
Right.
Yeah, you're a bad liar.
I don't know if they told
you... But I'm a hitman.
I'm not a fireman. I
don't save people.
Anything for a dollar, right?
You know the dark places,
too. Don't act like you don't.
I'm a soldier.
And you're a serial killer
who takes credit cards.
When the shooting
starts, and it will,
you'll cut and run.
6-1 is going down.
6-1 is going down hard.
Stand by. Drop the
ramp. Drop the ramp.
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Go, go! Come on!
All right. All right.
All right. Relax.
What a ride!
We're okay. We're okay.
Assets are undamaged.
Mind games.
- What's that?
- All this bomb in the neck crap.
That ain't real, mate
see, they're trying to trap
us with our own minds, right?
But you look around,
we're free, brah.
How do you know this?
Just trust me. I know,
all right? It's a con.
Now I'm going,
because I got a life to live.
Question is, are you coming?
- Yeah.
- Smart.
Where're you going?
Hold your fire.
Sorry. It's what I do.
Nanite detonation control armed
Damn it.
Now that's killer app.
Okay. You wanna keep playing
the Hollywood squares version
of "I'll blow your freaking head off?"
Are you next?
You tripping, homie.
You next, Deadshot?
Did you just threatened me?
Oh, yeah.
He just threatened me.
Move.
You have a boyfriend?
All right, I'm gonna kill him.
Well, you better make it quick 'cause
he's gonna kill all of us one by one.
I'm gonna drop him, the sword
lady. 5 or 7 of these SEALs.
After that, I'm gonna
need some help, you down?
Always. What about
the shit in our necks?
Your friend's gonna help
us out with that, right?
You're my friend, too.
Stay evil, doll face.
Spread the word.
So, I'm thinking if we move
together we can kill all of these guys
and go our separate ways, yeah?
Sounds good.
Spread the word.
Psst, Hoy. Hoy.
We need your help, man.
When the time is right,
you hit Flag with a fireball,
he'll be too busy burning to death
to have a go at us with his final doom.
Then what?
Then we get out of here.
And do what?
What are you, a bloody socker?
Ease with all the questions.
Freedom, man.
Freedom, you
remember that, don't you?
We're criminals,
you know that, right?
Yeah, it's great.
Come on, do the bastard.
Hey, be careful.
- He eats people.
- Solemn mother superia, what?
He eats people for reals, homie.
He's a cannibal.
Ah.
No.
What did you say to him?
Nothing. Just having a laugh.
No worries.
I'm standing by for
follow on tasking.
C2, what is the
operational load of the PLS?
Boss, we got people up here.
I'm on my way.
Shit!
Amanda, we have
hostiles up ahead.
Flag, get out of there.
We're not here to fight them.
We know that doesn't work.
Copy that.
We're diverting.
Bump out second
squad two blocks east.
We'll pass through you,
continue north.
Take bravo two blocks east.
We'll leapfrog through
you once you're in position.
Copy that.
Hey.
I like these odds, mate.
You just say the word.
Yeah.
Come on.
Yeah. Uh.
Hold that thought.
Rick, why do
they look like that?
Stay cool.
What the hell are they?
You cut and run. I'll
blow your head off.
Damn it.
Hit 'em!
Huh.
Hey.
Get off me!
Get off me, you son of a...
Flag!
- Good riddance.
- Harley!
He dies, we die.
- Thanks.
- Shut up.
Backblast, clear!
Pinky.
That's how I cut and run.
Hey.
Hey, come on.
What? I saw it move.
See? It flinched. I think.
Hey. You were
some help, Princess.
It's better this way.
Trust me.
Oh, yeah. You're
the fire bloke. Eh?
- Yeah, I was. Yeah.
- Right, yeah. Hey.
Well, looky here.
It's fire!
The brief said terrorist.
- You want to start explaining this?
- If I told you, would you believe me?
- What are they?
- I don't know.
That's bullshit.
Thing is, he owned
a $3000 watch.
Is that a person?
It was.
Now it's not.
Hey, don't!
What?
We got a job to do.
We're moving.
Get your boys moving.
Let's go.
Waller, we are moving
on the objective.
We lost contact with
bravo, you got a visual?
Stand by. Anything
on the other squad?
No, ma'am.
Go-7, I need your sensors
in those coordinates.
Flag, it's a negative. They
were engaged when you were,
but we lost them.
Seriously?
What the hell is
wrong with you people?
We're bad guys. It's what we do.
Hey, Deadshot,
I've been thinking.
We don't come together, no
one walking out of here alive.
Mm. And?
These people respect
you, you got influence.
- What's your play right now?
- You're a man of your word, right?
I want my mission.
And you want your
life and your kid back.
You help me keep this
motley corporate in line,
I'll hook you up.
While there is
the puppet master,
- you ain't got shit to hook me up with.
- I got plenty of my own strings to pull.
You just get me to the
top of that target building
and get my rescuee
on that extraction helo...
- And you're going to make sure I get paid?
- Yeah, you get paid.
You get paid and you
get your fresh start.
Take a knee.
Our body's at the
top of that building.
We get up there...
Pull them out of the
vault they're hiding in.
Helos extract us off the roof.
- It's Miller time.
- Check.
Flag, who's up there?
It's none of your concern.
- Do you know who's up there?
- Nope.
You...
You're not leaving me.
You're not leaving me!
You, you, you are
a pain in the ass.
I have done everything your said,
every test, every trial, every initiation.
I have proved I love
you, just accept it.
Gada gada gada ga...
I am not someone
who is... loved.
I'm an idea,
state of mind.
I execute my will according
to my plan and you...
Doctor, are not
part of my plans.
Please let me in. I promise...
Let me in. I promise
I won't hurt you.
Promise? Promise?
Hey, dickface!
Mind screaming at your
bitch somewhere else.
I was going to say, "I
wouldn't do that if I were you."
Don't hurt me.
I'll be your friend.
Do it. Do, do, do, do, do it.
My heart scares you
and a gun doesn't?
DO IT!
If you weren't so crazy,
I'd think you're insane.
Go... away.
Harlet, you coming?
Why do you eat people?
Give me power.
Would you like to eat me?
- Hell, no.
- Aw, why not?
I don't want your crazy.
Says the guys who
lives in a sewer.
At least I know it's a sewer.
Oh, I get it.
Because it's like,
this is a sewer too.
Only with nice shops
and restaurants, right?
You hate mankind much?
Let me guess.
Mommy didn't take you to Chuck
E. Cheese on your 6th birthday.
I can recommend
a good therapist.
Why?
Because I'm bored.
I need a victim, a mind
to pry apart and spit in.
You just leave it, mate.
She's a rabbit hole, don't fall in.
And here's one now.
Japanese, female,
mid-twenties, 5 foot 5, good health,
athletic and...
an only child,
with deep-seated father issues.
Daddy wanted a son, so
she has to hide behind a mask.
I am not... hiding.
Yeah, that was gangster.
Harley, why don't you stop
acting like a drunken stripper.
You want to tell me what
the hell is going on then?
Because...
I smell a rat.
If they don't blow
our heads off,
we'll have to fight
our way out of this city.
I need you to play nice
with the other children.
And quietly return to my cage.
Sure. Okay.
Hey, that's okay.
Sellout, I get it.
Like you. I know how
the world works, okay?
And when it comes to the heart,
everyone for themselves, right?
Waller?
We're about to enter the
building. Get that chopper ready.
What you say we
get this over with?
What the hell? Deadshot.
Fall back.
You mind if we tag along?
Looks like we have
a spot of luck, eh?
Be a walk in the park.
Easy peasy.
Don't make me shoot you.
God damn it. Harley!
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
I am close be ready...
Hey, guys!
Come on. Let's go.
Ma'am.
I got motion detectors
going off on the secure floors.
Flag.
- They're all around you.
- Hold.
Use extreme caution.
I don't like this, Flag.
I don't like it either.
Pussy.
I will knock your ass out.
I do not care
that you're a girl.
They're after Flag again!
Son of a bitch! Get off me!
Circle up! Circle around him!
Let me fight!
You die, we die.
Clear! Everyone move out.
- Where've you been, homie?
- This ain't my fight!
You know what? You
don't stand for shit.
You ain't about shit!
Don't touch me, man!
- Don't touch you?
- Don't touch me!
What you gonna do? I'm
touching you! I'm touching you!
- Do something.
- Don't touch me!
Do something!
- You wanna see something?
- Yeah, I wanna see...
- Yes, I wanna see something!
I was just trying
to get you there.
Phil Jackson, we good, right?
I knew you'd come through.
That's shit crazy.
Clear.
I gotta work on my cardio.
Question.
Would you die for me?
Yes.
That's too easy.
Would you...
Would you live for me?
Hm?
Yes.
Careful.
Do not say this
oath thoughtlessly.
Desire becomes surrender.
Surrender becomes power.
You want this?
I do.
Say it.
Say it. Say it.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty,
pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty...
Please.
God, you're so...
Good.
Oh, relax.
It's just me.
You ever been in love?
Nah, never.
Bullshit.
You don't kill as many people as
I've killed and still sleep like a kitten
if you feel shit like love.
Another textbook sociopath.
Clear.
- Nice.
- Clear the roof.
Sweep for shooters so we
can bring in our aviation assets.
Go to the roof.
Just oh...
Wait here.
Please.
I don't wanna gave this
dude a heart attack, okay?
Aww. He's embarrassed of us.
Hey, Flag.
This dude better cure
cancer after all of this shit.
You ready? Let's go.
You wouldn't have
made it without them.
We got lucky. I don't do luck.
I do planning and precision.
Admit it, Rick. I was right.
Yeah, I told you to
get on the damn truck.
Why did you stay?
I was studying your girlfriend.
She takes an average person...
A yoga mom, an elderly retiree
and she turns them into a soldier
who can take a
headshot and still fight.
It's an instant army.
How'd she do it, Flag?
How'd she game the system
with you watching her every move?
I'll accept the consequences
I am your consequence.
You might need to be careful.
They think we're
rescuing Nelson Mandela.
I can take care of myself.
- Shut it down, wipe the drivers.
- Yes, ma'am.
Copy that.
Hey man, I know
you can't hear me
'cause you're trapped in your
temple of soldierly self-righteousness.
But a two-faced dude like you
wouldn't survive a second on the street.
Oh, says the guy who
shoots people for money.
My cards is on the table, man.
It got done, didn't it?
Damn. That is just...
a mean lady.
Yeah, you'll get used to it.
And I'm the bad guy?
That's gangsta.
What?
They weren't cleared
for any of this, any of it.
I'm not judging. I've
buried a lot of mistakes too.
No way.
Let's go home.
Yeah, let's go home.
That sounds good. You
guys wanna go home?
Or you wanna go back to prison?
I'm not going back to prison.
What I'm saying is...
We kill the pair of 'em
now before they kill us.
I got this.
You all made it this far.
Don't get high-spirited on
me and ruin a good thing.
I like her.
Savior 1-0, this
is ground element.
Savior 1-0, how copy?
Savior 1-0, the LZ's clear.
Boss, they're not talking to me.
Our bird's been jacked.
Light it up!
What? I got a
hickey or something?
Professor, could
you pick up the pace?
Disarmed.
Now!
Harley!
Hello, baby.
Kill her!
Fail - safe mode.
Her nanite's disarmed!
Come on, baby.
Deadshot...
Shoot that woman, right now!
She ain't do shit to me.
You're a hitman, right?
I got a contract.
Kill Harley Quinn.
Do it your freedom and your kid.
Now she dead.
I missed.
Good one, mate.
It's Waller.
Savior 1-0's been
hijacked. Shoot it down.
Roger that, ma'am. Going hot.
Puddin'!
You got all dressed up for me?
Oh, you know I'd
do anything for you.
By the way...
I've got some grape soda on
ice, and a bear skin rug waiting.
Yeah?
Boss, we got a problem!
- This bird is baked.
- No.
Okay, honey. It's me and you.
Let's do it.
Target destroyed, ma'am.
Thank you. Now
get me off this roof.
Yes, ma'am. We're inbound.
The Joker and Harley
Quinn are no more.
You couldn't save her.
Roger, I see you.
Watch your step, ma'am.
Standby, I'll send another helo!
Waller's down.
It's over.
Ops just confirmed.
She's down, 1k west.
Let's go get her.
The mission's not over.
Nah, it is for me.
We had a deal.
Without Waller, you got nothing.
Hey, guys. I'm back!
I missed you all so much.
We're glad you could make it.
Hey, craziness.
With my heart returned,
I can finish my weapon.
Now tell me how to
destroy your armies.
Do your worst, bitch!
So, let me guess.
We're going to the swirling
ring of trash in the sky.
You know, 'cause
why wouldn't we?
When does this end, Flag?
Load up. We're in for a fight.
Top secret.
You tell everybody, everything.
Or me and you are
gonna go right now.
3 days ago,
a non-human entity
appeared in the subway station.
Waller, we're almost there.
So Waller sent me and a
woman with incredible abilities.
Enchantress
a witch.
See, nobody could
get near this thing, but...
the witch could.
Bomb's ready.
Set for two seconds.
You just press the
button and drop it.
Needless to say the
whole thing was a bad idea.
She bolted!
Shit!
And that's how she
escaped from Waller.
So now you know.
You can just kill
me right now but...
I'm going to have a drink.
Hey, Deadshot, I need your help.
No, sir. You need a miracle.
What's you having, KC?
Bloody Mary, right?
Rick goes to mind.
KC, it's the end of the world.
Have a drink with us.
Beer.
There he is. Give the man a "B".
How about you, hot stuff?
Water.
That's a good idea, honey.
Ninja, you want some sake?
Whisky.
What am I, twelve?
Here's to honor among thieves
I'm not a thief.
Oh. She's not a thief.
I actually prefer to think of myself
as an asset relocation specialist.
Well, we almost pulled it off.
Despite what everybody thought.
We weren't picked to
succeed, you know that, right?
We were all chosen to fail.
Yeah, I know that.
Worst part of it is, they're gonna
blame us for the whole thing.
And they can't have
people knowing the truth.
We're the patsies.
The cover-up.
Don't forget,
we're the bad guys.
So, you're going to tell us now
what your big deal with Flag was.
Same thing Waller
offered me, to kill you.
Chance to be a father.
Chance to have a life
outside the shadows.
I trusted Flag.
Flag had you chasing a
carrot on a stick, homie,
you don't know that?
I love this guy.
You played yourself, dog.
Bitch, I'm having a drink.
I'm... breathing fresh air.
For 2 sweet seconds...
I had hope.
You had hope, huh?
Hope don't stop the wheel
from turning, my brother.
You preaching?
It's coming back around for you.
How many people you killed, man?
You don't ask nobody
no question like that, ese.
You ain't ever whacked
down no women.
No kids.
I don't kill women or children.
I do.
See, I was born
with the devil's gift.
I kept it hidden
most of my life, but...
the older I got,
the stronger I got.
So I started using it.
For business, you know,
the more power
on the street I got,
the more firepower I got.
Like that shit
went hand in hand.
You know, one was
feeding the other.
Ain't nobody tell me no.
Except my old lady.
You know, she
used to pray for me.
You're welcome.
Even when I didn't want it.
Six die in arson fire.
God didn't give me this.
Why should he take it away?
Hey.
This is our home.
You put that back
where you found it.
I'm taking my kids to mom's.
You ain't taking
my kids nowhere!
See, when I get
mad, I lose control.
You know, I just...
I don't know what I do...
Till it's done.
And the kids?
He killed them.
Didn't you?
Own that shit.
Own it!
What'd you think was
gonna happen, huh?
Hey, Harley. Come on.
What you were just...
thinking you can
have a happy family...
and coach little leagues
and make car payments?
Normal is a setting on the dryer.
People like us, we don't get normal!
Why is it always a knife fight…
every single time
you open your mouth?
You know, outside
you're amazing.
But inside, you're ugly.
We all are.
We all are!
Except for him.
He's ugly on the outside, too.
Not me, shorty.
I'm beautiful.
Yeah, you are.
We don't want you here.
You get to the part in that binder
saying I was sleeping with her?
Yeah.
I never been with a witch
before. What's that like?
Apparently that's why the
creatures chase him all the time.
'Cause the witch
is scared of him.
The only woman I
ever cared about...
is trapped inside that monster.
If I don't stop the witch,
it's over. Everything is over.
Everything.
You're free to go.
Your daughter
writes you everyday.
Every single day.
You had these the whole time?
You had letters from my
daughter the whole time?
I'm gonna get you there.
And you're gonna end this.
I'm gonna carry
your ass if I have to.
'Cause this shit is gonna
be like a chapter in the Bible.
Everybody's gonna
know what we did.
And my daughter is gonna
know that her Daddy…
is not a piece of shit.
I'll come.
What?
You got something better to do?
Come on!
Pussies.
We think that thing's a weapon.
Here, lower.
We gotta take out the big one.
I left a big ass demo charge
down there in that subway.
There's a flooded tunnel...
Leads right
underneath that building.
SEALs, they can recover the charge,
swim in underneath that thing's feet.
We get in it's face and distract
the hell out of that son of a bitch
so the swimmers
can blow the bomb.
That's how we take it out.
I'm going with you.
We got this.
I'm not asking, bro.
I live underground.
Y'all are just tourists.
The man who killed her
husband used that sword.
His soul's trapped inside of it.
She talks to him.
Hey. Well...
You know what they
say about the crazy ones.
Huh?
Let's do this.
You must really love this girl.
And I thought love was
bullshit, getting serious.
Desire, mutual benefit whatever.
I mean, I get that,
but... actual love?
I mean, I rated that with UFOs.
A lot of believers, no proof.
And then I met June.
Do what you got to do.
I got your back.
You gonna fight with us?
What if I lose control?
Then maybe we'll have a chance.
Duck in.
Hey, everyone can see all
this trippy magic stuff right?
Yeah, why?
I'm off my meds.
That's your old lady, huh?
Yeah.
Well, you need to
handle this shit, all right?
Get up there, smack on her ass,
tell her knock this shit off.
I do not think that'd be wise.
I'm gonna draw out the big one.
My boys will detonate
the bomb underneath him.
You know, we should
get a drink sometime.
I've been waiting
for you all night.
Step out of the shadows.
I won't bite.
What the hell? Grab her.
Why are you here?
Because the soldier led you?
And all for Waller?
Why do you serve
those who cage you?
I am your ally.
And I know what you want.
Exactly what you want.
Normal
normal.
Baby.
Baby. It's just a nightmare.
It's just a bad dream.
I'm here.
Miss me?
I'll put the kids to sleep and
then... maybe we can kick it?
Yeah?
I can't change what I
did. And neither can you!
He married me.
It's not real.
I killed the bat.
No, homie, you don't want that.
What? I want that.
She's trying to play games
with you, man. It's not real!
He's right.
It's not real.
How long have you
been able to see?
My whole life.
You can't have them.
These are my people right here.
But it is our time.
The sun is setting
and the magic rises.
The metahumans
are a sign of change.
Lady...
You are evil!
Oh, wow!
Uh-oh.
Who is this?
It's gonna be bad!
We should run.
GQ, come in. We're in position.
We gotta get him in that corner.
That's where the bomb will be.
I'll do it! I'll get him there!
I lost one family. I ain't
gonna lose another one.
Look, think it through.
I got this.
Let me show you
what I really am.
Over here!
Go!
Rick, in position. Standing by.
Diablo, drive him
into the corner!
- Get him mate.
- Come on.
Yeah, do it!
Diablo, get clear!
Get out of there!
Blow it!
Blow it.
Now GQ, now.
No!
Everybody down!
You next.
My spell is complete.
Once you and armies are gone, my
darkness will spread across this world.
And it will be mine to rule.
That was our main
satellite uplink.
How did this witch even
know how to target this thing?
It's a secret facility.
You got a move here, Flag?
We gotta cut her heart out!
Where is she?
I can't see her!
While we're fighting,
that thing is laying waste
to the whole damn world.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Hey. Oh shit.
Look out, look out!
Uh-oh.
Sorry.
Flag!
Enough!
Of all who have faced me...
You have earned mercy.
For the last time...
Join me...
or die.
I'm not much of a joiner but...
maybe we should.
Hey.
She's trying to
take over the world.
So?
What's the world ever
done for us anyway?
It hates us.
Hey. Harley.
Hey, lady?
I lost my puddin'.
But you can get him back, right?
I can, my dear.
Anything you want.
You promise?
Yes, child.
You need only bow...
and serve beneath my feet.
I like what you're
selling, lady.
There's only one teeny problem.
You messed with my friends.
Her heart's out!
We can end this.
Hey, Croc!
Harley!
Please, Daddy. Don't do it.
The only way for us to be together
is if you don't pull the trigger.
Daddy, I love you.
Please, don't do this.
That was a great shot, man.
Hey, I don't do hugs.
I'm not a hugger.
I'm not a hugger. All right?
Let me join my brother.
Katana, no!
Give me that.
You bring June back.
You bring her back.
She's not coming back.
I'll crush this.
Do you hear me?
You bring June
back or I'll crush this!
Go ahead.
You don't have the balls.
Hey, Flag.
June.
She's gone.
I thought I killed you.
Y'all don't mind. I got me
a sewer to crawl back into.
Yeah, and I got some business
to handle back in Gotham.
I'm going to hotwire
a car, need a ride?
Your ass is not driving.
Why not?
How are you not dead?
We-we just saved the world.
A "thank you" would be nice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, we did all of this
and we don't get shit?
10 years off your
prison sentences.
Nah, that's not enough.
I'm seeing my daughter.
That can be arranged.
An other requests?
An Espresso machine.
BET.
10 years off a
triple life sentence?
Darling, I'm walking
out of here a free man
or we're going to start
having some real fun.
Why don't have some fun?
You're trying to
figure out this length.
That's the hypotenuse.
So you have to know this angle.
Okay. So, if you're up here...
- like in a building.
- Mm.
And you shoot a man
down here on the street...
That's how far the
bullet actually goes?
Yeah. That's-that's right!
You are so smart. Right.
The hypotenuse, good one.
So that would make you
have to know the angle
between the building
and the sidewalk.
You got to know that angle.
You know, I mean, in real life
you got-you got variables.
You know, you got rifling twist.
You got chamber pressure.
You got bullet weight.
Some shots you'll even have to take
the curvature of the earth in with the...
It's time.
...wind effect.
You know, there's a
lot... a lot of variables...
in the street.
I gotta go.
Are you coming back?
Yeah.
I'm working it out. All right?
You know, I promised my friends
that I would just, you know, go without...
without killing them all.
Bring it in.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you.
Hey! Let me out!
Let me out of here right now!
Hey! You feel that? Yeah.
Let me out of here, darling, please.
Please, I'm begging you, seriously.
Listen to me. Have you got a
car? Because I'm a brilliant driver.
Come on!
Joker.
Puddin'!
Let's go home.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
This is crown jewels
here, Mr. Wayne.
And you do understand
my legal exposure.
If anyone knew what
I've procured for you...
Listen, I can keep a secret,
okay? What do you want?
People are asking
questions about Midway City.
The kind of people
who can get the answers.
And if they can get those
answers, my head will be on a pike.
Consider yourself under
my protection, if you deliver.
Moone, June
Allen, Barry.
Curry, Arthur.
Why, Mr. Wayne?
I just like to make friends.
That's the difference
between us.
You believe in friendship.
I believe in leverage.
Goodnight.
You look tired.
You should stop working nights.
You should shut it down,
or my friends and
I will do it for you.