xX-Subs by Sergeddu-Xx
Flight 1549, Clear to take off.
Flight 1549, Ready to take off
Mayday, Mayday, Captain 1549, We've lost both engines
Both engines!
No rely on motor 2
Captain 1549, ,We can get a view on runway 148
We can't make it, We're turning back to La Guardia
La Guardia Tower, Flight 1549
We're going to try to make 13
Sully, We are too low
Sully, We are too low!
Come on!
It's  set on fire!
Sully
Lory I love you!
What the hell is the matter with you?
Everyone, EVERYONE survived on flight 1549!
You think you'll die, that's what you think
And then, miraculously you don't!
Thank you Captain, Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you Captain Sullbenger for being here today.
I would also welcome First Officer Skiles
Glad you made it at this point.
Not aswell as  we are.
For the record, we have an aircraft system investigation,
and also aircraft structures, MRT
Aircraft perfomance, ATCS, life factors,
survival factors
nd also emergency response
Today we begin
with our operations,human performance and investigations.
On the crash of US Flight 1549
The water landing.
Captain?
This was not a crash, it was a water landing.
We knew what we were trying to execute
It was not a crash, it was a forced water landing.
Why didn't you attempt to return
to La Guardia?
There was simply not enough altitude
The Hudson was the only place long enough and smooth enough and wide enough to attempt a landing.
Air traffic testified that you were returning to La Guardia but you did not.
As I began the left turn,
I realized I couldn't make it back
and I would have eliminated other options
Returning to La Guardia would have been a mistake.
Let's get into how you calculated all those parameters.
There was no time for calculating.
I have relied on my experience on managing the altitude and speed
on thousand of flights over four decades.
You say you didn't calculated...
I attempted.
- You attempted.
Yes.
The best chance passengers had was on that.
And I bet my life on it.
In fact, I did!
And I would do it again.
Aviation engineers theorize you had enough energy to get back to the runway.
Engineers are not pilots.
They're wrong.
And they weren't there.
Regardless, we have to follow all implications
as part of the investigation.
Our computers analized scenarios
run algorithms, write
simulations with the exact parameters.
the engine loss,
the altitude, everything you faced
when you made your decision.
I would like to oversee those computer simulations
Not possible during the investigation.
You staid it was a dual engine failure
due to multiple blows with birds?
That would be unprecedented!
Everything is unprecedented, until it happens for the first time.
How much sleep did you get the night before?
Eight hours, enough.
It was possible that blood sugar was low?
I was rested, alerted, and completely aware of my surroundings.
When was your last dring, Captain Sullenbenger?
Nine days ago.
Droghe?
No, mai.
First Officer Skiles?
I don't drink, I never have.
Captain,
have you had any troubles at home lately?
Well, not more than anyone else.
And nothing that affected my work.
Bullshit.
But why are they looking for something we did wrong?
That turned out right.
It didn't turned out right for the Airline and their insurance company.
We should expect some blowback.
Oh like what they can say?
That we shouldn't have saved everybody?
That's not personal.
The're just doing their job.
Relax, calm down.
Sully, they should give you a medal
and send you back to work.
Sorry, this mailbox is full.
I didn't called Lori this morning, I'm guessing someone  else did
Not meaning to bother, but I have to say:
It is an honor driving you today.
Thank you.
What new have said so far? Two building went down,
Many millions without work, and that's the first weeks of January.
But today's headlines:
This is beautiful!
Hey Mike, why don't we get the driver as a character witness?
Finally.
Oh, finally.
The Airline has given us trapped all day.
It's just... I need to hear your voice.
I've heared everybody else's.
You'd be amazed how many cousins you have.
It doesn't feel much like family.
It isn't quiet here too.
There are reporters asking for an update.
Inside the mind of Sully.
Lori, tell them you can't talk.
I cannot hear you, just call me later.
You don't have to talk with them.
Call me back.
Do you've got any news?
Have you achiedeved the impossible?
I think there's the press with a car.
Self-Defense, think the juror would convinct?
Do what you have to do.
No, I'm asking for permission.
Cops will be coming after you.
Sully what are you doing?
Sully, are you listening to me?
We should talk later.
I've been reading all day.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just tired, that's all.
How are the girls?
Oh good.
A bit overwhelmed, sounds like you are too.
Yeah, I'll be alright.
The whole world is talking about you.
Sully, I can't believe this.
Lori, I'll have to stay here,
Until the investigation is over, Did I tell that already?
And I apologize if I didn't told you already.
You don't need to apologize,
You're right where you need to be.
You know, I did the best I could.
Of course you did.
You saved everyone.
Maybe we should just talk in the morning.
I'm tired.
I'm overwhelmed by all these attentions.
I'm gonna be on TV next Morning, what are they gonna ask me?
Sully do you want me to come be with you?
No Lori
The girls need you.
Tell them I love them.
I love you.
Get some sleep.
Yeah, maybe when I'll wake up it'll be January 14th.
Wouldn't that be good?
I love you.
Why did Captain Sully made that faithful decision to turn the Hudson into a runway?
Well, only he can answer.
But we now know, it was a wrong choice.
A choice that endangered the lives of all of those on board.
So, while much of the country hails him as a hero
this new information will certainly change everyone's understanding
of the so called Miracle on the Hudson
Sully Sullenberger, are you a hero,
or a fraud?
Hello?
Jeff? Sorry for calling you so late.
It's ok, There's no sleep in this room either.
Can you believe they charged 5 dollars for a Snickers?
I can take the Airline to bankruptcy with four bites.
I thought you may wanna talk!
-Absolutely
Let's get some air.
Great
I will be there in 5 minutes.
Enjoying the shakes?
Nightmares? Little Heartbeat?
A little bit. The Union is offering us Counseling.
Yeah, what would you say? You were in a plane crash and lived.
It might have an impact in your day to day.
I don't like not being in control of the process.
I won myself that
Within 6 months we'll laugh about
as we know David Letterman
We're doing David Letterman?
Yeah, right after next week's interview.
I'm guessing David's gonna be excited for you.
This is so surreal.
I guess I'm having some problems in separating reality
from whatever the hell this is.
Yeah, this is two man freezing their asses off
Sully,
Don't worry, you did a great day.
It's gonna be remembered for a very long time.
Here's a funny thing:
I've delivered over a million passengers over 40 years in the air
But in the end I'lm gonna be judged for 208 seconds
Come on, tomorrow it's gonna be a good day.
Computers will prove you're right, and you'll put your wings back on
You wanna run?
Yeah, let's run.
Fucking cold out here.
This was obvious, it was a critical situation
Losing both engines at a low altitude
Over one of the most populated areas of the planet
But you chose to land on the Hudson,
that was still a big IF
I was sure I could do it
You were?
Yes.
How do you feel when people call you a hero?
I don't feel like a hero.
I'm just a man who is doing his job.
The right man for the job
at the right time
You've been flying for what?
Nearly 40 years?
42, That's been my life
My whole life
Aircraft
Bomb-craft
I'll be busy son, so you
keep the plane clean please.
They are $ 6 per hour
Consider it a lesson time
Pilots never stop to acquire knwledge.
You'll make mistakes, everyone does.
Never forget, no matter what's happening,
to fly the airplane.
Absolutely, sir!
One other thing, and this is important!
Sir?
You can smile !
Alright!
I apologize for my sweating.
Oh no, After all you did I don't think
Katie could be more intimidating
Oh that wasn't Katie, It was the light
and the camera you brought in.
Ok, we're done.
That was from my mom.
Her name's Brenda,
She told me to say thank you and she's single!
Well, tell Brenda thank you,
but I got a girl at home.
Lucky woman
Sully, SULLY!
Sully, where are you?
I'm standing here calling your name.
What's up with you?
You need to get focused, because the media
requests Avalanche continues.
Yeah, yeah.
Larry Rooney volunteered to jump in and run Shotgun
with you the rest of the way
Thought you might need a friend.
He will take you to NTSB now.
AirBus completed computer simulations aswell
Good, Good, that will help!
There's something else
The Agency called,
The left engine was still operating
Not possible, I felt it go.
It was like it stopped in mid-air.
They said there's a chance it was sub-idle.
I'm just letting you know, since
the NTSB already does.
You've got to be kidding me.
Our job is to investigate.
Our plane ended up in the Hudson River.
Isn't it a little bit early for you
to go fishing?
Searching facts is not exactly go fishing, Mr Skiles,
Let's see the most important fact:
There were only two people who know what happened
in the cockpit that day,
and I'm one of them.
And we appreciate your perspective.
Why are we here today?
Is it because Captain Sullenberger
did not return to La Guardia?
Look, I just finished training on the AR320,
And I can tell you the only reason the plane operated so well
Is because the Captain turned on
The auxiliary power unit on
He simply followed the QRH
No, no he wasn't.
He wasn't following proper procedure at all.
And I know because I had the QRH in my hands.
He switched to APU immediately after engine blowback.
According to the Airbus that's the 15th thing to do.
If he followed the damn rules, we would be dead.
Maybe that's the part you don't like.
You have answers to your guessing
Look, he's just saying that I held the AR320 what it does
and  what it does to do
I held recountless CVR transcripts of deceased pilots and I have
significant accident investigation experience.
There is no question that you're a talented,
dedicated, experienced professional.
Every crash investigated before are not object of this investigation.
Only US Airways 1549 matters today.
Your Union has been advised, The data relate that the
left engine continued setting himself on during flight.
Then the Data is wrong
The evidence showed that the engine was Idle or Sub-Idle
immediately following the bird strike.
You show me the left engine
I show you dead birds and no power
The left engine was lost in the crash,
due to excessive damage on touchdown.
We could circle back to that later,
Let's just assume, as you say,
a dual engine loss.
Your weight was 151.510 pounds, wind and temperature, nort, north-west, 21 degrees,
speed and altitude 200 nods and 2818 feet.
Correct.
The computer simulations of US Airways Flight 1549 showed that
the Aviation Engineers were correct.
There was enough speed and altitude after the bird strike
for a succesful return to La Guardia
Succesful?
The plane landed at LaGuardia intact, undamaged.
You got that from one computer simulation?
No, 20.
Including attempts made from LaGuardia runways.
Every Computer simulation with the exact flight parameters
demonstrated that return to LaGuardia was possible.
And not just possible, probable.
Does anyone here needs further computer evidence?
Captain Sullenberger?
First Officer Skiles?
Not this time.
I would like to go over the parameters.
We'll make them available for the Union.
And once the Investigation is complete,
we'll be able to share the actual computer simulations
For now, they remain confidential.
We cannot afford a leak to the press.
There has been far too much talk for the press already.
When the complete cockpit voice is compiled, alongside with onboard
transcripts we'll call you back .
Thank you gentlemen.
Good day.
Thank you.
We weren't playing Pac-Man, we were flying a plane for human beings.
Some other, will have to remember it.
This just doesn't seem right
It's because this is not right
You did everything you could, that's more than enough.
Ask your passengers, Ask your wife and kids.
Ask Lori
So what's the first thing you heard from the cockpit?
Brace for impact
Now, ever heard of that before?
No, actually no
Ever heard of that in any aspect of your life?
Take this show away from me.
Jeff was relaxed and fine.
He should be getting over with other requests.
Are they paying you?
For all this media stuff at least?
No payment is necessary.
Oh, I wish the bank felt the same way
Why? What do you mean?
That's just....
We got another notice.
About the Space in View County.
Well, we'll find a tenant.
It just takes time.
You've been saying that for 9 months, Sully
It's still vacant
The economy has to take a turn.
It feels like, if we lose that space, the next
thing will be the house.
Lori, we're not gonna lose the house.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm just anxious, and alone and
not enough sleep.
Yeah, I didn't get enough sleep either.
I'm sorry adding to your stress but,
Just tell me you'll be back soon.
Well not until the NTSB has finished
the investigation.
We need you flying.
Lori, If this goes wrong, my career as safety expert, will end,
as the website and the business card.
I'm more worried about your career as a pilot.
What if I did blow this?
What are you saying?
What if I did things wrong, closing my career?
If I endangered the lives of those passengers.
Sully, Watch the news!
You're a hero!
And everyone is going to get used to it,
Including the NTSB.
First case scenario:
the NTSB lists me as the probable cause.
That's immediate retirement, no pension.
My life is done.
Ok you're scaring me now, Sully.
What's going on?
The left engine might have still been idle-ing.
And the AirBus Simulations said I could still have made it back
to La Guardia safely.
But it doesn't make sense.
That's in discussion with everything I felt in the cockpit.
Then why did you do that Sully?
A land in the water?
That's not the much dangerous thing you could have done!
Good afternoon.
The Tuna Vasel or The Heaven Shatter.
Tuna Vasel, Very Fresh!
Thank you
Too cold today, too much cold!
When are you gonna come fly with me?
When U.S. Airways starts to fly to Hidro-Bar.
I will talk, see if can work.
This is Thursday!
Suitcase is already stuffed with gifts for Will.
Always fun to get things in the Airport.
Seems you travel too.
Mom, he's turning 1.
Don't think he can know what gift came from where.
But I will.
Maybe a Snow Globe.
Something he will remember.
Something from New York.
You forgot when we were kids?
Okay sweetheart, I'll get you a Snow Globe too.
Fine. Come on.
Good afternoon.
Captain.
Hey guys, Jeff!
We're not gonna make it!
I believed in you for this trip,
Just meet us at the Gate ok?
Altimeters verified, 3023.
3023.
Checklist complete.
You really think there are recess?
Checking the latests reports, We could
make it all the way to Charlotte.
From steaks to Frisco, on me.
I've never been.And I hear good things
Oh, Rhubarb will break your heart.
Yeah, I'm more like Porker House man.
Porker House will stop your heart.
Wait, Wait Wait!
Hi, I'm sorry, Spirit sent us.
We cancelled and you said you have seats.
Flight is closed.
Wait, see that guy, looking up there?
That's my Dad, it's an emergency.
He's got to be on this flight.
Okay, everybody say the same.
Golf emergency.
Did it go cancelled?
IDs please.
How many travelling?
3.
Nothing together.
We'll find a way.
Here we go: 22A, 6A and 6C
Thank you so much!
Glad you made it!
You're on 6 Jeff.
Oh no that's Jimmy, I'm gonna get some sleep.
Are you going to sleep here?
Not close to you.
Yo, yo, Goodnight!
Sorry, Excuse Me.
Yeah, of course.
I'm sorry, he likes to throw everything.
That's perfect, I like to catch everything.
I googled you last night.
Found you on the company's website.
That's impressive.
Thanks.
I thought I was a good bullshitter, but you!
You could go Pro!
Just kidding, but your site do not worry
about 100 employees and headquarters in 3 states
When searching for more, I realized that it was just you.
Now, go easy. I'm just getting it done.
I've never been acused being a bullshitter.
Do not misunderstand!
It is a compliment.
Now, with that website, I know you!
Good afternoon ladies and gentlemen, welcome on board
US Airways Flight 1549.
Get sure to follow the safety instructions card on seatback in front of you,
explains safety features on thi aircraft, aswell as locations of emergency exits.
La Guardia, this is 1549, ready for clearance
Ok 1549, 128 ready and protected.
Get sure to turn that off.
Just once I'd like to go to La Guardia in time.
Well you know hot to get to La Guardia.
No, what's that?
Fly at JFK.
Take-out fuel quality verified.
19000 Cargo aboard.
Captain's 1549, Runway 4, Clear to take-off.
Captain's 1549,  Clear to take-off.
Positive rig
Nice view on the Hudson
I can't get over on how beautiful is up here.
Life's easier in the air.
I guess, it is.
BIRDS!
Oh shit!
I'm worried, what's going on?
It's okay.
It might be a good idea to keep your seatbelts on.
We've got one rolling back.
We have both rolling back.
Ignition start.
Restarting APU.
Just double check your seatbelts please.
Seatbelts.
What do you think it was?
I think it was a bird strike.
We'll have to turn back to La Guardia.
Yeah.
Get out the QRH
We've lost both engines.
Mayday, mayday this is Captain 1549, we hit birds.
We've lost both engines, we're turning back to La Guardia.
Ok, you need to return to La Guardia?
Turn left at 220.
Which engine did you lose?
Both, both engines.
Soup, I have an emergency.
What's the report?
Both engines, both engines gone.
LaGuardia says go to runway 13
Tower, stop your departures, we've got an emergency returning.
Flight 1549, bird strike.
We've lost both engines, return immediately.
He lost both engines.
Captain 1549, if you can get a view, do you want to try land on runway 13?
We are unable. We'll end up in the Hudson.
I've got an A320 diving in the river.
Al, stack the inbounds in La Guardia.
Let's put a load in the Tower please.
I need a runway, Captain 1549 needs to get in an airport right now.
Newer Tower, what did you got?
Runway 29 ready. Need an emergency landing?
Yes, I'll be right side as Ftaburogh
Shit.
This is the Captain
Brace for impact.
What?
Brace, Brace, Brace
Heads down, stay down!
Captain 1549, turn right to 3-0.
You can land on run way 1 0 now.
That's negative, We're landing in the Hudson.
I'm sorry, say again?
Captain 1549, radar contact lost.
IC, come on over here.
I've got also a newer copy at 2 o'clock, about 7 miles.
Captain 1549, if you can, you got runway 29
available at 2 o'clock, 7 miles.
I'm sorry Patrick.
No, he's about to Newark, he's just out of the box.
Hook'em back up.
We need authorized news.
Attention all aircraft in vicinity of JW,
We see the USS ship...
1549, low over the Hudson
I got eyes on him
Ok
Hang on the chopper visuals.
He's out there.
He's heading to Newark, 7 miles.
Only 7 miles.
Captain's 1549, this is Departure Control,
On Guard, do you read?
It's going down
Captain's 1549, do you read me?
Shit, it's going down!
It's gonna hit the water!
Testers are gonna come down.
Meet Eliza, it's the standard.
His voice was so calm!
When he said the Hudson, I wouldn't believe it!
This isn't happening.
We have took out survivors on water landings, didn't we?
Embrace
I better go.
I am so sorry.
I love you.
Yeah, I gotta go.
Choosing to land in the Hudson was a big IF!
The evidence showed that a return to LaGuardia was possible.
The left engine was sub-idle
This is tasty 11
I have an emergency landing by breakdown
Roger that.
Looks like hydraulics.
Sir, we need to catch up.
Running a control test.
We need more altitude.
Tower, this is Tacy 11 with flight control
Roger that, turn left for 2-2-0
Unable
Okay, proceed straight for about 2 1
2 1, thanks a lot
2 1, Increasing speed
One, you look free to fly, no trace of smoke
Roger that 2
I copied, I approach runway 21
Following you in
We're heading 0-2-0
Ok, you're free
Tasty 11, check your speed.
I repeat, maintain control.
Avoiding to stall.
1, check your heading.
You're not going to make the runway!
I got it.
That was a hell of a landing sir!
Didn't think we were gonna make it!
I'm gonna start charging for this stuff, alright?
Hear me?
Hey, let me know if you need anything.
TV: What seems incredible is that
all passengers in the plane survived!
Hey, is that you?
Are you a pilot? Sully?
This is you, right?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
That was unreal what you did last day.
It's a real pleasure to meet you
We got a drink after you, as soon as that happened.
Ain't that right Manny?
Yeah yeah, you did!
The Sully! A shot of Grey Goose, with a splash of water.
To January 15th!
Best day in the year!
Hey Pete, Sully's here, and he's there!
He's everywhere!
He's a real hero man!
Keep coming, let's see how  they want!
No more people on board Cap,that's what it takes for GW
Alright, thanks. Roger that.
We're heading into Midtown in Sub-7.
I cannot believe you had to sat to say that.
I'd say it again, and with no question or hesitation.
It was the best picture in history of baseball.
Are you lying about the Lakers, is that what it is?
Or is it the mustache?
You're just jealous!
Jealous!?!
Brace, Brace!
Heads down, stay down!
It's ok.
Stay down!
I don't wanna die!
Evacuate!
Grab your life vests please
Opening door.
Confused screams....
Everyone, exits are usable. Move forward to your closest exit!
Move forward.
On the right there's an exit door.
Sir, Evacuate the plane right now!
Calm down, you'll be fine!
Here, it's gonna be cold out there.
Jump!
Oh my god!
We have to jump..no no Wait!
Can you see this?
Yeah
Oh Christ, that's a plane.
Mayday Mayday, Channel 1-6, Thomas Jefferson.
We have a passenger airliner in the north river!
We're in route, we will advise!
Let's go, Let's go!
Jimmy, Jeff has not got out.
We can't leave him there!
We've got him, We've got him!
He will be okay!
Keep moving forward!
Follow the instructions!
Sir, Sir! Can you come help us?
Everyone keep moving forward!
The plane's down, we got passengers on the wings.
Approach with caution
Put a blanket on her legs
You will be fine honey, go slowly
Wrap this around her leg, make it tight.
It's so cold out here.
Starting approaching, we're nearly there.
Pick it up.
Alright
3-2-1. It's good It's good!
Right there baby, Come on.
One at a time.
We'll get everybody!
We're getting them on the other way.
A little bit closer!
With a water temperature of 36 degrees and a windshield of -5
the survivors of flight 1549 literally have managed to live.
Get up here, there are other good people coming right away, ok?
50 yards, GO!
I'll keep you like that ok?
Ok.
Someone is still here, Come back.
Help me!
Captain!
Captain, We have to go!
Time to get off the plane, about now!
Alright let's go. GO!
I'll be right behind.
Sully, we got to go!
Everybody's okay?
All of them miraculously survived and they found
300 New Yorkers ready to help them
The only question remaining is: Will it be too late?
In Manhattan Bobby Cuza, New York One
Come on, give me your hand.
Come on.
I was sure I was gonna die.
Hey, no one dies today, ok?
Give me your hand
There you go Captain, this way!
Give me your hands sir!
We'll need more blankets over here!
Thank you, Thank you
Yeah, we got them all!
Hello?
I wanted to call to say I'm okay.
Oh good, are you still far away from home?
There's been an incident.
I'm okay, I just crashed somehow.
Turn on the television
What do you mean, turn on the television?
Lori I can't talk right now, I'll
call you when things calm down.
I had to land on the Hudson.
Sully, I don't understand
I love you and I'm ok, tell the girls I'm ok!
I have to go!
Girls turn on the TV
An extensive rescue after a US Airway flight has crashed into the Hudson River.
Oh my God.
Take your wet clothes off and wrap it up for the Red Cross.
You'll be okay.
Jeff!
Sully!
I need a damage report, how badly and I need it NOW!
155. That's my number, that's passengers included.
Ok, How are you?
I'll answer that question when you'll count 155.
Alright,
I'm alive. Shary, I can't believe I'm talking to you.
Captain, Captain I'm here to escort you to Mayor Bloomber and Police Officers.
If the Mayor want  to say hello,he'll have to come down here.
Sully, I refused to send you with a cop!
Jeff! I need a count!
We've got to have a count!
There's no way to give you a count.
Let's get you a drive before you freeze.
Captain, the Mayor and Chief McKelly, come down here to meet you.
I can't, because it was a domestic flight!
Yeah, we have no doubts, but we have to track the passengers informations down.
One by one!
Ok, can we help?
Yeah, I'm gonna call and get you a count!
Listen, you've done enough.
Let me take this for you!
Jeff!
I'm okay.
I was on the other wing.
They brought us to Jersey!
I couldn't see you.
I couldn't find you!
I could hear you shouted my name all time.
I shouted too, I don't know, I guess the river....
Are you okay?
I love you too.
We made it!
The plane.... the plane's crashed!
On the river!
Are you kidding me?
Oh, that's unbelievable!
I've never been so happy to be in New York in all my life!
Hey Betty!
Ain't you coming?
I guess he didn't hear.
I lost Captain 1549 in the Hudson.
Yeah, I guess you had a hurry, he hadn't, the son of a bitch!
Everyone's been pulled off!
It's a miracle!
I thought I lost them all.
Are my passengers alright?
Yes, 110.
110. That's not good!
It's alright, what do you mean it's not good?
Don't worry, 110 is extraordinary!
How is Dureene?
Farly severe laceration, but we'll keep
handling her infection.
I'm sure he'll be ok.
Has a scar, and a hell of a story to tell.
If someone believes it, I'm seeing it right now,
and i can't believe it.
You landed a plane on the Hudson without a scratch...
Erny...
The Union is pulling out all the big guns today...
You took a damn risk Sully.
Got a count.
155?
It's official.
Oh, 155.
Thank you Erny.
Hey Carl!
Yes?
Sully.
Carl.
You didn't blown up today, did you?
We're here, that's all I know at the moment.
Oh This is Miss May, from the Hotel.
Would like to have a quick word with you.
This won't take much time gentlemen, this only to say
that our staff is committed to protect your privacy.
If there's something you need, at all...
If it's possible, I'd like to have my uniform cleaned and ready.
Are you kidding?
I'd give you this whole hotel if I could!
Okay, well Thank you Ella.
Thank you very much.
Well, anything for Sully!
What just happened?
You just got hugged by a total stranger.
Ah come on Sully!
When was the last time you heard someone
landing a jetplane on the water?
And finally lived?
Exactly.
I got shaving cream, razor blades, two pairs and some clothes.
Do you think we're ninjas?
It's seven o'clock in the evening.
You find the Merch Brothers!
Yeah.
Sully.
What are you still doing in uniform?
Well, I don't know.
Look guys, it's been a long day.
Why don't you just get some rest?
Mike will be here later to make sure you ok!
Thank you Carl.
No, thank you Captain.
You know, it's been awhile since
New York had news so good.
Especially with airplanes.
I'll see you later Sully.
The word's city officials keep repeating....
And of course the precise timing of the pilot
Captain Sully Sullenbenger, the man who had almost no time
Became a man for all time.
Hey Sully, give me....
Come on, answer...
Larry, the CBR is in 2 days.
How fast can you interfere?
Sully?
I know Airbus has simulations for A320 manifacturer,
but that's next week.
Can you get them to reschedule?
On 3 in the morning?
I need you to make it happen, before
we listen to the CBR.
Before the testimony is complete.
Why?
I have a right to see these simulation, and I have a feeling that with a human pilot
and not a computer, the results would be different.
What if they show the exact same result?
If they do, I'll hang myself in.
It's everything about timing Larry.
You can accomplish anything in a hurry.
Sure as hell I agree with that.
Now the CBR is on Wednesday, that's 36 hours.
Can you make it happen?
I'll try.
I'll give a phone call.
It's already late, so you better get started.
Thank you Larry.
Hey Lory
Hi. I'm sorry bothering you.
Sweetheart, what... What happened?
I just realized that there were 155 people on that plane,
and you were one of them
We almost lost you.
Yeah, but you didn't.
I'm right here.
How are you holding up?
Please tell me that this is almost over.
It's almost over.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too
I'll call you when they're done with me.
Good Morning Sully.
Alright, Good Morning ladies and Gentlemen.
My name is Charles Porter
I've been assigned from the National Transportation Safety
in order to conduct this hearing today
We have a lot of material to cover.
But before we hear to the cockpit voice recording,
we will listen for the first time with you Gentlemen.
For the request of Captain Sullenberger and the Union,
AirBus has agreed to view pilot simulations.
Upload link, please.
Those simulations Sully, won't change my mind about
what happened up there.
Birds!
Number 1 is on rollback!
Auto-pilot's off.
Pilot off.
Flight director's off.
LaGuardia, due to engine failure, we have to return
Ok, I'm gonna turn left to LaGuardia on 3.
Activated the approach for you.
Activated.
Runway 13
Let's get down nicely.
*ALARM*
Too low.
Succesful landing at La Guardia.
Runway 13
For the record: The pilot's and the computer's simulations made the same result.
Second upload please, about the second run?
Birds.
Give me a heading in 3-1-0
Heading 3-1-0.
1 thousand.
Flaps too
Flaps too.
*ALARM* Too low
Succesful landing, runway 19
Multiple airports, runways, two succesful landings
We are simply seeing what the computer already told us.
A lot of toes  were stepped on in order to set this up for today.
But frankly, I really don't know what you gentlemen play the game by.
Can we get serious now?
Captain?
We've all heard about the computer simulations and now
we were watching for actual simulations but
I can't quite believe.
You simply haven't taken into account human factor.
Human pilot simulations showed that you could have made it back to the airport.
No, they don't.
These pilots were not behaving like human beings.
Like people who were experiencing this for the first time.
But they made up on reacting like you did.
Immediately after the bird strike they were turning back to the airport.
Correct?
That is correct.
They knew where to turn, and exactly knew where to fly.
They did not run a check, they did not turn on the APU
There were all the same paremeters that you faced.
No one warned us.
No one said : You are going to lose both engines
at a lower altitude that any jet in the history.
But be cool, make just a left turn to La Guardia like
you're going back to pick up the milk.
This was a dual engine loss at 2800 feet followed by immediate water landing.
155 souls on board, no one ever trained for an incident like that.
No one!
In the TeterBoro landing, with that unrealistick back angle,
we were not to find birds up there.
I'd like to know how many times the pilots practiced that
maneuvre before actually put it off.
I'm not questioning the pilots, they're good pilots.
But they were clearly instructed to head back to the airport
immediately after the bird strike.
You would have no time to analyze this decision.
In these simulations you take all of the humanity out of the cockpit.
How much time did the pilots had to prepare for this event, for these simulations?
You were looking for human air.
Then make it human.
This wasn't a videogame.
It was life and death.
Sully's right, that's worth a few seconds.
Please ask practicers how much they had.
17?
The pilot who landed at TeterBoro had 17 practice attempt, before the simulation we just witnessed.
Your reaction-decision time is 35 seconds.
35 seconds is not our time.
We only had 208 second total so....
I'll take it.
Upload link, return to La Guardia.
Now we added 35 seconds to response time.
Birds!
Gas off.
35 seconds.
Time's up.
Here we go.
Going for 13.
We're right ahead for the airport.
*ALARM* Caution, obstacle
We're about 7 miles away.
*ALARM* Terrain! Terrain!
*ALARM* Too low! Terrain!
Let's try Teterboro.
Upload the link please.
Birds!
Flight Director off.
35 seconds.
Engine 1 and 2 fail.
Let's see if we can make it.
Way too low.
*ALARM* Obstacle! Obstacle!
Does anyone need to see any more simulations?
Now that we seen what could have happened, can we listen at what we actually did?
We will look at other results in another date.
Elizabeth.
For the record, this is the CVR of the Flight 1549, January 15th, 2009.
Birds!
Shit!
We got one rolling back
We've got both of them rolling back.
Ignition start.
Get out the QRH.
Lost both engines.
Mayday Mayday, we lost both engines, we're turning to La Guardia.
Okay you need to turn to La Guardia?
Turn left at 220.
Which engine did you loose?
Both, both engines.
Check those flight ignition.
Ignition?
Ignition.
Thrust lighters. Idle?
Idle.
Captain 1549, you want to try land on runway 13?
We are unable, we're trying to land on the Hudson.
Emergency power. Emergency generators not online.
Not online.
Captain's 1549, it's gonna be runway 31.
Unable
Okay, where do you need to land?
You've got 10 seconds Captain. Talk to me.
Captain 1549, runway 4 is available.
I don't think we can make any runway.
Anything in New Jersey, maybe TeterBoro?
I'll be right side with TeterBoro Airport.
La Guardia Departure? Got an emergency inbound.
Captain 1549, he's going at the airport right now.
You got an emergency?
Yeah, bird strike, Can I get runway 1-1?
Captain 1549, wanna try with Teterboro?
*ALARM* Obstacle, obstacle.
Pull up!
*ALARM* Too low, terrain!
This is the Captain, brace for impact!
Captain 1549 turn right to 3-0. You can land on 1-0!
We can't make it.
Go ahead and try number 1.
We're going to end up in the Hudson.
All right, let's put the flaps down, flaps down.
Couple of flaps, want more?
No, it's good.
You got runway 2-9 at Newark, it's gonna be 2 o'clock, 7 miles.
You got any ideas?
Actually not.
I'd need to take a quick break.
What do they think?
Seeing what I just done?
I'll tell you what I think.
I'm just so damn proud.
You were right there, with all those distractions.
We did this together like a team.
Thanks Sully.
We did our job.
Alright, we got to get this hearing back to order.
Could you settle please?
Take your seats.
That was honestly, the first time I was listening to a crash recording.
While actually sitting with the Captain and First Officer.
It's extraordinary.
That was no simulation?
No it wasn't.
Gentlemen, I want to inform you that
the left engine was recovered.
I'll just proceed to a comprehensive report.
There was extensive damage to the fan blades of the engine,
5 compressor blades were fractured.
And 8 aerial veins missing.
So no thrust.
As you testified, it was completely destroyed.
The Aircraft's data was wrong.
I'd like to add something to a personal note:
I can say with absolute confidence that, after speaking with the rest of the crew
bird experts, aviation engineers, after running into every scenario,
after running each player, there were still accidents results..
And it's you, Captain Sullenberger, removing you from
the equation of math, just fails.
I disagree.
It wasn't just me, it was all of us.
Jeff, Donna, Shila and Dureene.
And all passengers, rescue workers.
And Traffic Control, Helicopter Crews and Scuba Cops.
We all did it!
We survived.
First Officer Skiles, is there anything you'd like to add?
Anything you would have done different, if you had to do it again?
Yes, I would have done it in July!
xX-Subs by Sergeddu-Xx