Alert! Alert! Alert!
You three criminals have been caught
in a further act of seditious treason.
General Zod, your only feeling
was contempt for our society.
Your only desire was to command.
Ursa, the only feeling you showed
was for your vicious general.
Your only wish, to rule at his side.
Non, you are as without thought
as you are without voice.
This council has no hesitation
in proclaiming you all...
Guilty.
You will lie down before me, Jor-El.
Both you, and them one day, Jor-El!
Jor-El!
- Here, I'll just get the door for you.
- Yeah, thanks a...
Sorry, affer you.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
- Morning, Phil.
- Excuse me, Kent.
Hi, Alice. That's a very
pretty blouse you're wearing today.
I'Il catch you later, Clark.
Hello?
I don't know. Okay. Yep.
- Morning, Leueen. How's it...?
- Okay. I'll check it.
How do you spell that guy's name?
Mr. White, how Iong
should we hold the front page?
Give it another 10 minutes, and...
Oh, I'll tell them.
- Sorry. Thank you.
- Hello, Pete.
If we don't get anything
new in 10 minutes,
go with the wire-service copy
and run the picture in three columns.
Kent, I need a story for the page-three
sidebar on this terrorist group.
Right.
Sorry, terrorists?
Get your head out of the clouds,
Kent. Where you been?
- I was at home.
- Don't you watch television?
I don't enjoy television. Too much violence.
I was just reading Dickens.
Mr. Kent, a gang of terrorists
sElzed the Elffel Tower in Paris.
He knows where the Elffel Tower is, Olsen.
- You do, don't you?
- Yes, sir.
- Has anybody been hurt?
- So far the hostages are unharmed.
- The hostages?
- Yeah, tourists. About 20 of them.
But that's just penny-ante stuff.
They claim if the government
doesn't meet their demands,
they've got a hydrogen bomb.
Mr. White, that's terrible.
That's why they call them terrorists, Kent.
Now, get to the morgue.
I wanna know everything on terrorism.
Mr. White, does Lois know about any of this?
- Does she know about it? She's in it.
- She's what?
The minute the story broke,
I bundled her on the first Concorde.
If Paris is gonna go kablooey,
I want my best reporter in the middle.
- But, gee, Mr. White...
- You're good, but Lois Lane is better.
No, I meant, isn't that
a little bit dangerous, sir?
That goes with the territory, Kent.
Don't worry.
If I know Lois Lane, she'll not only
come back with a Pulitzer Prize story
but a one-on-one interview
with a hydrogen bomb
titled "What Makes Me Tick."
Now, don't stand around, Kent...
- How did they get up there?
- They were disguised as repair workers.
Can you tell us why
they released the first hostages?
We insist they do this to show good faith.
If not, we refuse to negotiate.
Will they release
the rest of the hostages?
In return for a guarantee that
we will not launch an attack on them.
There will be no attack,
no attempt to overpower the terrorists?
- We've made a guarantee.
- And you'll honor it?
We have not the choice to refuse
if we believe it's a real
hydrogen bomb they have.
- Where is the bomb?
- It's in a big oilcan.
Hydrogen bomb? Are you sure?
How can we be sure? Today it's
possible for anyone to make a bomb.
This could blow up all of Paris.
What's the government's position?
Will they meet their demands?
I am not authorized to say what they will do.
At this moment, there is an emergency
meeting in the Elysée Palace.
Wait. Wait, wait.
- Stairs. Stairs? Stairs.
- Stairs.
Okay?
- AII right. We'll bring them down now.
- Get in.
- Come on. Watch out for any tricks.
- Do we Iook Iike the sort of...?
I don't know what you look like.
Get in. You're being released. Shut up.
- Come on then, everybody out.
- Okay, ready.
This way.
- Come on. Quick, quick, quick.
- Hurry up.
Look, you're being released. Get moving.
I'll take a last look around.
Okay, send them down.
Okay, up we go.
Pulitzer Prize.
Capital P... Darn.
Should we have let the hostages go?
They'll give in to us as
soon as we plant the bomb.
It doesn't matter one way or the other.
Nobel Prize.
Capital N,
little O, little B,
little E, little L.
Nobel. Nobel. Nobel.
Prize.
Now, be careful.
It's me that controls the bomb,
not the bomb that controls me.
I hope you have not
many sins Ieft to be forgiven
because if you let go of that,
you'll only have 60 seconds to list them.
- You are right.
- Did you hear something?
Sounded like someone
moving underneath.
It's your nerves.
- Where are they now?
- They are near to the lift.
But one is still inside with the bomb.
The third one has come out of the lift now.
- The third one is out now.
- The bomb, is it still in there?
Yes, we think so.
This is the boring bit.
Tell them to get ready.
Stand by.
Get ready. Come on.
We'll cut the cable
as soon as we get the word.
Are you sure
they haven't primed the bomb?
No, no, of course not. They haven't.
We've been watching them all the time.
Now!
- It started.
- Oh, my God.
I believe this is your floor.
Oh, thank God.
How did I get myself into this?
- You all right?
- Uh-huh.
A bomb! There's a bomb up there.
- They've got a bomb.
- I know. I know.
Nice fresh melons.
Nice fresh melons. Get them fresh here.
Good for the cooking, huh?
Look at this, the best.
- Hi, Lois.
- Hi, Clark.
Hey!
Clark.
- You ever heard of crosswalks?
- Yeah, but you know, I mean...
Do you have any idea how stupid that was?
Freak.
Clark, you know,
you were really Iucky that time.
You gotta be careful. When you
cross the street, look both ways.
Well, I mean, gee, Lois, usually I do, you know.
- Come in.
- Hi.
You know, maybe you ought
to get your glasses checked.
Uh, well, you know, not everybody
can have x-ray vision, you know, Lois.
Do I detect a note of jealousy in that voice?
Jealousy? No, no. Not me.
Golly, Lois, what are you doing?
When was the Iast time
you heard me sneeze?
You are never gonna hear me sneeze again.
- No?
- No. I read this book
and it says that if you get 1000
milligrams of vitamin C every day,
you stay in perfect health.
Golly, 1000? That's certainly
a Iot of oranges, isn't it, Lois?
- There are pills. I've seen them.
- Pills.
That's the modern way to do things.
This is natural.
Besides, I get my exercise that way.
And, Clark, you don't have to be jealous.
- Uh, I don't?
- No, you got so much going for you.
I do?
Do you mind if I give you
a little constructive criticism?
- Well, actually, yes, I...
- You gotta be more aggressive.
You have to go from the instinct.
You see something,
you want it, you go for it.
That's what I do.
Yes, I've noticed.
Perhaps I could help you there.
Oh, thanks. That would be great.
Let me see now...
Oh, I see.
Just put the orange in there.
That's really very clever.
Clark.
You know that I wouldn't say all
those things to you if I didn't really care.
- You do?
- Mm-hm.
I mean, what else are friends for?
- Friends, huh?
- Mm-hm.
Here, Clark.
Here's to friendship.
Hm.
This is how it ends for
the greatest criminal mind of our time.
Not with a whimper, not with a bang.
How do they choose
to reward Lex Luthor,
the greatest genius in this world?
Do they give him glory or treasure?
What, matter of fact, do they give him?
Life plus 25, Luthor. Get to work.
Don't feel bad, Mr. Luthor. It almost worked.
I mean, California almost fell down,
right in the ocean.
Millions of people was almost killed.
If it hadn't been for that guy Superman,
that overgrown Boy Scout.
- I want my Liberace record back tonight.
- There's a scratch on it.
What are you gonna do with a guy Iike that?
He flies around so fast and everything.
I mean, they can't even trace
that guy on that radar they got.
Every time they try, he just flies off.
- Where?
- North.
Why?
To ski?
Otis, every man has his vulnerable point.
Some, like you, Otis, have more than one.
I didn't see Superman's in time.
But now, through patience, invention, and skill,
my little black box is just about ready.
- Oh, that little black box in our cell?
- Shh!
That little black box, Mr. Luthor,
what's it for?
That little black box, Otis,
goes beyond any conventional radar.
- It tracks alpha waves.
- Oh.
Alpha waves. Hm.
Those alpha waves will take me north
to his secret.
And his secret will give me Superman.
The MAB is 190 at 0.5.
We ought to see the old beauty
when we top the rise there.
Follow the bouncing ball for a while.
It's giving me a headache.
Anyway, somebody's gotta
check up on those guys.
Yeah, I keep on forgetting about them.
How Iong they been up there, 45 days?
The whole world's forgotten about it.
Houston calling Artemis II.
Houston calling Artemis II. Come in.
- Morning, Houston.
- Hold on, Nate.
- Yo.
- How are things going?
AII systems normal, Houston.
- Andy is out doing the geological survey.
- Okay.
More rocks. Nice.
And cosmonaut Boris
is getting some soil samples.
By the way, Boris and I are engaged.
I had a feeling about you guys
when I saw your Rorschach tests.
Just a little détente humor there, Houston.
Surface conditions unchanged?
Well, it's mighty pretty out there. Mighty...
- pretty.
- Mighty pretty.
Right.
Look, Nate?
Nate, wake up, will you?
That's it. I'm dreaming.
Artemis, come in.
Well, Houston, we seem to have
an unidentified flying object.
U nidentified?
- What does it look like?
- Well...
a lot like a girl.
You.
- What kind of a creature are you?
- Just a man.
A man?
What a fragile sort of life form this is.
Houston, come in. Come in, Houston.
Come in, Houston. Come in.
Attempting manual liftoff.
Can somebody hear me?
Houston!
Come in, Houston!
Oh, no. No!
Somebody help me!
- Artemis, this is Houston calling.
- What's up?
- Artemis, Houston calling. Come in.
- What's going on?
- I don't know. We've Iost contact.
- So?
Well, we really...
Artemis, come in, please. Houston calling.
What was that he said before? He saw a girl?
- I thought he said "curl ."
- What's a curl?
Isn't that what the old
Canaveral guys used to call a comet
with an east-west trajectory?
How should I know?
I was back in high school in those days.
Strange. I tore those metal fibers like paper.
And what he did was amazing.
- Something is happening.
- Yes, to all of us.
The closer we come to an
atmosphere with only one sun,
a yellow sun,
the more our molecular
density gives us unlimited powers.
They come from there.
A place called Houston.
Then we will go there too,
to rule.
Finally, to rule.
Three-Elghty, out.
Three-Elghty-one, out.
Three-Elghty-two, out.
Three-Elghty-three, out.
Three-Elghty-four, out.
Three-Elghty-five, out.
Lights out, Luthor.
I said, lights out.
You guys are about 10 seconds
away from solitary, you know that?
I told you to...
Freeze, freeze.
Go out there and find it.
- What am I Iooking for?
- You'll know when you see it.
I think I found it.
What is it?
It's a ladder, you dummy.
- Hi, Miss Teschmacher.
- Shh!
Come on.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Come on, hurry.
Otis, hold that ladder. Hurry up.
50-yard line, touchdowni
Oh, what a beautiful play.
But there's a marker downfield.
It could be against...
- Come up.
- Come on.
Here I come, Mr. Luthor.
- Get off. Get off.
- Otis!
- We're sinking!
- Get off, get off!
Excuse me.
If you'd like to carry Mrs.
Smith over the threshold...
It's sort of traditional.
I can give you a hand
if you have trouble lifting.
- Oh! No, of course not.
- Honey. Thanks, I'll walk.
Certainly, dear.
- Well, here you are.
- Well, sure is pink.
Careful with the bags, please, sir.
Is this your first visit
to Honeymoon Haven?
- Together, anyway.
- Yes.
Let me just show you
some of our special features.
These are our Flames of Love,
exclusive with this motel in the area.
If you want the flames to
go higher, you just pull this.
Oh, I see.
- Look, dear. That's kind of romantic.
- In July?
- Honey?
- For a nominal charge,
our staff photographer
will be happy to prepare
a special souvenir album
of your honeymoon stay.
He'll photograph you in some
of our more intimate locations,
in the tub for two, on the bearskin rug.
Gee, real polyester!
And here's the bed.
Right. Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, of course. Um...
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
And have a happy...
whatever.
Ugh! Can you believe this?
Posing as newlyweds to expose
a honeymoon racket in Niagara Falls.
- Well...
- What a waste of a great writer.
Writers.
Perry White and his
Sunday magazine exposés.
How am I supposed to get a
Pulitzer Prize writing about a pink bear?
I don't know, I think this
kind of thing should be exposed.
They get kids who are just starting
out, and take them for every cent.
- That's what Mr. White says.
- Yeah?
On the other hand, this is kind of nice.
Complimentary champagne.
- Kissing contest tonight.
- Really?
Lois, would ...? Uh...
No.
Hey, Iook at this.
Lois? Gee.
Look what I found.
A complimentary corsage.
Yeah, everything's complimentary
around here till you get the bill.
Yeah.
Gee, you look very pretty.
Thank you, Clark.
Sure.
You know, Lois, um,
I was sort of thinking...
Well, later on... Well, I...
I was wondering what you
wanted to do about the arrangements.
What arrangements, Clark?
Well, um, I was thinking
primarily about the, um,
sleeping arrangements.
- Mr. Smith?
- Uh-huh.
- The complimentary couch.
- Right.
What? Ooh.
Gosh, it's alive.
Very good, Miss Teschmacher. Very good.
Why am I here? What am I doing here?
Miss Teschmacher,
is this a philosophy seminar?
No. This is a getaway.
- Getaway.
- Right.
Lex, how could you do that to Otis?
What else is ballast for?
Miss Teschmacher,
north. Due north.
Right. North.
- Where's Jimmy when I need him?
- Golly, isn't it beautiful?
Yes, gorgeous. Gorgeous.
- Lois?
- Yeah?
Look. EVerybody's holding hands.
Maybe we should hold hands too, huh?
- Here's my hand, Clark. Hold it.
- Thanks.
You know what? They're afraid to let go.
- Why?
- They let go, straight to the lawyer.
Oh, I don't know about that.
They look kind of happy to me.
That's because you're blind, Clark.
- Oh, yeah.
- Here.
- No, I've got it. No, I...
- Yeah. Clark.
You've gotta look after yourself.
You've only got one pair of eyes.
- God.
- Lois?
- Now, here.
- Right.
- Don't say I never did anything for you.
- Thank you.
Son! Excuse me, please.
- Be careful.
- What are you doing?
Get down! Get down!
You embarrass me here in front of everybody.
Lois, did you see what almost
happened there? That Iittle boy...
Hey, I'm hungry. You hungry?
- Lois, you're amazing.
- Why, because I'm hungry?
No. Here you are standing in front of one
of nature's most awesome spectacles
and you're thinking about food.
Aren't you impressed?
Clark, once a girl's seen
Superman in action,
Niagara Falls kind of
leaves you cold, you know?
Him again, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have a one-track mind, don't I?
Well, my one-track mind
is telling me that I'm hungry.
- Hot dog?
- Hot dog.
Hot dog.
Could I have some orange juice?
- Freshly squeezed.
- Freshly squeezed, I know. Okay.
Hey, Mom. Look!
Yeah, honey. That's nice.
Okay, it's two mustard and relish, and...
Oh, my God!
Help!
Somebody help!
Somebody do something!
Way to go, Superman!
What a nice man.
Of course he's Jewish.
- There you go.
- Again, again!
No, I'm sorry. Only one ride to a customer.
Superman. Superman, it's me, Lois!
Come here. You're gonna get it!
- Give me a heart attack here.
- It's me. It's Lois.
Lois Lane.
Well, hello and goodbye.
What's the hurry? I mean, seeing
as you happen to be in Niagara Falls?
Happen to be in Niagara Falls.
And Clark...
Clark is not around, as usual.
Hmm.
Lois?
Hey, Lois?
- Here you go.
- Where were you?
I was getting hot dogs.
What do you mean?
Well, it just seems kind of strange to me
that every time Superman's around,
you disappear.
Superman? You mean he was here?
- Golly.
- And you weren't. As usual.
So, what have you
got to say about that?
Darn, I forgot your orange juice.
Clark.
No orange juice?
Mush! Mush!
I am mushing.
Ice and snow.
Is this your idea of a good time?
A good time? Is that all you care about?
North, Miss Teschmacher.
North. North, north, north!
Yes, Lex. North.
Look. It's his home.
It's Superman's home.
Oh, good, more ice.
- Fantastic.
It's fantastic!
The construction goes far beyond
any known architectural theory.
- It's beautiful.
- Beautiful.
- This place is genius.
- Genius.
- Lex.
- I'Il be all right.
No, me.
Oh! Ah!
Why can't you be more careful?
- It's beautiful.
- Beautiful.
- It has everything.
- Wrong.
- Why didn't you go before we left?
- That was two days ago.
This Iooks like some kind of control panel.
- Don't touch anything.
- Ice.
- I said, don't touch it.
- It's not ice.
- It Iooks Iike a crystal.
Kryptonian memory bank.
Education crystal number 308.
- I told you it's a crystal.
- Shut up.
Earth culture, section B.
Trees by Joyce Kilmer
of the Planet Earth.
What's this?
I think that I shall never see
A poem lovely as a tree.
- A tree whose hungry mouth...
- He's not here.
It's a voice from the past.
That's cute. That's very cute.
A tree that looks at God all day...
I Iike trees.
So does your average cocker spaniel.
Give me another one.
No, no, no. The big one there.
Kal-El, my son,
as keeper of the archives of Krypton,
it falls to me to tell you of the
darkest episode in our planet's history.
Now, this I wanna hear.
After eons of harmony, there
appeared among us three rebel elements.
What you would call
on Earth "criminals."
Criminals. My kind of people.
Despite all our efforts, we were
unable to change their evil natures,
thElr evil ways.
And as you know, we had no death penalty.
- Sensible enough.
- Therefore,
our scientists constructed the Phantom Zone.
In it, we placed
these three arch criminals,
imprisoning them there for all eternity.
No possibility for parole?
Your father, Jor-El, thought
long and hard upon that question.
- I asked the right question.
- And there is one danger.
The Phantom Zone might,
just might, be cracked by
a nuclear explosion in space.
I wish you had not asked me that.
I didn't ask anything.
We do not know what would
happen if they were to escape.
On Krypton, these
villains were uncontrollable.
On Earth, they would have the
same powers, each one of them,
that you have.
- Think of it.
- The first of the three...
- Three.
- Is their leader, General Zod.
- Three super villains.
- Together with Non and Ursa...
Each one with the same power he has.
Each one totally dedicated
to corruption, violence and evil.
That explains the three alpha waves
I've been getting on my black box.
They'll need a contact on Earth.
Someone with the same contempt for
Iife, Iiberty and the pursuit of happiness.
South, Miss Teschmacher.
You know, it's really amazing.
I never started to
put it together before now.
It's just kind of funny, because a good
reporter doesn't let anything slip by her.
No, of course not.
Well, I'm beginning to get the picture.
As usual, Lois, I really don't
know what you're talking about.
Tell you what,
I'Il meet you back at the hotel.
What's your hurry, Superman?
Sorry?
I gotta admit,
your disguise is nearly perfect.
You had me fooled.
And I am nobody's fool, believe me.
No, of course not, Lois.
I mean, you just have
an active imagination.
You just get carried away sometimes.
- I understand. It can happen to anybody.
- Listen.
I'm so sure that you're Superman,
that I'm willing to bet my life on it.
What?
Now, if I'm right, you'll turn into Superman.
And if I'm wrong,
you've got yourself one hell of a story.
You think I'm Superman?
Boy, you certainly have
some imagination, Lois.
For a minute you almost
had me convinced. For a minute.
Bye-bye, baby.
Oh, my God!
Excuse me, please.
Superman!
Lois, swim. Swim!
Help!
Look out for the rocks! Oh, God.
Clark!
Lois, grab the branch!
What?
Help!
Lois, you all right?
I gotcha.
Here, here, here!
Clark!
You're what I thought was Superman?
Sorry.
This is really embarrassing.
So this is planet Houston.
A very strange surface.
A primitive sort of Iife form.
Hm...
Did you see that?
Did you see what I did?
I have powers beyond reason here.
We all have them, my dear.
Boy, I sure must have Iooked Iike an idiot.
Jumping in the river, waiting for Mr. Wonderful
who obviously had better things to do.
Well, I'm sure it must have
been something very important, Lois.
And then thinking that you were...
If Perry White could see me now.
Where's my comb?
God, not only have I Iost my mind,
I've Iost my comb.
Clark, can you pass me
that brush over there, please?
Sure.
Clark!
- No, no, no. It's okay.
- Let me see your hand. Give it to me.
- No, no. It's all right, Lois.
- Let me look at it.
- You are Superman.
- Lois, come on. Don't be s...
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have anything to be sorry about.
I don't know why I did that.
Maybe you wanted to.
I don't think I did.
Well, maybe you didn't want to with your mind
but maybe you wanted to with your heart.
We'd better talk.
I'm in Iove with you.
Well, we really better talk.
I'm listening.
We can't talk here. Perry will call
at about 6 to find out what's happening.
"What's happening"?
That's the understatement of the year.
Where do you wanna talk?
Lois.
Now that you know,
I think you should know it all.
I want to.
Let's go to my place.
Maybe I should change first.
Maybe you should too.
- They have a wide selection.
- I can't eat fish.
You can eat anything you want,
Duane. You can eat meat and potatoes.
I couldn't go anywhere
where I was expected to eat fish.
They got beans.
I can't eat beans. I'll come
out in a rash if I eat beans.
Look, Duane,
they have a wide selection.
I think I'll try the fish.
I don't know. From the Iook of them,
I'll bet $ 10 they're from Los Angeles.
Hey, you hippies,
get your butts off the road!
I Iike the globe.
It flashes red like our Krypton sun.
But not this irritating noise.
Make way.
Did I hear right?
That son of a bitch give me an order?
Duane, you take care of it.
- But I...
- Duane.
You gotta learn to kick ass,
you wanna be a peacemaker.
AII right. Just what in the hell
do you think you're doing here?
What is this symbol?
Do you follow another leader?
Follow the leader?
Holy skunk sweat.
- AII right.
- A weapon of some sort.
Huh?
Wha...? Oh!
How the hell did you do that?
Jesus H. Christ.
Crude noisemaker.
I'm just checking the tire, you know.
- Wow, this is your home?
- No.
Actually, I live in the city,
about three blocks from you.
No, this is a very special place for me.
I wanted you to see it.
Listen, you warm enough?
I guess I should be freezing, but I'm not.
Good.
Come on, Iet me show you.
You see? You only smell strong.
Whoa, baby!
It's only because I didn't want
to lose my place in the orchestra.
Oh, my. The circus is in town.
Hey, sweet thing.
Set them buns down here.
Let's just hold hands.
Let me know if this tickles.
Mm-hm.
Your right front tire is flat, Duane.
- Sheriff, what happened?
- Willie.
I think my arm's broke.
Girl or no girl,
you're gonna spit teeth. Get up.
What the sam hill?
Is that you, Boog?
U h, oh. Uh...
AII right. Get them up and keep them up!
These humans are beginning to bore me.
- Please, mister...
- He's a general.
Please, Mr. General.
Please let my daddy down.
Hey... Hey! Hey, hey!
You okay, Jody?
See, when my father died...
That's my Earth father, I mean.
...I found this crystal.
- Huh?
- Uh...
This is kind of hard to explain,
but you see, it, um...
It called to me.
Oh.
Yeah. And it brought me here.
It helped me to build this place.
Well, actually, it built it, really.
But, um,
that's when I found out who
I really was, and what I had to do.
So, what do you think? You Iike it?
Like it?
It's incredible.
I mean, not that it couldn't
use a woman's touch, you know?
- Especially around dinnertime.
- Dinner. Oh.
I'm sorry. See, I don't
usually do too much about...
Listen, tonight, sky's the limit.
Anything you want.
- I'm home.
- Oh!
Should we eat?
- Sure.
- Great.
Good morning, America.
This is East Houston, Idaho.
Until yesterday, a middle-American town
that Middle America had forgotten.
But today, the population...
Exaggerated reports put it at 123.
...Has increased by three.
And these three new arrivals
bring destruction in their wake.
As I Iook west into
East Houston this morning,
I see a town gripped with fear.
Who's the big guy?
Okay, yeah, we 've gotta be a...
- No.
- We 've got a crack
in that diode.
- Come in on him ifyou can.
- Try to wiggle it.
Who else is seeing this?
Well, with this satellite linkup,
just about everybody. The whole planet.
The whole planet Houston?
Earth. The whole planet Earth.
Get over to the commentator.
You may continue.
As the extraordinary story continues...
- As this extraordinary...
- Enough of this man.
If the whole planet is watching,
Iet's show them something interesting.
Throw down your arms and surrenderi
This is an order.
General Zod does not
take orders. He gives them.
Hey, you all right, buddy?
He was in the line of that fire
and nothing happened to him.
I haven't seen the likes
of this since Superman.
Yes? yes.
The Newsbeat control room has informed
me that a fleet of helicopter gunships is...
- Mr. President, sir, can't we...?
- There's nothing anybody can do.
They have such powers,
nothing can stop them.
Where's Superman?
Where is he?
Why doesn't he do something?
General Smythson has
said that nuclear weapon strikes
have been ruled out because of
the danger to the civilian population.
Starting fire run now.
- Stand by, rockets.
- Clear it!
Fire one.
Fire again.
Locked on target. Gotta take a run now.
The rockets didn 't have any effect.
Look. They need machines to fly.
What bravery.
Be nice to them, my dear. Blow them a kiss.
We 're out of control.
We don 't understand.
We 're coming in,
coming down. Can't control it
We 're coming down.
I win.
I always win.
Is there no one on
this planet to eVen challenge me?
- Mm. That was good.
- I thought we might, uh,
abandon the orange juice for once.
- Here, cheers.
- Cheers.
Must be tough being Clark Kent, isn't it?
No. No, I really...
I really like it sometimes.
Even though I do make a fool of myself.
But, you know, if it weren't for him,
I never would haVe met you.
But he is you.
It's kind of confusing.
Not to me, it isn't.
For the first time in my life,
everything's clear.
I'm gonna go change into
something more comfortable.
Come forward.
Your general wishes to speak.
I am General Zod, your ruler.
Yes, today begins a new order!
Your lands, your possessions,
your very lves will gladly be
given in tribute to me, General Zod.
In return for your obedience,
you will enjoy my generous protection.
In other words, you will be allowed to live.
So you are a general?
And who is your superior?
- I answer only to the president.
- And he will answer to me.
Or all of his cities will end up like this one.
Your father and l have tried to
anticipate your every question, Kal-El.
This is the one we hoped you would not ask.
But I have to,
because she's everything I want in life.
And she, the one you have chosen,
she feels as much for you?
Yes.
Then, if this is what you wish,
ifyou intend to live your life with a mortal,
you must live as a mortal.
You must become one of them.
This crystal chamber has harnessed
the rays of the red sun of Krypton.
Once exposed to these rays,
all your great powers
on Earth will disappear forever.
But consider.
Once it is done, there is no return.
You will become an ordinary man.
You will feel like an ordinary man.
You can be hurt like an ordinary man.
Oh, my son, are you sure?
Mother...
I Iove her.
You did all that for me?
Huh. I don't know what to say.
- Just say you Iove me.
- Oh.
Thousands of hours to create,
and they defaced it in seconds.
I magine what they'll do
to the world if we resist.
The whole place is gonna fall!
Watch it!
You are the one they call president?
I am.
I see you are practiced
in worshiping things that fly.
Good.
Rise before Zod.
Now, kneel before Zod.
You are not the president.
No one who leads so many
could possibly kneel so quickly.
I am the man they are protecting.
I am the president.
I'Il kneel before you if it will save lives.
It will.
Starting with your own.
What I do now,
I do for the sake of the people of the world.
But there is one man here on Earth
who will never kneel before you.
Who is this imbecile? Where is he?
I wish I knew.
Oh, God.
Zod.
Hey.
You're awfully quiet over there.
I'm supposed to be the shy one.
Hm? Oh.
Yeah, I was just thinking,
I can't believe what you've given up for me.
Are you kidding?
I didn't do it for you, Lois, I did it for us.
See, I told you there'd be
a hot dog place somewhere.
Okay. It sure takes longer
when you can't fly.
Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Okay.
My back's stiff.
Come on, it's my treat. Come on.
Oh, boy, it's Mr. Wonderful.
Thank you.
- Do you have a men's room?
- Yeah. Right in the corner.
- Want to sit down?
- Yeah.
Hi, what would you folks like?
I'd Iike a cheeseburger
with everything on it, and a Coke,
an order of fries
and a side salad, please.
- And for you, sir?
- I'Il think about it when I get back.
Right. That's one cheeseburger...
- Steak and eggs, over easy, coffee.
- Can I have my Coke?
Coming right up.
- Sorry, that seat's taken.
- It is now, sweetheart.
Can I buy you something to eat?
No, thank you.
Excuse me. I think
you're sitting in my seat.
Your seat's in there, four-eyes.
Gee, I think perhaps somebody
ought to teach you some manners, sir.
Yeah? Well, let me
know when he comes in.
- Look, Clark, we can just...
- Honey.
Excuse me, sir, would
you care to step outside?
I said, excuse me, sir,
would you care to step outside?
Now, listen, Rocky,
your steak's coming right up.
Keep it on the flame, Ron.
This is just a minute steak.
After you.
- Clark.
- It's all right, honey.
Clark!
You all right, fella?
He's gonna be fine, just give me that.
- Clark?
- Blood. It's my blood.
I think maybe we ought to hire
a bodyguard from now on.
I don't want a bodyguard.
I want the man I fell in love with.
I know that, Lois.
I wish he were here.
Clark.
Boy, you just don't have
enough sense to stay down, do you?
Settle down!
I don't like your meat anyway.
Oh, God.
Clark? Clark?
Clark, can you get up?
- It's all right. Come on. I got you.
- Go slow.
Try and get up in that chair.
- Sit down.
- I'm all right. I'm all right.
Okay, everybody, he's all right.
Just relax. We'll have some fresh coffee.
I'Il turn the box on.
We interrupt this
program for an urgent message
from the President of the United States.
This is your president.
On behalf of my country, and in the name
of the other leaders of the world
with whom I have today consulted,
I hereby abdicate
all authority and control over this planet
to General Zod.
Zod.
Only by strict compliance
with all his directions
will the lives of
innocent millions be spared.
Superman, can you hear me?
- Superman, where...?
- Who is this Superman?
- You'll find out. And when you do...
- Come to me, Superman, if you dare.
I defy you.
Come Come and kneel before Zod.
Zod!
- Here? When?
- When?
Where the hell have you been, Mac?
On a desert island?
I have to go back.
You can't go back.
- There's no way now.
- I have to.
I've gotta try, damn it.
I've gotta try something, anything.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know this was gonna happen.
They knew.
I heard them.
I just didn't listen.
Hey, come on! Please!
God.
Father?
Mother?
Boy, I really wish you could hear me.
Because I need you.
See, I...
I, uh...
I failed.
Father!
You're master of all you survey.
And so I was yesterday.
And the day before.
Hello, there.
Lex Luthor.
You've heard the name?
The greatest criminal mind on Earth.
I told you this was a puny planet.
Wait just a moment.
Wait until you get to know
me better. Will you, please?
Wait. Look, I can give
you anything you want.
I can give you the brass ring,
the unlimited freedom
to maim, kill, destroy.
Plus, Lex Luthor's keen mind.
Lex Luthor's savvy.
Lex Luthor's career guidance.
Lex Luthor's School of Better...
We have all of this without you.
You cannot bargain
with what you don't have.
Magnificent One,
what I am bargaining with
is what you do not have.
The son of Jor-El.
- The son of Jor-El? On this planet?
- Aye.
Possibly you know him better
by his nom de voyage
or his name he travels under:
- Superman.
- Oh.
So this is Superman.
How do you know of Jor-El?
My Fullness, as I explained to you before,
I'm about the best there is.
Revenge.
We will kill the son of our jailer.
- Revenge.
- Revenge! Now we're cooking.
- He flies, then?
- Constantly.
- He has powers as we do?
- Certainly.
But, uh, magnificent one,
he's just one
where you are three.
- Or four, if you count him twice.
- We will bring him to his knees.
Wait!
First, you must find him.
And Lex Baby is the only one
who knows where he is.
What do you want?
Well, general,
the world is a big place.
Thank goodness, uh,
my needs are small.
As it turns out, I have this
affinity for beachfront property.
What do you want?
Australia.
I can't understand it.
Where is he? He shows up
every time a cat gets stuck in a tree
and now he's decided
to pull a disappearing act.
Maybe we haven't figured out his game plan.
Game plan? It's fourth down,
the two-minute warning has sounded
and the ball is deep in our territory.
Just how brilliant do you have to be? I mean...
Superman's got something up
his sleeve. That's for sure, chief.
- We just haven't figured it out, right?
- He'll be here!
If it's at all possible, he'll be here.
See? Yeah, and she knows
his plays better than anybody.
Yeah, better than anybody.
Maybe he hasn't heard about it yet, chief.
Sounds like an earthquake.
Quick, take a picture.
Get down the back way! Get out!
Oh! Ow!
You all right, chief?
Even with all this knowledge when will
these dummies Iearn to use a doorknob?
Hi.
You should see the White House.
They'll be cleaning for months.
Lex Luthor.
You promised me the son of Jor-El.
Yes, Your Grace.
But what I've given you
is the next best thing.
You just hold on to that little lady,
and he'll be along.
See, they have this relationship.
She does all his public relations,
and he gives her every exclusive.
They're the best of friends.
You know what I mean?
What an undemanding male
this Superman must be.
You could use a tuck
here and there yourself.
Wait!
- Oh, I'm sorry!
- She lives for now.
Kill the rest, starting with him.
Wait. Wait.
Don't you remember the White House?
The Oval Room?
We had a few laughs, right?
General,
would you care to step outside?
Superman!
Superman, thank God.
I mean, get him!
Come to me, son of Jor-El!
Kneel before Zod!
Watch out. You all right?
Wait there.
Son of Jor-El.
- We were beginning to think you were a coward.
- I'm not a coward, Zod.
Let him prove it.
Then die as you deserve to!
Come on, come on, Superman! Get him!
Man, this is gonna be good.
Take him. He's yours.
Come on! Kill himi
Superman.
The big one's just as strong as Superman.
Ah!
Hold him.
Wow, home run.
Oh, my God! My baby!
Thank you.
This Superman is nothing of the kind.
- I've discovered his weakness.
- Yes.
He cares.
He actually cares for these Earth people.
- Like pets?
- I suppose so.
Sentimental idiot.
He's caged Non.
I'Il draw his fire
with some of my own.
Get out of here! The rig's gonna blow!
Get away from that truck!
- Did you see that?
- They went down there.
Hey, what the...?
Superman, help us!
Superman.
I never thought this thing
would go the distance.
You people, get back.
Here, take the end of this.
No! Don't do it!
The people!
Throw it!
- This way, please. This way.
- Help me.
Where's your wife, sir?
I got her. I got her. Don't worry.
He's dead. He's dead.
- Superman is dead.
- He's not coming out.
- They've killed Superman.
- Oh, no!
- What are we gonna do?
- He's dead.
Let's go get them!
- Come on, let's go!
- I know judo. Come on, let's go!
Hey, hey, hey!
What sound?
You forgot your cha...
Wait a minute!
- I'm holding it, I'm holding it!
- I got it.
I can't see what's happening.
- My hair!
- Your hair? What about mine?
Hold on!
Yeah, yeah, I got your message.
No, go ahead. Go ahead. Yeah?
Yeah? Yeah, yeah.
Look, he's alive. He's alive!
It'll be all right.
Come back, please!
Please come back!
So he is a coward affer all.
Damn it!
Come back, Superman!
What about us?
- Don't leave us!
- We can't handle it without you.
- It's not our fault.
- He chickened out.
Ah, phony!
Superman didn't even do nothing.
Come on, let's go.
Get away from here. Jimmy.
Our victory is complete.
The son of Jor-El has fled.
- Superman fled?
- I don't believe you.
- The next time, we will kill him.
- The next time?
The next time?
What am I gonna do with you people?
I held up my end.
I delivered you the blue boy.
What do I get from my triple threat?
"Bow, yield, kneel ."
That kind of stuff closes out a town.
Why do you say this to me
when you know I will kill you for it?
Kill me? Lex Luthor?
Extinguish the greatest
criminal flame of our age?
- Eradicate the only man on earth with...
- Kill him!
Superman's address?
Come.
The three of us will
crush the son of our jailer.
Why not increase his handicap?
Since he cares so much
for these Earth creatures,
Iet us take his favorite.
Hey, ever heard of parachutes?
Another small step for mankind.
Scruffy.
So morbid.
A sentimental replica
of a planet long since vanished.
No style at all.
I expect better manners from my guests, Zod.
We must combine our strength.
Fools! Take him!
What?
We used to play this game at school.
Never was very good at it.
Superman, I knew that you'd... Huh?
Wrong again, Zod.
No, no!
Release the general or we'll tear her apart.
Superman, no! No!
Superman, don't!
AII right!
Did you really think we
would give up our advantage?
Now, the son of Jor-El
will be my slave. Forever.
If not, the millions of Earthlings you protect
will pay for your defiance.
Destroy this place.
- Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
- We have no more use for this one.
- Kill him.
- Me?
Lex Luthor?
General, you came to me with nothing.
I gave you Superman.
Silence!
Well, look...
Watch it. Don't touch me.
Guy's a clod.
Promises were made, gifts exchanged.
I gotta hand it to you, you know.
You always told the truth.
A guy always knew
where he stood with you.
Try to get them all
into this molecule chamber.
It takes away their powers, see,
and turns them into
ordinary human beings.
Now, if you could...
Shh, shh!
- Don't go in there. It's a trap.
- Luthor, you poisonous snake!
That's a molecule chamber.
It makes people like you
into people like me.
You've done well, Lex Luthor.
General, the crystal there
activates the mechanism.
Lex Luthor, ruler of Australia,
activate the machine.
Thank you.
With your permission.
And now, finally...
Take my hand
and swear eternal loyalty to Zod.
He switched it.
He did it to them.
I mean, the lights were on out here
while he was safe in there.
Hey, you know something?
You're a real pain in the neck!
- Are you all right?
- Uh-huh.
I knew you'd double-cross me, Luthor.
A lying weasel like you couldn't resist.
Who, me? Are you kidding?
Hey, I was with you all the time.
That was beautiful.
Did you see the way
they fell into our trap?
Too late, Luthor. Too late.
Look. Look, Superman.
I got a proposition for you.
Now, don't stop me till you've heard this,
because I know I owe you one,
but we're in the North Pole, right?
Let's wipe the slate clean.
If you give me a ride back,
I promise to turn over a whole new leaf...
It looks so beautiful from up here.
I guess I'll never get to fly with you again.
Oh, no. Anywhere you want to go.
You don't have to worry.
I'll never tell them who you really are.
I know, Lois. I know.
See you later.
- Hi, Leueen.
- Hm.
Hi.
How'd you sleep? All right?
No, I didn't close my eyes all night.
- Look, Lois...
- I understand, I understand.
I sat up all night listening
to the voices of reason.
You know how vile it is to hear
the first bird of the morning
when you've been crying all night?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
I guess it's sort of like being
married to a doctor, you know.
The doctor gets awakened
in the middle of the night
and the wife has to cope
with the fact that he's gone.
I guess I'm just too selfish.
No, no. You're not selfish at all.
Yes, I am selfish when it
comes to you. I am selfish.
And I'm jealous of the whole world.
Lois, it may not be easy for you to
hear this now, but someday you'll...
Clark...
Look, don't tell me that I'll meet somebody.
You're kind of a tough act to follow, you know.
Now, I'm gonna be fine.
You don't have to worry about me.
I Iike worrying about you.
Would you stop?
Don't you know that this is killing me?
Do you know what it's like to
have you come in here every morning
and not be able to talk to you?
Not be able to show I
have any feelings for you?
Not be able to tell anyone
that I know who you are.
I don't even know what to call you.
Lois, I don't know what to say.
I don't know. Just say that you Iove me.
Um... Gee, Lois, are you okay?
What happened?
- I just got so dizzy.
- You all right?
- I don't know.
- Get her some water, will you?
That's what happens
when I don't have orange juice.
- I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine!
- Breathe. Breathe, Lois.
- I'm breathing, for heaven's sake.
- Good for you. Good.
- God.
- Just drink.
- Okay.
- Just sip it, sip it, sip it.
- I'm fine.
- Boy...
What was I talking about before?
If I know you,
it was probably about Superman.
- Him again?
- Clark, Clark.
You've gotta stop being threatened
every time the guy's name's mentioned.
Nobody expects you to be
anything but what you are.
Well, I'Il try to remember that.
You better remember that. I appreciate you.
- You do?
- Sure.
- Especially if you get me a hamburger.
- Uh-huh.
A hamburger. At 9 a.m.?
Yeah, and everything on it, okay?
Everything on it.
- Oh, and...
- Orange juice. Sure.
Freshly squeezed. Okay.
Isn't he a nice guy?
Well, let's see what trouble
I can get into today.
Leueen.
What's happening in the world?
Leueen?
- Hey, Ron.
- Yeah?
Give me another plate of this garbage.
Garbage? That's my number-one special,
Rocky.
AII right. Get me some
more coffee too, will you?
Gee, that's funny. I've never
seen garbage eat garbage before.
Excuse me, sir. I think
you're sitting in my favorite seat.
Come and get it, four-eyes.
Now cool it, Rocky.
Take it easy, will you?
I just had this joint
fixed. It cost me a fortune.
Oh, God!
This order's to go.
I'm terribly sorry
about all the damage, sir.
Oh, I've been, uh, working out.
Good afternoon, Mr. President.
Sorry I've been away so long.
I won't let you down again.