Next, please.
Come on, come on.
Next.
Name.
Gus Gorman.
Ah, yes. August Gorman.
Have you looked for work this week?
- Yes.
- What kind?
- Kitchen technician.
- Dishwasher. Any luck?
No, but...
According to our records,
you have been unemployed for 36 weeks.
No, it's 35.
Not counting this week.
You secured employment in June as a
messenger and were discharged after...
...one day for...
- No, they said I lost it.
I did not lose it!
It was stolen by a pickpocket.
A television set?
It was a teeny tiny, teeny weensy
Japanese television set.
The other employment you found was
in a fast-food joint, which lasted...
...28 minutes?
That's some kind of record.
Talk about fast.
Those people are crazy. They expect
you to learn that stuff in one day.
"Hold the lettuce. Hold the ketchup.
Can I have some sauce, please?"
- Mr. Gorman...
- "Two buns. No buns. Some cheese."
Mr. Gorman, the city of Metropolis
is generous to a fault but...
- I'm not the fault!
- 36 weeks of chronic unemployment.
36 weeks of living off the taxes
of hard-working citizens.
- You know what you are?
- Don't call me a bum, I'm not a bum!
You are, I was about to say,
no longer eligible.
- Well, look...
- Next.
What about this week?
I need this week!
Next.
You mean, that's it?
"Finished," like "over"?
Next.
"Next" as in "bye."
Next!
Name.
Excuse me, brother,
can I have a light?
- How you doing, Alex?
- Hi, Jimmy.
Excuse me.
Say thank you.
Way to go, Superman!
Your drink is on its way.
Sir.
Excuse me...
...but what if you want to program two
bilateral coordinates at once?
You can't do that. It's impossible.
- But if you can't...
- Oh, no.
Computer technology is very advanced,
young lady, but it can't do that.
But if you think we can't
do it that way...
Good Lord.
How did you do that?
I don't know. I just did it.
- Who's this?
- That's him, Ross Webster.
They presented him with
the Humanitarian of the Year award.
He is good-looking.
Because I gave him f.2 at a 50th.
One thing I don't understand...
...the point of the story Lois wrote
is how Ross got this great honor...
...and you bring me one picture of him
and 15 pictures of her.
- Who is she?
- Lorelei Ambrosia. She's Webster's...
She's just Webster's.
Let's leave it at that.
- Who's this other woman?
- His sister, Vera Webster.
- Picture looks fuzzy.
- What?
The picture's fine, Chief.
She looks like that in real life.
- She's VP of WEBSCOE Industries.
- I really don't understand you.
A boring banquet and you bring me
3,000 boring pictures.
Yet Superman saves a man from
drowning on Third Avenue...
...while you just stand there and
you don't bring me one picture!
Chief, I didn't have
my camera with me.
A photographer eats with his camera.
A photographer sleeps with his camera.
- I'm glad I'm a writer.
- Mr. White, please.
It's time for you to draw this month's
winning JINGO number.
Prize is an all-expenses trip
to South America.
- Why the idiot in circulation...
- Good morning.
- Hi, Clark.
- Hi, Lois. Morning, Jimmy.
You've got mustard on your lapel.
Mr. White, I hate to interrupt...
I'm busy.
I got a paper to get out here.
It'll never replace
the printing press.
- What's the number, Mr. White?
- 53.
- Mr. White...
- 53!
- You need to pull three more numbers.
I promised I'd call them back today.
What do you think?
- Well, I don't know, Kent...
- I think it'd make a terrific story.
What's a terrific story?
Kent's been invited
to his high school reunion.
- Say.
- Yeah.
Could we have the next number?
It's practically an American ritual.
Right, Jimmy?
I don't know. Most of the people
I know are still in high school.
33.
What I thought this story
would be about...
33.
- Is how the typical small town's
changed in the last 15 years.
Take me, for example:
Can I go back to middle America
now as a Metropolis sophisticate?
I'm really excited about this.
I was looking around...
...in my closet last night...
...and even found
my old high school sweater.
- Smallville.
- Mr. White.
Can I go ahead and
make my travel plan?
Same question about mine.
Tell your people the prodigal son and
his photographer are coming home.
Oh, gee, thanks, Mr. White.
It isn't easy for me to lose
one of my best reporters.
- That's okay.
- You deserve the vacation, Lois.
Thank you.
Lois, are you going someplace?
Clark, you know some people get to go
all the way to Smallville...
...and then there are others of us
who have to go to Bermuda.
Golly.
Bye.
- Have fun.
- Mr. White, the next number, please.
Well, I guess I better be going too.
So I'll be going.
Bye.
Could we get a computer to do this?
Hey, what is this?
First paycheck.
This is the first rip-off, man!
Supposed to get 225 a week, right?
This says, "$143.80."
How am I supposed to live on that?
State tax, federal tax,
social security tax...
So you still get some money
when you hit 65.
So I'm getting money when I... 65?
I want mine now!
I want to enjoy it while I'm young.
Get up and get down. Boogie.
Actually, it's probably more like
$143.80 and one half cent.
There are always fractions left over,
but big corporations round it down.
What do I do with half a cent?
Buy a thoroughbred mouse?
Everybody loses those fractions?
They don't lose them.
Can't lose what you never got.
Then what happens?
The company gets them?
They can't be bothered collecting that
from your paycheck any more than you.
Then what happens to them?
Well, they're just floating around
out there. The computers know where.
How many sugars?
One and a half.
It's quitting time. You coming?
Yeah. No, actually I got some
stuff to finish up so...
Working overtime, huh? What are you
doing, buddy? Looking for a raise?
Yeah, looking for a raise.
You bet.
But my Uncle Al on my father's side,
he won't eat her stuffing.
He says it should be on the outside
of the turkey but she puts it inside.
Aunt Helen's my father's half sister.
I told you that, right?
Yeah.
- And anyway...
- Hey, hey.
- Look at that.
- Wow!
Okay, your choice:
Turn back or pull over till it's over.
- How long?
- Can't tell with these fires.
I mean, that fire...
That's spreading like wildfire.
It's just a building burning.
It's not just a building.
It's a chemical plant.
You know what I mean.
It's like... It's like chemicals.
If that stuff goes up in smoke,
it'll be a hairy time around here.
- Clark.
- Yeah.
I want you to keep them distracted.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Remember what the chief said?
Photographer always
goes after a story.
That could be dangerous.
Danger goes with the territory,
Mr. Kent.
Help me!
- How can I help?
- Get this man a helmet.
- Oh, it's you.
- How bad is it?
It's a nightmare. Everything's either
explosive or flammable or worse.
- Get the ladder truck.
- It won't reach.
My God, they're trapped!
What's he gonna do?
Fly them down one at a time?
Let's go! Everybody, down there!
Move it!
Come on! Hurry up!
There you go.
Right down there. Take it easy.
All right. Everybody down there!
Get out.
I'll show you the quickest way.
Look after the others.
I can't leave here.
- Why not?
- I have to look after those.
That's concentrated Beltric acid.
If it heats up over 180 degrees,
we've got a crisis...
...that'll make this fire
seem like a picnic.
What does it do?
As long as it remains stable,
it's just ordinary acid.
But if it begins to heat up,
it'll turn volatile.
You'll get a great cloud of smoke
that'll eat through anything.
Steel, concrete, anything.
Who the hell is that?
- Hey, you! Get off of there!
- Just gonna get a couple more shots.
Tell them to bring their hoses
back here! Quickly!
Help!
Help me!
Help! Somebody help me!
- Help!
- It's all right.
- Superman! My leg.
- I got you. Take it easy.
We'll go nice and easy.
Okay, I'm sorry.
All right? Here we go.
Medics! Over here, please.
That's it. Here you go.
Go easy. It's the left leg.
- Camera.
- Yeah.
It's a clean break across the fibula.
- My camera.
- Sorry, Jimmy. You'll be okay.
Get the fire out! Or there'll be
a cloud of acid all over the East.
- Christ, the pump house is gone!
- What?
- The pump house!
- We've lost the water pressure!
- We've got to have water!
- How?
Lake Comooga's five miles away!
We'd need a five-mile hose!
- Where's this lake?
- That way.
- Tell them it's hopeless.
- We had an adequate water supply.
Water!
I tell you, that man's a miracle!
Carol, you got gorgeous!
Look at you.
That was against Mid-City.
I'll never forget it.
Fourth quarter, score was tied...
...we're back at the 25 yard line.
Coach sends in play,
Right Flanker Option.
You really have grown, Clark.
You look very well, Miss Bannister.
I can't complain. I take the stairs
a little slow and I have these spells.
But really, I can't complain.
Lana?
Clark?
Would you excuse me? There's
someone I'd like to say hello to.
Lana?
- Lana Lang? It's great to see you.
- Clark.
- You look wonderful.
- Me? No, you look... Wow!
- Let me give you a hand with that.
- I can manage.
First time you've come back
since your mom passed away.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I heard that you and...
...Donald split up.
- Did you eat yet?
No.
Beg your pardon. Excuse me. Sorry.
- That's not right.
- No?
You're right about Donald and me...
Hold that.
Oh, sure.
- Hi, Kent.
- Oh.
Hi. How you doing?
I'm sorry. I'm going nuts.
- Clark.
- Yeah.
Lana.
Uh-oh.
Hey, sweet.
Here I am.
Remember when you were prom queen?
All us guys were waiting for a dance?
There's only one guy on your
dance card now. Good old...
Brad Wilson.
- Hi, Brad.
- Hi, Kent.
Long time no see.
You know, see, see, see?
- Come on, Lana.
- No, I can't.
Clark already asked me.
- I did?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
Lana, I haven't danced...
Ah, Gorman.
Another week, another check.
Don't you have another one for me?
I put in a voucher for expenses.
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks for helping me out.
A lot of guys would like
to be where I am.
You'd be surprised at how many offers
I didn't get. Even Brad didn't stay.
- It really isn't easy.
- The streamers? You just pull.
No, not streamers. Everything.
Not that I'm complaining.
It's just that...
...I don't know why, I just feel
like I can talk to you.
What?
I feel like I can talk to you!
- You can?
- Yes.
- You know something, Lana?
- What?
I always...
I always wished that you would.
I mean, even back in high school.
- Remember when you were...
- Queen of the prom.
Three years after the royal wedding,
the king abdicated.
Isn't that terrible?
- Yeah, sure is.
- There's a ton of potato salad left.
You know what the problem is?
Don't know, too much mayonnaise?
Donald loved mayonnaise.
Why would that be the problem?
No, the problem is,
why do I stay in Smallville?
I've asked myself that.
Do you know how lucky you are to live
in Metropolis? The Big Apricot.
- Well, you could...
- Easy to say. What about Ricky?
Ricky?
My little boy.
- You? Oh, that's great.
- Yeah.
At least here we have a house and
I've got a job that pays the bills.
Except for last winter when
the fuel bills kept going up and up.
Yeah. Even had to pawn
my diamond ring then.
That's a shame.
You never got married?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Well, I was...
No. Not...
Years later you can look at
someone and think...
..."Well, I guess that's
the one that got away."
Give me that again, old buddy.
Run it by me just one more time.
- $85,000.
- Missing.
Embezzled, Mr. Webster.
Stolen from the firm.
By whom?
That's what I want to know.
By whom? Whom?
Vera, get ahold of yourself.
Nobody else ever will.
I don't know.
Whom?
In the old days, it was simple.
We kept books, we knew what was
going in and what was paid out.
If somebody wanted to rob you...
...they'd use a gun and say,
"Stick 'em up."
Now they get blasted computers
to do their dirty work.
My friend, you are yesterday.
Whoever pulled this caper,
is tomorrow.
Mr. Webster,
it's time for your massage.
Bubba, can she burst in...
Now, now, Vera. Simpson,
you know my psychic nutritionist?
- Hello.
- We are trying to hold a meeting here.
Why don't you hold your breath
instead? Maybe you'll turn blue.
- Improvement.
- I'm about to take a human life.
Simpson, would you excuse us
for a second, please?
- Mouths closed. Ears open.
- She's a big pig.
I can't have anyone with me
who isn't with me.
Now, girls.
Simpson.
Well, old chum. What now?
Kiss the 85 thou goodbye?
Keep on paying the thief his salary
until he shakes the money tree again?
- He's bound to slip sooner or later.
- Why?
That's what they always say
in the movies.
He won't slip up at all.
No, not at all.
He'll keep quietly taking
the bread from our mouths.
He'll keep a low profile and won't do
a thing to call attention to himself.
Unless, of course, he is
a complete and utter moron.
I'll go first. Andrew.
- I'll pick Chris.
- You feel good? You feel ready?
Ricky, your shoe.
- You mean, we've gotta take Ricky?
- You guys lost the toss.
All right, come on Ricky.
- Wait, wait...
- Come on, good luck.
- I just can't stand this.
- Oh, Lana. It'll be okay.
I know, I was a late bloomer myself.
It's not just that he's small, he's
the only kid in town without a father.
Oh, look. Stewed to the gills
in the middle of the afternoon.
- I only had chocolate milk.
- No, him.
Hey, sweet thing.
Little kid getting hassled, huh?
- Kent, you still here?
- I seem to be, Brad.
All he needs is a few pointers
from the old champ here.
I won the all-country bowling trophy
two years in a row.
I didn't know that.
Yeah. Natural athlete
can play any sport.
- It's all right. It'll be okay.
- He'll make it worse.
You watch, he'll get a spare.
Come on, Ricky.
Kid, you're holding it all wrong.
- Let old Brad show you how it's done.
- Brad.
Excuse me. Say, Brad, I think maybe
he'll be better off doing it his way.
For a guy lucky to be waterboy,
you've got a big mouth.
I don't think he needs a lesson
in front of the other kids.
- He needs a man to show him.
- He's doing just fine. Excuse me.
Here you go, Ricky.
And give it your best shot.
Okay? There you go.
Sorry.
Gesundheit.
Thank you.
Hey, Gus, the boss wants to see you.
He can see me all right.
Hello, Mr. Lewis.
No, not that boss. The boss.
You mean, the boss...
...wants to see me?
Oh, my God,
why would he want to see me?
I mean...
Why would the boss want to see me?
There's no reason.
Then why'd he?
Oh, I know!
It's my suggestion for
the volleyball uniforms.
That's it.
Ross the boss. Ross the boss.
The boss!
Be calm. Be cool. Be collected.
Mr. Webster? Mr. Webster?
Mr. Webster, I did not...
Mr. Webster.
Mr. August Gorman?
August Gorman here.
I know you're a man of compassion,
and I don't want to go to jail...
...because they have
robbers and rapists...
I just want to ask you one question.
You've been a naughty guy,
haven't you?
Come on, admit it, now.
You've been a little bit naughty,
haven't you?
- I was kind of...
- That's all right. I understand.
I can...
What do the young folks say today?
"Dig where you're coming from,
brother."
You want to be rich, right?
I was born rich. Never worn
the same pair of socks twice.
What do you do with your socks?
They're laundered and sent to
some charitable institution, I think.
I don't know.
Maybe they turn them into rags...
...or pen-wipers or something.
Or maybe socks.
Yes! That never occurred to me.
Gus, you know something?
You're a genius.
A naughty genius, but what the hell?
Nobody's perfect. Cheers.
Because of the half-cent thing
with the computers.
No, no, because computers rule
the world today.
The fellow that can fool the computers
can rule the world himself.
I've been searching for somebody
who can make these machines do...
...what they're not supposed to.
Get my drift?
Yes!
Webscoe, the Webscoe industrial
complex, is a family-owned cartel.
Some magnesium here,
some zinc there.
Railroads, farm machinery.
You follow?
I follow you, sir.
Gus, do you know what I want now?
I want coffee.
Black, cream, sugar, or?
No, you don't seem to understand.
Under different company names,
I control the price of coffee beans...
...in Venezuela, Brazil, Bolivia,
Jamaica and the Republic of Gabon.
But I've got a problem and I think
maybe you can help me.
One country won't play ball with me.
You know how that can bug a guy.
That could bug...
What country?
Colombia.
Colombia?
Colombia has two import and exports,
and one of them's coffee.
And I've tried to reason with them.
Believe me, I've tried.
But this one miserable,
pissant little country...
...has the gall to think it can
dictate the economy of an open market.
Gus, my friend...
...we're going to teach them
a lesson, aren't we?
Destroy the entire
Colombian coffee crop...
...right down to the last bean.
- The last bean, we are.
- Right.
But you got so much...
A wise man once said, I think
it was Attila the Hun:
"It is not enough that I succeed.
Everyone else must fail."
Seems fair.
- Gus.
- What?
You are going to do this for me.
- How?
- The weather.
You didn't say your mom was here.
I'm his sister. His baby sister.
Gus, tell me, have you ever
heard of Vulcan?
Hi, Ms. Vulcan.
Vulcan is the weather satellite
our government put up...
...to monitor the weather.
But if somebody were to reprogram it,
it could do much more.
It could make weather.
Storms and floods.
Blizzards, heat waves.
How do you do that?
Like everything else
in the 20th century, Gus.
You push buttons.
- There you go.
- It's the first time I won anything.
You won my hand, Maury.
But this is the first time
I won anything valuable.
Let's get one with the sombreros.
Mr. White, you'll be in this,
handing them their plane tickets.
- Why do I have to do this?
You're lucky I didn't fire you.
I get a chance at exclusive photos...
...of history's biggest
factory fire.
He comes home with a broken leg
and 12 melted rolls of film.
It was hot.
Smile, Mr. White.
South America!
I can't believe my luck!
See, if you don't want them
to trace it back...
...you've gotta punch in
to some little rinky-dink outfit...
...that has a little
Mickey Mouse computer...
Someplace you can sneak into, right?
Somebody could...
Someplace where nobody knows him
so they can't connect him with us.
Webscoe has 112 subsidiaries.
They're all linked into
the central computer system.
How about someplace...
...small?
Whoa, there. This is Smallville.
We'll have a five-minute stop here.
Mind your step.
Watch your step, please.
Thanks, Selma.
Thanks a lot, Lana.
Have a good day, now.
Let me help you, Lana.
I'm sorry.
- Thanks, Clark.
- Sit down, Buster. Good boy.
Come on, Buster, sit down.
Good boy.
You all set? Great.
I'm not saying another word.
That's it.
Jesus Christ!
Don't they have picnics in Metropolis,
Mr. Kent?
Well, not quite like this, Ricky.
- Mom and I do this all the time.
- You do?
- I'll help you.
- Stay close by and be careful, okay?
Okay, Mom.
Come on, Buster. Let's find you
a rabbit. Come on. Rabbit.
This is so nice for him.
It's even nicer when there's
a man around, which isn't that often.
- There's a lot of choices.
- The good ones are married.
So Brad thinks he's
God's gift to women.
He won't take no for an answer,
but he's the only one asking.
No, Lana, I meant
there's a lot of choices here.
This is really quite some picnic.
There's...
...some of that.
Green stuff.
Hey, pâté.
Boy, this pâté is really unusual.
I didn't make any...
Oh, Clark.
That's Buster's dog food.
- It's good.
- Don't eat it!
What time's the dog eat?
- This is nice.
- Here.
It's all right, Lana.
Thanks.
Hey, where you going?
Come on!
Buster, stop messing about!
- How much longer?
- I thought...
- Sorry. No, go ahead.
- You.
I was just thinking that...
...somebody like you could do
really well in Metropolis.
I have to face it. I'm not gonna
find what I want in Smallville anymore.
Could I make it in Metropolis?
What would I do when I got there?
Call me.
- No, I wouldn't want to call you.
- You don't want to call?
Yes, I want to call you, but I
wouldn't want to be a nuisance to you.
I don't think you could ever
be a nuisance to me.
Clark, may I tell you something?
My oil pan is leaking.
There's something dripping.
- Can I help?
- No, thanks.
With all the car trouble I have,
I studied up on auto repair.
Look at this.
Oh, boy.
I think I'll just go see
if Ricky's all right. You okay?
Gosh, is he all right?
Superman?
That's me.
Mom! Mom!
There you go. He's all right,
but have a doctor check him.
Thank you.
- I'm Lana Lang. This is Ricky.
- Nice to meet you.
And this is Clark.
I really have to be going.
So long, Ricky. Bye.
We were flying, Mom!
What were you doing, anyway?
I was looking for Buster.
I found him!
Come on, boy. That's it.
Mr. Kent, Superman was here!
- What?
- Yes, he really was.
Aren't you excited?
I'm from Metropolis.
I see Superman every day.
You do? Could you get me
his autograph?
I don't know. If I had a nickel
for every time some little kid...
Yeah? What do you want?
We're in big trouble, aren't we?
- What?
- We're in big trouble.
First, they lost the invoice.
When they found it, they realized
they came up short on a few items.
So I rented a car because I missed the
plane from Cleveland. 4:00, you know.
And a flat tire on the highway.
What a kicker.
Had to fix it myself
with these little pinkies.
And I figured your boss was gonna be
real peeved, you know what I mean?
What do you mean?
He is going to hang our butts
against the wall.
He wanted this special order
installed...
...in his office by tomorrow morning.
So let me in because
I gotta set it up tonight.
Get all what set up?
Pal, you are a real lifesaver.
I mean, a real lifesaver.
- Which way's the office?
- Straight ahead.
- Follow me.
- I'm right behind you.
Not bad. It's pretty good.
You know what's wrong with
this Singapore... wing?
Sling! Singapore Sling.
What's wrong with it?
There's not enough vodka in it.
There's no vodka in it!
What did I tell you?
Put some vodka in it.
What did you... you know?
Here. There's vodka in it now, buddy.
Yeah, perfect.
- You never do pass out, do you?
- Nope.
Never.
Job well done, buddy.
You thought I was drunk too,
didn't you?
Fooled you.
Get the keys, get the keys.
Hello, baby!
How's the little baby?
All right, let's get down to it.
Let's do it.
One, two, button your shoe.
"Both keys at the same time"?
Wait. Wait a minute.
Think you've won, don't you?
The Philly Flash!
Okay, ready?
One, two, three!
We'll see what we'll see.
Come on, please.
There it is!
Hello! Now...
...getting down to business.
I am a genius.
I am a...
Longitude...
...and the other thing.
Latitude, right?
Oh, look, Maury.
A native wedding.
No one said at the Daily Planet
that this is the rainy season!
Meteorologists are baffled by
the tornado and rainstorms...
... that struck Colombia
this afternoon...
... threatening to destroy its entire
coffee crop for the next five years.
Gale force winds up to...
...an incredible 250 miles an hour
lashed the countryside...
...while 12 inches of rainfall have
already been recorded in just one day.
A spokesman for the Department of
Meteorology said, this was, I quote:
"The most awesome display of
natural forces since Noah's ark. "
If I laugh any harder,
I'll split my sides!
- To defy all laws of
weather systems known to science.
What a shame.
Poor little Colombia. Well...
I'm gonna get you for that,
you big silly!
Bubba, do you realize
what we're onto?
Do I?
Every time a drunk sobers up,
he'll drink Webster coffee.
Why stop at coffee?
A cup of coffee gets the world
off to work in the morning.
But what keeps the world working?
Diet soda?
Vera, you mean?
You mean?
Today, coffee.
Tomorrow...
...the oil!
- Oil?
- If Gus can push the right buttons...
I can have it all.
Holy cats!
All the oil.
All the pumps.
All the tankers.
This is some nifty idea, Vera.
- Boss?
- Very nifty.
- Just the man I want to see.
- It's not my fault.
Isn't it neat? There...
- What's not your fault?
- Superman.
How was I to know he'd start
doing his thing...
...when you started doing your thing?
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talk?
It was just on television, man.
Didn't you see it?
Don't call me "man."
I just saw Colombia bite the dust.
You didn't see the man come flying
out of the sky? It was him!
With his cape flapping in the...
His cape was flapping in the wind!
He was flying! He was great!
He was just flying around...
His cape was blowing in the wind.
It looked like a flag!
And he landed right in the middle
of this big plantation!
And he checked everything out
with his x-ray vision.
And then he put these laser beams
out of his eyes onto everything.
Straight-out laser points.
Dried up everything!
Just like that!
Dried it up,
like the machines in the men's rooms.
You know what I mean?
Hot air comes out when you put
your hands under.
Sometimes they don't work.
But Superman's works!
You think he stood around
to take bows? Not this man.
No, sir. He flies off again!
Then he saw what
really caused the trouble.
He flew into the tornado...
...went down to the bottom of it,
and turned it upside down!
He made the little end on top
and the big end on the bottom!
I was gonna go crazy!
Big end was on the bottom.
Mr. Ross, it was...
The big...
Superman's bad.
I'll say he was.
I mean, he was bad!
No.
Here, let me help.
- The perfect plan. Foolproof!
- And we were the fools.
It's not my fault.
I did what I was supposed to do.
He ruined it.
That lousy do-gooder ruined it.
Now that he's pulled off this stunt,
he'll try and ruin my oil scheme too.
- I've got to get rid of him.
- How?
Shoot him?
You know about him and bullets.
- Kryptonite.
- What?
Or krypton-ham, or krypton-heimer?
I forget what you call it,
but it's stuff that can hurt Superman.
- How do you know?
- I know a few things.
I know,
from the graffiti I saw.
Wait a second.
She's right.
I remember reading about it
in an interview with him.
Where is it from?
The planet Superman came from:
Krypton.
Where is Krypton?
It's nowhere.
It blew up in space, years ago.
They sent Superman here from there
when he was just a baby.