Next!
Name?
Gus Gorman.
Ah, yes.
August Gorman.
Have you looked
for work this week?
Uh...yes.
What kind?
Uh...
Kitchen technician.
Dishwasher?
Any luck?
A little, but...
Mr. Gorman, you've been
unemployed for 36 weeks.
No, it's 35.
Not counting this week.
You secured employment
last June
As a messenger
and were discharged
After one day
for losing--
No, no, they said
I lost it.
I did not lose it.
It was stolen
by a pickpocket.
A television set?
A teensy-weensy Japanese
2-inch television set.
The only other
employment you found
Was in a fast food
joint which lasted...
28 Minutes?
That's some record.
Talk about fast!
They expect you
to learn stuff in one day.
Hold the lettuce!
Hold the ketchup!
Can I have some sauce?
2 Buns! No buns!
Cheese! No cheese!
The city of Metropolis
is generous to a fault.
I'm not the fault!
36 Weeks of
chronic unemployment,
Living off the taxes of
hard-working citizens.
Do you know
what you are?
I'm not a bum!
You are...
I was about to say,
No longer eligible.
No longer--
Next!
I need this week!
You mean that's it?
Finished? Like, over?
Huh!
Next!
Next.
Next as in "bye."
Next!
Name?
Excuse me, brother,
can I have a light?
Say thank you.
Wow!
Way to go, Superman!
Computer: your drink
is on its way.
Uh, sir?
Excuse me, but...
What if you want to--
Enjoy your drink!
Program 2 bilateral
coordinates at once?
You can't do that.
But if you--
Computer technology
is very advanced,
But it can't do that.
But if we can't
do it that way...
Sir?
Good lord!
How did
you do that?
I don't know.
I just did it.
Who's this?
That's him,
ross webster,
Just after he
received the award
For humanitarian
of the year.
Oh, he is
good-looking!
I gave him
F-2 at 1/50th.
One thing
I don't understand
Was the point of the story
lois wrote
Is how this ross webster
got this great honor.
And you bring me
one picture of him
And 15 pictures
of this other person.
Who is she?
Lorelei ambrosia.
She's webster's--
She's just webster's.
Let's leave it at that.
Who's this
other woman?
That's his sister Vera.
Picture looks fuzzy.
The picture's fine.
She looks like that.
She's vice president
of Webscoe Industries.
I don't understand you.
A boring banquet,
And you bring me
3,000 boring pictures.
Superman saves a man
from drowning
On 3rd avenue,
And you don't
get one picture!
I didn't
have my camera!
A photographer eats
with his camera,
Sleeps
with his camera.
I'm glad I'm a writer.
Time to draw
the jingo number.
The prize is
a south American trip!
I don't know why--
Morning,
everybody.
Hi, Clark.
Jimmy, you've got
mustard on your lapel.
Mr. White, I hate
to interrupt--
I'm getting
a paper out!
Stick to
the printing press.
What's the number?
"53."
Mr. White?
53!
You've got to pull
3 more numbers.
Mr. White,
what do you think?
I don't know.
I think it would make
a terrific story.
What's a terrific story?
Kent's high school
class reunion.
Say!
Could we have
the next number?
It's practically
an American institution.
Most of
my classmates
Are still
in high school.
"33."
I thought the story
would be about--
33!
How much small
towns have changed.
Can I go back
to middle America
After having become
a Metropolis sophisticate?
I was looking around
in my closet last night
And I even found...
My high school sweater.
Uh...Smallville.
So should I make
my travel plans?
What about mine?
All right, Kent.
The prodigal son
is coming home.
Gee, thanks, Mr. White.
It's hard losing one
of my best reporters.
Oh, that's OK.
But you deserve
the vacation, lois.
Thank you.
Lois, are you
going someplace?
Some people get
to go to Smallville.
Others of us
have to go to...
Bermuda.
Golly.
Bye.
Have a good time.
Mr. White,
the next number, please.
Well, I guess
I'd better be going, too.
So...I'll be going.
Bye.
Couldn't
a computer do this?
Hey, what is this?
First paycheck?
First rip-off, man.
I'm supposed
to get 225 a week.
How am I supposed
to live on 143.80?
State tax, federal tax,
social security.
You'll get money
when you're 65.
When I'm 65?
I want mine now,
while I can enjoy it.
I want to get down!
It's more like
$143.80 and 1/2 cent.
There are always
fractions left over
In big corporations,
But they
round it down.
What am I supposed
to do with 1/2 a cent?
You mean everybody
loses those fractions?
They don't
exactly lose them.
You can't lose
what you never got.
So the company
gets it?
Not really.
They can't be bothered.
Then what
happens to them?
They're just floating
around out there.
The computers
know where.
How many sugars?
One and a half.
It's quitting time.
You coming?
I've got some stuff
to finish up, so...
Working
overtime, huh?
What you doing,
looking for a raise?
Yeah.
Looking for a raise.
That's it.
You bet.
But my uncle Al
won't eat her stuffing.
He says it should be cooked
outside the turkey.
She cooks it on
the inside of the turkey.
Aunt helen,
my father's half sister--
I told you that,
right?
Yeah. Hey,
look at that.
Wow!
Turn back or pull over
here and wait.
For how long?
I don't know.
That fire's spreading
like wild...fire.
It's just
a building burning.
That's a chemical plant.
You know what I mean,
it's like chemicals.
If that goes
up in smoke,
We'll be in for
a hairy time around here.
OK.
Distract these people
So they don't know
what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
The chief says a photographer
always goes after a story.
That could
be dangerous.
Danger goes with
the territory, Mr. Kent.
How can I help?
Get this man
a helmet.
Oh, it's you.
Forget the helmet.
How bad is it?
It's a nightmare.
Everything's explosive,
inflammable, or worse.
Get me a number 3
ladder truck in here!
My god,
they're trapped!
What's he going to do,
fly them down one at a time?
Let's go!
Everybody down here!
Hurry up!
Go on down.
Take it easy.
All right,
everybody down.
You've got to
get out of here.
I cannot leave.
I've got to
look after those.
That's concentrated
beryltric acid.
If it heats
over 180 degrees,
This fire will
look like a picnic.
If it remains
stable, no problem.
If it heats up,
it'll turn volatile.
If that happens,
you'll get a cloud
That'll eat
through anything--
Steel, concrete, anything.
Who the hell's that?
Get off of there!
I'll just get
a couple more shots.
Oww!
Ahhh!
Have them bring
their hoses here! Quickly!
Help!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Help!
Superman!
It's my leg.
Take it easy.
We'll go nice and easy.
All right?
Here we go.
Medics!
Over here, please!
That's it.
Here you go.
It's the left leg.
My camera.
Yeah.
It's a clean break
across the fibula.
Ow! My camera.
It's all right, Jimmy.
You'll be OK.
Get that fire out, or
you'll have an acid cloud!
Christ!
The pumphouse is gone!
The pumphouse!
We've lost
the water pressure!
We've got
to have water!
Lake canoga's
5 miles from here!
Where's this lake?
That way.
You told me we had
an adequate water supply.
That man's a miracle.
Carol, you got gorgeous!
?? Tell Tchaikovsky
the news??
?? I've got a rockin'
pneumonia??
?? I need a shot
of rhythm and blues??
?? Whoo??
?? I think I'll
call in all the writers??
?? Written down
by the rhythm reviews??
?? Roll over,
Beethoven??
?? Rockin' in
two by two??
I'll never forget it.
Fourth quarter,
score was tied.
We were back on
our 25-yard line.
The coach calls for
right flanker option.
?? Roll over, Beethoven??
?? Rocking in
two by two??
You really
have grown, Clark.
You look very well.
I can't complain.
I have these
little spells,
But, really,
I can't complain.
?? Well, early
in the morning??
?? I'm a-giving you
the warning??
?? Don't you step on
my blue suede shoes??
?? Hey, diddle-diddle,
I will play my fiddle??
Excuse me.
There's someone
I'd like to see.
?? And tell Tchaikovsky
the news??
Lana?
Lana lang?
It's great
to see you.
You look
wonderful.
You look...wow!
Here, let me.
Oh, no, no.
I can manage.
Uh...
Isn't this
your first visit
Since your mom
passed away?
Yeah--I'm sorry.
Um...
I heard that you
and donald split up.
Did you eat yet?
No.
I beg your pardon.
Excuse me. Sorry.
That's not right.
You're right about
donald and me,
But hold this
a second, OK?
Oh, sure.
Hi, Kent.
Oh, hi.
How you...doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm going nuts.
Thanks.
?? Well, early
in the morning??
?? I'm a-giving you
the warning??
Clark.
Yeah.
Hey, Lana.
Uh-oh. Um...
Hey, sweet.
Here I am.
Remember when
you were prom queen?
Everyone wanted
to dance with you.
There's only one guy
on your dance card now.
That's good old--
Brad Wilson.
Hi, brad.
Hi, Kent.
Long time no see.
You know, see. See?
Come on, Lana.
I can't.
Clark already asked me.
I did?
Oh, excuse me.
Lana, I haven't danced...
?? Roll over,
Beethoven??
?? Stick to these
rhythm and blues??
?? Oh-oh-oh-oh??
?? Wa-a-a??
?? Earth angel??
?? Will you be mine???
?? My darling dear??
?? Love you
all the time??
?? I'm just a fool...??
Ah, Gorman.
Another week,
another check.
Don't you have
another one for me?
I put in a voucher
for expenses.
What?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Here you go.
Woooh!
A-hem.
Thanks for
helping me out.
A lot of guys would like
to be where I am.
You'd be surprised
how many offers
I didn't get.
Even brad wouldn't
stick around for this.
It isn't easy.
The streamers?
Just pull, and they...
Not the streamers.
Everything.
I don't know why,
I feel like
I can talk to you.
What?
I feel I can
talk to you!
You can?
Yes.
You know
something, Lana?
What?
I, Uh...
I always wished
that you would.
Remember when you
were queen of the prom?
3 years after
the royal wedding,
The king abdicated.
Isn't that terrible?
Yeah, it sure is.
There must be
a gallon
Of potato salad
left over.
You know what
the problem is?
Too much mayonnaise?
Donald loved mayonnaise.
Why would you think
that was the problem?
The problem is,
Why do I stay
in Smallville?
Do you know
how lucky you are
To live in Metropolis,
The big apricot?
Lana, you could--
How? And what
about ricky?
Ricky?
My little boy.
You have...
That's great.
Here we have a house,
and I've got a job.
I'm only a secretary,
but it pays the bills.
Except for last winter
When the fuel bills
kept going up and up.
I had to pawn
my diamond ring.
That's a shame.
You never got married?
Me?
Yeah.
Well, I was...
No. Not.
You know,
years later,
You can look at
someone and think,
"That's the one
that got away."
Give me that again.
Run it by me
just one more time.
$85,000.
Missing?
Embezzled,
Mr. Webster.
Stolen
from the firm.
By whom? That's
what I want to know.
Vera, get a hold
of yourself!
Nobody else
ever will.
I don't know, who?
In the old days,
it was simple.
We kept books,
We had ledgers,
We knew what
was paid out.
A robber carried
a gun and said,
"Stick 'em up."
Now these blasted computers
do their dirty work.
My old friend,
You are yesterday.
Whoever pulled this
caper is tomorrow.
Honey bunch?
Mr. Webster, it's time
for your massage.
Does she have the right
to burst in--
No, no, Vera, Vera!
Simpson, you know
My psychic
nutritionist?
Hello.
We're trying to hold
a meeting here!
Hold your breath instead.
Maybe you'll turn blue.
Ha! Improvement.
I'm about to
take a human life!
Simpson, would you
excuse us, please?
Tell her I won't
to stop-- let her--
Mouths closed.
Ears open.
She's a pig!
I can't have
anyone with me
Who isn't with me.
Now...
Simpson,
Well, old chum,
what now,
Kiss the 85 thou
goodbye?
Keep paying
the thief his salary
Until he thinks up more ways
to shake the money tree?
He'll slip up
sooner or later.
Why?
They say that
in the movies.
He won't slip up.
He'll keep
a low profile.
He won't do a thing
To call attention
to himself.
Unless, of course,
He is a complete
and utter moron.
We're first.
Um...Andrew.
I'll pick chris.
Um...mark.
I'll take Jamie.
We're stuck
with ricky?
You lost
the toss.
Come on, ricky.
Good luck.
I can't stand this.
He'll be OK.
I was a late
bloomer myself.
It's not just that
he's small for his age.
He's the only kid
in town without a father.
Look, he's stewed
to the gills
In the middle
of the afternoon.
He only had
chocolate milk.
I mean him.
Hey, sweet thing.
Kid getting
hassled, huh?
Kent, you still here?
I seem to be.
The kid needs pointers
from the champ here.
I won the all-country
bowling championship.
I didn't
know that.
Actually, I can play
any sport.
Brad, you'll just
make it worse.
Clark, he'll
Watch. He'll get
a spare.
Come on, ricky.
Hey, kid, you're
holding it all wrong.
I'll show you.
Uh, brad...
I think he'll
be better off
Doing it his way.
You got a big
mouth, Kent.
Ricky doesn't need
a bowling lesson
In front of
the other kids.
He needs a man
to show him.
He's doing fine
on his own.
Excuse me.
Here you go.
Give it
your best shot.
Oh! Sorry.
Ah-choo!
Gesundheit.
Thank you.
Hey, gus.
The boss wants
to see you.
He can see me
from here.
Hello, Mr. Lewis.
Not that boss.
The boss.
You you mean the boss?
Yep.
Wants to see me?
Why would
he want to see me?
Why would the boss
Want to see me?
There's no reason.
Oh, I know!
My suggestion for
the volleyball uniforms.
That's it.
Ross the boss.
Bossy ross the boss.
Be calm, be cool,
be collected.
OK, uh...
Mr. Web--Mr. Webster?
Mr. Webster?
Mr. Webster, I did not...
Mr. August Gorman?
Aah! Sir!
August Gorman here.
I know you're
a compassionate man.
I don't want
to go to jail
Because there's
robbers and rapists--
Just one question.
You've been
a naughty guy,
Haven't you?
Come on, admit it.
You've been
a little bit naughty.
I was--
That's all right,
I understand.
I can--what do
young folks say?
"Dig where you're
coming from, brother."
You want
to be rich, right?
Well, I...
I was born rich.
Never worn
the same socks twice.
What do you do
with your socks?
They're laundered
And sent to some
charitable institution.
Maybe they're turned
into dust rags
Or something like that.
Or maybe socks.
Yes. That never
occurred to me.
Gus, you know
something?
You're a genius.
A naughty genius,
But nobody's
perfect.
Cheers!
Because of the thing
with the computers.
Because computers
rule the world today,
And the fellow
that fools computers
Can rule the world.
I've been searching
for a long time
For somebody to make
these machines do
What they're not
supposed to do.
Understand?
Yes!
Webscoe, the Webscoe
industrial complex,
Is a family-owned
cartel.
Little
magnesium here,
Little zinc there.
You follow me?
I follow you.
You know
what I want now?
No.
I want coffee.
Black?
Cream or sugar?
You don't
understand.
Under different
company names,
I control the price
of coffee beans
In Venezuela, Brazil,
Bolivia, Jamaica,
And the republic of gabon.
But I've got a problem,
And I think
you can help me.
One country
won't play ball.
That can bug a guy.
That could bug...
What country?
Colombia.
Colombia!
Colombia has 2
important exports.
One is coffee.
I've tried
to reason with them.
But this one
miserable country
Thinks
it can dictate
The economy
of an open market.
Gus...
Gus, my friend,
We're going to teach
them a lesson,
Aren't we?
Mr. Webster...
Destroy the Colombian
coffee crop
Right down
to the last bean.
The last bean?
We are?
But you got so much.
You know--
A wise man said--
I think it was
Attila the Hun--
"It is not enough
that I succeed.
Everyone else
must fail."
Seems fair.
Gus.
What?
You are going
to do this for me.
How?
The weather.
You didn't tell me
your mother was here.
I'm his baby sister.
Gus, have you ever
heard of Vulcan?
Hi, miss Vulcan.
Vulcan is
the weather satellite
That's monitoring
the weather.
If somebody were
to reprogram it,
It could do more.
It could make weather.
Storms and floods.
Blizzards,
heat waves.
How do you do that?
Like everything
in the 20th century,
You push buttons.
There you go.
It's the first time
I've won anything.
You won my hand.
This is
the first time
I won anything
valuable.
Get one with
the sombreros.
Mr. White,
you be in this.
Do I have to?
Why do I?
You're lucky
I didn't fire you.
I get a chance
to get exclusive pictures
Of the biggest chemical
factory fire in history,
And he comes home
with a broken leg
And 12 melted
rolls of film.
It was hot.
Smile,
Mr. White.
South America.
What luck!
If you don't want
to be traced,
Punch in to some
rinky-dink outfit
That has
a mickey-mouse computer.
Someplace you can
sneak into, right?
Someplace where
nobody knows him
So they can't
connect him with us.
Webscoe has
112 subsidiaries.
They're all linked
Into the central
computer system.
How about
someplace...small?
Smallville!
This is Smallville.
We'll have
a 5-minute stop.
Watch your step, please.
Thanks, selma.
Have a good day.
Let me
help you, Lana.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thanks, Clark.
Sit down, buster.
Good boy.
Come on,
buster.
Sit down!
All set? Great.
Wow.
That's it, OK?
Jesus Christ!
Don't they have
picnics in Metropolis?
Not like this,
ricky.
We do this a lot.
You do?
Stay close
and be careful.
OK, mom.
Come on, buster.
Let's find
a rabbit.
This is nice
for him.
It's even nicer
When there's
a man around.
There's a lot
of choices.
All the good
ones are married.
That's why
brad thinks
He's god's
gift to women.
He won't take no
for an answer.
I meant there's a lot
of choices here.
This is some picnic.
There's some of that...
And...mmm!
Green stuff.
And...hey, pat?.
Boy, this pat?
Is really unusual.
I didn't make pa--
Oh, Clark.
That's buster's
dog food.
It's good.
Don't eat it!
This is nice.
Here.
It's all right, Lana.
Thanks.
Hey!
Where you going?
Come on! Buster!
How long--
I was thinking--
Sorry. Go ahead.
You.
Well...
I was thinking
somebody like you
Could do well
in Metropolis.
I have to face it.
I'm not going to
find what I want
In Smallville
anymore.
Could I make it
in Metropolis?
What would I do?
Call me.
I wouldn't want to.
Wouldn't want
to call me?
I wouldn't want
to be a nuisance.
You couldn't
be a nuisance, Lana.
Clark, may I
tell you something?
My oil pan
is leaking.
See? There's
something dripping.
You need a hand?
No, thanks.
I studied up
on auto repair.
Look at this.
Oh, boy.
Lana, I'll go see
if ricky's all right.
You OK?
Yeah.
Gosh!
Is he all right?
Hi.
Superman?
That's me.
Mom! Mom!
Ricky!
Have him checked
by a doctor.
Thank you.
I'm Lana lang.
This is ricky.
This is Clark.
I have to be going.
So long, ricky.
We were flying!
What were you doing?
Looking for buster.
Buster!
I found him!
Mr. Kent?
Superman was here!
What?
He really was.
Aren't you excited?
I'm from Metropolis.
I see Superman
every day.
You do?
Could you get me
his autograph?
If I had a nickel
for every time...
What do you want?
We're in big trouble.
What?
First of all,
they lost the invoice,
Then realized they were
short on some items.
I rented a car because
I missed the plane.
Had a flat tire
on the highway.
Had to fix it myself
with these pinkies.
I figured your boss
would be real peeved.
What are you
talking about?
He'll hang our butts
against the wall.
He wanted this order
installed
No later than tomorrow.
I got to set up tonight.
Get what set up?
Pal, you're a real
lifesaver.
I mean
a real lifesaver!
Where's the office?
Straight ahead.
Follow me.
Right behind you.
Oh, yeah.
Not bad.
Pretty good.
Do you know
what's wrong
With this
Singapore wing?
Sling.
Singapore sling.
What's wrong
with it?
There's not
enough vodka.
There's no
vodka in it!
What did
I tell you?
Put some vodka
in it.
What did you...
You know, hey...
There's vodka
in it now, buddy.
Yeah.
Yeah, perfect.
You never pass out,
do you?
Nope.
Never.
Cowboy's down, buddy.
You thought
I was drunk, too,
Didn't you?
Ha ha! Fooled you.
Get the keys.
Yeowww!
Some...some...
Somebody's drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Hello, baby.
OK.
All right.
Let's get down to it
And let's do it.
One, two,
button your shoe.
Then put it in...
Both keys...
At the same time?
Ho ho!
Wait. Wait a minute.
You think you've won,
don't you?
The philly flash.
Vroom! Vroom!
OK...ready?
1...
2...
3!
Yeah. Now...
We'll see
what we'll see.
Oh!
Oh...
Oh.
Come on.
Please let me in.
There it is!
Hello. Now!
Getting down to business.
I am a genius.
I am a...
Um...longitude.
And the other thing...
Latitude, right?
Oh, look, Morey.
A native wedding.
I arriba!
They never told us
this was the rainy season.
Newscaster:
meteorologists are baffled
By the tornado
and torrential rainstorms
That struck Colombia
this afternoon,
Threatening to destroy
the nation's coffee crop
For the next 5 years.
Gale-force winds
up to 250 miles an hour
Have lashed
the countryside,
While 12 inches
of rainfall
Have been recorded
in one day.
A spokesman from cal tech
Said this was the most
awesome display of--
Turn it off!
If I laugh harder,
I'll split my sides.
...Seems to defy
all laws of weather systems
Known to science.
Poor little Colombia.
Well.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ooh! I'll get you
for that,
You big silly!
Bubba, do you realize
what we're on to?
Do I? Every time
a drunk sobers up,
He'll drink
webster coffee.
Why stop at coffee?
Coffee gets
the world off to work.
But what keeps
the world working?
Diet soda?
Vera, you mean...
You mean--
Today, coffee...
Tomorrow, the oil!
Oil?
If gus Gorman can push
the right buttons--
I can have it all.
All the oil,
all the pumps,
All the tankers.
This is some
nifty idea, Vera.
Boss!
Just the man
I want to see.
It is not my fault.
What's
not your fault?
Superman started
doing his thing
When you started
doing yours.
What are you
talking about?
What am I--
It was on
television, man.
Don't call me man.
I saw Colombia
bite the dust.
You didn't see the man
flying out of the sky
With his cape
flapping in the...
His cape was
flapping in the wind.
He was flying!
He was great! Wooshhh!
His cape blew
in the wind like this,
And he landed
in the middle
Of this big plantation.
He checked everything out
with his x-ray vision.
Then he put laser beams
Out of his eyes
onto everything.
Bzzzz!
And guess what?
Dried up everything,
just like that!
Dried it up
Like machines
in men's rooms,
You know, where
the hot air comes out?
Sometimes
they don't work.
But Superman's worked.
And you think he took bows?
No, sir.
He flies off again!
He saw what
caused the trouble
And flew
into the tornado,
Went down to the bottom
of the tornado,
And turned it
upside down!
I thought
I'd go crazy!
I've never seen
anything like it!
The big end was
on the bottom.
The little end
was on the top.
Mr. Ross, it was...
Superman's bad.
I'll say he was.
I mean, he was bad!
No.
No!
Let me help.
It was a perfect plan,
foolproof!
We were the fools.
It's not my fault.
I did what I was
supposed to do.
He ruined it.
The lousy do-gooder
ruined it.
Now he'll stick his nose
into my oil scheme
And ruin that, too.
I've got to
get rid of him.
But how,
shoot him?
Kryptonite.
What?
Or Kryptonham...
Or Kryptonheimer?
There's stuff that
can hurt Superman.
How would you know?
I know some things.
So I understand from
the graffiti I've seen.
She's right.
Kryptonite! I remember
reading about it.
Where does
it come from?
The same planet
Superman came from--
Krypton.
Where is Krypton?
It blew up in space
many years ago.
They sent Superman here
when he was a baby.
I know some things, too.
Wait a minute.
You know what happens
when a planet explodes--
Debris, things
floating in space.
We have to find out
where in heaven Krypton was
And have gus contact
the Vulcan satellite.
Gus has
been thinking.
That's why
I keep you around.
I'm thinking I'm not
making enough money
For this gig.
Gus...
If there's anything
I hate, it's greed.
Greed? Mr. Ross,
just a minute.
Let me tell
you something.
I can't ski!
Ahhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Ohh!
Ross: once gus contacts
the Vulcan satellite,
He orders it
to search outer space
Around where Krypton
went bye-bye.
The laser probe
Locks onto a chunk
of Kryptonite.
The computer analyzes
the components,
And the lab
duplicates the stuff.
Unknown?
What the hell?
They don't smoke it.
Mr. White can't
be disturbed.
After all,
he is the editor.
Where is he?
He'll pay for this.
It's not
Mr. White's fault.
Get out your wallet,
Mr. Editor!
Good morning.
Don't "good morning" me!
"Old relationships suddenly
seem very much the same.
"The prettiest
girl in school..."
"Is still the prettiest
girl in school."
Hello.
Hello?
Oh, hi, Clark.
Lana! Hi.
I was just
thinking about you.
Oh! Listen, I have
a problem with ricky.
Why? What's wrong?
It's the autograph
you got from Superman.
He told the kids
Superman's coming for
his birthday Wednesday.
When Superman doesn't
show up, it's going to...
Well, in this case,
I think I can
speak for Superman.
We're pretty close.
Tell ricky Superman
will be there on Wednesday.
Well, he'll get the best
home-cooked meal
He's had
in a long time.
Tell Superman we think
he's wonderful.
But, Clark...
You're the best.
I'll take it to
the supreme court.
It wasn't our fault.
It was
an act of god.
In a church?
Hey, here's that
compound you ordered.
Can't imagine
what you want with it,
But you got it.
What the hell
am I afraid for?
I'm from earth.
Lana, I really wasn't
expecting all this.
I guess they
got carried away.
Superman...
We all know
That you're not
looking for honors,
But when we heard
You were coming
to see ricky,
We realized this
was our chance
To thank you
For putting
out the fire
And for saving
little ricky.
Since you already
have the key
To our hearts,
Superman...
May I present you
With the key
to the city?
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
As you were!
Now, listen up!
I just came directly
from the pentagon,
And you better believe
There's a damn
good reason I did.
Because god's given us
One of the greatest gifts
in the world--
Chemicals!
You like to sit in church
on Sunday, don't you?
You like to sit
and watch the super bowl.
Sit on what?
You sit on
molded plastic seats--
Molded to your
well-fed behinds!
I don't have
to tell you
That America leads
the world in plastics.
We cannot afford
a chemical plastics gap!
Now, listen to me.
Do you want
Our president
of the united states
Sitting down
to write a peace treaty
And have his
ballpoint pen bust open
And ink run
all over his pants
In front
of world leaders?
Now we all know
That last week,
Half of this
great nation
Almost bit the bullet,
If it wasn't
for this man here.
Yay!
All I can say
Is thank the lord
for Superman.
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Superman,
you saved our bacon,
And I'd like to
show our gratitude.
This is a small token
of our appreciation
For saving us from
a chemical plant disaster.
Thank you.
Thank you
very much, general.
It's very nice.
Thank you.
How do I know
what "unknown" means?
Unknown means nobody
knows what it is.
Hello, boss?
Gus Gorman here.
I know that.
How did it go?
You know how they're
trying to find the recipe
In that chicken
in the bucket,
And nobody knows
the ingredient
Because it's unknown?
Well, in Kryptonite,
there's an unknown element,
And Superman didn't die.
He didn't die.
I asked you
to kill Superman,
And you're
telling me
You couldn't do that
one simple thing?
Uh...
Hello?
Hello.
He hasn't had
a nap for years.
This was a big day.
Thank you.
Thank you for that
wonderful lunch.
I do like to cook.
You'll take coffee,
won't you?
Yes, please.
Decaffeinated,
of course.
Right.
Hello?
Yes.
What?
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
He's here.
I'll tell him.
Bye-bye.
That was my
friend betty.
There's been an accident.
A truck crashed
through the river bridge.
It's hanging off
the side of the bridge,
And the driver's
still in the cab.
I hate to rush you.
There's no rush.
But the bridge.
I always get
there on time.
Let's relax.
It's unusual finding
a good-looking girl
Like you
alone like this.
Listen, um...
Shouldn't you
do something
About the bridge?
What bridge?
You're right.
I have to
get going.
Get him
out of there!
Get him out, quick!
That thing's
going to go.
Everybody OK?
What can I do?
Nothing, now.
If only you'd
gotten here sooner.
Stronzo, Superman!
"At a special session
of the general assembly,
"178 Countries voted
to censure Superman
With only
Colombia abstaining."
I can tell you
one thing.
He wasn't so
mean and nasty
In Smallville.
He was so nice,
I hated laying that
big chunk of...
Kryptonite!
Don't you see?
That stuff wasn't
a complete failure after all.
After gus
gave it to him,
He became
an evil, selfish--
A normal person.
Now that Superman
Is out of the nice guy
business...
We can work
on that oil.
Ha ha ha...
Announcer: and now,
the supreme moment
As the last runner,
The one
given the great honor
Of lighting
the ceremonial flame
Runs the last leg
of a marathon
That began 7 days ago,
As this torch
was passed
From athlete to athlete
For 970 miles
Across the country.
How can he say
pure categories
Have no meaning
in transcendental logic?
What about
synthetic unity?
Hi, honey.
Am I in your way?
Stick around.
You might
learn something.
Hi, Lorelei.
Oil tankers are
controlled by computers.
Computers tell them
where to go
And where
to deliver oil.
Don't they
have captains?
Yes, but they
don't need them.
It's sentimental
seafaring baloney.
You'll command
the tankers
To sail toward
a 50-mile area
In the Atlantic.
And do what?
And do nothing.
Just sit there.
How will the people
get their oil?
You catch on fast,
old buddy.
Every oil pump
in America
Is run by--
Computers,
I know!
Stop interrupting!
I'm sorry.
You will command
the pumps
To stop pumping.
Then I want you to program
one special command
Into all these systems.
Tell them these orders
are irreversible
So it will be
impossible for anyone
To switch them back.
Can you do
this for me, old buddy?
Old pal?
You get your way
all the time.
And it's not right.
When do I
get a taste?
I think you've already
Had a taste of freedom,
haven't you?
Or would you
prefer jail?
You can't run
that jail number anymore.
I mean more
to you out here
Doing things for you
Than sitting in jail
doing nothing for nobody.
I see.
What do you want?
A wastebasket?
No.
These are plans.
Blueprints.
For what?
A computer.
You've already
got computers.
There's not a computer
like this anyplace.
It doesn't exist.
We have to build it.
What will it do?
Anything I tell it.
What will it do for me?
Anything you tell me
to tell it to do for you.
Tell me.
First of all,
If anyone attacks
this machine,
The computer
counter-attacks them.
It finds their weaknesses
and wipes them out.
Right. You deal
with my oil,
And I'll build you
your machine.
OK, I'll do it,
But I'm not sure about
this irreversible business.
All kinds of--
what the hell?
That's it.
The last tanker.
They're all mine now.
All mine.
Yay!
Not quite.
Hmm?
What's that in the upper
middle quadrant?
It's a tanker.
And it's going
the wrong way.
Skipper, there it is again.
"Proceed immediately
to latitude 30 north
"Longitude 45 west.
There await
further orders."
That's the middle
of the Atlantic.
I'm not going there
Just to await
further orders!
We're supposed
to go to Metropolis,
And we're going
to Metropolis.
That's where she is.
Get it up there!
Miss!
Miss, can you
hear me?
We're here
to help you!
Do not jump!
I repeat,
do not jump!
Thought you'd
never get here.
Don't expect
me to save you.
I don't
do that anymore.
I'm long past saving.
Well...don't let me
keep you from anything.
I'm in no rush.
What did you
have in mind?
Lots of things.
Oh, yeah?
Ah!
Ooh!
Do me one
favor first.
What's that?
Well...
There's this
little boat,
And it's
not going
Where it's
supposed to go.
Man: stop all engines!
Stop all engines!
The third
and fourth tank!
Hi.
How about a little
aprs ski?
Champagne?
Aah!
Take your turn
like anybody else!
Fred! Stop it!
He's coming
over here, Martha!
Ooh! Ooh!
Don't you do that!
Oh!
Please!
Hit him with
your handbag!
Please help me!
Somebody's beating up
my husband!
Jack,
go with her.
Third one today.
At night,
it's worse.
Somebody's
behind this.
You can't tell me
there's no oil
And that someone's
not getting rich off this.
Someone's always
getting rich.
And you know who suffers?
The small guy.
Radio: the east coast gets
the brunt of the spill.
Guys,
take that in here.
No, I cannot go out
with you tonight.
I'm busy
tomorrow night, too.
Doing what?
I'll think
of something.
I got to go.
Ricky needs me.
Brad, please
stop calling!
Listen to me.
You better
appreciate brad.
What else you
got in Smallville?
What else have I got
in Smallville?
I think I got
the right answer.
So do I.
Smallville airport.
What flights do you
have to Metropolis?
Mmm.
Where do I put this?
Over there.
There.
Where do
you want this?
Put it up there!
Are you kidding?
I'm not
going in there.
Hey! Hey!
Just leave
him alone.
I can't get through.
There's something
happening.
Look!
Superman's drunk!
I want to see
what's happening.
Ricky! Ricky!
Ricky!
Thank you.
It's a disgrace.
Nobody'll trust
that creep again.
What are you
looking at? Huh?
Excuse me, Superman,
It's me, ricky.
Ricky from Smallville.
Say you won't
hurt anybody!
Ricky, he's changed!
Maybe he's
just sick.
Superman, please
get better!
He's not listening
to you.
Yes, he is.
He's got
super hearing.
Superman, you're
just in a slump!
You'll be
great again!
Do it, Superman!
Superman, you
can hear me,
Can't you?
Superman, you're
just in a slump!
You'll be
great again!
You can do it,
Superman!
Superman, you
can hear me.
You're just
in a slump.
I know
you can...
You can do it,
Superman.
Aaaaaahhh!
He's gone nuts!
Come on!
Ha ha ha ha!
I can give
as good as I get.
Yeah? All right.
Come on! Come on!
Too warm for you, huh?
Huh?
Come on, chicken!
Come and get me.
Get up!
Aah!
You always wanted
to fly, Kent.
Now's your chance.
Skipper!
Would you
look at that?
Ross: Lorelei ambrosia
isn't at home,
But if you care
to leave a message,
Why not deliver it
to her in person?
So you've finally
shown your true colors.
If you're
looking for us,
Here's where
you'll find us.
Do drop in.
These are fun!
Fun? The fun's
just starting.
Wait till
Superman finds us.
Then you'll see fun.
You're going to
mess with Superman?
I want to be ready
When he
falls into our trap.
Why can't you
balloon down like us?
Oh...
No way.
I don't believe
a man can fly.
Gee! Watch out,
horsie!
No! Don't, don't!
Just don't
try to fly.
Don't try to fly.
Hey there!
Get out of my way.
Hurry!
Here we are!
I am hurrying.
I can't
see anything!
Turn on the light.
Where's
the light switch?
Where do you
usually find it?
Oh! It's
pitch black!
Ooh,
that's better.
Wow! What
a jukebox!
I told you,
didn't I?
There!
The ultimate computer.
It does everything
a normal computer can do
And a thousand things
none of them can do.
Let's give it
a dry run.
We've got to
wait for gus.
Who needs gus?
He's the only one
who can operate it.
I know enough
about computers
To put a ph.d.
To shame.
You didn't think
I'd let him run the show.
Peons never tidy up
when they're done working.
Come on, Bubba,
it's showtime.
Engage those buttons
To activate
the alpha circuit
And unlock
the modular grid.
You!
Activate circuits
29 Through W-7
And start full
power coordinates
On exterior
defensive systems.
In other words,
push this red button.
How did you
know about that?
He's here!
Let's give him
something to worry about!
Now let's see...
Tracking systems locked.
Let the games begin!
Don't tense up,
honey.
Nearly!
Come on, Bubba,
you're wasting rockets!
Come on,
Superman!
Let him have
it, ross!
Bubba,
keep firing.
I'll get
the M-X ready.
What the hell
is going on?
Yo! Hyah! Whoa!
Keep your rockets coming!
He won't notice the missile
until it's too late.
So much for your
catlike reflexes.
God!
Aha!
Oh! Oh!
No! No more!
Look! You sit!
Sit!
Help!
Hello!
Git, you jackass!
That's him out of the way!
Now, sister,
Would you
like to control
All the world's
weapons systems?
Baby! It's daddy!
What are you doing
with my baby?
Gus, old buddy genius!
Come join the fun!
He's still coming!
Arm the inner defenses!
Webster,
the game's over.
Hi, honey.
I don't know you.
But the other night...
I'm sorry.
That wasn't me.
That guy's gone.
You're next, webster!
Never underestimate
the power of computers.
How do you like it?
It's typical of you.
All you four want
is to help yourselves.
"Four...of you"?
You mean us...
Four?
Wait!
Oh, hey, man!
That's only
his last name.
Call him
Superman.
See, I'm not
with them, Superman.
You could
have fooled me.
That's very good.
Let's see how long
he can carry on without air.
He's going to get me!
Don't bet on it!
No! No...
Ahhh...
You're hurting him.
Ah!
That's Kryptonite!
This time
we got it right!
You're a genius.
You've invented
a machine
That finds
anybody's weak spot.
You'll go down
in history
As the man
who killed Superman.
I'm--no.
Superman!
No!
Wait a minute!
Turn the power up!
He's had
enough power.
Turn it up!
Power! More power!
Ah! Oww!
OK...75.
37, Then 75.
Please...
There's a current
level of 7.
It's not
supposed to be...
There it is!
Shh! Shh!
What's going on?
I don't know.
The power's gone.
Gus pulled
the plug out!
It works.
It works!
I got it!
I got the...
I...Ooohhh...
What have
you done?
Ohhhh...
Give me that.
This screw?
That screw.
Never.
Hey! I can't see!
Holy...
No! Make it stop!
It's out of control!
But how?
Where's the power
coming from?
It's feeding itself.
It wants to live!
What's this here?
We'll go to the zoo.
Then we'll go--
What's happening?
It's OK, ricky!
Turn the lights on!
Stop it!
You're killing him!
Don't! Stop!
Yeah!
Put me down!
Don't leave us
alone, Superman!
I get it.
The coaxial shaft
Is endangering
the grid source factor.
We're through, frogface.
I'm splitting!
Wait a minute!
Hey, girls!
Girls! Come on!
Sis!
Oh! Help me!
Sis?
Oh, my god!
What is that?
Lorelei!
She got me!
It's your Bubba!
Help me! Help!
Superman!
Honey!
Honey, I'm
stuck here!
What about me?
Look out!
Aah!
Bubba?
Thank you,
brother.
Regular
or premium?
What the hell?
Give her
the good stuff.
How you doing
there, gus?
Please don't talk!
I'm having enough
trouble hanging on.
I'll go slow.
You're perfectly safe.
Any man who can
trick my machine
Can do anything.
How did you beat
my defenses?
The machine didn't know
it was in trouble.
I went in there
with plain acid.
When that stuff
gets hot enough,
It'll eat
through anything.
Watch the trees.
I guess it died
of...acid indigestion.
What will happen
to webster
And the ladies?
They'll have to
see the police now.
Whoa! Are we in
Metropolis yet?
No. We're going to
make a little stop.
Whooooaaa!
We're on
the ground, gus.
You OK, supe?
I'm fine.
Excuse me.
Can you guys
spare one of these?
Sure, Superman.
It is Superman,
ain't it?
Are you kidding?
Didn't you see us
Fly out of the sky?
We're the only
2 men who can fly.
Just right.
OK, gus. Let's go.
I was thinking
about taking the bus.
Suit yourself.
Does your boss
have a computer?
Yeah, he's got
a little bitty one.
Tell him to give
gus Gorman a job.
Well, thank you, supe.
Take care.
I'll see you
around.
So long!
Take it easy, man.
Well, you got
good references.
If you want
that job...
Uh...
Well, nah.
This is not for me.
Where is
the bus station?
9 Or 10 miles
over there.
9 Or 10 miles?
OK.
You really
flew with him?
Superman?
Have you ever seen
Superman before?
No.
You don't know
about me and him?
Me and Superman?
Yeah, we go
way back together.
We always--usually--
sometimes--we...
9 Or 10 miles?
I think I'll walk.
Yeah, I'll walk.
Yeah.
Clark!
What a surprise!
Come in.
Hi, Mr. Kent.
Hi.
Mom's having dinner
with Superman tonight!
That's what
I came to tell you.
Superman's sorry,
But he's had
a problem.
He can't
have dinner tonight.
I guess he misses
a lot of dinners.
Would you
settle for me?
Any day!
I'll get my things.
OK.
Lana, I was talking
to Superman.
He and I talk a lot.
He felt badly
About you having
to pawn your ring.
And...
Well, he found...
He found this one
just lying around...
He wanted you
to have this.
A ring from Superman!
I'll get it.
Look at that!
Oh, Clark!
It's OK.
It fits!
Looks really pretty.
Well!
Brad!
Son of a bitch!
Kent, I hate you.
I've always hated you.
You know why?
No.
'Cause you're nice.
And nice guys
finish last!
Arrgggh!
Lois, I've got to
hand it to you.
Who else
turns a vacation
Into a story
About corruption
in the Caribbean?
I knew I was onto something
when I was kidnapped.
Lois, you're terrific!
I have to be.
Seems I've
got competition.
That story you wrote
on the class reunion?
I thought
it was terrific.
Thanks.
I liked the little
girl back home.
Tell me about it
at lunch.
I'm having lunch
With Mr. White's
new secretary.
Hi, Lana.
Lois, this is Lana,
Smallville's newest
gift to Metropolis.
I like your
writing a lot.
Thank you.
I like your
sparkler a lot.
I was surprised
When Clark
gave it to me.
Clark?
Yes.
Mr. White!
Look what
I've got!
I'm in love with
this machine!
I have errands
to run before lunch.
Go ahead,
Mr. White.
Where's the handle?
Just push
the button!
Giorgio, por favore?
Grazie.