Where are we? Is this the Pulitzer?
Nope. I've just gotta ask these people
a few questions and then we can go.
Can I stay in the car?
No, honey.
- Are we trespassing?
- No. Yes.
Hello?
I like the curly one.
Let's go. This was a bad idea.
Lex Luthor.
Lois Lane?
You're bald.
And what is your name?
I'm not supposed to talk to strangers.
- Cute kid, and smart.
- Thanks.
We're not really strangers, are we?
This is kind of a little reunion.
Heck, I'm a fan.
I love your writing...
...and your dress.
- I love your boat.
How'd you get it?
Swindle some widow out of her money?
That's funny. Didn't you win
the Pulitzer Prize...
...for my favorite article of all time, "Why
the World Doesn't Need Superman"?
Didn't you have a few more years to go
on that double life sentence?
Yes, well, we can thank
the Man of Steel for that.
I mean, he's really good at swooping in
and catching the bad guys...
...but he's not so hot at the little things,
like Miranda rights...
...due process, making your court date.
Did you have anything to do
with the blackout?
Are you fishing for an interview,
Miss Lane?
It's been a while
since you've been a headline.
Maybe it's time
people knew your name again.
How about we turn this boat around,
call a cab for my son...
...and then you can do
whatever you want with me.
No, I don't think we'll be
turning around, Miss Lane...
...which means that
we do have some time to kill.
How about that interview?
Yeah, just call me if you hear anything.
Okay. Thank you.
So, what did the school say?
She picked him up at 3:15.
- Hi, I heard about Lois.
- Yes, come in, Clark, come in.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Yeah, you're a reporter.
- Help Richard track her down.
- I'll check her computer.
Excuse me, Clark.
What do you know about crystals?
They make great chandeliers.
This crystal may seem unremarkable,
but so is the seed of a redwood tree.
It's how our mutual friend in tights
made his Arctic getaway spot.
Cute. It's a little small for my taste.
You're building an island?
You're not seeing
the big picture here, Miss Lane.
Let me enlarge it for you.
Not just an island,
an entirely new continent.
An extinct world, reborn on our own.
Why?
Land, Miss Lane.
I mean... Kitty, what did my father
used to say to me?
"You're losing your hair"?
- Before that.
- "Get out"?
He said, "You can print money...
...manufacture diamonds,
and people are a dime a dozen...
...but they'll always need land."
It's the one thing
they're not making any more of.
But the United States...
Will be underwater.
It's simple physics, Miss Lane.
Two objects cannot occupy
the same space at the same time.
And the rest of the world
will just let you keep it?
- They'll...
...what?
I'll have advanced alien technology...
...thousands of years beyond
what anyone could throw at me.
Bring it on!
And eventually...
...the rest of the world
will be begging me...
...for a piece of high-tech
beachfront property.
In fact, they'll pay
through the nose for it.
But millions of people will die.
Billions! Once again,
the press underestimates me.
This is front-page news.
Come on, let me hear you say it
just once.
- You're insane.
- No! Not that. No, the other thing.
It's dangling off the tip of your tongue.
Let me hear it just once, please?
- Superman will never...
- Wrong!
What is that?
I think you know exactly what this is.
Mind over muscle, Miss Lane.
Mind...
Who is that boy's father?
Richard.
Mr. Luthor, we're approaching
the coordinates.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir. Latitude 40 degrees north,
longitude 73 degrees west.
Don't let them leave this room.
Kitty, come with me.
You're not gonna want to miss this.
- Damn it.
- What?
She has a password.
"Jason."
"Richard."
Try "Superman."
"Superman." Great.
Don't touch that, honey.
Why don't you go play the piano.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lex, this isn't like the train set.
I know.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
- Honey, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Open this door! Open it!
Could you help Mommy open the door?
I'm sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay? It's gonna be okay.
We had a little problem downstairs.
Brutus is dead.
He got hit with the piano.
Where's the boy?
With the mother,
locked up in the pantry.
Oh, it's time for us to go.
My camera's not working.
And my phone's not working.
- Okay, I'm good.
- That was weird.
Hey, guys.
This just came through the fax.
It's Lois' handwriting,
I'd recognize it anywhere.
I just... No idea
what the numbers mean.
- They're coordinates.
- Coordinates.
That's just off the coast.
Jimmy, tell Perry I'm taking the seaplane.
Keep trying her cell.
What are these, lottery numbers?
I think they're coordinates, chief.
Chief...
Come on! Move it!
Chief!
Great Caesar's ghost.
- Daddy.
- Oh, my God.
How did you get here?
I flew.
Look out!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Jason, come here! Jason!
Come here! Watch your head!
Come here!
Mommy! Mom!
Jason!
Jason, hold on!
- Have you got him?
- I got him! Go!
Hold on! Hold on!
- Mommy!
- Give him to me!
Mommy!
- Mommy! Mommy!
- Come on, Jason! Come on!
- Lois! Lois!
- Mommy!
Jason, get on my back.
Give me your hand.
- Have you got them?
- Yeah.
Get buckled in!
She'll be fine.
I can't take off in this.
- I'll point you in the right direction.
- Thank you.
See anything familiar?
I see an old man's sick joke.
Really? Because I see
my new apartment...
...and a place for Kitty,
one for my friends...
...and that place over there, I'll rent out.
But, you know, maybe you're right.
You know, maybe it is a little cold.
It's... What's the word I'm searching for?
It's a little...
...alien.
It lacks that human touch.
You have something that belongs to me.
Metropolis Tower, this is seaplane
November-Seven-Two-Four-One-Hotel.
Do you copy?
Metropolis Tower, this is seaplane
November-Seven-Two-Four-One-Hotel.
Do you copy? Damn it!
Metropolis Tower, this is seaplane
November-Seven-Two-Four-One-Hotel.
Do you copy?
Lois! Are you all right?
Yeah. What happened?
- Superman.
- Where is he?
He went back.
- Richard, we have to turn around.
- What? No.
- We have to turn around!
- We barely made it out of there.
- Now you want me to go back?
- Yes, please!
He'll die.
All right, hold on.
Kryptonite.
You're asking yourself, "How?"
Didn't your dad ever teach you
to look before you leap?
Crystals. They're amazing, aren't they?
They inherit the traits
of the minerals around them...
...kind of like a son
inheriting the traits of his father!
You took away five years of my life,
I'm just returning the favor!
I'm still Superman!
Get up! Come on!
Now, fly.
So long, Superman.
Your leadership can stir others...
...to their own capacities
for moral betterment.
The human heart is still subject
to monstrous deceits.
Our destruction could have been avoided.
At this very moment...
...I could embrace you in my arms.
Your help would be called for endlessly.
Remember me.
Even for those tasks which human beings
could solve themselves.
Remember me, Kal-El.
Remember me.
Superman's down there.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Richard!
- Yeah, I saw him. Strap in.
Lois!
Don't move.
Come on, come on, come on.
Richard!
I'm trying! It's too choppy!
Oh, my God.
How did you find me?
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I have to go back.
You're hurt!
Goodbye, Lois.
The technology on Krypton,
Superman's home world...
...was based on manipulating
the growth of crystals.
Sounds like hocus-pocus to me.
Well, naturally, to the primitive mind,
any sufficiently advanced technology...
...would be indistinguishable from magic.
But imagine: cities, vehicles, weapons...
...entire continents, all grown.
Lex?
Are billions of people really going to die?
Yes.
Lex, what's happening?
Go, go, go. Get to the helicopter.
Go! Out, out! Now!
No, no, no, take nothing!
Take nothing! Go, go!
Got it.
Here.
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry!
No!
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry!
Watch it.
- Clear a path.
- Clear the way.
- Move!
- Trauma One.
- Where we going?
- Trauma One. Here it is.
Watch it!
Got him!
Okay, I think I got it.
Penetrating side wound
to right part of lower back.
No hemorrhage.
Shock at 200.
Is that enough? He's not human.
All right, charge to three, 360.
Clear!
It's kind of morbid, Perry.
Always be prepared.
How is she?
Thank you. Thanks, baby.
- Lois?
- Yeah.
We can leave whenever you're ready.
I mean...
...you don't have to be here.
Where else would I be?
Police have surrounded the area in order
to control thousands of visitors...
...who have arrived
to show their support.
Many are carrying signs and banners...
I could drive.
- no official announcements
over the past few hours...
...but unconfirmed reports
from inside tell us...
...the Man of Steel lies in a coma...
...his condition unchanged
since he was admitted late yesterday.
- Doctors have been vigilant in their...
- Foreign exchange markets...
- Where are you going?
- To the hospital.
I'd be careful down there, guys.
It's a madhouse.
- So much for parking.
- Do you think I can get in?
You're Lois Lane. They'll let you in.
I wanna go with Mommy.
Taxi.
I'll be right here.
Watch your head, okay? Here we go.
This way, Miss Lane.
Mommy? Is he gonna get better?
- I don't know.
- I want him to.
I like him.
Me too.
I don't know if you can hear me.
They say sometimes
that when people are...
That sometimes they can hear you.
I don't know if you can hear me.
I wanted to tell you...
Come on, honey.
Step back, please!
Lex, we only have six of those!
Six?
I would trade 300,000 coconuts...
...and every ounce of your blood...
...for a quart of gasoline!
But what will we have to eat?
You will be different.
Sometimes, you will feel like an outcast.
But you'll never be alone.
You will make my strength your own.
You will see my life through your eyes...
...as your life will be seen through mine.
The son becomes the father...
...and the father becomes the son.
Good night!
I...
Will we see you?
Around?
I'm always around.
Good night, Lois.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group