Misha!
Listen carefully...
...my son.
By now, Kal-El...
...you are entering the
atmosphere of the planet Earth.
I pray you have made a safe journey.
Your new home's yellow sun
gives you great physical powers.
But it cannot console your spirit.
Placed aboard this vessel
is an energy module...
...all that remains
of a once-powerful civilization:
Krypton, your mother planet.
It is my last gift to you.
Once removed, the ship will
grow cold and silent...
...and you will be finally alone.
The power in the module
can be used but once.
Use it wisely, my son.
Clark, you out here?
Clark Kent!
Hi, Mr. Hornsby. Over here.
- There you are.
- How are you, sir?
- I'm fine. How are you?
- N ice to see you.
- It's been a Iong time.
- A Iong time.
I was tidying up for you
to show it.
Did I mention there was
an offer to buy, sight unseen?
I don't want to sell
to a big developer.
The buyer has to want a farm,
not a shopping center.
Now darn it, Clark,
why are you so stubborn?
Today, nobody wants a farm.
You blink your eye and they'll
all be gone. That's progress.
Oh, my gosh, look at this.
Oh, what a joker
old Jonathan Kent was.
You know, I asked him
what happened to the baby's crib.
And he said:
"Oh, little Clark must've had
a bad dream and kicked it."
- I swear, Dad Iiked a good joke.
- Yeah.
Maybe you'd like
to keep these for your grandchildren.
Why, thank you very much, Clark.
Here, batter up.
- Oh, no...
- Come on. We'll hit a few.
Watch out now, these will
come in pretty fast.
You never could hit a curve ball!
My decision's final about the place.
I'm holding out for a farmer.
You are?
You're just as obstinate
as your father was.
I'm sorry, that's
just the way it is.
Be careful when you get back
to Metropolis.
It's a long way from
where you were born.
Yes, sir.
I never forget that, sir.
- Bye.
- Bye, Clark.
What is that God-awful noise
you're making?
Mozart, my low-forehead friend.
Even this wretched pit can't diminish
true genius.
Life itself started in a murky pit
like this.
A true genius like myself
Iearns to seize the moment.
You're the first to know...
...that I now have plans
to re-create Iife itself.
Luthor, start breaking a sweat
or we'II throw you to the wolVes.
Get them duds dirty.
- Move it, meathead.
- Let's see you sweat.
What's that car doing here?!
Stop that vehicle!
- Hey, stop!
- Hold it there, son.
Where the hell is this and how
do I get to Cedar City?
Ha, ha. You on the wrong side
of the state.
- No chance.
- Oh, no.
You got a fine, fine super-fine
sound system here, son.
I guess you dudes never seen
these Sensurround 100s?
Yeah, I seen one once in a magazine.
Well, heck. Come on, get in.
- Really?
- Come on.
- You want to hear it, come on!
- AII right.
Hop in, Bubba.
Let's give it a listen.
This is great!
Doors...
- What's going on?
- Windows...
- Whoa! What's happening?
- The top.
Seats!
Lordy! Lordy!
And away!
Y'all come back and see us!
Launch.
AII right!
Did I do okay or what, Uncle Lex?
Lenny, you're the Dutch elm
disease of my family tree.
But you did fine.
You gonna skip the country, Uncle Lex?
You pathetic product of the public
schools, I've thought of nothing else...
...since I've been incarcerated
except one thing:
- Destroy Superman!
Sorry.
Clark!
Help!
Help! Help!
Somebody get help!
Superman!
He's okay. He needs a doctor.
Gentlemen, one moment. I want people
to know that our subway...
...is the safest, most reliable
public transit. Thank you.
Thanks.
You're Iate, Kent.
- Sorry, won't happen again.
- Ha!
Where is everybody?
Boring.
Tedious.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Abominable!
Regardez, voilá David Warfield.
David Warfield who owns those
sleazy tabloids?
Au contraire. Who owns those
sleazy tabloids and The Daily Planet.
Tedious.
You only read the pictures?
The fact is, Mr. White,
that I only read the Iedger.
A ledger the previous owners
paid so Iittle attention to...
...I bought the paper from them.
The Daily Planet hasn't made
money in three years.
The name of the game
is making money.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my daughter, Lacy Warfield.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- It's nice to meet you.
Mr. White, Lacy will be helping you.
Helping me? Helping me what?
Here are some mock copies
of our new Iayout.
It's super. We can change the suit.
Excuse me, Mr. Warfield.
The world isn't on the brink.
Isn't that headline irresponsible?
Maybe, but it'll sell
a lot of newspapers.
Mr. White, don't do anything rash.
You won't turn this grand
old lady into one of your bimbos...
May I point out that Daddy
holds all of your contracts...
...which you must honor.
- Excusez-moi, your spoiled-ness. ..
- Why is Lois speaking French?
...I'm flying to Paris for
the emergency Ministers' Conference...
Not so fast. All trips are canceled.
You mean my trip to Paris is canceled?
Mr. White, I want to see your books.
Everyone get back to work.
This isn't fair.
I'll speak to Miss Warfield.
- Me too.
- Excuse me, Miss Warfield.
I speak for us all when I say
we'll cooperate.
Thank you.
But a reporter's first allegiance
is to the truth.
This city depends on us
and we can't let them down.
Thank you.
Is he for real?
100 percent, and I Iike him that way.
- Oh, you have a thing for him.
- For Clark?! No!
He's kind of cute.
Look, Miss Warfield...
...Clark is the oldest
living Boy Scout, okay?
He's trustworthy, he's helpful...
...he's loyal, he's obedient, he...
I don't know how to say it.
I just don't think he'd be attracted
to somebody like you.
Don't be silly. All men like me.
I'm very, very rich!
Why aren't there air travel expenses
for you, Mr. Kent?
I get airsick,
mostly when it's bumpy.
Lois, get in here!
Lois, explain this column of figures.
- The president is coming on live.
- Right now?
- It won't be good.
- You always overreact.
- It won't be that terrible.
- Hopefully very terrible.
Circulation will double
with a crisis.
Because the summit has failed...
...we have no choice but
to strive to be second to none...
...in the nuclear arms race.
Therefore, I am announcing
the following measures...
I know you're all upset
by the crisis.
The best thing we can do
is to try to think positiVely.
Now, is there anything we can do?
Doesn't anyone have a suggestion?
AII right, I'll make a suggestion.
Why don't we write to our congressman?
- That'll do a lot of good.
- Somebody has to be an optimist.
Jeremy?
What can we do about the crisis?
He doesn't know what's going on.
I know who I'd write to
who'd do some good.
- Who? Santa Claus?
- No, Superman!
Superman, in our new exhibit...
...donated a strand
of his hair to the museum...
...so we can have fun seeing
how strong he really is.
Here you see a 1000-pound load...
...easily suspended
by his single hair.
The museum will be closing soon,
so we should hurry.
Know what I can do with
a strand of his hair?
You could make a flying toupee.
That hair is
Superman's genetic material.
The building blocks of his body.
With my genius and enough nuclear
power to mutate the genes...
...I can create a being
more powerful than him.
With total allegiance to me.
You better stand back.
Keep your eye out.
- Miss Warfield, you want to see me?
- Hi, Clark. Come in.
I've come up with a brilliant idea.
Oh, really?
Daddy thinks it's brilliant.
You'll write a series
called "Metropolis Affer Hours."
Who, me? I...
It's wonderful.
It's great, isn't it?
- I don't think I'm right for this.
- You're perfect for it.
You're young, you're single,
you're successful.
I'm usually in bed by 10:30.
That's just it, you don't
flaunt it.
You're no slave to fashion.
Although...
- ...have you thought of contacts?
- They make my eyes itch.
Don't worry. I thought
we'd do this together.
- Oh?
- I know all the right places.
I belong to the right clubs.
We'll start tonight at the Metro Club.
- Oh, tonight.
- Yeah, it's a date.
A date! Ah!
- A date?
- Well, it's just business, actually.
I've got a letter here for Superman,
care of me.
- What?
- Superman gets mail here?
It's probably a photo request.
I'Il handle it.
I think it's more than just
a fan Ietter. Read it.
"Dear Superman, my teacher spoke about
the president's speech on the arms race.
We're all very unhappy about it.
And I said we should get Superman
to rid the world of nuclear arms...
...because only he could do it.
Once you've destroyed all the nuclear
missiles, they'll see I'm right.
Superman can make sure we don't
blow ourselves up.
I know you'll come through.
Your friend, Jeremy."
Poor kid. Oh, well,
I better get back to work.
- No, there's an angle here.
- An angle! He's just a kid!
Daddy loves whipping up campaigns.
And the public loves it!
- Lacy!
- We'll make the kid a celebrity.
The world is gonna be
wondering what Superman's reply is.
Welcome to Metropolis, Jeremy.
I'm Mr. Warfield and this is
my daughter, Lacy.
- Hi, Jeremy.
- Come along and meet the press.
- How was your trip?
- The car had a flat.
Sorry to hear that. Turn around.
Let everybody get a picture of you.
- That's it, everyone.
- Jeremy!
What a boy! Now come along...
...and tell the American public
what you told me.
I just said I wish Superman
would've said yes.
- Did you get that?
- No.
Well, say it again. Loudly.
I said I wish Superman
would've said yes!
Miss Lane!
Miss Lane, take a look at this.
Hot off the press.
Oh, my God!
This time he's gone too far.
Look, Clark.
Can't wait to see
the chief's reaction.
I'm through taking it lying down.
I'll be downtown.
Chief look different to you?
He looks like my father used to look
when he asked the bank for a loan.
I'll make sure he's all right.
There's nothing we can do.
It's Superman's decision now.
I'm sure he'll do the right thing.
May the elders watch over you...
...my son.
Their wisdom is all that's left
of a once powerful...
...and enlightened planet.
You must listen to them, Kal-El.
Listen.
I know I'm forbidden to interfere.
And yet the Earth is threatened
by the same fate as Krypton's.
The Earth is too primitiVe.
You can flee to new worlds...
...where war is long forgotten.
If you teach the Earth
to put its fate in any one man...
...even yourself...
...you're teaching them
to be betrayed.
Betrayed, betrayed...
...betrayed, betrayed!
Because the summit has failed...
...we have no choice but to strive...
...to be second to none
in the nuclear arms race.
To that end...
...this administration has pursued
and will continue to pursue...
...the most vigorous policy.
Therefore...
Just a minute.
- Lois?
- There you are. What happened?
- What do you mean?
- Nothing, just:
"Meet me in the lobby at 6:00
for the awards dinner.
Dress nice
and don't be late."
- You were talking about some other Lois?
- I'm sorry, I forgot.
Go get your penguin suit on
and we'll go.
I'd rather not, if you don't mind.
I've got lots of thinking to do.
But you go ahead. Okay?
Clark? Something's wrong, isn't it?
- Is there anything I can do?
- Yes, as a matter of fact.
- What?
- Could we go get some fresh air?
Fresh air?
Fresh air. Fresh air, sure.
Sure, Clark. Sure.
Who needs rubbery chicken anyway?
Let's go.
Let's get some fresh air.
Breathe. Do you feel better?
Clark?
Clark? Clark, things aren't
that bad! Stop!
Oh, Clark!
Clark! Clark!
Superman!
You okay?
Great.
Hey, look at that.
- There you go. Bye-bye!
- Ah!
- How'd you like going solo?
- I Ioved it.
Not as much as being with you.
I needed to be with you too.
You make me laugh.
You're the only one I can talk to.
See, sometimes I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
I'm always here for you,
you know that.
And you'll do the right thing,
no matter what. You always have.
Thank you.
- You know something?
- What?
- You don't even know my name.
- Kal-EI.
You remember, don't you?
I remember everything.
"Never set one of them above the rest.
Love all humanity instead ."
That's not fair.
- Lois! It's time to go. We'll be late.
- Huh?
Why am I out here
freezing my butt off?
Oh, you wanted some fresh air.
That's okay.
I don't want to catch a cold.
I feel kind of weird,
like I'm jet-lagged or something.
- Jeepers!
- Am I going crazy?
- How about you? Are you still down?
- Nope. Things are clear.
Good. Too much thinking
wears down your batteries.
- Clark, you gotta go with your gut.
- Hm.
Come on.
Here you go, Jeremy.
Mr. Warfield wants shots with local
color, but I can't think of anything.
- Hi, Jeremy.
- Superman!
Jimmy.
What a scoop!
- How'd you like to walk with me?
- Sure!
Jimmy, come on.
You can't! You'll get towed.
- Do you know how much tickets cost?
- It's only money.
Will you wait for me
in the gallery?
Sure, okay.
- Good luck, Superman.
- Thanks.
I saved you a seat.
Yeah!
AII right, Superman!
Madam Secretary, I'd like to
address the delegates.
Well, in that case,
you will need a sponsor.
I believe that will do. Please.
Thank you.
- What's he gonna say?
- Something wonderful.
Madam Secretary...
...honorable delegates,
ladies and gentlemen.
For many years now
I've lived among you as...
...a visitor.
I've seen the beauty of your cultures.
I've felt joy in your magnificent
accomplishments.
I've seen the folly of your wars.
As of today I'm not a visitor
anymore...
...because the Earth is my home too.
We can't live in fear.
And I can't stand...
...idly by and watch us
stumble into the madness...
...of possible nuclear destruction.
I've come to a decision.
I'll do what our governments couldn't.
Effective immediately, I'll
rid our planet of all nuclear weapons.
AII right, Superman!
Way to go, Superman!
Missile test Alpha, all systems go.
Three, two, one.
Oh!
Oh. Nice to see you guys!
Why don't you just relax.
I'll get on with the introductions:
Dixie and Trixie.
From the land of the free, the home of
the cost overrun, Harry Howler:
Nuclear strategist from
America's top think tank.
A great little warmonger
in his own right.
A hearty bienvenue
to Jean Pierre Dubois:
Nuclear warhead dealer to the world.
His motto is:
"If you didn't buy it from Jean Pierre,
it wasn't on the black market."
General Romoff.
People think of you
as the "Mad Russian."
I Iike to think of you
as just madly eccentric.
Please be seated.
Look guys. I know you're all choked
up, kind of overcome with joy...
...that Superman has ended
the arms race.
But if we work together,
we can make the world safe...
- ...for war profits.
- Get to the point.
I, Lex Luthor, the greatest
criminal mind of the modern era...
...know how to destroy Superman.
Behold, my unscrupulous friends...
Shut those blinds.
- The sun is hurting my eyes!
- Exactly.
You know what the sun is? Nothing
more than a huge nuclear bomb...
...with so much radiation, it'd
incinerate the average man like that!
Yes, but Superman is no average man.
Aha, right!
What is your plan?
Boys, old Lex here
has kind of a secret recipe...
...a genetic stew in this dish,
if you will.
If you'll help me put this
on one of your missiles...
...I promise, Superman will have
the biggest surprise of his life.
I'll introduce him to his first
nightmare, a "Nuclear Man ."
He'll pierce his skin, make
him mortal. He'll become sick.
We'll dance on his grave.
Why should we deal with
a scoundrel Iike you?
Remember my motto: "The more fear
you make, the more loot you take."
And the more missiles you sell.
Yes, but what's in it for you?
A tiny commission.
Something appropriate.
A number...
...with a lot of zeros behind it.
Lenny.
The new genetic material.
And now, Leonard...
...your Uncle Lex...
...with protoplasm grown
from Superman's hair cells...
...will duplicate creation itself.
Now the fabric.
U ncle Lex, this ain't gonna cover him.
The computer inside will...
...leave enough material to maintain
the high moral standards...
...that I've always subscribed to.
- Know what this means, Uncle Lex?
- What?
We're gonna be parents.
- What's your name?
- York, sir.
At ease.
Launch control. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
There's a weather problem.
We gotta hold.
Hold?
- What's your name, son?
- Goram.
"Goram, sir."
- Goram, sir.
- You know your code book?
Of course, sir.
27-0-6, inclement override.
Fire on my command. Fire.
Yes, sir. Stand by to Iaunch.
Ten, nine...
Missed us.
Reach out.
Come on.
Down.
Reach out.
And stretch.
Down.
- Up.
- Ugh!
- Are you okay?
- I think I better sit this out.
Are you sure? This would be great
for your series on Metropolis.
Let's try it again. Come on.
Two, three, four.
- One, two, three.
- Ugh.
- I don't think so.
- What, are you okay?
28, 29...
- ...33.
- Heh, heh, heh.
- Done. Great.
- Okay, you try it now.
- Let's set it a little higher for you.
- Okay.
Just push down.
- Are you okay? Just step down.
- Need some help?
He doesn't know his own strength.
Clark, this is Paul.
- He's a trainer.
- Nice to meet you.
Hey, I got just the thing for you.
Over here, Clarky.
Clarky?
It's real nice of him to help me out.
- He's really good.
- Here, try this one.
Clark! Are you okay? Sorry.
No pain, no gain.
Jeez, what a jerk.
Never realized it before.
I guess a lot of people I know
are jerks.
You must think I am too.
That's why you avoid me.
I don't think that at all.
Just been really busy.
But wait!
Lois is doing that interview
with Superman about his peace mission.
I was thinking the four of us can get
together at my hotel, have high tea.
It's very chic.
- Can you hand me those weights?
- Excuse me.
Wait, Lacy.
Come early. The view is romantic
from my balcony. See you.
- Oh, sure. Here.
- Not those! The other one!
No pain, no gain?
What was that?
Uncle Lex.
You're spooking me out.
There.
Madam, thank you very much.
I'm incredible.
Uncle Lex, he's like...
He's beautiful. He's perfect.
Welcome home, Nuclear Man.
Your father's happy to see you.
The power of the sun gives him
internally generated heat.
I'm a...
You are...
I'm... What? I'm a genius?
I'm incredible. I'm...
You are nothing. I am the father now.
- You have my voice.
- No, you have my voice.
Just remember, I made you.
Yeah, you're just an experiment,
freako.
What is that?
- Oh, no.
- I'm an experiment. I'm a freako.
I was just kidding about freako!
If anyone's a freako here,
it's gotta be me!
Oh, wow. Oh!
Oh, wow, I'm break dancing, hey!
This rocks. Hey!
- I made you. I can destroy you.
- Destroy.
Destroy Superman now.
You sweet thing.
But not quite yet, no.
Come here. We'll discuss
when the proper time is.
Uncle Lex.
Oh, no!
He's, like... He's, like, cold.
Of course he is.
That's his vulnerability.
The only way he'll be stopped.
What?
Lenny, my loud-mouthed nephew,
he gets his energy from the sun.
Without it, he's like you at night:
Useless.
Nobody's perfect.
I never had a double date before.
It's fun. How do I Iook?
Illegal. Like the last six dresses
you tried on.
Listen, Lacy? I don't want to
burst your bubble...
- ...but Clark won't notice your dress.
- Yes, he will.
- There's Clark.
- Fix that. There you go. You look great.
- Maybe it's just Superman.
- No.
No, Superman makes a different
kind of entrance.
- Hi, Lacy.
- Hi, Clark.
Can you break a 20?
Driver had no change.
Yeah, sure. Let me get my purse.
- Hi, Lois.
- Hi, Clark.
- Clark.
- What?
You won't believe
these questions...
...Mr. Warfield gave me
to ask Superman.
"Are you part of a plot
to weaken our national defense?"
- Oh, my goodness.
- I think his gray matter is...
- How will I ask him this?
- Well, politely I guess.
Let's see, I have 18 dollars and...
Clark, she really likes you,
so notice the dress.
...my American Express card.
- Dress.
- Oh, hey, neat dress.
Thanks. Be right back.
What's that?
Now, there's a different
kind of entrance.
- Hi, Lois.
- Hello, Superman.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Oh. Superman, this is Lacy Warfield.
She's the boss's daughter.
How do you do?
That's an attractive outfit.
- We should start our interview.
- Excuse me.
Two's company.
Oh, right, yeah.
Yeah, I'll go get Clark.
Clark is probably helping the cab driver
change a flat tire, or something.
That guy.
- Something smells wonderful.
- Thank you.
I'm cooking us some scallops
and some duck...
...in this wonderful mushroom sauce
with champagne.
In case we got hungry afterwards.
I mean, Iater.
You shouldn't have gone
through all that trouble.
Should we get on with the interview?
Yes, let's get on
with the interview.
Um...
Have you had any trouble
confiscating the missiles?
There always was the possibility
that warped individuals...
...would take advantage of
the world's goodwill, but...
Is there something wrong?
Oh! My dinner! My dinner!
I'Il be right back.
Be right back.
Hi.
- I missed you, Clark.
- Oh. Well...
Lois and Superman are boring.
Let's do something wild.
They're expecting us.
It's not polite.
Yeah, you're right.
How can one man be so square
and so delicious?
Let's go chitchat. If I
have to face Superman, so do you.
Lacy?
Oh, Clark.
Uh... Uh... Stop.
I don't believe it! I never had duck
turn out so perfectly. It's amazing!
- I'm out here, Lois.
- Oh.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yes, it is beautiful.
The whole world is beautiful.
I feel moments like this
should be shared with someone you...
Someone you care a lot about.
- Isn't that the doorbell?
- Yes. Heh, heh.
Lacy.
- Where's Clark?
- He was getting in the elevator...
- Never mind, it's a long story.
- It always is with Clark.
Great, it's him.
- Clark?
- Hi.
Those bellboys ought to
look where they're going.
Superman?
- I'm so glad you're back.
- Is dinner ready? Can we eat?
- Yeah, let's go sit down.
- Oh, great.
- Sorry!
- My goodness! That's okay.
Just leave it there.
It's on your pants.
Let me just get a rag.
Be right back.
Where's Clark?
Hello, Dolly Hello, Dolly
It's so nice to have me back
Where I belong
Don't be concerned, Blue Boy.
Only you can hear me.
It's my own private frequency.
You might call it "Lex TV."
Look to your left,
tall, dark and handsome.
I'll blow 20 stories off that building,
give or take a floor or two.
Peace.
Men.
- I hope Clark's okay. I'll look.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, but an emergency's come up.
My apologies to Miss Warfield.
Oh, but...
Superman! Take me with you!
I can cover the story!
- You seen Clark?
- Huh?
Guess who?
It's your old friend Lex.
I suspect if you'd actually planted
a bomb, you'd be miles away by now.
This is my nephew Lenny.
He worships me.
The dude of steel.
Boy, are you gonna get it.
Silly me, thinking that
I could fool a super guy.
You're right. No bomb.
It's just that you're so involved
in this world peace bit...
...you don't have time
for social calls.
I confess, I tricked you.
You look great.
Never mind the small talk.
What are you up to?
You know you're a workaholic?
You're playing a good guy
24 hours a day.
Why don't you stop and
smell the roses, huh?
Get yourself a hobby? A pet?
A kitten, a puppy?
I know you hate children and animals.
What are you doing back in Metropolis?
I want to be first to introduce
you to the new kid on the block.
Look closely at the cell structure.
You see anything familiar?
You've already broke
all the laws of man.
Now you've broken the laws
of nature too.
I assume you hid a device of some kind
in a missile I hurled into the sun.
Mr. Muscle, I'm gonna really miss
these Iittle chats we had together.
Only you can keep up with me.
- Lenny!
- What?
I wanna propose a toast.
To a nice guy, who's about
to finish last.
Destroy Superman.
Later. Heh, heh, heh.
He's a little bit anxious.
Can you blame him?
Not one of your great thinkers.
But I, in all modesty, am.
The touching thing about this plan
is, you helped me devise it.
Prison has twisted
your mind into a delusional state.
No, no, no. Listen.
When I escaped prison,
I had one thing on my mind:
The end of Superman.
There I was, the first time in my life...
...that I didn't have a long-range,
truly devious, criminal scheme.
And then I came up with it.
With this guy...
...and you gone, I'll make
a fortune rearming the world.
You'd risk nuclear war for
your own financial gain.
Nobody wants war. I just want
to keep the threat alive.
N ifty, huh?
Good night, sweet prince.
Parting is...
...inevitable.
Destroy Superman.
First, I have fun.
Help me!
Superman!
I said I'd get you to run one of our
papers yourself, and I meant it.
Congratulations, Miss Publisher.
Thank you, Daddy, that's very nice.
Step into your office.
- Where'd this come from?
- Somebody brought it in.
We bought it, cheap.
Okay, this time you've both
gone too far.
You can print your stupid rag
without Lois Lane.
And you certainly have
no right to this.
- Lois, I'm sorry!
- Let her go, darling.
I mean, she's useless.
And while you're at it,
fire Clark Kent.
He hasn't been around
or telephoned.
I know, I'm worried about him.
Oh, kitten...
...didn't we have a talk about
personal involvement with the help?
- Now that you're the publisher...
- Daddy.
- Yes, darling.
- Stuff it!
Lois. Lois, I'm sorry.
I promise, I had
nothing to do with that.
Have you heard from Clark?
No.
Just a minute.
Oh, Lois.
- What are you doing here?
- I knew it.
I just got a really bad flu.
What do you mean you knew it?
You haven't been to work
or called the office.
You haven't even called me back.
How could you not call me back?
Whatever it is,
you've got your reasons.
But I knew you were here, you know?
Somehow...
...something pulled me here.
I always know when Superman's
in trouble.
Heh, heh, heh. Superman?
Something's happened to him?
Everybody's saying that
he's dead but...
...it can't be true. I just know it.
I feel it in my heart.
I think he just needs help.
Wherever he is,
I'm sure he'll manage.
Well, if he can't manage...
...and if he really is in trouble...
...then there's a few things
I'd like to tell him.
I'd tell him...
...that I will always cherish
the time we spent together.
And that I never expected
anything in return.
And no matter...
...how few minutes I saw him for,
it always made me happy.
And I would tell him
that I love him...
...and that I'll always love him.
And that...
...whatever...
...happens to the world...
...I know that...
...he's doing his best to make sure
it's good for all of us.
Wherever he is, Lois...
...I know that he would
want to thank you.
Listen, I'm pretty tired, you know?
So I think I'll just rest here
for a while. Okay?
I'Il be fine.
It's okay. Please?
- I hope you feel better, Clark.
- Thanks.
If you do see him, or hear from him...
...he might need this.
Oh, Lex. We're very pleased
at all the nuclear arms...
...you helped us sell...
...and we've decided
to increase your commission.
Guys, really, that's great.
It is the least we could do.
I had another idea.
Gentlemen...
...I've decided to assume control
of the company.
My first official act
is to say, "You're fired!"
You're mad.
Oh, really?
If you want a reference for work...
...forget it!
That's a good bit.
You know with my brains, and your...
Frankly, your...
...brawn, the possibilities
are absolutely staggering.
I could be president,
emperor, king.
- See how scared those guys were?
- And what do you fear?
What? Now? With Superman dead,
and you're on my team?
It's Iike I'm the coach, and you're the
best power forward ever. What's to fear?
All that remains of
Krypton's energy is yours.
After it is gone...
...you will belong solely
to your new home.
If our dying planet can
save your life, my son...
...we have not died in vain.
- Where is the woman?
- You'll never find her.
If you will not tell me,
I will hurt people.
Stop! Don't do it, the people!
Whoa!
- What's happening?
- Easy, easy, easy.
AII right, stop! Stop! That's enough!
That's enough!
You win.
I'll take you to her.
- Where is she?
- Far away from here and safe.
She's not in there!
We must tone down the headlines.
Tone down our headlines?
That's all the common man reads!
- We can do with less sensationalism.
- Less sensational papers go broke.
I taught you that the
business of newspapers is business.
No, Daddy...
...our business is journalism.
We can't be irresponsible or we'll
lead everyone into disaster.
Don't be overdramatic,
young lady.
What kind of disaster could
we bring about?
Lacy!
What's going on? Hey!
Are you sure you know what
you're doing?
- Well...
- Uh... Ahem.
Here comes Mr. Warfield.
You'd better have
a good explanation, White...
...or else you'll be talking
to your lawyers from jail.
You know, I'm not a tycoon.
I'm just an old reporter.
But I've read enough in my own
newspaper over the years...
...about hostile takeovers
of big companies.
You, Mr. Warfield,
must'Ve been asleep at the wheel.
Because I convinced the city's bankers
that our Daily Planet...
...should be treated like a natural
resource, protected from predators.
They lent me the money.
I bought up all the outstanding shares.
And you, Mr. Warfield,
are now a minority shareholder.
- Everyone, back to work.
- Way to tell him, chief!
Yay!
I'm sorry.
You win some and you lose some.
Now, this is what I call a newspaper.
Compliments of The Daily Planet.
- Have a nice day. We did it!
- We're back! Ha, ha, ha.
- Hi, am I late?
- No. He's not here yet.
It must've been some effort for you
to drag yourself out of bed.
I'm feeling a lot better.
Had a visit from a pretty good nurse.
Must have been good.
Miss Lane said you were really ill.
Sometimes all you need is loving
attention from the right person.
Glad you're back.
And remember, I am covering
Superman's press conference.
- You tape reactions from the crowd.
- Reactions, okay.
Oh, dear. Guess I need
a tape recorder, huh?
- Be right back.
- Same Mr. Kent. He'll never change.
I hope not.
Ooh.
- How you doing, Superman?
- Lois. Good to see you again.
Good to see you too.
Morning, gentlemen.
Excuse me.
Thank you. We survived the threat
of war and found a fragile peace.
I thought I could give you
freedom from war...
...but I was wrong.
It's not mine to give.
We're still a young planet.
There are galaxies out there...
...other civilizations for us
to meet, to learn from.
What a brilliant future.
There will be peace when the people of
the world want it so badly...
...that their governments will have
no choice but to give it to them.
I wish you could see the Earth
the way I do.
When you really look at it,
it's just one world.
Do you think he'll find us?
Never. We'll lay low for a while,
a couple of years.
I'll come up with a new plan.
Good thing I bought my drums.
Whoa!
U ncle Lex,
you won't believe this...
- ...but it's Superman.
- Superman.
Heh, heh. Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
- Hey, this rocks.
- Morning, Father.
He's been under a bad influence.
Can you help him?
- Every boy can be helped.
- You're right.
- Good luck, son.
- Come with me.
You wouldn't happen
to have a drum set, would you?
Hey, Mozart's back!
- Duane, Mozart's back!
- I see him, Bubba!
- Shut up!
- Ha, ha, ha.
- Take him away.
- Thank you. Come on, Luthor.
- Just one thing, how did you beat him?
- High school physics.
I had time to figure out...
...that if it was born from the sun,
that was its energy.
- Will the world be vaporized?
- No, Luthor.
It's as it always was, on the brink,
with good fighting evil. See you in 20.