- Hello to you.
I hope you're fine.
Who knows
the electron wave functions
for Kryptonian covalent bonding?
- Sorry.
- Leah.
The cube root
of the wavelength...
- Greetings.
- Hello, Kara.
- Hello to you.
'Oh, it is beautiful!'
What's that gonna be, Zaltar?
I think, a tree.
A tree. What is a tree?
A lovely thing
which grows on Earth.
Earth?
You mean, where my cousin went?
Hm, and to where,
one day soon perhaps
I might venture as well.
I don't believe you. How?
- In that. Through there.
- The binary chute?
But you could never survive
the pressure. It'd destroy--
In that I can.
Zip-zap and I'm gone.
But you'd never leave us, Zaltar.
- You'd never leave Argo City.
- Indeed, I might, Kara.
Too much of a good thing here.
Perhaps, I'll try Saturn instead.
Yes, I think I might.
Saturn is...
Is that further away than Earth?
Silly question.
Did you not study
six-dimensional geometry
at school?
Do they not teach you
anything anymore?
Well, of course they do, I...
I know the equations. Well...
I just can't see 'em
in my head.
Most great artists find
mathematics troublesome, Kara.
- Only use your imagination.
- Mm-hmm.
Saturn and Earth
are in outer space
but we, we are in inner space.
Our city
has two great power sources.
This is one of them. Look.
An Omegahedron.
The Guardians let you have it?
Not exactly.
- I borrowed it.
- You stole it.
- Oh, Zaltar, they're gonna--
- No.
Borrowed it for the afternoon.
- For inspiration.
- Inspiration.
But I think that I shall
never see the branches
of a living tree.
Why? An Omegahedron
can create life, can't it?
It can't, child, it can't.
Just the illusion of life.
That's a fancy shadow
of the real thing
which is the most we can hope
for on this lonely old rock.
'Kara?'
Kara, I've been looking for you
for ages.
Well, I'm sorry, mother.
- Zaltar.
- Alura, join us.
We're just inventing miracles.
Put your fingers here, Kara,
and press hard.
Good. Now try it.
Let your imagination explode
and give it a try. Go on.
Zaltar, m-my husband tells me
you talk of leaving Argo City.
For where?
Parts unknown.
It is, alas, a fact.
'You and Zor-El
have a life here.'
'You have each other
and you have Kara.'
'But, Zaltar, you founded'
'this city. It's yours.'
As far as the eye can see,
right to the veil, smack.
And then what? What is beyond?
'Alura, I cannot contain myself
to Argo City only.'
'My head is boiling with ideas.'
'My imagination is too vast,
it's uncontrollable.'
If you want my opinion, Zaltar
you're starting
to repeat yourself here
with all this airy,
glittery stuff.
Exactly.
That's why I'm going to Venus.
Venus? When?
Tomorrow or the next day,
at the latest.
'Zaltar,
have you thought about this?'
'It doesn't make sense to me.'
'I have thought intensely.
My mind is made up.'
Kara, the power source!
Oh, Zaltar!
Save me! Please! Help!
- No!
- Kara!
Zaltar! Help!
No!
Are you okay, Kara?
- You took the Omegahedron.
- That's not correct.
I lost the Omegahedron.
- Oh, no, father, I did. I was--
- Shh, Kara.
No matter who.
Without it,
this city can't survive
more than a few days.
Our lights will grow dim
and the very air we breathe
so thin.
I know. So I shall find it.
I shall go
right to the end of inner space
and I shall return it.
'Impossible. How?'
No one can leave Argo City
and you know it.
This is our universe and
you've destroyed it with a game.
- A childish game.
- I think it can be done.
Through there, the binary chute,
in the traveler...
Kara!
Kara, no!
- You lunatic!
- She'll be killed.
Oh, no, she won't.
She will be safe,
through the binary
through the warp,
into another register.
- Another what?
- Gravitational radiation.
A pathway
from inner space to outer space.
Then she'll never
be the same, ever.
At least she'll be alive.
And my fate is sealed.
I've lost the Omegahedron.
I must be sent
to the Phantom Zone.
Your suffering will be short.
Mine...forever.
Some more champagne,
my dear Selena?
What are you thinking about?
It's such a pretty world.
I can't wait
until it's all mine.
The only way
you can rule the world
is to become invisible,
my pumpkin.
Invisible?
You'd almost know
how to make me invisible.
Oh, I do know.
'Take five black beans'
and the head of a dead man.
Place one bean in his mouth,
two beans in his eyes, then--
- Nigel, enough.
- But it works.
Then you can get anywhere,
do anything.
Nigel,
how long have we been together?
Ooh. Months, darling.
Then why does it seem
like years?
Because you're so impatient.
You want everything yesterday.
It takes a lifetime to discover
the secrets of black magic
from the ancient grimoires.
Holy cow!
I wonder...
Immortality be upon this one.
She is a sharer
of the sun's everlasting life.
There will now be
no danger of death.
This world
will keep her forever.
What is it?
What's going on?
Hey, what's going on?
I've just outgrown you, Nigel.
These things happen.
You can't treat me like this,
Selena.
Without me, you'd still
be reading tea leaves
at Lake Tahoe.
'Amsterdam and more.
That's TWA.'
'Never has flying been easier.'
You can't run out on me, Selena.
I've got the keys, sweetheart.
...that Superman
has indeed embarked
on a special peace-seeking
mission to a galaxy
scientists estimate may be
several hundred trillion
light-years from our own...
Oh.
Whoo-hoo!
Ah...
Now here's the weather
from the general Chicago area.
Increasing cloudiness
with a possibility of showers.
Breezy, but warm
with a high of 62.
Bianca!
I'm home.
What?
Show your face.
I have a surprise for you.
They've turned off
the hot water again.
I'm really gonna have to kill
somebody down at the DWP.
I figure the only way that we're
gonna pay our bills next month
in this dump is to just go ahead
and do what I said
which is to start our own coven.
No longer necessary.
I was reading in this book,
you know
"The Witch's Guide
To Heaven And Hell"
and if you start your own coven,
all you have to do
is charge five bucks a head
minimal admission. That's great.
- Chicken feed.
- Ah!
That's better than goose egg.
What's
in the Coffer of Shadow there?
- Where's little Nigel?
- Nigel, my dear Bianca...
- Is history.
- Oh, yeah? How so?
The water department is history,
the car payments are history.
The mortgage payments
are history.
- How are the property taxes?
- History.
The world is at last my oyster.
Now, this I like.
- Hello.
- "Hello," she says.
- Well, hello to you, honeybun.
- Hello.
I was wondering
if you could tell me where I am.
What do they call this place,
Eddie? Lovers' Lane, isn't it?
You got it in one, Billy boy.
Lovers' Lane.
Oh, no, you see,
what I meant was, is...
Well, those lights over there,
what are they called?
Check out the view
from back here, Eduardo.
Ah...
- Stop that!
- Hey.
You're, uh,
Superman's best friend, huh?
No. His cousin.
I've come here
to search for the Omegahedron.
It's a power source
vital to Argo City.
'You see, that's where I live.'
No kidding.
Eddie and me here
we're on a secret mission also.
We're out
looking for a good time.
And you just won
the brass ring, baby.
Ooh, she works out, huh?
Why are you doing this?
It's just the way we are.
Oh, no. Billy...
You shouldn't have
done that, baby.
Come on.
Oh, I see.
You really wanna play games,
eh, sweetheart?
Come on. Come...
Huh?
Eddie...
I think maybe we should
kinda keep this to ourselves.
'What do you think?'
Freddie, you little devil,
how are you?
Fresh ammunition, everybody.
Try telling your wife.
I need another one. Come on...
Where is it?
Where's the little mystery ball?
Just let me have a peek.
Maybe I can shed some light.
- I hate light.
- I mean, is it electrical?
Is it hot to the touch?
- Where is it?
- Safe and sound.
Go mix. Leave me to my thoughts.
"Go mix?" With these people?
You must be mad.
Who are they?
Wrinkly little wretches.
These are my foot soldiers,
Nigel.
My army of the night.
I'm considering nothing less
than world domination.
After you left me in the lurch,
I saw something
that should worry you greatly
if you're serious
about taking over this planet.
My secret was blue and red
and it knew how to fly.
I have a secret, too, Nigel.
I have the power.
Now, get that through your head.
Oh, I bet
they're in for it now, eh?
Count on it.
I have in my time
seen a great number of things
even more impressive
than a human cigarette lighter,
dear lady.
To wit.
What is that?
Overreaching ambition.
Take heed.
Touched a little nerve,
didn't I?
- Hello.
The red toad that lurks
in the briars and brambles
is full of sorceries.
There's a little bone
on the left side.
- A little bone?
- A little bone.
'Which if bound to a man'
stirs up the greatest lust.
- I wanna be rich and famous.
- Then stick with me.
I was put on this Earth
to thrill millions.
Mm, this is scrumptious.
'Why don't we go somewhere else
and dance cheek to cheek?'
Stop it, Selena!
That's not fair!
'Pick on me.'
Oh.
- Thanks.
- Hey, no sweat.
- What happened?
- Oh, nothing much.
Get out of my house, Nigel
and don't come slithering back.
I'm warning you, Selena
don't be so shortsighted.
Good morning.
Have you got it, Lucy?
It must be near that oak tree.
- Hurry up!
- Found it, guys.
What are you doing in there?
You're supposed to find the ball.
Come on, don't take all day.
You're holding up the game.
- Hey, it's your turn to bat.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Okay, okay. Let's play ball.
- Alright, batter!
I couldn't make it.
I have to finish my English...
Hey, toss the ball back, will ya?
Look at that. Whoo-whee!
Come on, make it two in a row!
Play ball.
- Where have you been?
- With the principal.
Danvers is doing his usual number.
Geez, another barfy new student.
They're really scraping the
bottom of the barrel these days.
Hang in there, Danvers.
Don't let 'em get to you.
Thirty days.
Semester just started.
- And you'll be...
- Hello. I--
Didn't knock.
Don't we teach you manners
around here?
'Don't we try to impress
on all our young ladies'
that animals in the jungle
never knock
but Midvale girls always do?
Where are you going?
Come back here!
Come in.
I forgot.
I'm just not used to the--
Wait a minute.
Wait just one second.
I have never before in my life
laid eyes on you.
- Have I, young lady?
- No, sir. I'm new here.
New here, well,
obviously, you're new here
if I've never laid eyes on you
before.
The question remains,
just who on Earth are you?
Um...
On Earth, I'm Lee. Linda Lee.
Where's your letter
of recommendation?
Letter?
I must talk to you, principal.
- I am busy now.
- So are they.
Them, all the little monsters
you admit to the place.
'They have nailed
my desk drawers shut.'
Never in all my years
as a school teacher...
- Come, Danvers.
- I will not be provoked.
I will not let him get to me
this semester.
I'll be strong. Be strong.
Be like a rock.
Now, what did you say
your name was?
O-oh, yes, yes, yes.
Linda Lee, huh?
Yes, my cousin
probably wrote you.
Um, maybe you got his letter
under K for Kent
in your files.
Kent? Kent?
It doesn't ring any bells.
Doesn't even ring a...
Well, here it is, big as life.
'"My dear Mr. Danvers,
I'm writing on behalf'
of a very special young lady..."
An orphan?
Well, don't expect
to be treated any differently
on that account, Ms. Lee.
Oh, no, sir, I won't.
One way or another,
we're all alone
on this miserable little planet.
Yes, sir, I know.
Since your school records
were obviously lost in the mail
you'll have to start
at the bottom.
It's only fair
to the other girls.
You'll have English, Latin, math
biology, computing...
- All at once?
- And chemistry.
Idle hands
are the devil's playground.
This way.
- Man on the floor!
Open up, Lane.
Hm, I know you're in there.
I'm not decent,
Mr. Danvers, sir.
And you never will be either,
you little liar.
Well, come on in. Come on in.
I haven't got all year.
Uh, no. I'm supposed to have
a single this term.
We don't always get
what we want, Ms. Lane.
Disappointments
thicken our skins.
Who wants thick skin?
I'm Linda Lee.
- Hi.
- Oh. Hi.
- I'm Lucy Lane.
- Lucy Lee, this is Linda Lane.
- No, it isn't.
- 'What?'
- She's Linda Lee and I'm--
- Lucy Lane.
You two know each other?
Oh, no. We just met.
- When?
- Just now.
But we've known each other
for years. Haven't we, Linda?
Oh, well, gee, I don't think--
Oh, of course.
"The Daily Planet."
Of course,
Linda's cousin works there.
A-and your sister,
what's her name
the one that's always calling me
and bothering me?
- Lois.
- Ah, yes. That's the one.
Anyway, uh, show our new Ms. Lee
around, Ms. Lane.
Oh, by the way,
she's an orphan.
But don't let her play
on your sympathies, hm?
So who's your cousin?
Clark Kent.
You're kidding me.
Clark Kent's your cousin?
You're putting me on.
- Do you know him?
- Do I know him?
Does my sister know him?
- Now, that's the big question.
- Oh, I see.
I guess if they work
at the same newspaper
they must know each other.
- Well...
- Is this where I'll sleep?
Well, this is your bed,
but we don't sleep around here.
Non-stop excitement
in this dorm.
All the real dementals
are sent here.
So when's the rest of your stuff
arriving?
I don't have any other stuff.
What,
it's all in that little bag?
Oh, well, you see,
I have the means to buy more.
It's just... Well, I just
haven't had the chance since...
Do you know him?
Superman? Sure.
'My sister's got something going
with the big guy.'
Hey, listen,
you can borrow any of my clothes
anytime you want.
Just dig in and help yourself.
Thank you. You're very kind.
He's a real character.
A real hunk.
'I'll introduce you to him
someday'
'if we wind up getting along.'
Now, then, focus your tiny minds
on the kind of problems that
used to take w-weeks of thought
before the computer.
Even now it can take a long time
without certain algorithms
which,
if you behave for two seconds
I might reveal to you.
Love. Hate. Love. Hate.
Love. The cards have decided.
People will do anything
for love.
They'll jump off cliffs
They'll drown themselves
like lemmings.
So...
...I'll make everybody love me.
Oh, no chance.
You're an awful person, honey,
remember? Forget it.
Use your imagination, pinhead.
That's what magic is all about.
Why are we not moving?
Because I'm in love.
Come here, you beautiful thing.
He's cute.
Hey, what's going on?
Here's an exercise in big
numbers I want you to try...
It's trying
to tell me something.
Well, what?
That we're near danger?
I don't know. How do I know?
- I know.
- Well, tell me.
My prince has come.
'Oh, no.'
I saw him first, Selena.
That's not fair.
I copied his number first.
Well done.
Now, let's get out of here.
'You'll be given the average
size of a Chinese family.'
'Average age of death,
average age of marriage'
'average age of pregnancy.'
'Use this equation to compute
the population of China'
in the year 2040.
Linda, are you with us?
Um...
- Yes, sir, I am.
- Oh, are you?
Where, might I ask?
W-well, here, sir.
On Earth, sir.
How fortunate
for the rest of us.
May I presume that whilst
you were staring at the wall
and not at your terminal, like
your other little friends here
you were in fact hard at work
solving this little equation?
Oh, yes, sir, I was.
I mean, I was--
Excellent. The answer, please.
Pay attention, class.
Ms. Lee
is about to enlighten us.
Five-billion two-hundred-
and-seventy-one million
nine thousand and ten.
Come on. Let's get out of here
before he makes you stay.
'Come on. Hurry.'
'Ms. Lee?'
- Oh, shit.
- Yes, sir?
Have you been going through
my papers?
Of course not, sir.
Then how do you know
the correct answer?
- 'How?'
- I guess I just--
It's all this crazy weather
we've been having, sir.
'All the storms, shock waves,
electromagnetism.'
It makes people smarter
than they are for a second.
We gotta go, sir.
Oh, boy. Thanks.
You know, I gotta learn--
How'd you know the answer?
I don't know.
Six-dimensional geometry.
- I never could do it before.
- Yeah.
Well,
you want some friendly advice?
Don't go showing it off,
'cause nobody's gonna like you.
I'll see you later.
Ah.
- Nice going.
- Well, she can...
Do you know
she tripped you on purpose?
Absolutely.
She's retarded.
'Come on,
we don't have much time left.'
'Come on, let's go.'
You take it, My.
Hey, Myra, see if you can
put Lane out for good.
'Come on, team!'
'Are you guys alright?'
- Oh, my God. What happened?
- Are you alright?
Hey, Myra, how did she do that?
It just hit her shoulder.
Hey, you guys,
did you see that cute guy
in the softball field?
'Oh, yes.'
With the black hair
and the big muscles.
- He was something else.
- 'Did you talk to him?'
'No, but I'm gonna.'
'He's working on the trees.
He could be around for a while.'
- Are they in?
- Yes.
'Myra, are you sure you wanna go
through with this?'
'Oh, boy,
I'm really gonna enjoy this.'
'I can't wait
to hear them scream.'
But, Myra,
why don't you shut off the hot
and give them an ice bath?
'Are you kidding?
That's nowheresville.'
If you shut off the cold,
you might scald them.
So they lose a little skin.
Serves 'em right.
'I want to see them suffer.'
Ah!
- I'm wet!
- Oh!
Myra, don't leave me.
Don't leave me.
- I hate you!
- You never looked better!
We'll get you all!
What do you think?
It looks the same to me.
It's kind of dull.
All you need is a couple of
streaks and your ears pierced.
I can do it for you
free of charge.
- My ears, what?
- Pierced.
Like, you know, I take a needle,
and then I heat it up
and then I dab it
with some alcohol and zap
all the guys go crazy.
Because I have holes
in my ears?
What, are you putting me on?
Sometimes I can't
figure you out, Linda.
So where are you going
this weekend?
- 'Nowhere.'
- Nowhere?
Well,
you can't stay around here.
This place is depressing.
'I mean, like the tombs.'
- Why?
- 'Why?'
What, were you born yesterday?
This is a three-day weekend.
A three-day weekend.
So, listen,
why don't you come home with me?
'I only live
about five miles from here'
and I got this guy
coming up from Metropolis.
I think he knows
your cousin Clark.
'His name's Jimmy Olsen.'
'I think he's real stuck on me.'
Anyways, I could ask him
to bring a friend along.
- 'What are you doing?'
- Oh, nothing. Heh.
'Nothing.'
No, I think I'm gonna
stay here and study.
Get things organized.
Don't forget
to call me Saturday.
Just a sec.
Hey, Linda, I'll see you later
at Popeye's then, okay?
Alright, I'll try. I promise.
You better.
It's gonna be fun.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Have a good time.
'Come along now, Lucy.'
'Get the dog in the car.'
"Take a spider off his web...
"...and shut him up inside
"two shells of a nut.
"Now, boil the nut in oil
"into which has been added,
some of the web.
"With a silver spoon
"put two drops of the oil
into some water."
Right.
"He who drinks the water
"shall be in love
with the first person he sees.
"So long as the spider
is shut up in the nutshell
"or one day goes by
whichever comes first."
Big deal. One day.
Why don't you just use,
you know...
I'm saving it for bigger things.
Hiya, folks.
You're listening to big Sam
the country-and-western voice
of the Chicago area.
Now to start off the hour,
something mellow and sweet...
Bianca, get the door!
Bianca!
You rang? Hey, you!
I said, you rang?
Oh, yeah. How you doin'?
Uh... I'm lookin' for some person
called Mrs. Selena.
- Madame Selena.
- Ah.
And you found her, lucky boy.
Entrer.
You must be very popular
in the neighborhood.
I always see your truck
parked around.
Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, I get
a lot of repeat business.
Uh, people like my work.
Yes, I'm sure they do.
- Wet your whistle?
- Huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah. As a matter
of fact, uh, don't mind if I do.
So, uh,
where's the lawn...at?
- It dropped dead.
- Where at exactly? Out back?
You know, I thought
we might get to know each other
a little more before we, uh,
dig in
and talk real turkey.
Well, um, see, I'm kind
of a private person, you know?
I mean,
I do my work, I go home.
- To your wife?
- No.
At the present moment in time
I'm currently enjoying
a single status
in my personal life.
- Cheers.
- Bottoms up, huh?
Bottoms up.
I, uh, I noticed you got
a pretty alkaline-lookin'
soil out there.
What I want are some
house plants inside here.
Something that goes well
with the house.
This is a house?
Of course it's a house.
There's the bedroom
over there.
I think it's
getting dark in here.
You know,
what kind of plants
are gonna wanna
grow in this dump?
I don't know.
Shade plants?
- To us.
- Hm?
And to the seeds
we'll plant together.
Yeah, I'll, uh,
I'll d-drink to that.
Mm. You probably killed him,
you know?
Sleep well.
And when you wake,
drown in my eyes
and be all mine.
If that's the goddamn
Jehovah's witnesses again...
I'll get it.
Oh, hello, Nigel. It's you.
Nice suit.
- Subtle.
- I want to see Selena.
She's indisposed at the moment.
'Whoever it is,
we don't want any.'
It's Nigel,
and he's not going away
until he talks to you.
What the devil do you want?
I want to make
a very serious proposal.
In that outfit?
This is a leisure suit.
I've got three days off
from those little beasts
at Midvale
and I intend
to let my hair down.
Oh. Oh.
That ball will not operate
at its fullest
until you internalize
your powers, Selena.
Some mosaic invocations.
- Some what?
- Come again?
Exactly. That's my point.
You girls are rank amateurs
playing with fire.
Because we own the matches.
I, of all people,
know a hustle when I hear one.
Goodbye, Nigel.
It was nice talking
to you, Nigel.
No, it wasn't.
I hate to seem pushy
'my fairest of the fair,
but--'
A word of advice, Nigel.
If I had your skin problems,
I'd stop bothering people
put a bag over my head,
and go live under a bridge.
- 'Ouch!'
- Ha-ha-ha.
There's nothing wrong
with my skin.
That bitch.
You know, some people.
Where is he?
Whoever he sees first,
he'll love with all his heart.
What, for a day, tops, right?
He was too young
for you anyway, you know?
No, I do not know.
Where is he?
'Hey, I know that guy.'
- Oh, the cable's out.
- What cable?
This is a mirror.
So how come we could
ever see him in it?
That was magic, damn it.
The power.
Oh. So make it happen again,
you know?
I can't make it happen again.
I don't know how I did it
the first time.
Oh. Maybe you should let that
thing out of its box, you know?
Maybe it's more powerful
if you let it out of its box.
- The box.
- Where is it?
- The box?
It's underneath the rug
where you left it.
Go ahead.
It's stuck.
This is not my day.
It's stuck?
How could it be stuck?
- It's growing.
- 'How could it be growing?'
'It's made out of lead.'
Oh, too bad there's no sound.
How come there's no sound?
Get off the road, turkey!
Hey, dummy, you wanna die?
'What are you smoking, stupid?'
'You wanna kill yourself?'
'Anyway, she saw a lawyer,
and now she's gonna file.'
I told her to take him
for every cent, clean him out.
- Thank you very much.
- 'You're welcome.'
'BLT-10, hold the mayo.'
Here you go, everybody.
- 'Who wants onion rings?'
- 'Yeah, here.'
- Thanks.
- 'Some French fries.'
'The French fries are mine.'
Chicken for myself.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- 'Side order tomatoes.'
- Thanks for inviting me, Lucy.
I'm glad you could come, Jimmy.
- 'You want a root beer?'
- 'Yeah, thanks.'
Oh, there's Linda.
Hey, Linda!
- 'Hi!'
- Well, hello.
That's Clark Kent's cousin?
- 'Who's Clark Kent?'
- 'Is that Linda?'
- Guess what.
- What?
There's this all-night party
tonight at Eddie's.
He's the guy with the tattoo.
His folks are out of town.
And the guy with the bow tie?
That's Jimmy.
So you wanna come?
Oh, I don't know. I'm not
signed out for an overnight.
Well, so what? Go back, sign in
and climb out the window.
Mrs. Murphy's drunk
as a skunk by now.
Totally on another planet.
Oh, I don't know.
It just doesn't seem right.
But that's why it'll be fun.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Get off the road, buddy!
- Hey, stupid!
Look at that dingleberry.
What's a dingleberry?
Hey, you, space cadet!
Get outta the street!
- What is wrong with him?
- I don't know.
He's probably on drugs.
And he's gonna get creamed
if he's not too careful.
- Hi. Jimmy Olsen, photographer.
- Oh, I-I'm Kara.
- Who?
Oh, I'm...c-concerned.
Well,
that if we don't do something.
Oh, yeah, you go out there,
and try to help a guy like that
and he's probably got
a gun or a knife.
You know, it's not too safe.
Hey, I'm starving. Let's eat.
Come on, Linda.
Power of Shadow...
Bring him...
...to me.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa!
Look at that.
Hey, turkey, get out.
'Look out. Watch out.'
'My car!'
Oh!
You've never seen
a tattoo before, Linda?
- 'Look!'
- 'What's that?'
'I don't know, there's
somebody hanging out of it.'
Oh, my God. It's a runaway!
- Somebody's gotta do something!
- Hey, what's she doing?
Lucy, be careful. Lucy!
- 'Lucy!'
- 'Wait!'
'Get the kids off the street!'
'Get off the street!
Get off the street!'
'She's still in there.'
- Oh, excuse me. I'm in a rush.
- I know the feeling.
Are you okay?
'It's gasoline!
It's gasoline!'
Hey! Look at that.
A storm dragon?
A super girl.
Oh, my God.
Don't. Don't look at her.
You're gonna be alright.
There's no broken bones.
I love you.
What did he say?
Looked like
I love you to me.
No! No!
You love me?
With all my heart, forever.
"A bird of free
and careless wing
"was I through many
a smiling spring.
"The cold repulse,
the look askance
"the lightning of love's
angry glance, stay.
Let me behold you."
I-I have to go.
Oh, I-I have to go.
'We've got everything
under control.'
Lucy!
'Just go on back to your homes.'
Lucy.
- Oh.
- Thank God.
- You alright?
- I think so.
I hit my head.
Nigel must know her.
She must be one of his students.
He must have put her up to it.
No. I don't think that at all.
Oh, she just happened
to be in the wrong place
at the wrong time, right?
Materializing
in a bulldozer, huh?
She's a wimpy little thing.
I don't know why you care
what she does, anyway.
Because nobody
gets in my way.
Why don't you just leave
this poor kid alone
and worry about
the other one that flies?
I worry about everything.
It's my job. Stand back.
Oh, come on, now.
She's just a teenager.
What good is a sword
if it's not unleashed?
But she's a total zero.
You don't even know her name.
The naming of names
is not necessary.
Let us concentrate
on her face.
And my shadow
will do the rest.
Your what?
Power of Shadow...
...take shape.
Look like a vicious dark star.
Seek out that wretched
young creature.
And destroy her
wherever she...
...are.
Oh, God. That's awful.
That's never gonna work.
Quiet, listen.
Oh, my God! Oh!
Oh, I'm scared.
Next time...
...remind me to
do this outside.
- Absolutely not.
- Why? It's terrific.
Leave this place
and do no harm.
There she is again.
What'd she say?
No, this is not possible.
This is not right.
Where's the wimp?
Ah!
Aah!
I think he can
take care of her.
See? Hee!
What did I tell ya?
- She quit, right?
- Wrong.
Every time!
Send a man to do a woman's job,
and that's what you get.
Damn her eyes.
Who is she?
Are you asking me?
I'm telling you.
- Find out!
- Well, sure, but...
You know, I think
I recognize the costume.
It wasn't his fault.
It wasn't his fault!
Well, then, who's fault was it?
Leave him alone.
Let him play.
Where have you been?
- Outside--
- Look at you.
Look at those clothes.
Oh, I'll go change.
I-I'm sorry--
And you'll put on
your proper school uniform.
And get out of that
ridiculous costume.
- Yes, ma'am.
- And cover your legs.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't you
"Yes, ma'am" me.
No, ma'am.
Cut that out!
I think you're blowing
this thing out of proportion
if you want my opinion.
No, this box is definitely
getting bigger...
...and uglier.
All I'm saying is
you can't go nuts
over a landscape guy
and a teenager in a blue suit.
She flies.
Can you get that
through your thick skull
and into your
tiny brain, Bianca?
The girl can fly.
Okay.
Now, let's get serious.
Come to mama.
'Oh.'
Oh! Whoa!
Selena, cut it out!
I'm not doing it!
I think we're venturing where...
...you know, fools rush in
and angels fear to tread.
I'm no angel.
It's the wimp again.
And she's trespassing.
Hello.
Oh, no. Not now.
'Tis only but me, my love.
Please, you'll let
everyone know.
What? That I love you?
I'd shout it
from the highest hill.
Please don't.
I know you think me the fool,
but at least tell me your name.
Linda. Linda Lee.
Linda.
Lovely Linda Lee.
These roses pale beside thee.
Oh.
Well, thank you, but I'm--
And sweet chocolates
for my sweet Linda.
Hm.
What're you doing?
Please?
Oh, no, I...
Well, alright.
But just for a minute.
You hate me, don't you?
Hate you?
I don't even know you.
I don't even know your name.
Ethan.
Say my name aloud but once,
and I shall die the happy fool.
- Look, Ethan--
- Huh!
Ethan.
Her soft caress
did at once renew
the beating
of his broken heart.
Are you crazy?
Marry me?
Marry you, but...
- I don't--
- Don't say it. Don't, please.
I know.
What?
We're from different worlds.
- You mean, you know where I'm--
- Just give me a chance, Linda.
Love makes everything possible.
A poor, uneducated gardener
can indeed worship
a rich debutante
and make her happy,
if she'd just...
Oh, Ethan.
I'm not rich. I'm just--
Well, then
I'll support us both.
You're nuts, you know that?
You're so sweet,
but you're out of your mind.
Over you.
What a touching scene.
Round and round they go...
...where they stop...
Boy, you're really getting
the hang of this.
Where is she?
Jesus.
Who are you?
I am Selena.
Diadanus of Catania,
priestess of Sekhnet.
I am the ultimate Siren of Endor
and you, little lady
are trespassing
on private property.
She means him.
I am Kara of Argo City.
Daughter of Alura and Zor-El.
And I don't scare easily.
- No?
- No.
Try...
...this.
This lady is improving my leaps
and bounds, I gotta tell ya.
Whoa!
You okay?
No.
You want a hacksaw
or somethin'?
Now I am really upset.
What's going on?
Whoa!
Put me down.
- Where am I?
- You're safe.
Safe? Where's Linda?
Put me down.
- Where's my Linda?
- Take it easy.
Ethan!
Very clever.
That oughta keep her out
of your hair for a few hours.
Clever?
A cheap trick.
Power of Shadow
bring him to me.
Bring him to me.
- Ugh!
- Didn't work, huh?
Maybe they're too far away.
I can make the sky rain coconuts
with pinpoint accuracy
but I still can't control
men's minds.
Not with her around.
So maybe...
Now, don't go through the roof.
But maybe we oughta back down
and give
old you-know-who a call.
You know who?
- Spit it out.
- Nigel.
I shall pretend
you didn't say that.
But I did.
All I'm thinking,
and forgive me
for thinking out of turn here
is that he is been around.
He knows things, we don't.
'Plus, the way you wrap him
around your little finger'
'I'm always amazed.'
What's in it for me?
- Me.
- Ah-ha!
My dear, Nigel,
the way to a woman's heart
is through the elimination
of her rivals.
- Murder. Are you proposing--
- Oh.
Certainly not.
Leave that to me.
You deliver the goods. Her.
Her? How?
By getting me him.
- She'll follow.
- Well, I don't.
- Follow any of this, I mean...
- Put that down.
Nigel, I want one thing.
Time to master my new toy.
'So we can rule the world?'
And you want him here?
Johnny Appleseed
in your living room?
Yes. In the flesh.
So she will follow?
No other reason?
- None.
- You're sure of that?
'Oops, I'm sorry.'
'The little spider got out.'
What?
Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Kara.
Kara?
What happened?
You got hit on the head
by a coconut.
- Huh?
- Hm.
What's with
the Halloween costume?
This is not a costume.
These are my clothes.
- What do you mean?
- Look, I, I have to go now.
I will come back
for you later, I promise.
I've just gotta get back
to the amusement park.
Amusement park? Linda!
I gotta find Linda,
she was in trouble.
Oh, Linda's alright.
She can take care of herself.
'No, no, no. She can't.
Something's wrong.'
She's in big trouble,
and I love her.
I love her.
Yeah, I do love her.
- I have to go, Ethan. Goodbye.
- Yeah, so do I.
Hey.
I told you,
Linda can take care of herself.
You just flew over my head,
didn't you? I saw you--
I'll go back there and I'll
take care of everything, so--
I said, you just flew over
my head. True or false?
True.
Like Superman.
He's my cousin.
He's your cousin?
Yes. I shouldn't be
telling you this though.
- I'm here--
- Wait a minute.
Wait one minute. I mean,
you can do the whole number
leap tall buildings
with a single bound?
- And look right through things?
- Yes.
- Bend steel bars?
Whoa!
Oh, Selena.
I have to go. Selena has--
Wait a minute.
Please, take me with you.
I have to find Linda.
What is it?
The Burundi Wand.
Pure, unadulterated evil.
Ready?
But how can you love her?
You don't even know her.
Oh, yeah, I do.
If she's in trouble,
then I got no business
standing here talking with you.
Even if you are
what you say you are.
Linda is not in trouble.
Look, uh, don't make me
get rough, okay?
You wouldn't stand a chance.
Please trust me.
Linda is alright.
How do you know?
I just...
...know.
Linda.
Oh, my God!
How did you do that?
Ethan?
Ethan!
Nigel, you are wonderful.
Pure genius.
You deserve...me.
And something else.
Now, let's get out
of this dump.
Hartley, you've seen this thing?
Look at this...
Hey, what's the matter?
You catchin' flies?
Lucy, look.
Oh!
What is it?
It's a mountain, Lucy,
isn't it?
Tell me I'm not seeing things.
How did it get there, Jimmy?
I don't know. It just appeared.
How can a mountain just appear?
Hey, there's something on the top.
Looks like a castle.
Looks more like a fortress.
Ethan?
Ethan.
Ethan!
Enjoy your prison, Supergirl.
Forever and ever.
No, Ethan!
Don't do this!
'Ethan!'
Where am I?
Hey, you can't arrest me
without a warrant.
'I'm calling my lawyer.'
- Slow down.
- We want Selena out!
Smile, lunkhead.
You're not a gardener anymore.
You're Prince Ethan, now.
Are we gonna stand up to her
or not?
- 'Yeah. Yeah.'
- Selena must go!
Who's this little twerpette?
She's someone
who believes in freedom.
Uh, Lucy, it's not a good time
to express yourself.
'I don't know who you
think you are'
or what evil force you represent
but if you think you can just
get rid of anybody
who stands up to you,
just make them disappear
like my friend, Linda...
- Who?
- Linda, my roommate.
She disappeared the day
that mountain showed up.
- The wimp.
Seize them!
'Drive off.'
Let me go now!
Nobody messes around
with Jimmy Olsen!
Now, let-let go off me.
I'm with the press!
- Zaltar!
- Squirt.
- Zaltar?
Zaltar, it's me.
It's-it's Kara.
I know.
Squirt.
What is that?
- Where are we?
- Nowhere.
The Phantom Zone?
It's lonely here, my Kara.
So sad.
I've been here forever,
and I shall stay here forever.
- Ethan?
- Yes, my darling.
Don't call me your darling.
You despise me.
- Get me the Coffer of Shadow.
- Yes, my darling.
Now...
I think we need something...
...there.
Oh, Jimmy.
Oh, terrific.
The old
dangling-in-a-cage routine.
Pathetic, Selena.
- Who's that guy?
- He's my math teacher, I think.
'What are they for?'
Insurance.
But you can't just give up.
You founded a whole city.
I did, and then
I doomed it to destruction.
That was an error. A tragic one.
When you're my age and you make
as many tragic errors as I do
it is a different tune
that you will sing.
I will not.
I will never give up.
I will never spend my entire
life in a place like this.
- I would die first!
- Strong words.
There are worst things than
dying, and I deserve every one.
- What is this?
- A horse.
I think.
On Earth, I think
it's called a horse.
- And you made this here?
- Mm.
- Then you haven't given up.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Earth, Zaltar.
Earth, a tree, a horse.
You keep making things
from Earth.
- The place intrigues me.
- Well, then, let's go there.
Certainly.
When is the next train?
Oh!
What is a train?
What's so funny?
Don't laugh at me, Zaltar.
I, I'm only laughing at myself.
For you...
...I weep.
Is this train
a way out of here?
There is no way out of here.
That is the point
of the Phantom Zone.
My neighbors know,
the criminals
the corrupt,
the evil, they're here.
Over the hill there.
With no way out.
But there's always a way out.
'If there's a way in,
there's a way out.'
There is a way.
- But it's impossible.
- Why?
'No, it wouldn't work.'
'You'll be swept into a
singularity if it didn't work.'
No.
Forget I mentioned it.
Have a squirt instead.
I could do it.
Then, please.
At least teach me how.
There's nothing to teach.
You can't, as they say,
practice at the rift.
You get one chance only.
- The rift?
- Sure, you won't have a squirt?
'Once you get used to it,
I think it's delicious.'
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
There is enough doom and gloom
in the air already.
And it is better
to accept defeat
than to take a chance and try
like fools to redeem ourselves
and save our city
and all those who we love there.
Plus, all the people on Earth
that this wicked sorceress
is going to make suffer
just because of us.
Cheers!
We could die trying.
But we won't.
We won't. Come on.
'Tomorrow.'
Thursday. Friday.
Just like here,
we go for the cops first, right?
Hm, and the army.
By Saturday, we have
the continental United States
Mexico, Canada.
'Oh, my God, Selena.
It's the box.'
- Hush it up!
- No.
What the box wants...
...the box gets.
- What is it?
- Fascinating.
I don't know.
Is this it?
Is this the way out?
Not yet!
This is the Quantum Vortex!
We must risk our destruction
in it.
To move mountains...
...you must make sacrifices.
Zaltar, I'm scared!
Accept your fears.
Confront your demons.
Find your destiny
in the maelstrom!
Zaltar, I can't. I can't.
You...can!
Two specks. Look!
What do I do?
How do you murder someone
in the Phantom Zone?
She's with some old guy,
it looks like.
Move, huh? Come on!
Calm down, okay?
Ah.
This is what I want.
The Salian Fireballs.
'"Page 321"'
'"chapter 6."'
Whoa!
- What was that?
- I don't...
- Aah!
- No!
No!
'No!'
"Power Of Rainmaking." No!
"How To Separate
Husband And Wife."
No, not now. Not now!
Well, you better find
something fast
like an atom bomb.
I found it.
"Summoning...
...the demon storm."
We go.
Higher, girl! Higher!
Come with me!
I am with you!
On, girl.
I am with you.
Zaltar!
Oh, thank God!
You've had your fun, Selena.
The game is finished.
Hardly.
One false step, bluebird
and even if you don't,
your friends will get the point.
Hey, no!
I don't like this.
Don't worry, Lucy.
Don't worry.
I wouldn't if I were you.
Well, you're not me.
Quick, get out of the way.
Into the alcove over there.
- Come on.
- Hurry, Jimmy.
- Out!
- Hurry!
The Omegahedron, Selena.
I want it.
Well, then, Supergirl
you shall have it.
Supergirl, above you. Look out!
Aah!
I think I'll be going.
If you'll excuse me.
That's what I said.
I'm staying, I'm staying.
You have no friends, Selena.
You treat everyone as if
they were put on this Earth
to serve you.
More or less,
I think they were.
You included.
Power of Shadow...
...appear!
...destroy her!
Ah!
Ah, I can't.
I can't...
You can!
On, girl!
Confront her with it!
It's the only way!
No, no, no, no, no!
Oh! I have to go.
I have to return this
to where it belongs.
And I must ask you all something.
It's alright, Supergirl.
We never saw you.
We never even heard of you.
Thank you.
Ethan, Linda, she...
Well, she had to leave
in a hurry, but she...
You don't have to say a word.
I know.
I'll explain about Linda.
Thank you, Ethan.
Take care of yourself, kiddo.
Phew! Wow!
That was some kiss.
Wow!
Goodbye, Linda.