- Hello to you.
I hope you're fine.
Who knows the
electron wave functions
for Kryptonian
covalent bonding?
Sorry.
Leah.
The cube root
of the wavelength...
- Greetings.
- Hello, Kara.
- Hello to you.
Oh, it is beautiful.
What's that gonna be, Zaltar?
I think...a tree.
A tree.
What is a tree?
A lovely thing
which grows on Earth.
Earth? You mean
where my cousin went?
Hmm, and to where,
one day soon perhaps
I might venture as well.
I don't believe you. How?
- In that. Through there.
- The binary chute?
But you'd never survive
the pressure. It'll destroy--
In that I can.
Zip-zap and I'm gone.
But you'd never
leave us, Zaltar.
- You'd never leave Argo City.
- Indeed, I might, Kara.
Too much of a good thing here.
Perhaps I'll try Saturn instead.
Yes, I think I might.
Saturn is...is that
further away than Earth?
Silly question.
Didn't you study six-dimensional
geometry at school?
Do they not teach
anything anymore?
Well, of course they do.
I know the equations.
I just can't see
them in my head.
Most great artists find
mathematics troublesome, Kara.
- Only use your imagination.
- Mm-hm.
Saturn and Earth
are in outer space
but we, we are in inner space.
Our city has two great
power sources.
This is one of them. Look.
An omegahedron.
The Guardians let you have it?
Not exactly. I borrowed it.
You stole it. Oh, Zaltar,
they're gonna--
No, borrowed it...
for the afternoon.
- For inspiration.
- Inspiration.
But I think that
I shall never see
the branches
of a living tree.
Why? An omegahedron
can create life, can't it?
It can't, child, it can't.
Just the illusion of life.
That's a fancy shadow
of the real thing
which is the most we can hope
for on this lonely old rock.
Kara.
Kara, I've been looking
for you for ages.
Oh, I'm sorry, mother.
- Zaltar.
- Alura, join us.
We're just inventing
miracles.
Put your fingers here,
Kara, and press hard.
Good. Now try it.
Let your imagination explode
and give it a try. Go on.
Zaltar, my-my husband
tells me you talk
of leaving Argo City.
For where?
Parts unknown.
It is, alas, a fact.
You and Zor-EI
have a life here-
You've each other and Kara.
But, Zaltar, you
founded this city. It's yours.
As far as the eye can see,
right to the veil, smack
and then what?
What is beyond?
Alura, I cannot contain
myself to Argo City only.
My head is boiling with ideas.
My imagination is too vast,
it's uncontrollable.
If you want my opinion, Zaltar,
you're starting to repeat
yourself here with
all this airy, glittery stuff.
Exactly. That's why
I'm going to Venus.
Venus? When?
Tomorrow or the next day,
at the latest.
Zaltar, have you
thought about this?
It doesn't make sense to me.
I have thought intensely.
My mind is made up.
Kara! The power source!
Oh, Zaltar!
Save me. Please! Help!
- No!
- Kara!
Zaltar!
Help! No!
You took the omegahedron.
That's not correct,
I lost the omegahedron.
- No, father, I did--
- Shh, Kara.
No matter who.
Without it this city can't
survive more than a few days.
Our lights will grow dim and
the very air we breathe so thin.
I know. So I shall find it.
I shall go right to the end of
inner space and I'll return it.
Impossible. How? No one can
leave Argo City and you know it.
This is our universe and
you've destroyed it with a game.
- A childish game.
- I think it can be done.
Through there, the binary chute,
in the traveler.
Like a coward you
choose instant destruction
while the rest of us
are doomed to stay here...
Kara!
Kara, no!
- You lunatic!
- She'll be killed.
Oh, no, she won't.
She will be safe,
through the binary
through the warp,
into another register.
Another what?
Gravitational radiation
a pathway from inner space
to outer space.
Then she'll never
be the same, ever.
At least she'll be alive.
And my fate is sealed.
I've lost the omegahedron
I must be sent
to the Phantom Zone.
Your suffering will be short,
mine...forever.
Some more
champagne, my dear Selena?
What are you thinking about?
It's such a pretty world.
I can't wait until
it's all mine.
The only way you
can rule the world
is to become invisible,
my pumpkin.
Invisible?
You'd almost know
how to make me invisible.
Oh, I do know.
Take five black beans
and the head of a dead man,
place one bean in his mouth,
two beans in his eyes, then--
Nigel, enough.
But it works. Then you can
get anywhere, do anything.
Nigel, how long have
we been together?
Ooh. Months, darling.
Then why does
it seem like years?
Because you're so impatient.
You want everything yesterday.
It's a lifetime
to discover the secrets
of black magic from
the ancient grimoires.
Holy cow.
I wonder.
Immortality be upon this one.
She is a sharer
of the sun's everlasting life.
There will now
be no danger of death.
This world will
keep her forever.
What is it?
What's going on?
Hey, what's going on?
I've just outgrown you, Nigel.
These things happen.
You can't treat me
like this, Selena.
Without me you'd
still be reading tea leaves
at Lake Tahoe.
Amsterdam and more. That's
TVVA. Never has flying been easier.
You can't run out on me, Selena.
I've got the keys, sweetheart.
The president confirmed
reports that Superman has embarked
on a special peace-seeking
mission to a galaxy
scientists estimate may be
several hundred trillion
light-years from our own...
Whoo-whoo!
Now, here's the weather
from the general Chicago area
increasing cloudiness with
the possibility of showers.
Breezy but warm
with a high of 62.
Bianca!
I'm home.
Wha-at?
Show your face.
I have a surprise for you.
They've turned
off the hot water again.
I'm really gonna have to kill
somebody down at the DWP.
The only way we're gonna
pay our bills next month
in this dump, is to just go
ahead and start our own coven.
No longer necessary.
I was reading in this book
"The Witches Guide
to Heaven and Hell"
if you start your
own coven all you've to do
is charge five bucks a head,
minimal admission. That's great.
- Chicken feed.
- That's better than goose egg.
What's in the Coffer of Shadow
there? Where's little Nigel?
Nigel, my dear Bianca,
is history.
Oh, yeah? How so?
The water department is history.
The car payments are history.
The mortgage
payments are history.
- How are the property taxes?
- History.
The world is at last my oyster.
Now, this I like.
- Hello.
- "Hello," she says.
- Well, hello to you, honeybun.
- Hello.
I was wondering if you could
tell me where I am?
What do they call this place,
Eddie? Lovers' Lane, isn't it?
You got it in one,
Billy boy. Lovers' Lane.
Oh, no, you see,
what I meant was is
well, those lights over there.
What are they called?
Check out the view
from back here, Eduardo.
Ah!
Stop that.
You're, uh, Superman's
best friend, huh?
No. His cousin. I've come here
to search for the omegahedron.
It's a power source vital to
Argo City. That's where I live.
No kidding.
Eddie and me here
we're on a secret mission also.
We're out looking
for a good time.
And you just won
the brass ring, baby.
Oh, she works out, huh?
Why are you doing this?
It's just the way we are.
You shouldn't have
done that, baby.
Come on.
Oh, I see.
You really wanna play games,
eh, sweetheart?
Come on. Come...
Cw!
Huh?
Eddie, I think
maybe we should
kinda keep this to ourselves.
What do you think?
Freddie, you little
devil. How are you?
Fresh ammunition, everybody.
Try telling your wife.
I need another.
Where is it? Where's
the little mystery ball?
Let me have a peek.
Maybe I can shed some light.
I hate light.
Is it electrical?
ls it hot to the touch?
- Where is it?
- Safe and sound.
Go mix.
Leave me to my thoughts.
Go mix? With these people?
You must be mad.
Who are they?
Wrinkly little wretches.
These are my
foot soldiers, Nigel.
My army of the night.
I'm considering nothing
less than world...domination.
After you left me in the lurch
I saw something that should
worry you greatly
if you're serious about
taking over this planet.
My secret was blue and red
and it knew how to fly.
I've a secret too, Nigel.
I have the power.
Get that through your head.
Oh, I bet they're
in for it now, eh?
Count on it.
I have in my time seen
a great number of things
even more impressive
than a human cigarette
lighter, dear lady.
To wit.
What is that?
Overreaching ambition.
Take heed.
Touched a little
nerve, didn't I?
Hello.
The red toad
that lurks in the briars
and brambles
is full of sorceries.
There's a little bone
on the left side.
A little bone?
A little bone, which
if bound to a man stirs up
the greatest lust.
- I wanna be rich and famous.
- Then stick with me.
I was put on this earth
to thrill millions.
Mmm, this is scrumptious.
Why don't we go somewhere
else and dance cheek to cheek?
Stop it, Selena!
That's not fair.
Pick on me.
- Thanks.
- Hey, no sweat.
- What happened?
- Oh, nothing much.
Get out of my house, Nigel
and don't come slithering back.
I'm warning you, Selena
don't be so shortsighted.
Good morning.
Have you got it, Lucy?
Must be near that oak tree.
- Hurry up.
- Found it, guys.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to find the ball.
Come on, don't take all day.
You're holding up the game.
- Hey, it's your turn to bat.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Okay. Okay.
Let's play ball.
Alright, batter.
I couldn't make it.
I have to finish my...
Hey, toss the
ball back, will you?
Come on,
make it two in a row.
Play ball.
- Where have you been?
- With the principal.
Danvers is doing
his usual number.
Jeez, another
barfy new student.
They're really scraping the
bottom of the barrel these days.
Hang in there, Danvers.
Don't let them get to you.
Thirty days. Semester
just started. You'll be...
- Hello, I--
- Didn't knock.
Don't we teach you
manners around here?
Don't we try to impress
on our young ladies
that animals
in the jungle never knock
but Midvale girls always do.
Where you going? Come back here.
Come in.
I forgot, I'm just not used to--
Wait a minute.
Wait just one second.
I have never before
in my life laid eyes on you
have I, young lady?
- No, sir, I'm new here.
- New here?
Obviously you're new if I've
never laid eyes on you before.
The question remains,
just who on earth are you?
Umm...
On Earth, I'm Lee.
Linda Lee.
Where's your letter
of recommendation?
Letter?
I must talk to you, principal.
- I am busy now.
- So are they, them.
All the little monsters
you admit to the place.
They have nailed
my desk drawers shut.
Never in all my years
as a school teacher...
Come, Danvers.
I will not be provoked.
I will not let him
get to me this semester.
I'll be strong.
Be strong.
Be like a rock.
What did you say
your name was?
Oh, yes.
Linda Lee, huh?
Yes, my cousin
probably wrote you.
Umm, maybe you got
his letter under K for Kent?
In your files.
Kent?
It doesn't ring any bells.
Doesn't even ring a...
Oh, here it is.
Big as life.
"My dear Mr. Danvers,
I'm writing on behalf
of a very
special young lady."
An orphan?
Don't expect to be treated
any differently
on that account, Miss Lee.
Oh, no, sir, I won't.
One way or another,
we're all alone
on this...miserable
little planet.
Yes, sir, I know.
Since your school records
were obviously lost in the mail
you'll have to start
at the bottom.
It's only fair
to the other girls.
You'll have English, Latin,
math, biology, computing...
All at once?
...and chemistry.
Idle hands are the
devil's playground. This way.
- Man on the floor!
Open up, Lane, I know
you're in there.
I'm not decent,
Mr. Danvers sir.
And you never will be either.
You little liar.
Come on in. Come on in.
I haven't got all year.
No.
I'm supposed to have
a single this term.
We don't always get
what we want, Miss Lane.
Disappointments
thicken our skins.
Who wants thick skin?
I'm Linda Lee.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
I'm Lucy Lane.
Lucy Lee, this is Linda Lane.
- No, it isn't.
- What?
- She's Linda Lee and I'm--
- Lucy Lane.
You two know each other.
Oh, no. We just met.
- When?
- Just now.
But we've known each other
for years, haven't we, Linda?
- Oh, gee, I don't think I--
- Oh, of course.
The Daily Planet, of course.
Linda's cousin works there. And
your sister, what's her name?
The one that's always
calling me and bothering me?
- Lois.
- Ah, yes, that's the one.
Anyway, show our new
Miss Lee around, Miss Lane.
Oh, by the way,
she's an orphan
but don't let her play
on your sympathies, hmm?
So, who's your cousin?
Clark Kent.
You're kidding me.
Clark Kent's your cousin?
You're putting me on.
- You know him?
- Do I know him?
Does my sister know him?
- Now, that's the big question.
- Oh, I see.
I guess, if they worked
at the same newspaper
they must know each other.
- Well...
- ls this where I'll sleep?
Well, this is your bed,
but we don't sleep around here.
Nonstop excitement
in this dorm.
All the real dementals
are sent here.
So, when's the rest
of your stuff arriving?
I don't have any other stuff.
What? It's all
in that little bag?
Oh, well, you see, I have the
means to buy more, it's just...
Well, I just haven't
had the chance since...
- Do you know him?
- Superman? Sure.
My sister's got something
goin' with the big guy.
Listen, you can borrow
any of my clothes
any time you want.
Just dig in and help yourself.
Thank you.
You're very kind.
He's a real character.
A real hunk.
I'll introduce you
to him someday
if we wind up getting along.
Now, then, focus
your tiny minds
on the kind of problem
that it used to take
weeks of thought
before the computer.
Even now it can take
a long time
without certain algorithms
which...if you behave
for two seconds
I might reveal to you.
Love, hate, love, hate.
Love.
The cards have decided
people will do
anything for love.
They'll jump off
cliffs for love.
They'll drown themselves
like lemmings.
So...l'll make
everybody love me.
Oh, no chance.
You're an awful person,
honey, remember? Forget it.
Use your imagination, pinhead.
That's what magic is all about.
Why are we not moving?
Because I'm in love.
Come here,
you beautiful thing.
He's cute.
Hey, What's going on?
Here's an exercise in big
numbers I want you to try.-.
It's trying
to tell me something.
Well, what?
That we're near danger?
I don't know.
How do I know?
- I know.
- Well, tell me.
My prince has come.
Oh, no.
I saw him first, Selena.
That's not fair.
I copied his number first.
Well done.
Now, let's get out of here.
..-average size
of a Chinese family
average age of death
and marriage and pregnancy.
Use this equation to
compute the population of China
in the year 2040.
Linda...are you with us?
Umm...
- Yes, sir, I am.
- Oh, are you?
Where, might I ask?
W-well, here, sir.
On Earth...sir.
How fortunate
for the rest of us.
May I presume that whilst
you were staring at the wall
and not at your terminal like
your other little friends here
you were in fact,
hard at work
solving this little equation?
Oh, yes, sir, I was.
- I mean, I was--
- Excellent.
The answer, please.
Pay attention, class, Miss Lee
is about to enlighten us.
Five billion, two hundred
and seventy one million
nine thousand and ten.
Come on, let's get outta here
before he makes you stay.
Come on, hurry.
Miss Lee.
- Oh, shit.
- Yes, sir?
Have you been going
through my papers?
Of course not, sir.
Then how do you know
the correct answer?
- How?
- I guess, I just--
It's all this crazy weather
we've been having, sir.
All the storms, shock
waves, electromagnetism.
It makes people smarter
than they are for a second.
We gotta go, sir.
Oh, boy, thanks.
You know I gotta learn--
How did you know the answer?
I don't know.
Six-dimensional geometry.
- I never could do it before.
- Yeah.
Well, you want some
friendly advice?
Don't go showing it off
'cause nobody's gonna like you.
I'll see you later.
Ah!
Nice going.
You know she tripped
you on purpose?
Absolutely.
She's retarded.
There's not much time left.
Come on, let's go.
You take it, Myra.
Hey, Myra, see if you can
put Lane out for good.
Come on, team. Come on.
He)!' YOU guys alright?
- Oh, God. What happened?
- Yes. You alright?
Myra, how'd she do that?
- It hit her shoulder.
- I don't know.
Hey, you guys, did you see that
cute guy in the softball field?
Oh, yes.
With the black
hair and the big muscles?
He was something else.
- Did you talk to him?
- No, but I'm gonna.
Talk? Who'd
waste time talking?
He's working on the trees,
could be around for a while.
- Are they in?
- Yes.
Myra, you sure you
wanna go through with this?
Hey, what's with you?
Chicken?
Oh, boy, I'm really
gonna enjoy this.
I can't wait to hear
them scream.
Why don't you shut off the hot
and give them an ice bath?
Are you kidding me?
That's nowheresville.
If you shut off the cold
you'll scald them.
So they lose a little skin.
Serves them right.
I want to see them suffer.
A-ah!
I am wet!
Cw!
Don't leave me. Don't leave me!
I hate you!
You never looked better!
We'll get you all!
What do you think?
It looks the same to me.
It's kinda dull.
All you need is a couple of
streaks and your ears pierced.
I can do it
free of charge.
My ears what?
Pierced. Like in you know,
I take a needle
I heat it up and then I dab it
with some alcohol and zap.
All the guys go crazy.
Because I've holes in my ears?
What are you, putting me on?
Sometimes I can't
figure you out, Linda.
So, where are you
going this weekend?
Nowhere.
Nowhere? Well, you can't
stay around here.
This place is depressing.
I mean, like the tombs.
- Why'?
- Why?
What, were you born
yesterday?
This is a three-day weekend.
A three-day weekend.
So, listen. Why don't
you come home with me?
I only live about five miles
from here and I got this guy
coming up from Metropolis.
I think he knows
your cousin Clark.
His name's Jimmy Olsen.
I think he's real stuck on me.
Anyways, I could ask him
to bring a friend along.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, nothing.
Nothing.
No, I think I'm gonna
stay here and study
get things organized.
Don't forget to
call me Saturday.
Just a sec.
- Hey, Linda.
- Hi.
I'll see you later
at Popeye's then, okay?
- Alright, I'll try. I promise.
- You better. It's gonna be fun.
' Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Have a good time.
Come along now, Lucy.
- Oh, mom, how are you doing?
- I've had a terrible week.
"Take a spider off his web...
"...and shut him up inside...
"...two shells of a nut.
"Now, boil the nut in oil
"into which has been added
"some of the web.
"With a silver spoon,
put two drops...
"...of the oil
"into some water.
Right.
"He who drinks the water
"shall be in love
with the first person he sees.
"Uh, so long as the spider
is shut up in the nutshell.
"Or one day goes by...
...whichever comes first."
Big deal, one day.
Why don't you just use,
you know.
I'm saving it
for bigger things.
Hi, folks,
you're missing the big sale.
Country and western boys
from the Chicago area.
Now to start off the hour.
Bianca, get the door.
Bianca!
You rang?
Hey, you!
I said...
...you rang?
Oh, yeah.
How you doing?
Uh, I'm looking for some person
called Mrs. Selena?
- Madame Selena.
- Oh.
And you found her,
lucky boy.
Entrer.
You must be very popular
in the neighborhood.
I always see your truck
parked around.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I get a lot of repeat
business. People like my work.
Yes, I'm sure they do.
- Wet your whistle?
- Huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, as a matter
of fact, I don't mind if I do.
So, uh, where's
the one...ha-ha at?
It dropped dead.
Where at exactly?
Uh, out back?
We might get to know each other
a little more
before we dig in
and talk real turkey.
Well, uh, see, I'm kind of
a private person, you know.
I mean, I do my work,
I go home.
- To your wife?
- No.
At the present moment in time
I'm currently enjoying
a single status in
my personal life.
Cheers.
Bottoms up, huh?
Bottoms up.
I, I noticed you got a pretty
alkaline-looking soil out there.
What I want...
...are some houseplants
inside here.
Something that goes well
with the house.
This is a house?
Of course, it's a house.
There's the bedroom
over there.
I think it's getting
dark in here.
You know, what kind of plant
is gonna wanna...
...grow in this dump?
I don't know.
Shade plants.
- To us.
- Hm?
And to the seeds
we'll plant together.
Yeah, I'll-I'll drink...
...to that.
Hm, you probably killed him,
you know.
Sleep well.
And when you wake...
...drown in my eyes
and be all mine.
If that's the goddamn
Jehovah's witnesses again.
I'll get it.
Oh, hello, Nigel.
It's you.
Nice suit.
Subtle.
I want to see Selena.
She's indisposed
at the moment.
Whoever it is,
we don't want any.
It's Nigel and
he's not going away
until he talks to you.
What the devil do you want?
I want to make
a very serious proposal.
In that outfit?
This is a leisure suit.
I've got three days off
from those little beasts
at Midvale
and I intend to let
my hair down.
Uh-oh.
That ball will not operate
at it's fullest
until you internalize
your power, Selena.
Some mosaic invocations.
- Some what?
- Come again?
Exactly, that's my point.
You girls are rank amateurs
playing with fire.
Because we own the matches.
I, of all people,
know a hustle when I hear one.
Now, goodbye, Nigel.
- It was nice talking to you.
- No, it wasn't.
I hate to seem pushy,
my fairest of the fair but--
A word of advice, Nigel.
If I had your skin problems,
I'd stop bothering people,
put a bag over my head,
and go live under a bridge!
Ouch!
There's nothing wrong
with my skin.
That bitch.
You know, some people.
Where is he?
Whoever he sees first,
he'll love with all his heart.
What?
For a day tops, right?
He was too young
for you anyway, you know.
No, I do not know.
Where is he?
Hey, I know that guy.
- Oh, the cable's out.
- Oh, what cable?
This is a mirror.
So, how come we could...
...ever see him in it?
That was magic, dammit.
The power.
Oh, so make it happen again,
you know?
L...can't make it happen again.
I don't know how I did it.
Oh.
Maybe, you should let
that thing out of it's box.
Maybe, it's more powerful
if you let it out of it's box.
- The box.
- Where is it?
- The box?
It's underneath the rug,
where you left it.
Go ahead.
It's stuck.
This is not my day.
It's stuck?
How could it be stuck?
It's growing.
How could it be growing?
It's made out of lead.
Oh.
Too bad, there's no sound.
How come there's no sound?
Get off the road, turkey!
Hey, dummy,
you wanna die?
Smoking, stupid?
You wanna kill yourself?
She saw a lawyer,
and now she's gonna file.
I told her to take him for
every cent, clean him out.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
Here you go, everybody.
Who wants onion rings?
- Yeah, here.
- Thanks.
- Some French fries?
- French fries are mine.
Chicken for myself.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Side order tomatoes?
Thanks for inviting me,
Lucy.
I'm glad you could come,
Jimmy.
- You want a root beer?
- Yeah, thanks.
Oh, there's Linda.
Hey, Linda!
- Hi.
- Oh, hello.
That's Clark Kent's cousin?
Who's Clark Kent?
Is that Linda?
- Guess what.
- What?
There's this all-night party
tonight at Eddie's.
He's the guy
with the tattoo.
His folks are out of town.
And the guy with the bow tie,
that's Jimmy.
So, you wanna come?
I don't know. I'm not
signed out for an overnight.
So what? Go back, sign in
and climb out the window.
Mrs. Murphy's drunk
as a skunk by now.
Totally on another planet.
Oh, I don't know.
It just doesn't seem right.
But that's why
it'll be fun.
' Okay?
' Okay,
Get off the road, buddy.
Hey, stupid.
Look at that dingleberry.
What's a dingleberry?
Hey, you, space cadet!
Get out of the street!
- What is wrong with him?
- I don't know.
He's probably on drugs.
And he's gonna get creamed
if he's not too careful.
- Hi. Jimmy Olsen, photographer.
- Oh, l-l'm Kara.
- Who?
Oh, I'm...
...concerned.
Well, that if
we don't do something.
You go out there, try to help
a guy like that and he's
probably got a gun
or a knife.
It's not too safe.
Hey, I'm starving.
Let's eat.
Come on, Linda.
Power of shadow.
Bring him to me.
Whoa.
Look at that.
Hey, get out.
Look out. Watch out.
MY Car!
You've never seen a tattoo
before, Linda?
- Look!
- What's that?
There's somebody hanging
out of it.
Doesn't look like
there's anybody driving.
Oh, my God.
It's a runaway.
- Somebody's gotta do something.
- Hey, what's she doing?
Lucy, be careful.
Lucy!
- Come on.
- Lucy!
God, there's the pump?
She's still in there.
- Oh, excuse me. I'm in a rush.
- I know the feeling.
Are you okay?
It's gasoline!
- Hey, look at that.
- What?
A storm dragon?
A Supergirl.
Oh, my God!
Don't. Don't look at her.
You're gonna be alright.
There's no broken bones.
I love you.
What did he say?
Looked like
"I love you", to me.
No! No!
You love me?
With all my heart,
forever.
A bird of free
and careless wing
was I through many
a smiling spring.
The cold repulse,
the look askance.
The lightning of
love's angry glance, stay.
Let me behold you.
L-I have to go.
Oh, I-l have to go.
Everything's under control.
Lucy!
Just go on,
back to your homes.
Lucy.
- Oh.
- Thank God.
- You alright?
- I think so.
I hit my head.
Nigel must know her.
She must be one of his students.
He must have put her up to it.
No. I don't think that at all.
Oh, she just happened
to be in the wrong place
at the wrong time, right?
Materializing
in a bulldozer, huh?
She's a wimpy little thing.
I don't know why you care
what she does, anyway.
Because nobody
gets in my way.
Why don't you just leave
this poor kid alone
and worry about the
other one that flies?
I worry about everything.
It's my job. Stand back.
Oh, come on now.
She's just a teenager.
What good is a sword
if it's not unleashed?
But she's a total zero.
You don't even know her name.
The naming of names
is not necessary.
Let us concentrate
on her face.
And my Shadow
will do the rest.
Your what?
Power of Shadow...
...take shape.
Look like a
vicious dark star.
Seek out, that
wretched young creature.
And destroy her
wherever she...
...are.
Oh, God.
That's awful.
That's never
gonna work.
Oh, my God!
I'm scared.
Next time...
...remind me to
do this outside.
Leave this place
and do no harm.
There she is again.
What did she say?
No, this is not possible.
This is not right.
Where's the wimp?
Ah!
Argh!
I think he can
take care of her.
Ah!
Argh!
See?
What did I tell you?
She quit, right?
Wrong.
Every time!
Send a man to do a woman's job
and that's what you get.
Damn her eyes.
Who is she?
- Are you asking me?
- I'm telling you.
Find out!
Well, sure. But, you know,
I think I recognize the costume.
Leave him alone. Let him.
Where have you been?
- Outside--
- Look at you.
Look at those clothes.
Oh, I'll go change.
l-l'm sorry.
And you'll put on
your proper school uniform.
And get out of that
ridiculous costume.
Yes, ma'am.
- And cover your legs.
- Yes, ma'am.
Don't you
"yes, ma'am" me.
No, ma'am.
I think you're blowing
this thing out of proportion
if you want my opinion.
Oh, no. This box is
definitely getting bigger...
...and uglier.
All I'm saying is
you can't go nuts
over a landscape guy and a
teenager in a blue suit.
She flies.
Can you get that through
your thick skull
and into your
tiny brain, Bianca?
The girl can fly.
Okay-
Now.
Let's get serious.
Come to mama.
- Oh.
Oh.
Whoa.
- Selena, cut it out.
- I'm not doing it.
I think we're venturing where
you know, fools rush in
and angels fear to tread.
I'm no angel.
It's the wimp again.
And she's trespassing.
Hello.
Oh, no. Not now.
'Tis only but me,
my love.
Please, you'll let
everyone know.
What?
That I love you?
I'd shout it from
the highest hill.
Please don't.
I know you think me the fool,
at least tell me your name.
Linda. Linda Lee.
Linda.
Lovely Linda Lee.
These roses pale
beside thee.
Oh.
Well, thank you,
but I'm--
And sweet chocolates
for my sweet Linda.
Hm.
What are you doing?
Please?
Oh, no, I...
Please.
Well, alright.
But just for a minute.
You hate me,
don't you?
Hate you?
I don't even know you.
I don't even know
your name.
Ethan.
Say my name aloud but once
and I shall die the happy fool.
- Look, Ethan--
- Huh!
Ethan.
Your soft caress
did at once renew
the beating of
this broken heart.
Are you crazy?
Marry me?
Marry you?
- I don't--
- Don't say it. Don't, please.
I know.
What?
We're from
different worlds.
- You mean, you know where I'm--
- Just give me a chance, Linda.
Love makes
everything possible.
A poor uneducated gardener can
indeed worship a rich debutante
and make her happy
if she'd just...
Oh, Ethan.
I'm not rich.
I'm just--
Well, then
I'll support us both.
You're nuts,
you know that?
You're so sweet,
but you're out of your mind.
Over you.
What a touching scene.
Round and round they go.
Where they stop.
Boy, you're really getting
the hang of this.
Oh.
Where is she?
Jesus.
Who are you?
I am Selena.
Diadanus of Catania.
Priestess of Sechnid.
lam the ultimate Siren of Endor
and you, little lady, are
trespassing on private property.
She means him.
I am Kara of Argo City.
Daughter of Alura and Zor-El.
And I don't scare easily.
No?
No.
Try. . -
...this.
This lady is improving by leaps
and bounds, I gotta tell you.
You Okay?
No.
You want a hacksaw
or somethin'?
Now I am really upset.
What's going on?
Oh.
Put me down.
- Where am I?
- You're safe.
Safe? Where's Linda?
Put me down.
- Where's my Linda?
- Take it easy.
Ethan.
Ha-ha. Very clever.
That ought to keep her out
of your hair for a few hours.
Clever?
A cheap trick.
Power of Shadow.
Bring him to me.
Bring him...to me.
Ugh!
Didn't work, huh?
Maybe they're too far away.
I can make the sky rain coconuts
with pinpoint accuracy.
But I still can't control
men's minds.
Not with her around.
So maybe...
Now, don't go
through the roof.
But maybe we
ought to back down
and give old
you-know-who a call.
You-know-who.
- Spit it out.
- Nigel.
I shall pretend
you didn't say that.
But I did.
All I'm thinking
and forgive me
for thinking
out of turn here...
...is that
he's been around.
He knows things
we don't.
Plus, the way you wrap
him around your little finger
I'm always amazed.
What's in it for me?
Me.
Ah-ha.
My dear Nigel, the way to
a woman's heart is through
the elimination of her rivals.
Murder?
Are you proposing that--
Oh, certainly not.
Leave that to me.
You deliver the goods.
Her.
Her? How?
By getting me...
...him.
- She'll follow.
- Well, I don't.
- Follow any of this, I mean--
- Put that down.
Nigel, I want
one thing.
Time to master
my new toy.
So, we can rule the world?
And you want him here?
Johnny Appleseed
in your living room?
Yes. In the flesh.
So, she'll follow?
- No other reason?
- None.
You're sure of that?
Whoops, I'm sorry.
The little spider got out.
What?
Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Kara.
Kara?
What happened?
You got hit on the head
by a coconut.
- Huh?
- Hm.
What's with
the Halloween costume?
This is not a costume.
These are my clothes.
What do you mean?
Look, I-l have
to go now.
I'll come back for you later.
I've just gotta get back to
the amusement park.
Amusement park?
Linda!
I gotta find Linda,
she was in trouble.
Well, Linda's alright.
She can take care of herself.
No, no. She can't.
Something's wrong.
She's in big trouble
and I love her.
I love her.
Yeah, I do love her.
I have to go, Ethan.
Goodbye.
Yes, so do I.
Hey!
I told you Linda can
take care of herself.
- You just flew over my head.
- I'll take care of everything.
I said you just flew over
my head. True or false?
True.
Like Superman.
He's my cousin.
- He's your cousin?
- Yes.
I shouldn't be telling you
this though--
Wait one minute. I mean you can
do the whole number, leap tall
buildings with a single bound?
And look right through things?
- Yes
- Bend steel bars?
- Yes.
- Whoa!
- Oh, Selena. I have to go.
- Wait a minute.
- Selena has the Omegahedron.
- Please take me with you.
I have to find Linda.
What is it?
The Burundi Wand.
Pure, unadulterated evil.
Ready?
But how can you love her?
- You don't even know her.
- Oh, yeah, I do.
And she's in trouble,
then I got no business
standing here,
talking with you.
Even if you are
what you say you are.
Linda is not in trouble.
Look, uh, don't make me
get rough, okay?
You wouldn't
stand a chance.
Please trust me.
Linda is alright.
How do you know?
L just...
...know.
Linda.
Oh, my God.
How did you do that?
Ethan.
Ethan!
Nigel, you are wonderful.
Pure genius.
You deserve...
...me.
And something else.
Now, let's get out
of this dump.
Did you see this thing?
Look at this!
Hey, what's the matter?
Catchin' flies?
Lucy, look.
One minute nothing.
The next minute this.
What is it?
It's a mountain, Lucy.
Isn't it?
Tell me
I'm not seeing things.
How did it get there, Jimmy?
I don't know.
It just appeared.
How can a
mountain just appear?
Hey, there's something
on the top.
Looks like a castle.
Looks more like a fortress.
Ethan?
Ethan.
Ethan!
Ah.
Enjoy your prison,
Supergirl...
...forever and ever.
No, Ethan!
Don't do it!
Ethan!
Where am I?
You can't arrest
me without a warrant.
I'm calling my lawyer.
Slow down.
We want Selena out.
Smile, lunkhead.
You're not a gardener anymore.
You're Prince Ethan, now.
Are we gonna stand up
to her or not?
Yes.
Selena must go!
Who's this little twerpette?
She's someone
who believes in freedom.
Lucy, it's not a good time
to express yourself.
I don't know, who you are.
Or what evil force
you represent.
But if you think you can get rid
of anybody who stands up to you.
Just make them disappear.
Like my friend Linda.
Who?
Linda, my roommate.
She disappeared the day
that mountain showed up.
The wimp.
Seize them!
Leave her alone!
Drive off.
Leave her alone.
Nobody messes around
with Jimmy Olsen!
Now, let go of me.
I'm with the press!
Zaltar.
Squirt.
- Zaltar?
- Squirt.
Zaltar, it's me.
It's-it's Kara.
I know.
Squirt.
What is that?
Where are we?
Nowhere.
The Phantom Zone?
It's lonely here,
my Kara.
So sad.
I've been here forever
and I shall stay here forever.
- Ethan'?
- Yes, my damn'.
Don't call me your "darling."
You despise me.
- Get me the coffer of shadow.
- Yes, my darling.
Now...
...l think we need something.
There.
Oh, Jimmy.
Oh, terrific.
The old dangling-in-a-cage
routine.
Pathetic, Selena.
- Who's that guy?
- He's my math teacher, I think.
What are they for?
Insurance.
But you can't just give up.
You founded a whole city.
I did, and then
I doomed it to destruction.
That was an error.
A tragic one.
When you're my age
and you make as many
tragic errors as I do,
it is a different tune
that you will sing.
I will not.
I'll never give up.
I will never spend my entire
life in a place like this.
- I would die first!
- Strong words.
There are worse things than
dying and I deserve every one.
- What is this?
- A horse...l think.
On earth I think
it's called a horse.
- And you made this here?
- Mm.
- Then you haven't given up.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Earth, Zaltar.
Earth, a tree, a horse.
You keep making things
from earth.
- The place intrigues me.
- Well, then, let's go there.
Certainly.
When is the next train?
What is a train?
What's so funny?
Don't laugh at me, Zaltar.
I'm only laughing
at myself.
For you, I weep.
Is this train
a way out of here?
There is no way
out of here.
That is the point
of the Phantom Zone.
My neighbors now: the criminals,
the corrupt, the evil...
...they're here.
Over the hill there.
With no way out.
But, there's always a way out.
If there's a way in,
there's a way out.
There is a way.
- But it's impossible.
- Why?
No, it wouldn't work.
You'd be swept into
a singularity
if it didn't work. No.
Forget I mentioned it.
Have a squirt instead.
I could do it.
Then, please.
At least teach me how.
There's nothing to teach.
You can't, as they say
practice at the rift.
You get one chance only.
- The rift?
- Sure? You won't have a squirt?
Once you get used to it,
I think it's delicious.
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
There is enough doom
and gloom in the air already.
And it is better
to accept defeat
than to take a chance and try
like fools to redeem ourselves
and save our city and all those
who we love there.
Plus all the people on Earth
that this wicked sorceress
is going to make suffer
just because of us. Cheers!
We could die trying.
But we won't.
We won't. Come on.
Tomorrow.
Thursday. Friday.
Just like here, we go
for the cops first, right?
And the army.
By Saturday, we have
the continental United States,
Mexico, Canada.
Oh, my God, Selena.
It's the box.
- Hush it up.
- No.
What the box wants,
the box gets.
What is it?
Fascinating.
I don't know.
ls this it?
Is this the way out?
Not yet! This
is the Quantum Vortex!
We must risk
our destruction in it.
To move mountains,
you must make sacrifices.
Zaltar, I'm scared!
Accept your fears.
Confront your demons.
Find your destiny
in the maelstrom!
Zaltar, I can't.
I can't.
You...can!
Two specks.
Look!
What do I do?
How do you murder someone
in the Phantom Zone?
She's with some old guy,
it looks like.
Move, huh.
Come on!
Calm down, okay.
Ah. This is what I want.
The Salian Fireballs.
Page 321. Chapter 6.
Whoa!
What is that?
Watch out!
"Power of Rainmaking". No!
"How to separate
husband and wife."
No, not now.
Not now!
Well, you better find something
fast, like an atom bomb.
I found it.
"Summoning...the demon storm."
Hurry...go_
Higher girl, higher.
- Come with me!
- I am with you!
On, girl.
I am with you.
Zaltar!
Oh, thank God.
You've had your fun, Selena.
The game is finished.
Hardly.
One false step, bluebird.
And even if you don't,
your friends will get the point.
Hey: "C!
I don't like this.
Don't worry, Lucy.
Don't worry.
I wouldn't
if I were you.
Well, you're not me.
- Oh!
- Ah!
Quick, get out 0f the way.
Into the alcove over there.
- Come on, out.
- Hurry, Jimmy. Hurry.
The Omegahedron, Selena.
I want it.
Well, then, Supergirl.
You shall have it.
Ah!
Supergirl, above you.
Look out!
Ah!
I think I'll be going.
If you'll excuse me.
That's what I said.
I'm staying, I'm staying.
You have no friends, Selena.
You treat everyone as if
they were put on this earth
to serve you.
More or less,
I think they were.
You included.
Power of shadow.
Appear!
Power of shadow...
...destroy her!
Ah!
Oh!
L...can't.
I can't!
You can!
On, girl.
Yes!
Confront her with it!
It's the only way!
Q-oh!
No, no, no!
Argh!
Oh!
I have to go.
I have to return this
to where it belongs.
And I must
ask you all something.
It's alright, Supergirl.
We never saw you.
We never even
heard of you.
Thank you.
(Supergirh
Ethan, Linda, she...
Well, she had to leave
in a hurry, but she...
You don't have to
say a word.
I know.
I'll explain
about Linda.
Thank you, Ethan.
Take care of
yourself, kiddo.
Wow!
That was some kiss.
Goodbye, Linda.