I guess I should be freezing, but I'm not.
Good. Come on, let me show you.
You see? You only smell strong.
Baby!
It's only because I didn't want to
lose my place in the orchestra.
The circus is in town!
Hey, sweet thing!
Set them buns down here!
Let's just hold hands.
Let me know if this tickles.
Your right front tire is flat, Duane.
Sheriff, what happened?
Willie...
I think my arm's broke.
Girl or no girl...
...you're going to spit teeth! Get up!
What the sam hill?
Is that you, Boog?
All right.
Get 'em up, keep 'em up!
These humans are beginning to bore me.
- Please, Mister!
- He's a general.
Mr. General! Please let my daddy down!
You okay, Jody?
When my father died...
...this is my Earth father, I mean...
...I found this crystal.
This is kind of hard to explain,
but you see...
...it called to me.
Yeah. And it brought me here.
It helped me to build this place.
Actually it built it, really.
That's when I found out who I really was...
...and what I had to do.
So what do you think? You like it?
Like it?
It's incredible!
I mean, not that it couldn't use
a woman's touch...
...especially around dinner time.
Dinner. I'm sorry.
I don't usually do too much about...
Listen, tonight, sky's the limit.
Anything you want.
I'm home!
Should we eat?
- Sure.
- Great.
Good morning, America.
This is East Houston, Idaho...
...until yesterday,
another middle American town...
...that middle America had forgotten.
But today the population,
exaggerated reports put it at 123...
...has increased by three.
And these three new arrivals
bring destruction in their wake.
As I look west into East Houston
this morning...
...I see a town gripped with...
...fear.
Who's the big guy?
Okay, yeah, we've got a P. O...
No.
We've got a slight crack in that diode.
- Come in on him if you can.
- Try to wiggle it.
Who else is seeing this?
With this satellite link up,
just about everybody. The whole planet.
- The whole planet Houston?
- Earth.
The whole planet Earth.
Get over to the commentator.
You may continue.
As the extraordinary story continues...
As this extraordinary story...
If the whole planet is watching, can't we
show them something more interesting?
Throw down your arms and surrender!
This is an order!
General Zod does not take orders.
He gives them.
You all right, buddy?
He was right in the line of fire
and nothing happened to him!
I haven't seen the likes of this
since Superman.
Yes. The Newsbeat control room
has just informed me...
... that a fleet of helicopter gun ships
is on it's way...
- Mr. President, can't we...
- I'm afraid there's nothing anybody can do.
They have such powers,
nothing can stop them.
Where's Superman? Where is he?
Why doesn't he do something?
General Smythson has informed us
that nuclear weapon strikes...
...have been ruled out because of
the danger to the civilian population.
Starting firing run now.
Standby, rockets.
Fire one.
Fire again.
The rockets didn't have any effect.
Look, they need machines to fly!
What bravery!
Be nice to them, my dear.
Blow them a kiss.
We're out of control. I don't understand.
We're coming in... coming down...
can't control it!
We're coming down!
I win.
I always win.
Is there no one on this planet
to even challenge me?
That was good.
I thought we might...
...abandon the orange juice for once.
- Cheers!
Must be tough being Clark Kent, isn't it?
No.
I really like it sometimes.
Even though I do make a fool of myself.
You know, if it weren't for him...
...I never would have met you.
But... he is you.
It's kind of confusing.
Not to me, it isn't.
For the first time in my life...
...everything's clear.
I'm going to go change into something
more comfortable.
Come forward.
Your general wishes to speak.
I am General Zod.
Your ruler.
Yes, today begins a new order!
Your lands, your possessions,
your very lives...
...will gladly be given
in tribute to me, General Zod!
In return for your obedience...
...you will enjoy my generous protection.
In other words, you will be allowed to live.
So you are a general...
And who is your superior?
- I answer only to the president.
- And he will answer to me...
...or all of his cities
will end up like this one!
Your father and I have tried to anticipate
your every question, Kal-El.
This is the one we hoped
you would not ask.
But I have to, because...
she's everything I want in life.
And she, the one you have chosen...
... she feels as much for you?
Yes.
Then if this is what you wish...
... if you intend to live your life
with a mortal...
... you must live as a mortal.
You must become one of them.
This crystal chamber has harnessed
the rays of the red sun of Krypton.
Once exposed to these rays, all...
... your great powers on Earth
will disappear forever.
But consider...
... once it is done, there is no return.
You will become an ordinary man.
You will feel like an ordinary man.
You can be hurt like an ordinary man.
My son, are you sure?
Mother...
...I love her.
You did all that for me?
I don't know what to say.
Just say you love me.
Thousands of hours to create,
and they defaced it in seconds.
Imagine what they'll do to the world
if we resist.
The whole place is going to fall!
Watch it!
You are the one they call President?
I am.
I see you are practiced
in worshipping things that fly.
Good.
Rise before Zod.
Now, kneel before Zod.
You are not the President.
No one who leads so many
could possibly kneel so quickly.
I am the man they are protecting.
I am the President.
I'll kneel before you if it will save lives.
It will. Starting with your own.
What I do now,
I do for the sake of the people of the world.
But there is one man here on Earth
who will never kneel before you.
Who is this imbecile? Where is he?
I wish I knew.
God.
Zod.
You're awfully quiet over there.
I'm supposed to be the shy one.
Yeah, I was just thinking...
...I can't believe
what you've given up for me.
Are you kidding?
I didn't do it for you, Lois, I did it for us.
See, I told you there'd be
a hot dog place somewhere.
Okay. It sure takes longer
when you can't fly.
Hurry up.
- Come on.
- Okay.
My back's stiff.
Come on, it's my treat.
Oh, boy, it's Mr. Wonderful.
Thank you.
- Do you have a men's room?
- Right in the corner.
- Want to sit down?
- Yeah.
What would you folks like?
I'd like a cheeseburger
with everything on it and a Coke...
...and an order of fries
and a side salad, please.
For you, sir?
- I'll think about it when I get back.
- Right.
- Steak and eggs, over easy, coffee.
- My Coke, please.
Coming up.
Sorry, that seat's taken.
It is now, sweetheart.
Can I buy you something to eat?
No, thank you.
Excuse me.
I think you're sitting in my seat.
Your seat's in there, four-eyes.
I think, perhaps somebody
ought to teach you some manners, sir.
Yeah? Let me know when he comes in.
- Look, we can just...
- Honey...
Excuse me, sir,
would you care to step outside?
I said, excuse me, sir,
Now listen, your steak's coming right up.
Keep it on the flame,
this is just a minute steak.
After you.
You all right?
He's going to be fine, just give me that.
Blood. It's my blood.
I think...
...maybe we ought to hire a bodyguard
from now on.
I don't want a bodyguard.
I want the man I fell in love with.
I know that.
I wish he were here.
Boy, you just don't have enough sense
to stay down do you?
I don't like your meat, anyway.
Oh, God.
Can you get up?
- It's all right. I got you.
- Go slow.
Try and get up in that chair.
- Sit down.
- I'm all right.
He's all right. Just relax.
We'll have some fresh coffee.
I'll turn the box on.
We interrupt this program
for an urgent message...
... from the President of the United States.
This is your President.
On behalf of my country and in the name
of the other leaders of the world...
... with whom I have today consulted...
... I hereby abdicate...
... all authority
and control over this planet...
... to General Zod.
Only by strict compliance
with all his directions...
... will the lives
of innocent millions be spared.
Superman, can you hear me?
- Superman, where...
- Who is this Superman?
You'll find out! And when you do...
Come to me, Superman! If you dare!
I defy you!
Come! Come and kneel before Zod!
- Here? When?
- When?
Where have you been?
On a desert island?
I have to go back.
You can't go back.
- There's no way, now.
- I have to.
I've got to try, damn it!
I've got to try something. Anything!
It's not your fault.
You didn't know this was going to happen.
They knew.
I heard them.
I just didn't listen.
Hey, come on!
Father?
Mother?
I really wish you could hear me.
Because I need you.
See, I...
...I...
I failed.
Father!
You're master of all you survey.
And so I was yesterday.
And the day before.
Hello, there.
Lex Luthor.
You may know the name.
The greatest criminal mind on Earth.
I told you this was a puny planet.
Wait, just a moment.
Wait until you get to know me better,
will you, please?
Wait, I can give you anything you want.
I can give you the brass ring,
the unlimited freedom to maim...
...kill, destroy.
Plus, Lex Luthor's keen mind.
Lex Luthor's savvy.
Lex Luthor's career guidance.
Lex Luthor's School of Better...
We have all of this without you.
You cannot bargain
with what you don't have.
Magnificent One.
What I am bargaining with
is what you do not have.
The son of Jor-El.
The son of Jor-El? On this planet?
Possibly you know him better
by his nom de voyage, or his...
...name he travels under.
Superman.
So, this is Superman.
- How do you know of Jor-El?
- My Fullness...
...as I explained to you before...
I'm the best there is.
Revenge! We will kill the son of our jailer.
- Revenge!
- Revenge! Now we're cooking!
- He flies?
- Constantly.
- He has powers as we do?
- Certainly. But...
Magnificent One, he's just one...
...where you are three.
Or four if you count him twice.
We will bring him to his knees.
Wait!
First, you must find him.
And Lex baby is the only one
who knows where he is.
What... do you want?
Well, General...
The world is a big place.
Thank goodness...
...my needs are small.
As it turns out,
I have this affinity for beachfront property.
What do you want?
Australia.
I can't understand it!
Where is he? He shows up every time
a cat gets stuck in a tree...
...and now he's decided to pull
a disappearing act?
- We haven't figured out his game plan.
- Game plan!
It's fourth down, the two-minute warning
has sounded and the ball is in our territory.
How brilliant do you have to be? I mean...
Superman's got something up his sleeve,
that's for sure.
- We haven't figured it out. Right?
- He'll be here!
If it's at all possible, he'll be here.
See?
And she knows his plays
better than anybody.
Better than anybody.
Maybe he hasn't heard about it yet.
Sounds like an earthquake.
Quick, take a picture!
You all right, chief?
Even with accumulated knowledge when'll
these dummies learn to use a doorknob?
Hi!
You should see the White House,
months of cleaning.
You promised me the son of Jor-El.
Yes, your Grace.
But...
...what I've given you
is the next best thing.
Hold on to that little lady...
...and he'll be along.
They have this relationship.
She does all his public relations
and he gives her every exclusive.
They're the best of friends.
Know what I mean?
What an undemanding male
this Superman must be.
You could use a tuck here and there.
Wait!
- I'm sorry!
- She lives for now.
Kill the rest...
...starting with him.
Wait. Wait.
Remember the White House?
The Oval Room?
We had a few laughs, right?
General...
...would you care to step outside?
Superman!
Superman, thank God.
I mean, get him!
Come to me, Son of Jor-El!
Kneel before Zod!
Watch out. You all right?
Wait there.
Son of Jor-El!
We were beginning to think
you were a coward!
I'm not a coward.
Let him prove it!
Then die as you deserve to!
Come on, get him!
This is going to be good!
Take him. He's yours.
Come on! Kill him!
Superman...
The big one's just as strong as Superman!
Hold him.
Home run!
This "super" man is nothing of the kind.
I've discovered his weakness.
He cares.
He actually cares for these Earth people.
- Like pets?
- I suppose so.
Sentimental idiot.
He's caged Non.
I'll draw his fire.
With some of my own.
Get out of here! The rig's going to blow!
Superman, help us!
I never thought this thing
would go the distance.
You people, get back.
Here, take the end of this.
No. Don't do it!
The people!
Where's you wife, sir?
I got her. Don't worry.
He's dead.
Superman is dead.
They killed Superman.
Let's get them!
Come on, let's go!
Forgot your change!
Wait a minute!
I'm holding it, I'm holding it!
I can't see what's happening!
- My hair!
- What about mine?
Hold on!
He's alive!
Come back, please!
So...
...he is a coward after all.
Come back, Superman!
- Don't leave us!
- We can't handle it without you.
- It's not our fault.
- He chickened out.
Phony!
Superman didn't even do nothing!
Come on, let's go!
Get away from here!
Our victory is complete!
The son of Jor-El has fled.
Superman fled?
I don't believe you.
- The next time we will kill him!
- The next time?
The next time?
What am I going to do with you people?
I held up my end, I delivered the Blue Boy.
What do I get from my triple threat?
"Bow, yield, kneel," that kind of stuff
closes out a town.
Why do you say this to me
when you know I will kill you for it?
Kill me? Lex Luthor?
Extinguish the greatest
criminal flame of our age?
- Eradicate the only man on earth with...
- Kill him!
Superman's address?
Come!
The three of us will crush...
...the son of our jailer.
Why not increase his handicap?
Since he cares so much
for these Earth creatures...
...let us take his favorite.
Ever heard of parachutes?
Another small step for mankind.
Scruffy.
So morbid.
A sentimental replica
of a planet long since vanished.
- No style at all.
- I expect...
...better manners from my guests.
We must combine our strength.
Fools!
Take him!
We played this game at school.
Never was very good at it.
Superman, I knew that you'd...
Wrong again!
No, no!
Release the General...
...or we'll tear her apart.
Superman, no!
Superman, don't!
All right!
Did you really think
we would give up our advantage?
Now...
...the son of Jor-El will be my slave.
Forever.
If not,
the millions of earthlings you protect...
...will pay for your defiance.
Destroy this place.
- Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
- We have no more use for this one.
Kill him.
Me?
You came to me with nothing,
I gave you Superman.
Silence!
Well, look...
Watch it. Don't touch me!
Guy's a clod.
Promises were made, gifts exchanged.
I got to hand it to you.
You always told the truth.
A guy always knew
where he stood with you.
Try to get them all
into this molecule chamber.
It takes away their powers, see,
and turns them into ordinary...
...human beings. Now, if you could...
Don't go in there, it's a trap!
You poisonous snake!
That's a molecule chamber.
It makes people like you
into people like me.
You've done well.
The crystal there activates the mechanism.
Lex Luthor, ruler of Australia.
Activate the machine!
Thank you.
With your permission.
And now...
...finally.
Take my hand...
...and swear eternal loyalty to Zod.
He switched it!
He did it to them!
I mean the lights were on out here...
...while he was safe in there!
You know, something?
You're a real pain in the neck!
Are you all right?
I knew you'd double-cross me.
A lying, weasel like you couldn't resist.
Are you kidding?
I was with you all the time.
That was beautiful.
Did you see the way they fell into our trap?
Too late!
Look.
I got a proposition.
Don't stop me
until you've heard this because...
...I know I owe you one,
but we're in the north pole, right?
Let's wipe the slate clean.
If you give me a ride back,
I promise to turn over a new leaf...
It looks so beautiful from up here.
I guess I'll never get to fly with you again.
No. Anywhere you want to go.
You don't have to worry.
I'll never tell them who you really are.
I know.
See you later.
Hi.
How did you sleep?
No. I didn't close my eyes all night.
- Look...
- I understand.
I sat up all night listening to
the voices of reason.
You know how vile it is to hear
the first bird of the morning...
...when you've been crying all night?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I guess it's sort of like being
married to a doctor, you know.
The doctor's awakened at night...
...and the wife has to cope with the fact
that he's gone.
I guess I'm just too selfish.
No. You're not selfish at all.
I am selfish, when it comes to you.
I am selfish.
I'm jealous of the whole world.
It may not be easy for you
to hear this now, but someday you'll...
Don't tell me that I'll meet somebody.
You're kind of a tough act to follow,
you know?
I'm going to be fine,
you don't have to worry about me.
I like worrying about you.
Would you stop?
Don't you know that this is killing me?
Do you know what it's like
to have you come in here every morning...
...and not be able to talk to you?
Not be able to show
I have any feelings for you?
Not be able to tell anyone
that I know who you are.
I don't even know what to call you.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know. Say that you love me.
Gee, are you okay? What happened?
- You all right?
- I just got so dizzy.
That's what happens
when I don't have my orange juice.
- I'm fine.
- Breathe.
- I'm breathing, for heaven's sake.
- Good for you. Good.
- God.
- Just drink.
- Okay.
- Just sip it. Sip it. Sip it.
I'm fine.
What was I talking about before?
If I know you,
it was probably about Superman.
Him again?
You've got to stop being threatened
every time the guy's name's mentioned.
I mean, nobody expects you to be
anything but what you are.
I'll try to remember that.
You better remember that.
I appreciate you.
- You do?
- Sure.
Especially if you get me a hamburger.
A hamburger. At 9:00 a. M?
Yeah, and everything on it, okay?
Everything on it.
- And...
- Orange juice. Freshly squeezed.
Isn't he a nice guy?
Let's see what trouble I can get into today.
What's happening in the world?
Give me another plate of this garbage.
Garbage? That's my number one special!
All right!
Get me some more coffee too, will you?
Gee, that's funny.
I've never seen garbage eat garbage before.
Excuse me, sir.
I think you're sitting in my favorite seat.
Come and get it, four-eyes.
Now cool it!
Take it easy.
I just had this joint fixed.
It cost me a fortune.
God!
This order's to go.
I'm terribly sorry about all the damage, sir.
I've been...
...working out.
Good afternoon, Mr. President.
Sorry I've been away so long.
I won't let you down again.