I know some things too.
Wait a minute. You know what happens
when a planet explodes.
- Debris. Things floating in space.
- So?
So all we have to do is find out
where in heaven Krypton used to be.
Then good ol' Gus contacts
the Vulcan satellite.
OI' Gus has been doing some thinking.
That's why I keep you around.
I've been thinking that I'm not making
enough money for this gig.
Gus, if there's anything I hate...
...it's greed.
Greed? Mr. Ross, just a minute.
Let me tell you something.
I can't ski!
Once Gus contacts
the Vulcan satellite...
... he orders it to search
through space...
... around where Krypton
went bye-bye.
Then the laser probe locks
onto a floating chunk of Kryptonite.
The computer analyzes
the components...
... and the boys at the lab
duplicate the stuff down here.
"Unknown"?
What the hell,
he ain't gonna smoke it.
Mr. White can't be responsible.
Where is he?
Please, Mr. Stokis.
He'll pay for this.
Get out your wallet!
Good morning.
Don't you "good morning" me.
"Old, old relationships
suddenly seem very much the same.
The prettiest girl in the school..."
- is still the prettiest girl
in the school.
- Hello?
- Hello. Oh, hi, Clark.
Lana! Hi, I was just
thinking about you.
Listen, I have a problem with Ricky.
What happened to Ricky?
It's Superman's autograph you got him.
He got carried away...
...and told the kids Superman was
coming on his birthday.
Okay, it was wrong...
...but when Wednesday comes
and Superman doesn't show up...
Lana, in this case I think I can go
ahead and speak for Superman.
I mean, he and I are
pretty close.
You can tell Ricky that Superman
will be there on Wednesday, all right?
Well, he's gonna get the best
home-cooked meal he's had...
...in a long time.
Tell Superman we think
he's wonderful.
All right.
- But, Clark...
- Yeah?
...you're the best.
And I'll take it to
the Supreme Court if I have to.
But it wasn't our fault.
It was an act of God.
In a church?
Hey!
Here's that compound you ordered.
Can't imagine what you want with it.
But you got it.
What the hell am I afraid for?
I'm from Earth.
I really wasn't expecting all this.
I guess they did get
a little carried away.
Superman, we all know...
...that you're not looking for
honors and awards.
But when we heard that you were
coming to see your pal Ricky...
...we realized that this was
our chance to say thank you.
First, for putting out
the Lake Camooga fire.
And not least, for saving
little Ricky.
So since you already have
the key to our hearts...
...Superman...
...may I present you
with the key to the city.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
As you were.
Now listen up.
I just came in directly...
...from the Pentagon...
...and you better believe there's
a damn good reason that I did.
Because God has given us...
...one of the greatest gifts
in the world:
Chemicals.
Now you people, you like to go sit
in church on Sunday, don't you?
You like to sit and watch
the Super Bowl.
Yeah.
Sit on what?!
You sit on molded, plastic seats!
Molded to your well-fed behinds.
Now, I don't have to tell you
that America leads the world...
...in high-grade plastics.
We cannot afford...
...a chemical-plastics gap.
Now, listen to me.
Do you want...
...our president of the United States
sitting down...
...to write a peace treaty...
...and have his ballpoint pen
bust open...
...and the ink run out all over
his nice, clean pants...
...in front of the world leaders?
No. No.
Now, we all know...
...that last week, half of
this great nation of ours...
...almost bit the bullet...
...if it wasn't for this man here.
And all I can say is,
thank the Lord for Superman.
Superman, you saved our bacon...
...and I'd like to show our gratitude.
This is a small token of our
appreciation...
...to show to you for saving us
from a chemical plant disaster.
Thank you very much, general.
This is very nice. Thank you.
It's very nice.
Unknown. How am I supposed to know
what "unknown" means?
It means unknown. It means
nobody knows what it means.
- Hello, boss?
- Gus?
- Gus Gorman here.
- I know that. How did it go?
You know how they're always trying to
find the secret recipe...
...in that chicken in the bucket?
And nobody seems to know
the ingredient...
...because it's unknown, right?
In the Kryptonite there was an unknown
element and Superman didn't die.
He didn't die.
I ask you to kill Superman...
...and you're telling me you couldn't
even do that one simple thing.
Hello?
He hasn't had an afternoon nap
for years.
This is the biggest day of his life.
I don't know how to thank you.
You did with that wonderful lunch.
Oh, well, I do like to cook.
- You'll take some coffee?
- Yes, please.
- Decaffeinated, of course.
- Right.
Hello? Yes.
What?
Oh, really?
Yeah, he's here.
I'll tell him. Okay, thanks.
Bye-bye.
That was my friend Betty.
There's an accident on the bridge.
A trailer crashed through the rail.
It's hanging off the bridge
and the driver's in the cab.
I'm sorry.
I hate to make you rush off.
Well, there's no rush.
But the bridge...
It's okay.
I always get there on time.
Come on, let's relax a little.
It's unusual, finding a good-looking
girl like you alone like this.
Listen, are you sure you shouldn't
do something about the bridge?
What bridge?
You're right.
I have to get going.
Get him out of there. Come on.
Get him out quick!
Get him away. That thing's gonna go.
Everybody okay?
What can I do to help?
Not much of anything now.
If only you'd gotten here
a minute sooner.
"At a special session
of the General Assembly...
...178 countries voted
to censure Superman...
...with only Colombia abstaining."
I can tell you one thing.
He wasn't so mean and nasty
the other day in Smallville.
In fact, he was so full of niceness...
...I hated laying
that big chunk of...
Kryptonite.
Don't you see? That stuff we ran off
in the lab wasn't a failure after all.
Right after Gus gave it to him,
he started to turn into...
...an ornery, evil, malicious,
selfish...
- A normal person.
- Yes.
And now that Superman is out
of the nice-guy business...
We can get to work on that oil.
And now, the supreme moment,
as the last runner...
... the one given the great honor
of lighting the ceremonial flame...
... runs the last leg of a marathon
that began seven days ago...
... as this torch has been passed
from athlete to athlete...
... for 970 miles...
... across the country.
How can he say that pure categories
have no objective meaning...
...in transcendental logic?
What about synthetic unity?
Hi, honey! Am I in your way?
Stick around, you might
learn something.
Hi, Lorelei.
All the oil tankers in the world
are controlled by computers.
They tell them where to go,
how much oil to pick up...
...and where to deliver it.
Don't they have captains
on these ships?
Yes, but they don't need to.
That's a throwback to some
sentimental, seafaring baloney.
You will command the tankers to sail
toward a 50-mile area...
...in the middle of
the Atlantic Ocean.
And do what?
And do nothing.
Just sit there.
How are all the people
gonna get their oil?
You catch on fast, old buddy.
Every oil pump in America is run by...
- Computers. I know.
- Will you stop interrupting?!
I'm sorry.
You will command the pumps
to stop pumping.
Then I want you to program
one special command...
...into all these systems.
Tell them these orders
are irreversible.
So it would be impossible
for anybody to switch them back.
Can you do this for me, old buddy?
Old pal?
You know, you get your way
all the time.
And it's not right.
I want to know when I get a taste.
I think you've already had
a taste of freedom, haven't you?
Or would you prefer jail?
You can't run that jail number on me.
Because I know I mean more to you
out here doing things for you...
...than sitting in jail
doing nothing for nobody.
I see.
What do you want?
What? A waste basket?
No. These are plans.
Blueprints.
- For what?
- A computer.
- We've already got computers.
- No, not like this.
There's not a computer like this
in the whole world, anyplace.
It doesn't exist.
You see...
...we have to build it.
What will it do?
Anything I tell it.
What will it do for me?
For you? It will do anything you
tell me to tell it to do for you.
Tell me.
First of all, if anyone attacks
this machine or anything...
...the computer counterattacks it.
It finds their witnesses
and wipes them out.
Right, old buddy.
You deal with my oil
and I'll build you your machine.
Okay, I'll do it.
But I'm not so sure about
this irreversible business.
They all kind of went...
What the hell?
That's it. The last tanker.
They're all mine now.
All mine.
Not quite.
What's that in
the upper-middle quadrant?
It's a tanker.
And it's going the wrong way.
Skipper?
There it is again.
"Proceed immediately to...
...latitude 30 north,
longitude 45 west.
There await further orders."
Hell, that's the middle
of the Atlantic.
I'm not taking my ship there
to "await further orders"...
...no matter what that says.
We're supposed to go to Metropolis,
and we're going to Metropolis.
All right.
That's where she is.
Come on, get it up there.
Miss?
Miss, can you hear me?
Listen, we are here to help you.
Don't jump. I repeat, do not jump!
Thought you'd never come.
Don't expect me to save you.
I don't do that anymore.
Don't worry.
I'm long past saving.
Don't let me keep you from anything.
I'm not in a rush.
What did you have in mind?
Lots of things.
Oh, yeah?
If you'll just do me
one little favor first.
What's that?
See, there's this little boat...
...and it's not going where
it's supposed to go and...
Stop all engines!
Hi.
How about a little après-ski?
Champagne?
Take your turn like everybody else!
Stop it!
He's coming over here, Martha.
Don't you do that!
Hit him with your handbag!
Help me! Please, help me.
Somebody's beating up my husband.
- I've gotta call the police.
- Jack, go with her, okay?
The third one today,
and at night it's worse.
Somebody's behind this.
You can't say there's no oil.
You can't say someone's
not getting rich off this.
Someone's always getting rich.
You know who suffers?
The small guy.
The east coast gets the brunt
of the spill.
No, I cannot go out with you tonight.
I'm busy tomorrow night too.
Oh, yeah? Doing what?
I'll think of something. Look...
...I gotta go. Ricky needs me.
Brad, please stop calling me.
I've told you!
Well, you listen to me, huh?
You better start appreciating
ol' Brad.
What else you got in Smallville?
What else have I got in Smallville?
I think I got the right answer.
So do I.
Smallville Airport, what flights
do you have to Metropolis tomorrow?
- Where do I put this?
- Over there.
- Where do you want this?
- Load it up there.
Just leave him alone.
I can't get through.
Something's happening.
Hey, look! Superman's drunk!
I want to see what's happening here.
- Thank you.
- It's a disgrace, that's what.
Nobody's ever gonna trust
that creep again.
He's washed up.
What are you looking at? Huh?
Excuse me. Superman?
It's me, Ricky.
Ricky from Smallville.
Tell them you won't hurt anybody!
He's changed.
No! Maybe he's just sick.
Superman, please get better!
He's not listening to you.
Yes, he is. He can hear me.
He's got super-hearing.
Superman, you're just in a slump!
You'll be great again!
You can do it, Superman!
Superman, you can hear me, can't you?
Superman, you're just in a slump.
You'll be great again.
You can do it, Superman.
He's gone nuts!
Come on!
I can give as good as I get.
Yeah? All right, come on!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
What's the matter, Kent?
Too warm for you, huh?
Come on, chicken! Come and get me.
You've been on my nerves
a long time!
You always wanted to fly, Kent.
Now's your chance.
Skipper!
God, would you look at that!
Miss Lorelei Ambrosia
isn't at home right now.
But if you'd care
to leave a message...
... why not deliver it to her...
... in person?
So you've finally shown
your true colors.
Well, if you're looking for us,
here's where you'll find us.
Do drop in.
This is fun!
Fun? The fun's just starting.
Wait till Superman finds us,
then you'll see some fun.
Wait, you gonna mess with Superman?
Let's go. I want to be ready for him
when he falls into our trap.
I just don't see why you can't
balloon down like the rest of us.
Well...
No way. Uh-uh.
I just don't believe a man can fly.
Watch out, horsy!
Don't, don't, don't.
Just don't try to fly.
Don't try to fly!
Will you get out of my way!
- Hurry! Hurry up!
- I am hurrying.
- I can't see anything.
- Turn on the light.
- Where's the light switch?
- Where do you usually find it?
I don't know.
I guess I'll check the doorway.
God, it's pitch-black in here.
Oh, that's better.
Wow, what a jukebox!
I told you, didn't I?
There. The ultimate computer!
It does everything a computer can do
and 1000 things none of them can!
Let's give it a dry run.
Wait. We've gotta wait for Gus.
Who needs Gus?
- Only he can operate it.
- Like fish, he is!
I know enough about computers
to put a Ph.D. To shame.
Come now, brother dear,
you didn't think...
...I'd let that little man
run the show, did you?
Why don't peons tidy up
when they're done?
Come on, Bubba, it's showtime.
Engage those buttons to
activate the alpha circuit...
...and lock the modular grid.
You! Activate circuits
29 through W-7...
...and start full-power coordinates
on exterior defensive systems.
In other words, push this red button.
How did you know about that?
He's here!
Let's give him
something to worry about.
Now, let's see...
Tracking systems locked.
Let the games begin.
Don't tense up now, honey.
Come on, Bubba,
you're wasting your rockets.
Come on, Superman!
Let him have it, Ross.
Bubba, keep firing.
Keep him occupied
while I get the MX ready.
What the hell is going on?
Keep your rockets coming. He won't
notice the missile till too late!
So much for your catlike reflexes.
Oh, God!
No more. Look, you sit.
Sit, sit!
Help!
Hello!
Get to, jackass!
That's him out of the way.
Sis, how would you like to control
all the world's weapons systems?
Baby!
It's Daddy!
Hey, what are you doing with my baby?
Gus, old buddy, genius.
Come up and join the fun.
He's still coming.
Arm the inner defenses.
All right, the game's over.
Hi, honey.
I don't know you, lady.
But the other night...
I'm sorry, but that wasn't me.
That guy's gone.
And you're next, Webster.
Never underestimate
the power of computers.
How do you like it?
I think it's typical
of people like you, Webster.
Instead of helping others,
you four just help yourselves.
Four...
...of you?
You mean, us? Four? Wait...
Hey, man!
That's only his last name.
He likes to be called "Superman."
See, I'm not with them, Superman.
You could've fooled me.
That's very good.
Let's see how long
he can carry on without any air.
He's still coming!
He's going to get me!
Don't bet on it!
You're hurting him.
- That's Kryptonite!
- Yes.
- This time we got it right!
- You're a genius.
You've invented a machine
that can find anybody's weak spot.
Congratulations, old buddy.
You'll go down in history
as the man who killed Superman!
I'm... No.
Superman!
No!
- Where do you think you're going?
- Never mind.
- Turn the power up.
- Don't you think he's had enough?
Turn it up!
Power! More power!
Seventy-five. Current 7.75.
There's a current level of 7
that is not supposed to be on bar...
Oh, here it is!
What's going on?
I don't know. The power's gone.
Gus must have pulled the plug out.
It worked.
It worked! I got it!
What have you got?
- Give me that screw.
- This screw?
- That screw.
- Never!
What?
Holy!
No! Make it stop!
I can't! It's out of control!
But how?
Where's it getting the power from?
It's feeding itself.
It wants to live!
It's this thing here.
We'll go to the zoo.
I'll do that tomorrow,
and then we'll go on to the...
- What's happening?
- It's okay, Ricky.
Put the lights on!
Stop it! You're killing him!
Stop it!
Hey. Put me down!
Don't leave us alone
in here! Superman!
Oh, I get it.
The coaxial energy shaft is engaging
the grid source factor. Right.
We're through, pugface.
I'm splitting.
Hey, wait a minute!
Girls. Girls, come out of there!
Sis?
Oh, my God.
What is that?
Sis, it's your Bubba!
Help me. Help!
Superman!
Honey!
Honey, I'm stuck here! Help!
What about me?
Look out!
Bubba?
Thank you, brother.
Regular or premium?
She hasn't had a drink in so long,
give her a tankful of the good stuff.
How you doing?
Please don't talk to me.
I'm having enough trouble hanging on.
Okay, we'll go slow.
You're perfectly safe.
I won't argue with you.
Any man who can trick my machine
can do anything.
How did you beat my defenses?
Those defenses are good as long as
it didn't know it's in trouble.
This time it didn't see the danger.
I went in with plain old acid.
It didn't know that when acid gets hot,
it'll eat through anything.
Watch the trees.
I guess it died of acid indigestion.
But what's gonna happen
to Ross and the ladies?
They'll have to see the police.
It's not your problem anymore.
Are we in Metropolis yet?
Nope. I'm just gonna make
a little stop. Right over there.
We're on the ground, Gus.
- You okay, Supe?
- I'm fine.
Excuse me.
Can you guys spare one of these?
- Sure, Superman.
- It is Superman, isn't it?
Are you kidding? Is that?
Didn't you see us fly out of the sky?
We're the only two men who can fly.
"Is it Superman?"
Just right.
Okay, let's go.
I was afraid you'd say that.
I thought I'd take the bus.
Well, suit yourself.
Does your boss have a computer here?
Yeah, he got a little bitty one
about that big.
You tell him he can do a lot worse
than to give Gus Gorman here a job.
Wow, thank you, Supe.
Take care.
I'll see you around.
So long.
Take it easy, man.
Well, you got good references,
so if you want that job...
Nah, this is not for me.
I think I'll take that bus.
Where's the bus station?
Yeah, about 9, 10 miles
over there.
Nine or 10 miles.
Hey. You really flew with him?
Superman?
Have you ever seen Superman before?
Oh, you don't know about me and him?
Me and Superman?
Yeah, we go way back together.
We always, usually, sometimes, we...
Nine or 10 miles?
I think I'll walk.
Yeah, I'll walk.
Clark.
What a nice surprise! Come in.
Hi, Mr. Kent.
- Guess who Mom's having dinner with?
- Who?
Superman!
Yeah, that's what I came to tell you.
Superman said to tell you he's sorry...
...but he's run into a problem
and he can't make dinner with you.
I guess he misses a lot of dinners.
Would you mind settling for me?
Any day.
I'll get my things.
Lana, I was talking
to Superman the other day.
You know, he and I, we talk a lot.
He felt badly about you having
to pawn your diamond ring.
Well, he found...
He found this one just lying around.
He wanted you to have this.
Wow, a ring from Superman!
- It's okay. I got it.
- Sorry.
- Oh, Clark.
- It's okay.
It fits.
It looks really pretty.
Thank you.
Brad.
Son of a bitch.
Kent, I hate you.
I've always hated you.
- You know why?
- No.
- Because you're nice.
- Not really.
And nice guys finish last.
Lois, I've got to hand it to you.
Who else could turn
a vacation into a story...
...that'll blow the lid off
of corruption in the Caribbean?
I knew I was onto something
when that taxi driver kidnapped me.
Lois, you're terrific.
I have to be.
Seems I've got some new competition.
The story that you wrote
on the class reunion?
- I thought it was terrific.
- Thanks.
And fascinating. I liked the part
about the little girl back home.
I'll take you to lunch
and you tell me about it.
I'd love to, but I'm having lunch
with Mr. White's new secretary.
- Hi, Lana.
- Hi, Clark.
Lois, say hello to Lana Lang.
Smallville's newest gift to Metropolis.
Glad to meet you.
I like your writing a lot.
Thank you.
I like your sparkler a lot.
Me too. I couldn't believe it
when Clark gave it to me.
Clark gave it to you?
Mr. White.
Mr. White, look what I've got for you.
People, I am in love
with this machine!
Excuse me, but I have a couple
of errands to run before lunch.
- Go ahead, Mr. White.
- Where's the handle?
There is no handle.
You just push the button.
Giorgio, por favore?
Grazie.