"In the decade of the 1930s
even the great city of Metropolis...
"...was not spared the ravages
of the world-wide depression.
"In the times of fear and confusion...
"...the job of informing the public
was the responsibility...
"...of the Daily Planet.
"A great metropolitan newspaper...
"...whose reputation for clarity and truth
had become a symbol of hope...
"...for the city of Metropolis."
This is no fantasy.
No careless product of wild imagination.
No, my good friends...
...these indictments...
...I've brought you today...
...specific charges listed herein
against the individuals...
...their acts of treason.
Their ultimate aim of sedition.
These...
...are matters of undeniable fact.
I ask you now to pronounce judgment...
...on those accused.
On this...
...this mindless aberration...
...whose only means of expression
are wanton violence and destruction.
On the woman Ursa...
...whose perversions
and unreasoning hatred of all mankind...
...have threatened even the children
of the Planet Krypton.
Finally, General Zod.
Once trusted by this Council...
...charged with maintaining the defense
of the Planet Krypton itself.
Chief Architect of this intended revolution
and author of this insidious plot...
...to establish a new order amongst us...
...with himself as absolute ruler.
You have heard the evidence.
The decision of the Council
will now be heard.
Guilty!
The vote must be unanimous, Jor-El.
It has therefore now become your decision.
You alone will condemn us if you wish...
...and you alone will be held responsible
by me!
Join us!
You have been known to disagree
with the Council before.
Yours could become an important voice
in the new order, second only to my own!
I offer you a chance for greatness, Jor-El!
Take it! Join us!
You will bow down before me, Jor-El.
I swear it!
No matter that it takes an eternity!
You will bow down before me!
Both you and then one day...
...your heirs!
Forgive me, forgive me...
An unpleasant duty
has been masterly performed, Jor-El.
They have received the fate they deserved.
Isolation in the Phantom Zone...
...an eternal living death.
A chance for life, nonetheless.
As opposed to us.
It's suicide.
No, it's worse, it's genocide.
Be warned, Jor-El.
The Council has already evaluated
this outlandish theory of yours.
My friends, you know me
to be neither rash nor impulsive.
I am not given
to wild unsupported statements...
...and I tell you that we must evacuate
this planet immediately.
Jor-El, you are one
of Krypton's greatest scientists.
Yes, but so is Vond-Ah.
I don't question your data.
The facts are undeniable.
It's your conclusions
we find unsupportable.
This planet will explode within 30 days.
If not sooner.
I tell you Krypton
is simply shifting its orbit.
Jor-El...
...be reasonable.
My friend...
...I have never been otherwise.
This madness is yours.
This discussion is terminated.
The decision of the Council is final.
Any attempt by you to create...
...a climate of fear and panic
among the populace...
...must be deemed by us
an act of insurrection.
You would accuse me of insurrection?
Has it now become a crime to cherish life?
You would be banished
to endless imprisonment...
...in the Phantom Zone:
The eternal void...
...which you, yourself discovered.
Will you abide by the Council's decision?
I will remain silent.
Neither I...
...nor my wife, will leave Krypton.
Have you finished?
Nearly.
It's the only answer, Lara.
If he remains here with us...
...he will die as surely as we will.
But why Earth, Jor-El?
They're primitives,
thousands of years behind us.
He will need that advantage to survive.
Their atmosphere will...
...sustain him.
He will defy their gravity.
He will look like one of them.
He won't be one of them.
No.
His dense molecular structure
will make him strong.
He'll be odd. Different.
He'll be fast. Virtually invulnerable.
Isolated. Alone.
He will not be alone.
He will never be alone.
The energy input to Jor-El's quarters
is now in excess.
Our data indicates the loss
is due to a misuse of energy.
Investigate.
And if the investigation proves correct?
He knew the penalty he faced.
He even is a member of this Council.
The law will be upheld.
You will travel far, my little Kal-El.
But we will never leave you.
Even in the face of our death...
...the richness of our lives...
...shall be yours.
All that I have, all that I've learned,
everything I feel...
...all this and more, I...
...I bequeath you, my son.
You will carry me inside you...
...all the days of your life.
You will make my strength your own...
...see my life through your eyes...
...as your life will be seen through mine.
The son becomes the father,
and the father...
...the son.
This is all I...
...all I can send you, Kal-El.
... which Einstein called his theory
of relativity.
Embedded in the crystals before you...
... is the total accumulation of all literature
and scientific fact...
... from dozens of other worlds...
... spanning the 28 known galaxies.
Early Chinese writings point out
the complex relationship between...
By carrying this complex equation
to its ultimate power, my son...
Chief among these powers
will be your sight...
... your strength, your hearing...
... your ability to propel yourself
at almost limitless speed.
The early history of our universe was
a bloody mosaic of interplanetary war.
Each of the six galaxies
which you will pass through...
... contain their own individual law
of space and time.
It is forbidden for you to interfere
with human history.
- What!
- What was that?
Now wouldn't that beat all get out.
Well, you...
Oh, Pa!
Oh, my.
All these years, as happy as we've been...
...how I've prayed the good Lord
would see fit to give us a child.
Honey, will you hand me that rag up there.
You take things easy now.
Remember what Doc Frye said
about that heart of yours.
Now the first thing we've got to do
when we get home is find out...
...who that boy's proper family is.
He hasn't got any.
Not around here, anyway.
Are you thinking
what I think you are thinking?
We could say he's the child of my cousin
in North Dakota...
...and just now orphaned.
Jonathan, he's only a baby.
Martha, now you saw how we found him.
Martha Clark Kent,
are you listening to what I'm saying?
Come on, gang.
That was a great game.
All right.
Come on, hustle. Let's go.
Stack your helmets neatly.
Remember about those uniforms,
cleaned and washed by tomorrow...
...and looking like a football team.
Clark, let's have those clothes washed
and ready for tomorrow's game.
Got to beat Mount Vernon High.
Can you give me a lift?
Lana?
Don't bother with these.
I'll take them in with the other equipment.
- Thank you, Clark.
- Sure.
Listen, a whole bunch of us are going up
to Mary Ellen's.
Play some records.
Would you like to come?
Sure.
Sounds like it could be a lot of fun.
Kent can't make it.
Still got a lot of work to do.
What are you talking about?
I've just finished stacking...
All that?
Oh, Brad!
Hey, come on, Lana.
Let's go.
- He has to clean up.
- 'Bye, Clark.
- 'Bye, Lana.
- Clean this up, Clark.
'Bye, Clark.
See you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
Mommy, I saw a boy out there
run as fast as the train!
Faster even!
Lois Lane,
you have a writer's gift for invention.
- I'll say that for you.
- But...
Lois, please read your book.
No one ever believes me.
Hey, look, there's Clark!
Clark?
How did you get here so fast?
I ran.
Ran, huh?
Told you he was an oddball.
Let's get out of here.
Been showing off a bit, haven't you, Son?
I didn't mean to show off, Pa.
It's just that guys like that Brad,
I just want to tear them apart.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I know I shouldn't.
Yeah, I know you can do
all these amazing things...
...and sometimes you think
that you will just go bust...
...unless you can tell people about it.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
I mean, every time I get the football
I can make a touchdown.
- That's for sure.
- Every time.
Is it showing off when somebody's doing
the things he's capable of doing?
Is a bird showing off when it flies?
No, no. Now, you listen to me.
When you came to us, we thought
people would take you away...
...when they found out
the things that you do.
It worried us a lot.
Then when a man gets older
and he thinks very differently.
And things get very clear.
And there's one thing I do know, Son,
and that is you are here for a reason.
I don't know whose reason,
or whatever the reason is...
...maybe it's because...
I don't know.
But I do know one thing.
It's not to score touchdowns.
Thanks, Dad.
I'll race you to it. Yeah.
You will?
Come on, Papa. Run. Come on. Move.
Go, go. Come on. Hey, Baron.
Jonathan!
Dad.
All those things I can do...
...all those powers...
...and I couldn't even save him.
Clark, get up.
Good morning, Smiley.
Clark, breakfast.
Are you going to sleep all day?
Clark, come on. Get up.
I have to leave.
I knew this time would come.
We both knew it
from the day we found you.
I talked to Ben Hubbard yesterday.
He said that he'd be happy
to help out from now on.
Mother!
I know, Son.
I know.
Do you know where you're headed?
North.
Remember us, Son.
Always remember us.
My son...
... you do not remember me.
I am Jor-El.
I am your father.
By now you will have reached
your eighteenth year...
... as it is measured on Earth.
By that reckoning...
... I will have been dead
for many thousands of your years.
The knowledge...
... that I have of matters,
physical and historical...
... I have given you fully on your voyage
to your new home.
These are important matters to be sure...
... but still matters of mere fact.
There are questions to be asked...
... and it is time for you to do so.
Here, in this...
... this fortress of solitude...
... we shall try to find the answers together.
So, my son...
... speak.
Who am I?
Your name is Kal-El.
You are the only survivor
of the Planet Krypton.
Even though you were raised
as a human, you are not one of them.
You have great powers,
only some of which you have...
... as yet discovered.
Come with me now, my son...
... as we break through the bars
of your earthly confinement.
Traveling through time and space.
Your powers will far exceed
those of mortal men.
It is forbidden for you to interfere
with human history.
Rather let your leadership stir others to.
In the next year,
we shall examine the human heart.
It is more fragile than your own.
As we pass through the flaming turmoil
which is the edge of your own galaxy...
... we will enter the realm
of the red Krypton sun...
... source of your strength
and nourishment...
... and cause of our eventual destruction.
The Planet Krypton, my son...
... your home as it was.
This year we shall examine
the various concepts of immortality...
... and their basis in actual fact.
The total accumulation of all knowledge
spanning the 28 known galaxies...
... is embedded in the crystals
which I have sent along with you.
Study them well, my son.
By the time you return to the confines
of your galaxy...
... twelve of your years will have passed.
For this reason, among others...
... I have chosen Earth for you.
It is now time for you to rejoin
your new world...
... and to serve its collective humanity.
Live as one of them, Kal-El...
... and discover where your strength
and your power are needed.
But always hold in your heart the pride
of your special heritage.
They can be a great people, Kal-El,
they wish to be.
They only lack the light to show the way.
For this reason, above all,
their capacity for good...
... I have sent them you...
... my only son.
Okay, this is it, mac, the Daily Planet.
Fresh fruit!
Hey, how about a tomato, lady?
Hey, fresh fruit and vegetables.
Smile.
How many "T's" in "bloodletting"?
Two.
What are you writing?
An ode to spring.
How do you spell "massacre"?
M-a-s-s-a-c-r-e.
Thanks.
Golly, how come you get
all the great stories?
A good reporter doesn't get great stories.
A good reporter makes them great.
Chief, here's that story on the murder case.
The way I see it, it's a headline
on the front page with my picture...
There's only one "P" in "rapist."
Lois Lane, say hello to Clark Kent.
Hello, Miss Lane, how are...
How are you doing?
Jimmy Olsen, photographer.
Hi. Clark Kent. Nice to meet you.
It's got everything:
Sex, violence, the ethnic angle.
So does a lady wrestler
with a foreign accent.
- Kent, can you open this?
- Sure, Mr. White.
This could be the basis
for a series of articles:
"Making Sense of Senseless Killings"
by Lois Lane.
We get psychologists,
sociologists, interviews...
Lois, you're pushing a bunch
of rinky-dink tabloid garbage.
The Daily Planet has a tradition...
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to shake it up like that.
Of course not, Lois.
Why would any one want to make
a total stranger look like a fool?
I'll take that.
Thanks. I'm sorry, Mr. White.
Why do I pay you $40 a week when
I should have you arrested for loitering?
- Go get Mr... a towel.
- Kent.
- Move, kid, move.
- Right, Chief.
- Make mine black, no sugar.
And don't call me sugar.
Right... Sugar.
Chief wants coffee, no sugar.
I'll take tea with lemon.
Lois, why don't you take Kent out
to meet everybody, huh?
Just introduce him around.
He's starting on the paper today.
I'm giving him the City beat.
Chief!
That's my beat!
Lois, Clark Kent may seem like
just a mild-mannered reporter...
...but not only does he know how to treat
his Chief with the proper respect...
...not only does he have a snappy,
punchy prose style...
...but he is, in my 40 years in this business,
the fastest typist I have ever seen.
That's great.
Here, you forgot my article.
Excuse me, Mr. White. I was wondering...
...if you could arrange for half my salary...
...to be sent to this address
on a weekly basis.
Your bookie, right?
My what?
Don't tell me!
He sends a check every week
to his sweet, gray-haired mother.
Actually, she's silver-haired.
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you very much, Mr. White.
Well?
Any more at home like you?
Not really, no.
I didn't think so.
Well, get yourself a desk over here.
Over here?
Here, there's some paper
and a file right there.
Sorry.
- Hi, Bill Breesen.
- Hi, Clark Kent.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome aboard.
- Here's your towel, Mr. Clark.
- Kent.
- What?
- Clark Kent.
- Jimmy Olsen.
- I met this really great guy, you know.
- Hey, fabulous.
We had this fabulous weekend.
I met him at this dude ranch.
I haven't been since I was seven.
- I got to mail these letters.
- Good luck tonight.
- Hi, Clark.
- Hi, Lois.
How did you like your first day on the job?
The hours were sort of longer
than I expected...
...but on the whole, meeting you
and Jimmy Olsen and Mr. White...
Gosh, on a whole, I'd say it's been swell.
- "Swell"?
- Yup.
You know, Clark...
...there are very few people left
in the world...
...who feel comfortable saying that word.
- What word?
- Swell.
Really? I always thought
it was kind of natural.
- Sorry.
- Clark.
- Sorry, Lois.
- Hi, Rex.
- Did you see anything good today?
- Not until you came along.
Rex, this is...
- Clark Kent. How do...
- See you around.
Lois?
Hey, where you going?
Can I help you with your coat?
- Thanks. Can you get that?
- Sure.
Did you like Mr. White?
He was a nice guy
and Jimmy was fantastic.
Come here. Come on.
Get in here, hurry up. Come on.
- We'd better get out of here.
- We'd better do what he says, Lois.
Come on, get in here, quick.
Don't, don't do anything.
It's all right, I'm coming.
We're coming.
Excuse me.
- Here?
- Yeah, yeah.
Don't point that at me, sir.
You could hurt somebody with that.
Okay, okay. Hold it there.
Just a minute.
Now I realize that...
...times are tough for some these days,
but this isn't the answer.
You can't solve society's problems
with a gun.
You know, buddy, you're right.
- I'm going to turn over a new leaf.
- Good for you, sir. That's the spirit.
He doesn't really want to hurt anyone.
Right after I rip off this lady's purse.
Of course!
Now come on, lady, hand it over.
Lois, I think you'd better...
Lois! What are you doing?
Are you all right?
What happened?
- Golly, I guess I must have fainted.
- Fainted?
- You fainted!
- I'm sorry.
Really, Lois,
supposing that man had shot you?
Is it worth risking your life over $10...
...two credit cards,
a hairbrush and a lipstick?
- How did you know that?
- Know what?
You described the exact contents
of my purse.
Wild guess.
Taxi!
- Hey!
- Hi, Otis.
So, what's happening, partner?
Look what we got.
Let's take him.
Wait a minute.
Maybe he'll lead us to the big man himself.
Lex Luthor?
You got it, Aramus.
We'll make Captain by midnight.
Hey, what do you read?
XK-101 rocket to be used.
- Hey, Matt.
- Hi, Otis.
Just getting a Daily Planet here.
Okay. All right.
See, I'm paying him,
and I got a pretzel, too.
Thanks, Otis.
How many bags, Shutzy?
This is Metropolis 46. We're on foot.
Over and out.
Let's go.
Your attention, please.
The Metropolis Flyer is now ready
for departure...
... on the upper level. Track 6.
He's going down on a train platform.
I'm going after him.
Okay, I'll call for backup.
Be careful now, will you?
All right, Aramus. All right.
Now boarding on the lower level...
Now 10 minutes, air-conditioned cars,
Mount Vernon, Poughkeepsie...
Board now. All aboard.
Metropolis Transportation
to Buffalo, Syracuse...
Smoking cars are forward,
move along now.
Luggage at the top.
Smoking cars are forward.
All aboard, boarding.
Aramus, Aramus, make it Track 22.
I've seen him and I'm right on him.
Lower level, Track 22.
So that's it!
It's amazing that brain can generate
enough power to keep those legs moving.
Harry...
Harry, where are you? Harry?
Sick!
Sick, you're really sick!
I'm sick, Ms. Teschmacher?
Sick when we're days
from executing the crime of the century?
No, no, no. Step away from that, please.
How do you choose to congratulate
the greatest criminal mind of our time?
Do you tell me that I'm brilliant?
Oh, no, that would be too obvious,
I grant you.
Charismatic?
Fiendishly gifted?
Try twisted!
Get away from that, get away!
Tell me, Lex.
Why do so many people have to die
for the crime of the century?
Why? You ask why?
Why does the phone always ring
when you're in the bathtub?
Why is the most brilliantly diabolical leader
of our time...
...surrounding himself
with total nincompoops?
I'm back, Mr. Luthor.
I was just talking about you.
You were followed again.
In spite of those cat-like reflexes.
Mr. Luthor, I'm sorry.
Is that the newspaper
I asked you to get me?
Yes.
Then why am I not reading it?
Because I haven't given it to you yet?
Right.
At last it's official.
Thanks to the help of the US Government...
...we are about to be involved in
the greatest real-estate swindle of all time.
Lex, what is this...
...obsession with real estate?
All the time, "land, land, land."
When I was 6 years old,
my father said to me...
"Get out!"
Before that, he said,
"Son, stocks may rise and fall...
"...utilities and transportation systems
may collapse...
"...people are no damn good,
but they'll always need land...
"...they'll pay through the nose to get it."
- "Remember," my father said...
- "Land."
It's a pity that he didn't see...
...from such humble beginnings
how I've created this empire.
An empire. This?
How many girls do you know
have a Park Avenue address like this?
Park Avenue address, 200 feet below?
Do you realize
what people are shelling out up there...
...for a few miserable rooms
off a common elevator.
What more could anyone ask?
Get this Loch Ness update
right into composing.
Yeah. No, that's it, Roth.
Put it to bed. Right.
- Why are you standing here for?
- I'm not.
- I wasn't going to say it.
- Go.
The sex maniac profile.
Right. Nine to five it's
a Pulitzer Prize winner. What do you bet?
There's no "Z" in "brassiere."
Nice job on that union scandal, Kent.
Gosh, thanks, Mr. White.
Hi, Clark. Good night.
- Here, let me carry that for you.
- Thanks a lot.
Lois, have you got a minute?
Excuse me, please.
And these two go to the addresses
on the envelope, okay?
I was wondering
if you'd have dinner with me?
I'm sorry, I'm booked.
Air Force One is landing at the airport.
This kid'll be there to make sure...
...you-know-who answers the questions
he would rather duck.
Don't you ever let up?
What for? I mean I've seen
how the other half lives.
My sister, for instance.
Three kids, two cats, and one mortgage.
I would go bananas in a week.
- Can I take you to the airport?
- Not unless you can fly.
"Ladies." I have to change, thank you.
Goodbye.
Maybe we could...
- Would you mail that for me? Thanks.
- Sure.
Good night.
Going down, please, going down.
Going down?
Going up. Up, up.
Good night.
Daily Planet, Copter One. This is ground.
Planet One, go ahead.
Miss Lane is here for a ride to the airport
to meet Air Force One. It's a hurry flight.
We're on our way over the river.
Have one aboard for transfer. Over.
Roger, Planet One. You're clear to land.
Wind 0-2-0-1-5. Altimeter 2-9-8-9.
Roger, Over and out.
A malfunction, can't get lift off.
- You've hooked a cable.
- What's happening?
Set it down.
My God, we've lost motor control.
I can't hold it.
He's lost it.
Wake up.
Help!
Step back, folks.
Get back. Move over
to the other side of the street.
Bring the canvas here. Get it up there.
There's helicopter up there.
Help me.
All right, folks. Let's move back.
Let these firemen get in here.
Help me!
Hold it. Get back.
Get off the street, folks.
All right, get along there.
Get away from the side of the building.
Hold these crowds back. Move.
Help!
Say, Jim...
Excuse me.
That's a bad outfit.
Okay, move these people.
Oh, my God! Look up there.
What the hell's that?
Easy, miss. I've got you.
You've got me? Who's got you?
I can't believe it, I just cannot believe it.
He got her.
Gentlemen, this man needs help.
I hope this little incident
hasn't put you off flying, miss.
Statistically speaking, of course,
it's still the safest way to travel.
Right.
Wait!
Who are you?
A friend.
'Bye.
Something wrong with the elevator?
Going down?
Officer.
Good evening, Officer Mooney.
They say confession is good for the soul.
I'd listen...