[theme music playing]
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
[door opens]
[Hyun-su] Today was the day
I had planned on killing myself.
But today, I'm leaving this place
so I can survive.
[Dr. Lim] Monster humans are creatures
who have been denied
the beautiful relief of death.
I'm sure you'll do well,
unlike the others.
I get the feeling we're about to witness
the birth of a very special MH, you see.
[Hyun-su] Can you use me
to develop a vaccine or a cure?
[Dr. Lim] You might end up dead though.
Are you okay with that?
[Sang-wook]
Nothing matters anymore at this point.
Just accept what you are,
nothing but a monster.
Yeah.
I'm a monster.
- [squelches]
- [groans]
[intense music playing]
Even when you bring out your very best,
you're still just a failure.
You can't save anyone, even yourself.
[Hyun-su]
There was nothing more I could do.
[electric buzzing]
I wanted... to become a better person.
[other Hyun-su]
Are you just gonna die a miserable death?
Is that what you really want?
[pensive choral music playing]
That's all lies.
Like I told you,
I can help you out.
I can do it all. I can give you...
everything you've ever wanted.
All right, dinner is served.
Oh, yum, yum, yum, yum.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
- [Su-a] How does it smell?
- [sniffs, chuckles]
[Hyun-su's dad] Try the broth first.
Hyun-su, you go ahead. Try it. Hmm?
- [chuckles]
- Here, this one's for Hyun-su.
[Hyun-su]
I know that none of this is real.
But why does that even matter
when you can finally be happy?
You'll live in a kind of dream world
while I hold down the fort
in this hellish reality.
No.
[sighs]
You can be so stubborn.
[tuts]
[crackling]
[groans]
[menacing orchestral music playing]
[infant crying]
I missed you!
[Kid] "You were a mistake.
You're a monster."
I gave birth to you,
why would you be a monster?
[Yi-kyung] Did you use those hands
to turn them into monsters?
[Hyun-su] Yi-kyung!
[Hyun-su] Yi-kyung is very sick.
She could die any moment.
[Kid] Mom's not gonna die,
so stop crying, please.
[Eun-yu] How could she turn so suddenly?
She wasn't showing any symptoms.
Her daughter did this to her.
Monsterization is uncontrollable
by humans.
- [screaming]
- [glass shattering]
[shaky breathing]
[Hyun-su] You don't lose your humanity
when you become a monster.
They're still a human deep within.
I can see it all.
I can understand what people
who turn into monsters are after.
But Yi-kyung is also miserable
on that side.
I have to stop her.
It has to be me.
You don't have to do anything.
Why am I still alive?
I'd be better off just becoming a monster.
[sobs, breathes shakily]
[pensive music playing]
[suspenseful music rises]
Cha Hyun-su.
[nervous breath]
[loud rumbling]
Are you going to hit me with that?
Bring him back.
Bring Cha Hyun-su back now.
He's hurt, you know.
Let him rest a bit.
I only came to help him
because the pain was killing him.
So don't be like that.
[flesh squelching]
[heavy breathing]
This is all your people's fault, you know.
I thought Hyun-su is in control?
I'm also Cha Hyun-su.
You're a monster. I mean the real Hyun-su.
We agreed to help each other out.
I can't exactly have Cha Hyun-su
dying on me, you know?
Why don't you leave him be and get lost?
You mean it?
Sure that's what you want?
Are you sure you'd be okay with just...
a weak Cha Hyun-su?
[shaky breathing]
Yes.
[tense music playing]
What are you doing?
Don't know.
What should we do?
What do you want?
[annoyed scream]
God, I can't deal with this crazy asshole.
[sighs]
It's unreal, seriously.
[heavy breathing]
Cha Hyun-su.
[sighs]
[Sang-wook] I knew you would come back.
That is,
if you hadn't been slain somewhere.
For you too, this place meant everything.
I don't think we've met before.
Oh, you know how it is.
Being a famous figure,
I simply can't recognize
everyone who recognizes me.
Were you a researcher?
I'm not all that interested in people,
so I don't like them, you see.
You showed a lot of interest in me
despite what you say.
Yeah.
So...
who exactly are you?
Your very first...
[gasps]
...test subject.
- [dramatic music playing]
- [heavy breathing]
[cracking]
[splashing]
[panting]
I really wanted to show you this.
[Sang-wook] What is it you called me?
MH-1, right?
Remember now?
I'm your dear friend, Nam Sang-won.
[gasps]
[dramatic music continues]
I'm glad we meet again.
I was worried, you know...
that you might be dead.
[breathes heavily]
You're saying you're Nam Sang-won?
You're putting a lot of effort
into this bullshit.
Se-yeon.
[breathing heavily]
This is your work.
[ECG beeping]
SANG-WON
Sang-won...
- [phone ringing]
- [fence rattling]
Ah...
[Dr. Lim] Oh no, Sang-won.
Seo Yi-kyung is dead.
[muffled grunt]
[Sang-wook]
Nam Sang-won's greatest desire.
He wanted to escape
those damned experiments,
- and this is the result.
- [muffled scream]
[screams]
[groans]
I was freed by the pain
you inflicted on me.
And you succeeded
in extracting the monster.
Congrats.
So is this the part where I die?
Why would you?
I'm actually thankful for you.
I was born from monsterization.
But I wasn't complete...
until I met you.
[tense violin music playing]
But why?
Why are you still here, in this place,
after what you've been through?
[music swells, fades]
Follow me.
[ominous music playing]
[music swells]
[Sang-wook] Been a while, huh?
Say hello, you two.
MH-3?
My name is Hwang Chi-seong.
Like I said, MH-3.
That's what I know you as, huh?
Names don't really matter,
do they, Number Three?
[Chi-seong] Call me that if you want.
After all,
it'll only make things that much easier.
In just a moment,
I'm gonna do some
particularly horrible things
- to these friends of yours.
- [doors open]
- [thwacks]
- [hooded man grunts]
[laughs]
[Chi-seong] Do you remember the old days?
Those experiments you liked to do?
Well, I'd like to do one of my own.
[panting]
[switches clicking]
[menacing music playing]
Yong... Yong-seok...
[shouts]
Yong-seok!
Sergeant Kim?
[panting]
Yong-seok!
Sergeant Kim!
[angry breathing]
[Ja-yeong] Choose.
You can take one of the three with you.
We keep our promises around here.
What's your objective then?
We're trying to find others like us.
[Chi-seong]
We want to stimulate their desires.
This is the first step
in creating a monster.
[imitating clock ticking]
Time's up.
- [Yong-seok] Don't die! No, no!
- [body thuds]
No, please!
Jong-hyun!
[wailing]
No! No!
Jong-hyun!
[cries]
- [sobbing]
- You're uncomfortable
because you're human after all?
It's a meaningless experiment.
If what Number Three here saying
is really true,
there'd be a lot more MHs to show for it.
It's clear to me that your experiment
hasn't amounted to much.
You're simply being far too greedy.
[heavy breathing]
[Jae-jin] At this rate,
you'll kill them all.
[heavy breathing]
Your time's running out.
Hurry up and choose one.
[sniffles, breathes heavily]
[Yong-seok whimpers]
[somber music playing]
[shaky breathing]
[Yong-seok] Don't do it, Sergeant Kim!
You can't!
Yong-seok.
This is all my fault!
No, it's not, Yong-seok.
No one's thinking that. You just...
gotta survive.
[shaky breathing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[monster growling]
The hell do you think you're doing?
We're the same, you know.
If I let you end up like this,
I'll just give up on everything too.
I'm gonna get everyone out.
Reckless bastard.
Get up.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
[both panting]
[menacing music playing]
[monsters gagging, growling]
[panting continues]
[monster gagging]
[shrieking]
[gunshots]
[monster screeching]
[monster hissing, gagging]
- [gun clicks]
- [grunting]
[monsters growling]
[both straining]
[both panting]
Kill them all.
[flesh trilling]
[Ja-yeong] I'll do it.
Don't let me down this time.
[monsters growling]
[monster screeching]
[teeth chattering]
- [thwacks]
- [grunts]
[Yeong-hu straining]
[grunts]
[monster growling]
[Seo-jin shouting]
[monster choking]
[shouting]
[panting]
[monsters growling]
[monsters screeching]
[gloomy music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[screaming]
[Eun-yu]
Are you sure this is the only way?
That was new to me.
I've seen monsters' desires
several times before,
but I've never been so immersed
like I was with Yi-kyung's.
She might still have a chance though,
if she can recognize
that all of this is fake,
like I did.
You think you can save her?
I at least have to try.
I can't give up on her.
Then I'm coming with you.
You just woke up a second ago.
What if that monster takes over again?
No.
- You can't.
- [Eun-yu] Hey.
[Hyun-su]
I'm sorry you're always waiting, but...
Yi-kyung is my priority.
I can't protect you as well.
[breathes deeply]
I need to save her
no matter what.
[flesh crackling]
[sighs]
[groans]
You should go now.
And don't come back.
Forget it.
She didn't want me there.
[vehicle approaching]
[engine stops]
Hey there, hottie!
We meet again.
See that? Told you we're meant to be.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[bats screeching, fluttering]
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[soft gasp]
[other Yi-kyung] Have a look.
It's your child, Yi-kyung.
She's looking for her mom.
- [Yi-kyung whimpering]
- [infant crying]
[Yi-kyung] It's not.
[other Yi-kyung] I'm telling you,
it's your newborn child.
[Yi-kyung] It's not!
[other Yi-kyung] Are you sure?
Then you don't mind if I kill her?
- Yi-kyung?
- No, no, no... No!
Leave her alone!
Drop the act now.
You know your maternal bond
doesn't go that deep.
Or do you even have such a thing?
You can't, you can't, you can't.
Just be honest. You wanted to kill her.
Isn't that what you truly wished for?
It's not, it's not, it's not!
[Yi-kyung whimpering]
Then do you want to protect her?
You think you can do it this time around?
I can protect her.
Please, I can do it! I can protect her.
[sobbing]
[crackling]
[flesh squelching]
[ethereal music playing]
[Kid] Yi-kyung!
[monster snarling]
[gasps]
[other Yi-kyung]
That's the monster you created.
[distorted screams]
[dire music playing]
She was born this way because of you,
and now she's killing people at random.
Do you think that's okay?
Even though she might kill
your real child this time?
Just kill her.
- [heavy breathing]
- [suspenseful music playing]
It's the only way
to protect your own child.
[monsters hissing]
[exhales heavily]
[Kid] Yi-kyung!
[Kid and Hyun-su] Yi-kyung!
[other Yi-kyung] Get a grip!
- That thing's trying to hurt your child!
- [all scream]
- [gunshot]
- [screaming]
[eerie music playing]
[Dr. Lim] Just a moment.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll be right back. Just a moment.
I must be losing my mind. Shit!
[panting, grunting]
[distant shouting]
[both grunting]
[monster snarls]
[monster gagging]
[whimpering]
[groaning]
Sergeant!
If you go, you'll die.
[heavy breathing]
Why did you do it?
Why?
Why did you do it? Why?
[suspenseful percussive music playing]
[wheezing]
[monster roaring]
- [thuds]
- [monster snarling]
[grunts]
[monster screeching]
[panting]
[shouting]
[monster growling]
Seo-jin!
[monster screeching]
[straining]
[monster growling]
[painful screams]
- [thwacking]
- [monsters screeching]
[shouts]
[panting]
[Seo-jin groaning]
[Yong-seok] Serge!
[engine starts]
Where are we going?
Back where you came from.
Things are finally coming to fruition.
[Sang-wook] It'll be different this time.
I have a feeling
something exciting is about to happen.
[suspenseful music playing]
Take me there.
To the stadium, let's go.
[Jin-guk] Is it true
that the Crow Platoon arrested Ye-seul?
[Jin-guk] Why?
Lady, you still haven't found Seung-wan?
Does this mean he's a monster,
or that he's hiding?
[Cheol-yong] Jeez, man,
why does that even matter right now?
They'll kill him either way.
[gate opens]
[footsteps approaching]
Hello, sir. Chief Ji has just come out.
[keys jangling]
OFFICE
[Dong-jun]
Now they've entered the workshop.
[door lock clicks]
[Chief Ji breathing heavily]
Hey, where are we going?
You're doing this
'cause you feel bad, right?
It's okay. I understand now.
[Ye-seul] Hey.
Why aren't you saying anything?
And now you're ignoring me?
- Mom, I did everything you asked for!
- [bag thuds]
Ye-seul.
Help me, would you? Hmm?
[In-hwan] From now on,
those with symptoms
who hide it from us will have to face
immediate judgment.
[squelches]
[clanking]
[mechanical winding down]
[In-hwan] Did you know about this?
[gasps]
I knew nothing about this.
Mom, let go.
[grunts]
Mom! Let me go!
Your actions have put me in real danger.
And this is the last thing
I can do to help you.
Now leave. This is the way out of here.
- Or just go back to Master Sergeant Tak.
- Wait, Mom.
Mom! What are you saying right now?
I know I messed up.
- Why are you doing this to me, Mom?
- Get... Whoa!
Why do you keep on calling me Mom?
Don't you realize your mom died
of monsterization a year ago?
Do you know how desperately
I wanted to hear the word "mom"?
[breathes shakily, sniffles]
I wanted to hear it,
even if it was just in a dream.
But not from you.
From my son.
That's right.
Yeah, my son.
[sighs]
I must really be going crazy.
[laughs]
We were close for only a short while,
I almost thought my feelings were real.
And so I nearly made a terrible mistake.
[keys jangling]
What, what is that over there?
[breathing shakily]
You should've just left
when I gave you the chance.
Mom, I'm really... Why are you doing this?
[Dong-jun] I definitely saw them
going into the workshop.
But...
[Ye-seul] Wait, Mom. Mom!
Mom, what's going on? I'm scared.
[yelps]
[Chief Ji] Ye-seul, say hello.
This is my son.
[monster rumbling]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ye-seul sobbing]
[rumbling, squelching]
[gasps, exclaims]
[Chief Ji gasps]
My son! My son!
[screaming]
[heavy breathing]
[heavy breathing in distance]
[music fades]
Hey there, jerk.
I see you're still alive.
[Eun-yu] How long has it been?
[Chan-yeong] I'm telling you now...
[sighs]
...there's nothing we can do.
I know.
You said he told you to wait.
- [metal clanging]
- [monster rumbling]
[monster grumbling]
[squelching]
[metal clanging]
[monster grumbling, screeching]
[shaky breath]
[monster growling]
[monster bellows, snarls]
[monster snarling]
[monster bellowing, growling]
[monster whines]
[screaming in distance]
[monster growls]
[monster screeching]
[loud footsteps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[Chan-yeong] We'll send a signal.
[monster roaring]
[monster screeching]
[screeching]
[monster squealing, bellowing]
- [gunshot]
- [screeches]
[monster screeching]
[monster groaning]
[echoing pulsation]
[infant crying]
[somber choral music playing]
[indistinct screams]
[grunting]
[Hyun-su] Yi-kyung!
Yi-kyung, stop.
Come on, we gotta go back!
You gotta stop. Please, try to wake up!
Yi-kyung! Yi-kyung!
- [both grunting]
- [thuds]
[monster roaring]
[monster chittering]
We won't last long in here.
If you're suggesting
we should just leave them...
We gotta pull them up
and get them out of here.
[rumbling]
[monster growling]
- [grunts]
- [monster growling]
[heavy breathing]
[both grunting]
[glass shattering]
- [Chan-yeong grunts]
- [bangs]
[monster growls]
Oh, God. Oh, no!
[panting]
[suspenseful choral music playing]
We can't go back up there yet.
What are you... Are you insane?
Hey, untie this. Untie it now. Let go!
Let me go!
[rattling]
[tires screeching]
[Eun-yu] Let me go!
No, no! Chan-yeong, what are you doing?
[shouting] No, no, no!
Put me down right now!
[monster screeching, bellowing]
[tires squeaking]
[Eun-yu sobbing]
[Eun-yu screams]
Park Chan-yeong!
[sobbing]
- [grunting]
- [blasts]
[monster roaring]
[flames crackling]
[grunts]
Cha Hyun-su!
[Chan-yeong] Cha Hyun-su!
Cha Hyun-su, wake up!
[panting]
[suspenseful choral music playing]
[Yi-kyung panting]
[Kid] Mom!
[panting]
[Kid] Over here, I'm over here!
Hey, Mom, I'm over here!
[breathing shakily]
[Hyun-su] Yi-kyung.
We gotta leave now.
Hurry, let's go.
[exhales heavily, gasps]
Who you see is not your child.
Your real child is waiting for you.
We gotta get out of here.
Let's go.
No.
[Hyun-su] Right now, we gotta go. Come on.
I can't.
[Yi-kyung sobbing]
- [Hyun-su] Let's go.
- No!
No! Let go!
[whimpering, breathing heavily]
[Yi-kyung wailing]
No! No!
[suspenseful choral music playing]
[thuds]
[grunts]
Cha Hyun-su!
- [monster growling]
- [grunts]
[monster roaring, screeching]
[intense music playing]
[monster bellowing, roaring]
[flesh squelching]
[screeches]
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[rumbling]
[rumbling continues]
[bats screeching]
[Chan-yeong groaning]
[heavy breath]
[flesh squelching]
[suspenseful music swells]
[music stops]
[pensive choral music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[music swells, fades]
[closing theme music playing]