It's not a disease.
It's a curse.
They complained of frequent nosebleeds
and auditory hallucinations.
It suddenly begins one day
and it never stops.
They turned into miserable,
desperate beings.
Throw it!
We're not gonna be able to overcome this.
Please, help us!
I was consumed by it too.
Protect them?
Is that what you want to do?
Are you okay?
Golden hour saved you.
There was someone out there
who knew about this
before the government's announcement.
If they last 15 days
without being consumed,
subjects enter a stable phase.
They become unstable beings,
something in between
both human and monster.
They are called… "special infectees."
Hyun-su is dangerous.
He's dangerous, but we need him.
You know he's using you.
You think I'm gonna harm you guys
if I turn back into a monster?
A monster is still a monster.
Humans have failed.
Accept it.
Surrender the infected immediately.
Survivors will be transferred
to a safety camp.
"Safety camp" sounds ridiculous.
You don't know
who'll turn into a monster or when.
So, how can they possibly ensure safety?
I'll come back.
No. Eun-hyeok! Eun-hyeok!
You promised me to come back!
Eun-hyeok! Eun-hyeok!
Your fiancé.
I know how he's doing and where he is.
Us and humans can't coexist anyway.
I'm gonna find others who are like us.
SPECIAL INFECTEE REPORT GUIDE
Come with me.
Cha Hyun-su.
Long time no see.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT BUREAU
CENTRAL COMMAND
Has his condition changed?
Doesn't seem like it.
So there's no use for him then.
Then why are we keeping him?
Well, he's still alive.
There's that.
You're going soft
because he's your friend?
I'm the reason he's like that.
Did you forget?
All right then. Made any discoveries?
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT BUREAU
C5 RESEARCH FACILITY
I've got a pet theory.
Our earth was formed
some 4.6 billion years ago,
and we, Homo Sapiens, came around
roughly 200,000 years ago.
Now, if that was a day,
then we've existed for 0.05 seconds.
Spit it out already.
I'm saying,
from the planet's point of view,
we're a speck.
But these specks
are starting to be an eyesore.
And now they're destroying anything
and everything in their way
all for the sake of greed.
Isn't it about time the Earth had enough?
It's time for new management, and you all,
think it's time to checkout.
So here's my theory.
Humankind is a virus.
And the monsters are the vaccine.
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
This is Central Command.
Our vehicle transporting
the special infectee has been hijacked.
Pursuit team, report your location
and everyone else, provide support.
Listen up, Black Kite Three,
this mission is critical.
Return immediately.
That man is extremely dangerous.
If you surrender, I guarantee your safety.
You'll guarantee my safety?
Who do you think you're talking to?
The nerve of this guy.
Who is this?
What the hell do you want?
I don't…
want anything.
And I'm a nobody.
You did this for a reason,
you son of a bitch!
I just wanna even the odds a little.
Who the hell are you?
What the hell are you talking about?
Cha Hyun-su.
Long time no see.
Jung Ui-myeong?
Man, was it that obvious?
That's a bummer.
This is Black Kite Nine.
The target vehicle
is headed toward Hannam from Ichon.
Target vehicle
is approaching Banpo Bridge.
Calling for support.
Why did you kill him, huh?
'Cause… 'cause of you.
You see,
you pissed me off, that's why.
Die!
This guy's still alive, isn't he?
Just say thanks.
You should've been thanking me.
Etiquette's important, Cha Hyun-su.
Target vehicle twelve o'clock.
Utilize all firepower.
Units, we need to stop them
on the bridge at all costs.
There's action in the target vehicle.
What's the status of the special infectee?
The special infectee is confirmed alive!
Stop trying to hold it in
and show yourself.
No.
You can't kill me.
This is Night Owl.
Cutting them off.
Fire!
The vehicle is getting away!
The target vehicle escaped!
It's heading towards Banpo.
Permission for direct fire.
Negative. The target
must be brought in alive.
He's the last special infectee.
Fire on the bridge, cut them off.
This is Night Owl.
The target vehicle is getting away.
We've lost visuals on it.
Check all possible routes
and resume the pursuit.
Search the area, pan out,
do a full sweep on every possible route.
Don't we have enough monsters
at Central Command? I mean, why are we--
Because he's special!
Half human, half monster.
- We need that for a cure.
- Wait.
Was it a success?
I don't know.
The monsters at Central Command
are useless now.
They'll all be disposed of.
That's why we have to bring 'em in.
The military pulled it off.
Doesn't mean we're safe now.
Well, there wasn't a single monster
the whole way here.
No people too.
Well, uh, um…
Oh, the soldiers probably already…
Blockade five.
A military vehicle containing survivors
is approaching.
We'll inspect the vehicle.
See? What did I tell you?
The vehicle looks clear.
Let them through.
Roger.
How long until the debris is cleared?
At least two to three hours.
We're moving the survivors back here then.
Oh.
Wait. He's not…
He's not… He's just sick!
He has leukemia.
There should be a doctor here
who can confirm it for you.
All right. We'll check then.
Tae-yun's gonna be okay, all right?
He's dead, sir.
He wasn't a monster.
Some good news. Clean up.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Back off now.
- Nosebleeds are one of the symptoms.
- You sons of bitches!
You sons of…
Stay down.
Oh, no.
Come on.
No…
Son of a bitch!
Motherfucker!
Fucking bastard!
Baby!
Oh!
Oh, you have to stop!
You got to stop, baby.
It's mom! This is wrong. You can't…
How did this happen to you?
Oh, my baby.
Enjoying yourself? Humming and everything.
What the fuck are you saying?
That wasn't you?
Then what the hell was that?
Can you hear it?
- What's going on?
- Move!
Hey! Where are you going?
I just…
There were sounds and…
- Scan him.
- He's clean, sir.
So what the fuck was that, huh?
Hey, get back to work right now!
Turn around!
Get over there!
I said move! Go!
Ready or not, here I come.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
Hurry up and move!
Ready or not, here I come.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
Run!
Ah! Watch out!
Quiet! Shoot it down!
Keep running.
Keep running! Go, run!
Hey, come here!
Over here!
Hey, quickly! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Run! Go!
- Hurry!
- Hey!
I said drive! Hey!
Start driving,
you son of a bitch!
Let's go already!
Start driving, asshole!
Hey! I said start driving!
What the hell are you doing?
Mommy!
- Mommy!
- He's got a child.
Stop shooting! Stop! Don't shoot!
Let go! Let go!
Mommy!
Mommy…
Mommy.
Yun-seo!
Yun-seo! Yun-seo!
Oh, my God!
Mommy!
Yun-seo! Yun-seo!
Mom. Mommy.
Yun… Yun-seo.
Yun-seo!
Were you trying to get us all killed?
Fucking…
Piece of…
Man, even soldiers have it rough.
Bom…
You piece of…
Bom…Where's my…
Hey, who gives a fuck
where your dog is, huh?
How dare you!
You'd be dead if it wasn't for Bom.
I saw you back there!
You didn't lift a finger, did you?
So what?
What's wrong with that, huh?
- That's like the same thing--
- Stop it, you guys.
This isn't the time!
What's going to happen to us now?
Hey, why do you…
Hey.
What is this?
You don't think I'd fall for that--
What do you want?
Gotta get somewhere.
That didn't make them pull back?
A bunch of idiots, huh?
SPECIAL INFECTEE REPORT GUIDE
Sergeant Kim, Sergeant Min.
Take your teams and do a sweep.
We'll check the rear.
Check it up and down.
Call in if you find anything.
Roger.
Sergeant Kim.
Doesn't something look off?
I mean, take a look at the bodies here.
Almost all of them were shot.
And the creatures?
Well, I doubt a monster was the shooter.
Plus the bodies aren't torn up either, so…
Well, by the look of things,
I think a monster was here, sir.
Most of these bodies
have gunshot wounds, sir.
Maybe it left after causing havoc.
Hold it.
Sign of a monster in the debris ahead.
Target location confirmed.
The monster's located inside.
Permission to fire.
Granted.
That's not the only one.
We got another over here.
Cease fire!
It's heading your way, Sergeant Kim.
Prepare suppressing fire.
Get in formation.
Seok-chan, on me!
The monster is on the move.
It's heading rapidly towards the front.
Where did this motherfucker
crawl out of, huh?
Hey!
Back off or it dies.
Back off!
Hey, Seok-chan, grab it.
Enough now.
Move.
What the hell is this, sir?
I just watched you spare
one of those things right now.
"Shoot and kill any and all monsters
on sight." That's our directive.
That's the primary objective
of Crow Platoon, am I wrong?
Sergeant First Class.
We're here to put down the ones
that attack us, Sergeant.
That…
is our objective and always was.
We only get one shot
at a first impression.
We're about to meet others like you.
You know, "infectees."
That name pisses me off though.
Any suggestions?
Hmm!
"Neohumanity."
God, you really look like shit.
None of this played out
how I wanted it to.
Sorry.
So you weren't planning
on a shopping spree?
Then why exactly am I here?
I want you to live.
I think you'd like that
compared to being a rat in the lab.
To liberate you, that's why I did this.
Humanity won't give up.
They already had you in their hands,
so I figured
they're taking this personally.
It doesn't matter.
I chose to do that.
That's right.
You walked right into their hands,
didn't you?
Why was that?
I thought I told you
they'll rip you into pieces.
They'll dissect you over and over.
How many more times
do you have to hear that?
Is that why you ran away?
Because you were afraid of them?
I just wanted to live, okay?
Try worrying about something else.
Saving humans, all that shit,
fuck that, forget all that.
Figure out what you're gonna do
starting now.
There's gotta be a reason
you're a neohuman, isn't there?
I'm not going to kill people
just to survive.
Not like you.
No, I don't think so.
Oh, God, help me!
Please help me!
Somebody please!
Please, help me. Help!
Fighting you, I'm past all that.
From now on, I'll stop killing wantonly.
You mean it?
Of course!
I promise I won't attack them first.
If they stay out of my way, they're safe.
How are we gonna find them?
Others who are like us.
That's the beauty of it all.
We're going to them right now.
Hey, you know that area, Bamseom?
They're waiting for us there.
I was headed that way already, so…
In that case, why did you…
That's not… No, that's not it!
That's not it.
That's ridiculous.
Them bringing you in there in chains?
No, but we're the ones walking in.
Aren't you excited?
This time,
you'll be rescuing the neohumans.
Once you see them, you'll understand.
The reason you were chosen.
This is Gate 2.
Unreported Black Kite vehicle approaching.
Major.
Weren't you out on a mission, sir?
I have an urgent report.
We're going to have to have you
fill in the entry log before we--
I'm sorry?
What part of urgent don't you get?
The vehicle is clear.
It's coming through.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT BUREAU
How far do you think you're gonna get?
You think my men will just stand around
while their commander has gone missing?
We got this far, didn't we?
Looks to me like no one's filed a report.
The military's stretched
too thin to worry about you.
Attention, all units! Alert!
Two individuals suspected
of being special infectees
approaching Gate 2.
I thought I was over it.
I guess it never left me.
It's all clear as day.
In this world…
because we don't have much time,
human beings should be decent
to each other.
Get out of my fucking head.
Fuck off!
Go away! Go away!
Stay away.
Get back! Stay away from me!
You monster.
Why are you doing this to us?
Just kill me already. Just do it!
Come on, please, it hurts so much.
Mom…
Beginning experiment on Sample D-126.
Hui-ji?
Our subject is the mother of D-126.
She volunteered for the test.
- Classification?
- Type yellow, sir.
According to the mother,
it was online harassment.
Hui-ji, where are you? It's Mom.
Hui-ji?
Hui-ji, Mom's here.
Hui-ji, it's me.
Hui-ji.
It appears prior connection
before monsterization don't matter
in type yellow either.
End of test.
Oh! Oh, God! No!
No! Don't! Don't do it!
Hui-ji! You can't!
You can't!
Oh, no. Hui-ji!
No! No!
You can't!
Hui-ji! Hui-ji!
Hui-ji…
Oh, God!
Oh, Hui-ji!
Oh, shit.
It feels so sick eating this body. Fuck.
I shouldn't have fucking even started.
Oh, shit, man. The son of a bastard
rubbed me the wrong ways…
What the hell, why won't it work?
Fuck.
Running away again?
Fuck it.
You said we were chosen, right?
Really? We're chosen?
More like abandoned.
Look at you.
You can't survive without a human host.
You see?
You're just a parasite.
Shut your fucking mouth.
Shut the hell up, you fucking disgrace!
Come with me.
Let go.
Let go, motherfucker.
Let go of me.
Let me go, you son of a bitch.
I'm gonna murder you, you bastard.
Fucking son of a bitch.
Let go.
I said let go of me, you fuck.
You bastard.
You are so dead when I get my…
I'll fucking kill you, you son of a…
Just a bit more.
I think it's better that we go together.
You're fucking crazy.
You think
they're gonna just accept you now?
Oh, fuck.
They're gonna turn you
into a goddamn pincushion,
and I know you're gonna regret this
for the rest of your days!
Please.
I can't go back there.
Not like this. Please.
Don't do this, please.
Just look at me. Look at me.
I can't go back there. Not like this.
Please! Please.
God, please.
Why?
Haven't you done enough already?
Why? Why are you doing this?
Huh, why? Why?
To make sure I won't forget.
So that I'll always know…
no matter what…
that I'm human.
Fine.
You should go to hell because of that.