[theme music playing]
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
[Hyun-su] I think I've finally
started to understand you.
I was always mocking you...
but now I'm stuck in your shoes.
[pensive choral music playing]
Tell me, Cha Hyun-su.
Why did I do that?
[shouting] Tell me why!
[breathing heavily]
To save Eun-hyeok?
Even from letting Eun-yu live,
all the way to that ridiculous bet
that we've made about you.
There are other things
I'm sure you'd do too.
You asked who I was.
Since the very beginning...
I was always you.
I've always been within you.
I was a mere version of you...
[inhales]
...that you didn't want
anyone to find...
Are you listening?
I'm sure you are.
Like I always was.
I wonder, if we become one...
which one of us will open his eyes?
[pensive music crescendos]
[ethereal pulsation]
[music fades]
[loud blast]
[thrilling music playing]
[ember crackling]
[soft gasp]
Cha Hyun-su?
[thrilling music crescendos]
[snapping]
[music subdues]
[Hyun-su] There's one thing
we need to set straight.
This time, you're helping me.
Not the other way around.
[hopeful choral music playing]
I'm sorry it took so long.
Cha Hyun-su.
Could it really be...
[Hyun-su] Has everyone
gone to the stadium?
Mm.
Then we should too. Let's go.
That's a gift.
No matter how fast you are,
you won't be fast enough.
[mellow piano music playing]
Remember that elephant slide?
It had a hole in the middle of it.
[sighs] If you hid in there,
no one could see you at all.
You hid there every time
we played hide-and-seek.
I would look for you until you cried.
Do you know how I ended up
finding that hole?
Remember when we were playing and
I got distracted by our neighbor's dog,
and its leash suddenly broke,
so I raced after it?
And then you popped out of the slide.
And I caught you.
[cheerful violin music playing]
The kid who was always last
in running races carried me on his back.
Get to the point.
[Eun-yu sighs]
You can learn.
If you have memories,
you can learn emotions.
Then you shouldn't lie about it.
You untied the dog.
You felt bad for it.
The leash didn't snap.
I guess your ankle's doing better.
You've stopped limping.
Are you hurt?
Nah, it's fine.
[Hyun-su] Looks like you're doing okay.
Really?
That's good.
It doesn't feel real.
You and Eun-hyeok being here again.
[music stops]
[bold music playing]
Head out to your locations.
[In-hwan] From now on, we spread out
and avoid the special infectees.
Gather as many survivors as possible
in each location, and wait for the signal.
FOOD AND WATER AT CHURCH
PS. FIRST COME, FIRST SERVED
Tonight,
we will leave the stadium
with all the survivors.
[bold music swells]
[indistinct chatter]
Excuse me.
[sighs]
[cane clattering]
[Jin-a groans]
I don't want the Crow Platoon's help.
[Dong-jun] You should come with us.
[shouting] Piss off!
[thuds]
[Jin-a] I'm sure you'd rather see me die.
I made Yong-seok go.
[music stops abruptly]
[Jin-a] I wanted to live...
even for just a few more days.
So I made him go.
Still want to help me?
That fucking idiot.
Just let me suffer alone.
It won't take long.
Oh, shit!
- [Cheol-jong] Looking for the kid?
- Oh, fuck! Where'd you come from?
Oh, shit!
I could kill you! You scared me.
[Cheol-jong] Well, you know.
I've been looking around, and I noticed
that no one is working harder than you.
Do you want to join our group?
Or you could join me, you know?
[scoffs]
Fine, I'll bite, then.
What is it?
First, we must get the girl,
hand her over and leave.
You really wanna go through all that
just to leave her here to die?
What nonsense.
Come on! Piss off.
How will you catch her then?
She's not just an ordinary kid
because she can turn people.
Who'd believe that? It's all bullshit.
I've seen her do it.
I saw her turn a person into a monster
with my own eyes.
[breathing deeply]
[sinister music playing]
[Jin-guk] So what's your plan?
[snickering]
You're working with others, aren't you?
Huh?
[Chi-seong] Do you really think
it would be okay to use humans
to do such critical work?
That's what you're worried about
after you lost my kid?
[Sang-wook] Look how hard they're working,
unlike you guys.
Where are Jae-jin and Ja-yeong?
Right. I'll bring them to you.
[Sang-wook] Get rid of them.
Sir?
[sinister music builds]
Kill those two.
[suspenseful music playing]
We all have to be here to start.
What? What the hell?
Wasn't it... first come, first served?
[Jae-chan] Did they bullshit
about giving us food too?
[Skinny] We should've just
looked for the kid.
Never mind that.
What's the point if you end up
becoming a monster in the process?
[Jin-ho] Can I help you?
There's someone I'm looking for.
In that case, you should wait.
They'll come here.
You don't know who it is.
[footsteps approaching]
Please wait inside.
[Peter] At least provide an explanation
if you're gonna lock us up.
You'll find out soon enough.
You aren't locked up here.
We're protecting you.
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[blood squelching]
[Dr. Lim straining]
[metal rattling]
[loud metallic clanging]
[panting]
Damn.
Ugh, what took you so long?
Sang-won talks a lot, doesn't he?
I couldn't just wait around forever.
[flesh squelching]
[In-hwan] Did you get it?
[Dr. Lim breathing heavily]
[eerie stinger playing]
[breathing deeply]
Are you ready?
[Dr. Lim] Oh.
Don't tell Sang-won about this.
He doesn't know that his little minions
were made with this stuff too.
If he finds out...
[breathes deeply]
...he'll lose it.
By the way,
what did Sang-won want?
[In-hwan] The child's missing.
[object clattering]
[chuckles] She's something, isn't she?
How did she manage to escape?
Apparently, she can
turn people into monsters.
[syringe clicks]
[tense music playing]
What?
[door lock clicks]
Ugh, shit. You startled me, jeez.
Well, how did it go?
Did you find the kid?
[groaning]
[door slams]
[door creaking]
Wait... Tell me that again.
Who can do what?
- You weren't aware of this?
- Wait, wait a second.
Are you serious?
[inhales sharply]
[ominous music swells]
Is it really true?
[Dr. Lim shuddering]
Sergeant Tak, I'm sorry.
But I think
I'll have to save this for later.
I think there's a more suitable
test subject out there.
What?
I was saving this for myself.
It would've been mine
if I'd just shown symptoms.
And yet, those goddamn symptoms
always kept passing me, and why?
Nearly everyone got it, so why not me?
[Dr. Lim chuckles]
I was ready to give it up
for the sake of humanity.
Now that I'm pursuing a good cause,
the gods rewarded me.
[crunching]
[grunting]
[dire music playing]
[Dr. Lim groaning and coughing]
[choking]
That kid, where is she now?
[snarling]
[yelps]
[breathing heavily]
- [Jin-guk struggling]
- [ominous music playing]
Hey, are you insane? What are you doing?
Wh-What's wrong with you?
Oh, shit. What? Wait!
What is this?
[ominous music swells]
What?
[gasps]
[glass smashing]
[Jin-guk choking]
[flesh squeezing]
Where's my dad?
[music stops]
Ugh, come on. Where is he?
Quietly follow us.
Huh?
Oh.
But why?
Oh!
I found you!
The scary-looking soldier.
Is your name Master...
Sergeant Tak?
- [chuckles]
- [suspenseful music playing]
Park Chan-yeong...
a-and Kim Yeong-hu,
you know them, don't you?
[door opens]
[door slams shut]
[Sang-wook] Why are you here,
and not looking for the kid?
Do you not care anymore
because you're symptomatic?
[In-hwan] This was originally mine.
[Sang-wook scoffs] Seriously?
You still can't let go of that?
[In-hwan] I heard you were
gonna take over the child's body
once she's found.
My friend can be a blabbermouth.
That's not true.
He never told you about your minions.
[suspenseful music builds]
He made them with your blood!
Maybe that's why
they were so loyal to you.
[tense music playing]
You really didn't know?
I thought you were pretending not to know.
Honestly, I never thought
you'd be fooled by him.
- [loud blast]
- [electricity crackling]
[monster arms rumbling]
What?
I was just disappointed.
I thought I'd get the opportunity too.
Are you saying you'll join me
after all this?
[inhales deeply]
I don't see why not.
There is only one more vial of your blood.
It was in Ja-yeong's stomach
and he took it out.
And then, what?
Dr. Lim ate it himself.
[music fades]
[matchbox thuds]
[exhaling shakily]
[ripping with teeth]
[breathing shakily]
[blowing]
[wheezing]
[inhales nervously]
Kim Yeong-hu.
[sighs nervously]
Sergeant.
So you described me
as a scary-looking man, did you?
- [sniffling]
- [somber music playing]
Is that not true?
You have a strong look,
and you don't speak much.
[rubbing in pocket]
[chains jangling]
[somber music builds]
You were right, sir.
Yong-seok,
Seo-jin,
U-seok,
Jong-hyun,
and Seok-chan.
The members of the search party,
deployed for Sergeant Choi Yong-seok...
All the members are dead.
[sniffling]
We all failed the mission, sir.
We shouldn't have gone.
It's my fault that those monsters
came in here too.
As a result of this,
I've come back as the only survivor.
[sniffling]
- I'm sorry, sir.
- [In-hwan] Don't be.
I'm the one who gave the order.
I'm the one who deceived you too.
I'm symptomatic.
It started even before
I sent you to Bamseom.
I kept it hidden,
trying to protect this place.
[breaking into tears] But...
I wasn't being honest
with any of you here.
[In-hwan inhales deeply]
Yeong-hu.
Go ahead, Sergeant.
What kind do you think I'll turn into?
[sniffling, then exhaling deeply]
You've never been anything
other than a soldier to me.
You served to protect...
[wheezing]
...or to kill.
[In-hwan] How about a bomb?
At least that way, I could be of use.
[somber music crescendos]
Will that be enough?
I'm not at all surprised by it.
[chuckles]
You were always a monster to us, boss.
- Didn't you hear the rumors?
- [chuckling]
[tearful giggle]
[Yeong-hu] And if we actually need to,
we'll make use of you,
even once you're a monster.
So please hold on
until the end.
That way, it'll be easier to use you.
Isn't that what it means to be a soldier?
[music fades]
[Eun-hyeok] Eun-yu.
[eerie music playing]
Lee Eun-yu.
[past Eun-hyeok] I'm going to work now.
- Don't just eat ramyeon, okay?
- [Eun-hyeok] Eun-yu.
[past Eun-hyeok]
Eat a proper meal, all right?
And if you're not home later,
I'm reporting you as missing.
Survivors, the first floor is safe now.
Come to the first floor,
we'll be safer together.
[music fades]
[past Eun-hyeok] We survivors...
must stick together.
[ominous choral music playing]
Eun-hyeok!
Thank you.
Thanks for coming despite everything.
[sniffling]
Hyun-su.
[somber music playing]
Just keep following this road all the way.
You'll see it once you get closer.
If you're in pain,
let me carry you.
I'll catch up with you guys shortly.
I'm just gonna rest.
[sighs]
[Eun-yu] Hey, hurry.
I'll feel uncomfortable
slowing you both down.
You'll see Ms. Cha and Yeong-su there too.
[chuckles] Oh, man.
They'll all be so happy to see you.
Say what you really mean.
What?
If I ever...
[breathing nervously]
...change or become like Eun-hyeok...
If I do...
If I do, then...
remind me every chance you get.
And don't be upset
if I get bitchy, okay, yeah?
And Eun-hyeok...
Don't you need to talk?
I'll do whatever I can.
I'll bring them back,
and we'll meet again.
[soft chuckle]
[leaving footsteps fade]
He grew up so fast.
[sighs]
[somber music continues]
Go back if you're worried.
Don't be so cold toward her.
She's your sister.
You mean, your first love.
I don't share a drop of blood with her.
[dramatic music playing]
[Hyun-su breathing angrily]
[Eun-hyeok] What?
'Cause she'll become a monster?
You knew it too?
Lee Eun-yu is safe.
Just focus on what's coming.
It's part of the process.
And at the very least,
she can protect herself as a monster.
[Eun-yu] If I ever...
[Eun-yu breathing nervously]
...change or become like Eun-hyeok...
[dramatic music builds]
If I do...
If I do, then...
remind me every chance you get.
And don't be upset
if I get bitchy, okay, yeah?
Even if I give you a lot of shit,
just let it slide.
Are you doing this on purpose?
You really felt nothing?
You're just acting, aren't you?
Cha Hyun-su.
Are you even serious
about killing the infectees?
[shoving]
I'm more interested in killing you first.
Try me.
But I'll just come back to life.
Why did you even bother turning up here?
You should've just died.
I told you, I don't die.
[dramatic music intensifies]
[sighs exasperatedly]
There's no point talking anymore.
[Eun-hyeok] I agree with you.
You can just stay that way.
Thanks to you, I know exactly what to do.
I'll find you, no matter what.
I'm going to find you
and drag your ass back to Eun-yu.
[music fades]
[footsteps]
Phew.
[loud breathing in distance]
Hello?
[eerie music playing]
You there!
[eerie music swells]
[breathing shakily] Oh, fuck.
[eerie music crescendos, then fades]
[panting]
[Ye-seul] Oh!
[eerie music resumes]
Yeong-su, where have you gone?
[Ye-seul] Huh?
Was that a...
Crow Platoon soldier?
[eerie music builds]
[eerie music crescendos]
[breathing shakily]
[somber choral music playing]
[hesitating]
[Ms. Cha] You...
Yeong-su, have you...
Have you seen my Yeong-su?
[menacing music playing]
[Ye-seul gasps]
Hey, what are you doing?
[music subdues]
[Ms. Cha whimpering]
[Slime Monster gushing]
[ethereal whoosh]
[Slime Monster gurgling loudly]
[Yi-su] Let go.
Believe me...
she doesn't recognize you.
Ms. Cha, let's go.
Those people are strange, okay?
[Ms. Cha struggling]
Yeong-su?
[somber stinger playing]
[Slime Monster rumbling]
[Ye-seul gasps]
[whimpering]
What on earth is that?
[Ye-seul whimpering]
What...
[breathing shakily]
[Ye-seul] Ms. Cha.
[Slime Monster rumbling loudly]
[Ye-seul] Ms... Ms. Cha.
Ms. Cha, let's go.
We need to go now.
It's dangerous!
[screaming]
[Ye-seul panting]
Yeong-su has come to me.
[Ms. Cha sobbing]
This is... This is...
This really is my Yeong-su.
[somber music playing]
[Slime Monster rumbling]
[Ms. Cha sobbing]
[sobbing]
[Ms. Cha sniffling]
[somber music continues]
[sniffling]
[sobbing]
Yeong-su...
[Ms. Cha weeping]
[chuckles] I found you.
[laughing] Over here...
[sharp stab]
[Ye-seul yelps]
[Ye-seul shuddering]
[thrilling music playing]
[Yeong-su] Mister.
Please don't do it.
[Ms. Cha whimpering]
[Ms. Cha] Mister.
You recognize me, don't you? [sobbing]
You're the one who returned
my daughter to us.
[music subdues]
[dragging feet]
[somber music playing]
[stomping]
[panting]
[thunder roaring]
[thunder clapping]
[somber music crescendos]
[music subdues]
[shutter creaking]
[breathing shakily]
[somber music builds]
[dramatic music playing]
[Ms. Cha weeping]
Thank you so much.
That's my Yeong-su!
[dramatic music intensifies]
Yi-su.
Take a good look.
This is what happens when you run away.
[sharp stab]
[menacing music playing]
[flesh squelching]
[thuds]
[monster arm withdraws]
[mournful choral music playing]
[Slime Monster crackling]
[Yi-su weeping]
[screaming]
[electricity crackling]
[inaudible scream]
[sinister choral music playing]
[sharp stabs on flesh]
[closing theme music playing]
[closing theme music ends]