[Yi-kyung grunting]
[whimpering]
[Yi-kyung grunts]
[Yi-kyung panting]
[Yi-kyung] I was scared…
of my baby
that was born into this world so soon
and of the decision I had to make.
[crying]
That all scared me.
[crying continues]
I couldn't bring myself to kill you.
So I left you.
[wistful music playing]
[Yi-kyung] I thought maybe I could forget.
I missed you!
[Yi-kyung] But I needed to know…
why you were born like this.
Was I to blame for bringing you
into this world so soon?
Was it my foul desires
that made you what you are?
What is my baby, really?
Is she a gift or a curse?
I just couldn't tell.
I thought…
you might have the answer.
I came too late, didn't I?
Not at all.
You're here now, right?
[Hyun-su] That's your mommy.
Say hi.
Hi there.
[Yi-kyung]
Seeing the normal little girl you were,
I was relieved.
[bells jingling]
[somber music playing]
Every day I spent with you,
hiding my worries and doubts…
Living every ordinary day
skating on thin ice.
[gentle music playing]
Maybe a life like this
wouldn't be so bad.
[music fades]
But it all fell apart
in one moment.
[ominous music playing]
The moment I thought I lost you,
but you stopped writhing in pain…
and before me stood something different.
That's when I realized…
[plaintive music playing]
no matter how much I denied it,
my little girl was a monster.
[Kid grunting]
[screaming]
[Kid crying]
[grunts]
[Kid breathing heavily]
[Yi-kyung groaning]
[Hyun-su] What's going on?
[Kid breathing heavily]
Why did you have to do this?
I'm her mother.
No matter how she changes,
or what form she takes,
I need to recognize my little girl.
I won't ever lose her.
[Yi-kyung] I don't know
if I'm protecting you from this world,
or if I'm protecting the world from you.
Don't take those off no matter what.
I'm just…
doing all I can to stay with you.
Understand?
[theme music playing]
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
[baby crying]
[heartbeats]
SWEET HOME
Mom…
The people…
They're all bad.
Did you say "Mom"?
You're no different.
[screams]
[wings flapping]
[Eun-yu grunts]
[grunting]
Cha Hyun-su.
Cha Hyun-su!
Are you really just gonna leave like that?
Were you expecting a hug or something?
Yeah, I was.
I expected at least a "Glad to see you.
How've you been?"
But I'm not glad to see you.
It's been you all along.
The construction site,
all of it was you, wasn't it?
You just had to confuse me, didn't you?
Just why are you trying to run away?
Will you say something?
What?
You're gonna run, aren't you?
What are you even running away for?
We cross paths and that's it.
I figured since we're not strangers,
I should help you.
Nothing more.
You understand?
[grunts]
[dark melancholic music playing]
[cracks]
You're trying to get yourself killed?
You monster piece of shit,
what are you doing here?
Get gone.
Hey, you crazy bitch.
Even Ha-ni knows
not to throw away her life.
Of all the things to do, you're spending
your time chasing after a monster?
You're lucky to still be alive.
Thank God.
Hyun-su is still…
alive.
[Eun-yu inhales shakily]
If you're gonna draw their attention
and bring monsters to our doorstep,
then just get lost.
- [Hyun-su] Why did you do that?
- [Kid] I don't like her.
So why don't you like her?
She's the reason you hurt my friends
and the reason you keep disappearing,
isn't she?
Protecting her, you…
you broke your promise.
[owls hooting]
I was curious
about humans at first 'cause Mom is one.
So I said "hi" and they…
they hurt me.
They yelled and they pushed and…
and they hurt me too.
And they killed
all my friends and monsters!
Leaving only just me.
They were just scared.
Afraid of losing someone.
Then I'll give them a reason.
Show them how scary it was.
You should feel it too.
I'm talking about my pain.
You'll feel it too.
I came to tell you that, that's all.
Let's get out of here.
Huh?
There's no place for me.
My house is gone.
[unsettling music playing]
[fire crackling]
[grunts]
[debris rumbling]
[foreboding music playing]
[Kid] I…
no longer need you,
or Mom anymore.
[soft gasp]
[fire crackling]
[monster cooing]
[cooing continues]
[whimpering, mumbling]
[yelps]
[monster whimpering]
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
[panting]
Yi-kyung!
Are you in here?
[monster mumbling]
Yi-kyung…
Hyun-su.
Are you okay, Yi-kyung?
It's all my fault it's like this.
I just wanted her
to be safe like you were.
[whimpers]
All I wanted was for her to…
[sobs]
It wasn't your fault.
[Yi-kyung groaning softly]
[sighs]
I should've killed her.
In the back of my mind,
I always had that thought.
I know…
I know she must've felt it
when I had those thoughts.
[breathing heavily]
You're wrong.
I know because I was there too.
You said you were a bad mother,
but you know that's just not true.
The fault is all mine.
I was the one who made her like this.
No, this is good.
It turning out like this is for the best.
[Yi-kyung gasping]
This way, when…
I don't have to kill my daughter.
Were you really going to kill her?
Why? You're her mother.
So why?
I don't deserve to be.
I had the same thought hundreds of times.
"Why is she cursed like this?" Why?
[Yi-kyung sobbing]
It's all my fault.
My awful thoughts and desires
turned her…
into a…
monster.
Yeah, so what?
Are monsters really all bad?
[monster cooing weakly]
This one saved you.
Saved you 'cause you're family.
You see, monsters
feel and recognize people.
'Cause they were human once too.
[cooing continues]
[exhales deeply]
- [rattling]
- [clattering]
[Ha-ni] What's with you?
[Ha-ni grunting]
Open your eyes!
- [grunts]
- What the hell are you doing?
I think he's dead, boss.
[Ha-ni groans]
What's going on?
What's going on with him?
What happened here?
[Ho-sang] He's been poisoned.
How much did he eat?
He had one bowl of that.
[Ho-sang] He had a whole bowl?
[Ha-ni laughing]
[sighs]
What was in this?
Mushrooms.
The magic kind.
[sighs]
[Ho-sang] This one's got a high tolerance.
But he's gonna need an antidote.
[Ha-ni] Hey!
[laughing]
Hey, wake up!
[laughing continues]
[sobs]
[Ye-seul] That asshole.
How many times is it now?
As if enlisting in the army
without telling me wasn't enough,
now he's gonna make me cry
over some bitch?
PARK CHAN-YEONG
Shit. You know what? Screw you!
[Ye-seul grunts]
[Seon-hwa]
I'll take it if you're throwing it away.
[sighs]
Seriously.
You think this is something
anyone could wear?
I found a whole stack of them
up there the other day.
No, it's not.
This was Chan-yeong's gift to me
and he's signed it too, just so you know.
Why did you throw it then
if it's so important?
[grunts]
You're so annoying.
[exhales sharply]
- Ready to head out?
- For what?
And where?
We're gonna go meet
with Father Peter today, remember?
[sighs]
I'm not really in the mood.
Come on. I don't wanna go alone.
[groans]
[Seok-chan] Let me come with you, sir.
No.
This is personal.
That makes no sense.
How is finding Yong-seok personal, sir?
Don't be dramatic, dumbass.
[sighs]
Let them know tomorrow.
That I went after Yong-seok.
I can't do that, I'm afraid.
I'm sorry, Sarge.
I have to make sure you're safe.
[footsteps approaching]
I heard the signal came from Bamseom.
That's correct, sir.
You can't do it alone.
Take some men with you at least.
If I may, why the sudden change of heart?
[Dr. Lim]
Since we're all heading the same way,
let me hitch a ride, all right?
[chuckles]
[clanking]
[exhales deeply]
Sergeant, right now,
it doesn't really matter.
Just make sure
to focus on getting back here alive.
[Seo-jin] I'm going.
Yong-seok's my boy too, isn't he?
- No, you should stay, man.
- [Seo-jin] Hey, Kim Yeong-hu.
Let me go on this with you, man.
We're brothers, did I get that wrong?
Hey.
But what if they get both of us,
then what?
Who's gonna lead the unit then?
Seo-jin…
I'll find Yong-seok.
Trust me on this one.
[Seo-jin] I do.
You've always been better at everything.
But this is one I can't…
This is one I can't back out of.
I can't just sit back while you guys go.
So just take me.
'Cause I mean…
If it's a bust
and none of you make it back…
I'll be useless.
Wow, you two are really
making it dramatic here.
But I'm coming as well, Sarge.
Well, I'm also coming, sir.
Bravo! Whoa!
Am I the only one cringing?
Whoo, just got chills.
Let's roll out.
Man, what am I doing?
I can't drive with my hand like this.
Let's go! Let's go!
[chuckles]
[exhales deeply]
Damn, it's too dark to see anything
with these on.
[Dr. Lim] Let's go!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Jin-ok] What's going on?
What's wrong? Why aren't you talking?
[sighs]
I really can't right now.
- [Ye-seul] I need some drinks.
- Hmm?
[Ye-seul sighs]
So you're just gonna steal
in plain sight like that.
[sighs]
Let me take the booze.
I'll pay.
Got any more?
Come on then.
[refreshed exhale]
So, uh…
are you gonna accept her or not?
Stop it. He's a priest.
That's inappropriate.
I mean, why? I didn't say get hitched.
He can date, can't he?
That's enough.
Hey.
[Ye-seul] What's that?
What's going on over there?
You a couple?
Are you playing with my girl here?
Just go if you're drunk.
Damn. All men are the same. Pussies.
And that's why you're alone.
That sort of shit's
what scares them away, you know?
Get a load of this fucking bitch.
Hey!
You don't fucking know love, do you, huh?
[mellow music playing on radio]
[sighs]
I thought I was turning into
a monster there.
I thought I was hearing things.
Gosh, don't say things like that!
That last incident
was only a few days ago.
Yo!
When's the last time
you heard music, huh? Right?
You've got quite the odds
and ends, Father.
Pay up first.
You better confess if you want a drink.
I know you skipped out earlier.
[scoffs]
Man, oh, man, that's harsh.
She's right, I mean,
what did you even bring?
[refreshed exhale]
Oh, wait, what?
I mean, greed makes monsters of us all.
The only cure for that
is to love and share.
[Jin-a]
Being a monster doesn't sound so bad.
Live a long life.
Never get sick again.
Or feel scared.
- Hey.
- [Gi-chun] That's right.
Sure. Living like this day to day
really sucks, but…
but we're still all here, huh?
I'm fine as long as I don't turn into
one of them.
[Gi-chun chuckles]
That's about all I can ask for.
There's so much
that I wanna go out and do.
If I could just hurry up
and get out of here.
It's a bit hard here.
What about you, Father?
You're always listening to us,
how about you talk this time?
[Jin-guk] Hear, hear.
- We're all ears.
- Let's hear it.
There isn't a before and after
for me, really.
Nothing's really different.
This is great.
I love this broken world.
Look how well we get along
now that we are all equals.
I'm so content.
I bet you were in debt.
You'd be dead wrong.
Stop talking out of your ass.
Bullshit. You were homeless.
How any rich person would rather
be boozing it up here, is ridiculous--
[annoyed sigh]
Ugh!
Ugh, I can't.
I, Jung Ye-seul,
need to lighten this depressing mood.
Get up.
All right. And here we go.
[mellow music playing]
I might have to change the sign.
[mellow music continues playing]
[sighs]
You seem happy, Doc.
You wouldn't get it, Sergeant,
being that you come up here all the time.
[Dr. Lim]
You try staying holed up for a year.
[breathes deeply]
It's all a breath of fresh air, huh?
Oh, I bet you're a special case, Doctor.
[Seo-jin] Most people would be scared.
That bag, what's in there?
A secret box.
What's in there?
[Dr. Lim] I just said it's a secret.
The more people know,
the less it's a secret.
[gasps]
[shouts]
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
No. Stop! Stop!
[Dr. Lim] Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Stop!
What's the matter?
My stomach is…
[grunting]
We're almost there, man.
No, this is an emergency, actually.
I'll make it quick. One second.
[grunts]
- Jong-hyun, hey.
- Sir.
You're on.
Ah, shit.
[Dr. Lim groaning]
Why the hell
would you bring that with you?
Doesn't hurt to be prepared.
[Dr. Lim] Oh, God.
[Yeong-hu] Hey, Jong-hyun,
is he about done?
Looks like it'll take a minute.
[Jong-hyun]
Jesus, what the hell did he eat?
[Yeong-hu] Stay alert.
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
- [rustling]
- [thuds]
[low growls]
[low snarling]
Sir, we've got movement ahead.
[Jong-hyun] Requesting cover.
Roger that.
[Yeong-hu] Sergeant, do you have visuals?
I've got nothing here.
Seok-chan, get ready to drive.
[Seok-chan] Yes, sir.
[growling]
[light suspenseful music playing]
- Hey, I wiped, okay?
- Shh.
[monster growling]
[growling continues]
[whispers]
What is that?
- [wheels squeaking]
- [clanks]
Leave it there.
I won't do that.
[wheels squeaking]
- [clanks]
- [Dr. Lim] Damn it.
- [monster growling softly]
- [thuds]
Fuck me.
[shouts]
Run!
- [monsters growling]
- [tense music playing]
[rapid gunshots]
[Dr. Lim grunting]
[Dr. Lim grunts]
[Jong-hyun grunts]
[Dr. Lim screaming]
[monster growling]
[intense music playing]
[tires screech]
[monsters growling]
[rapid gunshots]
[Dr. Lim] Faster!
[Dr. Lim screaming]
[monster grunts]
[Jong-hyun grunting]
- Whoa, don't hit that.
- Fuck this shit.
- I'm right here, okay?
- What the fuck's in your bag?
I almost broke my arm. It's so heavy.
That's why stretching is important.
[grunts]
Are you hiding something?
I'm not, okay?
Hey. Jong-hyun, open it.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. Hold on. Ugh!
[Seo-jin] Fuck me. Is this guy for real?
We should just toss it.
What the fuck are we doing?
I didn't realize
you're so scared, Sergeant.
This one's already dead.
That's what I'm saying.
What's the fucking point of all this?
What? Some kind of monster museum?
- Those monsters…
- [Seo-jin] Jeez.
The monsters just now.
You noticed it too.
[uneasy music playing]
Monsters don't recognize each other.
They never hunt as a group or go after…
a single target.
- Then what did we see?
- [Yeong-hu] Right.
Swarming all at once,
- like they were ambushing us.
- They were organized.
What? Are you saying
they set a trap for us?
Could've been they were trying
to protect their location.
[ominous music playing]
[clicking]
[epic suspenseful music rising]
[music fades]
[chuckling]
- [Chan-yeong gasps]
- [Ha-ni giggling]
[Chan-yeong gagging]
[gulps, grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Ha-ni giggling]
[retching]
[sighs]
Shit.
[Ha-ni giggling]
Oh. Shit, really?
What's that?
[Ha-ni giggling]
[gasping, grunts]
It's bitter. Just chew it.
No swallowing and don't spit.
I'm good.
I don't want anything from you.
Take his ass out of here before he dies.
[sniffs]
This is the cure?
Could you tell me
what I'm feeding him at least, huh?
What? You're worried I'm gonna poison
a dying bastard?
[Eun-yu] Open up.
Chew it.
- [muffed grunt]
- Just shut up and chew.
[grunts]
[retching]
[giggles]
[light suspenseful music playing]
Move out.
Look how quickly everything changed.
[Dr. Lim] Hey, wait.
It's been only a year.
How can it change this much in a year?
[Yeong-hu] Nature always finds a way.
What do you mean, sir?
With humans gone,
nature's starting to heal.
[Dr. Lim grunts]
Clear.
- Seok-chan.
- Yes, sir, what is it?
[Yeong-hu] Does doing that help?
As much as anything, I guess.
Think we're okay, sir?
[sighs]
Why are you asking me?
Why don't you ask your higher power, man?
I thought I was doing just that, Sergeant.
Don't ask me, jackass.
[Yeong-hu] You'll be coming with me,
Dr. Lim.
Seok-chan, you too.
Yes.
- Understood.
- What, we're not all going together?
That's a little scary.
Just a bit.
Seo-jin, take the men
and go find Yong-seok, all right?
On it.
Whoever's first, meet up with the other.
Hey, Seo-jin.
Watch your back and stay alive.
Go.
Which way are we heading?
To my sector over there.
The research laboratory?
Are you good in a pinch?
Killing monsters and all that?
Let's hope you are.
'Cause God knows what's waiting in here.
Let's move.
[suspenseful music playing]
You're always drawing that house.
Mm. It's my house.
Have they said when we can go home?
I'm missing my house.
Not right now.
I hope that we can, eventually.
It's taking forever.
You won't go back.
[Jin-ok] Yeong-su.
It's all a bunch of lies.
And doesn't lying make us monsters
like Jun-il's mom?
[Seon-hwa] You're being bad,
Yeong-su, huh?
You should stop trying so hard to be good.
You might end up dead.
- Kim Yeong-su.
- Don't touch me!
Why should I listen
to what you have to say?
You're not even my real mom!
Why do you even bother with that kid?
I really don't wanna hear it.
Do me a favor and get out.
[Jin-guk]
I don't think they're doing much better.
You think so?
I just hope this search is uneventful,
if you know what I mean.
- What do you mean?
- What do you mean, what do you mean?
You could bring the ceiling down
looking for ants.
Even a little house can fall apart.
A place this massive?
Jesus, God knows.
You're exaggerating, come on!
And if we work hard, we might get
a little something extra.
Come on.
You're going for it?
[Jin-guk whispers]
No reason not to.
Seriously.
[Jin-guk]
You don't have to do right, Ye-seul.
Why are you still working so hard, huh?
The Chief already takes good care of you.
Just trying to do my part, you know.
Just doing what I can,
not to embarrass her.
Ah! Ye-seul, your heart's just as…
- beautiful as you are.
- [sighs]
Sir.
Whoa, hey, now, I'm no "sir," okay?
I'm around your age, Ye-seul.
And how old is that?
Uh, well…
What is this? Do you like me?
Uh, well, I can't say I don't…
There isn't one guy here
who isn't crushing on you.
The thing is…
it's not mutual.
There's no chance.
Not even if hell rose.
Even if the world ended.
[annoyed sigh]
[scoffs]
- Wow, jeez, I mean…
- [loud bang]
What was that?
[banging continues]
[thumping]
[screeching]
- [snarling]
- [banging]
[banging continues]
- [heavy footsteps]
- [snarling]
[silence]
- [loud bang]
- [screams]
[suspenseful music playing]
Ye-seul.
Help me, would you?
You're the only one I can trust.
Hmm?
[soft radio static]
The search party sent a signal?
Yes, sir. They arrived
at Bamseom now it seems.
Can we make contact?
They're too far, sir. It'll be difficult.
[sighs]
Report back if you receive another signal.
Yes, sir. Understood.
[radio static]
What? What's this?
- What is it?
- [gasps]
[static]
[beeping]
[buzzing]
[devices beeping]
[uneasy music playing]
EMERGENCY
WARNING
DANGER
[beeping continues]
Something's jamming our signal, sir.
[Jin-guk] I'm sure of it.
I'm telling you, I heard it.
Inside the walls.
It was… It sounded like a monster.
You can tell Master Sergeant Tak.
Oh, yeah.
Sir. Uh…
Whoa.
[devices beeping]
This seems like…
Sir, it seems…
there's a creature here
inside the stadium.
[tense ominous music playing]
[alarm blaring]
[rattling]
[Jin-ho] Sir?
There's…
- a monster signal here.
- [Dong-jun] What the…?
[radio static]
[buzzing]
Damn.
[clanking]
What's going on here?
Emergency roll call.
If you'll follow us to the plaza.
I'll head over.
Ma'am, right now, I mean.
We're here on orders
from the Master Sergeant.
Did you find an exit then?
[Dong-jun] No, ma'am.
We think there might be
a monster in the building.
[foreboding music playing]
[alarm blaring]
[indistinct chatter]
They had this room
full of monster detectors,
and "beep, beep" all at once, like crazy!
So it's for real?
[people gasping]
Were you there, man? Huh?
Did you see it yourself?
Hey, if it wasn't for me,
we'd all be monster chow.
[indistinct chatter]
[cheers and applause]
Ugh, Jesus. This man makes me sick.
[Yeong-su] Me too.
Why are you alone?
You ran away?
Look who's talking.
That's different.
We had a spat, that's all.
God, you really are the opposite of cute.
[people murmuring]
As I got older,
I realized… it's all my fault.
When the adults tell you to do something,
there's a good reason for it.
So, apologize to your mother.
That's too bad. She's long gone.
What the…
Too bad you can have more than one.
You can even have two,
or even three, okay?
And Ms. Jin-ok is your mother.
Little brat.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [gate opens]
- [man] Chief!
- [indistinct chatter]
Wha-what's going on?
- Is the monster in here?
- Hurry up and kill it.
This wouldn't happen
if Crow Platoon was doing its job.
[people gasping]
[people clamoring in fear]
[tense music playing]
[people screaming]
Today's monster incident will get resolved
by Crow Platoon in due time.
No one can escape from this.
[In-hwan]
This is the nature of our catastrophe.
Family, friends,
lovers, we all had to watch
people we care about die.
And that won't be the last time.
So keep your guard up
in order to maintain our safe haven here.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[In-hwan] Hang on
and fight with everything you've got
instead of just asking others
for their help.
If you don't strengthen your mind,
you're going to end up consumed.
From now on,
those with symptoms who hide it from us
will have to face immediate judgment.
We request your cooperation
to avoid that.
Good God. What… what's he getting at?
Sounds like if we're sick,
they're gonna execute us.
They just declared
a reign of terror just now.
Hey, about the detectors earlier.
[Gi-chun] So what? Did they find it
or are they still looking, huh?
Are we safe then?
Ah, they handled it, I'm sure.
[clapping]
What a rousing speech.
But it's missing something.
You should stop hiding behind your men
and lead by example.
Won't you, Master Sergeant Tak?
[tense music playing]
Master Sergeant Tak?
Sir, you don't have to do this.
[tense music rising]
[light switch clicks]
[people exclaiming]
[scared whimper]
Shit.
[people clamoring]
There's no time to lose.
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[clanking]
- Does this look right?
- I think so.
I noticed
you haven't asked what we're looking for.
You're not curious?
Is it for your research?
[Yeong-hu] If that's all I need to know,
then I don't need to know.
I just need to make sure
we fulfill our objectives.
If it's important…
couldn't someone have taken it already?
[grunts]
They wouldn't find it.
I hid it very, very well.
You sure are confident.
[Dr. Lim] Of course.
What we're looking for…
isn't really a thing.
Oh, shit.
[bats chittering]
[Seo-jin] It smells crazy in here.
Jesus Christ!
The smell might get us first.
[creaking]
Stop.
[door creaks]
Something's here.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door creaks, bangs]
- [Seo-jin] U-seok!
- [banging on door]
[Jong-hyun] U-seok!
[banging continues]
[squelching]
[Seo-jin] U-seok!
U-seok!
[Jong-hyun] Oh, shit.
[creaking]
[ominous music playing]
You fucking bastards.
From this point on,
kill everything on fucking sight.
What the…?
What… How did it…
Doctor, I need you to fall back.
[Seo-jin] Yeong-hu.
Yeong-hu.
They got U-seok.
[static]
[Seo-jin] Yeong-hu. Yeong-hu!
Seo-jin, what's your status?
[static]
Come in. What's your status?
[Yeong-hu] Sergeant Min!
[suspenseful music playing]
[squelching]
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[Seo-jin] U-seok?
U-seok?
What are you doing, man?
U-seok, wake up, man.
U-seok, talk to me. U-seok!
Hey!
Wake up, man! Hey!
Answer me! Okay?
Talk to me.
Man!
Grab on. Grab on!
[grunting]
U-seok. U-seok!
Sarge! Sir, we have to…
[grunts]
- [Jong-hyun] We have to go!
- [grunting]
[Jong-hyun] We have to…
He's already dead, sir. We have to go.
U-seok's already dead, sir!
[Seo-jin grunting]
[both grunt]
- U-seok.
- Jesus!
Pull yourself together, sir. Please!
- U-seok. U-seok!
- Oh, fuck!
[both grunting]
[groaning]
- We have to go.
- U-seok…
Fuck.
- U-seok.
- Snap out of it!
- Please.
- [squelching]
- [Jong-hyun screaming]
[squelching]
[ominous music playing]
[Yeong-hu] Sergeant Min.
Sergeant Min, answer me.
Fuck.
Hey, Seok-chan, tell the men…
[ominous music playing]
Fuck.
They were monsters.
- The monsters are changing.
- [Seok-chan] Are you saying…
these were all monsters?
[epic suspenseful music playing]
Shit.
Don't touch anything.
Do you need a reminder?
Are you telling me
I have to leave this behind?
Why would I?
I'm just telling you
not to compromise the mission.
[sighs]
Sergeant.
This is how things are.
If you truly want something,
you have to be ready to make sacrifices.
I know you know this, Sergeant.
I know this is what you signed up for.
I need you to get this through your head,
do you hear me?
My men are not expendable,
but you just might be.
So you're saying that I can just
look at them from a distance?
Look but don't touch?
- [Dr. Lim] Oh, seriously?
- [Yeong-hu] We're finding your lab.
Is something wrong, sir?
[sighs]
I think something happened to the others.
They're not answering comms.
We need to find them right away.
- Let's go.
- You're not suggesting we leave now.
I can't do that.
I'm not going anywhere.
I can't leave this place empty-handed.
Then what are you suggesting, Doctor, huh?
Are you gonna stay behind?
Okay, okay. I get it. Sheesh.
Look…
I mean, I'll only slow you down
right now, so…
I'll wait out there
once I'm finished in here.
- Sounds risky.
- [Dr. Lim] I'm telling you, I'll be fine.
Well, now what?
Don't you have men you need to rescue?
Very well then.
Let's go.
Recover the asset and make sure
you don't touch anything else on the way.
Am I clear?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry. I'm a coward.
I won't try anything. Now go.
Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
- I'm fine, thanks.
- Huh?
No, careful, you'll fall.
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
So, which is it?
A brother? A boss? A dad?
What are you to each other?
Why the hell does it matter?
You just eat and get lost.
Um, why don't you come back with us?
You'll be safer there.
[soft gasp]
Are we getting married then?
Uh, that's… that's not what I'm saying.
Safe? You guys have just been lucky.
That, or you don't know better.
I think you might be underestimating
some of us.
I don't trust humans, okay?
I'm not surprised.
[Eun-yu]
But you don't trust monsters either?
And what about her?
- [Ha-ni giggles]
- You trust her?
Sure seems like it.
Let's go with them.
Let's go together, teacher, hmm?
Hey, let's go.
[tense sting]
What are you doing here?
[gunshot]
[Eun-yu sighs]
Please help.
This was the only place I could turn to.
How did she get like this?
And the kid? The girl who left with you?
First, get her inside.
- [Chan-yeong] Give me a hand.
- [Ha-ni] Okay.
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
Don't, sir!
You dare come crawling out here?
[Eun-yu] Stop it.
Stop, please.
I thought I was clear.
Don't bring any damn monsters here.
Why don't we talk this out?
- He's the person she's been looking for.
- Does that thing look human to you?
[suspenseful music playing]
Take one fucking step,
move a single muscle,
- and I'll cut her fucking head off.
- [scoffs]
Way to prove my point about humans.
Pulling this shit
after I saved your life is rich.
[Eun-yu] I said I'll take him with me.
I said I'll take him,
so just… what's your problem?
You're with monsters,
that makes you a threat.
And you call yourself human? Jesus.
[Eun-yu] What makes you special?
How are you sure you're gonna stay immune?
What if you were
to start showing symptoms?
Seems a bullet is your only option.
Since monsters have to die.
Stop it.
[breathing shakily]
And her?
Could you put a bullet in her?
[pensive music playing]
How about I save you the trouble?
Oh, yeah. So this is who you are.
- [Hyun-su] Stop it.
- [Ha-ni grunts]
Don't do this, Eun-yu.
Ha-ni.
[breathing shakily]
Let's get out of here.
You're just gonna stand there?
In this life, we weren't meant to be,
maybe the next one.
Get rid of the girl though.
[soft chuckle]
- [car engine starts]
- [car door closes]
Are you okay to move?
How's your shoulder?
It's okay.
I think we'd better go.
Monsters might have heard the gunfire.
Let's go.
Hypocrite.
Goddamn coward.
Are you going to say
you had no choice again?
You're just running from the truth.
You've been screwing up every decision
one after another.
[banging on door]
[banging continues]
[people clamoring, screaming]
[ominous music playing]
[boy crying]
[intense music playing]
[crying continues]
[In-hwan] Aren't you gonna protect them?
[In-hwan's son] Dad!
DAD
HELP ME
Help me!
[In-hwan]
Does this look like protection to you?
[In-hwan's son] I'm scared.
[In-hwan] Just come clean.
[In-hwan's son] Dad!
[In-hwan] Just tell everyone
that the monster in the stadium is you.
[In-hwan laughing]
[banging on door]
[Dong-jun] Sir?
Sir, may I come in?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Dong-jun] Sir? We have a problem.
Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[music swelling]
[closing theme music playing]