37 HOURS AGO
How is Hyun-su?
Doesn't remember anything.
Are you sure, though?
No, I'm not entirely sure.
If he doesn't remember
anything that happened,
I hope all his other negative memories
were gone as well.
I don't think he'd want that, you know.
If his memories of the past are lost,
he could potentially transform
into a monster.
Ji-su.
I have a request for you.
What do you need?
I don't think I'll be able to stay
with you all for much longer.
And when that happens, I want you to...
safeguard this place.
Protect Eun-yu
and everyone.
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
Make a left here.
GREEN HOME APARTMENTS
Damn it!
Why the hell are we returning here?
This is absurd!
Have you completely lost it?
What are you trying to do here?
Let's just go back.
Where to?
What?
You saw for yourself.
Did it look safe to you back there?
Is there even such a thing as a shelter?
If there is, why won't you tell us
where it is then?
It's because I don't know
if you pose a threat.
Anybody out there could be infected.
It's not like you're immune
to monsterization.
You never know who, when, or how someone
could become a monster.
Flat tire.
We can't go any further.
Wait for me here. I won't take long.
I'll be right back.
He may no longer be the Lee Eun-hyeok
that you remember.
You're wrong.
He promised me he would return, so...
He said he'd return no matter what.
So till I see him with my own two eyes,
that only then...
I won't believe anything or anyone.
Oh, fuck. Fuck!
Think this through.
It's a mistake to do this to us.
Is that a threat?
I've got nothing to lose.
And I'm the one with the gun.
Goddamn it.
GREEN HOME
THE HOLY BIBLE
GREEN HOME RULES OF SURVIVAL
QUARANTINE THE INFECTED
SURVIVORS, TURNING, DEAD
TURNING: LEE EUN-HYEOK
I'll come back.
Don't worry about me.
I'll come back safely.
Just kill them.
Without them, we'd just be considered
innocent survivors.
So let's just kill them both and go back.
It's as simple as that!
Choose wisely.
Don't you want the vaccine?
You mean, a vaccine exists?
He's right. It does say here
that they're working on a vaccine.
You people took Hyun-su away.
That means you can make a vaccine now.
There's not enough for everyone.
But someone who saved a soldier
might get it, though.
- Hey! Hey! What do you think you're doing?
- I'm not gonna fucking die like this!
Drop the gun!
Drop it!
You bitch!
Look at me! Come here, come here!
You little bitch.
Get up! Get up! Get the fuck up, bitch.
Come here.
Follow me. Come here, you fucking bitch!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you, you fucking bitch!
Come here. Come here. Bitch!
- What are you doing, you son of a bitch?
- I think you should see this, sir.
See what? They're all fucking dead.
These people...
they're Crow Platoon.
They're still warm, sir.
It hasn't been long.
There seems to be...
a monster in the vicinity.
Tie them all up.
We're heading back to camp.
Even the survivors, sir?
You think these assholes
look like survivors?
I wanna kill all of them
but I'm holding back.
They'll live if they're lucky.
But if they die, that's their fate, right?
I helped you, sir. You know that.
- Please take me.
- Get the fuck off of me!
I'm begging you!
Please!
You heard me!
Tie them up and get in!
What the hell are you doing?
Do you want to die with them?
The knot should come off easily.
As soon as we leave,
you need to find a place to hide.
Uh, Ms. Im?
What's wrong with Ms. Im, huh?
I guess she became a monster.
What the hell is that?
Holy shit, I'm fucking sick and tired
of these monsters.
I'll see you in hell, bitch.
Oh, shit.
Why did you do that, sir?
I'm just doing my job.
That was a human being.
That's it.
This thing was a monster
because I said so.
And that's the end of it.
Monster, monster, monster, monster...
It's a monster. It's a monster.
Hurry.
So what if you're human?
Do I even care?
Come on, Sarge.
We are at war here.
Humans have to win this battle.
And we'll kill every last one.
Go to hell. You deserve to die!
Let go of me. Huh?
Are you trying to murder us all?
- Crow One. We got a man down.
- Here, this way. Hurry.
- Requesting medical support.
- Move it!
Hurry!
Patient's status is critical.
Requesting immediate support.
Third floor's clear.
Entering the fourth floor.
Minimize the station.
Rescue the Third Platoon and extract.
On your six! Monster!
Open fire! Open fire!
This is Crow Four.
The monster's down, and we got
five injured men, two dead.
Third Platoon, extract the entry team.
Join the main element with the wounded.
Recon, do we have eyes
on the Second Platoon?
You see anything?
The building is blocking the view.
Can't get a visual on target, sir.
Come down.
Moving to their location.
We're not going, sir.
Hey, UDT, pack your things up now.
We're going back to base.
What the hell are you doing?
They're all too worn out, man.
They're wounded, starving,
and half asleep.
Our vehicles have broken down,
and we're running low on ammo.
Have you not heard?
Then what?
We desert the Second Platoon?
Yeah, I'm done.
We have to leave now.
Troops in the Second Platoon
are all but dead.
Let's at least save these ones.
Hey, Seok-chan.
Yes, Sergeant. Kang Seok-chan.
Six hours ago,
what did Central Command tell us?
They told us to return to base forthwith.
Sir, you are defying a direct command.
Men who aren't UDT, you can come too.
When I return to base, I'll take
full responsibility for my defiance.
The question really is,
how will you take responsibility
for yours, Sergeant?
Shoot me, sir.
Either way, your obsessive devotion
will eventually lead to our demise.
Shoot me.
Like you did to your own flesh and blood.
UDT and wounded men,
return to base with Sergeant Kim.
Let's go.
Hey, help me.
That was Ms. Im back there, right?
I think so, yeah.
That lady, she was the mother
from Room 1504, wasn't she?
Yeah.
Didn't you say
she turned into a monster, though?
You said it yourself back there.
Yeah, she did.
You think she was resisting it
like Hyun-su did?
Oh, you're right.
Did you see her eyes?
It didn't turn black or anything.
They just seemed like normal human eyes.
In case you didn't notice,
she was also butt-naked.
You call that a person? It was a monster.
Well, Ms. Im is a nice monster!
She even protected us!
There's no such thing as a good monster.
They all deserve to die.
No, they don't!
They don't! You're wrong!
Disrespectful little brat.
Don't talk to him like that. He's a child.
Excuse me. Ma'am, are you okay?
Hey, Ji-su.
Ji-su, are you okay?
I'm far from okay, thanks to you.
This time, you put us in a lot of danger.
Eun-yu.
We didn't make it this far
because we're lucky
or better than the others.
Others gave their lives
so we can make it out alive.
Don't let that be for nothing.
I'm really sorry,
but I'm never giving up.
I haven't seen him for myself.
So, to me, Eun-hyeok is still alive.
And I'm gonna keep looking for him
whatever the cost.
Oh! Oh!
What... What is it?
What is this? What's this?
Why... why are you stopping? Why?
There's a survivor.
God, no. You don't plan
on letting him on, do you?
Please, we can't do that.
My mission is to provide
survivors with a safe ride to the shelter.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Do you really have to do everything
by the book?
I'm scared, okay?
We can't just put ourselves at risk.
- Don't try to be a hero.
- All right, all right, all right.
She's right. Let's just go, please?
We'll keep this a secret.
No one will ever find out.
Oh, God. Let's just go.
No one will know.
I will, won't I?
Oh, well, I... No.
Where are we going?
Our final stop is the shelter.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT BUREAU
So we meet at last.
Thank you for coming all the way here,
Cha Hyun-su.
What, uh...
do I have to do now?
You'll find out soon enough.
I take it you're willing to cooperate?
Yeah.
If it means we can...
put an end to all this.
All right, Cha Hyun-su.
I believe in you.
Type Red.
They show aggressive behavior
toward blood.
Show us
that you're the true savior
who can put a stop to this destruction.
Begin the first experiment on MH-5.
So you're telling me that
MH-6 here was the special infectee
- who captured MH-5?
- Yes, sir.
But he died of gunshot wounds?
Are you sure he's dead?
He doesn't have any
vital signs and I've double-checked.
I mean, it's definitely a monster,
so how is it dead?
Could it be something
similar to what we have with MH-1?
MH-1 didn't die,
but it also had no vital signs
as a monster.
Extract whatever you can from the blood,
bone marrow, skin tissue,
and pituitary gland.
We'll have to do some tests
to compare with the samples from MH-1.
In any case, MH-5 should be arriving soon.
Make sure that we're prepared.
This could be our last chance
to solve this.
We need to aggregate all the data,
experience, and test findings
from MH-6 and MH-1
to further investigate MH-5.
What are you doing? Come on.
Muster up your strength, Cha Hyun-su.
I know you can do this. Come on.
Stop!
I order you to stop!
I just... I don't want to hurt anymore.
Help me.
Don't do this.
He's human.
He's human, please.
Don't do this!
Was it you
the voice telling me to cooperate?
Was that your voice?
Why did you kill him?
Why the hell did you kill him?
He was just in agony.
He wasn't a threat, whatsoever!
You didn't have to execute him.
I simply disposed of a test subject
that has served its purpose.
You killed him because he was a monster?
'Cause monsters deserve to die?
What makes you different
from these monsters?
You think you're better?
That bastard would go into a frenzy
at the slightest sight of blood.
Did you know that he killed
dozens of troops?
But after a brief battle with you,
he abruptly seized attacking.
Until today, no monster
had ever self-regulated its behavior
in such a manner.
It's a breakthrough.
You...
What did you do to him?
I know you did something to it.
I don't know what happened.
If you don't, who does?
Try to remember
that you were brought here
for that reason.
Answer me first and I will.
Can you use me to...
develop a vaccine or a cure?
I saw the flier that said you could
make a vaccine using special infectees.
Is that why you turned yourself in?
- Is it true?
- We've already made one.
Though it's all gone now.
Then why don't you
use me to make it again, Doctor?
You might end up dead, though.
Are you okay with that?
I wouldn't have stepped foot in here
if I wasn't.
What I meant is, you'll probably
end up begging us to kill you.
You should know better than anyone
the regenerative abilities of the MHs...
which I see is a blessing, are nothing
more than a curse to you people.
Monster humans are creatures
who have been denied
the beautiful relief of death.
Decent name, don't you think?
I came up with it.
Call me whatever you want to.
MH, monster, creature.
I couldn't care less.
I'm sure you'll do well unlike the others.
I get the feeling we're about to witness
the birth of a very special MH, you see.
Get plenty of sleep.
Starting tomorrow, it won't be easy.
The alarm will go off
if you get it wrong again.
Ms. Seo Yi-kyung?
This is the C5 research facility.
Follow me.
Where would that be?
Do you know me?
Ah.
I don't believe we've met,
but I've heard about you.
I'm Sang-won's friend.
Are you coming or not?
Why are you helping me?
Guess I've grown attached.
He's headed to research.
Come on, time's up. Let's go.
Damn it.
So you are still here.
In this...
sorry state.
How'd you get in here, anyway?
It can't have been easy getting this far,
but I doubt you'll be able to talk to him.
I highly doubt it.
But then again, who knows?
He might talk to his fiancée.
Were you waiting for me?
In statistical terms, the truth is dark.
Wouldn't you rather live
in blissful ignorance instead?
Are you sure
you want to see him?
Even if he's a monster?
Ms. Seo Yi-kyung, I have to see
how Sang-won will react
to your reunion.
It's a rare unique stimulation, you know.
You crazy motherfucker.
What brings you soldiers
all the way down here?
Mr. Soldier?
What is it?
I can't pee because I'm too scared.
There's nothing wrong with how I look.
Nothing's wrong with my face.
I'm pretty.
How do I look?
I said, "How do I look?"
Do I look pretty?
Do I?
Mister...
There's something wrong with your face.
What's wrong with my face, huh?
Take a good hard look.
Don't like my face?
Get out.
Get out!
Don't shoot my face.
Fucking shit.
Where's my face?
My face...
My damn face!
I'm not pretty!
Am I pretty?
You are hideous as hell.
My face, my face, my face!
No, no, my face!
Not... not my face!
Su-yeong, why won't you wake up?
Su-yeong!