[theme music playing]
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
- [Jae-jin grunting]
- [squelching]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Check out these new hands.
[grunts, panting]
Look, I have hands now.
[chuckles]
You should go.
Huh?
He told me to kill you.
[tense music playing]
[Chi-seong]
But I don't want your blood on my hands.
Consider it...
the final act of kindness
I'm making toward you.
[scoffs]
[Jae-jin]
But I did everything he told me to do.
And you saw me do it.
[exhales deeply]
[Jae-jin scoffs]
You said we were a team.
[breathing shakily]
You even said that I was one of you.
If you keep talking...
I'm gonna go through with it.
[exhales sharply]
He's gonna abandon you too, you know?
[Jae-jin laughing]
- [laughing continues]
- [somber music playing]
- [loud banging]
- Fuck!
[grunts]
[laughing continues]
[electricity crackling]
[screams]
[blasts, crackling]
- [people murmuring]
- [electricity buzzing]
[Cheol-yong] What happened?
- What is this?
- [man 1] Oh, my God! What's going on?
[Cheol-yong] Why did the lights go out?
[murmuring continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
Is this part of the plan?
No, but we'll use it to our advantage.
[Dong-jun] Master Sergeant Tak!
We have to leave now.
Evacuate everyone as quickly as possible.
- What's going on?
- More people are showing symptoms.
But there are so many...
that we can't count them all.
[paper rustling]
[In-hwan] Safely evacuate
as many survivors as you can.
I'll see you outside.
To your posts.
[Dong-jun] Let's go.
[people clamoring]
[suspenseful music continues]
[walking cane thumping]
[fire crackling]
[music fades]
Ugh, what the hell is going on, huh?
[sighs]
Did you kidnap me?
[Dr. Lim sighs]
[Dr. Lim] Huh?
[tense music rises]
You must be Sang-won's daughter.
Not much resemblance, huh?
[Dr. Lim] What am I supposed to do here?
[chuckles]
Hello.
You wanna shake hands?
Huh?
It's nice to meet you.
You said it's through pain?
[tense music continues]
The only way to free myself
from this body, right?
[Dr. Lim exhales softly]
[Sang-wook]
I think you're right about that.
Pain can...
give me renewed life.
[music swells]
So let's test your theory out.
[inhales sharply]
I think it'd be painful to watch you die.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[breathes shakily]
[Sang-wook] What's wrong?
This isn't what you had in mind?
Uh, I think there's been
some kind of misunderstanding.
[music swells]
I'm here to help you, all right?
[indistinct whispers]
Yeah, since when?
Are you sure
you haven't been using me this whole time?
[music swells]
You thought I couldn't tell?
[tense music playing]
[Sang-wook] I wonder how far down it is.
- [squelches]
- [groans]
[groans]
[intense music playing]
[groaning]
[loud groan]
[Dr. Lim groans, chokes]
[groans, gasps]
[Dr. Lim coughing, gasping]
[groaning in pain]
[glass shattering]
- [sizzling]
- [Dr. Lim] Why's it gotta be you?
Why is it you and not me?
[Dr. Lim wheezes, coughs]
I wanted it more...
[grunts, coughs]
I should've been a monster!
[breathing shakily]
Why?
I told you.
I'm the chosen one.
[Dr. Lim breathes shakily]
Do it to me.
[breathing shakily]
Please.
[Dr. Lim] Do it now.
[coughing, grunting]
[gasping]
Do it.
[Dr. Lim groaning weakly]
Do it now.
[coughs, gasping]
Turn me into one, please!
- [squelches]
- [groans]
[Dr. Lim coughs, gasping]
I want... Please!
[coughs]
I want to see it!
I want to see it too!
[intense music playing]
[Dr. Lim] I wanna find out...
how it looks...
[grunting]
...when I become a...
[Sang-wook] My friend.
You don't deserve it.
[screaming]
I want... I want to see it!
Please, I want to see it!
[music intensifies]
[screaming]
[flames roaring]
[mournful choral music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[electricity crackling]
[woman sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[electricity crackling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobbing continues]
[whimpering]
[Ye-seul sniffles]
[Ye-seul sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[music subdues]
[whimpering]
[pensive music playing]
[sobbing]
You're okay.
Come with me.
[sobbing continues]
[suspenseful percussive music playing]
[objects rattling]
[Sang-wook] Chi-seong.
Did you get rid of those two?
[Chi-seong] Yes.
Okay, good job.
[ominous choral music playing]
I think your work here is done.
[Chi-seong gags]
- [thuds]
- [Chi-seong grunts]
[Chi-seong screams]
[dramatic music playing]
Okay, time to go.
[music subdues]
We're almost there. I promise.
[ominous music playing]
[squelching]
[eerie music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
- [squelching]
- [grunts]
[dramatic music continues]
[eerie music playing]
[soft chuckle]
[music fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
[electricity crackling]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Hyun-su] It's empty in here too.
The blood splatter looks abnormal.
[Eun-hyeok] It's safe to assume
it was a special infectee.
I'm certain they were in here.
Are you gonna apologize?
[Ye-seul]
Why'd you leave without saying anything?
When did you get back?
Did you get hurt?
[sighs]
Did you leave with Lee Eun-yu?
Never mind. I don't wanna know.
Don't tell me.
You're still alive.
That's what matters.
I apologize for leaving
without telling you.
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps]
[tense ominous music playing]
[Ye-seul] Chan-yeong.
[Ye-seul breathes shakily]
She's a monster.
[Ye-seul breathing shakily]
[breathing shakily]
[electricity crackling]
They're all symptomatic.
They're acting strange, aren't they?
Because they were infected
against their will.
[electricity crackling]
[Eun-hyeok] Let's split up.
What?
Whoever finds him first deals with him.
You're scared to be alone?
I'm not. I'm just worried about you.
I don't wanna have to deal
with your corpse.
Where'd you learn to smile like that?
A photo.
[sighs]
It's creepy.
[electricity crackling]
[eerie music rises]
[music fades]
What took you so long?
[uneasy music playing]
Are you...
Are you okay?
[eerie music playing]
I think so.
Where's Yi-kyung?
Have you found her yet?
Yeah, I have.
Where is she now?
I'll take you to her.
[suspenseful ominous music playing]
[music intensifies]
[music swells, fades]
[people coughing]
All three groups are accounted for, sir.
Where's Jin-ho?
I told him to go ahead of us
to check the exits.
He'll be back soon.
Okay.
- Let's get going.
- [both] Yes, sir.
Crow Platoon, move out.
All right, listen up, everyone.
We gotta get moving.
Follow us. Let's go.
Take your positions.
[Dong-jun] Move out.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hold on for a little longer, okay?
Yong-seok...
[somber music playing]
...held on till the very last breath.
FOR HIV/AIDS
[somber music continues]
[sniffles]
I think that someone is missing.
Are you sure everyone's been evacuated?
[Yeong-hu sighs]
Why don't you just worry
about yourself for now?
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[Seon-hwa] I don't need to evacuate.
I'll just surrender myself to the Lord.
But Yeong-jun...
Please let Yeong-jun go.
And let his soul be free.
[gate rattling loudly]
[Seon-hwa gasps]
[Seon-hwa breathing heavily]
Where's everyone gone?
Why are you alone?
I think... they all went home.
[gasps]
- [Seon-hwa breathing shakily]
- [sighs]
Were you...
waiting for me?
- [breathing shakily]
- Because you like me?
- Huh?
- [tense music rises]
That must be why you stayed.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sizzling]
[lighter clicks]
[growling in distance]
[running steps]
- [Seon-wha breathing shakily]
- [Gi-chun grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
- [Seon-hwa gasps]
- [thwacking]
- [Seon-hwa] No, don't!
- [thwacking continues]
[sobbing]
Stop it. No, don't!
Yeong-jun!
[breathing shakily]
[breathes heavily]
Stop that.
[breathing calmly]
Why are you here?
[sharp sigh]
What are you doing here?
Everyone else already left.
I was waiting for you,
so we could go together.
[Seon-hwa] Yeong-jun...
[people screaming in background]
I'm sorry for dragging you all this way.
You'll go all the way with me, won't you?
Where is it we're going?
[ominous sting]
[Seon-hwa] Wherever it may be.
[car engine revving]
[Peter] Hey, Seon-hwa, stop the car.
- Seon-hwa?
- [engine revving]
S-Seon-hwa!
- [tires screeching]
- [crashes]
[Seon-hwa sobbing]
Please!
Please, someone save my Yeong-jun!
Somebody please help us!
- [sobbing]
- [somber music playing]
Yeong-jun, I love you...
[Seon-hwa] Yeong-jun.
I'm sorry.
[breathing shakily]
[sniffles]
[groans]
Damn it.
[Peter] Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
[breathes shakily]
[muffled sobbing]
[Peter] Let's go now.
[flashlight switch clicking]
[ominous music playing]
[flashlight switch clicks]
[flashlight switch clicking]
[ominous sting]
[eerie music rises]
Sergeant.
[ominous sting]
[Yeong-hu] Sergeant?
[indistinct whispers]
Sergeant.
[In-hwan breathing heavily]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [flashlight switch clicks]
[exhales sharply]
How's the exit?
I can confirm, it's as marked on the map.
Good.
[breathing shakily]
Get going.
[music swells]
[blood splattering]
[Dong-jun] Sergeant!
- [In-hwan grunts]
- [Jin-ho] Sergeant!
[Yeong-hu] Round up the survivors
- and leave now!
- [In-hwan] Go!
[survivors screaming]
- [Yeong-hu] Get moving!
- [Dong-jun] Yes, sir!
[tense ominous music playing]
- [In-hwan grunting]
- [survivors yelping]
[blood splattering]
[screaming continues]
[Yeong-hu] Sergeant!
[ominous music intensifies]
Are you all right, sir?
[ominous sting]
[In-hwan breathing heavily]
[in deep voice]
You can't go.
I won't let you.
[In-hwan breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[survivors clamoring]
[Yeong-hu grunting]
I won't...
[breathing heavily]
[shouts]
Get out of the way!
[dramatic music playing]
[both grunting]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[electricity crackling]
OFFICE
[blasts]
[growling in distance]
[monsters growling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[bodies thud]
I wouldn't try to fight me if I were you.
[monsters growling]
[monsters gagging]
[body thuds]
[squelching]
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsteady footsteps]
[frost crackling]
Sergeant...
[In-hwan] Yeong-hu.
What kind do you think I'll turn into?
You've never been anything
other than a soldier to me.
You served to protect...
or to kill.
[In-hwan] How about a bomb?
At least that way,
I can be of use.
[soft chuckle]
[frost crackling]
[sharp sigh]
[crackling]
[solemn music playing]
[Hyun-su]
All the symptomatic people in there...
you did that to them, right?
[Yi-su] That's right. I did it to them.
What about it?
Haven't you ever wondered
what your mom was thinking...
when she came here?
Why would I ever...
think about that?
She didn't raise you
like you were a monster.
She raised you as a human.
That's the problem.
Why should a monster...
be raised as a human?
[tense music playing]
Yi-kyung...
Where is she?
She's dead.
I mean...
I killed her.
You keep blabbering on and on...
"Seo Yi-kyung, Seo Yi-kyung."
[dire music playing]
Aren't you here to see me?
[slowly]
Cha...
Hyun-su.
Long time no see.
- [Yi-su] Long time no see.
- [breathes shakily]
You're still in there, aren't you?
[scoffs]
[Hyun-su] I promise I'll get you out.
Just hold on.
Don't let him win.
[dire music continues]
[eerie music playing]
[soft gasp]
[dramatic suspenseful music playing]
[crackling]
- [crackles]
- [Hyun-su grunts]
- [grunts, pants]
- [crackles]
- [Hyun-su grunts, pants]
[ominous music playing]
You're pretty determined, aren't you?
Who the hell are you?
[soft chuckle]
Me?
Pyeon Sang-wook?
Jung Ui-myeong.
Seo Yi-kyung's fiancé.
This kid's father.
[soft chuckle]
Nam Sang-won, that's my real name.
[Sang-won inhales sharply]
Apparently, there's no resemblance.
You agree?
You think we look alike?
- [squeezing]
- [grunts]
I guess it doesn't really matter anyway.
I am her now,
and she is me.
Fuck you!
[grunts]
[grunts, breathing heavily]
I didn't realize you two were so close.
Where have you been this whole time?
[squeezing]
[Sang-won]
Does she really even need your help?
[choking]
The second time I caught her...
she hardly even fought it.
[soft chuckle]
[loud thump]
[blood squelching]
[tense music rises]
What the fuck?
[choking]
[dramatic music playing]
[music stops]
[Hyun-su screams]
- [Eun-hyeok grunts]
- [breathing heavily]
[sighs]
What? You still don't get it?
The special infectee,
it's right there.
I can't kill her like that.
- You're not able to?
- I won't kill her.
Either fight me or do what I say.
It's your fault we didn't finish the job.
[dramatic music playing]
[fire roaring]
[screaming]
[panting]
[dramatic music continues]
[soft chuckle]
Did you really think that would work?
[Hyun-su grunts]
[Hyun-su] No, not yet.
Just give me a little more time.
[music subdues]
I'm gonna force him out...
and I'm gonna kill him once and for all.
[Yi-su] But...
can you really do it?
I'm not acting alone anymore.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues]
Give it your best shot.
[dramatic ominous sting]
[closing theme music playing]