[theme music playing]
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
[baby crying]
[heartbeats]
SWEET HOME
[tense music]
[gun cocks]
I'm not going to shoot.
- Yi-kyung, it's me.
- Step away from the girl!
Come over here.
[Yi-kyung] Now!
Next time then.
Yi-kyung.
I'm not going in there.
And I don't need your help.
You didn't see anything.
Wait.
Wait a second.
I have to ask you something.
[Eun-yu] Wait!
Oh, God, wait. No.
Don't go. It's dangerous.
I told you I'll kill you
if you get in my way, didn't I?
[Chan-yeong groans]
[grunts]
[Jun-il's mother sighs]
My boy…
My beautiful boy.
Oh, God.
Mom, are you still hurting?
No, honey. No more hurting, my boy.
Right.
You're hurting
too much, Mom.
That's why I'm sad.
Right.
Uh, but I…
I'm all better now.
I don't cough up blood anymore,
and my insides no longer hurt.
Ah, here. I even got my teeth back.
I'm all better now.
Right, but, uh…
I have to help you, Mom.
No, I… I can do it.
Ju… Jun-il…
I can do it if you won't be sick anymore!
I… I…
got you your medicine.
HERBICIDE
Jun-il, this is…
That's right. You have to die, Mom.
So you won't hurt anymore.
What's gotten into you?
I'm all better now.
You say you got better,
and then you're not better anymore.
And then better, and then better no more.
And better.
It's always like that.
[Jun-il's mom]
Jun-il, what's wrong with you?
I told you, I'm all better now.
Mama.
You have to die, okay?
[Jun-il] I can do it
because I'm a good boy.
Jun-il, stop this right now.
Drink.
Jun… Jun-il, I…
- [Jun-il's mom grunts]
- Just drink it and be quiet.
[groaning]
[retching]
[thuds]
[ominous music]
Mom.
Mom?
Are you dead?
So you're no longer hurting, right?
[sniffles]
It's, uh,
all over now.
Good job.
[Jun-il's mom moans]
[Jun-il's mom whimpers]
Why won't you die?
Why… why won't you just die?
You'll only keep hurting if you don't die!
- [gate clanks]
- Die!
Die!
Die right now!
[Jun-il] Die!
Die!
[clattering]
[tense music]
[Jun-il's mom] Jun-il.
It must've been hard for you.
I'm so sorry.
- [grunts]
- [blood squelching]
[blood squelching]
[Jun-il grunts]
[metal clanks]
[growling]
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
Oh, damn it!
[screams]
Goddamn it!
[grunts]
You won't find her so late at night.
She's already--
[grunts]
Let go!
[grunting]
Let go of me!
I said let go, you--
Let…
[grunts]
Let go of me right now!
I finally met her.
I can't let her go like this. I can't.
So just stop.
I swear I'll kill you
if you ever follow me again.
Wait a second.
[tense music]
- [Eun-yu screams]
- [Chan-yeong grunts]
[Eun-yu grunts]
[Chan-yeong grunting]
[Eun-yu yelps]
[groans]
[both breathing heavily]
[Chan-yeong grunting]
Let go.
No way.
Let go or we'll both die.
Hold on tight!
I'll pull you up on three.
I'll push you off the wall. Hold on tight.
[panting]
[grunts]
- [leaves rustling]
- [branch snap]
- [Chan-yeong screams]
- [Eun-yu shrieks]
[both grunting]
[both groaning]
[Eun-yu whimpering]
[Chan-yeong grunts]
There's something at the bottom.
Be careful.
On three, I'll let you go, okay?
Stay close to the wall and push.
One, two, three.
[both grunt]
[grunts]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[In-hwan sighs]
[Dr. Lim] It's Oh Jun-il's doing.
I was just gonna give him
a little stimulus,
but I had no idea
he would explode like this.
The blood sample I got from him
showed signs of monsterization,
but he had no symptoms.
He showed all of the signs,
but he had no nosebleeds
and auditory hallucinations.
I should've taken this step by step.
The specimen was so hard to come by,
I got ahead of myself like an idiot!
That's enough.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
Huh?
[thuds]
[In-hwan]
Oh Jun-il came to see his mother.
After giving into monsterization,
the symptomatic individual
killed her son and went berserk.
The doctor who witnessed the scene
called in for help,
and the Crow Platoon subdued the monster.
Isn't that right?
It's like you didn't hear a thing I said.
Are you deaf or something?
You want me to go over it again?
Jun-il became a monster
without showing any of the symptoms.
So what?
So, he's a fringe case,
unlike any we've seen.
[sighs]
Monsterization is already
beyond our understanding.
When you dragged me out here,
and built me a fancy research facility,
I thought you might have
some grand design.
So what? It was all just an act?
You're only half correct.
So what have you been planning?
Let me in on the bigger picture here.
Why do you think I kept you alive, huh?
Because you represent hope.
Hope that humanity
hasn't thrown in the towel yet.
Hope that we may overcome this someday.
- Far from the truth.
- The truth is not what matters.
What matters is what people believe.
Don't shake their faith.
You don't want everything
to crumble, do you?
[flame whooshes]
Oh, fuck. Shit.
[unsettling music]
[Yi-kyung] Get in.
I came out to find him.
Aren't you coming?
I'm not going anywhere until I find him.
Then why did you go there?
Why did you go where there are people?
[sighs]
[pedals creaking]
[mouthing]
Don't.
[soft snarl]
[unsettling music]
[keys jangling]
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[Chief Ji]
Has it already been over a month?
Just hang in there.
We're almost there.
[Ye-seul] Mom?
Mom?
Did you sleep here?
I can tell from your face
you didn't sleep well.
What are your hands for?
Are they just for makeup?
Why didn't you knock?
What are you doing here?
I just…
I was just worried. I'm looking for you.
You can enter my room, but not here, okay?
That's a warning.
I'm serious.
Mm-hmm.
Go.
It's time for roll call.
[alarm chimes]
[In-hwan] The banishment of the infectee's
schedule today had been canceled.
The infectee was monsterized last night,
and the Crow Platoon subdued her.
Please do not be alarmed
and prepare for roll call.
That'll be all.
So, did you get her?
What?
- Yeah.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Seriously. We can all sleep safe and sound
all thanks to the platoon and all.
[chuckles nervously]
Is this really something
to get so psyched about?
Huh?
A person died.
[Seung-wan] Oh.
Uh, it was a monster, not a…
not a person, though.
[Seung-wan groans]
It's a fine line.
If this wound heals,
you'll end up becoming one of them.
Hey, let's go.
Right.
Shit.
Have you heard anything about this?
What was that all about?
No idea.
Maybe the guys on night shift
had a hand in it.
I doubt they would have kept it from us
if that was the case.
They love bragging about fresh kills.
Hey, if Sergeant Tak said it happened,
it happened.
It's not like he would make stuff up.
He could.
Hey.
Watch what you say, man.
Can't you see that we're being kept
out of the loop here, man?
I don't trust anyone
other than Sergeant Kim right now.
Well, now, you really hurt
my feelings, you prick.
- [Peter] Come confess your sins.
- Huh?
Nothing beats a good old confession
when you feel like talking
behind someone's back, after all.
[keys jangling]
What happened here?
We were supposed to let her go
this morning.
We were going to let her go
as soon as she saw Jun-il!
We don't exactly live in a world
where promises are kept.
[Chief Ji] The hell?
What happened?
What happened here? Damn it.
See this here?
This is Jun-il.
If I told you, would you believe me?
You said it yourself. You called me
the last person to be trusted.
[Dr. Lim chuckles]
You really do have
great insight, you know.
But why are you getting
so worked up over this?
You weren't even
all that close to her, no?
Right?
Huh?
Who am I even talking to?
[Seo-jin] What, a girl?
Yeah.
Know anything about her?
No.
Are you sure?
[sighs]
There's no way Yong-seok wouldn't have
told me, if that was the case.
Anyways, this means that
he didn't desert us just to run away.
In which case, we should go get him.
I'll get the boys.
- It hasn't been approved.
- Huh?
What do you mean?
I'm going to have a word
with Sergeant Tak.
- Hey, Seo-jin.
- [grunts]
[Seo-jin] What?
Don't tell me that you agree with him.
Of course not, we need to find Yong-seok.
So what's this about?
The Platoon only acts for the public good.
[scoffs]
Yong-seok didn't go missing.
He went AWOL from the unit all on his own.
As things stand, Yong-seok's case
is nothing more than a personal miss out.
So what, we just ditch him?
You said he'd be here.
You said we can return to find him, huh?
Hey!
I only returned because I believed
what you told me.
Had I known you'd pull this crap…
I would've stayed behind to look for him.
We could end up losing the rest of our men
if we go out in our current state.
And don't forget that Yong-seok
has the radio and the transmitter.
Let's talk about finding him
once we get a signal.
You're a goddamn coward.
How are you any different
from Sergeant Tak, hm?
- Fucking hell…
- [clattering]
Out of my way.
[scoffs]
[soldier] Sergeant Kim.
Park Chan-yeong is missing, sir.
That, and we ran into a problem
while calculating the roll call tally.
There must be an exit we don't know of.
[Yeong-hu sighs]
Round up a group of survivors
and do a full sweep of the stadium.
Block off the exit once you find it.
Yes, sir.
Do Sang-jin, An Dong-gi, Lee Eun-yu,
and Park Chan-yeong are missing, sir.
Did they miss the roll call?
Yes, all four of them have gone missing.
Do Sang-jin and An Dong-gi held a grudge
for the expedition ban.
Lee Eun-yu likely left
because she fell on hard times.
Since the main gate wasn't opened,
there should be another exit.
Once we find it, we'll block it off.
I see. Do just that.
Find the exit, cooperate with Chief Ji
to block it off.
- Make sure to keep an eye on them.
- Yes, sir.
Are you just going to let
that bastard Chan-yeong be?
We can take disciplinary action
once he's back.
What's Min up to?
He won't leave the barracks, sir.
Round up the men
and look for an exit first.
[Seok-chan] Yes, sir.
You're Sergeant First Class Kim, right?
Please, sir…
find Yong-seok.
[gate creaking]
[tense music]
Have you found it?
[In-hwan] We're still looking.
Then what business do you have here?
Hmm, three people
left the stadium yesterday.
Do you know where they might've gone
and why they escaped?
Are you accusing me of something?
I don't know.
I have no reason to.
[objects clank]
You said there was no other exit
aside from the main gate.
And now we're looking
for that nonexistent exit.
Master Sergeant Tak.
How many hours a day
do you monitor the cameras?
It seems you want to know anything
and everything that goes on around here,
but this desire to know everything
all on your own,
well, that's how dictatorships begin.
Not that you haven't gotten
started on that already.
[metals clanking]
Tell me, is there a word
for hoarding knowledge for oneself
while keeping others in the dark?
Putting everyone in danger?
I know you're an important figure
in this place, Chief.
However,
you can't just do
whatever you like, you know.
Are you threatening me?
Nope. Just requesting cooperation.
So, just let me know
if you ever decide to change your mind.
[tool thuds]
[clanks]
[tense music]
[Jin-guk] She's probably dead, right?
Who is?
The girl from that family.
[Gi-chun] Mm-hmm.
Aah, I'm talking about Lee Eun-yu.
Oh, well, you'll never know.
She's as tough as nails.
Ah, Jesus Christ,
they're causing us so much trouble.
Just pretend you're looking.
If the Crow Platoon can't find it,
how are we going to?
That reminds me.
I heard the Crow Platoon's
youngest member went missing.
Come to think of it.
It looked like, um,
they both knew each other.
Is that right?
Oh, well, then.
Now that you mention it,
there was something
about the way he looked at her.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh. Could it be love?
[chuckling]
Damn, crazy you can elope
in a world that's gone to crap.
And why would they need to do that, huh?
No one said dating is forbidden
once you're in the Crow Platoon.
[laughs]
Yeah, you're right.
Guess that rules out the eloping theory.
[Ye-seul] Of course they didn't elope!
Another day of my life having to put up
with stupid-ass nonsense like this.
I mean, why would you ship
Chan-yeong and that crazy bitch?
Uh, well, their disappearances
did coincide--
Ugh, just stop!
If I ever catch you
spouting that nonsense again,
I swear, you'll regret it.
Shit.
[stomping]
They so eloped.
They were running from that one.
All right. Knock it off.
Mom?
Mom!
- Mom!
- [doorknob rattling]
Ugh! Mom, where did Lee Eun-yu go?
Jesus!
Ugh!
[metal creaking]
[ominous music]
Damn, this is how they did it
in the movies.
[lock clatters]
[clanks]
- What are you doing?
- Huh? What?
Mom, you're here?
I heard a noise, so I thought
something might have happened to you.
I told you not to come here.
Oh, I forgot that.
[chuckles nervously]
I'm just upset about Park Chan-yeong
and Lee Eun-yu is all.
Sorry.
[gasps]
I've coddled you for far too long.
I also let you use my name
to hold it over others, but no longer.
You don't know when to stop.
- Mom…
- Go.
Go.
Uh-uh.
[whimpers]
- Leave!
- [yelps]
[sighs]
[hammer thuds]
[lock clanks]
Mom?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom, I made a mistake.
I won't do it again.
Mom, please don't abandon me.
Please, Mom, please don't abandon me! Mom!
[Eun-yu grunts]
[groans]
Shit.
[grunts]
Damn it, why'd you have to follow me?
I had to find out what you were hiding.
Since…
it could have put the stadium at risk.
Why risk your life to protect the stadium?
We just happen to be stuck there
out of necessity.
- Is it really that important to you?
- There's nowhere else to return to.
To the survivors,
the stadium is all they've got.
And protecting it
is the Crow Platoon's duty.
Whatever.
No skin off my back.
- You're the one asking for it.
- You also risked your life.
We're not so different, you and I.
[Chan-yeong grunts, groans]
Let me see.
[inhales sharply]
Lift it up.
I'm never gonna tell you.
[Chan-yeong] I know.
You believe hiding
is the right thing to do.
So hide it.
And for the finding out,
I can work on that.
[monster snarls]
[gasps]
[monster growls]
[monster snarls]
[monster shrieking]
[striking, crying]
The day Mr. Kim died…
What you saw that day…
Was it really a monster?
It wasn't human.
That's okay.
I'm still okay with that.
At first, I thought that
the monster had gotten you and Mr. Kim.
But no.
As it turned out,
Mr. Kim was the only one dead.
And you survived.
[monster growls softly]
Yeah, maybe so.
There's definitely something out there
protecting me.
Who is it?
I don't know.
They won't ever show themselves.
I just want to believe
it's a certain person, that's all.
And who would that be?
[sighs]
I just…
I just want to see him
one more time, that's all.
[Eun-yu sniffles]
But considering the lengths
to which he's going to avoid me,
I wonder if I should just let it go.
I'm sure he's got a good reason to do so.
[sighs]
But for me, I'm really,
really okay with it.
Just one more time.
[Chan-yeong] No.
You'll meet him again.
You will.
[somber music]
[rustling]
Who was that?
Is there someone out there?
What if it's a monster?
As if a monster would throw down a rope.
[suspenseful music]
Here, I've got you.
All right. One, two, three.
[Eun-yu grunts]
On my shoulder.
[both grunt]
[panting]
[grunts]
[ominous music]
[grunts, groans]
Help me up.
You're not going to leave me, are you?
[Eun-yu] Promise me.
What?
That you'll never chase after me, or…
or ask me questions.
I can't promise that.
This isn't up for debate.
I can't make a promise I can't keep.
Fine, damn it. Have it your way.
Grab on.
[grunts]
- [rope stretching]
- [grunts]
[grunting]
- Whoa!
- [groans]
[grunting]
- [monster snarls softly]
- Huh?
Hey.
[gasps]
Wait a minute.
Something's here.
Get up here! Hurry! Hurry!
[grunts]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
What is it?
[sniffs]
It's gasoline.
Move!
[snarling]
[shrieking]
[leaves rustling]
You're still alive?
Aren't those the moles from the stadium?
You remember me, right?
We shared a ride
on the bus to the shelter.
Of course, I do.
I almost died because of you.
Go back to where you live,
and stop poking your head
where it doesn't belong.
Hey, Dad.
Can't we ditch the foxy bitch
and raise the other one?
You want to take him and raise him?
- Uh-huh.
- What are you doing?
It's not like you can walk with that leg.
I don't want more mouths to feed.
You kids be on your way now.
She seems to have different ideas.
[both grunt]
What are you doing?
I got no reason to trust you.
Why would I free you?
[Ha-ni] Oh?
- [chuckles]
- Put that down while I'm asking nicely.
This?
You want this back?
Hmm? I'll trade you for it.
I want this guy.
Do you have rocks in your head?
Don't you understand English?
I told you to take him
and raise him all you'd like!
[Ho-sang] Hey.
You're gonna have to pay
for ruining my trap.
Jesus Christ, you've got to be kidding me.
I'll let you out tomorrow, and once I do,
feel free to never come back.
- [Ho-sang] Ha-ni.
- Hmm?
Let's go now.
I'm coming, boss.
- I'm coming.
- Untie me right now.
Untie me!
Hey!
[door closes]
[lock clicks]
Open the door right now! I'm leaving!
What difference does it make
whether I leave today or tomorrow, huh?
Damn it!
[grunting]
[panting]
Hey.
What?
Did you really mean what you said?
What you just told her.
To take me and raise me.
[grunts]
Just stop.
I'm losing it right now.
I'm definitely losing it.
[lid pops]
RUBBING ALCOHOL
It's not like I can make a difference now.
I'll only feel worse if I think about it.
But, uh…
Jun-il's monsterization…
It progressed way too quickly.
He didn't show any symptoms.
Ah, shit.
Stop thinking about it.
[groans]
Let's just…
Don't think about it.
Let's just not think about anything.
[sighs]
Could that scar have been what caused it?
Shit!
Wait.
GIRL, MOM, FLOWERS, TREE, STIMULATION
Let's see now. Damn it. Damn it.
[beeps]
[Dr. Lim] Don't you remember?
[Jun-il] Uh, a kid.
Jun-il…
[Jun-il] Flowers…
Just what did you see?
And… trees.
- Was it human?
- [Jun-il] There was a kid. A girl.
- She was a girl.
- A monster?
Uh, she… she pushed me.
Could it…
Mom?
[screaming]
- [Yi-kyung gasps]
- [grunts]
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you still afraid of me?
Because I hurt you back then?
Get inside.
No, I didn't do anything wrong.
I did it to protect you.
Protect? Really?
You?
Lies.
It's all lies.
You're no different from those people.
You…
ran into people again?
Did you use those hands…
turn them into monsters again?
[Kid] So what if I did?
They became nicer.
[gasps]
It happened again.
You did it again.
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it again?
That's why I locked you up,
for your own sake!
I did it so you couldn't do something
like that again!
Let go of me!
No!
[grunts]
Let go!
[muffled sob]
[thumping on door]
[grunting]
[thumping]
[Kid crying]
[bells ringing]
[suspenseful music]
Don't come out, no matter what.
- Hey!
- [clanking]
[men grunting]
[both grunting]
[clatters]
[panting]
[grunts]
[blood squelching]
[grunts, heavy breathing]
[groans]
[men laughing]
[yelps]
[men laughing maniacally]
[epic suspenseful music]
[gunshot]
[laughing]
[man 1] Is the little monster dead, huh?
[man 2] No, of course she's not.
[bones crack]
[bone cracks]
[panting]
[ominous music]
[foreboding music]
What's gotten into you, man? Hey.
Hey!
[man choking]
[screaming]
Mom…
[monster cooing]
[yelps]
[gasps]
[Yi-kyung grunts]
[rattling]
[monster cooing, grunts]
- No!
- [grunts]
[shrieks]
Don't kill it!
[Yi-kyung panting]
- [monster coos]
- [gunshot]
No! Stop!
[water splashes]
Why would you do that?
- It was a monster.
- Are you gonna do that to me?
Of course not.
- Why would I--
- That's what you think of me.
Because I'm a monster.
I'm not like you,
no matter what you think.
I know how you feel.
That's not true.
I gave birth to you,
why would you be a monster?
Yeah?
"You were a mistake."
"You're a monster."
"I'm afraid of you."
What are you talking about?
"I just wish you'd disappear."
- I'm not--
- "I can't abandon you myself,
so you abandon me."
"Please just disappear
off to some place. Please."
That's not true.
[Kid] That's what
you've been thinking all along.
[somber music]
[shrieks]
[sobs]
[yelps]
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
[crickets chirping]
[rustling]
[unsettling music]
[thumping]
[door opens]
[chuckles]
What are you doing?
Are you gonna follow my brother?
Is he your brother,
your dad, or your boss?
Pick a lane.
He's my savior. Let's leave it at that.
So?
Are you coming or aren't you?
[soft sigh]
[soft chuckle]
You're awake now.
What about the girl that came with me?
I don't know.
She left a little while ago.
Where's my gun, ma'am?
- Why do you ask?
- I should head back now.
If you…
begin walking around on it too quickly,
you could lose your leg.
I'm familiar with this kind of injury.
It's not that bad.
[grunts]
Do you take me for an idiot?
What?
I feed you, I give you a place to sleep,
I care for your wound,
and this is how you repay me,
leaving just like that?
That is very rude.
Is that how morals work in your country?
We're from the same country, though.
Oh.
I'm from outer space.
Oh, okay.
I really appreciate your help.
I'll pay you back.
But I really have to go.
[scoffs]
[Ha-ni] Fine, have it your way.
Then…
have something before you go.
Eat up.
What's…
- What's this made of?
- [scoffs]
We're not exactly The Ritz.
You should feel grateful to be fed.
It doesn't exactly look like food.
Are you worried I could've poisoned it?
[slurps]
Mmm.
[gulps]
See?
You'd better not ask for seconds.
Okay, thank you very much.
[chuckles]
[slurps]
[ominous music]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[slurping]
Oh, God.
All right, all right, all right.
What took so long?
Stop slacking off, okay?
Don't you see all of this?
I'm over here
doing all the hard work for you.
Must be nice,
not to have a care in the world.
Aren't you worried about her?
That girl you came here with?
Of course you're not.
You know, you've got a heart of stone.
Oh, come on!
Why would I worry about someone
who's gone off for her own survival?
She's as good as dead to me.
I don't know everything about you,
but I heard you were only able to join
because of your ties to that girl.
So you should be thankful.
Keep acting so heartless, and…
you'll end up a monster.
[growls]
[chuckles]
Grateful, my ass.
Oh, shit. Look at this.
We're in trouble. We really are.
This won't keep us alive for long.
And those pricks from the Crow Platoon
aren't really doing much lately.
[Seo-jin] Hey, watch your mouth.
You motherfuckers.
[Seo-jin sighs]
Hey, you.
You know your predecessors?
They got fired for running their mouths.
Uh… uh…
You-you're not supposed to just…
to take it like that.
We risked our goddamn lives
to bring these back!
You people don't get a say in any of this.
Yes, sir.
- Are you at it again?
- Look the other way.
Yeah, sure, I will.
But if those people report it
to Sergeant Tak--
Fucking hell!
Let them snitch for all I care!
Then I'll also be able
to get the hell out of here!
Come on, sir. Someone's going to hear you.
It's bad enough that people are calling
desertion our platoon's latest fad.
Which fucker said that?
Like Yong-seok's the same
as that useless private.
Sons of bitches.
You all owe your lives to us.
Ungrateful cocksuckers,
bitching behind our backs.
Sergeant Kim has been looking
for you all day.
He can fuck himself.
It's not like being here
is gonna win me any medal or something.
We're all gonna fuck about aimlessly
until we die meaningless deaths.
Fuck.
[Dong-jun]
This one's going to last a while.
[ball thumps]
[sighs]
Aren't you going to search for him?
How did you get in here?
Why aren't you trying to find him?
You know what he said?
He's a Crow Platoon member,
and that you're like family to him.
You let him out of here.
You should've stopped him.
You knew the risks involved.
Why let him go?
I heard you're sick.
What was it you needed?
Just why in God's name…
[grunts]
…did he leave without a word?
I need new medicine.
I know the disease is terminal,
but I wanted to live longer.
That's why I let him go.
I told him not to,
but he wouldn't listen.
He insisted on it.
He did it for my sake.
Is that so wrong?
So bring him back.
He needs you, so go do it!
What is it you want?
Is it Yong-seok,
or the medicine he's bringing?
Does that matter?
Is that your answer?
[clattering]
[door opens]
[heavy breathing]
[static]
[beeping]
[beeping continues]
[static]
BAMSEOM
[entities whispering]
Shit.
[In-hwan] Hypocrite.
You're not real.
Of course not.
The real me died on that day.
The moment you strangled your own family
with your own two hands.
How did it feel?
You actually enjoyed it, didn't you?
[breathes heavily]
You enjoy it after all.
Killing people.
It's what you do best.
Just do it.
[gun cocking]
You're not even particularly attached
to life, anyways.
[chuckles]
I'm not done.
What?
I'm not…
- [breathes heavily]
- [snickers]
[maniacal laugh]
I am not
done here yet.
[grunting]
- Doctor!
- [gasping]
Oh, God, no. No.
[Dr. Lim] It's PTSD.
Post-traumatic stress disorder.
[Dr. Lim panting]
It has to be.
Right?
[In-hwan sighs]
I think I might be able
to help you out, Sergeant.
[breathing heavily]
I'm above petty threats and blackmail,
just so you know.
There are nicer ways of putting it.
A deal, a quid pro quo. Scratch that.
A negotiation, huh?
What do you want?
Let me out of here.
[monster snarls]
[snarling continues]
[monster growling]
[Dr. Lim] Do you know the implications
of the Oh Jun-il incident?
It's challenged the very laws
of monsterization as we know them.
I'm saying things might be different now.
Are you just going to sit around?
You have to do something.
All the experiments have failed,
and there's nothing you can do
about it, Dr. Lim.
[Dr. Lim] Jesus.
You have the wrong idea.
I'm not saying
I'm going to treat monsterization.
I'm saying I'll help you resist it
so you won't turn into a monster.
You know the special infectees, right?
I can turn you into one.
If you go down, it won't be long
before this place follows suit.
You said you wanted to protect this place.
[low growling]
[breathing nervously]
[Kid] He won't attack you.
I'm looking for Yi-kyung.
You know where she is, right?
I have to meet with her.
Mom…
The people…
They are all bad.
Did you say "Mom"?
You're no different.
[screams]
[whooshing]
[dramatic choral music]
[closing theme music]