KIM SU-YEONG
From here on, we'll go by foot.
Yeong-su, hey.
Let's get going.
But what about Su-yeong?
We can't bring her with us.
Then I'm going to stay here!
Yeong-su, hey…
I'm not going to survive this way.
And I'm not waiting to see you turn!
Don't say that!
I'm not gonna turn into…
Go away! She's my sister.
Don't touch me!
Let me go!
I said let go of me!
I'm staying!
I said I'm not going!
Su-yeong!
Take her with us!
I said take her with us!
Su-yeong!
I said I'm not going!
Su-yeong…
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT BUREAU
Oh, shit.
Guys, you didn't have to do all this.
I would've come if you just asked.
I don't have a lot of time, so…
That briefcase seems familiar.
Isn't that great?
We've recovered such a key asset.
Yeah, it really is.
You managed to actually find it.
Can I ask where it was?
And the one who had it, are they dead?
I think that's a safe bet. Why?
Do you know them?
No, it's nothing like that.
You all saw how torn up I was
when we had lost this thing, hmm?
Do the honors.
What for?
So what are you gonna do?
Are you taking this away?
You motherfucker! Just do it now!
Command must be secured at all cost,
so that's priority number one!
That's a funny way to say you're scared.
I didn't say I wouldn't.
Sure you won't regret it?
It prevents monsterization.
That's been confirmed.
Well, in a broad sense, yes, but…
I mean, before we figure out…
Wow, I'm really feeling
this vibe right now.
The pressure is--
Your mission was
only to create what's inside the case.
Yes, of course.
Moment of truth.
Oh.
What?
What have you done?
What did you do with my vaccine?
The vaccine is secure from…
being discovered, especially by…
you.
Hey. Hey.
Get up.
Okay? Wake up.
Um, I should get going.
You're going off alone?
I should report in 'cause duty calls.
You're going back to them?
You should stay with us.
Yeah, I mean, just take off
your uniform, right?
What are they going to do,
come after you?
Don't say things like that.
Desertion is a capital offense.
I'm sure that there's a way for me
to report back over here.
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
Please lower your masks and look this way.
Standard procedure. Put it down.
Sir, place your belongings down.
Get your hands off me while you still can.
- It's standard procedure.
- It's a gun!
- Shit! Hands off.
- Grab him! Open his bag!
- Grab it!
- Shit.
- Take him in.
- What's going on?
This way, asshole.
Get him out of here.
What is that?
Damn it!
Hey! Get him out of here!
Move it, keep going.
Quickly now.
Why did they beat him up like that?
Let's go, hurry up.
D7, Regiment-9, Private Park Chan-yeong.
During the mission, I got separated.
I would like to report in.
Black Kite, a soldier has returned.
Private Park, 7th Division, 9th Regiment.
PITCHER
PARK CHAN-YEONG
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
RESTRICTED MILITARY AREA
What's this about?
Sergeant Lee Gi-baek…
and Sergeant Kim Dae-un, they're both…
They didn't make it.
We could've saved them, but…
these sons of bitches,
they didn't even lift a finger.
Now they're telling us to go back to camp.
What did you just say?
They're kicking our platoon to the curb.
Effective at 1200 hours,
the whole fucking unit is dismissed.
General Han,
you formed this unit yourself.
You said…
you'd make sure to never turn a blind eye.
That's the reason
I responded to your message.
Right.
I did say that.
Why are you doing this, sir?
Because the Crow Platoon
is no longer needed.
No amount of cleaning up
will ever fix this now.
This job…
What about our mission?
Are you saying we should give up?
It's not giving up, it's a choice.
Master Sergeant Tak.
In-hwan.
Get out of here.
This nation never thanked you.
Just take your best soldiers and go.
You get out of here while you still can.
You're telling me
to head to camp and do what, pray?
No. Anywhere, but there.
You can't go there.
General…
what is it that you aren't telling me?
SHELTER ADMISSION PROTOCOL
1. CHECK TEMPERATURE
2. CHECK FOR MONSTERIZATION SYMPTOMS
Move.
What is it?
No, there must've been a mistake. Hey!
Hey! I'm telling you, I'm not sick!
It's a mistake, okay? Let me go, man!
Let go! I'm not sick! Okay?
- Let go! Fuck! Let me go!
- Wait.
- What the hell do you think you are doing?
- Open up.
No!
- Move!
- Is this how you treat people?
Open the gate!
NOT ADMISSIBLE
Have you had a nosebleed
or fever recently?
Look this way.
Look at me.
This is an announcement
regarding an update in protocol.
Effective immediately,
we will no longer be sorting arrivals.
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
I repeat.
Effective immediately,
we will no longer be sorting arrivals.
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
Bang Jin-ho.
Yes, sir.
It's a bit late.
I haven't heard
from Master Sergeant Tak yet.
You mean, the Master Sergeant Tak
who doesn't care if we die?
Don't talk
about him like that, sir.
What?
We weren't always
in the same unit, you know,
yet I still treat you
with the same respect.
As you should for Sergeant Tak.
You're talking like a dummy.
I know that you think
the world of the guy.
But he really doesn't deserve
your respect.
So you think the rumors are true, then?
That he killed his family?
The rumor itself is the issue, Jin-ho.
All I see…
is a man who's definitely capable of it.
Oh, shit.
They weren't easy to hide.
Why would I tell you now?
Seems like you don't fear
for your life, Dr. Lim.
I'm the only one
who can make a vaccine, right? So…
We started on a bad note.
Why don't we try this again, huh?
I've already given you enough chances.
I thought I made myself very clear.
And look where my leniency has gotten me.
I'm done waiting.
I really don't have time for this.
Sir, wait!
This is the beginning, Doctor.
Let's not make this more difficult
than it needs to be.
All right, so tell me.
Where are they, hmm?
What is it that you aren't telling me?
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENT
TOP SECRET
Sergeant Kim.
We're all being called in.
What's going on?
Yeong-hu, I chose already.
Keep your head straight from now on.
About your pet theory, Dr. Lim.
If monsterization really is a work
of nature like you claimed,
then it probably won't end
until all of mankind
is wiped off the face of this planet.
So that's why I got you
this little present.
Well, that is,
if you don't disappoint me again, Dr. Lim.
What are you doing?
Cleaning up.
PLEASE COOPERATE WITH THE MILITARY
TO RESTORE ORDER AND SAFETY
We'll wipe them out
before they get a chance to turn.
That should keep the world clean
for the time being…
And who knows?
Maybe it'll even end this whole mess.
Thoughts, Dr. Lim?
And what does that mean?
I love it.
That's perfect.
That's it. That's right.
It's exactly what I'd do.
We should've been cleaning house
from the start.
We've all just…
We've all been living
with our heads in the sand.
That's the reason for this shit.
I'm just… I'm…
waiting.
Go for it.
What about you?
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
I'll take you to it. I will.
Great.
Let's clean up then.
Why is that coming this way?
Must be some sort of error.
It's coming.
It's coming!
Out of my way!
Ji-su!
Yoon Ji-su!
Su-yeong!
So, you're not going to talk, are you?
It might take time,
but I'll find it, no matter what.
I think you will never find it.
There was something I couldn't crack.
Damn, it's such a shame.
Goodbye then.
Target, clear!
Hey!
You're all going to die!
Bastard!
I'm going to kill all of you!
You bastard!
Hey, move aside!
Sir, it's complete.
We'll blow up
the isolation zone first.
The rest of you, get medical supplies
and get ready to move out.
Tell me, what do you desire?
I don't know.
Do you believe
you can overcome this?
What happened to your family?
They're all dead.
Did you kill them?
Have you killed a human?
Why did you do it? Tell me.
- Stop it.
- What do you desire? What do you desire?
Then what are you now?
Are you a human?
Or a monster?
I asked you a question.
Answer me.
How was your stay?
Was it better than you thought, or…
was the pain too much?
Trying to save humans.
Just look at you now.
What a sorry sight.
What should I do then?
Save you or is it just better
to kill you, once and for all?
Fuck it.
I'm done with this.
You stay in there
and watch this place just…
fall apart at the seams.
Get up. We're not done.
Just accept what you are.
You're nothing but a monster.
Yeah.
I'm a monster.
Nothing matters anymore at this point.
The reason I went easy on you
is because you're new to all this.
But you messed it up.
You even got me to act
like a fucking idiot, didn't you?
But not anymore.
I won't fall
for that fucking shit anymore.
You don't have what it takes, do you?
Just slowly wither away.
Actually…
I want you to know…
that even when you bring out
your very best,
you're still just a failure.
You can't save anyone.
Even yourself.
So just stay right here.
See?
Oh, no…
Yeong-su.
Yeong-su. Yeong-su. Yeong-su.
Get up.
That's right, Yeong-su.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
Go on now. Yeong-su, hurry.
Hurry. Hurry.
Yeong-su, you have to move now.
Yeong-su, hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Now, Yeong-su.
Now!
Yeong-su, go! Get out of here!
Get out. Now. Get up.
Go! Go!
Yeong-su, go!
Get out of here, hurry!
Hurry up! Go!
Yeong-su, please. Please. Yeong-su.
Go!
Hurry up, please. Yeong-su…
Go on. Go now. Yeong-su, get out of here.
Ji-su…
- Go!
- Yoon Ji-su!
Yoon Ji-su!
Yeong-su, please.
Come on, get out, now! Now!
Get out of here, hurry!
Ji-su!
Ji-su! Ji-su, get up!
Oh, no. Please!
It can't… This can't…
No! No, please! Please!
No…
Ji-su!
This will be our base camp.
We don't know what's here.
Lock up all entry points.
Yes, sir.
What do we do
about supplies, sir?
We don't even have any water.
We'll just find what we can.
We'll head out as soon as we're situated.
Freeze! Don't move!
Hold it.
How many of you are here?
Four hundred, give or take.
That's good. We can definitely
accommodate them, then.