Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
THANGALAAN
The forest reigns supreme out here.
Now the footprints are turning back.
The stench of blood fills my nostrils, brother.
Let the 'parai' drums resound.
The aboriginals don't spare anyone
who goes there seeking gold.
There is no gold there.
There is nothing there
except for demons that kill people.
Even recently, five people were killed.
People are lured there
with false promises...
...not even their bodies
could be recovered.
That's the reason there is a ban
on that area.
Frank, who was here before,
just wrote some nonsense.
That is all a lie.
Please do not disturb me
with this anymore.
Lunch was nice.
Let me take your leave now.
- Hey, Varadha...
- Careful!
Where is your mind at?
Still basking in your nuptial bliss?
Your ceremonies are barely over...
and you are already in a hurry
to take your wife along to work?
He never listens.
Easy for you to talk, sister.
What would you know of my worries?
You sleep way past the rooster's call...
and rise only when the sun
hits your ass...
cook, and eat leisurely
and then finally head to work.
Yeah, right!
Only I know the hardships that come with
that quarter cawnie of land.
At least you own a quarter cawnie.
Can't say that about us.
Unless we start working in the fields
before dawn...
our livelihood will go for a toss.
The landlord will surely
ruin my happiness.
Eww! Mind your language.
Isn't that the truth?
Would the landlord spare latecomers?
- See you, sister.
- Okay, Arasani.
Oh, shush.
Keep it down.
The day has just begun.
Now, where did that boy go...?
Asoka!
What is it, Mom?
I am by the peepal tree.
You're off so early to sit and daydream?
Everyone's off to work
at the crack of dawn.
But look at my man here.
Like the tale of the king
who went to hunt pigs...
he is cosily tucked in and curled up.
Hey, you.
Wake up, man.
Wake up, you.
Calm down, you.
Calm down.
Shit!
You scream as though you're possessed.
Look, you've scared the kids.
You play this same tune every morning.
It's fine, dear.
Oh my, I was just jesting.
Woman...
How often must I tell you
not to rouse me from sleep?
If something were to happen to you,
what would I tell my children?
Why bother?
Your children don't even need me.
All that's left is for you to suckle them,
you shameless man.
Really,
what goes on in that mind of yours?
Look at them having a laugh.
Get up. Let's go.
Come on kids, let's go.
Hello, mate.
Tell me, mate!
You know that shiny fabric with silver
borders that the landlord's wife wears?
I want one of those made for Gunavathi.
Done, mate.
I will make one.
You're crowing too loud.
The cavalry might just answer your call.
You are quite the father to your kids.
Why don't you ask your beloved
what she desires?
Girl, Thangalaan belongs to you.
Uh-huh. These words that wash away
like tracks in the rain don't sway me.
Get this clear...
for this harvest festival,
you better buy me the kind of blouse
that the landlord's wife wears.
Or I'll snatch that
proud nose of yours, be warned.
Listen to your mother, kid.
She's dreaming for a second youth.
Why? I'm still in my prime.
You don't have to do it for nothing.
For every dress you gift me,
I'll birth you a child.
Huh?
You think this works like a barter?
You can never repay me,
you indebted woman.
I'll get you a hundred dresses.
Will you bear a hundred children?
I will. Buy me, and I will.
- How, my woman?
- Like that, that's how.
Hara Hara Govinda Govinda!
Om Namo Narayana!
Om Namo Narayana...
What are you babbling?
Raise your hands.
- Achuthaya Namaha...
- Om Ananthaya Namaha...
So, here's the thing...
you aren't from an oppressed community.
Yes...
you are the children of Lord Perumal.
Perumal's children, eh?
From now, avoid cow meat and
stop mingling with those slum-dwellers.
Got it?
We are a different folk.
We must follow specific rules and ways.
After our death, our liberated bodies
must ascend to Lord Narayana's realm.
Get it?
Hey, Asoka.
Don't just be gawking at me.
Come and wear the holy thread.
Join our side.
Hey Asoka!
His mother, for heaven's sake!
Scram now.
I will be back, priest.
Asoka...
I was right here,
watching the priest.
So when are you
going to become a Brahmin?
Sure, he will.
Gengu wants all the slum folks
to don the thread.
Didn't I tell you to keep away from him?
Holy ancestor Gengamma,
Mother Kanniyamma!
It's nothing, it's alright.
That is it.
"The eastern sky shines bright
Shimmering clouds gleaming light"
"Dreams we cradled dearly
have taken flight"
"Grains glittering like
gold fill our sight"
"Seeds we sowed with care
Now have sprouted through the air"
"Gone are those days
Of serving our masters"
"The fruit of our labour in these lands
Are now in our hands"
"Those glass bangles, oh my!"
"While I'm busy reaping these grains"
"While I'm busy reaping these grains,
my dear... They're stealing my attention"
"My youthful reaper, standing tall"
"I'll heed your wishes
And be a fine wife, my husband"
"Oh my young husband
my sweet husband"
"I turn crimson when our hands touch"
"I feel secure when you
break into a blush"
"I shall even bestow a deed
just so you feel secure"
- "For real, my love?
- Of course, dearest"
"They strung you like a precious pearl
chain, those sweet in-laws of mine"
Dad, how does the landlord own
so much land...
when we have so little?
Didn't you know? These lands once belonged
to your father's ancestors?
You better believe it,
all of this land is ours.
The Zamindars, Jagirdars
- and the taxmen...
- Hey, do not touch me!
...were instigated and backed
by the British lords.
They tricked us and took our lands.
Land must belong to those who toil in it.
How can it belong to those who don't toil?
"Husband, you promised to adorn me in gold
when you asked for my hand"
"But now I'm toiling
under the scorching Sun"
"Now I'm toiling under the scorching Sun"
"My golden chariot"
"How sweetly you ask me
to adorn you in gold"
"How sweetly you ask me"
"Adorn yourself with these golden grains
my golden treasure"
"While I lug stacks of the day's yield
My competitive husband matches my zeal"
"My farmlady,
who stands tall in the farm..."
"My farmlady, who stands tall in the farm
No man can ever match your form"
"My sweet wife!
Bring on the meat curry"
"My dear leftover porridge!
Here comes the landlord, get thrashing"
"Nightfall will soon be upon us
We must secure the cattle"
"Let's work with pride
and lead a prosperous life"
Hey, come and eat a little.
I don't want.
You eat.
Hey, Gengamma.
Are you asleep?
Yes, I am.
Dad!
Hey...
- Kids, you're still awake?
- Nagamma...
I'm not sleepy, Mom.
Of course you aren't, you night-demons.
Tell us a story and we'll sleep.
I'll smack you to sleep!
Mom, you don't need to tell us.
Dad will.
- What story, my dear?
- A spooky tale, Dad.
- Dad, tell us the one with Aarathi...
- When you were trapped hunting for gold.
Dad, tell us. Tell us!
Dad, tell us.
No, that one will scare you, dear.
Hey, all. Quiet down.
Dad, tell us. Tell us. Tell us!
What kind of children have you birthed?
Little monsters.
- Please tell us, Dad.
- Alright, I'll tell you.
I will tell you the story.
But listen closely, alright?
So...
Long, long ago...
just like what you see over there...
there was a terrain of rolling hills.
Beyond the hills, forests and river...
there was a place called
Aanamalai (elephant hills).
An elephant?
Not an elephant,
but a mountain that
looks like an elephant.
The forest echoed with the rumble of the
elephants,
roaring leopards, and wild pigs.
There was a massive river there
called Ponnar (golden river).
At the bank of that river...
Our king, returning victorious from
a battle with a rival kingdom...
while leading his large army
back home...
Who are they?
In the River Ponnar,
my grandfather...
my great-grandfather,
Kadayan, was mining gold.
Hey!
They're a tribe that gathers gold dust.
Oh.
Freeze, don't move.
By the order of the Monarch,
all of you are hereby imprisoned.
Monarch, eh?
Unadulterated gold...
I want it.
I want more...
I want more.
Monarch...
Only those truly in need will find it.
If we look on your behalf
we will not find a speck.
Step into the river.
Monarch...
the gold dust drifts in the water.
Just like baby fish, it can't be caught.
What of the gold in the land?
Only the gold dust in water
can be gathered.
It is the grace of Mother Earth
for its people.
The gold in the land is not for us.
I want that glittering rock.
All that glitters is not gold, Monarch.
It is doom.
March ahead.
Serpents!
How are you unaffected by cobra venom?
No, Monarch.
Our bodies have grown resilient.
It won't affect us.
It can't.
The cobras prevent us
from extracting gold.
They allure us with glitter, tempt us...
and then kill those
who dare to extract it.
Who is the sorcerer behind
these deceptions and spells?
Not a sorcerer, Monarch.
A sorceress.
Aarathi!
Descendant of the Nagas,
she reigns over these forest lands.
She stands guard over this gold-rich land.
She is the queen of this land.
All land belongs to my king.
How ignorant can you be?
This is not your land.
This land is held under her spell.
There's nothing you can do.
Go back to your village.
The cobras won't trouble us any longer.
March ahead.
Retreat.
Stand guard.
Can no one bind those sorcerers?
Why?
We can.
I will.
Then do it.
Go.
What's in it for me?
Hey, why spew such nonsense?
Don't you know what to
seek from the monarch?
Do you take me for an ignorant man?
You descendant of a wayward clan!
I want the gold.
What do you seek in return?
Land.
I want land, Monarch.
Donations to holy temples,
tributes to the Gods...
lands grabbed from us
under countless pretexts...
and bestowed to these priests,
higher up in the Varna system...
we need that land back.
Look at the arrogance
of the untouchable.
A lavish life handed
to the immoral, huh?
- You--
- Priest!
Yes, you will get half of it back.
I desire that gold.
Bring it to me,
and your land shall be yours again.
Stand back!
You are a great warrior.
I declare you the Commander
of my forces.
Your reward.
Gold...
Take every last bit of it.
look, it is gold.
- Gold!
Gold!
Glittering gold...
It is all gold.
It is mere mud.
- Mud!
- Trickster!
Is this the gold you spoke of?
Give it.
Give it back.
Monarch.
This Aarathi possesses the power
to turn gold into mud.
Shame on you,
don't use such deceit on me.
You're nothing but a charlatan.
King!
The erected idol of this Saint
is the cause of this turmoil.
It is this spirit that's causing
all of the sorcery occurring here.
Behead this spirit-saint's idol
and toss it away.
And the gold will be ours.
Gold!
All the gold is mine!
Gold... gold!
Blood spurting out of her gut,
spilled all over the ground...
turning soil, stones and rocks
into glittering gold.
But...
in the end, I couldn't bring back
even a speck of gold.
Hey.
Enough with the tales now.
Sleep.
Hey, hey!
Who is it?
Hey.
Hey, Asoka.
Mom, who is it?
Dad!
Hey!
Pour water.
Help, help!
Stay there.
Mom!
Pour water!
Who is it?
Who are you?
What are we going to do now?
Resident of North Arcot District,
Kudiyatham Taluk, Vepur Pariah's slum...
Farmer Thangalaan Muni,
for his two cawnies
of land and its water sources...
as per the village's 'Rythuvari'
tax system, must either pay 10 pagodas...
or 80 vessels of grain as tax.
And in accordance with
the British government tax system...
is liable to pay an amount of 20 pagodas,
or 160 vessels of grains as tax.
The taxes must be paid
as per government orders.
- Hey!
- Hold on.
Thangalaan!
Stand back!
Dad!
The landlord will pay the 30 pagodas
owed by Thangalaan to the British.
To work off this debt
and the interest incurred...
Thangalaan and his kin,
all seven of them
including his two-year-old son...
are ordered to work as
bonded farm labourers.
They are forbidden from working elsewhere
or leaving the village.
On violation of these terms,
they will be hanged to death
for defying government orders.
Step into the field.
Let the hands do the work,
keep your mouths shut.
First they seize our lands,
then they thrash us.
Dad, aren't you strong?
They push us around and talk to us as
they wish and yet you don't utter a word.
It's making me so mad,
I'm gonna lash out on you.
Shut up.
Eat quietly.
All the Untouchables of Vepur's slums...
are ordered to assemble under
the peepal tree right away.
This is the order of the British Lord.
Sir, we have reached Vepur village.
You lowlife!
Move. Step away.
Hey, listen up.
Hey, quiet down.
His Excellency, Lord Clement...
has come to your village
seeking your favour.
Since the days of the Chola rule,
until the
reign of the Muslim ruler Tipu Sultan...
you people, living in the Kolar region
of Mysore and the North Arcot district...
have helped in mining gold.
Now, His Excellency Mr. Clement Lord...
desires to resume the good work with you.
No. Not happening.
Hey, stop.
Asoka! Asoka!
- Stop...
- Go home, you. Beat it.
Listen to me, go home.
There are no ghosts.
- Let's leave.
- That is just superstition.
Don't just stand there like a rock.
Come on!
You will come with me.
That is an order.
- Go get them.
- Yes, sir.
There are no ghosts or beasts there.
The lord will give you
the daily wage you ask for.
One pagoda a day.
Free rice and meat on top of it.
Hey!
We need Thangalaan to do this to
protect our slum, Gengamma.
Look, no matter what you say or do...
he's not coming.
Go and find someone else.
This won't work, Thangalaan.
Figure it out with her.
You insist on going and want to
take my son along too?
Am I to leave him behind then?
If we all cower in fear,
what do we tell the British lord?
Exactly.
Quit wailing, woman.
Fine, let's go convince Varadhan.
Woman, why are you being this way?
Get lost!
Are we and our kids to bow before
the landlord all our lives?
Even if just for a day,
we must live and die with dignity.
Understand?
Dignity counts, woman.
It is the only thing that does.
- Come, now.
- Leave me alone.
What kind of a woman are you?
It's okay, come now!
Get lost!
Hey...
Aren't you a brave woman?
No harm will come my way.
Listen, take care of the kids.
I will return soon, alright?
I'm just here to
tend to your children...
I just don't count, do I?
Oh, my precious!
You are an adorned treasure.
Hey...
Being away from you...
is like having a thorn
pierce through my heart.
Woman, I leave now but the thought
of you will never leave me.
You're leaving us behind...
leaving us to worry about
the dangers you might encounter.
it makes my gut churn.
Feel me quiver all over.
Here.
Touch me here.
I want to savour the warmth
of your hands just for a while.
Then warm me up all over.
I will offer you all the
warmth in my body.
Hold on to it safe.
Believe me, I'll return
before that fire dies down.
Sure you will.
- Come now.
- Quit it, move.
Gunavathi, kids... look up at the moon.
Look at the reflection
in water of the manger.
Go on, take a peek, Nagamma.
Om Namo Narayana!
Hara Hara Govinda, Govinda!
Govinda, Govinda!
Trust me. You will be fine.
- I don't want to...
- Go!
Go!
All set to leave, uncle?
Hey, take care of Asoka.
Stay close to dad, brother.
My husband...
Move it!
My dear, my father, my divine mother...
protect us and ward off evil.
What are they doing?
They call it as hero's stone.
People who die in war and
for the welfare of their villages...
and hunters of tigers and pigs
are considered as heroes, sir.
It's worship of a small god.
That's it.
Narayana, if our journey
proves safe and bountiful...
I vow to erect you a temple
with my earnings.
For that alone, I am going, Lord.
- Hey...
- Master?
Sacred ash? Sacred thread?
It's an insult to the
sanctity of the thread.
Take it off right away.
But I must ascend to
the lord's abode after death, master!
You, untouchable!
You think anyone who dons a thread
can ascend to heaven?
Is there no limit
to who desires what?
What a disgrace!
This entire fiasco is Ramanujam's doing.
The truth is...
- our birth is not in our hands.
- Quiet!
You are excessive.
One more word, and I'll rip off
that thread and send you packing.
- Let's get going.
- Govinda, Govinda!
The path ends here.
Just forests beyond this point.
Lord, over here!
If we venture through the woods and
cross that river, we'll get there.
Right here, yes, over here.
I know it well, Lord.
There is a path.
We just need to follow it.
- Come on, let's go.
- Hey.
Stupid! Fool!
Your hand. Give me your hand.
These white men are
determined to find the gold.
But there are ghosts standing guard!
In a few days,
they'll see it for themselves.
That to seek gold here
is to seek death.
Plan a quick return
to your village, fellows.
Be mindful with the use of supplies.
Understood?
I will take their consent and leave.
Sir, with your permission...
I will take leave.
Have a safe journey.
Hey, move aside.
Standing in my way!
There.
That is the way.
Get ready to leave.
I've known these primal lands
from my time as a young hunter.
I've heard the tales of
ghosts cloaked in stone.
I'm aware that scorpions riding on snakes
will obstruct our path.
What you looking at?
Move.
Hey, move.
- Let's go.
- This is the path.
Come on, little brother.
Uncle, are all the lands
beyond the river filled with gold?
Yes.
We can step in.
The currents are favourable.
We will advance on this side.
Let's go.
Lord... no, hold on!
Go... that side.
What do you know?
Let's go, Lord.
Lord, listen.
There is a pit over there.
Quiet down.
I will take you, Lord.
Quiet.
- Is this the way?
- Yes.
Oh, brother.
The wild streams that conceal the path...
and spiralling storms that raise dust...
the slithering snakes and their sting...
and scorpions itching to strike...
are the guardians of this land.
Even lives are trite here,
steel your body.
March on ahead!
Brother!
We know no fear,
it's not in our nature.
We are born strong,
in mind and body.
Here he goes.
Asoka, watch out.
Careful, everyone.
Careful.
Little brother...
The current is getting stronger,
hold tight.
- Uncle!
- Don't stop.
Keep moving.
Asoka!
Thangalaan, where are you?
Uncle!
Hold on tight.
No, Gengu! Gengu!
Keep moving.
Come on.
You are safe.
My Holy Bible!
Jesus.
Why did you lead us down here
against my advice?
Are you trying to get us all killed?
You demon!
What more is to come?
Lord Perumal...
Even lives are trite.
Steel your body, brother.
March ahead, brother.
You are Satan.
He is Satan.
Enough.
It's alright, alright...
It's done. It's done.
Slowly, Grandpa.
It's nothing.
Gather our belongings.
Let's get going.
You are all demons.
Dad...
The Elephant Hill from your tales.
Is that it?
Lord...
The Kings of the past...
where they mined gold...
those lands lie beyond that mountain.
Beyond it.
Towards the Elephant Hill...
Go.
We will find gold.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey...
Do not speak.
Do not open your mouth...
until we depart from here.
Demon.
Demon, do not mislead us.
William...
what do you see?
You see the rich vegetation
surrounded by parched lands?
That means the land is mineral-rich.
Possibly gold.
Not only gold...
But also silver, brass, copper and iron.
However, gold will be found in abundance.
- It's only rocks!
- Hush, you fool...
The gold could be
concealed in the mud.
You might uncover just a tiny fleck
when you break the rock.
It won't be easy to spot.
Centuries back, the Cholas and recently
Tipu Sultan mined gold from this region.
We are close, very close.
Less fire.
Wages for our labour?
Wages, Lord...
Pay... Pay me...
Keep yours.
Dig here.
We dig in this area.
Hey... you!
What are you looking at?
Get working.
Lord,
the peacock will lead us to the gold.
It is known that gold will be
in abundance wherever it lands.
Lord... this is the spot!
This is where the gold must be.
We will find it soon.
We will.
Look at these flowers
glistening like gold.
If we dig around these flowers,
we'll find gold.
- Give it back, kid.
- Stop!
- It belongs to us.
- It's ours.
He got it!
You got it.
Wow.
Priest!
Priest, wait for me.
Move! Put it out.
Why did you send me here, love?
Can't you picture me, draped in gold?
Even the upper-caste women
would pale in comparison.
Doesn't it all seem
splendid just to imagine?
There's no gold or anything here, Arasani.
Come and take me home.
Lord Narayana, show us the path, man...
A tunnel!
Lord...
I've found a tunnel
from the era of Cholas!
We've found it!
Get down.
Lord, this is not a tunnel...
The saint's...
It's a lightning pit.
Don't talk about things
you know nothing of.
I know for sure.
- It's a tunnel from Chola period.
- Hey!
It's true, I'll prove it.
Hey, what?
- Nothing.
- Come on then.
Uncle, I found a head inside.
- I was scared shitless.
- Inside?
Lift me up.
- There is a head inside?
- Must be nothing.
Step aside.
Asoka! No! Hey...
Are you out of your mind?
Don't you know what to keep from him?
Asoka!
A beast...
- It's a beast! Save me, Lord Perumal!
- Hey! Enough.
Head of the Saint.
Our king...
Gold...
Kill...
King...
Gold... Kill...
Shush!
Scared-chicken...
Quit being a crybaby.
Shut your mouth, now.
Disrupting my sleep.
What is it to you?
You've lived a good life.
I can't stop thinking
about my wife, Uncle.
My heart feels heavy.
The pain torments me.
If only you'd let me, I'd just walk
through the wilderness and get home.
Why did you come then?
I keep telling everyone that we must
break that head, but nobody listens.
Everything will be fine if we break it.
Instead,
you go on about aborting the mission.
We are being controlled by demons here.
Are you cognizant that this is
just a childish superstitious story?
Do you understand what I am saying?
I am not sure if what
he is saying is true.
Let us look for this land
that he calls Elephant Hills.
Perhaps we might find what we seek.
No, no...
- I cannot accept this.
- Arthur!
I fear that this mission
will not be successful.
My coffers are empty.
I cannot go back with nothing
to show for my endeavours.
Even if fate is against us...
we will still prevail.
We will, Jesus is with us.
- But do not believe them.
- Jesus?
Enough.
Look at me.
Do I look like an
Englishman to you right now?
What would be the fate of
my family when I am gone?
Even these untouchable Indians...
look at me with overbearing contempt.
He may be right.
We will follow him.
He is my last hope.
Are you intent upon
dooming yourself to hell?
He is a demon. Look at him.
Even if the devil himself
were to show me the path...
I would still follow him.
Arrant nonsense.
Jesus.
Many kings were buried under this land.
- Are the tales for real or mere myth?
- You.
Lead us.
Everyone, up.
We move out.
Dad, we found the Saint's head here...
then the torso must
be somewhere nearby too, right?
If we locate the torso,
we'll discover the gold, won't we?
If we chance upon the
idol's head or torso...
it means a curse is upon all of this land.
Do you know what this land is called?
The Satan's Wrath.
We need to shatter that
head and bury the pieces...
or else we'll face the Satan's wrath.
Everyone, keep moving.
- Thangalaan, something's not right.
- Don't stop.
Hear me out, hold on.
Keep moving, don't stop.
Please don't venture ahead, listen to me.
Where the blackened rocks cry out...
and forests blister and burn.
- Dark spirits quake beneath the earth.
- This land has incurred the Satan's wrath.
Destroy that.
A supercharged animal will
emerge amidst the dust.
No, no, no...
Don't...
Brother, this sprawling
blackened land is no ordinary land.
It is the sacrificial
offering for my Satan.
Sharpen your ears and listen closely.
You'll hear a tremble like the
screams of a thousand insects.
The Saint's torso must be around here.
Come.
Oh my... you are Satan. The Satan himself.
- Yes, this man is actually right.
- I won't come.
And not that dark spirit.
No!
Stop, you demon.
- Hey, stop.
- Stop.
You stop...
or I will put a bullet
into your dark heart.
Lower your bloody gun...
or I will put a bullet in yours.
Clement, listen to me.
This time, listen...
- Hey!
- Ouch!
Hey!
Run, everyone. Hurry.
Run!
Careful, uncle.
Hey, Thangalaan.
Come on, now.
Hey!
Kid... stop.
Thangalaan!
Uncle, careful.
- Oh no!
- Get up, Dad.
Get up!
- Asoka, careful.
- Watch out, Asoka.
Go on, shoot.
Uncle, get up.
Uncle!
Oh, no. Watch out, uncle.
Dad!
I knew this would happen.
The devil has shown its true colours.
Look at me.
Look at me, Clement.
Now do you see him for who he is?
We are almost there.
I am going to kill you.
Thangalaan, you are a beast.
Let's move ahead.
- Arthur...
- Demon!
You shot my father?
- Asoka, don't!
- Hey!
- Move!
- It is all your doing.
Don't you get it? Listen to me.
Asoka...
- Ashoka!
- Move! Move away.
- Don't run.
- I'll kill you.
Hey, priest.
Where are you running to?
Run past the Elephant Hill.
Get back.
Uncle...
March ahead.
You descendant of a wayward clan.
I want gold.
What do you seek in return?
What are you doing here?
A hand!
Lord, look it is the hand.
- It is the Saint's hand. Dad...
- Now...
- Dad, the hand is over here.
- It is time to die.
Oh no, dad.
- Dad.
- Asoka...
Dad, the saint...
the saint's hand...
- What are you saying?
- The Lord.
- Dad... the Saint's hand.
- Wait, wait...
As I unearthed the Saint's hand,
someone struck down the White man.
He fell down.
Arthur.
- Arthur, wake up.
- There are people all around us, Uncle.
They are all around us.
I am really scared, Dad.
- Watch out. It is the Satan.
- Priest!
William, stay back.
Hey, come over here.
Take it.
Cover that side.
You can see the pit, covered up with sand.
You can hear life stirring within it.
Hey, brother...
the guns on our backs
push us into bottomless pits...
but the shooter aiming at our
hearts doesn't know the truth.
This isn't just a body, it's gold.
Narayana!
The scent of bad omen is thick in the air.
Bones buried deep inside
rise from under the earth...
I sense them coiling around my
ankles, tightening their grip on me.
Come on, brother.
Rise and fight bravely so the
darkness in our life may retreat.
There's no sin nor
virtue on the battlefield.
The moment is ripe to settle our scores.
I will defeat this formidable woman
before my boiling blood turns cold.
Turn up the heat.
Throw in some more firewood.
Damn... rain.
- Hurry up.
- Make it quick.
Is it there?
What do you see?
Gold!
- Gold.
- Jesus, finally, we've found it.
- It is gold.
- Hey, shut it now.
Son, be careful.
Uncle, get over here.
Run.
Hurry.
No, William!
No!
This Earth has taken you.
But in return...
it has given us gold.
This is you, William.
This is you.
Thank you.
What are you still doing?
Let's leave.
What's done is done.
Let's help them gather the gold,
take our share, and leave, priest.
No, just listen to me.
Let's go back home to safety.
Lord, we are departing.
Let's just leave.
Lord.
Take it.
Thanga...
...you are a truly worthy man.
I...
am grateful to you.
This, to me...
Is of paramount importance.
Now...
we can show the world who we are.
We've found gold, man.
We've made history!
History!
Your life is about to change.
All your lives...
your mothers, fathers...
your children...
is about to move up.
And everyone will look at you all...
with respect.
You wear these.
Wear.
Arthur, Thangalaan and I
will return with more money and men.
You're in charge until then.
Until then, all of you
keep up your good work.
Look, a horse!
Mind your job.
Is that Dad?
Indeed, it is.
Gangamma...
- Hey!
What?
- Have you returned, my lord?
- Get up.
My dearest!
The moment I saw your face...
my dwindling life surged back alive.
Shut up. Get up, now.
What is wrong?
Come on now.
I feel like I've risen
from my own grave.
Listen to yourself, woman.
What do you mean?
All I could think of was you
the whole time I was away.
My Kaniya!
What is up, my boy?
Where is my son?
Where is he?
Your son is safe and sound
over there. Don't worry.
- Arasani, get over here.
- My girls!
My precious girls.
You're strutting around
like an English Lord.
- Doesn't it look great?
- Yes, it does.
Hold on, I'll just come.
So, book-keeper...
No, don't do it.
Don't you dare come close...
Get over here, book-keeper.
- Thangalaan, what are you doing?
- Stay out of this.
Count it.
The amount...
The amount seems to be right.
But you still owe the landlord 31 rupees.
- You need to pay that.
- On what grounds?
Is it some sort of interest or tax?
How do you account for the lifelong
labour of me and my entire family?
Listen up, return my deed.
Hand it over.
Uncle...
My husband, the poor dear,
is such a scared-cat.
I constantly worry about
where he is and how he's doing.
He's fine, dear.
He eats his fill...
...he works like a mule.
He talks about you all the time.
"Arasani is so fond of gold.
She likes it so dearly."
He's always talking about buying you
jewels, with a sparkle in his eye.
Is there gold really?
Are you seriously
asking me if there is gold?
Arasani, they've found the gold.
All that's left is to dig it up.
He's here, dressed like a Lord,
to recruit people for the job.
Be wary, you might think he's
back out of love for his family.
Watch her grinding Thangalaan
to shreds while grinding meat.
- Oh, woman...
- That's exactly right, Uncle.
Uncle...
Last night I saw my
father in my dream again.
A nightmare.
I was so scared.
Why hasn't my father
returned yet?
Your father's guarding
all that gold, dear.
Why fret?
We'll go see him, okay?
Brother,
did my father send anything for me?
Your father Muniyan always thinks
long and hard before he speaks.
I knew it'd be forever before
he spoke a word, so I rushed back.
Did you hear that, woman?
You're all amazed by this story?
There's so much more.
Doesn't matter if
it's a lord or whoever...
I'll ensure you get your
wages once the job is done.
That's our Thangalaan!
You're the one who dangled
the landlord by his hair.
The way you rode in on a horse...
and threw the money at his face!
Wow!
I've never seen a miracle quite like that.
True, these English lords
stand no chance against you.
That's all fine, Thangalaan,
but what is the purpose of this?
Why don't you cut to the chase?
What?
Why do they seek us out when there
are millions of people in this land?
Because we can work through rain or shine,
battle dark forces and
retrieve the gold, yeah?
No one but us can do
this job in this land.
So you're here to march us to our doom.
What kind of life are you leading now?
You are bound to toil like beasts.
Endlessly cultivating
all kinds of grains...
doing all of the farming...
but can you bring even
a handful of grain home?
Isn't this our land?
Yet do any of us own even a small patch?
Even if we do, why do they
snatch it from us?
The land is ours,
the labour is ours...
yet they don't even pay
us our rightful wages.
If our children are also
doomed to be born as slaves...
what's the point of this life?
Are you saying things
will change if we go there?
Yes, it will change.
Didn't you all see for yourselves?
Today, my piece of land is mine.
Understand?
What? Have you forgotten already?
Weren't you the one warning us
about ghosts and monsters there?
Now you're pitching grand ideas,
calling us there.
Woman, do you not venture into the
fields at night to safeguard the crops?
Do you not manage the
watering in the dark?
What if we stayed holed
up out of fear of the dark?
You can't live
if you're afraid of dying.
Look...
I'm not saying
we'll live like royalty there.
But rather than die under those who
discriminate us based on our birth...
it's better to die trying to change it.
Know what the
Englishman has planned for us?
Houses. Schools, like ones
the landlord's kids attend...
decent wages, and clothes,
like the one I'm wearing.
- Isn't that enough?
- Scram, will you?
It all sounds nice, but is it feasible?
Say, we agree to go,
would the landlord just let us?
What?
The Englishman has given it
in writing with his stamp.
Let's see who dares to
defy the Whites and hold us back.
See this?
Are we just going to sit here
in our rags, rotting away?
Or get educated like the Whites,
wear these shirts...
and hold power?
Listen up.
Gold will change our lives.
That's all.
Still on about it, woman?
Give everyone the sweets I brought.
Don't you have hands?
Can't you do it yourself?
Thinks he can show off,
in his fancy outfit...
Mate, here! Have some.
Arasani, hand it out to everyone.
- Did everyone get some?
- Move...
Here, here.
Hey.
- The thing you asked for...
- What?
A dress.
- Is it for me?
- Who else?
What's this?
Is it a woman's dress?
- Hey, hey...
- Hold on.
There's one for everyone, no squabbling.
Look at this, Arasani.
How do we put it on?
- How?
- Not that way, I guess.
Mom, what about me?
Your father has got one
for everyone. Ask him.
Like this?
- Looks nice, doesn't it?
- It's lovely.
Come on, ladies.
Let's step out.
Here, look.
Take a look!
How does it look?
Look at you, sister.
You've aged backwards.
Feels like it's being held upright, yeah?
- Feels less heavy now, eh?
- Exactly!
How do I look, husband?
- Hey, what's this?
- What?
Take it off.
Off with it.
If you keep it hidden away,
how will you feed my kids?
Oh, goodness.
So concerned about his
children getting their milk.
I'm her first child, dear.
"You sweet bird... You colourful bird"
"Sweet, colourful bird...
So elegant her moves, this dancing bird"
"Every step like lightning...
She came and stood before him"
"And our dear uncle is left blushing,
look how he's swooning"
"All dolled up, look
at her shimmering,
when she walks tall,
how he's simmering"
"All stirred up,
look at her light,
when she's gleaming,
it's quite the sight"
"With a newfound bliss...
Water in the stream glints"
"With naughty eyes
watching... The little bird bathes"
"With our uncle feigning work,
his headscarf comes undone"
"With the pretty flower
teasing to give in just a little bit"
"When facing this fierce female,
why do my eyes
behave as if bewitched?"
"He follows you
everywhere crazy in love..."
"All dolled up, look
at her shimmering,
when she walks tall,
how he's simmering"
"All stirred up,
look at her light,
when she's gleaming,
it's quite the sight"
"Inquisitive eyes five or six...
Scrutinise her with a smile transfixed"
"The cattle and sheep are taken aback.
Dumbfounded, they just gawk"
"All the scarecrows on the
cornfield are all putting on airs"
"Even the nonchalant crows are
entranced by my sister's blouse"
"The clouds are ganging
up won't they pour for us?"
"We've bottled up much despair
won't they dissolve in the air?"
"While our 'parai'
drums resound dance and rejoice!"
"All dolled up, look
at her shimmering,
when she walks tall,
how he's simmering"
"All stirred up,
look at her light
when she's gleaming,
it's quite the sight"
How dare they?
Who gave them the
right to leave the village?
If they leave,
who'd do the work here?
Apparently,
the Englishman has put it in writing.
Defying it would be anti-national.
We can't do anything, Master.
Or they'll revoke our
taxation rights, landlord.
Get it done with.
What a nightmare.
Not a drop of water in such a big stream?
Oh, I wonder what else awaits us.
Goddess Gangamma, you show mercy on us!
Hey, get over here.
Seize that donkey from him.
And the gun on his shoulder.
You people are to move
and settle in over there.
You'll be provided with rice and
pulses. Don't come back here.
Head straight over there.
- I'm off to see the lord.
- Halt!
Out of the way, idiot.
Think you're an envoy for
the British Viceroy, huh?
Go and sort out the people you've brought.
Wants to see the lord, he says. Scram.
Go.
Go away.
If the Lord had seen me,
he would've rushed right over.
Seems like he's tied up.
Alright, keep moving.
My husband!
Dad!
Arasani! My love!
Oh, Arasani!
What's all this?
Why did you come, child?
Who brought you here?
I told them not to!
Where is Asoka?
Varadha, where is Asoka?
Asoka!
Asoka?
Strange things went down
when you were away, Uncle.
What?
That Lord Clement you keep
gushing about...
he brought those guards and
gunned down the Nagas of the hills, Uncle.
Elderly, children -they spared
no one. They stabbed them all.
The poor people ran,
scared out of their wits.
But one old man got caught.
Asoka has been acting strange
ever since he heard that man's wailing.
Poor child keeps looking up,
looking down, then this way and that.
Where is he?
- Since he hit the guards--
- What?
- they beat him up real bad, Uncle.
I couldn't do a thing, Uncle.
What are you saying?
Where is he?
Asoka.
Where is Asoka?
Answer me.
Where is he?
Asoka, my boy.
My child, my dear boy...
Wake up, son.
Open your eyes.
Asoka!
Lord, will you look at my boy?
Sir, please spare my child.
That's my son!
What are you staring at?
Break his bones.
Hit him.
Step back, back!
First rip those English clothes off him.
Go!
Oh, dear.
Lord!
Enough. Step away.
Lord.
Lord, look at my boy.
They have thrashed him, Lord.
I've never laid a hand on my boy.
They've torn away my clothes, Lord.
I am deeply sorry,
Thangalaan. Deeply sorry.
Kailasam...
- Release this boy.
- Sir...
Do it.
Asoka...
He is not in good health.
- Give him all the assistance he needs.
- Yes, sir.
- Brother...
- Asoka!
Kailasam, look after the labourers.
Make sure they settle.
It's okay...
These are my people, Lord.
I've bought them all here, at your behest.
My thanks to you all.
We...
are creating history...
...at this time.
You all have rights...
over the gold that we mine.
But it is Thangalaan...
that you need to thank for this.
He is a truly remarkable man...
...who has restored
pride to your community.
May all you be safe
in your endeavours.
Yes, sir.
The Lord says...
You are my slaves.
Wage labourers.
- Mind your jobs.
- No...
He is twisting the Lord's words.
That is not what he said.
We are going to create history here.
We all have rights over
the gold we find here. Yes.
Our futures will be bright.
Thangalaan...
it's all thanks to me.
That's what the Lord said.
And also...
he apologised for them hitting me.
Take your belongings.
Let's go to our stay.
The Lord seems to have
such respect for Thangalaan.
Indeed, Uncle.
Tonight,
I will satiate all of my cravings.
Don't cry!
The white man has held on to
the monster's idol despite my warnings.
I was desperate to see you, Dad.
But now I'm terrified
of all that I'm hearing.
The Lord promised us a portion of the gold
we discover here, okay?
Let's collect it, finish the construction
of Lord Perumal's temple...
and convert all the slum-dwellers to
follow Ramanujam's teachings, okay?
Then who'll dare label us low born?
Why do you keep
staring at the dress?
Didn't those guards stain and tear it?
You acted like an English lord.
They couldn't stand to see it.
"How could he stand as our equal,
like a respectable man?"
They just can't take it.
Anyway, stop dwelling on it.
Throw it aside and come.
Hey, why is our boy acting strange?
Something doesn't feel right.
You're keeping secrets from me.
What are you implying?
Don't worry, just trust me.
Why haven't you left this place
where death is certain?
Why linger here?
Leave at once.
You are making a mistake.
Gold is a treacherous ghost.
It will kill you.
It will kill you all.
Go, warn everyone.
Tell them to leave this place at once.
Shut up!
Stop blabbering.
Give that.
Hey, what are you thinking?
Why are you just standing transfixed?
We've overcome many dangers,
why let this faze us?
Come on, now.
- We are here now, let's get to work.
- These are my workers.
Thangalaan.
Let us begin.
Come on.
Get to work,
what are you gaping at?
Hey, let's begin.
Guard us,
Lord Perumal.
Get to work.
Come on now.
Let's begin.
Bring the tools.
I pray to you, Lord Eshwara.
Jesus, save us.
Till the ground and
gather every piece of stone.
Don't leave out a single stone.
Gold could be hidden
in the dark stones...
or in the ones that appear to
be covered in fungus.
White, red, yellow, or black -
gold could be in any type of stone.
Understood?
Take all the stones you've collected
and dump them over there.
Then smash those stones, grind to dust,
mix them with water...
and unload them here,
where the Englishmen are.
Understand? Hurry up.
Idiots!
- Mayandi.
- Mayan.
Arasani, step forward.
He got us the wages as promised.
Thangalaan is a man of his word.
Let's earn enough wages
to buy back our lands.
The end has come.
Make merry for one last time.
Aaran.
You tree that has forgotten its roots!
This war that has raged
through centuries...
is about to end now.
Hey, what is wrong?
Nothing.
What do you mean "nothing"?
The spirits are baying for blood.
Strange things are unfolding.
You are hiding something from me.
I am not hiding anything.
You're not?
Whatever was running in your head
is now running in his head too.
What's happened to my son?
He was all well.
What have you done to him,
bringing him out here!
Don't cry, dear.
What happened to me
is now happening to him.
That Aarathi...
she's possessed my head--
Not again!
Aarathi, Aarathi, Aarathi!
She's not real.
She is just a lore.
This is not a lore.
It's the truth.
You keep running in your head
the stories you heard as a child...
...and now you're searching for it.
It is true, yes.
Snap out of it.
This is not a lore.
Gengamma.
This is true, this is not a lore.
This is not a lore.
She who has been running in my head,
I saw her with my own eyes.
I fought her.
I shot her with these hands.
This is not a lore.
This is true.
Everything is true.
Stop babbling nonsense,
and come sleep.
Everything is true.
Hey, please believe me.
I saw her in flesh and blood.
Right here.
She emerged as the leader of the Nagas.
They whisked her away
and ran when I shot at her.
They did not run away.
They will return.
Get lost, you.
Who are you talking to?
To her, standing right here.
Mother...
whether or not you're real,
whether or not you're here...
we've left our homeland
and the soil that fed us...
waded through wilderness
to make a living here.
Please spare my husband,
my child and my people.
You will be blessed for ages.
My dearest, divine mother!
Reveal where the gold is, Mother.
We shall return home.
This is gold, isn't it?
Dear, look!
Get over here.
This must contain gold, right?
It is gold.
Hey, it is just a rock.
It's not gold?
- Damn it.
- My precious, to me, you are gold.
Soon, we'll find gold
and you'll be decked in it.
- I was sure that was gold...
- We'll find it soon.
- But I thought that was gold.
- We will find gold.
Idiot! Stand up, rise.
Get back to work.
You are always goofing around.
Get to work.
What are you staring at?
Get back to work.
Hey, be swift.
So far, we have found...
some percentage of iron,
some percentage of silver...
but no gold in this land.
It is true.
This land is disappointing us.
Which rocks do contain gold?
It is not to be seen in black,
white or even red-coloured rocks.
Okay, I will show you.
We have all these rocks in our village.
We came all the way here to pick these?
What do you keep staring at?
I am looking for my husband's mistress.
I wonder where she is.
She causes him such distress.
If I happen to find her...
I will rip her to pieces.
Ma, do you mean the ghost?
Why? You think I can't take her?
Sister.
Look, it is Aarathi.
- Where?
- Over there.
Over there.
Where is she?
I don't see her.
I am... I am...
Aarathi.
You people...
will be led to your doom.
- Hey! Arasani!
- What happened?
Get back to work.
- I am going to whack you.
- Get back to work.
Did I scare you, sister?
Hey, shut up.
- Get to work, Varadha.
- Did I scare you?
Oh, get lost.
What do I do with you?
Everybody stop laughing
and do the work.
Hey, keep working.
Something is shining.
Lord...
Hey, come here...
Callous beast.
Varadha, bring me the Kariyat leaves.
- Tie this up.
- Arthur, what's happened?
A snake bit him.
Take him to my tent, quickly.
Hey... look at all those snakes!
Here, get over here.
Come on, kids.
Get up, Asoka.
- Ashoka, come.
- Ma.
Oh, no! My child!
Hey, come here.
Gengamma.
What is this?
The venom has spread.
She is not breathing.
Varadha, bring me the Kariyat leaves.
Her head has slumped.
Look, her head is down...
- Oh, no!
- My little girl is gone!
My child.
Open your eyes, dear.
My baby...
My baby died before my eyes.
"The tall dreams of our ancestors"
"They've come crashing down to dust"
"Oh Earth, Oh Earth
You rugged Earth"
"You devoured the king of kings
You bloody red earth"
"As the blood of the good men
Flows through your veins"
"Now this great clan
Faced with a never-ending famine"
Her bloodlust won't be quenched.
Don't you know?
How our forefathers mined the gold here?
We need to do the same.
How did we discover the gold
under the Saint's idol?
It was revealed by the blood
of the Naga woman.
This is an age-old conflict.
That forest girl is who
we now know as Aarathi.
It is when her blood drenches the soil...
that all the gold here
will be revealed to us.
Go on and gear up for the task.
Uncle...
what are you saying?
If I intended to do such a thing,
I'd have done it on the day we arrived.
If not by toiling,
how else can we earn?
Do you think I'll dance to her whims?
You will break this rock.
That is an order.
We can't grieve for your loss.
We are losing time.
There are no ghosts or monsters here.
You won't drop dead.
I want that glittering rock.
Get to work.
A rock from the era of the king.
The same glittering rock.
If we fall apart,
we will remain fallen.
Let's get to work, move!
We are almost there.
Rise. Get up.
Breaking this rock is no easy task.
Gather all the mud around carefully.
Don't stop, keep working.
This is not enough.
- That's all you get, move it.
- How is this fair for six of us?
From now, you will be paid
only if you find gold.
What are you looking at?
Chase them away.
Uncle, they're saying we will be paid
only if we find gold.
We trusted you.
What fresh hell will
you bring upon us now?
- We are hungry, master.
- How dare you, scoundrels?
I have lost all hope.
Whilst you're lying there.
Sleeping.
You are selfish, my friend.
You are selfish.
You won't even drink with me.
Are you going to drink with me?
Drink, drink, drink...
Kill me!
No one...
there is no one.
Get up!
I know...
that you are mocking me.
You are trying to make a fool
out of Clement.
There is gold here.
Why would you not show it to me?
Am I not worthy enough?
Am I not worthy?
Where is the gold?
You...
Lord.
Lord...
Lord?
This is all your fault!
It's your fault.
You are the reason behind all of this.
It's all your fault!
Aaran...
Each of your misdeeds drives a
deeper wedge between us.
Yet, in truth, you're
meant to be alongside me.
You share responsibility
for this gold too.
Don't talk in riddles.
Quit bothering me.
I...
I am going to bring my
people to break this rock...
and mine all the gold from here.
Oh, no!
Our huts catching fire by themselves.
We have no food here.
It's better to be out of jobs
than to die here.
Let's get out of here.
Wait up, guys.
There is gold in that rock.
Believe me.
Let's burn the rock,
and break it...
and turn our lives around
with the gold from that rock.
Remember what the Lord promised us?
That we all get a share of the gold.
I will get it for everyone.
Listen to me...
- Gengu, don't leave!
- Go away.
We're all leaving.
None of us will stay back.
Priest!
I will kill you.
Spare him.
Gengu.
Lord, don't do it!
Trying to run away, are you?
I'll kill you all.
You can never run from me.
O Brother...
Constantly cursing our oppressors
is pointless.
Rise, stand tall, and march ahead
to alter your fate.
The bull is here to satisfy our hunger.
Every single last one of you...
Oh, sacrificial bull.
Your food has arrived.
Eat well.
Eat it well and become so strong that
not just that rock...
but all the hardships of our people
should crumble.
Yes!
Those who sacrificed
their lives for our freedom...
we are nothing but their remains.
My children are gone.
Uncle Muniyan is no more.
Many others are gone too.
The upper castes beat us
and the white men kill us...
but should we give up our fight?
No.
- Is this fight merely for gold and riches?
- No.
For generations,
we've fought to reclaim the dignity,
pride and rights of our people.
Yes.
Life here is for those
who brave death.
Yes, yes!
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
The gold we're on the brink of mining...
is set to change our lives.
Gold will kill you.
The rock is hot now.
If we dig now,
we'll get all the gold.
Keep striking, don't stop.
These are the Chola mines.
Not just Cholas...
this is the where even Tipu Sultan
attempted and failed to get gold.
Lord, this is the Chola mine
I told you about.
We've found the gold.
Arasani, we've found the gold.
Gold.
Uncle, look. It is gold.
Narayana! Lord Perumal!
You showed us the way.
Narayana!
Watch me turn these into jewellery
and strut around the upper caste women.
You'll look like a queen.
So much gold!
You could have grabbed more gold.
This is plenty for us, sir.
- What?
- There's so much more down there.
We took what we could.
What do you mean you're taking it?
Give it back.
- Why? It's ours!
- Put it down.
Let go of her!
Give me that...
No. No. No.
This gold is mine.
Nobody steals from me.
Nobody.
Dear!
Wake up, dear.
- Dearest...
- This belongs to me.
- Oh no, my love!
Do you hear me?
Kailasam.
You will tell them...
if anyone steals from me...
I will kill every single last one of them.
Open your eyes, my dear.
- Yes, sir.
- Tell them.
Hey...
The gold you mine here
doesn't belong to any of you.
Put it all here.
If any of you dare to take it,
you'll meet the same fate.
Understand?
Arrogant pricks.
Now, get me all of it.
Now.
Now, mine me all the gold
Or I will feed you to the dogs.
Hey Gengu, step over here...
and fetch us all that
gold back from your folks.
Remain a loyal slave and you'll have
it all- the rewards, titles, bonuses.
Cut the crap!
Enough with the lies.
You recite the Vedas
but you're tearing down temples.
Who wants your rewards,
titles, and money?
This is our blood and sweat.
We've bled and worked hard
for this, you get me?
How do you have rights that we don't?
Who gave you the rights?
What was your first promise to us?
Didn't you promise us
half of what we dug up?
Now, you're backtracking.
I can't give it.
I won't hand it over.
- I swear on Narayana, it's not happening.
- You imbecile.
How dare you?
Put it down.
Hit me all you want.
I won't give it.
What makes you so bold?
Won't hand it over, huh?
Die, you.
Die.
Look at this, William.
You will go in there
and collect all the gold...
that these dogs are hiding from me.
Do you understand?
Go.
Let us go.
What are you doing?
This is not gold.
It's just some rock
that glitters like gold.
This is not gold.
Hey, stop!
This is not gold?
We worked so hard for this?
What are you guys doing?
Aarathi is playing tricks on us
with rocks that glitter like gold.
It's all her shadow tricks.
Look, look... it's all just rocks.
Why are you fighting?
This...
is...
fake.
I know how to get the real gold.
Now!
Aaran...
He who is unaware of his own self
embodies destruction.
The people who have taken him
as their leader shall follow him to doom.
Despite my warnings,
you still haven't backed down?
You haven't.
You haven't, Aaran?
I will not, Aarathi.
What is it?
Everyone, follow me.
Let's stand with Aarathi.
This is Rebirth and Redemption.
Aarathi.
Attachment is the root cause of suffering.
The duty of protecting the gold
from the ones consumed by greed...
falls upon Aaran and Aarathi.
Aarathi...
Aaran...
The troops on horseback
are approaching our land.
You are the protector of this forest.
We are marching into war to guard our gold
from the bounty hunters.
War!
Aarathi
What is this?
I am Aaran.
And this is my land.
This land belongs to our people.
I will not let you take even
a speck of gold from here.
You...
Do it now.
Now get the gold.
Aarathi.
I...
I have realised who I am.
Forgive me.
Please, forgive me.
We, who went to war...
were defeated.
Just like those people...
we changed our ways of living...
In due course, we were defeated
by the Varna Caste system.
We lost our country,
we lost our lands.
Exiled, we lived on the fringes
of our own villages.
I arrived as Aadhi Muni,
as Kaadaiyan...
as Nadha Muni.
I attempted to find gold
and was deceived.
Now I've arrived as Thangalaan.
It's our responsibility
to protect this forest.
It is also our duty to protect the people
who protect the gold in these forests.
In this material world...
to meet our survival needs that were
snatched away from us...
this is the only way.
Please let us through.
Will gold solve all your problems?
Make way...
Try.
Go!
A new dawn breaks into our lives.
Brother!
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger "
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Break the shackles of caste
Our dawn is near"
"People of the soil shall stand tall
Your 'Parai' beats will resound"
"Break the shackles of caste
Our dawn is near"
"People of the soil shall stand tall
Your 'Parai' beats will resound"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"
"Oh Thangalaan
Thangalaan..."
"Break free, oh harbinger"