Terrific.
What's up, numb-nuts?
Read 'em and weep.
Van Halen at the centrum.
Third row!
You should take jolene, man.
I heard she got big nipples.
This is van freakin' Halen, man.
Get serious.
Besides, I'm just not into girls anymore.
Dude, I'm into guys, too!
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
I'm into women.
Hey, Mary.
I got two tickets to van
Halen this weekend.
What time should I pick you up?
It is miss mcgarricle, Donny.
And that's cute,
but I am your teacher, not your girlfriend.
Whoa, miss mcgarricle,
who said anything about girlfriends?
Let's just start with a summer fling,
couple of hand jobs,
no expectations.
Don't get all psycho on me right away.
That is a month's detention.
What's a hand job?
I don't know, but I think I want one.
Can I go to the bathroom?
No. No talking in detention, Mr. berger.
All right, I'm sorry for what I did.
I promise I won't do it again.
You're in a lot of trouble, Donny.
Wait, you're not gonna
tell my dad, are you?
He'll kick my ass. He's crazy.
What were you trying to do, anyway?
Impress your friends?
Well, you know, you're...
You have a little crush on me?
No.
"No. " So, you...
You don't want me.
No. Yeah.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to say right now.
Is that gum in your mouth, Donny?
You know,
I've been watching you all year, Donny.
When you hit that shot to beat Fairfield
and you were jumping up and down
in your little Larry bird short-shorts
and sweating like ajar of pickles
in the hot sun...
Oh, God.
That was so hot.
Is this really happening?
This is happening.
It's happening right now.
In my office.
Okay. Awesome.
So, I'm totally in.
How do you want to do it?
'Cause I made sex before, lots of ways.
So you want to go straight to hand jobs
or eating me out or taking me from behind?
I'll teach you.
I'm a virgin.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Who? Me?
Hey, Donny, what'd you get?
And if I'm elected
eighth grade class president,
I promise to...
You're getting so good at this!
I promise to do my best to lower prices at
the school stores and...
All of our practice is really paying off!
I like the sound of that.
Timmy, stop. Hold on a second.
My dad's gonna kick my ass.
Calm down!
Donny! Donny! Donny! Donny!
Who's the man?
Yeah! You want some of me? Who's the man?
All right, everybody!
Enough!
I am aware that a lot of people think
that this young man
is not really a victim,
but someone that's living
the ultimate teenage boy's fantasy.
Absolutely.
But this is a serious crime.
Mary Beth mcgarricle, rise for sentencing.
The fact that this relationship
has resulted in a pregnancy
and you show absolutely no remorse,
saying, and I quote,
I would fuck that kid again and again.
"He makes me feel like there's a rainbow
coming out of my beaver."
Leaves me absolutely no choice
but to Levy the maximum penalty.
Thirty years
in the Massachusetts women's penitentiary.
And furthermore, the court grants custody
of the unborn child
to Donald berger's father...
Dumb-ass.
Until Donald turns 18,
at which time he will assume full custody.
Take care of our baby, Donny!
Miss mcgarricle!
I'll never stop loving you!
That is just fucking mental.
The kid is young, he's attractive,
he can probably keep a hard-on
longer than this fucking guy.
Made you flinch, pansy.
Go ahead! I don't need you!
I'm Donny freakin' berger!
I'm wicked famous
and I got a wicked big sch-long!
Hey, here's something.
Donny berger's back in the news.
That kid who got his teacher pregnant?
- Exactly.
- I love that guy.
Seems like he bought a round last night.
Okay... For everybody
in Boston garden.
Oh, my God, he's my hero.
That kid is burning through that money,
but he's having a good time doing it.
So, guy, how'd we do?
What them fuckers at the IRS say?
Well, they said a lot of stuff.
The thing that really jumped out
- was "three years in prison."
- Three years?
Yeah, you haven't paid taxes
since '94, Donny.
What... I thought they were
taking it out automatically!
I told them that's what you thought,
and they said
it's the stupidest thing they ever heard.
But there is some good news.
If you can pay
the balance off by the end of the weekend,
they'll suspend the sentence.
Oh, okay, there you go.
What are we talking about? Hit me.
Forty-three thousand.
Forty-three grand?
No!
Come on, Donny!
Don't screw up my tom Brady poster.
It's my favorite one.
Look at that jaw line.
Just the right amount of scruff.
I'm sorry! I'm just freaking out here!
I don't got 43 grand!
Well, look, hey, good news.
Monday's Memorial Day,
so you don't need
to get the money till Tuesday.
All right. That'll give me time to
sell my diamond lamborghini!
Hey, hey, hey! You're killing me, man!
Don't mess with the genius.
Jimmy, I got $28 to my name.
Twenty-eight, huh? Okay.
I got a hot tip on a long shot
that just might come in.
- What is it, a horse?
- No.
This is tubby tuke, fat guy.
Fat guy?
Gonna run the marathon.
Odds on him winning are 8,000-to-1.
But this cat's got wheels on him.
I think he's gonna win, I really do.
All right, I'll put 20 on the fat fuck,
but I can't count on that.
It's a long shot, you said it yourself.
But what about your kid?
Maybe he can come up with the dough.
We don't talk no more.
He kind of moved out when he turned 18,
and that's the last I seen of him.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
I loved that little han solo
more than anything in the world, too.
- You named your kid han solo?
- Yes, sir.
Han solo berger?
Coolest name in the world, right?
Why don't you just Facebook him?
I can't afford that shit.
What am I, a billionaire?
I don't think he wants
to be found, anyways.
Especially by me.
Hey, look! It's us!
- On the cover!
- Don't we look great?
Yeah, well, you look good.
I kind of look like a ventriloquist.
I don't know, it's still
kind of weird, right?
I mean, it's got our faces and our names.
It just seems like anyone could find us.
"Find us"?
Honey, did you take your Xanax today?
Yeah, two.
I always double down
when your parents are in town.
Do you have your security undies?
- Yep, right here.
- Good.
I know that makes you feel better.
There's stranger things than walking around
with an extra pair of underwear
for emergencies.
Look, just this once, don't be so weird.
We're gonna have the best wedding ever.
Okay.
Holy shit. What the hell happened
to my life, champale?
Don, honey, no way to come up
with that money, huh?
No. The only thing
I'm good at is being Donny berger,
and no one wants to pay for that anymore.
Aw, Donny.
Wow!
My face is your toilet!
Show some fucking respect
over there, Kenny.
Hey, whoa.
Hey, mom, did you want
some breakfast after you finish your dance?
Give it to me now, honey.
Donny doesn't mind, do you, Donny?
Holy cow, that's my son!
Who, han solo?
I thought you said he was a fatty.
No, no, no.
He must have lost the weight or something,
'cause I swear to God, that's my boy.
It says, "Todd Peterson to
wed Jamie Martin this Sunday"
"at all saints church on Cape COD."
Todd Peterson?
He changed his name!
Why?
What was wrong with han solo berger?
It's the coolest fucking name of all time.
"Peterson is one of the youngest"
"large-cap hedge fund managers
in the financial industry."
He got rich on us, huh?
"All the more impressive
considering he was orphaned"
"at age nine, when both his parents died
in a horrific explosion."
He fucking blew me up and his mother?
Donny, maybe your son could
help you, financially.
I don't know. This kid changed his name.
He doesn't even want
to be a berger anymore.
He's not gonna want to talk to me.
That was the incomparable champale.
And now, looking hot
and ignoring doctor's orders,
let's welcome Amber.
What the fuck happened to her?
Fuck you, Kenny!
Hey, what's up, robe-cop?
This is where your boss lives?
It's actually just his summer home.
- Summer home. What a dick.
- Dad!
Oh, my goodness.
Todd, it's just breathtaking!
Hey! There he is.
Hey, Mr. Spirou.
There's my golden boy.
Come over here, champ.
Come on, get over here.
Hi. Yeah.
Look at you.
Look at you, the lovely bride.
What a couple!
Mr. Spirou, it's so amazing
that you're letting us all stay here.
Seriously, thank you so much.
Steve, these are
my parents, Gerald and Helen.
- It's a pleasure.
- Hi.
Your daughter's a sweetheart.
You can tell she likes Todd for Todd,
not because he's gonna be rich.
I wouldn't want
my boy to end up with some gold digger
like the last three whores I married, huh?
True story. All three? Whores.
Well, guys, this weekend,
mi casa es su casa.
You know, every member of my staff
are lucky to be in this country,
so feel free to abuse the shit out of 'em.
Go get the fucking bags!
Well, Mrs. Spirou,
I've always said that if the finance game
was an amusement park,
your son would be a roller coaster,
and I would just ride him all day long.
That came out weird.
Yeah, well, Stevie likes to think
that he's the star of the family.
But before he was born,
I modeled a bathing suit
for a woolworth advertisement.
Well, you still have
quite a figure on you there, delores.
Yeah, I can see
where Steve got his rocking bod.
Why, thank you.
Chad's here!
- Oh, my God.
- Hooray.
Fantastic.
I guess they didn't want to see it.
Yay, Chad!
- Come here.
- Mom.
- Sweetheart.
- I'm home.
Dad, how are you, sir?
- You look great.
- Thank you, sir.
Hey, Chad, I'm Todd.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, I missed you, sis.
That's a good hug.
Chad, this is my fiancé, Todd.
Pleasure to meet you, chadwick.
Are you a soldier?
No.
- Sailor?
- No.
- Airman?
Girl scout?
No.
Well, then I'd prefer if you take
your fingers away from your forehead
and you shake my hand
like the civilian you are.
Yeah, sorry, I'm stupid.
I don't know why I did that.
Honest mistake. Come here,
I want to show you this.
Look, if you ever do anything
to hurt my sister, I will take
my government-issued service revolver,
stick it straight up your fuppin'
poop chute, and empty the clip.
Do you feel me?
Yes, I totally feel you... dawg.
Randy Jackson, right?
I've got 10 ways
to kill you with my bare hands right now.
Don't. Don't.
Hi, sweetheart, how are you?
Can I see Randall Morgan possibly?
Yeah, you're gonna need an appointment.
I knew you were gonna say that.
But you know what?
Tell him Donny berger's out here.
He'll be pretty psyched
to see an old friend.
You know what? Mr. Morgan's
on vacation right now. I'm sorry.
- He's on vacation? That son of a...
- Oh, hey!
Vanilla ice.
Randall's just getting makeup.
Go ahead to the green room.
Vanilla, what's up, guy?
It's been a long time. How you been?
Are you seriously giving me
the silent treatment still?
You know that hurts me.
Yeah? Well, that's why
I'm giving it to you.
How's it feel, chump?
It's breaking my heart.
We were friends for 20 years, guy.
We were friends until you banged my mother!
I didn't know it was her, I swear to God!
It's not like her last name is ice.
You should've known by the haircut!
Aw, come on, vanilla bean latte.
- Will you just...
- What?
I'm just saying, I'm in big trouble, guy.
This, like, monetary thing.
I'm going to prison
if I don't get 43 large, so...
What, do you think I got
that kind of money?
Of course you got that kind of money.
Royalties from ice ice baby,
you must be fucking loaded!
Man, listen, queen took 50%.
Suge took the other 60%.
I fucking owe money when
that shit gets played, man!
Dude, come on, will you please
stop, collaborate and listen?
- Oh, here...
- What? No, I love that song.
You know that shit.
I was on top of that, fucking day one.
Listen, man. I work at a ice rink now.
I deep-fry chicken nuggets, man.
I'll get you a deal on
a barbecue sauce packet.
Fucking a, buddy.
Both of us. This sucks.
Broke. Who'd have thought
this would happen to us?
Maybe I should call your mother.
She'll give me the money, I know that.
- What?
- What? What? What?
Hey, dude.
Didn't spill my beer, fucker.
Fuck you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Nobody comes in here
and starts busting up my joint
unless I got cameras rolling.
Look, Donny,
nobody remembers what Tiger Woods did,
let alone something
that happened 25 years ago.
I'm telling you, when I
walk down the street,
people are like, "there's that guy!"
I'm still fucking big, dude.
All right, how about this?
I'm doing a show on '80s train wrecks.
Maybe I slip you in
after that milli vanilli guy, all right?
- Who, fab? He's a fucking buddy of mine.
- Yeah.
That would be huge, dude.
How much money?
Maybe 400 bucks.
Four hundred bucks?
Dude, I need 43 g-birds.
What are we talking about right now?
You need $43,000?
Are you back on drugs?
- Yeah.
- It's never...
This is never going to happen. Never.
Little bit more blush if you can.
Just like you did that John Wayne bobbitt
in his penis reunion show.
That's actually a good idea, a reunion.
Me and miss mcgarricle, together again,
live from a women's prison.
A women's prison.
Very sexy.
We could shoot it this weekend.
You could give me the money.
Very sexy.
You know, you could eat that ass
after I leave the room,
but I need an answer right now.
What do you think?
What about your kid?
My kid? What about my kid?
He's got to be a walking gong show.
No. What are you talking about?
He's doing great.
He's, like, a hot shit now.
He's getting married
- down at the cape this weekend.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
"Horny teacher baby makes good."
Smell that? Smell it, Donny?
What? That's not me.
She probably cut the cheese.
No, no, no. No, ratings.
I smell ratings.
My kid is very publicity-shy, so I...
You know, to be honest,
I don't think he'd do
a piece of shit show like this.
All right, here's the deal.
You get yourself and your actual kid
up to the women's
prison this weekend, I will shoot it,
I will give you 50 grand in cash.
'Cause I'm going to guess, Donny,
you want to be visiting a prison,
not living in one.
So, Todd, how does one get into
the hedgehog business anyway?
Oh, it's actually hedge funds.
You think you're better than me?
No.
Chad, did you know
that Todd is really great with numbers?
- You got to see this.
- Jamie, no. Don't make...
What's 452 times 77?
84,304.
Oh, he could just be making that up.
No, he's not!
There's a calculator on my cell phone.
Okay.
What is 94
times 312, Todd?
29,328, Helen.
Freaky.
I don't know. It's just something I can do.
Are you sure you're not a chinaman?
Oh, that's inappropriate.
White whore.
I'll get it.
Oh, my God. You must be Jamie.
You're, like, even hotter
than you looked in the paper.
Look at your hair,
blowing in the wind like tawny kitaen
when she was fucking dry-humping that car.
Okay.
And you must be...
Donny.
What's the matter?
Chubby never even mentioned me?
Chubby?
Oh, I mean Todd Peterson.
Why do you say it like that?
It just comes out that way.
Where are my manners, right?
Could you hold that?
Take a chug if you'd like.
I got you a fucking great gift.
Here it is.
I'll take the brew back.
Just, you got to read it, though.
It's fucking...
Yeah!
I don't know where they
come up with this shit,
but it's pretty fucking funny.
Spencer's gifts never fucking fails me.
I want to meet Mr. Spencer one day and say,
"thanks, motherfucker, for all the laughs."
Hey, I also made you a mix tape.
Who the fuck is rich in this house?
Jeezum, it's huge.
Todd, your old man is here?
'Wassup!
Helen, oh, my gosh. I'm so sorry.
No, it's... Let me
just get that for you.
- That's...
- What? No.
Oh, sorry, those are yours. I...
Donny, what... what the fuck, man? Sorry.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I thought you said your parents were dead.
No, they are. Super dead.
He's hilarious.
My old man.
My old man friend.
From...
'Wassup!
Right?
Well, aren't you going to introduce us?
- No.
- Yes.
Yes. Here we go.
This is my future father-in-law, Gerald,
and his lovely wife, Helen.
And Jamie's brother, Chad.
- Hey-0!
- Don't. That's...
What?
I like the look of this. Who's this?
Okay. This is my boss Steve's mother,
delores, who's awake now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's where you
get all the looks from, huh, sweetie?
Yeah, no, we're not related.
Oh, yeah? Well, she wishes,
'cause you got the fucking...
You're stacked pretty good.
Anyhow, jame, this is my old friend, Donny.
Your best friend.
I'm his best friend.
Yeah, no.
Remember I told you we met...
Where'd we meet?
- We met...
- Where?
- Come on.
- It's coming to me.
I saved his life.
Well, more metaphorically.
No, no, no, no, no. Here's what happened.
It was, like,
one of them train track kind of deals.
My man over here, I see him,
he drops his burrito on the tracks.
I'm like, "all right, that happens."
Next thing you know,
homeboy leaps down there,
and he tries to retrieve the burrito.
Okay? I see a train whizzing at him.
I'm like, "this guy's about to die,
and he don't know it."
I fucking leap down there myself, right,
and I give him a little
shove on the heinie.
"Get out of the way, buddy!"
Next thing you know, I realize
this thing's going to hit me.
I fucking remember, though,
I had a kung fu instructor
who taught me
how to tighten the diaphragm,
and I bring it in there.
And I feel the train go by.
My eyes are closed.
Rips my shirt off my body, okay?
I open my eyes.
I see all these chicks just kind of looking
at me, going, "what is that?"
"That's the fucking
most chiseled guy I've ever seen."
I worked out at the time.
Anyways, the place goes bananas for me,
I sign a couple of titties,
and I started hanging out
with this guy ever since.
Best friends, right? Here you go, my boy.
I just can't believe
I've never heard that story before.
Why wouldn't you just
get another burrito, Todd?
Wouldn't it be dirty?
Great questions.
It's one of the many things about this
story that's pretty hard to believe.
So, where are you staying, Donny?
He's not staying.
No.
I can't stay. Yeah, no, he's right.
Oh, pshaw. I mean, invite him to stay here.
You have to stay.
He's your best friend.
You're his best friend.
Sheesh, I'm not messing with her.
I mean, you are my best friend, guy.
And, Jamie, you can be my breast friend.
Breast, with an with an.
By the way, dude, you look fantastic.
You lost all the weight, homeboy.
I miss the titties.
You saved my life? Seriously?
What? They ate that up.
You came up with a whole lot of nothing.
That's a nice suitcase, by the way.
What is that, Louis Vuitton?
This is a hefty bag.
What the fuck are you talking about?
What do you want, Donny? Money?
You heard I was doing well,
so you came looking for a handout?
I don't want none of your money.
How is that? Okay?
I get it. You don't like me.
I exploded.
I wish you had exploded.
That way, I wouldn't have to
see your stupid face anymore!
Did you happen to notice
I created a whole fake life
just so I could get away from you?
Your mother's sick, by the way.
I don't believe you.
They don't know how long she's got.
What is that, nunchucks?
I told her you would
visit her up at the prison.
I'm kind of thinking you're the kind of guy
who would pull through for mumsie.
Know what I'm saying?
She'd do the same for you.
Really?
Yeah. Saturday's the last visiting day
before the big surgery, so...
So let me get this straight.
You want me to go visit my "sick mom"
that I haven't talked
to in years, in prison,
the day before my wedding.
Correct.
Not happening, asshole.
What the fuck did I do to you
to make you hate me so much?
I am fucking baffled right now.
Well, maybe you don't remember, but you
were basically the worst parent ever.
Me? I did everything for you, buddy,
and I never gave you
an ounce of shit about nothing.
You never gave me nothing.
I gave you a snake.
Yeah, and then it died
after it ate all your quaaludes.
That was the only time
any body's ever seen a king cobra laugh.
And I take pride in that, so fuck you.
Yeah, great. You know what?
I basically had to raise myself, Donny.
I never learned how to swim.
I don't even know how to ride a bike.
You know how fucking humiliating that is?
What about Mr. mitty? Remember him?
What? No. What's that?
Mr. mitty. I used to put
an oven mitt on my hand.
He would cheer you up
all the time when you were sad.
"Don't be upset, young man."
"I'm your best friend."
"Even though I'm an oven mitt."
No, I don't remember that, okay?
You know what I do remember?
You making me
drive you home from the beach
'cause you got too drunk.
It makes sense to me.
When somebody's hammered,
they have another guy drive home.
I was eight!
Well, you looked 14
'cause you were such a huge fat fuck.
I'm sorry.
You are such an asshole.
Dude, you're a millionaire now,
and you're marrying that hot chick.
I must have done a pretty decent
job as a dad, don't you think?
Oh, yeah? You want to check in
on your pretty decent job?
Oh, my God.
You're a junkie? 'Who's your supplier?
'Cause I'll smack that motherfucker around.
It's Insulin, you dick.
I'm a diabetic 'cause you let me eat
cake and lollipops for breakfast every day.
But that's what you fucking asked for.
Yeah, you're supposed to say no.
You know, I weighed 400 pounds
by the time I was 12.
You know how hard it was
to take that weight off?
All right, all right.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I had no one helping me.
Grandpa was a psycho. You know that.
Han solo, don't be like this.
I'm a good person.
Okay, don't call me that, all right?
My name's Todd now.
Call yourself han solo.
You're dressed like him.
Good one.
I'm just saying, buddy, give me a chance.
Do you have any axe body spray?
No, Donny, I don't have any axe body spray.
Because I'm not a fucking douche bag.
That's a douche bag thing?
When did that become a douche bag thing?
Todd, the guests are arriving. Let's go!
All right, can you lighten up a little bit?
We got a party to attend.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Good person, how about
you put on a tie, okay?
It's a cocktail party,
not a quiznos opening.
'What? I haven't worn a tie
since my mother's funeral when I was three.
I'm not going to start that up again.
That's great. Put on a tie.
- No.
- Put on a tie!
I'll never sell out.
I'll give you 100 bucks.
Where's the tie?
Look at this.
Jamie is going to have it all.
By the way, Mr. Spirou,
I read the opec report, and I was thinking,
if we hedge our position on oil,
we could really...
If we were to short the euro, we could...
Come on, Todd.
This is your wedding weekend.
You are marrying a real workaholic.
You do know that.
Yeah, but isn't that
what you want in a partner?
She's good, this one.
She's good.
All right, all right.
I haven't made that decision yet,
but I love this kid.
You lost your dad in that explosion,
and I lost my son.
I thought your son
was a ski instructor in vail.
He's a pot-smoking bum!
Not like you, Todd. Oh, no.
You're the type of boy
a father can be proud of.
Yeah, we'll never know, will we?
- Who's that?
- I'm not here.
That's Donny.
Donny, come on. Say hi to everyone.
Oh, God, hang on.
Let me swing these free.
Glad all the children saw that.
Donny.
This is Steve Spirou, Todd's boss.
'Wassup!
Is that back?
Because I've been dying
for that to come back.
'Wassup!
Yeah!
That's my boy! Look at him!
He ain't a tight-ass.
'Wassup!
- 'Wassup! - 'Wassup!
- 'Wassup!
'Wassup!
What's up?
Boo!
That was terrible, Todd.
So, I see the train coming,
and something
kind of like takes over me, you know?
- Here you go, Abigail.
- Thank you.
And so, I decide to jump
off the platform, right?
Snaps my legs in two.
What did I expect?
It was a 25-foot drop, you know?
Twenty-five feet?
So I grab burrito bandito over here,
and I just roll him out of the way.
The train missed our skulls by inches.
Why would you do
something like that, Todd?
You know, I really don't know, Steve.
I mean, why wouldn't you
just buy another burrito?
Yeah, no, I know.
I don't know what I could
have been thinking.
Maybe he was high on the hashish.
Hey, how about I
get you another beer, huh, Donny boy?
Twenty's my limit.
No! No, no.
But, Donny boy
has got to go to bed, though, right?
Oh, fiddlesnatch.
It's the afternoon.
Remember you told me
you wanted to get to bed early?
Oh, okay. Yeah, no, no, no.
Todd's right.
Oh, my God.
You're right, it is him.
- You're Donny berger.
- It's him.
Do you remember that kid who got
his teacher pregnant in somerville?
Wait a minute, that is you.
Donny berger.
Didn't you and your teacher have a kid?
Wait a minute. What was his name?
Indiana Jones, huh?
It was something fantastic like that.
Yeah, han solo berger.
Yeah, han solo, han solo.
What ever happened to him?
What happened to him?
He actually became a dick.
A private eye, I mean.
One of the biggest
and hairiest dicks in the world.
Okay.
Hey, look, this might seem weird,
but do you think you would ever...
Bone your wife? Yeah, I mean, I'd love to.
She's a hot little number.
'Well, you know, I was just
going to ask you for an autograph, but...
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry. On her tits or...
- Or a piece of paper would be fine.
- Yeah, or a photo.
Okay, well, this has been fun.
- But, Donny...
- Not to toot my own horn,
but I got kind of close once.
Mrs. weiss, freshman geometry.
And I think she would have done it, too.
I just didn't know how to make the move.
You know what? I would have killed
to bang my eighth grade
biology teacher, Mrs. cohn.
I used to dream of
dissecting her with my penis.
It's so weird what goes on upstairs
when you hit puberty.
I actually stole
my middle school librarian's glasses
to wear while I masturbated.
What is that about?
In my day, when I got into trouble,
the headmaster would
slap your hand with his dick.
She wins.
You know, Todd was working at the cubicle
next to mine one year,
12 weeks and one day ago
when he met a pretty girl
at the gym named Jamie.
How many days is that, Todd?
Computing, Steve.
451.
It's actually 450.
Battle of the brainiacs!
Yeah, this guy forgot
about leap year, I guess.
He's smarter than Todd!
Okay, we're talking a lot about numbers,
but let's get back to love.
What's the matter, hot stuff?
Where do you think you get it from?
Your mother was a math teacher,
and I was pretty much a whiz kid myself.
The ability to make a bong
out of a taco bell cup
doesn't make you a whiz kid, Donny.
Leap year, motherfucker.
I think it's kind of a magical moment.
You know, Todd's oldest friend, Donny,
miraculously appearing like this.
What?
So I am graciously
going to step aside and allow Donny
to take over as the best man.
Give it up for Donny!
Oh! No; No,
Phil, you don't have to do that.
No music. No, no, no, no.
Kill the music. Phil, Phil, you...
That's so nice of you,
but you don't have to do that.
Oh, I don't mind. You two are very close.
We are. We are very close,
but you and I are close, too.
Well, we work together,
but I wouldn't call us close.
I mean, I was actually kind of surprised
when you asked me to be your best man.
Made me feel a little sorry for you.
That's true. He had no idea who he was.
No.
I accept. I do. I love it. It's an honor.
- Way to go, Donny!
- Are you kidding me?
You got Fenway park in your backyard?
I had that built
when my son started little league.
He never used it.
The little douche bag
just sat in his room listening to reggae.
Well, let's lose these ties
and hit some dingers.
What do you say? Come on!
No, no, no.
Please, don't let this be happening.
Don't let this be happening, please.
No sports.
All right, guys,
let's see what we got out there.
Please don't hit it to me. Please don't
hit it to me. Please don't hit it to me.
Get under it, kid.
Yeah!
Moron.
Here we go! Taking down two there!
All right, Gerald, kid! Here we go, guy!
Stay on it!
Oh. My God!
Grandma, what's up, honey?
Are you awake, sweetheart?
Here we go.
Get under it! Get dirty!
What the fuck?
- Got it.
- Nice catch, mama!
Let's let Todd-0 get this one, huh?
Oh, no, that's okay.
Todd, come on!
No, no. Hit one to that two-year-old.
He hasn't gotten one yet.
Here you go, big man.
- What?
- Quit showing off
for the girls, buddy. They're mine.
Come on, now.
You got it. You got it.
Okay, Todd, you all set, buddy?
Don't hit it to me.
Coming to you, homie.
Holy shit.
Oh, my God. Are you all right, guy?
Come on. You're fine.
Throw it in there, guy.
I think the ball's broken.
Throw it in, Todd.
Todd, throw the ball.
Come on, Todd!
Throw it, you big vagina. Do it.
Todd, we want to keep playing, buddy.
We need a ball, kid.
Just throw it.
Such a pussy.
On a rope!
Holy fuck!
We now return to the Donny berger story,
starring Ian ziering.
- Yo!
- Donny.
- I'm in a jacuzzi. Hang on one sec.
- Yeah.
Fucking... here.
- Who'll take the cigar?
- Oh, no.
- Donny.
- Keep that lit for me.
Take my fucking shades.
- Wear them if you want.
- Yeah!
All right. So, hang on.
I want to wear them.
I'll be back.
All right.
My goodness!
Yeah, what's going on?
Guess what's on TV?
Hey, there, little buddy.
I'm Mr. mitty.
I will always love you.
What is that, the Donny berger story?
Hell, yeah.
Don't you get money
every time that shit is shown?
This could be your "get
out of jail free" card.
Last check I got for that was 85 cents.
Is han solo gonna do
the show at the women's prison with you?
You know, I haven't
discussed any particulars with him yet.
I am actually just trying
to be a dad right now.
You're gonna go to prison on Tuesday.
You have got to get that money somehow.
Kenny, what the fuck?
I thought this was a bathroom!
Fuck you!
- Honk!
- Oh, nobody squeezes my titty
for free, honey!
Okay, good luck with that.
God, you're such an idiot!
Todd, you already messed up my flowers!
- I'm sorry.
- Just get the cake!
No walnuts! No fucking excuses!
I love you! Do you love me?
What?
"You screwed up my cake!"
It's me, it's me. Can I come in?
- Yeah, sure.
- What's up, buddy?
What was she yelling at?
What'd you do wrong?
She's just stressed out
'cause of the wedding.
Oh, really?
You sure she's not stressed out
about maybe sex or something?
Have you been going down on her?
- What?
- No, I'm just saying,
a lot of times, girls
I've met over the years,
when they've been
ragging on me and yelling at me and shit,
if I kiss their pussies, they kind of go,
"you're right, you're a good guy."
Yeah, that's personal, Donny.
Yeah, no, no.
You know her better than me, fine.
So...
You wear a bathing suit in the shower?
- You know that's fucking nuts, right?
- Are you serious?
I can't even take my shirt off
in front of other people because of you.
Because of me. What did I do this time?
Let me jog your memory.
The new kids on the block!
Holy shit!
Their heads are all warped now!
Oh. My God!
Yeah, it's 'cause I got it
when I was in third grade.
My body grew.
I'm sorry. It's fine, it's fine.
Let me see it again.
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh.
You got a back tattoo.
Their heads are fucking warped.
- You suck.
- Come on, dude.
Why you getting so serious?
I still got the tattoo I got when I was...
'When I was a teenager.
And I'm fine with it, you know.
"De plane! De plane!"
"De plane!"
Yeah, I remember it.
I still don't know who that is.
It's fucking...
"De plane, de plane" guy
from fantasy island.
Tattoo.
I got a tattoo of tattoo.
I thought that was funny.
Well, it's not.
Lighten up, dude. Come on.
- "De plane!"
- Don't. Donny, don't.
- I'm serious.
- "De plane!"
- No.
- You're still ticklish.
No, I'm not ticklish!
- Come on, now!
- The tickle monster.
- I tickle you like that.
- No.
Stop! No, stop it!
Watch yourself.
Stop it! Stop it, no!
Give me that, hansie.
Why is your dick in my face?
And why is it kind of hard?
What are you two homos doing?
Just rasslin'.
All right.
'Cause you're looking at an all-state
fucking wrestling champion,
and I got the winner.
Okay. Well, he won.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah, you did. You won.
What? No, I didn't.
You're gonna love it, buddy. Wrestle him.
- Yeah, Chad.
- No, no.
It's actually a funny story.
We were having a tickle fight.
We weren't wrestling at all.
I was losing, admittedly.
Aw, God, I got to start doing
some crunches or something.
Look at this.
Oh, you don't like him?
Oh, we don't like you.
He's talking to his dick, buddy.
Now he's hitting it.
No! Why?
You got to puff that fucker up!
Oh, what? No.
You don't have to puff that fucker up.
Let's do this.
Chad, I'm sure you're
very athletic... okay!
Okay!
I tap out. You win, you win. I tap out.
Do you like fucking my sister, Todd?
I mean, do you like
sticking your dirty booger fingers in her?
Whoa, what was that?
Let's all just keep our heads, okay?
We've all been drinking a lot tonight.
I'm gonna skull-fuck you...
And that is the end of that.
What, you're mad at me?
How am I the fucking bad guy right now?
You're gonna fucking give me shit
with that tattoo on your back?
Look at that stupid fucking thing.
Good buddy, he'll be fine.
Yeah, so we got Chad
all tucked in, safe and sound.
I never heard of him
passing out drunk before.
Yeah, it was crazy. It was like,
one second, he was with us, totally awake.
Next thing you know, he's face down,
birds a-chirpin'.
What do you think?
You look amazing.
Oh, wait! Isn't it bad luck
for me to see the dress
before the wedding, though?
This is a $12,000 vera wang dress.
I'm gonna wear it whenever I want.
You'd look hot in a $12 wang chung dress.
That sounds like a line Donny would say.
Yeah, except he'd say,
"you'd look friggin' hot
in a wang dang sweet poontang dress."
Just think he's, like,
trailer park-y or something, you know?
- Yeah.
- That's probably why his son ran off.
His what? What? Who? His son about...
What'd he say?
What did you hear? Did he say something?
Just look at the first page of that book
he's been handing out to everyone.
He has? What? No.
Head in the class?
He said it's like head of the class,
only with blowjobs.
It's gross.
Yeah, it's gross. Blowjobs are gross.
We don't do those.
"Dear Jamie,
I know you'll make Todd very happy"
"if you bleach your little brown eye."
Oh, no, not this part.
Wow, that's sad.
That weirdly got me.
I don't know why it got
me, but it just got me.
Can I get a hug right now, or...
No, no, no, no! We can't wrinkle the dress.
Hey, if you don't want
to wrinkle the dress,
may I suggest we just remove it?
Did you take two Xanax?
I actually took three Xanax.
And you know that the Xanax makes me.
"H" to the "o" to the "r"
to the "n" to the "y."
So horny for my fiancée.
No! Down.
I don't want to have sex
with my family in the house.
No, I know.
I don't want to have sex
with your family, either.
In the house.
Came out weird.
Possibly my last night of
spanking the hell out of it
without having a roommate
watching me, so...
What do we got to work with here?
Rich people magazines.
Let's see what we got.
If I hadn't partied with her husband
so many times, I would.
But it's disrespectful to him.
I don't know.
Hello.
Jeezum crow, you really were a model,
weren't you, grandma?
Yeah, old Mr. woolworth really, really knew
how to pick them, didn't he?
I love that old-time bathing suit.
I could take you
to the speakeasy, and we could,
we could do the naked Charleston.
I have to ship out in the
morning to fight the Nazis,
so you better give me
something to remember.
What's that?
Oh, my God.
Old lady grandma wants to
get in on the action, too.
Should we let her?
I think we should.
Oh, my God.
Why do I like her better right now?
Oh, you bad... What
have you done to me?
What have you done to me?
We got to go for round two,
but give me a little bit of time.
Give me a little bit of time.
Oh, lovely.
Just lovely.
Goodness.
Oh, my word.
Best man, wedding rehearsal in an hour.
There's so many tissues.
Oh, God. You know,
don't touch those, okay? Let's...
Okay.
I'm gonna just clean that up.
Yeah, Donny's sick.
You don't want to touch these
'cause you'll get sick.
He's got post-nasal drip, so...
The tissue's stuck to my picture.
Here, let me.
I'll grab that from you. I got it.
Oh, look at that!
There's a little tissue beard there.
No, don't touch it, please.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, that poor dear.
I'll just get him some nice, fresh juice.
Juice. That's a great idea.
Thank you, grandma d. Thanks.
You know, hon,
if he's really under the weather,
maybe it's best
if he doesn't masturbate so much.
That's good advice.
I'll tell him that, thank you.
Okay, you can stop
pretending to sleep, sir jizz-a-lot.
The old broad knew I was whacking to
her the whole time, didn't she?
That's so funny.
But your improves were awesome.
"Post-nasal dick," or whatever you said.
You know, I can't believe
your balls produce that much stuff.
Dude, at least I got balls.
What's that supposed to mean?
Let me just crack open
some happiness first, yeah.
All I'm saying is the Chad thing,
when that dude came at you last night,
you kind of, like,
looked like a deer in headlights.
Your whole aura is
actually that of a pussy.
Or a kiss-ass.
It is not.
It is, too.
What the fuck am I doing?
No, I'm just saying
you got to stand up for yourself
every once in a while, buddy,
or she's never gonna bang you.
I'll have you know, she
bangs me all the time.
All right? She bangs.
Does she live the LA vida loca, too, or...
Very funny.
Well, good day, everyone.
Father.
Father McNally, thank you so much
for coming out to the cape.
My honor.
Very cool.
Oh, yes.
Chad.
You'll excuse me, won't you?
While you're in this church,
you'll show the proper respect.
No e-mailing, no texting,
no face-booking,
no sky-ping and no angry birds.
That one hurts.
No, no. I get it.
It's the 2010s.
Everyone's having sex and drinking lattes.
No, father.
But, you see, this is my world.
We'll abide by my rules while we're here.
Maybe we should start
with the father of the groom.
His father passed away.
He died in an explosion.
Sounds fishy, but it really happened.
I'm truly sorry to hear that, son.
Thank you, but it's fine.
He deserved it.
So... What is that
supposed to mean?
Oh, I didn't mean anything by it.
He just, you know, wasn't a great dad.
So your father, he abused you, did he?
No, nothing like that.
Was he a murderer? Rapist?
No. Father, I'm sorry, I...
My father beat me every day with a rake.
But you don't hear me smack-talking him
like some baby little princess.
Not here in the House of the lord.
You know, I can't hear
a word you're saying.
All I can focus on is your shit breath.
I'd like to show you the
garden for a minute.
Now, then.
Okay, you know what? Let's just...
Fucking old guy's got
- a Cannon on him.
- What happened?
What happened
is I think he's having a mini-meltdown.
- Yeah, he's taking his shirt off now.
- Oh, my God.
And he's pretty ripped for an old fuck,
so we're in trouble right now.
What is going on here?
All right, all right.
Go time, go time.
No, think about what you're doing!
Be careful.
He bit me!
Did you see that? That was amazing!
This could get ugly.
The father actually
killed a guy in the ring.
That's why he became a priest.
Just keep your hands up, kid!
Get 'em down!
Hang in there, guy!
He keeps punching him!
Come on, guy.
That's my boy!
Why, you came right back
with your own shit. Nice, kid.
What the fuck is that?
Okay, he's going to
a whole other place right now.
You know what? Maybe just run.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go, go, go, go, go.
No.
I'm not gonna run.
Finish him, father McNally!
Finish him!
Geez. He went down
like a sack of potatoes, huh?
What is the matter with you?
You know, we've known
father McNally for 30 years.
- Thirty years! Thirty years.
- Thirty years.
I ought to rip off your head!
Gerald!
I'm sorry.
Sorry's not gonna keep you
from burning in hell, Todd.
Hey, this is all my fault.
I shouldn't have hit the
guy with the bottle.
I'm, like, a moron over here.
No, now, Donny,
I will not let you take the blame for this.
You had to do it. You saved his life again.
And you looked very sexy doing it.
Why was the sound of
that bottle so familiar?
Todd is such a loser.
Here comes your girl. Here we go.
Jame, I'm sorry, but, look,
you got to admit,
I stood up for myself back there.
Do you have fucking rocks
in your head, Todd?
No.
Well, where are we gonna get married now?
We got kicked out of the church!
Jame...
What is everybody's problem?
You were awesome out there.
You kicked ass.
- You should be proud of yourself.
- Proud of myself?
For what?
I got my ass kicked,
and everyone's pissed off at me.
And, by the way,
thanks for the fatherly advice, guy.
That's the last time I listen to you.
- I'm gonna choke him out!
- He's an asshole!
I'm gonna choke him out.
I'm just gonna choke him out.
Hey, guys, guys?
Can I just say
something before we all turn on Todd?
Churches freak the kid out,
ever since his father's funeral.
After the explosion,
all that was left of his dad was, like,
a kneecap and a little bit of nut sack.
It was supposed to be a closed casket,
but there was a foul-up at the mortuary,
and he actually saw a squirrel
run into the coffin and kind of
squeak out of there with his
dad's ball bag in his mouth.
You know, that's gonna
fuck any of us up, so...
So you actually knew Todd's father?
Of course I knew the guy.
He was handsome, he had fucking great hair,
a jedi with the chicks.
Went down on girls for a wicked
long time 'cause he was a giver
and he wanted to see others be happy.
I wish I could have met him.
Sounds like a gentleman.
Was he there enough for the kid?
No, maybe not. But,
you know, he probably felt bad about it.
You know, and there's nothing
he can do about it now, so...
Toddsy.
Oh, Todd.
I had no idea.
Poor thing. Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
It's fine, but
sometimes I do still have nightmares.
Oh, boy.
That squirrel and its demonic eyes.
Tiny piece of skin flapping in its mouth.
One lone scraggly hair.
A pubic hair.
I mean, maybe this is
a blessing, though, guys.
Do we really want
father mcnutty to be the one
who brings these two guys together?
I mean, I don't think so.
I'm pretty tied into the church crowd.
Rageaholics anonymous and whatnot.
I could find a priest for you.
I mean, what type are we looking for?
Maybe a younger guy.
Younger guy.
How about a black guy?
Now, I like that.
It's very urban, very street.
Okay.
But that still doesn't get us a church.
Well, I'll tell you where I would tie
the knot if I was these two sexy kids.
Donny, this is just such a great idea.
- Thanks.
- Don't you love the pergola?
They're gorgeous!
You know what, maybe a little
more girly shit up on the arch.
You know, you're right.
Excuse me, sir,
put some more girly shit up there.
Calling all ladies!
The bus for the bachelorette party is here!
Come on!
Honey, you guys have fun
at the bachelor party!
Okay.
Don't get too crazy. Know your limits.
- Okay.
- We're having a bachelor party?
That's, like, my thing, man.
Hookers, blow, balloons filled with piss.
I mean, the sky's the limit, kid.
No, no, no. Donny, we're all set.
I have arranged
a very special evening for us tonight.
This is gonna be awesome!
I read about this place
in Oprah's magazine.
I don't know if she writes
the articles herself,
but there's some real
good stuff in it.
Hi, we're for the Todd
Peterson party, please.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Mrs. Ravensdale.
Phil, what a blessing.
Welcome to your bachelor party package
here at he time spa for men.
Woo-hoo, motherfucker!
Okay. All right.
We're gonna set you up
with some nice plush robes,
and then we have
a wonderful full evening planned
with massage, facial and nail treatments,
and then we're going to send you home
with a special gift
of our house-made lavender scrub.
Confucius say,
"what the fuck are you talking about?"
No, Donny,
Phil thought
it would be nice before the wedding
for us to all take a little time
to just chill and mellow.
My wife and I have been
burning it on both ends all week
with the preschool applications,
and I am ready to be pampered!
All right, all right. Now we're talking.
Hey, thanks, honey.
What the fuck's your name?
- Jessica. All right.
- Yeah.
Hey, come on. Here's to the kid.
He's fucking getting all fucked up tonight!
Last night!
Fucking last night of
poontang for this kid.
What the fuck is this?
It's water infused with cucumber,
rose petal and harvest sandalwood.
It tastes like fucking
dick infused with balls.
And a side of fucking rod Stewart's jizz.
Wait a minute. What are we drinking water
at a fucking bachelor party for, Phil?
You got to show my son your tits later.
Promise me. Promise me.
That's nice. Yeah, good.
This is great, sweetheart.
Really good.
Nice work. You're going deep on us, huh?
That's it.
What's this, sir?
That's just a little tip, you know,
if you give me a full package.
Okay. That's a $150 additional charge.
You're talking to the wrong guy.
That's a little out of my price range.
It includes scalp treatment, reflexology.
How much is it to tickle my pickle?
To yank my crank?
To give me a ho-Jo to go?
Sweetheart, I'm not asking
for a finger up the ass.
I just want you to just
jerk it a little bit.
Donny, this isn't a brothel.
Then I'm completely confused
what the fuck we're doing here right now!
So, what, you're just going to
get a hand job in front of all of us?
I don't know. Am I?
I guess not!
You know, I have worked
very hard on this night, don,
and you're being just plain rude.
- Phil, no! Phil!
- No, no. Don't do this.
Nice. That's nice.
That's good. That's good.
It tickles.
Just fight through it, man. It's worth it.
If you stop, I swear I will kill you.
You know what,
if I don't see a tit in five minutes,
I'm going to strangle this motherfucker.
You should be ashamed of yourself
for fucking arranging this bullshit!
Well, I feel very relaxed,
and I think this was
a good use of a groupon.
You fucked us, buddy!
Five more minutes till you
get to choose amongst four
artisanal house-blended
chocolates, gentlemen.
We can't let tonight end like this, boys.
We got to go out.
I'm telling you, I can't
let my son have a...
My son of a gun best friend
have his bachelor party be this.
You fucking... you guys got your
face covered in leprechaun shit.
We should be getting whacked off,
all of us, as a fucking team!
Donny, I think
we've had enough excitement for one night.
Besides, it's not like you can throw
together a whole other party this late.
I could have six chicks making out
with each other on our laps in 10 minutes.
I could stay out a little later.
Bam!
We gonna get our dicks sucked.
There it is.
Unless, Mrs. Ravensdale,
you want to whip them knockers out?
We'd love to see them.
All right, you know what?
You are an imbecilic,
immature, asinine, childish,
caveman-like, hairy-knuckled,
single-chromosomal,
obnoxious, uneducated, ignorant asshole
who I would like to fuck hard and long!
So, I'm going to go put a dent in that.
You guys get that green jizz off your face.
I'll be back in 20.
We're going out, boys!
Hey, this is the shit,
this place, I'm telling you.
The hottest chicks, the
best Denver omelets.
- You have to eat one.
- All right.
Donny!
Yeah, this is who I
was telling you about!
- What's up? Give me that.
- I'm so happy to see you.
- You look so fucking cute!
- I know, right?
And you brought a military man.
What's your name, soldier?
Chad Martin, private first class,
United States marine corps.
You think you can keep that dick
at attention for a couple hours?
That's an order!
Already on it.
Look at my man!
You guys, let me get in here
and introduce myself.
Hello. I'm Phil.
I'm married with four children,
and I have actually
only seen three vaginae in my entire life:
My wife's, my baby's
and my aunt's once by accident
on the back of a tandem bike.
Well, here's number four, baby!
I'm going to count that
as numbers four and five.
Champale would like to dedicate this
to Mr. Todd Peterson.
- Yeah, baby. Yeah.
- Here you go.
Oh, hey.
Do you want any eggs?
No. I really have to watch what I eat.
No fatty foods. But thank you.
I'm brie.
I'm Todd. Nice to meet you.
I know who you are, han solo.
No, you can't...
Don't worry, your secret's safe.
Who did that?
- Gerald, get in the car.
- I love you, Donny!
Yeah, I love you. Get in there.
Man, you got to give me the recipe, man.
Can't buy everything, Spirou!
Bro, but they use olive oil, not butter.
That's the big secret.
Okay, Chris, get him in there.
Be gentle, he's protecting our country.
All right, good night, guys!
Gerald, you're a sick man, buddy!
Whoa.
Hey, what... where's everybody going?
I sent them home, guy.
I thought we could have a little
best man/groom alone time.
But shouldn't I go with them?
'Cause Jamie's gonna get mad at me.
Easy, guy.
You're gonna have plenty of time for her
to be mad at you when you're married.
I got you a wedding gift, and I want
to give it to you alone, all right?
You got me a gift?
Of course I got you.
And I think you might dig it.
An earring.
Yeah, I know, but that's an earring
that your mom gave me,
and I thought maybe we could
keep it in the family, you know?
Just kind of keep it going,
generation to generation, actually.
Yeah, but I don't have
a pierced ear, Donny.
Yeah.
No.
All right, fuck it, fuck it.
Do it, just do it.
It's not gonna hurt, buddy.
You got a nice buzz going.
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
Hang on.
Yeah.
Liquor it up.
Fuck!
Come here. Come here.
Hang in there! Go ahead,
just sit still, homie.
Yeah!
How we doing?
Oh, God.
That's it. That's the way to man up.
- That wasn't so bad.
- Let me see it.
Am I bleeding?
- I don't think so.
- No?
Does it look good?
You look like you could be playing
drums for foreigner or some shit.
You look like a bad-ass.
- Really?
- Yeah.
'Cause it makes me feel kind of...
Dangerous.
There he is, man!
That's your personality,
like when you were seven years old,
me and Uncle vanny used to
laugh our asses off from you.
Uncle vanny, that's right.
What happened to that guy?
Dude, you know what it's time for?
To get you back together with the old gang.
Come on.
I just hope the guy will talk to me.
Phil!
Come on, you're gonna get arrested, buddy.
I shouldn't be doing this.
No, don't stop, don't stop.
All right, look.
I came here to tell you I'm sorry
about what happened
with me and your mother.
It was an accident,
and it will never happen again.
That's all I've been waiting for
all these years, man, a simple apology.
It's water under the bridge.
Don't sweat it. Holla.
Wait, are you vanilla ice?
Was Uncle vanny vanilla
ice this whole time?
'Who did you think I was?
I don't know, a friend of my dad's
that wore a lot of parachute pants?
Man.
I want to be honest with you, too.
I never did knock boots with your mother.
- No?
- No.
I think she whacked me
off outside the pants.
- No.
- But I didn't finish.
- Vanny, I didn't finish. I couldn't.
- Yeah?
- Mom.
- Yeah.
You know, she did like to fuck.
That's fucking... look at him.
Back to it. Fuck, yeah.
Hey, han solo, you're looking great, man.
Thank you.
- You lost some weight.
- Is this kid all right?
- You're not a little fat kid no more.
- No, no, no.
- Remember this one?
- No, no.
Yeah, we used to do this
to you all the time.
- Remember, back in the day?
- Hey, nugget pocket.
- Nugget pockets.
- No, I'm not a nugget pocket.
- What's up, nugget pocket?
- No.
No, but seriously, iceberg,
me and my boy got a
little head start on you,
but you got any desire
to get wasted with us?
More than life itself.
In fact, I might have
a little head start on you guys.
What?
- Yeah.
- It's so illegal.
I don't want to do that in front of my kid.
Turn around for a minute. Just turn around.
Give me that fucking shit.
What?
Hey, let's get out of here.
I did not do that.
- Let's go have some fun.
- Hey!
Hey, where you think you're going,
Mr. vanilla ice cream?
I'm going out for the night, man.
Hell no, man! You know I don't know
how to fry no damn chicken nuggets!
It's Todd Bridges.
Yeah, yeah, watch this.
What you talking 'bout, Willis?
You come back and say that to my face,
you fake white rapping motherfucker!
Todd, seriously, though, you look great.
How's Mr. drummond doing, huh?
Mister... fuck you!
"Mr. drummond. Mister..."
Man, I... what you want?
Bowl of chili nuggets.
A what?
You know, that shit ain't on the menu, man!
Shit, it is. Damn it.
Fucking skate! Just fucking skate!
The berger boys are here!
Come on, look out! Look out, now!
What the fuck?
Hey! Give me my hat back!
- Do it, do it!
- Give it back!
Hey, it's a fucking lovely night, ain't it?
Oh. My God!
You fucking assholes!
Go, go!
What the... go!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck? Get out of here!
Holy shit!
You know, they seem like fun guys.
We're all gonna dive! Let's go!
What are you doing?
Oh. My God!
I didn't... I didn't spill my beer!
I fucking love it.
- Fuck!
- You fucking hard-ons!
"You fucking hard-ons."
Fucking...
- What are you doing?
- No, no, no, no!
You don't fucking do
that, you fucking idiot!
Yeah!
Look at this, fuck face. Look at this.
What the fuck?
Come on.
- You fucking guy. I say, take it.
- I can't.
- Just go, go, go, go, go.
- No, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop.
I changed my mind. I'm scared.
I don't want to do it.
- Oh, man.
- I can't do it.
You're rubbing your underwear.
What is that? Why are you doing that?
I suppose I'm the reason.
Yeah. Yeah. Remember in first grade
when you were supposed
to pick me up after school,
you left me waiting for five hours?
I had detention myself, guy.
What the fuck was I supposed to do?
- Yeah, well, I shit in my pants.
- All right.
Then I had to walk all
the way home alone.
All right.
With shit in my pants.
Dude, I promise you,
I'll never forget you again.
I swear to God.
Throw the fucking things away.
- Don't fuck with me.
- Throw them away.
Throw them away. Throw them away.
Get rid of the fucking underwear,
you don't need that.
You're better than that, guy.
Okay, fuck it. Okay, fuck it.
Squeeze it out and fucking... yeah.
You're a good kid.
Come on, fucking hit this thing
and let's get it rocking.
- All right. All right?
- Here we go.
- Come on. Push, push. I got you.
- Okay.
- I'm not good at it.
- All right.
It's balance, it's just balance.
You got this, kid. You're an athlete.
You got it. No, it's in you, buddy.
- Straight.
- I don't know how.
I got you. I ain't gonna let you fall.
- Don't let me go.
- I won't let you fall.
- Don't let go.
- All right, I'm still with you.
- Okay.
- I'm still with you.
Let's pick up some speed, though.
I'm with you, guy.
I'm with you. I'm with you.
- I'm not letting go.
- Don't let me go.
I'm not letting go. I'm with you, my boy.
- Wait...
- I'm with you, my boy!
- Yeah, that's all you!
- I'm doing it!
- Yeah! Yeah, yeah, baby!
Oh. My God!
Are you... Kid, are you...
Are you all right, buddy?
Sorry.
- Dude, I'm trying to make love to my wife!
- What the fuck?
- No!
- Fucking naked people.
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Oh, my God, they're chasing me!
What the fuck? Get off him!
Go!
- Oh, my God! Look out!
- Go!
Keep going, guy!
Donny!
- Yeah!
- You're the best.
- You are, Jay.
- Good luck!
I like your fucking hairdo!
Good luck with the taxi business!
- Love that guy.
- Classic. Classic.
Classic.
It's a classic night.
No way! Party's not over!
Come on!
Dude, Uncle vanny's fucked up.
I love you, son.
I do.
I've always loved you, all right?
Sorry to spring that on you like that.
It's all right.
It's cool, Donny. That's nice, thank you.
Hansie, hansie.
Why don't you not call me
"Donny" when no one's around.
You can call me "dad."
Yeah, I know, I know.
It's...
I don't know if I'm ready for that, Donny.
- You know?
- Yeah, yeah.
No prob.
Sorry.
Sorry if you fucking don't like me.
I probably would've fucked my teacher, too.
Yeah.
But...
So, what time are we gonna
go to the prison tomorrow?
Wait, you'll go to the prison?
Yeah, I'll go.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
That's... they canceled that.
I talked to the warden, and he says
that your mother was just pulling our leg.
She's only got the chicken pox.
- What?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
She said she was dying because
they give you better food
if you're wicked sick like that,
like beefaroni or microwave pizza
or some shit, so...
That just made me hungry.
Well, check your pockets.
A treasure!
Come on, eat it.
- No, it's nasty.
- Come on, I'm telling you.
Fucking Todd Bridges
worked hard on that thing.
Yeah. You like that.
Pretty good.
Look at me, I'm a fountain!
Throw a penny in here!
Make a wish, motherfucker!
What the...
Grandma d, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
Well, you've had the fantasy,
so now it's time that
you try the real thing.
No, no, no, I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I appreciate the offer.
No, no, no, don't.
I can't. Don't you... I shouldn't.
Oh, God.
You got the old-timey bathing suit on.
Okay, I'm in.
I'm going to ride you like a model T.
Yeah.
Jamie.
You're wearing your dress again.
You look beautiful.
I want you so bad.
Be nice to me.
Make me feel good.
All right, all right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh. My God!
Help me!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Do I sound okay?
You puked all over my wedding dress!
Prepare to get fucked up, motherfuckers!
Sorry, I heard you scream.
I thought Jamie was getting murdered,
so I was gonna fucking
smack someone around.
- What happened?
- I don't know!
I just found my wedding dress
covered in barf!
And something else, something sticky.
It's jizz.
You puked on my dress and then fucked it!
You're a madman.
No, no, no, no. No.
- Sweetheart, it wasn't my boy.
- You shut up.
Donny, just shut up!
Who wants a piece of this, huh?
- Who wants a piece?
- Whoa, no, no, no!
It's okay, buddy.
Todd just fucked the dress.
It's under control.
What is vanilla ice doing in our room?
He's my other best friend.
Yeah. And a wicked good rapper.
Give it up for him. Come on, now.
- Let's give it up.
- My boy.
I don't know what's going on here,
but I don't have time to
deal with this, so...
Okay, this is what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
I'm gonna go to pilates.
You're gonna take that dress
to the dry cleaners!
And then we're gonna have
rehearsal dinner tonight,
and you're gonna be
the normal Todd from three days ago, right?
And you can start by taking out
that stupid Duran Duran earring!
I was thinking it's more foreigner.
No? No, no,
Duran Duran's a good call, though.
Guess I'm gonna go
finish up with grandma delores.
- Yeah.
- Is that all right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Have fun, buddy. Have fun.
Not too much, though. Don't hurt her.
No, no. I get it right and keep it tight.
Okay.
Look, I need a couple hours to fix this.
Hey, we've all been in that situation,
and you'll be fine, kid.
I'll whip up some pancakes
for everyone else, all right?
- All right.
- I love it.
You jizzed on a mannequin.
Respect it.
But you were only 13.
She took advantage of you.
No, all right.
That's what the law says, su-Jin,
but I don't know...
We were kind of like soul mates.
You know, there was...
There was a connection there.
I never had it with anyone else.
I'm getting a call. I'm sorry, guys.
Do not touch these plates.
I'm cleaning them.
Okay, su-Jin?
Go for Donny B.
'Wassup!
Hey, big man. What's going on?
How'd it go with the lady?
You patch things up?
Yeah, pretty much. It was amazing.
The dry cleaner said they've
definitely seen that combo of fluid before.
You see? Yeah, those things
go together like gin and tonic.
Hey, listen, while I got you,
I left you a little
best man gift on your dresser.
I think you'll get a kick out of it.
You did not. Oh, my God.
My whole body, like,
got a shocked feeling over that.
Buddy, no one gets me a gift.
- Where are you, anyways?
- I'm in the car.
I decided to go see mom after all.
You did what?
Oh, my God. Dukes of Hazzard!
Hansie.
Donny, what are you doing here?
We got to get out of here now.
What? What are you talking about?
It's your wedding weekend, dude.
You come here after the wedding.
You show your mother your new ring.
That would make her happy.
Wait, are you nervous to see her?
Hansie, can we just blow this place off
and have a beer, please? I'm begging you.
Look. Is that her?
Oh, my God.
There you are.
My little hansie, you're all grown up.
Hi, mom.
I didn't know if I'd ever see you again.
I know. I'm sorry I stopped visiting.
It just got too hard.
No, I totally understand.
Wow.
You still have my eyes.
Is that the earring that I gave
you after the lover-boy concert?
Yes, it is, miss mcgarricle.
You know, I think about you every day.
Fuck, I love you so much, miss mcgarricle.
I never stopped.
I love you, too.
Do you remember...
Oh, God, here we go.
All the nasty things
that I taught you, Donny?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course I do, miss mcgarricle.
Are you still my dirty boy?
Yeah, I'm the dirtiest boy
you'll ever know, miss mcgarricle.
Donny.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
I'm hard right now. I'm hard.
Okay. Yeah, I'm hating that, so...
But it is really good to see you, mom. I...
It's good to see you, too, baby.
Can you describe
what you're feeling right now, han?
TV's Randall Morgan?
What are you doing here?
Must be quite emotional
for you to be face-to-face
with the woman
who molested your father, isn't it?
- What is going on right now?
- Who is this dude?
Listen, before you get mad at me...
This is why you came to see me?
For some reality TV ambush?
- No.
- How much they paying you, Donny?
Nothing, I swear to God. I'm not getting...
Fifty thousand dollars
to deliver you to this prison.
All right, it was 50 grand, but I'm not...
I'm not...
I'm not going to do it. I swear to God.
I'm not... I would never take his money.
Donny berger, what have you done?
Hansie, dude, it's me.
It's the guy from last night.
We had fun. Don't fuck it.
I'm telling you, this is...
This is something that can be fixed.
- You're unreal.
- Hansie.
What...
You go after him, Donny,
and you take care of our son.
- Hansie.
- Come on, he is pissed. Fuck!
- Take care of our baby, Donny!
- Hansie!
Hansie, please, let me explain to you...
I can't believe I let you
back into my life again.
Guy, guy, just come on. Listen to me.
I owe the IRS a lot of money.
- Of course you do.
- I know, I know. I'm a fuck-up.
But if I don't give them 43 g's by Tuesday,
I'm going to prison.
Wait, so you're telling me,
if I give you 43 grand,
you don't have to go to jail?
I will pay you back, I swear to God.
Would you loan me the money?
No! Fuck you!
- Get your shit out of my boss's house!
- Okay!
No! Don't do that.
That's my boy there.
No.
I think he just shit his pants.
Tell me you got that on camera.
You made me throw out my extra underwear!
I'm sorry. I didn't know
you were going to shit yourself again.
That was awesome.
Donny, couldn't have gone any better.
Loved it.
You know what I need from you, Todd,
is I need you
- to sign the release form right...
- Fuck you!
Get away from me!
Get those cameras off me!
I hate you, dad.
Hansie!
I can't pay you a dime
unless I got a release form.
Fuck.
Did I get any shit on me?
Let me off here. Let me off.
Let me get off. I'll fucking run up.
Keep it running.
I got to pick my shit up.
You're so adorable.
No, I know, but I told you
not to call me on this line.
What if Todd picks up?
No, no, no, I want to.
No, Steve.
Todd doesn't know anything.
I don't care if he finds
out after the wedding.
There's nothing he can do
about it then anyway.
You're so sweet.
Steve, huh?
Well, Steve Spirou, I'm
going to fuck you up.
I'm going to fuck you up!
Well, I got some great news.
I've made my decision
on who my new partner is.
Phil!
Phil, I knew you could do it.
Look at Phil's face.
I'm just busting your balls, Phil.
No, I'd never pick you.
Oh, no.
It's you, Todd. Partners.
Partner.
Oh, my gosh.
It's going to be a lot more hours
and a lot more responsibility.
You know that, right?
And a lot more money!
- Somebody's going shopping!
- Yeah!
I thought he left.
Yeah, that's what you wish, Steve.
I need to talk to you, homeboy. Yeah.
Hey, Jamie.
Listen. Listen.
Dude, this is not about
you and me, all right?
You're not marrying the right girl.
She is cheating on you.
You are unbelievable.
Can't you just let it go?
This is my last chance to be normal.
Are you determined to ruin my life?
- Honey, what's going on?
- Nothing.
Don't "honey" him,
you little snake in the grass.
I heard your phone call.
"Steve, why'd you call on this line?"
"Todd could have picked up."
That's right, Sonny boy.
Your wife-to-be's fucking your boss.
Right there.
Fuck you, buddy.
You are an idiot!
Is that right, sweetheart?
- Yes, it is.
- Yeah, yeah. Why?
I was on the phone with Steve.
Steve Goldstein,
the Boston herald wedding reporter.
Yeah, he's doing a piece on
the most beautiful places to get married,
and I didn't want Todd to know
because he doesn't like being in the paper.
So, I am sorry
that I wanted everyone in the world
to know I married the perfect guy.
Honey, do you think you can forgive me
for keeping such a big secret from you?
Okay, due to this newfound evidence,
the conclusion might be
that I'm an asshole.
Bye.
Fine.
Have a good wedding.
I'll leave with pride.
I'm a good person.
Bye! I'll see you tomorrow!
Wow, what a stressful day, huh?
Can't wait to get back
to the beach house.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Just the two of us, you know?
No, honey.
I'm staying in the city tonight, remember?
- What? No.
- Yeah, the bride and groom,
they're supposed to sleep separate
night before the wedding.
So see you tomorrow, big guy.
I'm going to drop Jamie
at the Fairmont copley.
Mom and dad,
you guys got the hedgehog. Okay!
- Love you.
- Watch the door.
- Love you. Okay.
- Sleep well.
Wait, but don't they not have a car?
All right, Donny, go.
There's your chance. Go.
I ain't got no more chances, buddy.
The kid hates my guts.
Right? 'Cause you guys don't have a car.
I'm not talking about him, Donny.
- Wake up, man.
- What?
Jamie's the gatekeeper for your son.
- Yeah?
- Win her over, then she'll convince han
to give you another chance. Boom!
How am I ever going to get her trust?
She freaking hates me.
Donny, you want to know
what all women love?
Ice cream.
Hi. I'm Todd Peterson.
No, you're not. You're Donny berger.
You fucked your teacher
in the seventh grade.
Hi. I'm Todd Peterson.
Hi, Mr. Peterson. What can I do for you?
What room was my fiancée in again?
Let me check. 641.
You're a fucking stud.
Hey, when the legendary
Donny berger comes in here
using a fake name, you go with it!
All right, I will.
641. 641.
All right, come on, sweetheart.
Oh, yeah!
What, did Todd come out here?
You're half the size of Todd
but you use it so much better!
I guess not.
Oh. My God!
Oh, my God.
Fucking shit!
Fucking shit.
Yeah. Okay.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay.
Yeah!
You do not deserve these treats.
Are you finished, sweetheart?
Oh, my God.
Your fiancé's at home, you know.
This really gets me upset.
You know why?
'Cause he's too good for you.
He is.
And you're sitting here
gallivanting with...
I think I know who.
Don't I, Mr. Steve Goldstein?
Wait. Are you...
What am I seeing?
No... it...
With each other?
Am I... this is...
Is he your stepbrother at least
or adopted or something?
No reply... So it's real.
Oh, my God.
Donny, Donny, you don't...
You don't understand what's going on here.
I don't think Charlie sheen
would understand what's going on here.
Look, I love Todd,
and we're going to get married,
and we're going to have
a great life together.
And yes, I've had sex with Chad
from time to time.
It's what good-looking people do.
They have sex with
other good-looking people.
You know? Just so happens that
this one particular good-looking person
is my little brother.
Okay.
It's all making sense to me now.
I know that sounded bad, but, Donny,
this was going to be the last time.
I would never carry on
with a married woman.
I've got better morals than that, Donny.
Chad, adultery is bad,
but incest is fucked up!
Please don't let him tell mommy
about our secret tickle time.
"Secret tickle time"?
You got a name for it?
And with a United States
military man, no less.
You are a disgrace to that uniform!
No, he's not a marine.
He buys those uniforms on ebay
so dad doesn't find out
he's a modern jazz dancer.
What?
That's possibly worse
than the incest thing.
This is an abomination. I'm telling Todd.
- No, he won't believe you.
- Yeah, he will.
No, he bought that Steve Goldstein story.
Come on, you think he got
that partnership on his own?
With that "beep boop beep" shit?
No, I gave him a boost.
How many people have you fucked?
Well, maybe he'll believe this.
Nice. Save.
You two have fun together.
Sickies.
All right, how much?
I'm going to be a very rich woman.
I can write you a big fat check.
What's it going to take
for this to go away?
Todd has to pop a Xanax
when he loses a contact lens.
What do you think he's going to do
when he finds out about this?
Todd's happy...
You really want to take that away?
Hey, buddy.
I got something to tell you, and...
I'm not expecting you
to believe this, but...
I got the money.
That's great, Donny.
Your son came through for you, didn't he?
Yeah. His fiancée gave me $50,000
to keep quiet about her
having sex with her brother.
Yeah, I've been there.
We've all been there.
She said it was her last time, so...
Maybe things will work out.
Then how come I feel like shit right now?
Yeah, it's kind of a moral thicket.
But the good news is
you stay out of the slammer, right, Donny?
Donny?
"Go do something."
I don't know, Mr. mitty.
I don't know if I can fucking handle it.
"Be a good person."
Donny?
- No, no, don't hit me.
- No, no.
Just give me a moment, please, Todd.
Just a moment. Relax.
You know, after praying with the monsignor,
I realize that I committed the sin
of prideful anger in the church,
and I hope that you'll accept my apology
and allow me the honor
of being a part of this joyous day.
Well, what about father Shakalu?
Stupid bird.
Come on, fly!
Well, he's cool.
Great. Sounds good.
By the way, Todd
was it you that hit me in the head
with the bottle?
No.
Well, then, who, then?
It was Chad.
Interesting.
Two, three, four.
Fosse, and fosse,
- and fosse.
- Interesting.
Yo! Donny berger! All right!
I'd sign something for you, buddy,
but I got no time right now.
Ice!
Ice, you in there, buddy? I need you!
You still got the 5.0?
What does that mean? Is that a yes or no?
I don't understand the pose.
Yeah? Let's go, let's go!
Go. Baby, go!
No!
Look at this fucking guy!
Man!
No, no, no, no, no! We're stuck!
We're stuck!
To hell with the 5.0.
Let's run for it, man.
- But we need great tunes!
- Come on, let's get them!
Right here, I got a walkman.
- The walkman!
- Yeah, baby.
Let's go!
- Damn it, man!
- Come on! Let's go!
Oh. My God!
Hey!
You forgot to pay!
So, Jamie, do you promise
to provide Todd here
with unending empathy,
encouragement and honesty,
till death do you part?
I do.
Hey, Donny. Come on!
What are you doing, guy?
You jumped?
There was a door right here!
Come on, we got to get there!
And you, Todd, do you promise to love,
honor and protect this special lady
for the rest of your life?
Don't answer that question!
Oh, shit.
We ran well over a mile.
I object to these two getting married.
No, we're past that part already.
What are my options, then?
How about leaving?
You shut the hell up, you satanic hose-bag!
Hey!
Gerald! I'm sorry it sounded so harsh,
but you'll understand
why I said that in a few minutes.
There ain't gonna be a few minutes,
- you goddamn son of a bitch!
- Calm down!
Calm down!
Let the boy talk.
I can't let you marry this chick.
I can't believe you're doing this.
Listen to me, buddy.
You don't love this girl.
I'm telling you. I had
love, it's different.
It's a different feeling.
Love is like...
It just leads you to a special connection.
It's full of, like,
feelings of awesomeness.
And the feelings you...
That wrap around you.
It's deep in your stomach.
It's in your head.
It's in your fucking nut sack.
It's in your dick when it gets hard.
There's still love at the tip.
And it fucking sprinkles out
like morning dew
shooting all over the grass.
Okay, I've had just about enough of this.
Phil, sit down before I tell your wife
what you did at the strip club.
Okay.
Son, I'm sorry, I just...
I can't let you marry this skank.
"Son?"
- Your son?
- Son?
What is he talking about?
Honey? You can tell me.
I'll forgive you.
That's what love's about, right?
Forgiveness.
All right, fine.
Donny's not my best friend.
He's my father.
Oh'
my parents didn't die in an explosion.
I lied because I'm the product of
an inappropriate
teacher-student relationship.
Teacher-student relationship?
Do you know how gross that sounds?
You're disgusting!
Are you fucking kidding me right now?
She can still cancel that check, Donny!
Chad.
Cancel what check?
I don't...
She gave me 50 grand
to keep my mouth shut.
Fifty grand? Jamie.
Yeah, it was... I was gonna hold on to it,
you know, to get me out of jail, but...
Yeah, yeah. That's what I think of that.
That's how much I hate this fucking whore.
Wait. Keep your mouth shut about what?
Todd, don't listen to him.
He's a liar and he's crazy!
Father McNally, please continue.
I promise to do
all that shit you mentioned
and so does Todd, right?
Wait, what is going on?
Tell him.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't tell him, don't tell him.
You tell him or I'll tell everybody here.
It's up to you.
Come on.
Okay. Well, that's not that bad.
What? You didn't tell him,
you fucking lying piece of shit!
Get on it now or I'll fucking crush you!
No.
Jame, you can tell me.
I mean, how bad could it be?
What?
Okay, she told him.
You fuck your brother?
Oh. My God!
Fucking white people.
I'm not looking so bad now, am I, dad?
I'm out of here.
Mom, she started all this.
I didn't want to. I'm still
your little soldier, I...
- Fuck!
- Take that uniform off.
You're insulting us all.
No, no, no. Don't you see?
It's gonna be even better now.
You're a mess, I'm a mess.
Come on. Doc Shakalu, get your ass up here!
I got to be part of this shit?
Todd?
Please.
Come on, baby. Come on,
Todd, let's do this.
Yeah, yeah.
No! Let's not do this.
Okay?
And for the record,
my name's not Todd Peterson.
It's han solo.
Named after the man who made
the kessel run in less than 12 parsecs.
And I am a berger, like
my father before me.
Also, I want to tell everyone here
that I've got a pretty huge.
New kids on the block tattoo on my back.
The heads are warped,
but fuck you guys, it's funny.
It is fucking hilarious.
And Steve?
Nothing personal, man, but I quit!
No, no. Come on, Todd, don't be like that.
We quit, too.
Fuck you!
Good call, han solo,
'cause your fiancée banged him, too.
What?
I didn't know
about the brother thing, though.
I am as sickened as you, believe me.
You know what? It's all right, Steve.
'Cause guess what?
Donny and vanilla ice fucked your mom!
Vanilla ice banged grandma?
That's fucking awesome!
Donny, look out!
Word to your mother, brotherfucker!
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not supposed to hit a chick,
but I got to tell you, it felt good.
I mean, I wouldn't do it again,
but with this psycho, you know,
it was warranted.
Donny! I'm gonna kill you!
At ease, bitch.
Dude! That's it! Nice!
Hang on, though. Hang on.
No, don't hurt me.
Even Steven.
Father, take off the collar.
That's right. You're not meant for this.
- Well...
- Yeah.
Nicely done.
All right, come on.
Let's get out of here, dad.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
My son called me "dad!"
He called me "dad!"
That's right!
The berger boys are back, bitches!
Wassup? Wassup?
Wassup...
Shut up.
His boss and her brother?
It sounds like a Rodney dangerfield joke,
but it actually happened to my boy here!
Now we got to find han solo
one of them new girls.
One that don't care about
all that money he make.
- No, no.
- Yeah, like a girl version
- of Todd Bridges would be perfect.
- That's right!
Female version of me. That's right.
Well, you know, I actually might be
doing okay in that department, so...
What's that?
What the fuck... what the heck?
Todd and brie, sitting in a tree.
I have balls down to my knee!
- What?
- He said it! Yeah!
- Donny!
- Yeah, buddy?
You're my best friend. I'm gonna miss you.
I know, I know.
But there's good news.
You know what,
miss mcgarricle gets out in three years,
so the timing's kind of perfect
for us to start our lives together.
Dad, let me just give you the money.
No. No. I'm not gonna do that.
It's time for Donny berger
to take responsibility for his screw-ups.
I made my bed, now I got to lie in it.
Donny! Donny! Are you watching?
Turn on the TV! Turn it on!
There he is, the fat guy we've been
talking about all day, tubby tuke,
actually gaining on the Ethiopians
here in the final stretch.
Is this the fat guy I put the money on?
Twenty bucks at 8,000-to-1.
- A hundred and sixty grand?
Come on, you fat shit, move it!
Go, tubby! Go, tubby!
Keep running! Keep running!
Pass those Ethiopians!
Pass them skinny fucking Ethiopians!
This defies every law of science,
but it's happening!
Get the fuck up!
He's up! He's up! He's up!
That'll replenish him!
No!
Listen to the roar of that crowd.
Fat guy! Fat guy! Fat guy!
Fat guy!
Can he possibly win it?
He's gonna do it!