My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present...
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Who is your accomplice, Nora?
The cure's finished, and it works.
- What do you do?
- Trust me.
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
We made an arrangement.
We cure him and then Grace.
That is a new timeline
struggling to break through.
Something big is coming.
What's going on?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
Please!
If Cicada doesn't exist anymore,
who was that?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I've missed you, Uncle Orlin.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Something went wrong.
We got Dwyer. We gave him the cure.
This should all be over.
But another Cicada showed up,
took Dwyer and the dagger.
Thawne! Did you hear what I said?
Another Cicada showed up.
I know.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Who is that?
I have no idea.
♪ ♪
You said manipulating the
timeline would stop Cicada.
You said you knew what you were doing!
I know what I said.
♪ ♪
I was very wrong.
What do we do? What do we do now?
I can't help you anymore...
little runner.
What?
You have to help me.
[TIMER CHIRPING]
It's too late.
No.
There's gotta be something we can do.
You... you have to help!
There is only one thing left to do.
♪ ♪
Tell your father.
You tell your father everything.
♪ ♪
- Original sub by by VitoSilans Resync by firefly - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[GRUNTING]
Your lung's healing.
It'll take a while for you to get
the rest of your strength back,
but don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
Like you took care of me.
♪ ♪
Who are you?
Grace?
♪ ♪
Hi, Uncle Orlin.
But you were...
A ten-year-old girl in a coma?
Eventually, that girl
at the hospital wakes up.
She grows older,
and she becomes me.
You're from the future,
like Flash's daughter.
I came back here to work with you again.
And I remember everything
you taught me, Uncle Orlin.
♪ ♪
Now, get some rest.
Wait. [STAMMERS]
[BLADES CLATTER]
Where are we?
♪ ♪
No one will find you while I'm gone.
There's noodles in the
pantry if you're hungry.
And ice cream.
Where are you going?
[PANTING, GROANING]
♪ ♪
To take care of something important.
When I get back...
We're gonna figure out how
you get your powers back.
♪ ♪
[DOOR HANDLE SHUFFLES]
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
And Dr. Ambres never talked
about her relationship
with Orlin Dwyer?
She never really talked about anything.
After her fiancé died,
she wasn't quite the same.
How so?
Angry. Withdrawn.
Only time she seemed happy
was when she was with
that girl in the coma.
Can you think of anything
that might help us find Dwyer?
I'm sorry, Detective.
[ETHEREAL WHOOSHING]
Okay, if you come up with anything,
would you give me a call, please?
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Somebody's gotta know something.
Everyone we've talked
to is telling the truth.
I think Ambres was the
only one working with Dwyer.
Well, look, we'll pore
over the files at CCPD.
Maybe we missed something.
We'll let you know if we come
up with anything, all right?
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You okay?
I just, uh...
don't know what to do.
Yeah, me neither.
We've hit walls before, though.
We'll figure it out.
♪ ♪
[MONITOR BEEPING]
All right.
Nora West-Allen, let's
see what we have here.
Boring. Boring. Boring.
Banality. Boring. Boring.
Come on.
I know you're working
with someone, but no names.
[SCOFFS]
Clever girl.
- [INTERCOM CHIRPS]
- Hey.
Cortex isn't gonna
clean itself, you know.
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
Oh, nice table. Liking the new digs.
Well, technically, they're old digs,
but I guess there is an upside
to remodeling after an attack.
Did you guys find anything?
Well, I put out an article,
but none of my readers have seen Dwyer
or this new Cicada.
I talked to Earl Cox, all
my contacts... nothing.
How long till the satellite
can scan for dark matter?
How about now?
Well, if this new Cicada
even has traceable dark matter.
I mean, we've seen Cicada
numéro deux do things
that we've not seen before, right?
Yeah, I mean, he can dampen powers,
he can control the
dagger just like Dwyer,
but it's... I don't
know, it's also like...
Like he could take control of us.
Let's hope Caitlin can figure that out
at the Tannhauser site
while we figure out where he is.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We got a Starchives
asset in Kolins Woods.
Starchives? What is this?
Well, it's a place where we house
everything Flash related...
Prototypes, super suits...
I mean, everything since day one.
Okay, and the alarm
is going off because...
Because somebody just
stole something from us.
Something really, really, not good.
♪ ♪
You guys at the Starchives yet?
We just got here.
No sign of forced entry.
Or overhead lighting, apparently.
[CHUCKLES]
Pretty sure that's a vacuum.
Okay, keep looking!
Remind me again what we're looking for?
Uh, it's like a huge round glass bubble.
You mean like that?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- Yeah...
- BOTH: We found it!
Thawne's Time Sphere? Are you sure?
What do you mean "Am I sure?"
- Pretty sure.
- I'm looking right at it, why?
♪ ♪
'Cause we're looking right at it too.
So it's here and it's in the Starchives
at the same time?
Somebody stole the plans
and made a duplicate?
Not exactly.
Guys, cue up Operation: Shazam.
♪ ♪
Ready.
One scratch on two
different Time Spheres.
Or one scratch on one Time Sphere.
That's impossible... unless...
Unless it's the same one.
It is the same one.
This is our Time Sphere.
Which shows up here at the same time
that someone who looks like
Cicada kidnaps Orlin Dwyer.
It's not a coincidence.
So whoever kidnapped Dwyer...
Is the Cicada from the future.
♪ ♪
♪ What a wonderful night ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
[ENERGY SIZZLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CICADA HISSING]
[GUN COCKING]
You move, I shoot.
♪ ♪
That was dumb.
[GASPING]
♪ ♪
[FLESH CRUNCHES]
[BLADE WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
[SOMBER MUSIC]
It was him, wasn't it?
The other Cicada.
Guy didn't know what hit him.
You said he was after a cold case file?
- Are any of them digitized?
- Not yet.
But the only way to
figure out what's missing
is to see what's still here.
I mean...
I could help with that.
All right, everybody. Clear out.
CSI needs this scene.
♪ ♪
Hey, by the way,
this might not be our only lead.
Do you remember that Time Sphere
that we built for Thawne?
That big hamster ball thing?
Someone stole one in
the future to come here.
For what, our... Our Cicada copycat?
It makes sense.
I can't even believe I just said that.
Okay, son, you're on.
Yup.
Okay, I went through everything.
There was indeed one file missing.
And it's... thank
you... It is from 2017.
That's it.
All right, I'll do some digging,
see why this was so important,
they had to cut a hole in the wall.
- I'll help.
- Yeah.
[LIVELY MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
Are you sure you want to do this?
I mean, this is a big deal.
Like, "not Penny's
boat" kind of big deal.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ ♪
Okay.
Kamilla Hwang, you
and I are officially...
"In a Relationship."
- Social media official!
- What!
- Yeah.
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
Larry, my usual.
It's Jason.
Ralph! What's, um...
What are you doing here?
Same as you... Taking a break
from saving the old world.
- Um...
- Look at you two.
Young love.
So, uh, K-Dawg, when
you gonna meet the group?
Uh, the group?
Yeah, the squad, the team. The gang.
Uh, hey, we're actually in
the middle of a date here.
Actually, we're at the
end of a date, babe.
- I have that gig.
- Oh, right.
Your Easter thing. You have to go.
- She has to go.
- Oh, uh, Cisco?
I'm supposed to tell you that
Barry wanted to talk to you.
[IRREVERENT PIZZICATO MUSIC]
Probably could've texted that.
Yeah, probably.
♪ ♪
Okay, well, Easter Bunny photos
aren't gonna take themselves.
It's kind of a bottom-of-the-barrel
photography gig, but gotta
start somewhere, right?
- Totally.
- Anywhere but here.
- Why don't I walk you out?
- Oh, okay.
♪ ♪
[SPURTS]
Damn it, Larry!
Still Jason!
[ETHEREAL MUSIC]
[EXHALES NOISILY]
Voilà, voilà, voilà.
Let's see what we have here.
♪ ♪
Thawne's Time Sphere.
What are you doing, Sherloque?
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
Well, I'm pursuing a new lead
to identify the mystery Cicada.
Well, if you needed information
about the Time Sphere,
you could've just asked.
That's right, but
memory can be deceiving.
Especially for a regular human.
No, I prefer a primary source.
And this new lead,
were you pursuing it last night too?
- That's right.
- And all last weekend?
That's right. I am working
very hard to get...
to get what I want.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Joe traced the file
that our new Cicada took.
There was a meta attack
here two years ago.
Two people died, and
the meta was never ID'd.
So this new Cicada might
be going after this meta?
- Well...
- Okay.
What do I vibe?
Well, we're not exactly sure.
All the street cameras were
destroyed by the explosion.
The original ATM was too
fried to recover any data.
- For real?
- Yeah.
Well, I'm out.
I can't vibe a crime
scene that does not exist.
Literally does not exist.
I mean, even this ATM is,
like, brand-spanking-new.
But this concrete isn't.
It still has scorch marks on it.
Hold this.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EERIE SCREECHING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
♪ ♪
Sweetie! You forgot your ATM card.
[SCREAMS]
♪ ♪
What'd you see?
The victims.
♪ ♪
They were Grace Gibbons' parents.
In Grace's mindscape,
she saw herself as Cicada.
And another Cicada shows up
targeting her parents' killer.
It has to be her.
The new Cicada is Grace Gibbons.
From the future.
♪ ♪
Time travel sucks.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
Grace, what's wrong?
♪ ♪
Look at this.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
♪ ♪
It's your parents' murder file?
Do you see what they did?
Nothing!
Three witnesses saw a woman
in a hoodie leave the scene,
but did Central City's finest
put out a search party or an APB?
No. They thought it sounded
like a job for the Flash.
♪ ♪
Look at this debris from the scene.
Looks like a chemical burn.
It's not a chemical burn.
It's charred dark matter residue.
We can track the meta who left it.
How?
I can't track an exact
real time location,
but I can get close.
♪ ♪
Found her.
Grace, what are you doing?
In the time I'm from,
their plague spreads
across the world, unchecked, unabated.
But now that I'm here with you,
we can change that.
And the mission can succeed.
What mission?
Ours.
To kill every last meta-human.
♪ ♪
Starting with the rat
bastard who killed my parents.
♪ ♪
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
So, Cicada II is really
Grace from the future,
and she's trying to
get revenge on the meta
that murdered her parents
and that killer meta is here?
Cisco saw the last PIN that
was entered into the ATM.
The card belongs to
Vickie and John Bolen.
We already went by their house,
and a neighbor said they
were having a party here.
Um, I think this is them.
Excuse me, sir?
Detective Joe West, we're from CCPD.
Are you Mr. John Bolen?
I am. How can I help you?
What's going on? Oh.
Sorry to be rude,
but we're in the middle of a party.
This won't take long. Um...
Do you remember using an
ATM on Kingswell and 42nd
around May 4th, 2017?
There was an explosion that day.
We think a meta-human
might have been involved.
Hon, why don't you and
Alice start gathering
the kids for a team photo?
I'll talk to the nice officers.
Okay.
I can't believe you found
me after all this time.
We'd just like to know
what happened that day.
Did you blow up that ATM?
I-it all happened so fast.
I touched the machine,
and it was like
something turned on in me.
You hyper-accelerated
the molecules in the ATM,
causing a violent chain reaction.
I just know I saw sparks and ran.
Then I heard this explosion
and money was flying everywhere.
It looked like I was
trying to rob the bank.
I was too afraid to go back.
At least no one got hurt.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
Mrs. Bolen, we have reason to believe
a killer is targeting you.
Why?
It's because of your... abilities.
Listen, we'd like to put
you in federal protection
and to keep your family safe.
And what would I tell my husband?
Or my daughter?
"Hey, sorry, Mommy has powers."
We all have to leave our lives behind.
They don't know about your powers?
Of course not. No one does.
You think I'm proud of this?
I think they have a
right to know the truth.
They're your family.
♪ ♪
And who the hell do you think you are,
telling me what to do?
We're not going anywhere.
That's final.
Please leave.
♪ ♪
She's not safe. We're staying put.
I got your text. What's the emergency?
Okay. Listen to me very carefully.
I took a break from serial
killer kidnapper madness
to do something awesome.
So I decided on a new career path.
Photography was always my passion,
and I figured why not make it my job?
These are great, Kamilla.
I Peter Parker'd her.
Dibs, sidebar.
Sidebar?
Sidebar, now!
♪ ♪
You have, uh... Peter Parker'd her.
Yeah, I mean, Kamilla
is a great photographer
and I thought she could start
taking some pictures for Iris,
and then maybe she'd start
to come around S.T.A.R. Labs.
I don't know, if we're lucky, get bitten
by something radioactive.
Become, like, a Spider-Person.
So, while you thought,
did it occur to you
that no one asked you to do this?
♪ ♪
You don't think she'd
make a good Spider-Person?
You listen to me and you listen good,
you turkey on stilts.
It is not your job
to get my girlfriend on the team!
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, you two!
You guys are getting
along in there, I see that.
What's going on?
Your friend Iris was actually
just giving me a photography gig.
Well, it's small, but
Kamilla has agreed to shoot
the Fairway parade for
the "Citizen" this weekend.
Shut the front door.
That is unbelievable.
Congrats. That's amazing.
Hey, why don't you and I
go, uh, drink and celebrate?
Oh, sure. Um, I will text you later.
Yes, that sounds great. Thank you.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Well, well, well.
Bonjour, Eobard Thawne.
If I am Eobard Thawne,
what kind of man am I?
Patient, right?
Master of Science.
But also...
A master of...
[EERIE MUSIC]
Subterfuge.
Because not only...
am I...
Eobard Thawne,
but I'm also...
♪ ♪
Dr. Harrison Wells.
And that man...
that man would keep his secrets...
[ARMREST CHIRPS]
♪ ♪
...close.
What have we here?
♪ ♪
Well, well, well.
Bonjour.
How could Vickie not know
she killed two people?
There was a time in Central City
where not all meta attacks
were public knowledge.
Why not? I mean, people should know...
Former Mayor Bellows... [SIGHS]
...tried to keep certain
things out of the media.
Said he didn't want to create a panic.
Turns out he had metas on the payroll.
Didn't want the heat.
That's Cecile. I'll be right back.
Hey.
[CLEARS THROAT]
You were wrong, you know.
About what?
About Vickie not wanting
to tell her family
about her abilities.
It's her choice not to tell them.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
Look, keeping a secret like that
from her family is... It's dangerous.
I mean, they might get hurt or worse.
She's just trying to protect them.
I get that, I do, but...
I-I used to think that
keeping secrets from people
for their own good was a noble decision,
that it would protect them.
But when you do that,
you just rob those people
from making their own decisions.
I even did it with you.
Like when you didn't want
to take me to your past.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't want you to see how painful
things got for me as the Flash
or how bad things got for your mom.
But secrets are like walls, and...
you can't really know someone
with walls between you.
♪ ♪
[WINCING] Ah!
- Hey!
- [GASPS]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey. Are you okay?
I must have connected to Grace's mind.
She's coming.
Grace is coming.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I don't see Cicada anywhere. Do you?
It's the Flash!
Mom, you got Flash and XS
cosplayers for the party?
Yes, I am the Flash! And I love...
Soccer, do you guys love soccer?
Do you want to... Yeah, or... awesome!
Come with me! Here, let's play
some soccer over here.
This way. This way. Come
on, come on, come on.
Help me with the kids. Come on, come on!
Far away from there.
- What's going on?
- Cicada is coming here.
- What?
- Now.
We can move everyone else out of here,
but you and your family
have to come with me.
All right.
- [GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[CICADA HISSING]
- Murderer.
- Grace, stop.
She's innocent. It was an accident.
There are no accidents, Nora.
[ENERGY WHIRRING]
♪ ♪
Vickie?
- We have to help Mom.
- Alice!
[GRUNTS]
- Alice, no!
- [GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
Alice!
[PANTING] My speed's back.
We need to get them out of here.
[CICADA HISSING]
♪ ♪
I'll find you.
I can't believe
that little girl in there
grows up to be a
time-traveling serial killer.
Why can't we just wake her up right now?
We tried before. It didn't work.
What about the meta
cure y'all cooked up?
We'd need Grace's consent.
Besides, Caitlin says that her condition
is too fragile to even try.
And I'm assuming that destroying
the time-traveling hamster ball,
that messes up the timeline?
Yeah, it would probably
just make things even worse.
- Oh, God!
- Whoa, what's wrong?
Her mind.
It's exactly the same as the Cicada
that attacked us at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Oh, my God, it's filled
with nothing but hatred.
Nora found out when she
went into Grace's mind
that Grace could hear
Dwyer, even in her coma...
His anger, his rage.
She was listening.
She can carry out his words.
Uh, hey, guys.
Uh, Alice is back from
the OR and she's okay,
but her parents are really not.
Vickie, I asked you to leave!
She's my daughter.
No. I want my dad.
Can't you see that
she's terrified of you?
She could've been killed!
I was trying to protect you guys.
By lying? You're a meta, Vickie!
A human time bomb! How
do you keep that from us?
Mr. Bolen... let's take a breath.
Let's step outside.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey, we did the right thing.
We kept this family safe.
Then why does it feel like
we made everything so much worse?
♪ ♪
Need any help with that, uh...
Nope.
Unless you came here to break something,
in which case you'd be
the perfect candidate.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I deserve that.
Never should've interfered with Kamilla.
Sometimes, I forget how...
embarrassing I can be.
I'm not embarrassed by
you, and I'm not embarrassed
by anyone on Team Flash.
You guys are my family.
You're not the problem.
This is the problem.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
Kamilla is blissfully unaware
of any of the madness that
goes on in S.T.A.R. Labs,
or that we routinely save
the city from evil metas.
Or that you have a secret identity
and dress up in leather
and go all pew-pew!
- Especially the leather.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
She and I, we got a good thing.
And being with somebody
has never felt so...
so easy.
And when I'm with her, for once,
I just feel like a normal dude,
with a normal life
and a social-media-official girlfriend,
who happens to be a very
talented photographer
and not... a Spider-Person.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
♪ ♪
It's... that's amazing,
man. It really is.
And I promise that I will respect that.
♪ ♪
But I gotta ask, how long do you think
you can keep those two worlds separate?
Look... my mom dated this guy, Craig,
and Craig was a tax accountant
and a freelance bull rider.
Never let one world
know about the other,
and... it just tore him up.
More than those bulls ever did.
Mm. I should definitely be working.
Look, the thing is, I
get why you're afraid
of losing what you have with Kamilla,
but if you keep her out of this world...
it seems to me that you're always
gonna be turning off a part of yourself.
That's not right.
And if Craig hadn't
been crushed to death
by that huge filing cabinet...
I know he'd feel the same way.
♪ ♪
[FORLORN MUSIC]
[DOOR SLAMMING]
[METAL CLANGS]
I didn't get her.
♪ ♪
Well, maybe that's a good thing,
'cause I've read this file
and it doesn't make sense.
Grace, there was no money
taken from the crime scene.
I think what happened
to your mom and dad
might've been an accident.
She killed my parents, Uncle Orlin!
It wasn't an accident!
You sound like them.
Why do you sound like them?
Grace, your head.
We gotta get you to Dr. Ambres.
She'll know how to help.
She's not helping anyone. Not anymore.
Why not?
I killed her.
But Dr. Ambres saved your life.
And destroyed yours.
You had a gift.
An unbreakable weapon that fell
from the sky for you to use.
For you to control.
And she took that power away from you.
No, Grace.
I wanted that cure.
And I wanted you to have it too.
No. No, that's impossible.
We were supposed to do this together.
Grace, I just wanted you to be happy.
That's all I ever wanted.
I love you, Grace. You're my family.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
And you'd do anything to save me, right?
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I know what I have to do.
Grace, stop.
[YELLS]
♪ ♪
Grace, stop! Grace, please!
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
Bonjour, Gideon.
I believe I have
something that belongs...
right here.
Video log, entry 247.
I have long struggled
with time's insistence on change.
One variable changes the timeline.
Our memories are changed
too, without any knowledge
of time's other possibilities,
but not anymore.
Where is he going with this?
Just as the human body
is made up of DNA,
so, too, is the multiverse made up
of its own unique source code.
- Hmm.
- One that cannot be altered.
No matter what timeline you're in.
Until now,
because I have cracked that code.
Oh.
So the timeline may be malleable,
but my knowledge...
will be intractable.
Gideon, freeze video log.
Capture the clear board.
Run against handwriting
sample number two.
The journal of Nora West-Allen.
Analysis complete... Handwriting match
for Harrison Wells confirmed.
- Will that be all, Dr. Wells?
- [HUFFS]
Yes, Gideon.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
That will be all.
And that's why I didn't
tell you about my powers.
I thought it would be too hard for you.
But you're tough.
Tougher than I've ever been.
So maybe you can be tough for me too?
[TENDER MUSIC]
They're a good family.
Told you they'd figure it out.
♪ ♪
Dad...
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
I need to tell you something.
- Ah!
- Oh, baby, what's wrong?
Grace's mind.
Oh, it's getting so much stronger.
She's here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
♪ ♪
Are you okay?
Vickie Bolen!
Give yourself over to me,
or your husband dies.
This Cicada doesn't care
if someone's a meta or not.
She'll kill anyone
who stands in her way.
XS, get her out of here
before Cicada tries that again.
Do not slow down.
Detective, we need to
get her somewhere safe.
- Mom?
- I'm not leaving without Alice.
You're the target, Mrs. Bolen.
She's safer without you.
Come on, Alice, let's go.
Come on, sweetie, let's
get you somewhere safe.
XS, go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BLADE WHOOSHING]
- What do you got?
- Well, we have a situation.
Or two, actually.
So that's the new Cicada,
and that's the dagger
chasing Nora and Ms. Bolen.
- Guys, I need help!
- Time to move.
Grace.
Let him go.
[CICADA HISSING]
I know you want revenge
for your parents, but...
But it wasn't that woman's fault.
♪ ♪
That doesn't change that they're dead.
Or that I became this.
- We can help you.
- With your cure?
There's only one cure for this, Flash.
Death.
[ENERGY WHIRRING]
Guys, I can't keep this up.
Nora, you need to hang on
for a little bit longer.
- You're gonna turn on...
- The alleyway on Fuller.
The alleyway on Fuller. Be ready.
For what?
♪ ♪
- Ooh, I am not loving that.
- Nope.
[GRUNTING]
Guys, we need you two at the hospital.
Let's go.
[BOTH GRUNTING, PANTING]
- What the hell was that?
- Cisco, what happened?
I don't know. Something's
wrong with my breach.
We can't get through it!
I've always wanted to
be up against the Flash
and his legendary team.
I guess I wasn't missing
out on anything after all.
Grace!
Don't do this.
Please.
This isn't the way to make
the world a better place.
You hated them.
[HISSING]
I heard you.
I was wrong.
And that hate turned
into something even worse.
It was wrong to make you
feel that way, Gracie.
But you don't have to go
down the same path I did.
You don't have to hold
on to this... this anger.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Let it go.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
But my parents.
It was an accident.
♪ ♪
Let it go.
Before it's too late, like it is for me.
♪ ♪
You're right, Uncle Orlin.
[BLADE WHOOSHING]
Um...
♪ ♪
No!
[GROANING]
It is too late.
♪ ♪
Ah!
Hey, hey, hey.
[GROANING]
Save my Grace.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I can't believe she killed Dwyer.
Yeah, as brutal as Dwyer was,
his love for his niece always kept him
from crossing certain lines.
Not Grace.
No, and her powers are
incredibly dangerous.
I ran some tests while I was
at the Tannhauser offsite...
Her dark matter has some
sort of binding quality.
It allows her to
telekinetically manipulate
dark matter within a certain proximity.
Including the dark matter in us?
I think so.
I think what makes her
powers different from Dwyer's
is that they came from
a wound in her head.
That's why she's so much stronger.
How was Nora able to see
what Grace was seeing?
Nora and Grace seem to
be psychically connected.
I think it's because of
the time that Nora spent
in Grace's brain.
- Is there any sign of her?
- No.
She definitely ghosted.
What about Vickie and her family?
Uh, federal protection.
They're gonna be fine.
They're getting new
identities as we speak.
I don't know about anyone else,
but I could use a drink.
- Not a bad idea.
- Yeah, I'm in.
- You want me to call a sitter?
- Yeah.
Cisco, you want to bring Kamilla?
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Not for this one.
♪ ♪
Nora, you coming?
Nora.
[ETHEREAL WHOOSHING]
You want to tell us
something, don't you?
♪ ♪
She wants to tell you her secret.
Right?
She doesn't know where to start.
Difficult to know where to begin
when your secret threatens everything,
everyone around you.
Sherloque, stop it.
Maybe start at the beginning.
It's a very good place to start.
When you first time-traveled.
So careful to leave
the lightest footprint.
Until you suddenly change course
and brazenly interfere
with the Thinker satellite
as it crashed to Earth.
I think to myself, "Nope, nope.
This excessive action
doesn't make sense."
Until you understand that...
it wasn't your idea.
[STIRRING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC]
Please stop.
Someone instructed you to do it.
- Stop.
- Someone...
whose handwriting is in your journal.
Someone who wrote, "The
timeline is malleable."
Same person who's been
directing you all this time,
making puppets of all of us
as he seeks to alter the timeline
to suit his own purpose.
♪ ♪
Eobard Thawne.
The Reverse-Flash. Your teacher.
Your partner.
Your secret.
Nora?
♪ ♪
Please tell us this isn't true.
She can't.
- Dad...
- Because it is true.
♪ ♪
Mom?
I wanted to tell you.
I-I tried to tell you.
Dad.
Dad, please!
Dad!
I'm sorry I lied to you!
♪ ♪
So am I.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHIMPERING] Dad...
[SOBBING]
- Original sub by by VitoSilans Resync by firefly - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44