[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
Cisco, what hap...
♪ ♪
Frost, Frost.
Barry?
Help her. Help her.
Iris. Iris!
♪ ♪
[beleaguered breathing]
Help her.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Is she gonna be okay?
When you pulled Iris
out of the Mirrorverse
and she resisted, it
created a molecular anomaly.
All her neural pathways are disjointed.
Looks like her brain's been remapped.
How do we get her back?
I don't know.
All we can do now is let her rest
while I run some more tests.
You gonna be okay?
I remember everything,
hurting my own team...
forcing Iris through the portal,
leaving Kamilla and Singh trapped.
I'm sorry.
- That wasn't you.
- Yeah, it was.
Man, no, It wasn't.
You were not yourself.
Trust me, we get that.
That's why we're gonna
to put it behind us,
and we're gonna move on, all right?
We're a team. We've
got each other's backs.
We're going to figure
out a way to save Iris
and Kamilla and Singh. I promise.
But Eva's still out
there, and I can't stop her
'cause I don't have my speed anymore.
But you will.
I'm running a full diagnostics
on the artificial Speed Force machine.
It worked before. It can work again.
All we need to do is just figure out...
No. I'm done with that thing.
You saw what it turned
me into. I'm not Thawne.
Connecting with something artificial
isn't gonna work for me...
and since the real
Speed Force is dead...
[phone rings]
CCPD.
Wait, your wife tried to attack you?
Why would you neighbor try
to make you look into mirrors?
Hold on. CCPD.
If he's not your uncle, who is he?
Let me get this straight.
You want to help bring your daughter in,
Mrs. Dearbon, so that I can arrest her?
Sue's in trouble.
We want to help her
see things more clearly.
People change, sometimes overnight.
♪ ♪
Captain, can I speak with you?
It's relevant.
Excuse me.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Oh, damn.
Sue, I thought you and Ralph
were laying low until
we could clear your name.
Yeah, Ralph's tracking a lead.
Arrest me if you have to. I had to come.
You mind telling me what's so important
that you would risk your freedom?
Those people in there,
those are not my parents.
I know it sounds crazy,
and then Ralph mentioned
pod people a while back,
I thought it was nuts too,
but I'm telling you, that's not them.
No, I believe you.
I've gotten over 100
calls in the last hour,
exact same complaint.
All saying that people
they've known for years
just aren't themselves anymore.
Do you think this has anything
to do with the craziness at McCulloch?
Damn, I know what's happening.
Move.
[bizarre chiming]
What the hell?
♪ ♪
Chaos has broken out in
downtown Central City
over another meta attack.
So after all that, I'm like,
"Well, at least Grandma Runk
is still my grandma, you know?"
'Cause I was at Jitters
ordering a vibaccino.
Next thing I know, a pair of T2 arms
jumps out of the countertop
trying to grab me.
You know, fortunately, Chester P. Runk
knows how to mind his surroundings.
Yo! I just heard back from Joe.
Whatever is happening
out there, it's spreading.
Yeah, Eva is getting more powerful.
I'll say. I analyzed footage
from Eva's live interview.
It's not just mirrors
that she's manipulating.
It's any reflective surface now.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
Light photons are elementary particles
that exist everywhere in nature,
so as long as there's light
around from either natural
- or artificial source...
- Call Joe back.
We've got to black out the city.
He can get the mayor to
declare a state of emergency.
- Okay, I'm on it.
- Okay, why is Eva doing this?
I mean, why does she want
us in the Mirrorverse?
She wants us out of the way.
These aren't just abductions.
[sirens blaring]
It's a full-blown invasion.
And with every person
that gets replaced,
Eva's army grows.
Oh, man, body snatchers.
So what are we gonna do?
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
Boss, you have to get better.
♪ ♪
"The Citizen" doesn't work without you,
so just please come back, okay?
'Cause we're not giving up
on you, especially Barry.
♪ ♪
What you two have is amazing.
No matter how strong you both are
on your own, you're
even stronger together.
Don't let Eva McCulloch
end what you guys have.
♪ ♪
The mayor is doing her best
shutting down the power.
Joe said it won't be 100 percent,
but I told him we'd
take whatever we can get.
In the meantime initiating shutters
on all windows in S.T.A.R. Labs.
We should cover all the mirrors too
- and kill the lights.
- Yes, I'm on it.
Hopefully everybody in Central City
does the same thing.
If I had my speed I could patrol,
help people keep safe.
♪ ♪
There's got to be a way to save 'em all,
to get Iris back.
[ethereal whispers] There is,
there is, there is.
There is, there is, there
is, there is, there is.
[bizarre chiming]
Hey, were you saying something?
Uh, guys, where's Barry?
♪ ♪
[bizarre chiming]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
You're powerless, Flash,
but I can help you...
if you let me.
You want to help? Tell
me how to save my wife.
She needs to go back where she belongs.
All of you do. Back to the Mirrorverse.
You see, in the last six years
I've watched people like Joseph
destroy the gift around you,
the glorious world filled with wonder.
You and everyone else on
this planet have failed.
♪ ♪
So now I'm filling
it with my children...
and we will treat it
and everyone in it with respect.
And what happens to us?
You adapt to your new world,
same as I did.
Don't worry, Barry, I'm
not gonna kill anyone.
I'm not your enemy.
♪ ♪
What I am is a mother
to a newer, better world.
You want me to give in just like Ramsey.
Ramsey thought he was a hero.
He wasn't.
You are.
Lead your people to the Mirrorverse.
They'll follow you. They'll be happy.
- Were you?
- Stop fighting me.
You've been watching me, Eva.
You know I'd risk my
life to save this city.
Those are brave words, Flash,
but are you really willing
to do whatever it takes
to ensure the survival of humanity?
The applications of my
reflective chip technology
are endless.
I can grow crops tenfold in abundance.
I can end starvation overnight.
Why haven't you?
Why haven't you done the
work that really matters?
Why haven't you made
this world a better place?
[dramatic music]
Because you can't.
♪ ♪
I can, and I will.
I'm not human.
♪ ♪
I'm something better.
That is why I am showing you mercy.
So please consider my offer...
♪ ♪
And make the right choice.
Satellites have him at McCulloch.
Barry, I am not losing you too.
Frost is ready to come out.
♪ ♪
[bizarre chiming]
Oh, thank Tupac.
- How did you escape?
- I didn't.
- Eva let me go.
- Why?
- What did she want?
- To tell us that we can't win.
Well, I hope you told her where to go.
No, she's right. We can't.
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
[ethereal whooshing]
♪ ♪
Nash?
No, my name is Harrison...
Dr. Harrison Wells.
♪ ♪
Look, I don't know who you are,
but I saw Nash die.
All the other Wells died with him.
Exactly, and when Nash
Wells gave his life
to power the artificial Speed Force,
he transferred all the
multiversal particles
of all the other Wells
into the fusion sphere
except for 0.01 percent, and that's me.
[soft dramatic music]
How do particles become a person?
I have a theory that when Nash
and all the other Wells
were removed from the timeline,
the universe required...
a balancing act.
One Wells to make up for all those lost.
Isn't that cosmic?
Crisis.
There was an event.
It took people from other planets
and brought them here together
to the same planet in one timeline.
A temporal coalescence.
That... could explain this.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
Of all the Wells, you were the one
I wanted to meet the most.
♪ ♪
- I'm B...
- Barry Allen.
I know.
The other Wells may be gone,
but they left an imprint, memories,
and so let me just say
that, whatever is wrong...
♪ ♪
Let me help you because
they would want me to.
You can't.
This enemy that we're facing
is all-powerful,
plus my speed is gone.
Aren't you the Paragon of Love?
Look, anyone can save the
world with their speed,
with their might, but
it takes a real hero...
A once-in-a-lifetime hero,
to do it with his heart.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means run, Barry.
Run toward love.
♪ ♪
- Nash?
- No.
Allegra.
Nash thought... very highly of you.
♪ ♪
A new Wells.
How is that possible?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're here to save us, right? [chuckles]
Also, which one is he?
I'm the original.
♪ ♪
Okay, I had Allegra
put out a "Citizen" e-blast
to warn the city about Eva.
- Good work.
- Thanks.
[sighs]
[eerie music]
What is it?
That window was blacked out.
Where is everyone?
Oh, I'm feeling an overwhelming sense
of passion, confidence, focus.
Joe, I... [screams]
♪ ♪
You may as well give up, Captain.
Joe?
Captain West requesting backup.
No one's coming, Captain.
Cecile, run!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
The windows.
My phone's not working.
She must have jammed the signal.
♪ ♪
Unfortunate.
Wells, Wells, Wells, Wells,
Wells, Wells, Wells,
Wells, Well, and Wells.
And that's how I got
here. Any questions?
- Uh, I don't get...
- Hey.
Help! Guys, we need help.
Sue? Ralph?
- [groaning]
- Holy plasmas.
Dibs, where's your face? It
looks like mashed potatoes.
- Don't! Don't touch him.
- Oh.
His body temp's a toasty 500 degrees.
Wait, you mean something
actually melted Elongated Man?
Holy sweet Hawking.
Ralph texted me to meet
him at McCulloch Labs.
He was looking for evidence
to clear your name, wasn't he?
Yeah, he figured security would be down
because of the blackout.
He was inside when Eva
blew the whole place up.
I got caught in the blast radius.
He walked out holding this.
[dramatic music]
Can you fix him?
Right, I'll get him in the mobile
biogenic containment unit.
Okay, we're going this
way. Right this way, Ralph.
Come with me, Sue. I'll
take a look at your arm.
♪ ♪
That's looking a little toasty.
Okay.
- Anything?
- [sighs]
- I mean, not real...
- [computer beeps]
Wait. [chuckles]
Yeah, Ralph found evidence
to clear Sue's name.
♪ ♪
- Once a hero, always a hero.
- Amen.
I know you're still in there somewhere.
I'll never stop fighting to reach you.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
I may be the Paragon of Love, but...
That's only because you're my heart.
Please come back to me.
[electricity crackles]
♪ ♪
I don't get it.
How are you supposed to
get your speed back exactly?
Iris. Iris is the key.
Yeah, still not following.
The Speed Force, we all thought
it was dead, right?
I just felt a spark with Iris just now.
Barry, your speed is gone.
No, but the Speed Force
is an elemental part of the universe,
so theoretically...
Theoretically it could
have never disappeared.
And you think it's still in Iris.
I always wondered why I was
chosen as the Paragon of Love
and how it related to my speed.
I think it's because of
my connection with Iris.
Our love is just as strong
as the lightning bolt
that hit me seven years ago,
plus Iris did have speed once.
And Nora was a speedster
whose lightning was purple and yellow.
That is so romantic.
If Speed Force energy is still in Iris,
how do we get it out of her?
Well...
We repurpose the ASF to
tap into an organic source
instead of an artificial one.
I can help with that.
Okay, well, I'm gonna need...
Yeah, I got it.
If this works,
we can all take the
fight to Eva together.
[dramatic music]
[sirens blaring]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Bring them a new life, my children.
- Go, go, go!
- No!
♪ ♪
[door thuds]
Knock, knock.
♪ ♪
It's too late, Captain.
This is mother's world now.
- Can she get through?
- Yes.
That door wasn't designed
for tactical force.
[door thuds]
Ah! Well, it should have been.
These old buildings still
have the original ductwork.
Human beings took this
world for granted, Captain.
We won't.
♪ ♪
I don't want to leave you.
Please, Joe, come on.
Kiss Jenna for me.
[door thudding]
Now go.
♪ ♪
Okay, she's breathing.
What's the ETA on that
energy coupling reroute?
Energy cycle is rerouted.
And fusion sphere completely remapped.
I have to say, is this
how you guys operate?
Because that much contact
with that much unrefined power,
this is a huge gamble.
Mr. Allen, if you're wrong about Iris,
every atom in your body
will be split in two.
Barry.
[spirited music]
♪ ♪
We need you.
I'll be okay.
♪ ♪
Energy's climbing.
Run, Barry, run.
Run towards love.
♪ ♪
Oh, yep, ain't no A in this SF.
Incredible.
We're at 100% organic speed.
We need you. We need you.
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
[screams]
I knew you'd find your way back to me.
You'll always be my lightning rod.
[dramatic music]
[people screaming indistinctly]
♪ ♪
[screams]
Don't be afraid.
You're going someplace
better. I promise.
Take them.
No!
Flash!
You've made your choice.
Now face the consequences!
♪ ♪
It's over, Eva.
Why doesn't Flash use his speed?
Well, Eva's body's made
up of quantum protons,
which are capable of sub-light speed,
- so technically...
- She's faster.
♪ ♪
[door thudding]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
You're not Cecile.
No.
But she's close.
And if you want to be with her...
♪ ♪
There's only one way.
Why should I trust you?
♪ ♪
You have no choice.
Hmm.
[dramatic music]
You and I could have worked together
toward a common good.
It's too late now. Humankind is done.
My children are taking over the world,
and I'm their queen mother,
and tonight I begin my reign
as Mirror Monarch.
Actually, we're just getting started.
[soundwave blasts]
How do you like the sonics, my lady?
[YONAKA's "Teach Me to Fight"]
But wait, there's more.
♪ ♪
Now, Flash.
♪ Small town baby ♪
♪ Got his knickers in a twist ♪
♪ Doesn't like the way that
this car suits my lips ♪
♪ What you think? ♪
Not fair. You brought your team.
♪ You're trying to be your best you ♪
♪ Suited and booted ♪
Maybe I should bring mine.
♪ Trying to act a grown-up ♪
♪ Now that's pretty funny ♪
♪ I fired everyone, now
I be making plenty ♪
♪ I'm feeling pretty empty ♪
♪ This attitude's expensive ♪
♪ Take a trip and you might find ♪
♪ Let's make this public ♪
♪ Let's take it outside ♪
♪ Put down your small talk ♪
♪ And teach me to fight ♪
Sounds like Iron Heights on
a Saturday night out there.
♪ ♪
♪ Caught in the middle ♪
♪ Karma can raise your face ♪
♪ Trying too hard ♪
♪ Yeah, it's gonna make you age ♪
♪ Walk into the room ♪
♪ Everybody looks the same ♪
♪ I'm so tired of this place ♪
♪ Yeah, why you scared
of change, yeah ♪
♪ Too many photos and
not enough friends ♪
♪ Waiting on the next
fad and the next trend ♪
♪ Posers in the hall ♪
♪ And they clogging up the stairways ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Come on, baby, let's play ♪
♪ Let's make this public ♪
♪ Let's take it outside ♪
♪ Put down your small talk ♪
♪ And teach me to fight ♪
Cover me!
♪ Let's make this personal,
stop wasting my time ♪
If I can't fix these things in time...
You better figure something out...
and fast.
Let's do this.
♪ It's all I seem to see ♪
♪ And it's all you seem to know ♪
♪ Bet you're itching to find out ♪
Frost!
♪ But the party's is going to go ♪
♪ See you turn up at my door ♪
♪ But you don't know anyone ♪
♪ And the party's over now ♪
♪ Can't you see you're on your own? ♪
Every big bad has a weakness.
What did we miss?
♪ ♪
The fact that Barry
needs more than speed
to win this fight.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[screams]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
Finish him.
Flash!
No, Eva, please don't.
It's too late. Flash has had his chance.
And so do you.
Eva, you're destroying this world.
No, I'm liberating it
from an infestation.
My children deserve this
planet more than humankind does.
I'll deal with him. Join the others.
♪ ♪
Eva.
You just can't give up, can you?
Fine. Good-bye.
♪ ♪
That's impossible.
You're still not strong
enough to beat me.
- Not yet.
- Eva.
You told my husband
that you wanted to bring
peace to this world.
You are using brutal force
against defenseless people.
Eva, my duplicate,
she was connected
to this world with herself,
but your other children,
they are filled with hate.
Look around. Is this your idea of peace?
Please, no! No, please!
[people screaming indistinctly]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Is this really what you want?
Get back. Now is our chance.
No, please. Just wait.
No.
No, I...
I wanted to make things better.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I failed two worlds.
Eva, it's never too late
to do the right thing.
You've told me about
your dream to help people.
You still can right here,
right now by ending this.
♪ ♪
The foundation for a better world
is compassion, not violence.
A true monarch knows that.
[sirens blaring]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
Keep going! Keep going!
[screams]
♪ ♪
It's not working.
[people screaming]
♪ ♪
They've grown too
strong for me to control!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
We did it.
What about the people we lost?
♪ ♪
Chief Singh? Sir, what happened?
- Are we...
- Dead?
No, Officer, we're very much alive,
and I'm pretty sure we owe our lives
to a certain speedster
and his better half.
♪ ♪
Joe?
Oh, oh!
[phone buzzes]
Is it really you?
No, it's Chewbacca.
It's Kamilla, the real one.
If she's back then...
That means the rest
of Central City is too.
- Where are you?
- I'm back at "The Citizen."
I was in that other place.
I never thought I'd get out.
Don't go anywhere.
I'ma kiss you like there's no tomorrow.
♪ ♪
I love you, Kamilla.
I love you too.
- [chuckles]
- Need a ride?
I'm ice bridging...
safest way to travel.
Knowing you, I find
that hard to believe.
So what will you do now?
♪ ♪
Go back to the Mirrorverse,
do what I should have done
a long time ago... start over.
♪ ♪
This time my children will
be born of love, not hate,
free to choose their own path.
Good luck.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
Any sign of Eva?
No, looks like Mirror Monarch
was serious about starting over.
Iris, what you did out there,
what if you're a meta now?
I'm pretty sure Eva took
my mirror powers back
with her when she left.
Maybe when she went
back to the Mirrorverse
it severed the link.
Without it, no powers.
Well, the pod people are gone.
We got everyone else back.
Singh, Dearbons, Kamilla.
That's a good day's work, people.
Oh, wait, where's OG Wells?
With Cisco and Allegra.
They wanted to say their own good-byes.
Ah.
You sure you have to go?
I heard Team Flash always has a Wells.
Well, that's overrated, plus
Flash has his speed back,
Mirror Monarch is
back where she belongs.
It's time.
But I need someone to train me.
Allegra, you have your
own wavelength to follow,
and, as it turns out,
somehow I have mine.
The universe gave me
my life back somehow,
and now I can see all 92
years of that life past,
present, and future simultaneously,
and somehow can travel
to any moment I want.
Timeless Wells. That's a new one.
It's amazing and utterly useless
unless I can share it
with the woman that I love,
my wife, Tess.
We had 4 brilliant years
together before she...
Before we both were killed,
and so I now have a choice
between moving forward
from this point without her...
Or going back to her.
Well, I'm going to relive
those 4 years we had together
over and over and over
again until I'm out of time.
Good luck.
Allegra, good luck to you.
I get that,
wanting to be with the person you love.
If Kamilla and I are lucky enough
to share half of what
you and Tess have...
You will.
This is weird.
- Yeah, we just met.
- Right?
It's like I barely even know you.
We barely know each other.
I mean, you're nothing like him.
Like who?
Oh, the Harrison Wells you used to know.
Or the man I thought was Harrison Wells.
Of course, he turned out to be a...
both: A jerk?
- Yeah.
[both chuckle]
How do you miss someone
you barely even know?
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Before you go, how exactly
do you travel in time?
♪ ♪
Easy.
Just... like this.
♪ ♪
Oh, just like that.
Well, we spoke to Captain West.
Actually, I did.
Ralph's voice would
have freaked him out.
What's not to love about my silky tones?
Dude, you sound like a Dalek.
Yeah, I feel like the
helmet's more Daft Punk.
What?
You know I love to lose myself
to dance every once in a while.
- Baby, do not... do not.
- You love it.
Don't worry, Ralph.
A few more days in the BCU,
and you'll be good as new.
Either way, it's good
to have you back, Caity.
Frost, too.
So now that my parents are okay
and CCPD has evidence to clear me,
- thanks to Ralph...
- We should celebrate.
Sue, did you ever think
about joining Team Flash?
We could use somebody with your skills.
Me, teaming up with Dr. Perfect
and a squeaky clean do-gooder
like Fleet Feet here? [chuckles]
Not my style.
Besides, Ralph and I have
some unfinished business.
Black Hole is dead, but there's
an organization just like them
in every country in the world
preying on good people like my parents.
And we're gonna pay them a visit.
And clean house.
Ralph, we've been through a lot
since you joined this team.
Ah, save it, Bar. This ain't goodbye.
I'll be back when you
least expect it, and then,
Frost, we'll go on that road trip, okay?
- She says, "Hell, yeah."
- Well, if you ever need help,
just call. I'll come running.
Thanks, you do the same. Come on, slick.
Stay flashy. Dibny, out.
They make quite the team.
[spirited music]
♪ ♪
So do we.
_
[electricity crackling]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --