NETFLIX PRÉSENTE
AU DÉBUT DU XVe SIÈCLE
Where go you, my friend?
Où allez-vous ?
You're crawling in the wrong direction.
Vous rampez du mauvais côté.
That wind you feel is coming from England.
Ce vent que vous sentez vient d'Angleterre.
Scotland's that way.
L'Écosse est par là.
My lords.
Mes seigneurs.
I'm most sorry for making you wait.
Mes excuses pour cette attente.
I know you've traveled far and from great travail. I pray you will know that this time of civil unrest...
Je sais que le voyage a été long et éprouvant.
J'espère que vous savez que ces temps de troubles
consumes me...
me consument
day and night.
jour et nuit.
I understand...
J'ai appris
battle with the rebel Scots was hard fought.
que ce fut une rude bataille contre les rebelles écossais.
It was, my liege. We lost some 300 men.
Certes, Majesté.
Nous avons perdu 300 hommes.
- Amen. - Amen.
Good Hotspur...
Mon bon Hotspur,
you led the charge. Were any prisoners of note taken?
vous avez mené la charge. Y a-t-il des prisonniers ?
Many.
Maints.
- Are they in train? - No.
- Sont-ils en route ? - Non.
And why is that? Why have they not been brought to me directly?
Pourquoi ne pas les avoir menés directement à moi ?
Why will you not pay cousin Mortimer's ransom?
Vous refusez de payer la rançon de Mortimer.
You'll need to speak up, my boy.
Parlez plus fort, mon garçon.
I'm an old man.
Je suis un vieil homme.
My ears... are filled with hair.
J'ai les oreilles bouchées.
Cousin Mortimer is held by the rebels of Wales.
Les Gallois retiennent le cousin Mortimer.
Why do you refuse to pay his ransom?
Pourquoi refuser de payer sa rançon ?
I refuse to pay Mortimer's ransom because I refuse to believe him a prisoner.
Car je refuse de croire qu'il a été fait prisonnier.
I rather believe Mortimer a traitor.
Mortimer est comme un traître.
He has joined the Welsh rebels.
Il a rallié les rebelles gallois.
He has betrayed England and is now an enemy of mine, and, therefore, of yours.
Il a trahi l'Angleterre, il est désormais mon ennemi et donc le vôtre.
You agree with my précis, young Hotspur?
Partagez-vous mon précis, jeune Hotspur ?
- No. - My son... I believe yours to be the ramblings of a crazy old demon.
Ce sont là les divagations d'un vieux démon fou.
Harry, please, stop this.
Harry, je t'en prie, cesse.
Oh, no, let him speak.
Non, qu'il parle.
- I wish to hear him. - My liege...
Je souhaite l'entendre.
Yours are the ramblings of an old man so saturated with malice and mistrust
- Majesté... - Vos divagations
that he no longer knows up from down,
sourdent tellement la malveillance
que vous avez perdu le nord,
can no longer see beyond the walls of his own monstrous schloss.
derrière les remparts de votre monstrueux château.
My family have served you. We aided you in your ascension, and still we fight for you.
Ma famille vous a servi, a aidé à votre ascension.
Cousin Mortimer has fought for you.
On combat pour vous, comme Mortimer.
And yet, now, whilst you slobber over that chicken's wing,
Et tandis que vous bavez sur ce poulet,
he shivers in a western prison awaiting mutilation at the hands of Welsh witches.
lui croupit dans leurs geôles
où les sorcières galloises le mutilent.
My liege...
Majesté,
you must excuse my son.
veuillez excuser mon fils.
He needs rest.
Il est exténué.
We come only... to advocate for your help in securing Mortimer's release. All that we've done for you we have done for the good of England.
On est seulement venus quérir votre aide pour faire libérer Mortimer.
On vous a aidé, ainsi que l'Angleterre.
But our lands are now more riven with war than ever before.
La guerre déchire plus que jamais nos terres.
The Scots aren't finished. The Welsh have only just begun. And for what?
Les Écossais tiennent bon. Les Gallois commencent. Et pour quoi ?
Why do you think this might be, old man?
Pour quelle raison, croyez-vous, vieil homme ?
Who do you imagine might be to blame for this?
Qui imaginez-vous tenir responsable ?
Chickens can't fly.
Les poules ne volent pas.
But I've seen one...
J'en ai vu une
eke enough wing flap to clear a fence.
franchir une barrière en battant des ailes.
Then it's free.
Vers sa liberté.
But then so too are the foxes.
Les renards sont libres, eux aussi.
You are right, young Percy. I owe you much.
Il est vrai, Percy. J'ai une dette envers vous.
I owe your family still more.
Envers votre famille, davantage encore.
But if the Scottish traitors you've taken prisoner are not brought to me as speedily as they might travel,
Si les traîtres de prisonniers écossais
ne sont pas menés devant moi au plus vite,
I will hang you by your fucking neck.
je vous pendrai haut et court.
Has this been heard, young Percy?
Est-ce bien compris, jeune Percy ?
Your Majesty, please forgive us.
Majesté, veuillez nous pardonner.
What a venomous boy.
Quel garçon fielleux.
He'll betray me now. I'm sure of it.
Il va me trahir. J'en suis certain.
If only he were my son.
Si seulement il était mon fils.
Hal.
Mm.
Hal?
Hal ?
Hal.
What is it? Falstaff has injured hisself.
- Qu'y a-t-il ? - Falstaff s'est blessé.
Yeah. See?
Oui. Regardez.
- How did you get inside? - The door was ajar.
- Vous êtes entrés ? - La porte était entrouverte.
It was not. Yes, it was. It was ajar.
Point du tout.
Si. Elle était entrouverte.
It was not ajar.
Aucunement.
Well, how else might we gain entry?
Comment aurait-on pu entrer sinon ?
Are you accusing me of having cut myself a secret key?
M'accusez-vous de m'être fabriqué une clé secrète ?
Yes.
Oui.
Falstaff has injured hisself, Hal. Will you perform the small repairs?
Falstaff s'est blessé, Hal. Pouvez-vous le soigner ?
No.
Oh, no.
Your Highness.
Majesté.
There's a fresh coin in this for you, you know.
Vous aurez une belle pièce en récompense.
I don't want your coin.
Je n'en ai cure.
I will require your undiminished loyalty from here till Megiddo.
Votre loyauté d'ici jusqu'à Megiddo me suffira.
You have that already.
Elle est déjà acquise.
You're a soft negotiator.
Quel piètre négociateur.
Hey! You're wasting good wine.
Tu gâches du bon vin.
- I'm keeping it clean. - Give it.
- Je nettoie la plaie. - Donne.
Oh. That looks very hot.
Ça m'a l'air très chaud.
Do it.
Allez-y.
Ow!
Prince Henry.
Prince Henri.
Who are you?
Qui es-tu ?
We come from the royal court. We wish to speak with you privately.
On arrive de la cour. On aimerait une entrevue.
For what?
Mais encore ?
Please, sire. Privately. Oh, privately, in the middle of Eastcheap?
Je vous en prie, sire. En privé.
Au beau milieu d'Eastcheap ?
Should I make a quick up and down and request a mass covering of ears?
Je demande aux gens de se couvrir les oreilles ?
Please, sire.
Je vous en prie.
What is this?
Qu'y a-t-il ?
Your father, His Majesty King...
Votre père, Sa Majesté le roi...
Your father, His Majesty King Henry, is ill.
Votre père, Sa Majesté Henri, est souffrant.
He requests your presence.
Il vous fait mander.
Hmm. I suggest you return to the palace directly and tell him his request was wholly ignored.
Je te suggère de rentrer au palais
et de lui dire que je n'ai cure de sa requête.
I've been instructed to deliver the request with great urgency.
Je dois transmettre sa requête toutes affaires cessantes.
You might tell him the urgency was also wholly ignored.
Dis-lui que je n'ai cure de ses affaires.
My lady. My lady, it's time to leave. Why?
Madame. Il est l'heure de partir.
Pourquoi ?
The day has begun. See? Out there. It is well underway.
Le jour s'est levé. Regardez. Dehors. Le soleil est haut.
You might miss it.
Vous allez le rater.
Get up now. It's important that you leave.
Levez-vous. Vous devez partir.
Up. That's the spirit.
À la bonne heure.
Right.
Now, lift your arms.
Levez les bras.
Very good.
Fort bien.
You must get that door fixed.
Faites réparer cette porte.
What is it?
Qu'y a-t-il ?
Visit with your father.
La visite à votre père.
Go away.
Pars.
If your father is indeed gravely ill enough to request your presence,
Si votre père est assez souffrant pour vous faire mander,
then you must visit with him.
il faut lui rendre visite.
It should be better to regret having done so than it would to have not.
Mieux vaut le regret d'avoir obéi que de ne pas s'être déplacé.
If your father is ill, no matter your feelings for him, you must visit with him.
Si votre père est souffrant, qu'importe vos sentiments,
vous devez aller le voir.
But...
Mais
I say this not out of concern for our king's well-being,
ce n'est pas tant par préoccupation de la santé de notre roi
but more for fear of the drunken soak to which you'll be likely to succumb
que par crainte de l'ébriété dans laquelle vous risquez de sombrer
should you fail to heed his call and he were to die
si vous faisiez fi de son appel
without you having squared your ledger.
et qu'il mourait sans que vous ayez pu régler vos comptes.
I fear that would be soak enough to put even me to shame.
Dans pareil état, je crains que vous ne m'en remontriez.
Do it.
Faites-le.
If nothing else I ever suggest.
Dussiez-vous ne jamais plus m'écouter.
While I see the strain your treasury is under,
Votre trésor est mis à rude épreuve,
I cannot help but wonder if the canker of Lollardy be at the root of this suggestion that the church be burdened with a tax
je me demande si la plaie des Lollards
est à l'origine de cette suggestion d'accabler l'église d'un impôt
to relieve problems that are not of the church's making.
pour résoudre des problèmes auxquels l'église est étrangère.
Your Majesty.
Votre Majesté.
Henry, Prince of Wales.
Henri, prince de Galles.
My son.
Mon fils.
Come in.
Entre.
I feel my life nearing its natural end, and yet, still...
Je sens que ma vie touche à sa fin, et pourtant,
even I must appear of ruder health than you.
ma composition paraît plus robuste que la tienne.
The time has come for us to consider...
Le moment est venu pour nous de considérer
the issue of...
la question...
my succession.
de ma succession.
You will not be king.
Tu ne seras pas roi.
While you are my eldest son,
Bien que mon fils aîné,
for reasons that are on display for all here to see,
pour des raisons évidentes au vu de tous,
smell...
au fumet de tous,
you will not inherit this crown.
tu n'hériteras point de la couronne.
Nor have I sought it.
Je ne la sollicite pas.
That privilege and responsibility will instead fall to your brother Thomas.
Ce privilège et cette responsabilité échoiront à ton frère Thomas.
He is soft, but he is eager.
Il est tendre, mais passionné.
He will lead my army against the newly treasonous Harry Percy.
Il mènera mon armée contre le nouveau félon Harry Percy.
I will assume that this news comes as neither surprise nor disappointment.
Je pars du principe que cette nouvelle n'est ni une surprise ni une déception.
But it is my duty as king, and father...
Mais il est de mon devoir en tant que roi
et en tant que père
to say it to you directly.
de t'en informer en personne.
When do you fight?
Quand combattras-tu ?
I set off tomorrow.
Je pars demain.
We fight by week's end.
Combat en fin de semaine.
You need not fight.
Nul besoin de combat.
These feuds need not be yours.
Ne fais pas tiennes ces querelles.
I have said...
J'ai déclaré
what you were summonsed to hear.
ce que je voulais te dire.
Leave us now.
Laisse-nous.
- Your Highness. - Stop.
- Votre Majesté. - Arrête.
Move it!
Lord Dorset.
Are your men ready for the day?
Vos hommes sont-ils prêts ?
They are, sire.
Oui, sire.
Very good.
Fort bien.
Tell me of your preparations.
Exposez-moi vos préparatifs.
My lord.
Monseigneur.
Why are you here?
Que fais-tu ici ?
I will not allow this havoc to transpire.
J'empêcherai cette dévastation.
I've come to see it stopped.
Je viens l'arrêter.
This is my battle.
C'est mon combat.
If I have my way, there will be no battle.
Il n'y en aura pas si j'ai mon mot à dire.
You. Come here.
Toi. Approche.
- My lord. - You have no place here.
Monseigneur.
Ta place n'est pas ici.
Go to the rebel camp, deliver the following message to Percy Hotspur.
Va au camp rebelle, remettre ce message à Percy Hotspur.
Tell him that Prince Henry challenges him to settle today's score man on man. He and I.
Dis-lui que le prince Henri le met au défi de régler ça d'homme à homme.
We will fight in our armies' places.
On combattra à la place de nos armées.
Yes, my lord.
Bien, monseigneur.
Who do you think you are?
Pour qui vous prenez-vous ?
I am nobody to you.
Je suis un moins-que-rien.
I will fight him.
Je l'affronterai.
And I will defeat him.
Et je le vaincrai.
That you surely would, my son.
Je n'en doute point, fils.
But it cannot be.
Mais ce n'est pas possible.
The prince speaks not for his father.
Le prince ne parle pas pour son père.
You are eager to fight, my son.
Tu es impatient de combattre, mon fils.
And you will.
Et ça viendra.
And we shall fight alongside you.
Nous combattrons à tes côtés.
We will burn them.
Nous les brûlerons.
We will burn Henry's reign to the ground.
Nous réduirons le règne d'Henri en cendres.
- You have no place here. - You do not know war, Thomas.
- Tu n'as rien à faire ici. - Tu ne connais pas la guerre.
- I do know war. - You do not.
- Si. - Non pas.
You've been recruited to our father's madness,
Tu as été embrigadé dans la folie de notre père,
to wars that need not be fought.
dans des guerres qui peuvent être évitées.
These men are not our enemies. - Our father has made them thus. - Why then are you here?
Ces hommes ne sont pas nos ennemis. Ils le sont par la faute de notre père.
Pourquoi es-tu ici ?
You so disapprove of our cause, and yet, still, you find it necessary to upstage me.
Tu réprouves notre cause,
I do this not to steal your thunder, brother.
mais tu ne peux t'empêcher de m'éclipser.
Je ne cherche pas à m'attribuer tes mérites.
I do it to save your life. Pardon me, my lords.
Mais à te sauver la vie.
Pardon, messeigneurs.
Our herald is returned from the rebel camp. They have refused Prince Henry's offer.
Notre héraut est rentré du camp rebelle.
Ils refusent l'offre du prince Henri.
They want battle.
Ils veulent se battre.
Whoa, whoa.
Ha!
Ha! Go!
Where is Henry?
Où est Henri ?
I come to fight him in our armies' stead.
Je veux l'affronter à la place de nos armées.
No.
His offer was refused. The offer has been reconsidered.
Son offre a été refusée.
Nous nous sommes ravisés.
I said... no!
J'ai dit non !
Why is the little dog barking?
Pourquoi le roquet aboie-t-il ?
Hm?
Where be the big dog?
Où est le molosse ?
It will be done.
Qu'il en soit ainsi.
And here I am with the whoring fool.
Me voilà face au fou débauché.
This fight need not be had, Percy.
Ce combat est inutile, Percy.
My father will soon be dead. Your grievances will die with him. Don't be afraid of our small contest, young Hal.
Mon père va mourir. Vos griefs mourront avec lui.
Ne crains pas notre petit affrontement.
I promise to finish it quickly.
Je promets d'en finir vite.
Come on.
Your father...
Ton père
is plague to England.
est un fléau pour l'Angleterre.
Come for me, big dog!
Je t'attends, molosse.
No!
Oh! Oh!
Hmm.
Someday this will be your head, dropped at the feet of a man
Un jour, ce sera ta tête,
who might otherwise have been your brother.
jetée aux pieds d'un homme qui aurait pu être ton frère.
Come with me now, Thomas, please.
Suis-moi, Thomas, je te prie.
Walk away from this field.
Éloigne-toi de ce champ.
After you have stolen its prized scalp?
Après que tu as volé son heaume ?
This is what will be spoken of tomorrow.
Voici ce dont on parlera demain.
This field was mine.
Cette bataille était mienne.
It was to mark my dominion.
Le haut fait de ma souveraineté.
Instead now...
On ne retiendra
it marks only this head.
que cette tête.
This fucking head!
Cette foutue tête.
Move.
On y va.
John.
Go away.
Va-t'en.
You might want to see to your otherwise well-appointed friend.
Vous devriez aller voir votre ami autrement bien nommé.
He seems to have taken a pitiful turn.
Il semble pris dans des affres.
Beale.
Hal's up-chucked again.
Hal a encore dégobillé.
Hello, friend.
Bonjour, mon ami.
Many times have I seen men in your state.
J'ai souvent vu des hommes dans votre état.
I've been in it many times over myself.
J'ai moi-même souvent connu cet état.
For all our rejoice of... courage and valor,
On a beau se rengorger de courage et de bravoure,
nothing stains the soul more indelibly than killing.
rien n'entache l'âme plus durablement que de tuer.
Never have I felt so vile... than standing victorious on a battlefield.
Jamais je n'ai ressenti un si grand dégoût que victorieux, sur un champ de bataille.
The thrill of victory fades quickly.
Le frisson de la victoire s'estompe promptement.
What lingers long after... is always ugly.
Toujours remplacé à terme par l'horreur.
Never again, I say. Stop talking, old man, please.
Jamais plus.
Tais-toi, vieil homme, je t'en conjure.
Please stop talking.
Cesse de parler.
I will never stop talking, Hal.
Je ne cesserai jamais, Hal.
Never.
Jamais.
Never ever.
Au grand jamais.
Out.
Dehors.
My lord.
Monseigneur.
What business? It is a matter of great urgency.
Quelles affaires ?
Une affaire de la plus grande urgence.
Mm. You should hurry along then.
Tu ferais mieux de te dépêcher.
Please, my lord.
Je vous en prie, monseigneur.
It is your father.
C'est votre père.
He's dying.
Il se meurt.
Hmm, that hook has lost its worm.
Je ne mordrai plus à l'hameçon.
Wait outside.
Attendez dehors.
No doubt...
Nul doute,
your father has brought...
votre père est à l'origine
much trouble to this kingdom,
de bien des conflits en ce royaume...
and I fear the chaos that might erupt in his absence.
et je crains qu'en son absence s'ensuive le chaos.
England needs a king, and I suspect those sentiments of yours
L'Angleterre a besoin d'un roi, et m'est avis que vos sentiments
that had you resile from him are precisely those the governance of this land needs.
qui vous ont fait le désavouer
sont précisément ceux dont la gouvernance de ce royaume a besoin.
You must be king.
Vous devez devenir roi.
Why do you say this to me?
Pourquoi me dis-tu ça ?
Speak to Thomas.
Parle à Thomas.
Is he not to be your new king?
Ne doit-il pas devenir ton roi ?
I'm afraid that is not possible.
Je crains que ce soit impossible.
Your brother was killed in Wales.
Votre frère a été tué au Pays de Galles.
After your defeat of Percy Hotspur,
Après que vous avez défait Percy Hotspur,
young Thomas pressed on to the western fields.
le jeune Thomas s'est précipité sur les champs occidentaux.
This is where he met his end.
C'est là-bas qu'il a succombé.
It is said he gave valiant account of himself.
On raconte qu'il a fait preuve d'une grande bravoure.
Where is he?!
Où est-il ?
Where is the monster?!
Où est le monstre ?
Where is the monster?
Move. Leave him. The King needs rest. - Soon he will have it. - He's dying.
- Laissez-le. - Le roi doit se reposer.
- Ça viendra. - Il se meurt.
Leave.
Partez.
You feel this cold?
Vous ressentez ce froid ?
Wretch.
Misérable.
Hal.
You must be king, Hal.
Tu dois être roi, Hal.
Please.
Je t'en prie.
You must be king, Hal.
Tu dois être roi, Hal.
Je ne sais pas ce que j'ai fait.
I know not what I have done.
Pas ce que j'ai fait.
You know not what will become of you.
Vous ignorez ce qui vous arrivera.
So, I offer you this...
Je vous propose ceci...
The most blessed reprieve,
le répit le plus heureux...
the most dreadful misery.
la souffrance la plus effroyable.
You shall suffer the indignity of serving me,
Vous souffrirez l'indignité de me servir,
the wayward son you so revile.
le fils rétif que vous honnissez tant.
But know now you will be watched over by an altogether different king.
Sachez que vous serez suppléés par un roi autrement différent.
What is this?
Qu'est-ce que cela ?
Who are you?
Qui êtes-vous ?
I am I.
Je suis moi.
Who are you?
Qui êtes-vous ?
What is your purpose here?
Quel est votre dessein ?
I think you just woke me up from it, didn't you?
Vous venez de m'en tirer.
Rise from that bed at once.
Sortez de ce lit sur-le-champ.
Who are you?
Qui êtes-vous ?
Where is Hal?
Où est Hal ?
These lodgings and their contents are the property of the King of England.
Ce logement et son contenu appartiennent au roi d'Angleterre.
You are trespassing and I order you to vacate at once.
Vous violez cette propriété, quittez les lieux sur-le-champ.
What King of England?
Quel roi d'Angleterre ?
Amen.
All hail King Henry. King Henry!
Vive le roi Henri.
King Henry! King Henry!
Roi Henri !
King Wenceslaus of Bohemia presents this gift to King Henry of England.
Le roi Venceslas de Bohême
offre ce présent au roi Henri d'Angleterre.
To long and good health.
Longue vie en bonne santé.
Beautiful.
Magnifique.
I'm sure you all know...
Vous devez tous savoir
my young sister Philippa has joined us here today. Queen of Denmark.
que ma jeune sœur Philippa est avec nous.
La reine de Danemark.
I'm thankful she and her husband,
Je la remercie, ainsi que son mari,
the good King Eric, have traveled all this way.
le bon roi Éric, d'avoir voyagé jusqu'ici.
I wish for you take this vase, my dear.
Je souhaite t'offrir ce vase, ma chère.
Let its beauty stand for your beauty, which stands in turn for England's beauty. I thank you, my lord.
Sa beauté reflète ta propre beauté, qui reflète celle de l'Angleterre.
Je vous remercie, sire.
His Serenity, the doge of the Republic of Venice,
Sa Sérénité, le doge de la république de Venise,
present this gift in your honor, my liege.
offre ce présent en votre honneur.
- It says it is a bird from Constantinople. - A bird?
Ce serait un oiseau de Constantinople.
A dead one, I should suppose.
Un oiseau ? Mort, j'imagine.
If I may, my liege.
Permettez, Majesté.
Unnatural mechanics from the edge of Christendom.
Des mécanismes artificiels des confins de la chrétienté.
Hmm.
A wonder.
Une merveille.
This belongs to my cousin, Cambridge.
C'est pour mon cousin, Cambridge.
Of all at this table, none have I known longer than I have you.
Parmi tous ceux présents, je te connais depuis le plus longtemps.
Indeed I have known you longer than I have my own young sister.
Plus longtemps même que je connais ma propre sœur.
We were raised together. You're like an older brother to me.
On a été élevés ensemble. Tu es comme mon frère aîné.
So, I think it only fitting that you should have this magical bird.
Il est donc normal que cet oiseau magique te revienne.
Let's hope its magic isn't black and unholy.
Pourvu que ce ne soit pas de la magie noire impie.
From the Dauphin, son of His Majesty, Charles, King of France.
De la part du dauphin, fils de Sa Majesté, Charles, roi de France.
A ball.
Une balle.
There is no accompanying message from the Dauphin?
Aucun message n'accompagne ce présent ?
No, my liege.
Non, Majesté.
I shall keep this gift.
Je garderai ce présent.
This one is sent only for me.
Il m'est destiné.
For the boy I once was.
Pour le garçon que j'étais.
The ball is an insult to you and to your kingdom.
Cette balle est une insulte envers vous et votre royaume.
You must respond.
Vous devez répondre.
Remember where, as prince, I whiled and how I spent my days?
Vous rappelez-vous à quoi je consacrais mon temps avant ?
You spent them in considered privation.
Vous le passiez dans une privation réfléchie.
Drinking, clowning.
En beuveries et pitreries.
So, is there not some truth in this jest?
Cette plaisanterie ne recèle-t-elle nulle vérité ?
If the Dauphin wants from me a paroxysm, why give it him?
Si le dauphin cherche à me provoquer, pourquoi céder ?
It would not be a show of foul temper for you to respond forcefully to an insult such as that.
On ne saurait vous taxer de mauvais caractère
si vous répondiez rudement à pareille insulte.
It would be a show of strength. I appreciate your umbrage, William,
- Vous feriez montre de force. - J'apprécie ton ombrage,
but my strength does not lie in me flapping up and down at the slightest barb like...
mais ce n'est pas être fort que de m'affoler au moindre camouflet
- some unholy mechanical bird. - Mm.
tel un oiseau mécanique impie.
Make sense of this. This is what is pressing.
Il faut régler cela. C'est bien plus urgent.
Civil strife has consumed us.
Les luttes intestines nous ont rongés.
The war drains the purse like little else.
La guerre vide le trésor en grande partie.
This strife must end.
Ces luttes doivent cesser.
And it will end... by conciliation.
Et cela se fera par la conciliation.
We shall pardon our adversaries.
On pardonnera nos adversaires.
And we shall pay Mortimer's ransom and have him returned from Wales.
Et on paiera la rançon pour que Mortimer rentre du Pays de Galles.
I will write these pardons in mine own hand.
Je rédigerai ces pardons de ma propre main.
I want it known these sentiments are so personal to me.
Que l'on sache que ces sentiments sont les miens.
We shall let these men know they were my father's enemies, not mine.
Que ces hommes sachent qu'ils étaient ennemis de mon père, pas de moi.
Certainly, my liege.
Assurément, Majesté.
How does this strategy greet you?
Cette stratégie t'agrée ?
Great reforms are best enacted with regime change.
Un changement de régime facilite les grandes réformes.
If this is how you wish to proceed,
Si vous souhaitez procéder ainsi,
then, yes, my liege,
alors, oui, Majesté,
now is the time to do it.
c'est le moment idoine.
Did you reconcile with our father before his death?
T'es-tu réconcilié avec notre père avant sa mort ?
There was no reconciliation to be had.
Nulle réconciliation n'était possible.
He did untold harm to this kingdom.
Il a rendu ce royaume exsangue.
His death will bring calm with it.
Son trépas apportera le calme.
I ask not after the kingdom.
Je ne parle pas du royaume.
What of you?
Je parle de toi.
I want an end to this unrest.
Je veux mettre un terme à ces troubles.
Look around that table last night.
Repense à la table d'hier soir.
Look at the faces of the men seated at it.
Aux visages des hommes présents.
I can feel this calm of which you speak.
Je ressens ce calme dont tu parles.
I do believe they wish you well.
Ils sont favorables à ta cause.
But I also see that they have their own kingdoms behind their eyes.
Ils n'en oublient pas pour autant leurs propres royaumes.
Do you understand what I say?
Comprends-tu mes propos ?
I've been away too many years and I'm now to return to Denmark.
Je suis partie depuis maintes années au Danemark.
But I have, in my time in that court, been privy to its commissions.
Mais, quand j'étais à la cour, j'ai connu ses coulisses.
I have seen there, again and again, that no one ever speaks true, wholly true.
J'ai vu qu'inlassablement, personne n'exprime jamais le fond de sa pensée.
Choose your steps wisely, dear brother.
Fais des choix avisés, cher frère.
I speak to Charles of France's claim
La revendication du roi de France
to be the legitimate sovereign ruler of said lands.
d'être le souverain légitime desdites terres.
It is said that the Salic law would have no succession
La loi salique proscrit toute succession
if the French crown fall to a woman.
si la couronne échoit à une femme.
Meaning, no rule left in the lineage of the female shall, by rights, pass to her issue.
Un pouvoir légué à une femme, par droit, ne saurait être transmis
à sa descendance.
Now, the law Salic, which is of Frankish land
La loi salique, propre aux terres franques
and tethered to said lands is not...
et attachée aux dites terres
not therefore legally bound or adherent at all, in fact, to the lands of France, but to those of Francia,
n'est pas légalement liée ni affiliée, de fait, aux terres de France,
which, as you know, lies between the rivers of Elbe and Saale.
mais à celles des royaumes francs,
délimités par l'Elbe et la Saale.
I claim here, with proof, that hence it follows that the law Salic,
J'avance donc, preuve à l'appui, que, selon la loi salique,
which has seen French sovereignty stolen as such from a true lineage... Thrice, as I can illuminate, the French have cited the law Salic
la souveraineté française a été usurpée, à trois reprises,
comme je le mets en lumière, les Français ont cité la loi
- as reason to bar a female succession... - With reverence.
- pour empêcher une femme... - Avec respect.
Yes, my liege?
Oui, Majesté ?
I'm finding this story impossible to follow.
Cette histoire est absconse.
My liege, I question the so-called French king's claim
Je remets en question la prétendue revendication du roi de France
to the throne upon which he sits.
au trône sur lequel il siège.
Is that so?
Vraiment ?
What confuses me now is why you are telling me this story.
Je ne saisis pas pourquoi vous me narrez ce récit.
My liege, I simply aim to bolster your claim to France
Je cherche à appuyer votre revendication à la France
should the need to meet her with force soon arise.
si d'aventure nous devions l'affronter.
And you believe that need will indeed soon arise?
Et vous estimez que ce sera bientôt le cas ?
I...
Je...
My liege...
Majesté,
by way of preparedness, - I believe it always wise... - Preparedness?
dans un souci de préparation, j'estime sage...
If we are to war with France, it will not come as a consequence
De préparation ? Pour guerroyer contre la France,
of an old and impenetrable madrigal.
nul besoin d'un vieux madrigal obscur.
France was your father's long-held ambition.
La France était l'aspiration de votre père.
Had he not been bogged in civil feud,
S'il n'avait pas été embourbé dans les querelles,
he would most surely have taken the fight to her.
il aurait assurément attaqué la France.
And then... on to Jerusalem.
Et ensuite, Jérusalem.
Jerusalem?
Jérusalem ?
We're all the way to the Holy Land, are we?
Jusqu'en Terre Sainte, c'est ça ?
And presumably to sack the rest of Christendom along the way.
Vraisemblablement pour piller le reste de la chrétienté au passage.
I am not my father, archbishop.
Je ne suis pas mon père, Monseigneur.
I would have thought this to be clear by now.
Je pensais que c'était bien clair.
We must forgive our archbishop.
Nous devons
pardonner à notre archevêque.
He is a far...
C'est loin
far from gifted orator.
d'être un orateur inspiré.
Which is strange, given I would have thought gifted oratory
Chose étrange,
to be a requirement of the position.
je pensais que c'était un prérequis pour ce poste.
Why is the archbishop speaking to me of war with France?
Pourquoi me parle-t-il de guerre contre la France ?
What we are witnessing is a stirring,
Nous assistons à une agitation
of which we must be wary.
dont il faut se méfier.
I applaud... your restraint.
J'applaudis votre retenue.
After so many years of strife,
Après tant d'années de conflit,
you are proving to be more than your father's son.
vous vous révélez être bien plus que digne d'être roi.
You wish to be a king for the people.
Vous voulez être roi pour le peuple.
Now, we must ensure to that end, however,
Pour ce faire, on doit s'assurer
you do not remain oblivious to the mood of the people.
que vous soyez bien conscient de l'état d'esprit du peuple.
And what mood is this?
Quel état d'esprit ?
That France is taunting us.
Le fait que la France nous brocarde.
Do you share this mood?
Partages-tu cet avis ?
Well...
this mood is a fantasy.
Ce n'est que fantasmes.
But that does not mean it is not felt true.
Mais c'est le ressenti du peuple.
- Where are you going? - Disgusting.
Où vas-tu ?
Répugnant.
- No, we can't be going to Hooper's. - Yes, we can.
On ne peut aller chez Hooper.
- No, she won't have you. - Yes, she will.
Mais si.
- Elle ne veut pas te voir. - Ça ira.
- Nope! - Yes.
- No. - Yes!
You're not welcome here.
Tu n'es pas le bienvenu ici.
Unless you've come to pay me what you owe me. I have paid you.
Sauf si c'est pour payer ta dette.
You've paid me a snatch of what you owe.
Je t'ai payée.
Une bribe de ce que tu me dois.
And I presume, too, from the proceeds of thieving.
Et j'imagine que c'est le fruit d'un larcin.
Lies.
Mensonges.
By all account, you be not specially good at thieving neither.
Et à ce qu'on dit, tu n'es pas très doué.
Lies.
Mensonges.
How dare you address me so?
Comment oses-tu me parler ainsi ?
Why would you be so churlish with the very man most likely to lift you from your stinking rat hole?
Pourquoi tant de discourtoisie envers l'homme
le plus susceptible de te tirer hors de ce trou à rat ?
Oh, maybe you've forgot.
Ou auras-tu oublié.
My associations now stretch to the highest reaches of the realm.
Mes associations s'étendent aux plus hautes sphères du royaume.
Your insolence might as well be directed to the king himself.
Autant tourner ton insolence envers le roi.
Ponder that now.
Médite là-dessus.
Are you speaking of Hal?
Parles-tu de Hal ?
Ah.
Where is he?
Où est-il ?
Where is Hal? Oh.
Où est Hal ?
Where's our king?
Où est notre roi ?
He be gone weeks and weeks now. Where is he?
Des semaines qu'il a disparu. Où est-il ?
I would say... you be the one that's been forgot.
C'est plutôt toi qui as été oublié.
- Oh. - I would say that your dalliance with the upper reaches of the realm
Je dirais que ton badinage fugace avec les hautes sphères du royaume
was short-lived in and around his stinking sick bucket.
s'est limité à son pot de chambre.
Seems you were little more than passing keeper of a prince's puke. Shut up.
Tu n'as guère été plus qu'un vulgaire gardien de vomi de prince.
Ton caquet.
Ponder that now.
Médite là-dessus.
Nell, Sir John is down on his luck.
Sir John est en déveine.
I am not.
Pas du tout.
You find someone to pay your way here.
Trouve quelqu'un pour payer ta dette.
I'll not be paying it for you.
Je ne l'épongerai pas.
Head.
Tête.
Who are you?
He seeks asylum in return for his tale.
Il demande l'asile en échange de son récit.
I do not doubt this can be arranged.
Nul doute que ça peut s'arranger.
Can it or not? You are the King, no?
It can be arranged.
I have been sent by the King of France to assassinate you.
Charles himself sent you?
You know this to be certain?
The order's origin I know, yes.
From the King.
What was the order?
That I should kill the King of England.
How?
However. Any way.
There are many ways to kill a man.
It is my talent...
killing men who do not expect to be killed.
At such a time as I endeavor to foster a fresh and peaceful air
Alors que je m'efforce
for this kingdom to breathe,
d'encourager un vent nouveau à souffler dans ce royaume,
it is not in my interest to stir hostility with another.
je n'ai aucun intérêt à provoquer les hostilités.
This is an act of war.
C'est un acte de guerre.
We share your longing for peace, my liege,
Nous partageons votre désir de paix, Majesté,
but to ignore such an audacious act of aggression
mais ignorer un acte d'agression aussi audacieux
will be seen as weakness.
sera vu comme une faiblesse.
This is no game ball. This is an assassin.
Ce n'est pas un jeu. Il s'agit d'un assassin.
Would you consider me weak, Chief Justice?
Me considérez-vous faible, juge en chef ?
No.
No, I speak more of the kingdom.
Non, je parle du royaume.
What the kingdom sees. What the kingdom sees. Mm.
- Ce que voit le royaume. - Ce que voit le royaume.
How, pray, might the kingdom see the weasel beneath our feet?
Dis-moi comment le royaume pourrait voir cela comme une lâcheté ?
If France's animus towards you runs deep enough for them to send an assassin,
Si l'animosité de la France à votre égard
est ancrée au point d'envoyer un assassin,
it will be felt in the street, ours and theirs.
la rue le ressentira, ici comme là-bas.
It will be known.
Cela se saura.
We share your concerns. But peace today needs more than harmony.
Nous partageons vos inquiétudes. Mais l'harmonie ne suffit pas à la paix.
It needs strength... and confidence.
Elle requiert de la force et de la confiance.
These are qualities that can originate only in you,
Qualités qui ne peuvent émaner que de vous,
the king.
le roi.
Our king.
Notre roi.
Take down these words...
Notez ces mots...
addressed to King Charles of France.
adressés au roi Charles de France.
This assassin you send
Votre assassin
can be taken as nothing other than an infant act of war.
est le prémisse d'un acte de guerre.
If this be your intention,
Si telle est votre intention,
I say you let it be known plainly and that you desist from this timorous slither
exposez-le clairement et cessez
in which you presently engage.
ces sournoiseries timorées dans lesquelles vous êtes engagé.
If it be war you seek,
Si vous voulez la guerre,
send the full weight of your army.
envoyez tout le poids de votre armée.
For a lone, cowardly assassin
Car un assassin lâche et solitaire
will not topple this King Henry the Fifth of England you so underestimate.
ne renversera pas ce roi Henri V d'Angleterre que vous sous-estimez tant.
Fill this with gunstones and send it back to France.
Emplissez ça de boulets et envoyez-le en France.
Go get the master.
- Who is it? - A Frenchman, sire.
Qui est-ce ?
Un Français.
He says he wishes to speak with you privately.
Il souhaite vous parler en privé.
About what?
À quel sujet ?
He wouldn't say, sire.
Il ne l'a pas dit.
I asked of him, he wouldn't say.
Je lui ai demandé, pourtant.
My king has sent me to seek out men he feels he can trust.
Mon roi m'a envoyé trouver des hommes dignes de confiance.
He believes there is discreet discussion to be had.
Il pense qu'un conciliabule peut être mené.
What discussion?
Quel conciliabule ?
He believes there is discussion to be had about your new king of England.
Il pense qu'il faut discuter de votre nouveau roi d'Angleterre.
Only myself and Lord Grey were met.
Il n'a rencontré que Lord Grey et moi-même.
We knew not where to turn about what was spoken to us.
On ignorait vers qui se tourner concernant cet échange.
We're all of us aware there's a standing problem.
On est tous conscients qu'il y a un problème.
Our king is of low repute.
La réputation de notre roi est mauvaise.
The French king... teaches you this?
C'est ce que vous apprend le roi de France ?
Is he not thankful
N'est-il point reconnaissant
for our young Henry's light reaction to his provocation?
de la réaction modérée de notre jeune Henri face à sa provocation ?
The assassin he swears he knows not of.
Il jure ne rien savoir de cet assassin.
'Tis a charge he denies.
Il nie l'accusation.
His plot came to naught. Of course he would wish to wipe his hands of it.
Son complot n'a rien donné.
Normal qu'il s'en lave les mains.
Whatever the root,
Quelle qu'en soit l'origine,
they have expressed grave concern
ils ont exprimé leurs préoccupations
regarding our king's mental fortitude.
quant à la force d'âme de notre roi.
This envoy is to be trusted, is he not, Cambridge?
On peut se fier à cet émissaire, n'est-il pas, Cambridge ?
I believe so.
Je le crois.
Charles wishes to dethrone our king.
Charles souhaite détrôner notre roi.
The issue is not France.
Le problème n'est pas la France.
This is but a reminder to us of a more general lunacy.
Ce n'est qu'un rappel d'une démence plus générale.
A boy who but weeks ago was a drunken boor from the sewers of Eastcheap now wears England's crown.
Un garçon qui n'était qu'un cuistre aviné
dans le cloaque d'Eastcheap est désormais le roi.
- Hmm. - What shall become of us?
Qu'adviendra-t-il de nous ?
What shall become of us when civil misdeeds are forgiven as if they were but indiscretions?
Qu'adviendra-t-il quand des méfaits civils
seront pardonnés ?
- When traitors... - Yes, yes, Lord Grey, your...
- Que des traîtres... - Oui, Lord Grey,
Your concerns are current.
votre préoccupation est légitime.
And they are numerous.
Et il y en a bien d'autres.
Something must be done.
Il faut faire quelque chose.
Something will be done.
Quelque chose sera fait.
Give me quiet.
Retirez-vous.
Thus is a king's burden.
Tel est le fardeau d'un roi.
A king must make decisions
Il doit prendre des décisions
lesser men are...
que des hommes moindres
neither willing nor able to make.
refusent ou ne peuvent prendre.
A king is indeed presented with quandaries
Un roi est mis face à des dilemmes
lesser men might never encounter in the course of their whole lives.
que des hommes moindres ne rencontrent jamais au cours de leur vie.
I wish it were not so.
Oh, qu'il n'en est autrement.
But problems...
Mais les problèmes,
And this is my experience.
et là est mon expérience,
Problems that are left unattended...
les problèmes laissés en suspens
have a habit of becoming crises.
ont coutume de se transformer en crises.
You have a chance here to unite the land, Hal.
Vous avez l'occasion d'unir le pays, Hal.
Truly.
Pour de bon.
You have refreshed its mood with promise.
Vos promesses ont revigoré les mentalités.
But promise must be fulfilled.
Or une promesse se doit d'être tenue.
Promise can never be an end in itself.
Une promesse ne saurait être une fin en soi.
As of this day, we're at war with France.
Nous sommes en guerre contre la France.
Twice I have given her the benefit of my doubt.
Deux fois, je lui ai accordé le bénéfice du doute.
This third affront will not be left unchecked.
Ce troisième affront ne restera pas impuni.
And so, in order to flush these French rats from their nests,
Et, par conséquent, pour faire sortir ces rats de Français,
I will have it communicated to them that we are now at war.
je leur ferai savoir que nous sommes désormais en guerre.
My Lord Grey.
Lord Grey.
Cambridge.
I would ask you to deliver this message to France, given your...
Je vous confierais de transmettre ce message à la France, au vu
familiarity with its recipient.
de votre familiarité avec le destinataire.
But I believe in the morning you be otherwise engaged.
Mais demain matin, vous aurez d'autres engagements.
Pray how, my liege?
Lesquels, Majesté ?
Tomorrow you will have your heads cut off.
Demain, vous serez décapités.
No.
I have chosen to send you as an advance party to Hell
Je vais vous envoyer en tant qu'éclaireurs en enfer
for the considerable French number that will soon be needing to find space there.
pour les innombrables Français
qui devront bientôt y trouver place.
You were once my friend.
Tu étais jadis mon ami.
I am your friend...
Je suis votre ami,
cousin.
All leave.
Sortez tous.
Now.
Maintenant.
You.
Toi.
Stay.
Reste.
You...
Toi,
leave.
sors.
This is my place.
Je suis chez moi.
The hostess can stay.
L'hôtesse peut rester.
I will not jump to your attention.
Je ne me mettrai pas au garde-à-vous.
And surely not to retread vile ground I vowed never to walk again.
Et surtout pas pour sombrer dans la fange,
j'ai juré qu'on ne m'y prendrait plus.
I acknowledge my neglect of you, John.
Je reconnais t'avoir négligé, John.
A new chapter of my life has begun before the last could be properly closed.
Un chapitre de ma vie s'est ouvert avant que le précédent ne soit fermé.
These concerns are mine and mine alone.
Ces préoccupations ne regardent que moi.
But the fact that this here be the first occasion I've had to sound them aloud to anyone other than myself
Mais le fait que je ne les énonce
speaks volumes.
de vive voix que maintenant en dit long.
It speaks to the loneliness of the position in which I find myself.
Cela révèle la solitude du poste que j'occupe.
To steer our present course, I've been forced to rely upon the counsel of men
Dans la situation actuelle, j'ai dû me reposer
whose loyalty I question every waking moment.
sur des hommes dont je remets en cause la loyauté en permanence.
Every waking moment.
En permanence.
I need men around me I can trust.
J'ai besoin de conseillers fiables.
I'm here because you are my friend.
Je suis ici, car tu es mon ami.
A king has no friends.
Un roi n'a pas d'amis.
A king has only...
Un roi n'a que
followers...
des sujets
and foe.
et des ennemis.
I'm sorry my occasion to visit...
Je suis navré de venir te voir
carries with it this doleful weight.
avec ce fardeau si funeste.
Hal.
I will come with you.
Je viendrai avec vous.
I ask only one favor in return.
Je ne demande qu'une faveur en retour.
Square my account with that terrible hag...
Réglez mes comptes avec cette harpie.
over there. Would you?
Elle. Vous voulez bien ?
We welcome those newly arrived here.
Bienvenue aux nouveaux arrivés.
Turn us now in common poise, with one mind, sharpened.
Puisse notre force être commune, un seul esprit, affûté.
Together...
Ensemble,
we will bring France down.
nous ferons ployer la France.
Together...
Ensemble,
we will bring her to her knees.
nous la mettrons à genoux.
Captains all, to this end,
Mes capitaines, à cette fin,
I wish to introduce to you a new marshal of our campaign.
je vous présente un nouveau maréchal pour notre campagne.
Sir John Falstaff.
Sir John's experience in battle should need no recitation. You know of him.
Nul besoin de conter son expérience au combat. Vous le connaissez.
Some of you have had the honor of fighting alongside him.
Certains ont eu l'honneur de combattre à ses côtés.
Others have heard tale of his exploits.
D'autres ont entendu le récit de ses exploits.
But I have tasked Sir John to join this campaign for one most vital reason alone:
J'ai chargé Sir John d'intégrer cette campagne
pour une raison vitale :
he respects war as only a man who has seen its most monstrous form can.
il respecte la guerre comme seul un homme qui a connu sa monstruosité le peut.
He lusts after it not,
Il ne la désire point,
but rather regards it with the grim sobriety that you and your men should hope he would.
mais la considère avec la dure gravité
que vous devriez tous avoir.
Welcome,
Bienvenue
and thank you...
et merci,
good sirs.
messeigneurs.
You're all well met.
Je vous salue.
Very good.
Fort bien.
Bonsoir.
Are you ready for what awaits us?
Es-tu prêt pour ce qui nous attend ?
One is never ready for what awaits us.
Nul n'est jamais prêt pour ce qui nous attend.
Get!
Hue !
You believe Sir John there to be fit and suitable enough to captain this effort?
Vous estimez que Sir John est apte à commander
cette entreprise ?
John is a good man.
John est un homme bon.
They meet us at sea or upon landing.
On combattra en mer ou en débarquant.
We shall know soon enough.
On le saura bien assez tôt.
You must rest.
Il faut vous reposer.
John.
Thank you.
Merci.
What for?
Pour quoi ?
For being here.
Pour être là.
With me.
À mes côtés.
Well, it's a small price to pay to keep that detestable Hooper woman off me back.
Ce n'est pas cher payé
pour me libérer de cette Hooper.
Get some rest too, my liege.
Reposez-vous aussi.
We land quickly!
Débarquons prestement !
Check every building.
Vérifiez chaque bâtiment.
No man!
Aucun homme !
Watch.
- No man here! - Clear!
Aucun homme ici !
- No man here. - No man.
Aucun homme.
Go on. Faster.
Light.
Pull!
We must storm that castle.
Il faut le prendre d'assaut.
It will be bloody. We will most surely sacrifice souls.
Le sang coulera. On sacrifiera sûrement des vies.
Thus is the nature of war. It is bloody and soulless.
Telle est la nature de la guerre. Sanglante et sans âme.
We have no way of knowing how well supplied they are behind those walls.
On ignore leurs réserves derrière ces remparts.
This siege may take months, and months, I fear, we have not at our disposal.
Ce siège pourrait prendre des mois,
des mois dont nous ne disposons pas.
Men in these numbers, fixed here,
Nombreux seront les hommes, ici,
will fall to hunger and disease.
qui mourront de faim et de maladie.
Sir John.
War is...
La guerre est
bloody and soulless.
sanglante et sans âme.
Yes.
The archbishop has arrived.
L'archevêque est arrivé.
Surely you cannot simply idle here until they decide to come out?
Vous ne pouvez vous contenter d'attendre ici qu'ils sortent.
That is precisely the definition of a siege.
C'est précisément la définition d'un siège.
How long might that take? Surely there's no way of knowing.
Combien de temps cela prendrait-il ? Nul ne le sait.
Uh, that too, is a common characteristic of a siege.
C'est là aussi une caractéristique d'un siège.
- I will not send my men up that hill. - But why in heavens not?
- Je n'y enverrai pas mes hommes. - Pourquoi ?
I will not sacrifice my men so flagrantly, nor so speculatively.
Je refuse de les sacrifier si éhontément et sur de simples spéculations.
Well, then why do you not simply go around?
Pourquoi ne pas le contourner ?
If they insist on hiding in their castle, why do you not simply go around it?
S'ils tiennent à rester terrés, pourquoi ne pas contourner le château ?
So well versed in the art of warfare.
Si rompu à l'art de la guerre.
We must take this town, Archbishop.
Nous devons prendre cette ville.
We must establish a garrison foothold here...
Et implanter une garnison ici
for our lines of supply from England.
pour notre approvisionnement d'Angleterre.
Do not forget that I have underwritten this campaign.
N'oubliez pas que j'ai garanti cette campagne.
I have interest here.
J'ai des intérêts ici.
And I will be heard.
Et je serai entendu.
Not today, Archbishop.
Pas aujourd'hui, Monseigneur.
My liege.
Majesté.
They have surrendered.
Ils ont capitulé.
- Our debate now, it seems, is for nothing. - Hmm.
Notre débat semble avoir été en vain.
As are the archbishop's bleatings.
Comme les bêlements de l'archevêque.
The day is yours.
We ask only that our women and children be freed.
Many are hungry and wounded and becoming sick.
Upon full account of the castle,
I see no reason to deny your request.
You will have tonight to oversee this evacuation
and to corral your men prisoners.
Come.
He wishes to slow us.
Il cherche à nous ralentir.
Who wishes to slow us?
Qui cherche à nous ralentir ?
We have received word that the Dauphin is en route.
On a appris que le dauphin est en route.
He wishes conference with His Majesty.
Il souhaite rencontrer Sa Majesté.
And we know nothing of his purpose?
Et on ignore tout de son but ?
We know only that he desires conference.
Seulement qu'il désire vous rencontrer.
I would hope his purpose be to deliver his father's early surrender.
J'espère qu'il vient nous informer de la capitulation de son père.
I strongly advise we disregard this word of his approach and ready our movement.
Je conseille d'ignorer la nouvelle de sa venue et d'avancer.
We must make advantage of their disarray.
Il faut profiter de leur confusion.
Sir John, your counsel.
Sir John, votre avis.
I've never met the man... this French prince.
Je n'ai jamais rencontré ce prince français.
I can't speak to his motivation.
J'ignore ses motivations.
My liege.
Majesté.
He's here.
Il est là.
Your Majesty.
Votre Majesté !
Ah!
To... your little... victory.
À votre petite victoire.
Ah.
Do you wonder why I have come?
Vous vous demandez pourquoi je suis venu ?
Hmm?
Do you wonder this?
Vous le demandez-vous ?
I have not come to offer you surrender
Je ne suis pas venu pour offrir notre capitulation
if that is what you are hoping.
si c'est ce que vous espérez.
I have come to describe for you
Je suis venu vous décrire
your end days,
vos derniers jours,
the screams of your men
les hurlements de vos hommes
as they die slow.
dans leur lente agonie.
And so, King of, uh, England,
Et donc, roi d'Angleterre,
you seem so intent on making France your new home,
vous semblez si déterminé à vous emparer de la France
so let me help you.
que je vais vous aider.
I will drain your body of its blood
Je viderai votre corps de son sang
and bury it under a tree.
et l'enterrerai sous un arbre.
A little French tree.
Un tout petit arbre français.
Very young, very small.
Très jeune, très petit.
Since perchance that is fitting of your mind for you to come here.
À l'image de votre idée de venir ici.
Small.
Petit.
And maybe your...
Peut-être que vos...
I mean, no, your balls must be big, no?
Vos testicules doivent être gros.
Giant balls.
Géants, même.
Giant balls... with a tiny cock.
Des testicules géants avec une queue toute petite.
And the sound of your wives and children weeping
Et le son des pleurs de vos femmes et de vos enfants
shall lull me to sleep at night.
me berceront pour m'endormir.
Have you heard what I said?
M'avez-vous entendu ?
I have.
Oui.
It was stirring.
C'était émouvant.
Sir John, please walk with me.
Sir John, veuillez m'accompagner.
Good night.
Bonsoir.
Ready the men to move.
Prépare les troupes.
Waste no time.
Ne perds pas de temps.
Run!
Fuis !
Hush, hush, hush. Hush. Hush.
Silence.
Hello, little boy.
Bonjour, petit garçon.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
N'aie pas peur.
I want you to deliver a gift to your king.
Je veux que tu donnes un cadeau à ton roi.
Will you do this for me?
Tu veux faire ça pour moi ?
Good boy.
Gentil garçon.
No!
Double the guards to 20 yards through the night.
Doublez les gardes à 20 m cette nuit.
Three hours at a watch.
Relèves plus fréquentes.
I want these men fresh and alert.
Je les veux alertes.
Any man caught sleeping will have his eyes gouged.
Quiconque sera surpris à dormir aura les yeux arrachés.
Any caught speaking will lose his tongue.
Quiconque parlera aura la langue arrachée.
And I want all French prisoners in our train put to death.
Et faites exécuter tous nos prisonniers français.
Leave their corpses speared on pikes by the river's edge.
Empalez leurs cadavres sur des piques près de la rivière.
The first command I'll heed.
J'obéirai au premier ordre.
The second...
Le second,
you'll have to carry out that mass execution yourself.
je vous laisserai réaliser cette exécution de masse.
What did you say to me?
Que m'as-tu dit ?
You are not that man.
Ce n'est pas vous.
How dare you defy me?
Comment oses-tu me défier ?
Show your feeling in here, with me. - Don't let it outside this tent. - How dare you defy me? I am the king.
- Réfléchissez-y bien. - Comment oses-tu ? Je suis le roi.
And where is the fearsome old warrior Falstaff about whom I've heard so much?
Où est le redoutable guerrier Falstaff
dont on m'a tant parlé ?
You've been mute since we crossed the sea.
Tu ne dis mot depuis qu'on a débarqué.
I seem to be serving as my own chief tactician, my own commander, my own counsel.
Je suis mon propre tacticien,
commandant et conseiller.
Where is the fearsome old warrior Falstaff?!
Où est le redoutable guerrier Falstaff ?
I speak only when there's something to be said.
Je ne parle que quand c'est nécessaire.
Too often have I seen men of war
Par trop souvent, j'ai vu des guerriers
invent work for themselves,
s'inventer des tâches
work that leads to nothing but vainglory and slaughtered men.
qui n'entraînent que vaine gloire et massacres.
I'm not that man.
Je ne suis pas ainsi.
And this here is the war that you have chosen to wage.
Et nous menons la guerre que vous avez décidée.
I will disembowel you right here with mine own hand.
Je t'étriperai de mes propres mains.
You are not that man, either.
Ce n'est pas vous non plus.
Evening, M'Lord.
- Gentlemen. - M'Lord.
Messieurs.
Lord Dorset, summon your fastest rider.
Lord Dorset, convoquez vos cavaliers les plus rapides.
My liege.
Majesté.
Dartmouth!
Dartmouth !
Sires. What can I do for you?
Que puis-je pour vous ?
Tell me what lies over that hill. Ride fast, return directly.
Dis-moi ce qu'il y a par-delà cette colline. Reviens vite.
Hyah!
We are both outnumbered and out-positioned.
On est en infériorité et mal placés.
They have the downslope in their favor.
Le terrain leur est favorable.
Our need to advance puts us already at disadvantage.
Notre besoin d'avancer nous désavantage.
The longer we wait, the larger their force will grow, and with it, our disadvantage.
Plus on attendra, plus leurs forces grandiront,
comme notre désavantage.
Your archers, my lord, are of superior faculty.
Nos archers sont bien supérieurs.
French crossbow is no match for an English longbow.
L'arbalète française ne fait pas le poids contre nos arcs.
We should hobble their number on first assault by these means alone.
Clairsemons leurs rangs de cette façon au premier assaut.
York's charge in center faces four lines of mounted knights.
York est face à quatre lignes de chevaliers montés.
Our archers here might weaken those by half. But...
Nos archers peuvent les réduire de moitié.
But not eight lines.
Mais pas huit lignes.
Nine. Ten. More.
Neuf. Dix. Plus.
You speak true, my liege. The longer we wait, the greater our disadvantage.
Vous dites vrai, Majesté.
Attendre nous désavantage.
But it is possible our disadvantage has already grown insurmountable.
Il est possible que ce désavantage soit devenu insurmontable.
A great many men are already desperately ill
Nombre d'hommes sont déjà gravement malades
and weak from hunger.
et affaiblis par la faim.
What then, my lord, do you propose we do?
Que proposez-vous donc que l'on fasse ?
I propose we consider turning back, my liege.
Je propose qu'on songe à faire demi-tour.
I know it will not bring the outcome we desire,
Ce n'est pas l'issue désirée,
but nor will the evisceration of our army.
mais pas plus que l'éviscération de notre armée.
I'm reticent to speak for others here now,
Je rechigne à parler pour les autres,
but I'm certain my fears are shared.
mais mes craintes sont partagées, c'est sûr.
Who here agrees with Lord Dorset?
Qui est d'accord avec Lord Dorset ?
You can win this battle.
Vous pouvez remporter cette bataille.
Is that so, Sir John?
Vraiment, Sir John ?
Yes.
And precisely how is that so, Sir John?
Et comment, précisément, Sir John ?
You fight without horses and without armor.
En combattant sans chevaux ni armures.
Heavens above, please spare us from this man.
Grands dieux, gardez-nous de cet homme.
Their forward defense is a front line of mounted men.
Leur défense avancée est une ligne de cavalerie.
Many deep.
Très profonde.
Knights all.
De chevaliers.
All on horseback, all with heavy armor.
Tous à dos de cheval et en armure lourde.
The ground out there...
Le terrain
is a flood bowl,
est une cuvette,
already half-sodden.
à moitié détrempée.
When it rains tonight, as I know it will,
Quand il pleuvra ce soir, c'est une certitude,
that ground will turn into a muddy bog.
ce terrain deviendra un marécage.
And with their horses and their armor,
Et avec leurs chevaux et armures,
they will get stuck, they will fall,
ils seront coincés, ils tomberont
and they will flounder like upturned beetles.
et se débattront tels des scarabées retournés.
As shall we.
Tout comme nous.
Not if we travel light,
Pas si on s'allège,
without horses and without armor.
sans chevaux ni armures.
Speed and mobility will be our advantage.
Vitesse et mobilité seront notre avantage.
And how, Sir John, can you be so sure of rainfall tonight?
Et comment, Sir John, savez-vous qu'il pleuvra ce soir ?
My right knee is aching. It only does that when rain is near.
J'ai mal au genou droit. Cela indique que la pluie n'est pas loin.
Oh, save us, my liege. Please put a stop to this drivel.
Majesté, faites cesser ces balivernes.
This would require their armored front line come meet us in the mud.
Leur première ligne devrait nous rencontrer dans la boue.
How do you propose we invite that?
Comment procéder ?
A small forward armored attack of our own.
Une petite attaque avancée.
A false advance.
Une fausse avancée.
They will counter.
Ils répliqueront.
We save our weight and our muscle for a nimble assault from the flanks.
On conserve notre poids et nos forces pour un preste assaut des flancs.
They shan't be so easily deceived. They will not respond to false attack.
Ils ne sauraient être si aisément dupés par une fausse attaque.
Hmm.
They will respond.
Ils réagiront.
We move, they will meet us in the mud.
Si on bouge, ils nous rencontreront.
Our men-at-arms are outnumbered. This they know.
Nos soldats sont en infériorité numérique. Ils le savent.
They will hope to overwhelm us, so they will meet us with full force,
Ils espéreront nous submerger, ils déplaceront toutes leurs forces,
no matter how small our first advance.
qu'importe si on est peu nombreux.
Our great longbows will rain chaos on them from above.
Nos archers feront pleuvoir un chaos de flèches du ciel.
That chaos will be your favor.
Ce chaos sera à votre avantage.
My liege, I implore you, we mustn't... we mustn't listen to this madness.
Majesté, je vous en conjure, n'écoutons pas cette folie.
What is the true experience of this man? He once fought for Richard many years ago.
Quelle est sa véritable expérience ? Il a combattu pour Richard jadis.
Since then, he has done nothing...
Depuis lors, il n'a rien fait,
other than ride with the companies,
hormis chevaucher en bandes,
robbing and tormenting.
détrousser et torturer.
I never robbed anyone who didn't deserve to be robbed.
Je n'ai jamais détroussé personne qui ne le méritait pas.
If it rains tonight,
S'il pleut ce soir,
we fight tomorrow.
nous combattrons demain.
If you have concocted this plan, half-baked and speculative,
Si tu as concocté ce plan gauche et bancal
merely to prove to me your worth,
pour me prouver ta valeur,
please say so now.
dis-le sans ambages.
All plans are speculative.
Tout plan est bancal.
And as I say, I only speak them when I feel them true.
Et je vous l'ai dit, je n'évoque que ce que j'estime être vrai.
This one I feel in my bones.
Je le sens dans ma chair.
This one I feel in my knee bone.
Je le sens dans mon genou.
Here we are on the eve of this fight, and I am...
À la veille de cet affrontement, je...
I am scared to wonder, to tell it true,
j'ai peur de m'interroger, à dire vrai...
why we are here.
sur la raison de notre présence.
You best discover the answer for that.
Mieux vaut découvrir cette réponse.
The men out there deserve it.
Nos hommes la méritent.
They've given their lives to you.
Ils vous ont confié leurs vies.
I cannot say what forces have conspired to bring you here,
J'ignore tout des forces qui ont ourdi votre venue,
but these men need you,
mais ces hommes ont besoin de vous,
just as you need them.
comme vous, d'eux.
These men deserve your confidence.
Ces hommes méritent votre confiance.
And if you cannot give them that,
Si vous ne pouvez leur accorder,
at least then tell them a magnificent lie.
alors, contez-leur un mensonge sublime.
Though you might not think it possible...
Bien que tu croies cela impossible,
you are my friend.
tu es mon ami.
Good night, Hal.
Bonsoir, Hal.
Sleep well.
Dormez bien.
This wind whips from the north.
Le vent souffle du nord.
The rain was sent from England.
La pluie arrive d'Angleterre.
Why are you being fitted with plate? We were to fight without armor.
Pourquoi ce plastron ? On combat sans armures.
We need a front line to draw them in.
La première ligne doit les attirer.
It cannot be you.
Ce ne saurait être toi.
The idea was mine.
C'était mon idée.
Some man must lead the first push to sell it well.
Un homme doit mener l'offensive pour qu'ils mordent à l'hameçon.
My men have been assembled.
Mes hommes ont été réunis.
And I cannot, in good conscience, send them out there to realize my speculative drivel
Et je ne peux, en mon âme et conscience,
without getting muddy alongside them, can I?
les envoyer exécuter mon plan
sans patauger dans la boue avec eux.
I will fight with you.
Je combattrai à tes côtés.
It's noble, but you know that cannot be.
C'est noble. Mais c'est impossible.
This is what I was built for.
J'ai été formé à ça.
I die here or... I die over a bottle in Eastcheap.
Je mourrai ici ou une bouteille à la main à Eastcheap.
And I think this makes for a much better story.
Mais ici, j'en sortirai plus glorieux.
And you have things still to do.
Vous avez encore des tâches à accomplir.
You will join this fight.
Vous combattrez.
But promise me you don't join too early.
Mais promettez-moi
de ne pas arriver trop tôt.
It doesn't matter what you see out there.
Qu'importe ce que vous verrez.
We must first draw them all in. All of them.
On doit d'abord tous les attirer. Tous.
Promise me that, Hal.
Promettez-le-moi, Hal.
Win, my friend.
Triomphez, mon ami.
Maybe then you'll lighten enough to have a drink with me. Hmm?
Vous vous dériderez alors assez pour boire avec moi.
Where is the Dauphin?
I humbly thank you for receiving me, noble lord.
Please.
S'il vous plaît.
Please speak English.
Parlez anglais.
I enjoy to speak English.
J'apprécie de parler anglais.
It is simple... and ugly.
C'est simple et laid.
I have been waiting all morning,
J'ai attendu toute la matinée,
all the night...
toute la nuit
for your surrender.
votre capitulation.
It might have saved a great unease
Bien des inquiétudes eussent été épargnées
had it come sooner.
si elle était survenue plus tôt.
I know you do not speak for your father. I do speak for my father.
- Vous ne parlez pas pour votre père. - Je parle pour mon père.
I know you do not speak for your father, so I come to you now directly.
Vous ne parlez pas pour lui, je viens donc à vous.
I have not come to surrender.
Je ne suis pas venu capituler.
Too much Christian blood will be spilled on this field today.
Trop de sang chrétien sera versé sur ce champ de bataille.
So, I propose this:
Voici ma proposition :
You and I fight, one man on one man.
combattons vous et moi, d'homme à homme,
We fight in our armies' stead.
en lieu et place de nos armées.
If I lose, my men will leave this place forthwith and forever.
Je perds, mes hommes partiront sans délai et pour toujours.
You will have my head.
Vous aurez ma tête.
If I win,
Je gagne,
I will assume this kingdom's crown upon your father's death.
la couronne du royaume me reviendra à la mort de votre père.
What say you?
Votre réponse ?
Are you scared, young Henry?
Avez-vous peur, jeune Henri ?
What say you?
Votre réponse ?
Are you scared of this battle?
Avez-vous peur de cette bataille ?
There is no shame of it.
Il n'y a aucune honte à avoir.
Save your men.
Sauvez vos hommes.
You save your own men.
Sauvez vos propres hommes.
You came here. To me!
Vous êtes venu ici. Me voir, moi !
Surrender to me!
Capitulez devant moi !
I cannot do that.
Je ne le peux pas.
Well, then, boy,
Dans ce cas,
let us make famous... that field out there.
faisons passer ce champ à la postérité.
This little village of Agincourt,
Ce petit village d'Azincourt,
that will forever mark the site of your callow disgrace.
qui sera à jamais le symbole de votre disgrâce naïve.
You expect of me a speech?
Vous attendez un discours ?
I have only one to give, and it is the same one I'd give were we not standing on the brim of a battlefield.
Je n'en ai qu'un, et c'est le même que je donnerais
si nous n'étions pas prêts à guerroyer.
It is the same one I'd give were we to meet in the street by chance.
C'est le même que je donnerais si nous nous croisions dans la rue.
I have only ever hoped for one thing...
Je n'ai jamais aspiré qu'à une chose,
to see this kingdom united under this English crown.
voir ce royaume uni sous la couronne anglaise.
All men are born to die. We know it. We carry it with us always.
Tous les hommes sont mortels. Nous le savons. Nous l'acceptons.
If your day be today, so be it.
Si vous devez mourir aujourd'hui, alors, soit.
Mine will be tomorrow.
Moi, je mourrai demain.
Or mine today and yours tomorrow. It matters not.
Ou alors, l'inverse. Nulle importance.
What matters is that you know, in your hearts, that today you are that kingdom united.
Tant que vous savez, dans vos cœurs,
que vous êtes ce royaume uni.
You are England. Each and every one of you. England is you.
Vous êtes l'Angleterre. Chacun d'entre vous. Le pays, c'est vous.
And it is the space between you.
Tout comme l'espace entre vous.
Fight not for yourselves, fight for that space.
Ne combattez pas pour vous, mais pour cet espace.
Fill that space. Make it tissue. Make it mass.
Comblez cet espace. Faites-en du tissu. De la masse.
Make it impenetrable. Make it yours!
Rendez-le impénétrable. Faites-le vôtre !
Make it England!
Faites-en l'Angleterre !
Great men to it. Captains, lords.
Allons, hommes illustres. Capitaines.
Great men to it!
Allons, hommes illustres !
For the King and St. George!
Pour le roi et Saint-George !
Les imbéciles.
Archers.
Archers!
Archers !
Archers.
Archers! Now!
Archers ! Maintenant !
Draw!
Armez !
Loose!
Décochez.
Halt!
Halte !
Ready!
Parés !
Loose!
Décochez !
On me!
Avec moi !
Come then...
Venez...
King of England.
roi d'Angleterre.
Hail the King.
Vive le roi.
My liege.
- God save the King. - Hail the King.
Vive le roi.
Hail the King.
- Hail the King. - Hail King Henry. Hail the King.
- Vive le roi. - Vive le roi Henri.
My liege.
Majesté.
The prisoners we have took are a rabble.
Les prisonniers sont du petit peuple.
I fear we will not secure them should their army regroup.
Nous ne pourrons les retenir si leur armée se regroupe.
Kill them all.
Tuez-les tous.
Your Majesty...
Henry, King of England.
Hmm.
Your Majesty...
Votre Majesté,
Come sit here with me.
asseyez-vous à mes côtés.
Please.
Je vous en prie.
I like to have the sun on my skin, but not too much.
J'aime le contact du soleil sur ma peau, mais point trop.
Too much is very dangerous.
Trop, c'est très dangereux.
This conversation we are about to have...
La conversation qui va suivre
has been had many times before, and will be had many times again for centuries to come
a déjà souvent eu lieu par le passé
et aura encore souvent lieu dans les siècles à venir
between men of vanity and men of good reason.
entre hommes orgueilleux et hommes de bonne raison.
I would hope that you and I are men of good reason.
J'espère que vous et moi sommes hommes de bonne raison.
I have, of course, traveled here to offer you my surrender.
Je suis, bien sûr, venu jusqu'ici pour capituler.
Do you ask anything of me in return?
Voulez-vous quelque chose en retour ?
No.
I do, however,
J'ai bien
have for you a proposition.
une proposition à vous faire.
You take the hand of my daughter, Catherine,
Prenez la main de ma fille, Catherine,
in marriage.
en mariage.
It is most uncanny...
C'est très inhabituel,
that the great movements of history
mais les grands mouvements de l'histoire
so frequently find their origins in the minutia of family.
trouvent fréquemment leur origine dans les menus détails de la famille.
That in ways I dare not unsettle here,
À bien des égards, je n'ose évoquer
my relationship with my son
ma relation avec mon fils
and yours... with your father.
et la vôtre avec votre père,
These are the things that have led us here today.
ce sont ces choses-là qui nous ont menés ici aujourd'hui.
We are leaders of lands and peoples,
Nous dirigeons des terres et des gens,
and yet... it is family that moves us.
or, c'est la famille qui est notre raison d'être.
Family...
Nos familles
consumes us.
nous consument.
My condolences to you...
Mes condoléances
for the loss of your friend, Sir John.
pour la perte de votre ami, Sir John.
I know you must feel this loss deeply.
Je sais combien il doit vous manquer.
Thank you, William.
Merci, William.
Your loyalty to me has been comforting.
Ta loyauté m'a été un réconfort.
You have proven yourself to be a most worthy king.
Vous vous êtes révélé être un roi des plus dignes.
I would say you have proven yourself to be one of England's great kings.
Je dirais même que vous vous êtes révélé
être un des grands rois d'Angleterre.
Your Majesty, the crowd has gathered.
Votre Majesté,
une foule s'est réunie.
So I hear.
J'entends ça.
Leave us.
Please sit, Your Majesty.
You are beautiful.
Merci.
I will no longer speak French.
We must speak English.
I cannot speak English.
You will learn.
I wonder, then,
how our union might proceed in the meantime.
There is much I wonder about a great many things.
Je m'interroge beaucoup sur bien des choses.
Indeed there must be for you to contemplate marriage to a woman about whom...
C'est bien normal
you know so little.
de réfléchir à un mariage avec une femme dont vous savez si peu.
Hmm.
I will not submit to you.
Je ne me soumettrai pas à vous.
You must earn my respect.
Vous devez gagner mon respect.
I understand that.
Je le comprends.
Do you?
Vraiment ?
I do.
Oui.
Do you feel a sense of achievement?
Ressentez-vous de l'accomplissement ?
In what regard?
À quel sujet ?
In any regard.
À tous les sujets.
I have achieved that which my father never could.
J'ai réalisé ce dont mon père a été incapable.
I have united this kingdom in common cause.
Unir ce royaume autour d'une cause commune.
Hmm.
You have achieved momentary respite.
Vous n'avez obtenu qu'un répit fugace.
A unity forged under false pretense will never be a unity that prevails.
Une unité forgée sous un faux prétexte ne prévaudra jamais.
How, pray, have my endeavors been forged falsely?
Comment mon entreprise a-t-elle été façonnée faussement ?
Why did you bring war to France? Your father came on spoiling.
- Pourquoi cette guerre contre la France ? - Provocation de votre père.
How so? How was he spoiling?
Comment vous a-t-il provoqué ?
He sent an assassin.
Il a envoyé un assassin.
There was no assassin.
Il n'y a pas eu d'assassin.
There was no plot to kill you.
Ni complot pour vous tuer.
How might you know?
Qu'en savez-vous ?
Because I was with my father when he received word of your charge.
J'étais avec mon père quand il a reçu vos accusations.
I know him well enough to know his reaction to be genuine.
Je sais que sa réaction était sincère.
How was his reaction?
Quelle a été sa réaction ?
He laughed.
Il a ri.
He laughed very much. He said you must be drunk.
Il a dit que vous deviez être soûl.
Your father is a madman.
Votre père est un fou.
He may be mad, but he is true.
Peut-être bien, mais il dit vrai.
His madness makes him true. He says only what he believes.
Sa folie le rend sincère. Il ne dit que ce qu'il croit.
That is why he is loved.
Il est aimé pour cela.
The assassin then was sent by your brother. - My brother? - Mm-hmm.
L'assassin a été envoyé par votre frère.
My brother was too stupid to conjure such a plan.
Mon frère était trop bête pour tramer un tel plan.
What was your true reason? Did you know of the ball he sent?
- Quelle était votre véritable raison ? - Il m'a envoyé une balle.
The ball he sent to me?
La balle qu'il m'a envoyée ?
A ball?
Une balle ?
He sent to you... - a ball? - Why should you question my intent?
Il vous a envoyé une balle ?
Your father's rule is illegitimate. He has no right claim to his throne.
Pourquoi douter de mes intentions ?
All monarchy is illegitimate.
Le règne de votre père est illégitime. Le trône n'est pas à lui.
Toute monarchie est illégitime.
You yourself are the son of a usurper.
Vous êtes le fils d'un usurpateur.
It would seem that you have no explanation for what you have done.
Vous ne semblez avoir aucune explication pour vos décisions.
You have shed the blood of so many Christian souls, and yet...
Vous avez versé le sang de nombres d'âmes chrétiennes, mais
before me now, all I see is a...
je ne vois devant moi
young and vain and foolish man so easily riled.
qu'un jeune impudent prompt à l'agacement.
So easily beguiled.
Facilement dupé.
I must leave you now.
Je dois vous laisser.
Gentle.
Doucement.
Ah.
We must be sure to revel in this day, my friend.
Nous devons nous assurer de savourer cette journée, mon ami.
A crowd has gathered in honor of our victory.
Une foule s'est réunie en l'honneur de notre victoire.
These are the rare moments for which a king truly lives, I would imagine.
Ces rares moments sont la raison d'être d'un roi, j'imagine.
In all my preoccupation, I have... neglected to ask after your family.
Préoccupé que j'étais, j'ai omis de te demander si ta famille va bien.
Oh.
Your preoccupations are hardly trifling.
Vos préoccupations ne sont pas des vétilles.
You have two sons.
Tu as deux fils.
I do.
Oui.
And...
Et...
your wife minds your estate in your absence.
ton épouse gère tes biens en ton absence.
She does.
Tout à fait.
Yours is sheep.
Des moutons.
You're a man of wool.
Pour la laine.
As was my father before me.
Comme mon père avant moi.
How many head?
Combien de têtes ?
At last count, some 4,000. Mostly Dorset Horns.
Au dernier comptage, environ 4 000. De la race Dorset.
How much land have you?
Combien de terres ?
Oh.
To be true, I'm not...
À dire vrai, je n'en
wholly certain, but...
suis pas certain.
but many... many hundreds of beautiful, beautiful acres.
Mais de nombreux magnifiques hectares.
What lands in France have you now annexed?
Quelles terres as-tu annexées en France ?
Stop.
Arrête.
Hmm?
Now that France is ours, how much of her land is now yours?
Maintenant qu'on a la France, combien de terres possèdes-tu ?
Oh, well...
Ma foi.
That has yet to be determined.
Cela reste à déterminer.
Your conquest is so recent.
Votre conquête est toute récente.
- Why do you ask this question... - Stay up there.
- Pourquoi cette question ? - Reste.
- Hmm? - Stay up there.
Reste là-haut.
Oh.
How did my assassin come to you?
Comment mon assassin est-il venu à toi ?
I fail to remember the moment.
Je ne m'en souviens plus.
Remedy this failure.
Remédie à cet oubli.
So much has happened in the intervening months.
Tant de choses sont arrivées depuis.
An event as pivotal as this one
Un événement aussi crucial
should be amply equipped to penetrate the fog of time elapsed.
devrait aisément percer les brouillards du temps écoulé.
No?
Of course.
Bien entendu.
Let me recall.
Que je me rappelle.
Was it in the street?
Était-ce dans la rue ?
Did he come to you in the street?
Est-il venu à toi dans la rue ?
Yes. Yes, it was in the street.
Oui. C'était dans la rue.
He approached me...
Il m'a abordé
most unusually.
de façon très étrange.
My liege, please, tell me the cause of this concern.
Majesté, je vous en prie, dites-moi ce qui vous préoccupe.
Stay up there.
Reste là-haut.
Did he know your name?
Savait-il ton nom ?
I don't believe he did.
Je ne crois pas.
How, then, did he know who you were to approach?
Comment a-t-il su qui tu étais ?
Ah.
The memory is returning.
La mémoire me revient.
He surrendered himself to palace guards and the matter was brought to my attention.
Il s'est livré aux gardes du palais,
I was taken to him.
l'affaire a été portée à mon attention, je suis allé le voir.
So, he did not come to you in the street. No. No, it was not in the street. Forgive me.
- Il ne t'a pas abordé dans la rue. - Non. Pas dans la rue. Pardonnez-moi.
I was summoned to his cell.
J'ai été mandé à sa cellule.
Has a problem arisen...
Est-ce qu'un problème est survenu...
Hal?
Hal ?
Yes. A problem has arisen.
Oui. Un problème est survenu.
And it wobbles before me now on its silly little stool
Et il vacille devant moi sur son tabouret ridicule
- at mine own elevation. - I'm afraid I don't understand.
- et me toise. - Je ne comprends pas.
- Please, please, stop this charade. - Sincerely, I do not understand.
- Cesse cette comédie. - Je ne comprends vraiment pas.
Stop the fucking charade! Stop it!
Cesse cette putain de charade ! Arrête !
I have given you what you wanted, boy!
Je vous ai donné ce que vous vouliez, petit !
Have I not?!
N'est-il pas ?
Mm.
You wanted peace. Did you not?!
Vous vouliez la paix. N'est-ce pas ?
This is how peace is forged.
La paix est forgée ainsi.
It is forged in victory.
Elle est forgée dans la victoire.
Listen.
Écoutez.
That is the sound of peace.
C'est le bruit de la paix.
That is the sound of your peace.
C'est l'écho de votre paix.
That is the sound of your greatness.
C'est le bruit de votre grandeur.
Hmm?
- My liege. - My liege.
My liege.
I ask nothing of you...
Je vous demande une chose...
only that you will always speak to me clear and true.
de toujours me dire la vérité.
Always.
Toujours.
Will you promise me only that?
Me le promettez-vous ?
Long live the King!
- Long live the King! - I will.
Oui.
Long live the King!
King Henry!
FRE Sous-titres Luc Kenoufi
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412