My name is Barry Allen, and
I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry. Run.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensics scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed
to fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother.
- Mom.
- And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously, on The Flash...
Who do you think you are?
This is what we talked about,
using my speed to do good.
We talked about you helping
us contain other meta-humans.
After all of these journalism
classes, I started a blog.
I thought you were taking journalism,
not science fiction writing.
Ever since I have known you,
you have believed in the impossible.
What if you were right about
the night that your mom died?
Something out there is saving people.
See you soon, Barry.
How often do you think about
why your friends came into your life?
Was it random, by design,
or maybe a little of both?
Nice.
Regardless of the reason,
some friends you just know
are gonna be by your side for a while.
Others, you're not so sure.
And then there's that one
friend who, well, you hope,
someday becomes something more.
But "friend" will have to do for now.
And that's okay.
I guess.
I'm glad you invited Caitlin and Cisco.
They're cool, right?
They saved your life, Barry.
That makes them the coolest
people I've ever met.
It's nice that you guys became friends.
To friends, old and new.
Ooh. I'm up.
Wish me luck.
I'm going to destroy you.
Don't get cocky, West.
Guys? I have a problem.
We all do when guys like him exist.
Yeah, he's so hot.
Uh, I mean, genetically speaking.
Because I'm a geneticist, of course.
Oh, my God, do I sound like Felicity?
I'm not talking about Eddie.
I'm talking about this.
I can't feel anything.
Yeah, that's usually what
happens when you drink too much.
No, the alcohol is not affecting me.
I mean I literally feel nothing.
It's your hyper-metabolism.
I need a sample.
I'll get more shots.
I swear, I had a Vacutainer here.
Wait, you carry a blood
collection kit in your purse?
You have your hobbies.
- 14th floor is secure.
- Roger that.
[Whistling]
Hold off on that check.
Lock down the building!
Hold it!
Don't come near me.
You need to come with me. Come on.
Get down!
[Loud blast]
- Still nothing?
- I can't get drunk.
I mean, I'm only 25,
and my drinking days are already over.
Come on, Allen. You're up.
[Cell phone sounds]
There was a bombing on 8th and Pass.
- I got to go, babe.
- Okay.
Sorry, guys.
I've got an early shift at Jitters.
Barry, we'll catch up tomorrow.
It's getting late,
anyway, so I'm just gonna...
Help! Help!
Somebody!
Guys, there's a window
washer, and he's gonna fall.
Don't try and catch him.
You don't have super strength.
Well, is there, like,
a bed store near here?
What if I get a bunch of
mattresses and stack them?
Barry, this isn't a roadrunner cartoon.
Help! Help!
How fast would I need to go
to run up the side of a building?
How far up do you need to go?
Hurry, somebody!
I don't know. 50 meters, give or take.
32.56... [murmuring]
- Guys, hurry!
- Help!
Just run really fast and you'll be fine.
But you need to maintain your
velocity on the way down, or...
Or what?
Splat.
- Great.
- Help!
All right. All right,
all right, all right.
Here goes.
Synced and Corrected by Nsiko
www.Addic7ed.com
Barry? What do you got?
Bombers typically have
their own unique signatures.
Crimped wires, fragmentation.
The level of sophistication is
telling once I've analyzed it.
You show me a bomb, I can
usually find a clue in it.
It sounds like there's
a "but" coming.
Yeah, I haven't found any
sign of an oxidizing agent.
It's as if the floor just blew itself up.
Things don't just blow up.
Security guard said our
bomber was a woman, red hair.
Must've cut the security camera's feed.
There's no footage, but
there might be something else.
Some kind of small charge
blasted the doorknob off.
Any idea what's missing?
My guess is one of these files.
It's gonna take days
to figure out which one.
Let's let Barry do his thing.
- What's going on?
- I have no idea.
But they came in here
like they own the place.
Been talking to Singh
for the last half hour.
This can't be good.
General Eiling, this is Detective West.
Detective.
What's this all about?
The army's taking over
the bombing investigation.
I'll need everything you have.
Physical evidence,
photographs, witness interviews,
and all your personal notes.
I've been on the job nearly 20 years
and never heard of the army
investigating anything civilian.
Well, it's not civilian.
She's one of ours.
We'll send over everything we got.
Very kind of you.
I think we'll take it now, though.
Give them what they want, Joe.
You heard him, Joe. Give me what I want.
Hey, what's going on?
General Eiling is relieving
us from the bombing case.
Give these men everything that's relevant.
Sure thing, yeah.
You and a few civilians
from S.T.A.R. Labs
might want to check into that.
I think we might.
Can I talk to you for a minute, Joe?
It's about Iris.
Hey, dad. You're home early.
What were you doing at
the bomb site last night?
Don't deny you were there.
Officer Vukuvich saw you.
It's... Complicated.
You can't be coming to every crime scene
because you're worried about Eddie.
He's a big boy, Iris.
I didn't go there to see Eddie.
I went there to see the streak.
The streak. Hmm, why is that?
My blog.
I've been collecting Internet posts
about the streak sightings,
and writing about them.
Baby, there's no streak.
Yes, there is.
I saw him last night,
dad. I looked right at him.
Something incredible is
happening in Central City.
And I am gonna write about it.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, I have to get to work.
Blogging about supernatural
events doesn't really pay well.
A va file number is all the
info you have on the bomber?
C.C.P.D's been ordered off the case.
Well, who has the power to do that?
The army. Some general.
His name was Eiling, I think.
General Wade Eiling.
- You know him?
- Yeah, I know him.
About ten years ago, General Wade Eiling
contracted S.T.A.R. Labs to develop
enhanced gene therapies for soldiers.
I was interested in the potential
medical benefits for civilians.
General Eiling really wanted to develop
mind reading capabilities
for interrogation purposes.
I stopped the study when I
saw his techniques up close,
but our split was less than amicable.
He took all the evidence
I collected on the bombing.
Everything but the folder.
Well... Lucky for us, the va finally
joined the new millennium
and digitized their records.
A lot of redacted info.
But our girl's name is Bette Sans Souci,
an EOD specialist for the army.
- EOD?
- Bombs.
Is there an address?
Hold on. Here, we go.
One person in case of emergency.
Cameron Scott. Inglewood.
Bette Sans Souci?
I need you to come with me.
Don't touch me.
Get whatever you're wearing off of you.
Hurry.
Barry?
Can you hear me? Barry?
There must be a perfectly
reasonable explanation
for why he's not answering.
Barry?
Uh...
Don't ask.
I'm gonna ask. Where's my suit?
It's... Gone.
What do you mean, it's gone?
What did you do with my suit?
It blew up, dude.
I managed to get out of it
before it went, "kaboom."
My suit went "kaboom"?
Fun fact about Bette Sans Souci.
She's not carrying bombs.
She touched the emblem on the suit
and turned it into a bomb.
She's a meta-human.
With the ability to
cause spontaneous combustion
upon tactile contact.
- She blew up my suit.
- You have, like, three more.
Okay, I have two. And I loved that one.
All right, what else
do we know about her?
Oh, I don't know. She's pure evil.
We're gonna find this girl
and send her butt into the pipeline.
No one blows my tech to smithereens
and gets away with it...
Unless she looks like that.
I don't think she meant to hurt me.
Well, her being a meta-human
explains General Eiling's interest in her.
And why he stole the case from us.
He didn't want anyone to
know what she could do.
- Detective.
- Doctor.
So... Human bomb.
Must be Tuesday in Central City.
Yes, and General Eiling's
not one to give up a potential
asset without a fight.
We have to find her before he does.
Barry? Can I see you for a second?
When were you planning on telling me
that Iris saw the streak?
That was not planned.
She caught me off guard.
We had a deal.
You keep her in the dark
about the meta-humans,
and I don't go Floyd Mayweather on you.
Okay, Joe, I know.
And she's writing a blog now.
I already talked to her about that.
Talk to her again.
And be more convincing.
Okay.
- You mean, right now?
- Yes, I do.
All right.
You've got to stop writing about this guy.
- He doesn't even exist.
- I saw him, Barry.
He wears a red suit, like,
a uniform or something,
with a lighting bolt on his chest.
I mean, Iris, come on.
You were drinking last night at the bar.
I was not drunk, and I know what I saw.
He wears a mask.
I think he smiled at me.
Okay, first of all,
if he is wearing a mask,
that probably means he doesn't
want people to know who he is.
It doesn't matter who he is.
What matters is that people
know that he's out there.
What is wrong with you?
This is important to me.
Why can't you be more supportive?
I'm just... you haven't
even put your name on it.
How serious can you be
about an anonymous blog?
Okay, you know what? Our entire lives,
you couldn't scream loud enough
that the impossible existed.
And now it's actually
happening in Central City.
I have proof of it, and you
don't want to know about it?
That doesn't make sense, Barry.
So when you're ready to tell
me what this whole routine
is really about, then we can talk.
- [Cell phone vibrates]
- Yeah.
We've piggybacked onto General
Eiling's own surveillance.
According to what they're saying,
the lovely Ms. Sans Souci
was just spotted in Inglewood.
The same neighborhood as
Dr. Harold Hadley's office,
the military surgeon who performed
several procedures on her.
That's why she was looking for the folder.
You got to get to
her before Eiling does.
Okay.
- Sgt. Sans Souci.
- You remember me.
Good. Because I remember you, doctor.
I remember waking up from a coma.
You started cutting me open.
I was only trying to
help ease your condition.
You couldn't control it.
You did this to me. You and Eiling.
Go bring me my asset.
You okay?
Look, I can get you out of here.
I can help you understand
what happened to you.
- How?
- Because it happened to me too.
Please.
Target is gone.
As the detonation dispersed
throughout Central City.
A number of people were exposed to a wave
of unquantifiable energy.
One of those people... Was you.
You were in Central City ten months ago.
I had just returned from Afghanistan.
I was there defusing roadside bombs
and... Shrapnel ripped through me.
I was flown back state side.
Spent months at the base recuperating
and next thing I know,
I became the thing that almost killed me.
And Eiling's favorite, new lab rat.
The dark matter must have combined
with the bomb particulate inside your body.
I thought Eiling did this to me.
Eiling is not smart enough
to create someone like you.
Clever enough to see your value.
Do you know of any
others who were changed?
There've been a few.
But no one that looks like you.
I'm sorry. That was inappropriate.
Please don't leave.
I know how to perform a lobotomy.
Her cellular structure's
unlike anything I've ever seen.
Her nitrogen levels are off the charts.
Do you think we can help her?
To answer that question,
we have to understand
how she works, and to understand that,
first we have to study her in action.
You want her to blow stuff up.
- Yes, now we're talking.
- Not in here.
- She's too unstable.
- I know.
I know you know.
So this is your life now, huh?
Testing people like me?
Stopping people like you.
It's not what I thought I'd be doing.
Actually, aside from Barry,
you're the first meta-human
that we've tested.
- "Meta-human"?
- It's just a term.
Oh, my God, what happened?
Why didn't you say that you were shot?
It just grazed me.
There's something in there.
A tracker.
Lock down the pipeline.
Get Bette out of here.
I'll take care of Eiling.
Harrison Wells. How
the mighty have fallen.
General.
S.T.A.R. Labs.
This place used to be so important.
Tell me, what does one do
after such a spectacular, public failure?
One adapts. One evolves.
One becomes intent on
reversing one's fortune.
Always the idealist.
- What do you want, Wade?
- Where's my asset?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
We tracked her here, Harrison.
Turn her over to me before you see the rest
of your precious palace crumble.
Oh, Wade, Wade, Wade.
We could've changed
the world, you and I.
427 kPa's.
Her Trauzl rating is around 45.
That's the same as any plastique.
Plastique. Ha... first try!
Didn't really think
this one through, did you?
Downrange, insurgents
started booby trapping cars.
The rest of my tour, I was terrified
to touch another vehicle.
Now, I'm gonna spend the rest
of my life terrified to
touch another human being.
Have they tried to help you?
Yeah, they've helped me
learn how to use my powers.
Not reverse them.
If they could reverse it so
you weren't a meta-human,
would you?
A friend told me I was
given my speed for a reason.
That I was chosen.
I don't know if I believe that,
but I always wanted to help people.
Now I can.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Sorry. Hey, Joe.
I see your little conversation
with Iris was a rousing success.
She just posted another
story about the streak.
Joe, I tried. I really tried.
She's got her name on it now, Barry.
What? Joe...
It's my fault, I shouldn't
have asked you to say anything.
I just wanted you to know.
Okay? Bye.
What was that about?
Iris posted about the streak again.
She signed her name to it.
- Oh, that's not good.
- No.
If one of these bad meta-humans
we're dealing with figures
she knows something...
Then they may target her, I know.
[Knock at door, bell chiming]
Sorry, we're closed.
Oh, my God, it's you.
Iris West,
I hear you've been writing about me.
You are real.
I should, um... let
me just clean up...
Meet me on the roof.
I'll give you a head start.
I need you to stop writing about me.
There are a lot of
people who need someone
like you right now.
To know that you're out there.
I have so many questions.
Where are you from?
I can't say.
Who are you?
I can't tell you that, either.
How can you do what you do?
You're a terrible interview.
There's more to this
than you can understand.
Just trust me, please.
I need you to stop.
Can you stop?
Running into buildings and rescuing people
without them even
knowing that you're there?
I don't do this for the glory.
So why do you?
Look, I have this friend,
an he had something terrible
happen to him when he was a kid.
His whole life, he's been telling stories
about this impossible thing.
And people laughed at him.
And shrinks analyzed him.
And he's been searching for
an explanation ever since.
But now, suddenly, it's
like he's lost his faith.
But you... you are proof
that he wasn't crazy.
Help me save my friend.
He's a lucky guy.
Hey, what's wrong?
Did Eiling find out you're here?
No.
Caitlin was about to give
me the not-so-good news.
The shrapnel in your body
has merged with you on a cellular level.
And the technology required
to unsplice your DNA...
it hasn't been invented yet.
Bette.
It's okay. Roger that.
I just need a minute. Don't worry.
Pretty sure I can cry
without blowing stuff up.
- What now?
- She joins us.
- Becomes a part of the team.
- Barry...
You have an amazing ability to help people.
She makes things explode.
She's the first meta-human not hell-bent
on destroying this city.
It's too dangerous.
Well, she's not going in the pipeline.
I'm not suggesting
she go in the pipeline,
but were she to remain at S.T.A.R. Labs,
it would put all of us at risk.
From who? Eiling?
Eiling is a dangerous man, Barry.
We do not want him as an enemy.
After the lighting bolt,
what if you hadn't found me?
It could've been me.
Hunted, on the run, cut off from
everyone I know and care about.
You guys saved me.
And I want to save her
just as bad as you do, Barry.
We all do.
Joe. What are you doing here?
Going over the materials
in your mom's case.
How's it going with you?
Stellar... I made friends
with a human bomb
who I promised I could
help, and then, I couldn't.
And I finally diagnosed why
Iris is writing about the streak.
She's doing it for me.
To prove the impossible is possible.
How do you know that?
The streak may have talked to her.
Barry, don't you think Iris
would recognize your voice?
No, I can do this cool
thing with my vocal cords,
where I vibrate them so I sound like this.
I know. It's cool, it's cool.
Whoa.
Well, you put that out there now, so.
I want to keep her safe.
You know the only real
way to get her to stop
is to tell her the truth.
Man, you really want to tell her.
- I tell her everything.
- Mm...
Not everything.
Is it that obvious?
Not to her.
But how long have you known for?
I have watched you be in love with Iris
since you were old enough
to know what love is.
And I've been waiting
years for you to tell her.
But you haven't.
Guess I was too slow.
Now, she's happy and
with someone else, so...
When the universe wants
to make something happen,
whether it be giving a
young man lighting speed
or putting two people together,
it has a way of figuring those things out.
And I got to get home.
Thanks.
Cisco?
He went home.
I think our Cisco's developing
a little bit of a crush on you.
Not sure I'm prize winning
date material anymore.
Change is hard.
The same accident that changed
you put me in this chair.
Sorry. I didn't know.
I don't share that story
with you to garner sympathy.
I tell it to you to
illustrate a larger point.
And what point is that?
That I would do anything
to get back what I lost.
- As would you.
- I would.
I just don't know how.
You soldiers, you call yourselves
Sheep Dogs. Am I right?
Happy and normal until
someone attacks our flock.
Every good person who
was changed that night,
people like you, people like Barry Allen,
those people are your flock now, Bette.
And General Eiling will never
stop attacking that flock,
and he always gets his target.
Unless you stop him.
You know your duty, Sergeant.
Kill Eiling.
One last mission. And then you go home.
Where's Bette?
- She left.
- What do you mean?
- Where did she go?
- She didn't say.
Well, where the hell could she be?
- Go, go!
On me.
I'm ready to give myself up.
Oh, I highly doubt that.
You think you can pull one over on me?
You can't.
Stand down, soldier.
I got back on the military feed.
Looks like they've gone to the waterfront
to rendezvous with Bette.
She's turning herself in.
She's not turning herself in.
Please, let him get to her in time.
All over the world, people are
plotting to destroy our country.
To end our lives.
Brave American soldiers
are gonna die in that fight,
but they don't have to.
Because of you, we could have victory.
All I've ever wanted was to
make the world a safer place.
And it will be when you're not in it.
Take cover!
What are you doing here?
Being a soldier doesn't
mean you're a murderer.
Don't become one now.
I'm sorry. I didn't see him.
Don't be. It's not your fault.
I'm glad you stopped me.
I'm gonna get you back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Barry, Dr. Wells. He... he...
Guys, we have a problem.
Is Bette okay?
No. Eiling killed her.
She's glowing. She's gonna detonate.
Oh, my God, a mass that size,
the explosion, it would be...
Devastating.
Barry, you have to get
her away from the city.
But there's no time.
Can I run on water?
I built up enough speed
to run up a building.
How fast do I need to go to run on water?
Assuming your weight...
450 pounds of force per
step for vertical suspension.
Accounting for fluid drag.
Approximately 650 miles an hour.
You have to outrun the
blast or you'll die too.
Nothing out of the ordinary occurred.
The military was simply conducting
an underwater weapons test.
There is no need for panic or alarm.
Central City is safe. I guarantee you.
He murdered Bette right in front of me.
And there's nothing we can do to him.
Powerful men have a way
of avoiding consequences.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
You can walk on water.
Puts you in pretty interesting company.
If you came to do laundry,
I already have a load in.
Uh, no. I-I came to talk.
I was working a case.
Someone I really thought
I could help befriend.
But they died.
Barry, I'm really sorry.
I didn't know her that
well. But it still hurts.
And as bad as I feel right now,
I know how much worse it is
to lose someone who's family.
Iris... Writing about this stuff,
putting your name out there,
it's dangerous.
So I'm asking you one
last time, please, stop.
And I am asking you one last time
to tell me what is
really going on with you.
Why am I the only one of
us who's interested in this?
I guess, just, all
this stuff with my family,
I finally just put it behind me.
I'm asking you to also.
That may have been how this started,
but it's about something
more than that for me now.
Whoever this streak is,
wherever he comes from,
I am not stopping until the rest
of the world believes in him.
Maybe we shouldn't see
each other for a while.
Yeah.
Can I get another club soda, please?
Hey.
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
We thought we should have a toast.
Doesn't work on me, remember?
Barry Allen, you of all people
should know that nothing is impossible.
I distilled a highly
fermented, potent suspension.
It's basically 500 proof.
I figured if anybody could use
a drink tonight, it was you.
So here's to Bette.
Bette.
Whoa, oh.
That hit too quick.
Are you buzzed?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm buzzed for sure.
Whoa. Whoa, that is good stuff.
And it's gone.
Work in progress.
For a guy who has experienced
his fair share of mysteries,
one mystery I still can't figure out
is why some people come into our lives.
Why some people go,
and others become a part of you.
Some friendships feel
like they'll last forever.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey.
There's dinner in the fridge.
Okay, thanks.
Iris, about your blog...
I don't want to talk about it, okay?
And others end far too soon.
Not every friendship is
meant to last a lifetime.
What does last forever is the
pain when that person is gone.
[Alarm sounds]
I was wrong about you, Harrison.
You're still one step ahead.
Impressive for a man
without the use of his legs.
I'm afraid I don't know what
you're talking about, Wade.
A girl who can
transform ordinary objects
into explosives with the touch of her hand.
Today I saw a man who can move
faster than the blink of an eye.
Extraordinary.
The night your particle accelerator died
was the night the impossible was born.
I think we should start working
together again, Harrison.
I think you should leave.
You know, I can have a
squadron of soldiers here
in minutes.
You know, I can have an
army of press here like that.
Believe me, General, I'd be more than happy
to testify to your involvement
in activities that were less than humane.
Threaten me again and I
will end you, General.
And I am not talking about your career.
You know, I figured out
your little secret, Wells.
Won't be long before the
public catches on as well.
This is everything we've
been working to achieve.
We may have the same goals,
General, but not the same means.
I will not have this project
end before it even begins.
And as long as he's on my premises,
I will not have him subjected
to that kind of cruelty anymore.
We're done.
We're done. General.
Get out.
Hey.
- It's okay.
- [Heavy breathing]
It's okay, boy.
- It's okay.
- [Snarling]
He's gone.
Don't you worry.
I have a whole different
future in mind for you.
Synced and Corrected by Nsiko
www.Addic7ed.com