I've fooled them. Job done.
So, how are things back at the Palace?
Fine, but guess
who's still living in my guest house?
Ooh, Bin Laden?
Yes, Osama.
Bin Laden flooding the bathroom
every time he showers...
And how hard is it to put a bath mat
down, Bin Laden?
Hey, do you remember
my favourite sports car?
You mean your Porsche?
Yes... the 911.
911, it's the best!
So I was driving my 911 near the
palace one day...
and I totally crashed!
It's ok, I've already ordered a new one.
A brand new 9112012.
You know, while you are here, you
should try to see some of the sights...
such as the Empire State Building...
and Yankee Stadium.
And I'd love to see the fireworks
over the Statue of Liberty.
Hey, have your old back problems been
bothering you?
It's been terrible! It got so bad that
I made myself a back brace.
- Really?
- Yes, look, I'm still wearing it.
Hey, my English is getting good...
I bet I can count down from five
faster than you can!
Five, four, three, two, one!