Do it!
I never got a chance
to say goodbye to Lenny.
You're the fucking reason he's dead.
You're the one who abandoned him.
You're a fucking monster.
It takes one to know one.
Hughie, you shot up
an untested drug from vought.
That was stupid and dangerous.
Annie.
I thought the drugs had fucked you up,
but this is all you.
Kimiko! No!
Nate!
You hurt my brother.
You're not gonna get away with it.
You think that soldier boy
is going after the rest of payback?
Why would he kill crimson countess?
He was your team leader.
Do you have any idea?
Anything?
You help me find the rest of my team,
and I'll help you with this homelander.
This is a bad idea.
Homelander helped make me
america's sweetheart.
Homelander is the worst of them.
He's gonna regret that.
A vnn special report.
A nation betrayed.
It's been five days, and still
nothing but lies from vought.
Soldier boy is still out there
and Maeve is still missing.
Miss Barrett, your reaction?
Once again, Maeve is in rehab.
And the soldier boy thing
really takes the cake.
He died in '84.
She is trying to incite a panic.
I wonder if starlight's actions
could be considered treason.
- Me, too.
- So, is starlight just hysterical?
Another woman scorned,
after homelanderjilted her?
Or is she trying to change the subject?
- From what?
- Her ties with this woman,
a known terrorist with the
shining light liberation army,
a notorious human trafficking ring.
Connect the dots, Cameron.
J" if you want to be happy j“
j” living a king's life j”
j" never make a pretty woman your wife j”
j" now, all you have to do
is just what I say j"
j" and then you may be jolly,
merry and gay j"
j” therefore, from a logical
point of view... j“
- what are you watching?
- Old mistakes.
J" uglier than you j”
j” from a logical... j”
I actually produced this piece of shit.
Between you and me,
soldier boy did to singing
what pantyhose did to finger-fucking.
Yeah.
- What'd he want?
- Um, well,
he wanted me to tell you
that you're out of astroglide.
Jesus Christ. You know,
I would say you fucks
are overstaying your welcome,
but what welcome?
I thought you
and soldier boy were friends.
Why, 'cause he forced
his way into my home?
Let me tell you something, kid.
I don't make friends with talent.
They're all the same.
- I mean, they're not all the same.
- Eh.
Come on, soldier boy was a hero, right?
I mean, he stormed normandy.
Yeah, he did. Two weeks after d-day.
For the photo op.
- So he didn't see any action?
- Not in Germany.
Sprayed a fire hose in Birmingham.
Some target practice at Kent state.
- There were rumors about dealey Plaza.
- Wait, what?
Yeah, and they call 'em
the "good old days."
The thing is, to be American
means knowing you're the hero.
So what do we do? We sweep
all our filthy shit under the rug
and we tell ourselves
a myth like soldier boy.
And I get stinking rich selling it.
There you are.
Oh, fuck me. Is he still at it?
J' and I can't fight j“
j” this feeling anymore... j“
You got a minute?
Oh, good. Lube? Huh?
Come on, I can't go in raw.
Please don't make eye contact.
Hughie, listen, these women,
they're like fine wine.
Okay, the older they get,
the more delicious, but the drier.
Mary, Lucille, come on, chop-chop.
Break time's over.
That shag's not gonna vacuum itself.
Come on.
What's the problem?
What's the problem? First of all,
I can never fire
those girls now, thank you.
And second of all,
this bed has seen two jaclyns.
You know that? Smith and bisset.
Y-You're treating it like a Reno cathouse.
- Jesus.
- The problem
is you gave me 11
of mindstorm's last-knowns.
So far, I've had a look at three
and found fuck all.
I-I'm chasing me fucking tail here, mate.
Sounds like that's three down
and eight to go.
Yeah, and that's gonna take weeks,
and weeks I don't got.
Egyptian cotton sheets and now,
I got to fucking burn 'em.
The deal was, we get the rest of my team,
- then we get homelander.
- And what I'm saying,
is I could use an hand figuring it out.
I told you. Mindstorm's a paranoid fuck.
But, hell, if you could hear everybody's
shitty thoughts, you'd be, too.
Look, he bought up all these
run-down cabins all over the place.
He's Howard Hughes without the piss jars.
He's batshit crazy.
Mindstorm's not crazy. He's bipolar.
- He's bipolar?
- Yeah.
Does he take meds for it?
I believe so. At least he did.
Girls, it smells like sex
and bengay in here.
Lithium prescriptions aren't that common.
I mean, I doubt he's making it. Maybe...
I-If we look at the cabins and we...
And then check the local pharmacies.
Yeah.
See who's handing out lithium.
Nice one, hughie.
We're gonna need more reefer.
J” thought I might j“
j” and I can't fight
this feeling anymore j”
hey. How you doing?
Look, i-I'm sorry about all this.
I wish I could say you get used to it,
but you never do.
So, where are they hiding?
Butcher and soldier boy.
Where are they?
Wait, is...
Is that concealer?
Do you have a bruise?
Yeah...
Do you have any idea
what you've set loose?
Butcher has powers.
I assume thanks to you.
They've killed crimson countess
and seven other heroes, Maeve, seven.
The ones that-that survived are done,
they're powerless.
Soldier boy fried the v
right out of their blood somehow.
Maeve, do you understand,
that could happen to any one of us.
Yeah.
That's the difference between you and me.
You need to be a supe.
I can't wait till it's over.
Maeve...
Why are you letting me live?
Maeve.
You know, back when things were, uh,
better between us...
I used to dream of having kids with you.
- Oh.
- No, I did.
A family. Nesting, you know.
I-I mean, can you imagine
how perfect our kids would be?
Sublime.
Twice as strong as Ryan.
No kid of mine would ever know
a room like this, I'll tell you that.
Just so you know,
I'll fucking shatter whatever
you try to stick up there.
Maeve! Don't be so crass.
We're not savages.
I respect what you are, even if you don't.
I would never force myself on you.
But I am gonna harvest your eggs.
That way,
if, god forbid, you do die,
whether by accident or choice,
you'll die knowing
that the very best of you carries on.
With me.
See, Maeve, I'm not letting you live.
I'm keeping you alive.
This is still a top-three day in my life.
Because today is the day I saw you scared.
The hell happened to you two?
- It is but trivial.
- Trivial, my ass.
Y'all look like y'all got hit by a truck.
Oh, my god,
you shouldn't even be on your feet.
Come here, come here. Come on.
Yeah, um, we're just gonna
go lie down for a minute.
Okay? Come on.
She insisted when you called, right?
Butcher is everyone's problem now.
We're here to help.
Frenchie, are you high?
Well, that goes without saying.
Okay, satellite view has mindstorm's place
about two miles in, due west.
Two miles?
Fuck me.
We could've parked closer.
So, do you mind telling us
what we're walking into here?
All you got to know is,
if he tries to make eye contact
with you, close your eyes.
Or what?
Just don't make eye contact with him,
then you got nothing to worry about.
Hey, why do you keep buying him,
like, hefty bags full of weed?
Better high than mental.
Takes the edge off his PTSD.
Wait, he has PTSD?
Yeah, I saw it at herogasm.
It's why he keeps blowing
the fuck out of everything.
We got to keep that cunt dozy as a lamb.
So, just to recap, uh, he's radioactive,
highly traumatized
and heavily self-medicated.
Feels good, feels right.
Tell me about it.
I mean, what sad bastard
self-medicates like that, eh?
Earving, sooner or later,
you're gonna have to t-t-talk about it.
Remember when you were nine,
a-and you hid in that ball pit
right over there,
after you p-p-p-paralyzed Lewis frankel?
This is just like that.
You can't hide from soldier boy.
We're your best pals, aren't we?
We got you through that erection
in the seventh grade,
that hard rock cafe m-m-massacre in Lagos.
And by golly,
we'll get you through this, too.
- That's right.
- You're our friend.
What'd you say?
- W hat?
Nothing, mate. No one said nothing.
Hey, hey. Uh, your... your brain's leaking.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is this shite?
Mum.
Oi, mum.
Fucking mindstorm.
Knock it off, you little fucking freak.
Come on.
Butcher, wake up. Wake up!
Fucking freak slipped away.
- He's gonna pick us off one by one.
- Butcher, wake up.
Wake up, butcher. Butcher! Wake up!
No, you're wasting your time, he's gone.
- What did mindstorm do?
- Well, if it's his usual mo,
trapped him in an endless nightmare
till he dies of terminal dehydration.
No, there's got to be a way
we can wake him up.
Mindstorm put him into this.
He can snap him out.
- Okay, great, great. Uh...
- But he's about to be dead.
Wait, wait, just hang on.
If we, if we, if we grab mindstorm,
- we make him help butcher...
- No way.
And then you can kill him.
Then you can go to town on him, man.
I don't give a fuck.
Hey. If you're gonna act hysterical,
I'm gonna slap you like I'm Connery.
Now, unless you want to end up
like your friend there,
it ain't worth the risk.
Look, chin up, okay? Deal's a deal.
You help me finish this,
I'll kill homelander.
Butcher would have given up his life
for that in a heartbeat.
So, we doing this or not?
Leave it. We got to move fast.
Do you hear that?
Uh... You might
want to lay off the weed, huh?
And you might want to gargle my ball sack.
Where is she?
Lenny! Where the fuck's Lenny?
Shit. Come on.
Left his bloody bike
in the garden again.
Lenny!
Lenny?
Billy?
Leave off 'em, you cunt.
Gotcha.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
Where is he?
Who?
Don't fuck me about. Where is he?
Fucking snotty little cunt.
Lenny, i-it's okay.
Jesus. I thought you quit.
The lord hates quitters.
Is that halothane?
I chucked some at him at herogasm.
The motherfucker didn't even flinch.
It will be the greatest sorrow of my life
that I missed herogasm.
But no, this is not halothane.
- You see the texture?
- Mmm.
- It's all wrong.
- What is it, then?
Well, let's find out.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
It's just, uh, UN peu kétamine.
It's okay. You know, the...
Frenchie, you're a fucking mess.
Well, that makes two of us.
-J' will and what will be j“
-okay, sorry.
J" she's a maniac j“
j" maniac on the floor... j“
okay. Should be good.
Is there anything else that you need?
Are you hungry?
J“ she's a maniac, maniac j“
Oh. Kirkland.
A fine choice. Yeah.
Oh. When you grow up in Iowa,
there is not much else to do.
Here.
Mmm.
Ooh.
When did you have your first drink?
Right now?
Oh, my god, wow.
Okay, um...
Okay, well, cheers to that.
I tried.
He doesn't want to be saved.
With what?
What about it?
You want me to...
Kimiko, uh, hang on, hang on,
hang on, hang on. Hang on.
The...
You know that I can't go to the tower.
Even if I could,
this would be such a bad idea.
No, but you don't know
if it'll do that again.
I mean, you could get yourself killed.
I won't do it. I'm sorry, I can't.
I can't.
Still can't believe this shit is legal.
I locked up so many assholes
for it back in the day.
What the fuck did you say?
Uh, uh, literally nothing.
- Jesus. How hard?
- What?
How hard did butcher suck your dick
that you miss him that much?
Hmm? His mouth must feel
like a hoover deluxe.
God, every single thing
you say is so gross.
He saved me, okay?
More than once.
- So I owe him.
- Oh, bullshit.
You're on a mission. You get the job done.
Okay? I stormed normandy.
I fought the Nazis.
You want to know what I do when I'm sad
or scared?
Fucking nothing.
'Cause I'm not a fucking pussy.
You didn't storm shit.
Your whole Marlboro man act?
It's fucking crap.
And I... oh...
I warned you.
J“ saying I love you... j“
Oh, hi.
Babe.
Why don't you put that work shit down,
get that little butt over here.
What is the occasion?
Well, not a big deal.
Just, uh, found out I'm gonna be
on hannity tonight.
- Hannity, babe.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- Uh, when-when do you tape?
- We need to prep.
- No, no, no, no, babe. Don't worry.
I got it. I got it. Trust me.
- This is a big deal, Kevin.
- I know.
- Okay? So we need to go over everything.
- Okay, hey.
I got us this far, didn't I?
Y-you got us this far?
Just relax a little bit.
Turn around.
Come here. Just...
- Get into the moment.
- Okay.
But listen, I've been wanting
to talk to you about something.
You know that I love you.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I know that you love me, too.
But we both know that our marriage...
Sex life has gotten a little vanilla.
So maybe...
It's time we branch out.
- Branch out?
- Yeah. Like, um,
you know, uh, introduce a new partner.
Just to spice things up a little bit.
Well, is there anyone you had in mind?
Well, I'd like to introduce you
to someone.
Oh. Okay.
J“ then you couldn't make things new... j“
babe, this is ambrosius.
She's very pretty,
and she thinks you're superhot.
I, um...
I don't want to, uh, do that.
Cassandra, I need this.
J“ more than words j“
oh, fuck.
Ooh.
Hey there.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Ambrosius says she wants to taste you.
No. No. Okay, I can't.
I'm out. I'm out. No.
I'm-I'm done. I'm done.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Honey, are you okay? What's wrong?
- You want me to fuck a-a fucking fish!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
One, she's a mollusk.
Two, she has feelings.
It's okay.
How long have you been fucking it
behind my back?
Okay, it's not an "it." It's a "her."
Get your pronouns right.
I have given up a year of my life for you.
I gave up my tenure at vassar.
I-I propped you up.
I've steered your comeback. And this?
This is how you repay me?
You propped me up, huh?
Right, you wrote a few lines.
- I'm the one who had to fucking sell it.
- Okay.
Okay, let's, um...
Let's see how well you do without me.
I'll be great without you.
Without you over-noting me
all the fucking time.
You're an idiot, Kevin.
Then why did Dave eggers say
I have a formidable intellect, huh?
Formidable intellect!
God. No, she's...
She just needs time to cool off, babe.
Come on, earving.
Me and the others have
something to sh-sh-sh-show you.
C-c-c-come on!
Something you pushed
d-d-d-deep, deep down.
Lighten up, gunpowder.
I'm just playing ar...
You fucking pussy.
You're late. We started at 3:00.
I really wanted that movie.
- The hell are you talking about?
- I just got off the phone with my manager.
It's a no-go on Beverly Hills cop.
- Oh. That.
- I was...
I was born to play Axel Foley.
Why would you say
all those horrible things about me
to Don Simpson?
- Jesus, Ben, really?
- Zip it, cooze.
The guy's supposed to be funny.
You're not funny.
- Well, I could've been.
- You're not good enough.
Now shut your cockhole and get to work.
But-but wait.
- Stop it!
- Take it easy.
- Stop it. You're hurting him.
- Take it easy. Calm down.
- For god's sake, dude.
- Take it easy. Take it easy.
- Guys. Guys, leave him, leave him alone.
- Don'...Get off.
- Get him off him.
- That's enough.
- Get off of him.
- That's enough!
- Hey, now.
- Come on. That's enough!
Which one of you wants next? Huh?
Thought so.
You think you can be me?
You're not a movie star.
You're not shit.
I see you getting out of line again,
trying to move on up,
I will put you in the fucking ground.
Understood?
Please don't tell my old man.
You were
selling marijuana, William.
You know I have to tell him.
And we both know your dad.
You're a smart boy.
I'd just hate for you to...
Turn out like him.
- Fucking snotty little cunt!
- Please stop! Please!
Butch, what are you doing? Stop!
Fuck, Lenny. I-I didn't mean to. I...
I-I'm-I'm sorry. I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
The world's an ocean of shite, lads.
- You either sink...
- Or you swim.
Today, Billy, my boy, you swam.
Some cunts need a slap.
Don't they?
Here.
Oi. You ought to take a page
out of his book.
You don't want to be
a fucking little poof all your life.
Don't you listen to him.
Don't you listen
to that worthless lump of shite.
Not a bleeding word.
Maybe we should walk back
to that town we saw.
It was five miles away.
It'll take forever to get there.
We're never gonna get to the retreat now.
Oh! Oh, you startled me.
Son, are-are you a superhero?
Yes, father. You folks need some help?
- Yes. Yes, please.
- Okay, well, it's not safe.
There's a fugitive in the area.
You should get out of here
before you get hurt.
Uh, well, we can't.
I don't suppose
either of you know engines?
I'll have a look.
Oh, I'd appreciate that very much.
Uh, so, where you guys headed?
We're just on our way
to a samaritan's embrace retreat
over there in danville.
Oh! Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! What the fuck?
This is mindstorm's mo.
He brainwashed them.
That priest was gonna shank us.
And she will, too.
- Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Father Wallace, no!
Hey, hey, she doesn't
look brainwashed to me.
Take my word for it.
Everyone's coming for us.
- Everyone, every day.
- Whoa, no! No, no!
You have PTSD!
You have PTSD,
and you are super fucking stoned.
All right? Maybe this isn't
what you think it is.
- Move. Move!
- She's a human being. A nun.
And if there's one thing I know...
Die, you fucking cocksuckers!
Oh, my god! Do something!
- If you stay still, I...
- Fuck you! Get her off me!
Oh! Fuck me!
No! Hard pass on this exorcist shit!
What's black and white and red all over?
Okay, first off, I don't have shell shock.
Fuck you.
Second, this is what I'm talking about.
This is being a soldier.
Come on.
It's been five days,
and still nothing but lies from vought.
Soldier boy is still out there,
and Maeve is still missing.
And you know what?
More people are just going to die
until they admit to what's going on.
So, I guess
you've all heard about starlight's
"alleged" involvement
with a human trafficking ring?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
And I suppose it's "pure coincidence"
that, uh, she opened starlight house
for runaway teens.
Huh? Come on, we can put
two and two together, can't we?
What the holy fuck
does he think he's doing?
Those poor kids.
They pass through her doors,
they disappear.
They are never seen again. It's horrific.
But we got to face the truth, people,
no matter how ugly it is.
Starlight is a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Plain and simple. She fooled me.
She fooled you. She fooled all of us.
Right? Now she wants to take me down. Why?
Because with me out of the way,
there is no one who can stop her.
No one, and she knows it.
- No chance.
- Exactly.
Do you think the media,
our buddies over here...
Do you think the media
is gonna report on that?
No, no, no, no, no. Of course not.
Ah. Tell you what. You guys, love you!
All right!
And vote for Bob singer.
He's, uh, he's... great.
Let's hear it for homelander.
J“ ah j“
j“ now I don't hardly know her j“
j“ crimson and clover j“
j'ahj'
j“ I wish she 'd come walking over j“
j“ now I've been waiting to show j“
skip breakfast, did we?
Nope.
Nope. Uh...
She's in pain, so I tried to help.
Look, I'm gonna tell you the truth here
because no one else will.
Pull your shit together,
admit it's soldier boy
and take control of the situation.
You think, uh, I'm not in control?
No. I think you just spent the last
20 minutes ranting about starlight
instead of talking up
the next president of the United States.
You're homelander.
Button your shit up. You're flailing.
This whole fucking scene
right here. Jesus Christ...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Go on, please.
You need someone you can trust.
- Someone like you?
- I got rid of Edgar for you.
That cost me a lot.
I'm proposing a strictly
transactional relationship.
You help me out with one small favor,
and I help you.
Where did you get this?
You're awake. Fantastic.
What happened?
Pretty fucking nuts, man.
I mean, how soldier boy attacked you
and blue hawk at herogasm.
Yeah.
Soldier boy murdered blue hawk
right in front of you.
You tried to save blue hawk,
of course, but...
Must've been awful for you.
Yeah.
It seemed like you two were on your way
to a healing place,
which is why you're gonna love this.
Blue hawk will live on
because we gave you his heart.
A super-abled heart.
No more heart disease.
You're gonna get to run again.
Can I get a "what-what"?
Look, you'll need insane amounts of rehab,
but luckily, you heal fast, bro.
That's...
We're gonna get you back in your old suit.
We're gonna get you out there asap.
You're okay talking shit about starlight?
- Yeah, sure. Why?
- Oh, amazing.
Oh, my god, I almost forgot.
We are already
working on your new movie.
Training a-train.
Gritty biopic.
You're a roughneck gangbanger
from the south side slanging that yayo
when a track coach...
We're thinking Tom Hanks...
Teaches you a more civilized way.
That's not at all how that happened.
My brother's my coach.
We're out to sir Julian
fellowes to write, so...
- No. I'm not doing that.
- You're gonna love it.
Anyway, I got to bounce.
But the a-train's back, baby!
- Right?
- Uh...
That's your...
Okay.
Senator bishop, will you confirm
you're about to join the ticket
as the vice presidential candidate?
Well, if! Was lucky enough to be
so honored, you'll be the first to know.
And now,
if you will all excuse us,
I want to get a deep-fried twinkie
before my wife finds out.
It's not a gas.
- W hat?
- It's vapor.
Vapor. Vapor. Just a delivery system.
- This.
- You think I can read this shit?
Novichok.
Russian nerve agent.
Expose you or moi to novichok,
our nervous system shuts down.
Multiple organs fail. Painful death.
But for soldier boy, it's a nap.
All right. So where can we get some?
Another vacation to Russia?
Motherfucker.
Huh? Qu'est-ce que c'est?
No clue.
You're still hurt.
I'm still high.
J“ stars shining bright above you j“
j“ night breezes j“
j“ seem to whisper "I love you" j“
j“ birds singing in a sycamore tree j“
j“ dream a little dream of me j“
j“ say nighty night and kiss me j“
j“ just hold me tight
and tell me you'll miss me j“
j“ while I'm alone and blue as can be j“
none taken.
J“ dream a little dream of me j“
j“ stars fading j“
j“ but I linger on, dear j“
j“ still craving your kiss j“
j“ I'm longing j“
what do you mean?
J“ to linger till dawn, dearj“
j“ just saying this... j“
why? This is everything
you said you did not want.
No. Listen to me. Listen to me.
You can walk away. You and me.
We go together to Marseille.
Your freedom, your humanité.
You have it. Mon coeur, please.
Si! Te plait, don't do this.
"Annie.
I know I'm asking a lot.
At first I hated the v
because I didn't choose it.
But now it's my choice.
I think that matters.
I blamed my powers for my problems.
But it's not true.
The v isn't good or bad.
It just depends on the person using it.
I wanted to use my powers to do good.
To fight for the ones I love.
I almost lost frenchie
because I couldn't fight.
I can't risk that again."
Oui.
Oh, my god.
Jesus Christ.
By 1984, things had gotten so bad.
There was only so much m-m-more
of soldier boy's abuse you could take.
So when st-st-Stan Edgar
made you an offer in Nicaragua,
you jumped at it.
Vought's really okay with this?
Sometimes, old soldiers just fade away.
I don't want the details.
- Just do what you need to do.
- Why now?
Vogelbaum has a replacement.
Just a child,
but they're convinced
he'll be stronger than soldier boy.
And he can fly.
- Will the others go along?
- Everyone but gunpowder.
Good luck, earving.
Can you please stop eating those
in front of me? I'm allergic.
What the fuck is this?
Something we should've done
a long time ago, you piece of shit.
Tnt detonate!
Hold him down.
Fucking piece of shit.
Get him, mindstorm.
- Scramble his fucking brains.
- No!
Fuck you, motherfucker.
This is some tough stuff, I know.
But when you gave him to the Russians,
you knew soldier boy
would come back one day.
You need to f-f-f-face him.
No one really knows you.
But we know how s-sensitive
- and s-s-scared you are.
- Yes.
- Hey, we got your back.
- We're here for you.
It's okay.
Bravery isn't having no fear.
Bravery is having fear,
but you d-d-d-do it anyway.
Time to finish what you started.
- Get the fuck out the car.
- What's wrong?
You heard me.
- Daddy?
- Hey, baby.
I need you to go
inside the house with your mama.
Daddy needs to talk to Todd alone.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Marvin, what are you doing here?
- You're okay with this?
- What?
- He took her
- to a homelander rally.
- Yeah, so?
Excuse me. You took her where?
- It's fine.
- No, it is not fine. You didn't ask me.
Janine. Come on. Inside, honey.
Everything's fine. Just relax.
Don't tell me to relax, Todd.
Soldier boy is out there
gunning for homelander.
Do you have any idea
what kind of danger
you put my baby girl in?
There's no danger.
Starlight is making all that up.
Read any news
outside the establishment media.
Todd, Todd, they're lying.
- Really? All of them?
- All of them.
Homelander is lying to you.
- He's a fucking psychopath.
- Worse than starlight?
She's trafficking kids
the same age as Janine,
as the... as the kids in my classroom.
Homelander is the only one
protecting them.
Okay, you guys. That's enough.
Homelander ain't protecting shit,
all right?
He's feeding you this insane fairy tale,
and you're too fucking stupid
and-and brainwashed to fucking see it!
- Hey, fuck you.
- Both of you, stop.
You know what?
If you want to risk your life, fine.
Have at it.
But not with my baby girl.
You're not her father.
Someone's got to be.
.Marvin!
Oh, my god, Todd.
Todd. Oh, my god, Todd.
Todd. Todd. Open your eyes. Wake up.
Here she is.
Did you think I wouldn't know
the second you walked through the door?
Well, we broke up.
It was time to pack my shit and go.
Okay.
So, here's what happens now.
You're gonna march into vnn studios,
and you're gonna recant
everything you said.
It was a tragic cocktail
of heartbreak, Zoloft and despair.
You regret any harm that your lies
have caused vought or me,
but me in particular.
- Mmm. Okay.
- Good.
Okay. But, um,
you want to hear my counter?
I stop soldier boy
before he murders more people,
and I find Maeve.
If she's still alive.
Maeve's just learning her manners.
And you should do the same.
Seriously, before you throw away
everything you've worked so hard for.
- Hmm?
- You know what? I could give a shit.
Really? You sure about that?
Your fame is the only thing
protecting you.
Here's the thing.
I'm not scared of you anymore.
I'm not. I see who you are.
I see how small you are.
I saw it.
I saw it the night
that you killed supersonic.
You know what I remember from that night?
I remember what I told you
would happen to hughie.
You walk, that's next.
Good luck with that.
Now that you've told
my 190 million followers.
I'm still pretty famous.
Hey, everybody!
Oh, that's me.
I got to go.
Starlight, uh, wait.
You're not supposed to record us
when we're running lines.
Shit!
- What the hell?
- Okay, wait! Wait.
- Why the fuck am I naked?
- I can explain, okay?
You're with soldier boy.
- You're trying to fucking kill me.
- No!
- No. No, I just saved your life.
- Leave me alone!
Please, calm down.
I only want to talk, okay? Just talk.
I'm not bothering anyone.
I'm just trying to get away
from all the fucking voices.
from the voices.
I'm just trying to get away
from the voices!
Hey, hey. I'm gonna
open my eyes, all right?
Please don't coma me.
Okay. Hey. We're cool.
Very chill. Very cool.
Also, we-we don't have to do this naked.
All right?
Just-just clothes. They're clothes.
I'm gonna reach in.
I'm gonna grab you some, okay?
Look. Look, hey, I don't want to be here.
H was pretending to be someone I'm not.
I'm not like soldier boy.
That guy's full of shit.
I mean, no one is that tough, and then...
And the people who say they are?
They're lying.
And I'm... I'm done.
I want to go home.
So, I'm just... I'm begging you...
To please wake up my friend.
I've been inside his head.
- That guy's a piece of shit.
- It doesn't matter.
I-I don't want to be someone
who leaves people behind.
I want to be someone who saves his family.
And for better or worse...
He's family.
- Please wake him up.
- No.
- No way.
- I can get you out of here.
If you just please, please wake him up,
I'll teleport you away.
You'll be safe away from everyone,
including soldier boy.
I'll take you wherever you want to go.
And I will never tell a soul
where that is.
Hand to god.
No. Not here.
So, that's it then, Billy?
Jesus, Lenny.
Just gonna piss off,
no goodbye or nothing like that?
I'll be back Christmas, once I got
everything sorted at the barracks,
you can maybe come out and see me.
Billy. Please don't leave me
alone with him.
I can't hack it.
You'll be all right.
No, he won't. Fucking listen to him.
If I stay, I'm gonna end up killing him,
get sent off to borstal, or prison,
and what's that gonna do to mum, hmm?
Break her bloody heart, is what it'd do.
Besides, the old cunt hates me the most,
so maybe if I'm gone, he'll leave you be.
You stupid fucking twat.
Don't you leave him.
I got to go, len.
- Billy, please.
- Leave off.
For fuck's sake, Lenny,
it ain't my job to look after you.
Don't be such a fucking poof
all your life.
Right.
Please, don't go.
You served me up to him on a plate.
No, I... I didn't.
I-I wouldn't.
It's been six months,
and you come home to check on me
not once.
Len, i-I'm sorry, but they...
They just wouldn't let me out
of the barracks.
Oh, Jesus, please. Please, fuck, no.
He's beating the living shit
out of me, Billy.
Day in and day out.
- I can't take no more.
- Please, len, don't.
You fucking knew what he'd do.
It's your fault.
No, don't say that.
That's... that's not true.
I... I'm not that bastard.
Come off it, Billy. You always have been.
'Cause anyone who's ever loved you,
you end up getting them killed, don't you?
Me. Becca.
Now, hughie,
the last person on god's green earth
trying to stop you from being a monster,
and what do you do?
Drag him down to your level.
When he dies, and he will,
then no one can stop you.
Can they?
No!
-Lenny, no! {Gunshofl
I'm sorry. I'm so fucking sorry!
Sorry for what?
- Hughie.
- It's okay, butcher.
It's okay. You're all right.
Here. You're okay.
Hey, kid.
Right, right, yeah.
Okay. Deal's a deal.
Where we headed?
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Hiya, Dan.
It's-it's not what you think.
It wasn't my idea.
Oh, I know. It was noir's,
but how does that work, huh?
'Cause no way he makes a fucking move
without vought.
- They gave him the green light.
- Why would they do that?
What? That's impossible.
What'd he say?
Hello?
- I need to talk to hughie. Where is he?
- Oh, starlight.
How delightful.
He's just popped out for a bit.
Okay, well, he's not answering his phone.
Bit hard to keep a phone when
you're teleporting all day, innit, love?
- How can I help?
- Temp v is gonna kill you both.
Well, it's gonna have to join the queue.
I was just in the lab. It causes lesions.
Okay? It turns your brain
into fucking Swiss cheese,
so, please, be honest with me,
and tell me how many doses have you taken?
- Just a couple.
- Jesus Christ.
Butcher, three to five doses kills you.
You need to tell hughie.
Yeah, yeah. I will, I will. I promise.
Okay, but I'm calling back
every five minutes until...
Butcher?
Goddamn it.
Okay.
Hi. Only thing open
was long John silver's,
so, I guess that's kind of
fish and chips, right?
Yeah.
- Nice one.
- Everything all right?
It's, uh...
- It's the temp v.
- What about it?
We got to swing by the office
and get some more.
And then you, me,
and granny fucker are gonna
finish this fucking job.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
- Your call has been fon/varded...
- Fuck.
Do you think monsieur charcutier
will tell hughie?
Do you?
I'm gonna save hughie,
even if he doesn't want me to.
Ready, mon coeur?
Enjoy them
before they feel like bendy straws again.
Mon coeur?
Obviously, I didn't realize
the little bitch was recording me, did I?
No, no. A...
Ashley, I don't fucking care.
You're the spin doctor,
go fucking spin it.
What?
Sir, I apologize for disturbing you...
But you have a call.
He says he's...
Well, he's claiming to be soldier boy.
Put him through.
This really you?
The situation's changed.
I thought we should have a conversation.
I don't know who the fuck
you think you are,
but you got lucky once
because you fucking ambushed me.
Fall 1980,
I get called into vogelbaum's lab
for an experiment,
some shit about genetics.
I still remember the penthouse I used.
June.
Danielle deneux, bush like a pomeranian.
- What?
- I beat my meat into a cup.
Turns out...
Vogelbaum made a kid.
Born spring 1981.
A boy.
You know what the bitch of it is?
If they'd have just kept me around,
I 'd have let you take the spotlight.
What father wouldn't want that
for his son?