[EMMIT FENN'S "CLOSER TO YOU"]
♪ Don't know what to
say I'm doing fine ♪
♪ But I'm not okay ♪
♪
♪ Still hear your voice
all on my phone every day ♪
♪
♪ And I don't like how
you left that day ♪
♪
♪ Your mother cried ♪
♪ She had nothing to say ♪
♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You left your heart in my hand ♪
♪ It's almost like you never left ♪
♪
♪ And it brings me closer ♪
♪ Yeah, closer ♪
♪ Yeah, closer to you ♪
♪ Closer, yeah, closer ♪
Clear!
♪ Yeah, closer ♪
♪ Yeah, closer to you ♪
♪ And it brings me closer,
yeah, closer to you ♪
[ALARM BLARING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SIREN WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Freeze! Put your hands in the air!
[GRUNTS]
Well, hello, officers.
[SUIT HISSING, WHIRRING]
♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Now, that was fun.
♪
I am so not in the mood for this.
[PANTING] All right, big guy.
I'm gonna give you one
chance to stand down.
I'll give you one chance to beat it.
Chester, what's he wearing?
Chester?
Sorry.
Just give me a second to, um...
okay, okay, I got it.
The armor matches the description
of an exo-suit stolen from Ivo Labs.
It's charged by amplifying
the wearer's biochemistry,
so everything from his movements
to even his emotions...
Are fuel that makes him stronger.
You should've run away when
you had the chance, Flash.
Now this has to happen! [GRUNTS]
[RUMBLING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
There's a lot of people in there.
Okay Flash, he just compromised
two steel girders in that substructure.
That building's gonna collapse.
Allegra, Cecile, I'm
gonna use my lightning
to weld those girders back together.
Take this guy down.
Okay, let's do a classic
corral and contain.
Allegra, charge up and
hit him with a UV burst.
Hey, Snow Pants!
Over here.
And then Frost, you swoop in to...
♪
[GRUNTS]
- Allegra!
- The blast knocked her out.
But she's still breathing.
Guys, I'm... I am so sorry...
Chester, I need you to focus.
You gotta help me figure out
how I'm gonna stop this guy.
Your friend should learn how to aim.
If you can try to calm his emotions,
that could de-power the suit.
You trying to mess with my head?
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [SCREAMS]
What just happened?
It's all of my grief from Frost...
and all the panic inside the building.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
I can't take it! It's overloading me!
I can't use my powers!
Pathetic. Worst heroes ever.
♪
[GASPING]
Okay, okay.
- You guys okay?
- Yeah.
- Chester, where'd he go?
- I don't know.
He just vanished.
♪
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
[NOTIFICATION CHIMES, PHONE BUZZES]
♪
CCC tip line still has
nothing on Mark Desmond,
AKA Blockbuster.
Keep digging, please.
Chester says his suit has
some kind of cloaking tech
we can't track, which means
we're not gonna see him again.
Until he attacks.
And when he does...
♪
Iris, we can't go back
out there like this.
I mean, we should have
easily stopped Desmond,
but Allegra and Cecile
were almost killed.
We're all still pretty
messed up about Frost.
I think with any normal job,
we would take time off to grieve.
But with Team Flash...
This isn't a normal job.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Iris, how am I supposed to tell people
who just lost a family member
they need to find a way to mourn
and still get the job done?
I don't know.
♪
But if there's anyone who
can find the right words
to inspire us right now, it's you.
♪
Thanks for taking the time
for this meeting, guys.
Yeah, we realize it's a crazy
time with everything going on.
Of course. Yeah, we...
We need to be together,
now more than ever.
- Speaking of, where's Caitlin?
- I didn't want to bother her.
I think she's preparing
for the funeral tomorrow.
Maybe we should do the same thing.
Look, while your satellite
is looking for Desmond,
Kramer put out an APB,
and she's got a unit placed
at every bank in town.
Luckily, we have the
time to take a break.
In a perfect world,
it'd be great to take some time off.
God knows we all need it,
but at any moment, we
could face something worse.
And whether we like it or not,
we're this city's first line of defense.
We all saw what happened out there.
If it had been Bloodwork or Despero?
Frost is gone.
And we all need to mourn her,
but we also need to find
a way to protect this city.
Didn't realize we were
having a team meeting.
♪
We figured you might
need some alone time.
It's fine.
I haven't been sleeping very much,
so I could use the distraction.
Are you sure? I mean, I know
you must be dealing with a lot.
And I know how hard it can
be to organize a funeral.
Actually, my mom is handling
all the arrangements.
Okay. I mean, if that's what you want,
but we're all happy to pitch in...
Like I said, my mom's got it covered.
But if you've got a problem with that,
feel free to give her
a call, offer your help.
'Cause I'm not going
to any damn funeral.
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Caitlin...
- Bar.
- Give her some space.
- Dad, she's hurting.
Baby girl, I know. We all are.
♪
But like Barry said...
we just lost a family member,
and that pain will keep us
from protecting those in need.
It will cloud everything we do
until we face it and heal.
Yeah, but how are we
supposed to do that?
By honoring Frost.
Look, I just...
took watercolor classes
at the community center
because Frost made me promise
that I would try to
express myself through art.
And I got to admit, when
I saw the first canvas...
♪
I felt Frost smiling down on me.
And we all have to find
our own ways to honor her,
'cause it is the only way
we are going to heal as a family.
♪
[SOFT MUSIC]
There's still zero hits on
the tip line about Blockbuster.
It's already tough knowing
that people almost died
because we weren't ready to face him,
but knowing that he could
reappear at any moment,
it makes what we're going
through that much harder.
I know.
Which reminds me,
I think I've decided how
I'm gonna take Joe's
advice and honor Frost.
After her court battle last year,
wrongly imprisoned metas,
that became a cause
really close to her heart.
So effective immediately,
I'm gonna dedicate 25% of
my caseload to pro bono work
in her honor.
- Frost would love that.
- Yeah?
I'm gonna write a special
obituary for her on CCC.
That's a great idea.
Yeah, but every time
I sit down to write it,
I can't,
because...
I mean, to write about
her in any meaningful way,
like how she died
saving her sister, I...
[WHISPERS] You risk exposing yourself
- as a member of Team Flash.
- Yeah.
But this is my job, so
why can't I push through?
♪
Hey, Aariz.
When you interviewed last year,
you mentioned writing obits once?
For "Stars and Stripes."
When I was on active duty
with the Army in Afghanistan,
sometimes I'd help write
obits for soldiers who died
on classified missions or had no family.
If I wasn't privy to all the details,
I'd find other ways
to honor their memory.
That's amazing.
Do you think that you
could take over Frost's obit
for tonight's headline?
I always admired
how she handled those
ridiculous charges against her.
I could have it ready in, say, an hour?
Yeah, that would be great. Thank you.
You got it.
[WHISPERS] Hey, Iris.
Honey, are you sure you
want to hand over something
so personal to somebody
who never even met Frost?
Well, I think an objective point of view
is exactly what I'm missing.
♪
So does it do her justice?
Well...
You think Aariz did a terrible job?
It's well written and
factually accurate,
but it feels cold.
Like it was written by
someone who didn't know Frost.
But that's not why I wanted to talk.
I could have read this over email.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
I wanted to see how you're doing.
♪
[SIGHS]
I feel the same way.
♪
Iris, why didn't you write this?
I mean, you've known
Frost longer than I have.
I guess at first, I felt like if I...
wrote it, I wouldn't be able to say
everything that I wanted to say.
But the more I think about
it, the more I realize that...
I don't know what to say.
♪
Carla, I may have known
Frost longer, but I didn't...
get to know her.
And now you're angry at
yourself for lost opportunities
because you thought you had
all the time in the world.
♪
I felt the same way,
being estranged from
Caitlin for so long,
and then I almost made the same mistake
when Frost came around, but... [CHUCKLES]
Luckily for me, she didn't let me.
♪
And in the end, I got
to know her just a bit.
And I'm... I'm better for it.
♪
So what do I do now?
Well, here's one thing I do know.
Frost wouldn't care about some
obituary that sung her praises.
She didn't give a damn
what people thought.
She just wanted to protect them.
That was her legacy.
[SOFTLY] Yeah.
[SOFT MUSIC]
Thank you, Carla.
♪
- I think I know what to do now.
- Okay.
♪
Thanks.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
♪
Oh, excuse me. Could
I get that iced drink?
- The "Frost"?
- Sure.
But it's actually called "Killer Frost."
♪
Well, it shouldn't be.
Never mind. Thanks.
♪
[SIGHS]
Welcome to "Citizentopia,"
where you, the citizens of Central City,
share your stories.
I am here today to talk
about a fallen hero,
someone who was often misunderstood,
a woman that you all know as...
Killer Frost.
But to the people who really knew her,
she was no killer.
Frost saved lives,
and she changed them for the better,
and I'm here with two
people who are proof of that.
Kamiko, Jamal, thank you for joining us.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Sure.
- Thanks for having us.
So I understand that you both had
a unique encounter with Frost?
It was during Bloodwork's
attack on the city,
and we were in the subway.
It was just completely
overrun by his Blood Brothers.
- I was so scared.
- We all were.
It was a bunch of strangers trapped
while those things
picked us off one by one.
Until Frost showed up.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Seeing her courage in court...
I knew I was on the
wrong side of the bench.
So when she was released,
I reached out, asking for forgiveness.
And she caught me right
in the middle of it.
But she didn't turn me in.
It was amazing.
Frost froze those Blood Brothers
and helped us escape.
We owe her our lives.
And what did Frost say?
That I did my job...
but maybe I should get a better one.
[CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLING] Man, I was a tagger.
If it wasn't for Frost,
I'd be in jail right now.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
Instead, I got my first
gallery exhibit next week.
So the next day,
I quit the state prosecutor's office.
Now I'm defending metas in Star City.
If it wasn't for Frost, we... [CHUCKLES]
We would have never gotten married.
♪
So wherever you are, Frost...
thank you.
♪
[SOFT MUSIC]
There must be one perfect thing to do
- to honor Frost.
- Just because Joe
handed out some greeting card advice
doesn't mean it's the right thing to do.
I don't know. Sounded
pretty on point to me.
How can one thing honor
someone as amazing as Frost?
[SCOFFS]
Barry told us about
the eternal flame for Oliver Queen.
- [SIGHS]
- [CHUCKLES]
What if we made, like,
a... Frost-ified version?
Yeah, yeah, like if I
took her superhero costume
and I put it in a glass
case with cryo-coolers
so that it could create
a self-sustained blizzard?
So it'd stay frozen forever.
You mean a snow globe?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
You know, it'd help if...
I wasn't the only one
coming up with good ideas.
Passive-aggressive much?
No, no. Not passive.
Passive-aggressive is
getting Hershfield's
to put hummus on our sandwiches.
Oh, wow.
I didn't see you getting
butthurt over a sandwich
on my bingo card today.
- Also, you love hummus.
- I do, I do.
Hummus is wonderful,
but it's not a condiment.
Ketchup is a condiment.
Mustard? Also a condiment.
Hummus is like a side dish.
No, no. Hummus is a dip.
Easy, condiment king.
I don't need you
Runksplaining hummus to me!
Well, I don't need you being
so cavalier with our sandwiches.
Well, don't worry, because I am never
- bringing you lunch ever again.
- [SCOFFS]
- Ugh!
- Sorry, sorry.
Do you guys know where
the arctic parkas are?
- The cozy ones?
- Yeah.
- Starchives.
- Right.
Thank you. Gotta run.
[SCOFFS]
[NOTIFICATION CHIMES, PHONE BUZZES]
[TENSE MUSIC]
CCC tip app's blowing up.
Something crazy is
happening at O'Shaughnessy's.
Is Blockbuster here to
settle his late fees?
No, it's not Blockbuster.
But I have a feeling
we're gonna wish it was.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
- Oh, come on, man!
[RECORD SCRATCHES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[THE DEATH SET'S "BAD DECISIONS"]
I am a party god!
♪ I like making bad decisions ♪
♪ Is this ever gonna change? ♪
- [BOTTLE SHATTERS]
- [GROWLING]
We can never unsee this.
Hey.
- Is that your friend?
- Uh...
'Cause that jerk just
froze half the bar!
[ICE CRACKLING]
Uh... sorry.
He's had a rough week. Here.
[SIGHS] I'm going on break.
If he's not gone by the time I get back,
I'm having him arrested.
♪ I like making bad decisions ♪
Hey, Chuckles! Garcia!
Come to join the party, have you, yeah?
[GRUFFLY] Yeah, you did!
[GRUNTS]
[BOTTLES CLINK] [BOTTLE SHATTERS]
What's your poison? Huh?
You look like a fuzzy-navel man.
- [GLASSES TINKLING]
- Coming right up.
Thanks, but I actually, uh...
I actually don't drink.
Awesome. More for us.
[HUMMING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[LAUGHTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[THUD]
[GRUNTS]
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[PANTING]
Oh, a big night out, huh?
Yeah, I've been there myself.
Now, sure, right now,
love is all cupcakes,
puppies, and monster trucks.
But just you wait until one of you dies
battling an
interdimensional death demon.
Oh, yeah.
Pain is coming.
♪
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. Use your knees.
There you go. No, no. Oh.
- You're okay, buddy.
- All right.
Well, you guys want to rob
a tech facility or something?
Might quiet the voices.
This man needs
Vibeaccinos. Lots of them.
I can run to Jitters.
And leave me here with Chillbooze?
No way.
You know, you can't
just shoot down my ideas
without offering another.
Fine. Let's get some food in him.
Do they serve fries here or something?
They must.
Ketchup bottle. See?
Mustard bottle.
[GASPS] Ooh, look.
- [SCOFFS]
- No hummus bottle.
Case closed.
- It's a condiment.
- It's a dip.
- You're a dip.
- Well, call me hummus then.
- Ugh, you are impossible.
- I can't believe you.
Hey!
BOTH: What?
You two are really
killing my party's vibe.
All right?
Besides, you're not even fighting.
You're just doin' what friends do, baby.
Helping each other to see
the world in your own...
unique way. [CHUCKLES]
[SOFT MUSIC]
It's what Frost did for me.
She shared her real self with me.
♪
Only I was too dumb
to share me with her,
and now it is too late.
♪
But I'm glad I got
to see things her way.
♪
[SNORING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[BOTH GRUNT]
Oh, all those muscles are heavy.
Sweet dreams, party god.
[BOTH PANTING]
♪
- Al, I am so sorry...
- Chuck, I'm sorry...
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I can't believe we're fighting.
Over a dip.
[SNIFFS]
Yeah, I miss her too.
You know, even though Mark
might be drunk as a skunk...
he was right.
We are really good friends. The best.
So if we listen to each other,
I'm sure we could find that one
perfect thing to honor Frost.
Yeah, actually, now that
I'm listening to you,
I think that your costume
idea was onto something.
Yeah?
Can I suggest one tweak, though?
For sure.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
[PENSIVE MUSIC]
♪
She told me she first felt like a hero
wearing this jacket.
Now that's how we'll remember her.
Always.
♪
[DARK MUSIC]
[WIND GUSTING]
[LIGHT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[ZIPPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[SAW WHIRRING]
[ICE SHATTERS]
♪
[SPEAKING FRENCH] _
_
♪
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Hold on to your badges.
We have a tight one.
CSI Barry Allen
and reigning champ Officer Daisy Korber
down to their last dog,
and...
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[BUZZER BLARES]
Allen wins it in the
upset of the century!
[LAUGHTER]
Thank you. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS] Fine.
But I want a rematch next year, Allen.
Sure.
♪
Yeah.
[RAPID BEEPING]
[CRASHING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
How long were you in there?
[PANTING]
I was hoping you could tell me.
Hey, do you mind telling the contractors
to knock off all the
hammering or whatever that is?
Uh, that's...
not construction.
Oh, great.
Guess I overdid it with the bourbon...
♪
And the tequila...
and the vodka.
[PILLS CLATTER]
Hey, what's that?
Satellite scans looking for Blockbuster.
No sign of him yet, but... [INHALES DEEPLY]
He'll show up sooner or later.
This team still isn't ready to face him.
Not all that. Talking about this.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Did you do all of these already?
How are you doing?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
I never even got to tell her how I felt.
Did she ever tell you about
the time that she signed us up
for a couples tag team
wrestling tournament?
I mean, we crushed it, obviously.
But then she gave our
championship belts away
to some kids at the ramen
joint where we were celebrating.
'Cause it wasn't about winning.
It was about the experience.
You really knew her well.
I thought so, yeah.
I also...
thought finishing this
list would be a way
to honor her memory,
but even with everything crossed off...
it still doesn't feel complete.
Look, man,
as wild and crazy as her
lust for adventure was,
what my Snowflake lived
for, more than the thrills,
was taking care of the people she loved.
That's what she really
wanted to do with her life.
Hell, she was literally
born to be Caitlin's savior.
♪
She never lost sight of that.
[SOFT ENERGETIC MUSIC]
♪
I know how to honor Frost's memory.
But right now, it seems impossible.
What's impossible for the Flash?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[SOMBER MUSIC]
'Cause I'm not going
to any damn funeral.
[BILLIE EILISH'S "EVERYBODY DIES"]
Caitlin. [WORD ECHOING]
♪
♪ Everybody dies ♪
♪ Surprise, surprise ♪
[SIGHS]
♪ We tell each other lies ♪
♪ Sometimes, we try ♪
[SIGHS]
♪ To make it feel like ♪
♪ We might be right ♪
♪ We might not be ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪
♪ Everybody dies ♪
♪ That's what they say ♪
♪ And maybe in a couple hundred years ♪
♪ They'll find another way ♪
♪ I just wonder why you'd wanna stay ♪
♪ If everybody ♪
♪ Goes ♪
♪ You'd still be alone ♪
♪
♪ I don't wanna cry ♪
♪ Some days I do ♪
♪ But not about you ♪
♪
♪ It's just a lot to think about ♪
♪ The world I'm used to ♪
♪ The one I can't get back ♪
♪ At least not for a while ♪
♪ I sure have a knack for seeing life ♪
♪ More like a child ♪
♪ It's not my fault, it's not so wrong ♪
♪ To wonder why ♪
♪ Everybody dies ♪
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
♪ And when will I? ♪
I'm still not going.
I... I just...
I came to apologize.
And to listen.
I suppose it's no use shutting the door
on someone who can phase through it.
Look, Caitlin, um...
about yesterday morning in the lounge.
It's fine.
I know you were just trying to help.
You know, trying and knowing
the right words to say
aren't the same thing.
And I'm sorry. I said everything wrong.
We've both been through a lot
over the last couple of days,
so I think it's okay to
let ourselves off the hook.
But you don't have to worry about me.
I'm good, honest.
♪
You're still having trouble sleeping?
I've had a lot on my mind.
So yes, I've had a few sleepless nights,
but medically speaking,
I'm not in any danger.
So thank you for coming.
Caitlin, I know you'll regret
not going to your sister's funeral.
Unbelievable.
I mean, do you hear yourself right now?
This isn't even about me.
This is about you
and your need to be the hero.
I am not one of your missions, okay?
And not everything can just
be fixed with speed healing.
But I need to grieve
Frost in my own way.
So if you don't mind,
will you please leave?
♪
[SIGHS]
Look, Caitlin,
I will leave you alone if
that's what you really want,
but before I go, just
ask yourself one thing.
♪
What would Frost want?
For you?
♪
You knew her better than anybody.
Would she want you to pull away?
Would she want us to let you?
But you gotta promise
me something, all right?
You will never shut yourself off
from me or the rest
of the team, all right?
♪
She'd tell me to stop being an idiot,
get off my ass, and live my damn life.
♪
That does sound like her.
You know, Frost was
the voice inside my head
before I even knew she had a name.
♪
She was the one telling me to be brave,
to be strong when I felt weak,
or that I was never as powerless
as others made me feel.
♪
[SIGHS]
Barry, when Frost died...
her singing died too.
Her laugh.
♪
[QUIETLY] That voice...
that voice that made me whole.
♪
So I can't go to the funeral,
because if I do, if I
see her in that casket...
♪
I'll know that she's gone for good.
[SOFTLY] What if that's not the case?
What do you mean?
♪
Her voice is still inside you.
As long as that's true...
She's not really gone.
♪
Joe suggested that we all
find a way to honor Frost.
♪
It was pretty hard finding my answer.
But you?
You just have to listen to her.
So what's Frost saying
she wants you to do?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪
[SIGHS]
Most of you know that I did
not want to be here today.
Not at first.
I was afraid that seeing her here
would make her death seem more real.
And I was scared.
You see, Frost was always
the fearless Snow sister.
Like that time she went
swimming with sharks
and picked a fight with a shark.
Or when she was at Jitters
for their slam poetry open mic night
and just grabbed the mic and read a poem
she'd scribbled on a
napkin five minutes before.
[SIGHS] See, Frost was always honest.
♪
[SHAKILY] And the truth is...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I thought that if I saw
my sister laying here...
♪
That I would have to say goodbye.
[SNIFFLES]
♪
But then...
A friend of mine reminded me that...
that's not true.
That she lives on in all of us,
not just in me.
In her selflessness,
her unique way of seeing the world,
and her deep love for
her family and friends.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
So if we keep those
parts of her alive in us,
then she's not really gone,
and I can't think of a better
way to honor her memory.
♪
I'll keep you alive, Frost.
I promise.
♪
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
It normally works.
Dad, what were you thinking?
Look, bleach takes out stains,
and the curtains were dirty, so...
[LAUGHING] I'm sorry, but no! No!
This whole retirement thing,
he's still real new at it.
Look, this the cleanest
spot in the whole house,
and I would have done a whole lot more
if Frost hadn't taken
my cleaning supplies
for her collages. [LAUGHTER]
Oh yeah, I still don't know
how she carried that stuff
- while ice-bridging across town.
- She didn't.
People were finding sponges
and yellow gloves for miles.
Actually, I think Wild Dog
uses one of Joe's mops as a bo staff.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Really?
This feels good,
remembering Frost like this.
Your advice worked, Joe.
That had more to do
with you than with me.
It was a beautiful eulogy.
More than anything
we did to honor Frost,
you helped us heal today.
Thanks for putting us back together.
I didn't make it easy on you guys,
so thanks for telling me
what I needed to hear anyway.
[PHONES CHIMING, BUZZING]
- Ooh.
- [BEEPING]
That Blockbuster jerk's back.
I'll have Kramer called CCPD.
No way. This guy's ours.
Plus, we all wanted a rematch, right?
And this time, we're ready.
Barry?
Tell Kramer to warm a holding cell.
Let's go get this guy.
♪
I will tell the troops to
prepare an early headline.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Hey.
♪
- You got somewhere to be too?
- Nope.
'Cause I'd love to hear some
more stories about Frost.
I'd like that too.
I'm gonna make us some coffee.
Perfect.
♪
Hey. We need to talk.
[WHISTLING]
- Hey.
You know, it's rude to
keep your guests waiting.
I've got a bar I'm supposed to be
getting thrown out of right now.
Sorry, I thought I had
time for one more supply run
before you got here.
Is that a genome sequencer?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- Yes.
- And did you steal it?
I borrowed it.
Whatever, Caitlin.
Game recognizes game.
♪
Look, you called. I'm here.
What do you want?
Your help.
Wow.
♪
Did you forget to pay
your electricity bill?
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Okay, that's not too creepy or anything.
Caitlin, what is it that you want?
♪
I'm gonna bring Frost back.
And you're gonna help me.
♪
So what do you think?
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SIGHS] I think we just found
tomorrow's front page.
[GASPS] Crushed it!
Uh, I mean, thank you.
I will interface with publishing
and get this out the door ASAP.
It's okay. Own it.
This is a great article.
You should be proud.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I still have a ton of work to do.
It's gonna be a late night.
Sure. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
♪
By the way, it's really good
to have you back from Coast City.
CCC Media was not the same without you.
You guys had Allegra.
I hear she did great filling in.
From who? [LAUGHS]
I'm... I'm gonna leave now.
[CHUCKLES]
♪
But hey, about the
Flash's latest takedown,
I know he worked with Frost,
but there have been reports
of him working with other people, too,
only no one knows who they are.
Shouldn't we investigate them?
Hmm, um...
I will think about it.
♪
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
Oh.
♪
I forgot my...
phone.
♪
Iris?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --