(MEN WHOOPING)
(CLAMORING)
(MEN SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
(MEN WHOOPING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(MEN SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
Najid, cut
the horses loose!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(ALL SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
We have to turn back.
We have been riding
for six months.
And we've lost 20 men.
But we survived.
Yes. By chance.
Any one of us could
have met that same fate.
We were the strongest.
Remember why you're here.
In the West, we would be
enemies, and I would have to kill you.
At least here,
we have a common goal.
RIZZETTI: Oh, yes.
This black powder.
It turns air into fire.
And kills a dozen men
at one time.
It is the weapon
of our dreams.
And what if
it's just a myth?
Men have sent word
that it's real.
And those men are dead.
And we are next.
We have no maps,
no medicine
and no food.
No one is going back.
We take inventory
of what we have left
and finish
what we started.
TOVAR: There's not much here.
The moon is strong.
When the horses
are fresh, we move.
To where?
WILLIAM: North.
If they keep after us, we'll
kill them in the mountains.
The magnet.
Too heavy.
TOVAR: Useless.
I'll have it.
It's all yours.
(MAGNET THUDS)
Amigo, only you would carry a
stupid magnet through the desert.
I can use it
to make a compass.
Rizzetti won't make it.
The wound is festering.
We'll be dragging
a corpse.
I heard that.
He's earned the right
to die where he wants.
I've been left
for dead twice.
It was bad luck.
For who?
The people who left me.
(TOVAR CHUCKLES)
Maybe Rizzetti's right.
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
Where are they?
(CREATURE GROWLING)
(GASPS)
Hill tribes?
It's no man.
(WHISPERS)
Then what is it?
Whatever it is,
it's hunting.
(CREATURE GROWLING)
(PANTING)
What was that?
I don't know.
I took its hand.
TOVAR: We need to move.
WILLIAM: Agreed.
I'll take the hand with us.
What the hell for?
So someone can tell me
what I just killed.
(HORSE SNORTS)
(HORSES APPROACHING)
TOVAR: Persistent bastards,
aren't they?
We'll take the rise,
make a stand there.
What a long shitting
way to go to die.
(MEN WHOOPING)
(MEN SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
Mother of God.
(MAN SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(SWORDS DRAWING)
(IN ENGLISH) I have no need
to go down fighting.
Agreed.
I say we take our chances
with the gents in front of us.
I haven't surrendered
in a while, eh?
It'll come back
to you.
Follow my lead,
we'll be fine.
Of course,
my friend.
Where you go,
I follow.
You're doing such
a great job already.
(SOLDIER SCREAMING
IN MANDARIN)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(IN ENGLISH)
They know what it is.
And they don't
look happy to see it.
All the more reason to
get the hell out of here.
Our weapons
are on that table.
Have you lost
your mind?
I can take out the guards
on the perimeter with my bow.
You cut the legs out
from under the officers.
I must confess, this
is not my favorite plan.
LIN: Where was this found?
You speak English.
Fantastic.
Where was this found?
It wasn't found.
It was taken.
That thing killed three
men before we took it down.
Where?
Two days' ride.
North, in the mountains.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Two of you,
you did this?
Well...
(STUTTERS)
I killed it.
Alone?
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Tell me how.
A swing of the sword.
The hand,
it came away clean.
The beast fell back
into a chasm.
Why are you here?
We came to trade.
We were ambushed.
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(GRUNTING)
(IN ENGLISH) You are soldiers.
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(SIGHS)
Mmm.
(DRUMS BEATING)
(IN ENGLISH) Are you
killing us, sister?
Two lost travelers?
(SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH)
I think she'd like that.
If it is death, my dear,
we need time to pray.
I'm trying here.
Sister, I know a siege
when I see one.
What comes at you so hard
you need a wall like this?
What the hell
did we kill out there?
STRATEGIST WANG:
Tao Tei.
You killed
a Tao Tei scout.
You killed it alone.
You're correct.
We are under siege.
But we did not expect the
attack for another nine days.
TOVAR: Attack?
Tao Tei.
What the hell
is a Tao Tei?
Many things about your
story have importance.
You are not to die today.
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(KEYS RATTLE)
(WHIRRING)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SOLDIER GRUNTS)
(METAL CREAKING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(IN ENGLISH) The black are
the foot soldiers.
And the red?
Those are the archers.
And the blue?
They're all women.
What the hell
do they do?
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Look at this army.
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
Incredible.
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
They look nervous.
(SIGHS) It's a big wall
to be so nervous.
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
Do you hear it?
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING)
(SCREECHES AND GROWLS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(WHIRRING)
(IN ENGLISH)
William, over there.
Why isn't he tied up?
There's our escape.
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(GROWLING)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS) (IN
ENGLISH) We need to move!
We need to move
or we die!
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(GROWLING)
(IN ENGLISH) Go, go!
Go and fight!
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Cut me loose!
Fight or run?
Run where?
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
WILLIAM: Aim for the eyes!
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(SCREECHING)
TOVAR: William!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
TOVAR: Hey! Bitch!
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHES)
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
TOVAR: William.
I need a shot.
(SCREECHES)
(SHRILL CRY)
What god made
those things?
None that we know.
Think they'll
hang us now?
I could use the rest.
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) You've earned
General Shao's praise.
Will they come back?
Yes.
SHAO: All we can do
IS prepare.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
MAN: (IN ENGLISH)
Who are you?
(PANTING)
Easy.
I'm Ballard. Hmm?
William.
This is Tovar.
BALLARD: What are
you doing here?
We came looking
for black powder.
I bet you did.
I came with mercenaries
for the same thing.
Twenty-five years ago.
And did you find it?
Finding it and leaving with it
alive are two different things.
You saved the west turret.
That was extremely diplomatic.
We weren't
being diplomatic.
We were trying
to stay alive.
You smell like animals.
Thank you.
Clean up
and they'll feed you.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES) He
knows where the powder is.
Then why is he
still here?
He needs help
getting out?
Right.
We play our part,
take the powder
and go home.
I didn't sign up for this.
Which part?
Well, all of it.
But mostly the monsters.
There's a lot of them.
We really do smell.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
General Shao welcomes
you as honored guests
of the Nameless Order and
thanks you for your skill and courage.
We are honored
to be honored.
Is that the best
you've got?
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SCOFFING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
LIN: (IN ENGLISH)
Commander Chen thinks your bow
is not worthy
of your skill.
Tell him there's no
better weapon here.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(ALL LAUGH)
(SHAO SPEAKING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(IN ENGLISH) They wish
to see you shoot.
In here?
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) What was that?
LIN: He thinks you have fear.
Too many people.
Get one of the cups.
Now?
I want to eat.
(SLURPS)
You remember
how to do this?
Last time didn't go so
good. We were drunk.
How high?
Ten yards.
Six hands to the right.
Turn around.
No, I'll do it this way.
On my count.
Amigo...
One.
Two.
Three.
Pull.
(ALL CHEER AND APPLAUD)
(YAWNS)
Good luck with that.
I want food.
Who taught
you English?
Sir Ballard.
English and Latin.
Heard he's been here
for 25 years.
You won't
let him leave.
He must stay here.
What about us?
Pace yourself.
The meals
are regular here.
I hope not
to stay that long.
I like your thinking,
but I suggest you keep
your plans private.
You aren't
the first Westerners
to come here looking
for black powder.
We'll discuss it tonight.
Bring your partner.
How long
have you been here?
Always.
I was not five years old
when I came here.
I have no other family.
We're the same.
I was given to an army
before I can remember.
As a soldier?
Worse.
As a gleaner.
Packs of children, we'd
clean the battlefields.
After, when the
fighting's over.
I became a page,
a pikeman's boy...
For your country?
No. I fought for food.
You fight to eat.
You live long enough,
you fight for money.
How many flags
do you fight for?
I don't know.
I fought for Harold
against the Danes.
I saved a Duke's life. I
fought for him until he died.
Fought for Spain
against the Franks.
Fought for the Franks
against Boulogne.
I fought for the Pope.
Many flags.
We are not the same.
Meet me on the Wall. I
have something to show you.
He should be
careful with her.
She's very powerful here.
Then it is a fair contest.
Come.
Hmm.
You wish to try?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(WOMAN SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(ALL CHUCKLE)
(IN ENGLISH) She says men
have so much to teach us.
(GIGGLES)
I don't think
that's what she said.
You know what I think?
I think you're afraid.
You said that
this morning.
And yet,
here I am.
Yes.
Here you are.
Will you jump?
Or not?
WILLIAM: These men know
what they're doing?
LIN: Wrong question.
Whether or not
the cable is attached,
that is the question.
(WILLIAM CHUCKLES)
And the answer?
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(STUTTERS)
Xin ren.
(IN ENGLISH) Xin ren
means trust. To have faith.
Here, in this army,
we fight for more
than food or money.
We give our lives
to something more.
Xin ren is our flag.
Trust in each other.
In all ways,
at all times.
Well, that's all well and
good, but I'm not jumping.
I'm alive today
because I trust no one.
A man must learn to trust
before he can be trusted.
Then you were right.
We're not the same.
(MEN GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(LAUGHS)
(IN ENGLISH) My God!
(CHUCKLES)
A taste, a glimpse.
A few pilfered grains from Strategist
Wang's supply of black powder.
He's mastered the
transmutation of these elements.
People speak
of a weapon.
There are many
weapons here.
Why have we
not seen them?
(SIGHS) There are many
things you have not seen.
And many things you
should pray will not be needed
before the siege
is through.
The Tao Tel will return.
When the drums
call to battle,
the guards leave their posts and
take their positions on the Wall.
That is our moment.
We want to be
riding away
as the battle rages.
And the armory doors?
You have keys?
I have black powder.
Enough for
several doors.
He brings us in.
We get us out.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(MAN SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) As you fought,
where was this stone?
In my bag.
Its unseen force
is powerful.
I believe this strange
stone could help us.
We try everything.
Where are the
Tao Tel now?
STRATEGIST WANG:
The mountains, regrouping.
Where do they
come from?
About 20 centuries ago,
there was an emperor whose greed
brought deep suffering to all of China.
The heavens sent the meteor
that struck Gouwu Mountain,
turning it green
and releasing the Tao Tei.
From that day on, the
Tao Tei rise every 60 years
to scourge
the north of China.
They come to remind us of what
happens when greed is unchecked.
They eat anything,
alive or dead,
and take food
to their queen.
She depends on her
soldiers to feed her.
Only with the food they
provide is she able to multiply.
The capital, and its two million
people, is only 800 li away.
If the Tao Tei ever had
that much nourishment,
no corner of the world
would be safe.
You can't hunt them?
Men try.
They disappear.
We never find
their bones.
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SHAO SPEAKING)
(TAO TEI GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
(SOLDIERS MARCHING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(CRIES SOFTLY)
(GROANING)
(THUDS)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(MAN SINGING)
(ALL SINGING)
(IN ENGLISH) This is envoy
Shen from the palace.
He has brought important records
to help with the coming battle.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) A
900-year-old battle report.
(CONTINUES IN MANDARIN) BALLARD:
(IN ENGLISH) At the Hansha gates,
three beasts
mounted the Wall.
They killed many men
as they went forward.
Then, by the grace
of the ancient gods,
the beasts stopped...
(READING IN MANDARIN)
...and sat peacefully
as we slaughtered them.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) At the Hansha
Gate, was a magnet just like this one.
I believe that magnet was the
reason that two of you Westerners
killed the Tao Tel
so easily.
I believe the magnet
makes the Tao Tei deaf.
Without instruction,
they fall still.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
How can we be sure?
Why not try it?
Capture a Tao Tei.
See if it works.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
LIN: (IN ENGLISH) How?
No net is strong enough.
Hunt them.
Like a whale.
You know what that is.
Uh... A water beast.
Hundred times
the size of a Tao Tei.
A spear that grabs. Hook
the bone. Pull them up.
(STRATEGIST WANG
SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) I've seen
it done in Spain.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) What the hell
are you doing?
We need to be free
when the attack comes.
How many chances
do you think we will get?
Be injured. Be
missing. Be a coward.
Get out of this.
We did enough.
(MAN SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(WHIRRING)
(BOWL SHATTERS)
TOVAR: (IN ENGLISH)
He'll be here.
When?
When it's over?
We start
and he will find us.
Start?
We're jumping
off a cliff here.
I have everything.
Powder, tools, maps.
It's all hidden and
arranged along the route.
Once we start,
there's no going back.
(METAL CREAKING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHES)
(SOLDIER 1 SCREAMING)
(SOLDIER 2 SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SOLDIERS RESPOND)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(ALL SPEAKING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(IN ENGLISH) I'll find him.
Forget him.
He'd rather die trying to
impress the new general
than grab the key to every counting
room and brothel in the world.
Good God, man.
The time is now!
I can't go
without him.
More the spoils for us!
We need his bow!
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(STRAINING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(SCREECHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(IN ENGLISH) No, no, no. Stop!
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
WILLIAM: (IN ENGLISH)
There's too much tension.
Chain will break.
That way. That way.
Let him run!
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(SCREECHING AND WHIMPERING)
(IN ENGLISH) Stop! Stop!
We need longer for the
sleeping potion to work.
(SCREECHING)
That way. That way.
We need to isolate it.
Separate it from the others.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SOLDIER SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
STRATEGIST WANG: (IN ENGLISH)
The chain won't hold much longer!
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
LIN: (IN ENGLISH)
William, wait.
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) These arrows
will scream as the Tao Tei run.
Aim for the sound.
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(ARROWS REVERBERATING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TAO TEI GROWLING SOFTLY)
(CONTINUES GROWLING)
(CHAINS CLANKING)
(GRUNTS)
(WILLIAM GRUNTING)
(MAN SPEAKING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(ARROW WHOOSHING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(IN ENGLISH) I'm only saving
you so I can kill you myself.
Grab an ax,
we're fighting blind.
(ARROW WHOOSHING SOFTLY)
(WHISPERS) Not yet.
I know what to do!
(ARROW WHOOSHING)
(SCREECHES)
The fire's not
holding them back.
Die well, brother.
What the hell
are you doing?
She's listening.
(ARROWS WHOOSHING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(PANTING)
(CHAIN CLANKING)
(SOLDIERS SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(PANTING)
(MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WILLIAM SIGHS)
(IN ENGLISH) Did it work?
Yes. The beast
was captured.
(GROANS)
My friend...
He was unharmed.
Why did you go
over the Wall?
(SIGHING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Did I say it right?
Thank you.
Black powder.
It is a terrible weapon.
It would be better if
you had never seen it.
I know very little
of the outside world.
But it seems to me,
the greed of men is not that
different from the Tao Tel.
Is that true?
The strong take
what they want.
Forget what you have seen.
(TAO TEI GROWLING)
(CAGE RATTLING)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(STOPS GROWLING)
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
Hmm?
(IN ENGLISH) You're much
braver than they think.
You wounded?
I was looking for you.
To say thank you.
(SCOFFS)
TOVAR: You feel good, huh?
Maybe you sing
a little song, eh?
I will join you.
We can sing together how
you saved the grateful chinos.
You saw what happened out
there and that's what you say?
I see black powder.
I see a man
forget his friends.
The black powder's
not going anywhere.
What goes nowhere is you.
You'll never get
what you want from this.
You think they see you
as some kind of hero?
A man of virtue?
Maybe you can fool them,
but I know what you are.
You know what you are.
A thief,
a liar,
and a killer.
And you can never undo
the things you have done,
and you will
never be anything.
(GRUNTS)
Good to see you again,
amigo.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Nothing?
No.
How do you know
he won't betray us?
I don't.
They'll kill him. They'll
kill him no matter what.
The time they spend
Killing him
is time they are
not chasing us.
Careful with that.
There's powder here.
Tovar.
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Have a look.
See if it's gone out.
Is it safe?
Of course it is.
(WATER RUNNING)
(BOTH COUGHING)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
BALLARD: Shake it off, man.
To work.
TOVAR: I thought
you said it was safe?
We're in, aren't we?
You're here.
We've come
to our senses, eh?
TOVAR: Ballard has
planned well.
Getting out is easy.
There's a gate.
20 miles west.
We dodge
the hill tribes.
We can make it.
They need us here.
They need more than us.
(SIGHS) These people are doomed.
Don't be a fool.
I've been a fool.
I'm done with it.
Brother, please.
We've been fighting
for nothing.
For greed.
Amigo,
after all the blood,
and cold, and pain,
with this black powder
in our saddle bags,
we win.
You come with me.
I can't do that now.
Stay and fight.
William...
BALLARD: Think he's dead?
It'd take a lot
more than that.
(STRATEGIST WANG
SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
TOVAR: Come on.
Hyah.
(INDISTINCT MURMURS)
(TAO TE| SNORING)
(ALL GASP)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) I tried to stop
them... You dare to speak to me?
I didn't do this.
And you came here
to trade.
And you knew nothing
of black powder.
What a fool
you must think I am.
If I was with them,
why would I be here?
I tried to stop them.
I tried...
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
You lie.
Some part of you knows
that's not true.
If I were not the General,
I would kill you myself.
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR LOCKS)
(IN ENGLISH) Which way,
left or right?
Go up and take a look
from the high ground.
Hyah!
(HORSES NEIGHING)
No!
No! Bastard!
(PANTING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
WILLIAM: (IN ENGLISH)
What happened?
We have failed.
The Tao Tel
are in the Kingdom.
You are free to leave.
Take what you wish and go.
This was the
General's final order.
Where is she?
To do what?
To fight?
Is there a chance?
There's only one.
Kill the Queen.
Kill the Queen,
or we all die.
Leave.
Tell the world
what you have seen,
and tell them
what is coming.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I'll need my bow.
If I'm to join you,
(SOLDIER SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) He wishes
to join us.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(MEN APPROACHING)
(ALL GASP)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(SNORING)
(ALL GASP)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(CHITTERING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(MEN LAUGHING)
(MUFFLED IN ENGLISH) No.
No.
No, don't throw
that thing near fire!
(EXPLOSIONS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(MEN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(TAO TEI GROWLING)
WILLIAM: (IN ENGLISH)
Above you!
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH) Behind you!
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(LIN GRUNTS)
I set you free.
And here I am.
There's the Queen!
They will not attack
while the Queen is feeding.
We have a chance!
Hold on!
(SCREAMING)
(CLATTERING)
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(HORSE SNORTING)
(IN ENGLISH) There is
an underground canal here.
WILLIAM:
Has it been breached?
The Tao Tel should
all be above ground.
And the one we captured?
STRATEGIST WANG:
We load it up.
We feed it.
And it will return
to its Queen.
Good.
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(TAO TEI SCREECHING)
(MAN YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
You'll have one hell of
a scar, but you'll live.
(LIN SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
We'll come back for him.
(TAO TEI SHRIEKING)
LIN: They've broken through!
(TAO TEI BREATHING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLS)
Patience, William.
(SNIFFING)
And it will go to the
Queen when it's done?
It should.
It will.
(SHRIEKING)
Let it in.
(GROWLING)
I can get a shot
from above.
(DOOR THUDDING)
Go! I'll hold them back.
Wait. Not yet.
WILLIAM: Hit.
Go higher.
I'll get
a better shot.
(GROWLING)
(CALLING)
STRATEGIST WANG: General!
It's up to you now!
(GROWLS)
(CALLING)
We have one black
powder weapon left.
Give me the spear.
I've trained for
this my whole life.
(SPEAKS IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
I'll get you the shot.
(ALL SNARLING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(LIN GRUNTS)
I've got you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CLATTERING)
So, how's life
without me?
A little slow.
You're a hero after all.
Well, it looks that way.
You seem pleased
with yourself.
And what are they giving you
for all of your troubles?
A bag of gold?
A victory parade
along the top of the Wall?
All the black powder
I can carry.
And a cavalry escort
to get me home safely.
Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
So what is this? You're
here to rub my nose in it?
Well, would you
blame me?
The last time I saw you,
you left me for dead.
And the time before that,
I saved your life.
True.
You know, the Emperor
gave me a choice.
I could take
the black powder,
or I could take you.
Please tell me
you chose the powder?
I don't even
know you anymore.
(CHUCKLES)
The horses are
saddled and waiting.
Best we ride
before nightfall.
I'll be inside.
Don't leave
without me.
I came to say goodbye.
I understand
congratulations are in order.
General of the
northwest territory.
That's quite
an honor.
Seems you've made
your choice.
Him?
Believe me, I'm already thinking
about trading him back for the powder.
(CHUCKLES)
TOVAR: I heard that.
Perhaps we were
both wrong.
We are more similar
than I thought.
Thank you, General.
(HORSE GRUNTS)
Are you sure you don't
want to go back?
Of course I do.
I just don't trust you to
make it out of here alone.
(TOVAR LAUGHS)