- Hey, come on, folks. Give us a break.
- Hey, back it up.
There's enough fire here for everybody,
all right?
What kind of pool is it?
Well, that's the beauty of it.
You get to pick the spot where El Flasho
makes his next appearance.
Come on.
You don't even believe he exists.
Of course I don't, but you do.
And so does every badge in Homicide
and Narcotics and Vice.
You could make a lot of money here.
I don't know, Murph.
That's the third barn burn
in three weeks.
Whatever's going to hell down here
is going up in smoke.
It's scandalous to let
the old gal go this way.
She was a real beauty in her time.
My husband used to work up there.
Back when they was moving hooch
through the back room.
That was a long time ago, though.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
- What are you, some kind of goon?
- Just doing my job, lady.
Life ain't hard enough, huh?
So you wanna keep a record of it.
You never know what you'll miss.
Look, the kids up there
on the second floor.
So, Murph, when does that pool start?
Come on, guys, I'll get you out of here.
Thanks, Flash. At least somebody around
here knows how to rescue a kid.
Cross the fireman off my suspect list.
Why don't you go home, girl.
Ain't nothing more to see.
You didn't see him?
How could you miss him?
- He was standing right there with the kids.
- I saw a fireman with those kids.
But it doesn't matter. That's the beauty
of the Flash pool, it's reported sightings.
- What?
- Good evening, my dear.
I'm Officer Murphy. May I help you?
Not unless you can cut, rinse
and blow dry for under 35.
Well, that leaves one more possibility.
Central City Police.
Yeah, police lab. Barry Allen, please.
- He's not in.
- He isn't?
- Any message?
- No. No message.
And how do you look in red, Mr. Allen?
Hey, there he is.
Joe Klein, Voice of the City,
any comment on the state's allegations...
...about your illegal gambling
and racketeering?
The jury made my comment. "Not guilty."
I'm a legitimate businessman.
Does that mean that you didn't order
the murder of a State's witness?
You know, one of these days you're
gonna lose your voice, Mr. Klein.
And I don't mean by a sore throat.
Legitimate businessman?
Yeah, babe, and I'm Connie Chung.
You know what I'm saying?
What kind of district attorney
are you?
Simonson would've had more trouble
in traffic court.
Next time, have the police bring me a case
that will stand up in court.
Your guys couldn't even get their names
straight on cross-examination.
They were into their third straight
double shift when they arrested Simonson.
Simonson's running the riverfront
like his own private kingdom.
- Numbers, vice, extortion.
- You're right.
He's worse than his father ever was,
and you can't seem to make anything stick.
Well, I'm gonna nail him.
With or without the police.
Gum under the craps table.
Where were these people raised?
Go ahead, shoot the DA
in your illegal casino.
I'd like the movie rights
to that one, Arthur.
You shouldn't be here, Castillo.
Two of your bogus corporations just bought
the torched riverfront properties.
Why wasn't I told what was going on?
If we are making any allegations,
please, talk to my lawyer.
- I talked to your lawyer already, in court.
- I know. He walked all over you.
Arthur, it's an election year.
I need to win a few.
Well, I'll get someone to take a fall,
make you look good in the papers.
Can't afford to lose you.
Yeah, well...
...we need to talk about that too.
I need a better deal.
Our current arrangement is unacceptable.
Our arrangement is fine.
Haven't I taken care of you
since law school?
Go home, Tommy boy.
Having the DA around
is bad for business.
Right.
Sabrina's got this girlfriend.
She's young, she's hip,
she's single, she's perfect for you.
Yeah, like the last perfect one,
the one with the phobias.
- So she was afraid of spiders, big deal.
- Yeah, along with hats, fish, suitcases...
...and anything with fur. I'm too busy
with this arson case to worry about women.
Look, you get too caught up in the job,
and the engine just...
All right. Okay. So what's the word on that
metal scrap you found at the warehouse?
Fragment of incendiary fuse.
Asian, according to my analysis.
That only narrows it down to
a few hundred firework factories...
...between Seoul and Hong Kong.
- Can I help you boys?
- Mrs. Grosso.
- Yes?
- Hi, I'm Barry Allen.
And I wanted to ask you a few questions
about the fire on the docks last night.
Yeah, and I'm here to find a birthday
present for the woman of my dreams.
A romantic.
I remember when everybody
in this town was like that.
Now, about the fires.
You know, it's a miracle those kids
weren't hurt.
They don't have anywhere else to play
but outside there.
But we've got a contribution up
to replant Riverside Park.
Check it out, Barry.
Lights are low, she's on fire...
According to your statement...
...you saw all three recent fires.
- Saw them?
I almost burned around them.
But I was really worried
about the old cannery.
- The one on Angel Street.
- Yes.
You see, my second husband
got me a deed for it...
...and I was hoping that the developers
would buy me out...
...so that I could send my grandchildren
to school.
- But all these fires burning through...
- It's a love machine.
Julio.
Can you describe the blazes?
Well, at first it was a big burst...
...and then a lot of little fires
that break out all at once.
Isn't that suspicious?
That explains a lot.
Look, if you're gonna nix this date tonight,
I gotta call Sabrina.
Julio, I got arsonist records faxing in
from the capitol, all right?
Not till tomorrow.
Judith, huh?
- What did you tell her about me?
- That you're 4'8"...
...with a mug like a scouring pad.
What do you think, man? Just trust me.
I'm living proof of what love can do.
Yeah, but inhaling lab fumes
does the same thing.
My face is precious.
- First date, huh, buddy?
- First, double, blind.
- This one's on me.
- Thanks.
Baby, why take pictures
when you got the real thing, huh?
I'm flattered,
but I'm expecting my date any minute.
Doll face, bring me two of those
l-wanna-iguana cocktails...
...for me and my new
best girlfriend here.
I have other plans, but I'm sure
that girl in red over there...
...would love to have you buy her a drink.
- Sweetheart, you won the lottery tonight.
Hey, babe, come on, relax...
...and let me bring you
to the threshold of unearthly delight.
He slipped crossing the threshold.
Do you do this professionally?
Listen, if you wanna press charges...
...l'm a police officer.
And here I heard they were never around
when you needed one. Excuse me.
Hey, wait a minute.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey, wait a minute. Excuse me.
What do you mean "wait a minute"?
We're not walking backwards here.
Hi, Barry.
Your mom pick that suit out for you?
This is my best friend from high school,
Judith. This is the guy I told you about.
Hi.
You've had a near-death experience.
I can tell by your aura.
My aura?
Would you excuse us a moment, please?
Be back in a second.
Julio, you're a dead man.
What the hell are you doing here?
Who would have thought you could get
that acrobatic in a motel room?
Feet off the desk, Mr. DA.
And those are confidential.
What about the job, Ms. Lockhart? You've
been tracking suspects for three months.
And I've been working for three months,
thank you.
Flash doesn't advertise. I've cross-indexed
every piece of data I could find:
News footage, reported sightings.
Plotted against demographic...
...and psychological profiles,
as well as random variables...
...like atmospheric disturbances.
You got your money's worth, pal.
This can't hurt your reputation any,
Ms. Lockhart.
He's obviously a concerned citizen,
and we have to know how to reach him.
And you'll be the one with his number.
Or won't this salvage
your re-election campaign...
...with your opponent slaughtering you
in the polls?
I don't plan on being district attorney
forever. What do you have for me?
I've narrowed it down from a cast
of thousands to one front-runner.
But no names yet.
I still need hard evidence.
I'll have the man behind the mask
by Friday.
Fine, Friday.
Okay, Barry,
you're number one with a bullet.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
She wasn't exactly your type.
- Not exactly?
- Sabrina thought you two hit it off.
Yeah, maybe if I'd been the reincarnation
of Joan of Arc or Flipper.
- Look, Sabrina's cousin...
- Yo, Julio, Barry-o.
We got a pool going here, the next spot
the Flash shows up, five bucks.
- I never win at those things.
- You never get in.
Put me down for the five you owe me.
I'll take Chinatown.
- Chinatown. You got it.
- All right, tell you what...
...pick Central City Park, man.
Another five bucks.
That's a good bet. You know,
you're at the opposite side of the city.
I got lucky there before. Why not.
Listen, you guys. Heard anything else
about that warehouse fire?
Yeah. You know, your hunch
was right, Barry.
That's right. Jamoe's cousin over at
the fire department confirmed it was arson.
- That's what I thought. Thanks.
- See you in a bit.
Hey, Barry. Don't forget Helltown's still
open, in case you change your mind.
Thanks, I'll remember.
From the FBI.
Look, you may be right. It says
that fuse is from a Saigon manufacturer.
What, we got a Vietnamese firebug
torching the dockside?
No, not necessarily.
This fuse was used during the war by a U.S.
Demolition team known as the Fire Lords.
Those guys could
start a firestorm during a monsoon.
Wait, someone's paying top dollar
for a pro who trained with Uncle Sam?
Yeah, but who's making money
off these torchings?
Ladies and gents,
the royal creed from the kingdom of chance.
Twenty dollars buys you an invitation.
Find where the little lady is hiding...
...double your money.
Go ahead mister, pick a card.
I think he's got it.
Too bad. Maybe next time.
Try your luck again.
Here we go, once more.
Okay, pick a card.
Hey, what's he doing?
I don't think you quite got it, pal.
It's one card at a time.
Hey.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Move along, folks.
Only winner in three card monte
is the dealer.
What kind of racket are you playing?
This is harassment to free enterprise.
Come on, you got along fine
with my father and brother.
I'm Barry Allen.
- You're Henry's younger boy.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I was real sorry to hear about Jay.
He was okay.
Listen, I need a little help, okay?
I'd like anything you got
on fires on the wharf.
I could use a little down payment.
- How about I don't bust you for fraud?
- Okay, okay.
Tell me one thing.
How'd you pull that little gag before?
I'd already palmed the queen
in the first place.
TV magic cards when I was a kid.
Call me with anything.
Witnesses say they saw a red blur.
Makes the fourth time
this month this mysterious...
Star Lab.
Star Labs' van again.
What do they have to do
with the Flash?
Sherry, can you come in here, please?
Okay, there's a couple of things.
If Dr. Carter Hall calls...
...can you tell him I'll be in
the gene-splicing lab?
- I just have to find something to write on.
- Sherry?
Sherry had like a...
You know, a female thing.
- I'm the New York City College intern.
- No problem.
- Heather.
- Yes, of course.
Okay, that's Dr. Carter.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
It's just that I don't have a pen.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I didn't have a pen.
Never mind. Just hold my calls.
Okay. Great. I mean, anything that you
need, because I really need this job.
Especially after the last one. Who knew
those chemicals would be so volatile?
Listen, just hold my calls.
- "Hold my calls."
- And don't touch anything.
- "Don't touch anything."
- Please.
"Please."
Following the Flash around, eh, McGee?
Hyperkinetic field studies.
Still waters do run deep, Dr. McGee.
Or at the very least, classified.
You didn't talk that way
to my father.
And unless you want to lose a hand...
...you won't take that tone with me.
Mr. Spanier. Again, a pleasure.
Wonderful work, just wonderful.
I take no pleasure from my calling, sir.
Can a man take fire
in his bosom and clothes not be burned?
Yeah, right.
I've got big plans for the riverfront:
Hotels, casinos. All legitimate.
You see, I can't buy property...
...the city has put aside
for historical restoration.
But if it burns,
there's nothing to restore.
Our days on earth are a shadow...
...and there is none abiding.
Whatever you say.
Meanwhile, your next job
is the customs house off Bleaker.
What a way to earn a living.
Hey, big Earl. Look what I got.
Excuse me.
Just checking the cable. We've been
having some problems with line outage.
Your landlady let me in.
Iguana's, right?
You're a cable-repair person?
Putting myself through school.
Neurosurgery.
Great. I didn't think
I'd ever see you again.
Particularly not in my apartment.
I'm just a regular bad penny,
keep showing up.
Hey, how did you learn those moves
in the bar, huh?
- Older brothers.
- Yeah. Well, listen, you hungry?
I know a great Odessan restaurant
right around the block.
I have to take a rain check.
Work, work.
Yeah, I see.
Earl!
Hey, big guy.
Well, Earl likes you, so it's settled.
- How about this weekend?
- I'm kind of involved.
- Triplets.
- Triplets? That's involved.
And you should answer that.
My van is double-parked.
If I add the science channel,
can I call you?
Hello?
Fosnight, slow down.
What, Spanier?
Yeah, Spanier. Noble John Spanier.
I just spotted him tonight.
Last time I saw this guy was 15 years ago,
right after the Polo Club fire.
- The one that killed Simonson's father?
- Right.
And junior made a fortune
on the insurance.
Listen, this Spanier is kind of
a Bible belter, you know what I mean?
He was in and out of jail
all his life until...
- ... the Special Forces got hold of him.
- One of the Fire Lords?
Yeah. Hey, not bad.
Anyway, Spanier's a real case. Guy's got
one foot in the church and one foot in hell.
- Where did you last see him?
- By the old custom house over on Pier 23.
What, no thank you?
Yeah.
Mr. DA, get out your checkbook.
Well, how should I know who it is, Earl?
Hey, who's the watchdog around here?
We have to talk.
District Attorney Castillo,
it's 3 a.m.
So let's cut to the chase.
I know you're the Flash.
Earl, did you hear that?
Have you got the wrong apartment?
Like you said, Barry, it's 3 a.m.
Let's cut the comedy.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The lightning bolt, your brother's death,
the woman at Star Labs.
Do I have to go on?
Barry.
You need a patron.
You need a mentor...
...to guide you.
To direct you. Unofficially, of course.
How else to condone a masked vigilante?
The city needs you, Barry.
And you need a friend in high places.
Let me be that friend.
Because you sure as hell
don't want me as an enemy.
I don't know what you're talking about
here. I mean, we have nothing to discuss.
In your short career, you've already made
enemies in all the wrong places, Barry.
- Lf your identity was made public...
- My identity?
Everyone you love would be in danger
from everything in Central City.
You family, your friends, your dog.
Here, boy.
Fetch.
Four-second fuse. Three, two...
Four-second fuse.
Three...
...two...
...one.
I'll give you 24 hours to get smart.
Either you work for me, or that reporter
Joe Klein gets the videotape...
...of you flashing out of here
earlier tonight.
You know where to find me.
Damn!
Videotape.
I can't believe Castillo,
threatening my family like that.
I'd like to bash his head
into a wall at hyper speed.
Barry, stop.
You're not going to hurt Castillo.
And your anxiety level
is not doing your metabolism any good.
But the thing is,
part of what he said is true.
Sanction from downtown couldn't hurt.
But not from a crusading DA
who throws a grenade at Earl.
No, of course not.
The man's crooked.
On the other hand, I can't go public,
endanger the people I love.
Mom, Dad, Eve, Shawn, you.
Think of the heat
it could create for you.
Barry, don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
I'll play your little game for now, Castillo.
But I promise you,
you threaten me or my family again...
...and there'll be hell to play.
I want you to hit Simonson's casino
at the wharf.
Throw a monkey wrench into the works.
His free ride at the riverfront is over.
Think of the good you'll be doing, shutting
down a known criminal's operations.
- Our goals are the same, Barry.
- Yeah, but your methods stink.
Hey, big guy. Listen, a friend of mine
gave me her card for the evening, all right?
But no names, see.
Her husband would never understand.
Babe, one 100-dollar chip, please.
It's all I need.
Thanks.
Another out-of-work gigolo
with time to kill?
Playing your own money.
I bet you got a system too.
No, I just feel lucky.
Timing is everything.
You just have to know when to move.
I guess you do.
You're hot. All right.
- Yes!
- Seven. Winner.
I don't believe it.
Two different dealers,
he's still a quarter of a mil ahead?
You know this guy?
- I feel particularly lucky.
- I'm gonna stay.
Hit me.
Let's hope both of us
are honest men, sir.
I'm a very bad sport
when it comes to sharks and cheats.
- Twenty-three. Bust.
- Now, why don't we call it a night...
...and quit while we're ahead.
And if I ever see you in this room again,
you'll regret it.
And if I don't see you in my room,
we're both gonna regret it.
You can't afford me.
Thank you.
Yes, that's lovely.
Thank you very much.
That's nice.
Thank you. Later.
What the hell is happening here?
Shut the place down, damn it!
Two-hundred-seventy thou and change.
For the love of...
I thought I told you to lock up.
Damn it, Castillo. Enough with the showing
up already. You'll get us both indicted.
I'm not hired help anymore.
We are partners as of right now.
- You're flipped out of your head.
- How much you lose tonight?
One-fifty, 200 grand?
I could arrange for you
to lose like that every night.
How long do you think it'll take
the Flash to break you?
The Flash? That punk in shades?
Of course not. The Flash is so quick,
you never saw him.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm supposed to buy that?
Who else could beat your rigged game?
Who else could have diffused the bomb
at the customs house?
But don't worry.
He won't be visiting
your real-estate fire-sales anymore.
The Flash works for me now.
Just like you do.
Boy, I hate these cheap divorce jobs.
Nice p.j.'s. Where did you buy them,
Ringling Bros.?
Where do you get off...
...breaking and entering,
hiding a camera in my home?
Just doing my job.
You wanna press charges, fine.
- I'm working here.
- To hell with your job.
You had no right to interfere in my life.
The moment you put on that mask,
you gave me that right.
I wear a mask to protect
the people I know and love...
...who might get hurt for what I do.
You're a cop,
you know wearing masks are illegal.
All right. But what would you do,
run through the streets...
...stark naked at 350 miles an hour
with bells on your toes?
No, you're too busy to worry
about the consequences of your actions.
- To hungry for the paycheck.
- What is so noble about running around...
...in a Halloween costume?
You should see a psychiatrist.
I can sleep at night.
How about you?
Doesn't working for a man
like Castillo bother you?
- What does that mean?
- He's out for all the power he can grab.
Thanks to you,
he's got me up against the wall.
He's my client.
He pays his bills. So what?
So what?
So he's threatening
my family and my friends...
...unless I do his dirty work. Get it?
It's Mrs. Kief. She's got a gun.
Oh, my God.
She would've killed her husband.
Anything on that scrap of cloth
from the second sweep of the warehouse?
Department-store polyester.
Our man's not making
this year's "best dressed" list.
- Can I help you?
- No, thank you. I'm here to see...
Julio, go downstairs and check
on the test results.
Sure thing.
Hey.
I loved what you did to Simonson.
I loved it.
So where's the cash?
Made a very sizable donation
to the Riverside Park Fund.
- I didn't tell you to...
- You didn't say anything about the money.
Anyway, I'm finished with you.
Like hell you are.
Your father's an old man. Your sister-in-law
can't watch your nephew all the time.
What now?
I want the list of my
opponent's campaign contributors...
...and any other dirt
you can dig up on Paul Van Duzer.
Van Duzer's the cleanest politician
this town has seen in years.
Nobody's completely honest, Barry.
Everybody's got something to hide, right?
Password.
"A.S."
Arthur Simonson?
Running with a dangerous crowd,
Castillo.
Certain doors have to be closed.
Take out Megan Lockhart.
And since information is valuable
only if it's exclusive...
... get rid of Christina McGee.
- Dr. McGee.
- Why aren't you two in radiation suits?
Weren't you told about the leak?
Excuse me,
what are you people doing in my lab?
Come on, McGee,
they're trying to kill us.
- Heather!
- I'll explain later.
- I have nothing to say to you.
- Shut up and listen. She just saved my life.
- I checked on Castillo...
- He's in bed with Simonson.
- That's why he's never been convicted.
- Barry, stop. What is going on here?
I think I've got this thing figured.
There's a bill in the state senate
to legalize gambling.
And that would put Simonson's
illegal casinos out of business.
Right. So he hires Spanier
to torch the waterfront.
Then he buys it dirt cheap,
using a phony corporation to cover his tail.
Then when the gambling bill passes,
lo and behold...
...Simonson has valuable property,
perfect for a major casino strip.
Putting him back in business,
bigger than ever.
That's the gold ring
Castillo's looking for?
Yeah. Just got a call from my informer.
The firebug's headed to the waterfront.
If I can catch him,
I can bring this scheme down.
Simonson and Castillo both.
- Let me help.
- Forget it.
Does that weird you out?
All the time.
I beheld Satan
as lightning falls from earth!
I told you to put the screws
to the senator.
- What are you stalling for?
- I know what I'm doing.
I don't need anyone to tell me
how to run my business.
You've been sitting on your hands.
The moment's passing.
A little patience goes a long way.
The hell with patience. You've had
Senator Clark on your payroll for years.
Can't move on the gambling bill
until after the election.
Then I say we push him right now.
He don't play, we roll right over him.
Slow down!
I've spent too many years on this...
...to see you blow it. You want it all,
but you can barely handle...
...what you've got.
- That's right, what I've got.
Oh, mine enemy!
I'm not ready for eternity yet!
Shut the hell up.
Listen to me, Spanier, who hired you?
- Who hired you?!
- Arthur Simonson.
Tell that to the police, or I'll be back.
He's the one, officer.
He's been torching the waterfront.
But he didn't get my cannery.
No, sir.
- Gosh, ma'am, how did you manage this?
- The Flash did it.
I seen him with my own eyes.
The angel of Satan, red as the devil!
Ah, nuts. Who had Pier 23
in the office pool, Bellows?
Get out of here.
No more calls. We have a winner.
Was every job I did for you a crime?
You know this woman?
She's got enough on this
to lock us both away for life.
The awful truth is I used you
because nobody's gonna miss you...
...one way or the other.
- You pig!
Get her out of here.
- Kill her and dump her in the river.
- Slime dog.
Watch out, Red!
- I thought you worked for Castillo.
- I don't work for anybody.
Take this.
You've just been closed down.
Tie him up.
I've got to go after Castillo.
- He'll expose you.
- I know.
I have to risk it.
- End of the line, Castillo.
- No way, Barry. You're a boy scout.
You believe in that whole
"good guy, bad guy" rap.
I open my mouth, they'll be all over you.
The mob doesn't get you...
...you'll end up dissected by the feds.
The only way to stop me is to kill me.
And you won't.
Castillo was out of his league
from word one.
Mob justice.
Yeah, you got that right.
Simonson wasn't about
to take orders from Castillo.
That's the problem with secret lives,
they can really screw you up.
You know, I still resent you for
poking around in my personal life.
Yeah, and if I hadn't, you never
would have nailed Simonson and Castillo...
...not to mention Spanier.
Yeah, but how can I be sure
you're not gonna blow my cover...
...the minute you leave town?
- You did save my life.
It's a heavy marker, wouldn't you say?
Yeah, but I need to be sure.
You might just trust me a little
after all that's gone on.
Look, this is really hard for me to say...
...but you taught me a real lesson
when you zoomed...
...into that hot-sheet hotel. I can't go
traipsing through other people's lives...
...until I figure out
what I should be doing with my own.
I got to take responsibility
for my actions.
Here's every frame I ever shot of you.
I fudged the computer records to blur
any connection between you and the Flash.
But you still got to watch out
for that cute little red behind of yours.
To think,
I was just about to ask you out.
It wasn't dinner and a movie...
...but I'd call an evening's action
at a local hot spot...
...one hell of a first date.
- Yeah?
That's all for now.
- I'm not that kind of girl.
- Well, it's never too late to start.
[ENGLISH]
www.tvsubtitles.net