BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
...but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
NARRATOR:
Previously on The Flash:
Iris West.
I hear you've been writing about me.
-I collect posts about the Streak.
-There's no Streak.
IRIS:
I saw him, Barry. He wears a red suit.
I've finally diagnosed why Iris
is writing about the Streak.
She's doing it for me.
I'm gonna find out who really killed Nora
and I'm going to get you out of here.
Whoever the Streak is, I am not stopping
until the rest of the world believes in him.
Maybe we shouldn't see each other
for a while.
IRIS: To understand what I'm about
to tell you, you need to do something first.
You need to believe in the impossible.
Can you do that? Good.
Because all of us,
we have forgotten what miracles look like.
Maybe because they haven't made
much of an appearance lately. Our lives...
...have become ordinary.
But there is someone out there
who is truly extraordinary.
I don't know where you came from.
I don't know your name.
But I have seen you do the impossible
to protect the city I love.
So for those of us who believe in you,
and what you're doing, I just wanna say:
Thank you.
Heh.
[SIGHS]
You're welcome.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
How did you--? I literally just hit send.
Speed reading.
It's crazy what you can do to your voice.
You need to stop writing your blog.
People need to know that you exist.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
What else can you do?
-This is not an interview.
-Come on, you gotta give me something.
Hobbies, pet peeves, favorite color.
-Wait, scratch that last one. Red. Obviously.
-You're not hearing me.
My hearing is fine, it's just selective.
What should I call you?
Anything but the Streak.
Fine. Suggestions?
You said you were writing about me
to bring hope to someone you care about.
How would he feel if doing that
put you in harm's way?
He and I aren't exactly on the same page
these days.
Besides, you're giving hope
to a lot of people.
So I'm doing this for them.
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING NEARBY]
To be continued. Gotta run.
Wait. You can't just leave me up--
Here. Wow.
Woo-hoo!
-What kind of a tool steals a yellow Humvee?
-What kind of tool buys a yellow Humvee?
-Get these people back.
-I need everybody back.
Son! Out of the way! Out of the way!
What the hell?
Eddie, Eddie.
Yeah.
Step out of the vehicle.
If you say so.
Uh-oh.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
Looks like you were born to take a beating.
Check the math.
Your dispersal models don't correlate.
Uh, they do if you factor in the seasonal
fluctuations in reproduction cycles.
What are we debating?
The average number of bugs
Barry swallows in a day of running.
I look forward to seeing you accept
your Nobel.
Barry?
Barry, are you okay?
[GASPS]
Thirteen fractures. That's a new record.
And that's just in your hand.
You also have a concussion,
three cracked ribs and a bruised spleen.
Even with your powers,
you'll need a few hours to heal.
-What exactly did you hit?
-A man. A big, bad man.
His skin changed when I hit him.
Like it turned to metal.
Interesting. A man of steel.
So you went after a meta-human alone?
-Dude, why didn't you call us?
-I didn't know what he was.
[GRUNTS]
Besides, I was off duty.
Hmm.
Lucky he didn't knock out your teeth.
Those puppies don't grow back.
-Strange thing is I feel like I knew him.
-What do you mean?
He said something that was familiar.
But he's gonna hurt someone.
So how do I fight a guy that's made of steel?
-We will find a way. Tonight, you heal.
-Yeah.
YOUNG BARRY: There was lightning
in my house. Yellow-and-red lightning.
There was a man in yellow.
Then I was on the street.
I don't know how I got there.
Please, you have to believe me.
Hey.
-What happened to you last night?
-Got beat up by a steel-plated sociopath.
Good times.
-So he is meta-human.
-Yeah.
That particle accelerator
is the gift that keeps on giving.
-You okay?
-Relatively.
Any idea who he is?
Eddie's taking point
while I run down a lead.
-I need you to work with him until I get back.
-Why me?
Because he saw something impossible
that he's got questions about.
Questions that I can't answer.
In other words, make up
some science-y stuff to throw him off.
Exactly.
Heh.
He stole the Humvee and evaded capture.
So pleased you could join us, Mr. Allen.
Rough night?
Uh, just a little beat, sir.
As I was saying, our perp yanked
three ATMs after he boosted the vehicle.
ATM security cameras caught him on video.
We got a hit in the database.
Tony Woodward. History of violence,
petty theft, assault, going way back to juvie.
Dropped off the radar 10 months ago.
Looks like he's back.
Increased pressure produces heat, and
if you don't release it, you get combustion.
I don't know how do you remember
all this stuff, Barry.
Because he's a little freak.
Just like his old man.
-Don't talk about my dad.
-Or what?
Is he going to murder me too?
Looks like you were born
to take a beating, Allen.
EDDIE:
Allen.
Hey, Allen.
-Hey.
-You okay?
Hey, yeah. Sorry, Eddie.
Listen, I saw something last night
I just can't get my head around.
Uh-huh.
I fired a dozen rounds at our car thief
and it was like they sparked off of him.
Huh.
Well, I mean, he must have been
wearing some kind of body armor.
On his face?
-Um....
IRIS: Hey.
Barry.
Hi, babe, I saw the news. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Which you'd know if you checked
your messages. I tried you three times.
Sorry, I had to work late.
Um, so I heard that the Streak saved a kid.
Any comment, detective?
All I know is our perp got away.
But Barry here is gonna help me find him.
-Yeah.
-Fine.
I have other sources. I will see you tonight.
-Bye.
-What is going on with you two?
-What do you mean? Nothing.
It's fine. It's-- It's fine. I don't know.
Okay.
-Dr. Wells.
-I guess you heard about...
...Barry's incident last night.
If you're looking for him, he's at the station.
I came here to see you.
-I need your help solving an old case.
-What case is that?
The murder of Barry's mother.
Your childhood nemesis
is now an unstoppable meta-human.
-That is seriously messed up.
-I had a childhood nemesis.
Lexi La Roche.
She used to put gum in my hair.
Jake Puckett.
If I didn't let him copy my homework,
he'd give me a swirly.
Now that we've established
that we're all uber-nerds...
-...what are we gonna do about Tony?
-Glad you asked.
We're gonna train you, man.
Karate Kid style.
Behold.
-I call him Girder.
-For the record, not my idea.
Fighting is physics.
It's not about strength, it's not about size,
it's about energy and power.
Channel your speed the right way,
you can totally take this bad boy down.
Now, obviously,
your Girder is a moving target.
So....
I have ice and bandages standing by.
[GROANING]
I'm pretty sure
I just dislocated my shoulder.
[SHOUTING]
Okay, not gonna lie. This is
gonna be quick but extremely painful.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Oh, speaking of pain. Eddie, hey.
EDDIE: We found the stolen Humvee
in the alley at Fremont and Lawrence.
-Need you down here to do your thing.
-Great, I'll see you in a sec.
Okay. Okay, let's do this.
So, Barry, when you said
you were off duty last night...
...you weren't visiting Iris again,
you know, in disguise?
That would be reckless and a little creepy.
-Nope.
-Good.
[SHOULDER CRACKS
THEN BARRY SCREAMS]
EDDIE: Allen, you really need a car.
BARRY: I usually manage on foot okay.
What do we got?
The rig Tony Woodward
boosted last night.
No sign of the stolen ATMs,
probably got those where he's holed up.
Though he's going to have
one hell of a time breaking them open.
I wouldn't be so sure.
-So about you and Iris.
-Look, Eddie, we had a fight...
...and I just don't really feel comfortable
talking about it with you.
I get that. And I get that you two
go way back.
To be honest,
I was a little threatened by you at first.
-You were threatened by me?
-Sure.
I mean, I've seen how close you two are,
but you seem like a good guy...
...and Iris, I just want her to be happy.
From my experience...
-...good friends are hard to find.
MAN: Detective. Excuse me.
Sir, we ran the plates on that Humvee....
-Come on, Barry, you can do it.
-Bar, focus.
-I am.
-Son, son, you're getting frustrated.
You need to learn
how to control your emotions.
-Iris, come here, sweetie.
-You want me to hit a girl?
He wants you to try.
Relax, Barry, I've had her in gloves
since she was 6.
She's tougher than she looks.
[GRUNTING]
Sorry, Barry.
Son, sometimes the best way
to win a fight is not to start one...
...but if you do come up against somebody
you know you can't beat, be smart.
It's okay to run the other way.
All right?
EDDIE:
So, what do you think?
Judging by the mud and kegs...
...I'd say he got hammered,
stole a big-ass truck and went joy-riding.
I bet the kegs are stolen too. Rusty Iron Ale.
It's a microbrew right over in--
-Keystone. I know it. Let's check it out.
-Yeah.
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Barry described a tornado
of red-and-yellow lightning...
...inside a man in yellow.
Then, bam, he's blocks away, on the street,
doesn't know how he got there.
-When I arrived, the place was a wreck.
-Nora Allen is dead.
Single stab wound to the heart.
Henry Allen covered in her blood.
Despite all the evidence
that Henry is guilty...
...now you believe this man in yellow
is responsible?
Last night I saw Barry rescue
a young boy from being run over...
...and it looked exactly like
what Barry described happened to him.
It got me thinking, what if somebody
with Barry's abilities killed Nora?
There's just one flaw with your theory, detective,
and that is that all of this happened 14 years ago.
Which is long before--
-Your machine gave Barry powers.
-An accident gave Barry powers.
Do you think it is possible
that somebody with Barry's super speed...
...could have existed before the explosion?
Detective, I deal in probabilities
as a scientist.
And in this case, it's highly unlikely.
Gentlemen. C.C.P.D. Any chance some of
your merchandise was stolen last night?
No. I don't think so.
How about this guy. You seen him?
You know Tony, don't you?
Hey.
Allen, come on.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
-Allen, you okay?
-Oh, never better.
-Get up.
-Unh. I didn't do nothing, man.
So why did you run?
-Look, it was an accident.
-What was?
Tony falling, okay?
-But I swear to God, we didn't kill him.
-Keep talking.
About 10 months ago, Keystone Ironworks.
Boss was handing out pink slips.
Tony gets his and he just snapped.
He started beating the crap out of the guy.
We pulled him off.
Then the lights went out,
some kind of power surge...
...and Tony went over the railing
right into a vat of molten scrap.
-Just gone.
-Lucky for you, he's still alive.
What?
-How did you get in front of us?
-Shortcut.
[TERRAPLANE SUN'S "GENERATION
BLUES" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I've been meaning to ask you,
where's your shadow?
-What shadow?
-Barry.
-He hasn't been in all week.
-Getting his fix somewhere else.
Too bad. He's cute.
I kind of miss having him around.
Iris? Long time, no see.
I gotta say, Iris, you look amazing.
-Thanks, Tony. Um, you too.
-Oh. Yeah, I keep in shape.
Got a gym at my place.
Been living out in Keystone. The west side.
You should, uh, stop by sometime.
So, uh, can I get you a drink?
No, I came to see you.
-How did you know I was here?
-Been reading up on the Streak.
Found your little blog.
-Why are you writing about this guy?
-People say that he's a hero.
I say he's a coward.
I happen to know that he took a beating
last night and ran off like a little girl.
You should write about that.
Do you, uh, have any idea
who leather boy is?
No clue.
So, um, if you don't want to drink,
I should get back to work.
Actually, I'd prefer to buy you a drink.
What time are you off?
Thanks, Tony, but I don't think my boyfriend
would approve.
-He's a cop, like my dad.
-I never really did like cops too much.
STACY:
Iris.
Well, he's picking me up
for the policeman's ball.
Wall-to-wall cops, can't swing a cat,
I should call to see where he is.
Give me the phone, Iris. Now!
Sorry.
For the damage.
We'll pick this up some other time.
CISCO:
Barry. Check it out.
The gravel you pulled from Tony's ride?
It contains 76.8 percent hematite...
...consistent with the mines
at Keystone Ironworks.
Which closed down 10 months ago.
It's the perfect hideout.
Barry? Do you mind telling me about this?
"I have info about someone
you're looking for. He was here.
You know where to find me."
Now who could she be talking to?
-I guess you got my message.
-Are you okay?
Cop's daughter. I can handle myself.
-Not with this guy.
-I knew him when we were kids.
He didn't want to hurt me.
He wanted to impress me.
But he is fixated on you
and not in a good way.
Do you know where he went?
Said he had a place in West Keystone.
Bragged about how big it was,
but I have no idea where.
-I do.
-Wait. There's something else.
His hand, it transformed.
Like an iron fist.
-He's like you, isn't he?
-Yes.
And writing about me
is what brought him to you.
-I know but maybe I can talk to him--
-No.
He's too dangerous.
Damn, that's my ride.
Eddie insisted on a detail. I have to...
...go.
Barry, talk to us. What are you doing?
Dude, don't run angry.
We don't know how to defeat him yet.
This is definitely the place.
You're trespassing, freak.
There's nowhere left to run.
CAITLIN: Barry?
CISCO: Barry, where are you?
Caitlin, over here.
Barry?
Please say something.
Say something so we know you're okay.
[GRUNTS]
-Ow.
-Get him out of there.
What were you thinking?
I told you that we would figure out
a way to deal with him.
-I'll heal.
-You can't heal when you're dead.
-He could have killed you.
-I know, all right? I know.
In the past 36 hours,
I've had my ass handed to me twice...
...by the guy that tortured me as a kid.
I couldn't stop him then
and I can't stop him now.
Even with my powers,
I'm still powerless against him.
Not necessarily. Cisco.
Any material,
if struck at a high enough velocity...
...can be compromised.
CISCO: We ran an analysis on the metal
in Tony's footprint.
Based on its density and atomic structure,
if you impact it at just the right angle...
...at just the right speed,
you could do some serious damage.
-How fast would I have to go?
-Factoring in the metal's tensile strength...
...estimated dermal thickness,
atmospheric pressure, air temp...
...you'd have to hit him at approximately...
...Mach 1.1.
You want Barry to hit something
at 800 miles an hour?
-Eight hundred thirty-seven, actually.
-That's faster than the speed of sound.
I know. He would create a sonic boom,
which, as I said before, would be awesome.
-I've never gone that fast.
-Yet.
I can't believe we're actually
entertaining this idea.
I mean, he'd need a straight shot
from miles away.
Yeah, 5.3 miles, theoretically.
Do it right, you'll take him down.
Do it wrong,
you'll shatter every bone in your body.
-Barry.
-Joe, I've been beaten enough for one day.
-I gotta--
-Hey, wait.
An anonymous tip led us
to Tony Woodward's hideout.
The place was trashed. What happened?
He showed up at Jitters to see Iris.
I had to go after him.
-Iris? Where is she?
-She's fine, she's fine.
Eddie put a detail on her to be safe.
I thought I could handle him this time.
I tried.
Look, I know what this punk
put you through...
...but you can't let emotion
cloud yourjudgment.
Toll-booth camera got a shot of Woodward.
Stolen car headed out of town.
State police are taking over. We lost him.
Don't worry, Eddie. They'll get him.
-I wanted to take this guy down.
-Not half as much as I did.
-Let's go, Allen.
-Go where?
Blow off some steam.
I need to hit something.
-What?
-I don't think he meant hit you. Go.
So I heard you and this Woodward guy
have a history.
Hey, Allen, it's okay.
Trust me, I had my fair share of bullies
at school.
Somehow I find that hard to believe.
I was short, fat, and the son of a politician
who closed a factory in my school district.
So not so popular.
So, what did you do about it?
I got my ass kicked. A lot.
Until my gym coach took pity on me. Ha, ha.
She said the key to fighting is patience.
Here.
A lot of guys waste energy
trying to land the most punches.
All it takes is one.
But you gotta make it count.
Choose your spot and drive through it.
Like it's 6 inches behind the target.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Harder.
[EDDIE COUGHING]
The seam was starting to split.
[CHUCKLES]
Appreciate you coming down.
Mm. These days, it's rare to find someone
happy to have a drink with me.
Well, our conversation yesterday
got me thinking.
You said as a scientist,
you look for the probable.
That's right.
And we've both recently seen things
that have redefined what is possible.
Yes, we have, and we both know
the direct cause of those things.
Your accelerator explosion.
Evolutionary leaps follow the creation
of new technologies. It's that simple.
Like the Roomba. Ha-ha-ha.
Yes, like the Roomba.
So humor me here.
If we know that...
...meta-humans were created
by the particle accelerator...
...and testimony shows that a meta-human
may have been involved...
...in the murder of Barry Allen's mother
14 years ago...
...it seems to me that way back then...
...there must have been
another particle accelerator.
Another particle accelerator?
Mm.
I can assure you that's extremely unlikely,
detective, and if there were...
...I don't recall any dark-matter
lightning storms before I moved to town.
Do you?
No.
No, I don't.
When did you move to town, Dr. Wells?
Something tells me that you already know
the answer to that question, detective.
This whole "help you solve
the murder of Nora Allen"....
You were never looking for my help,
were you?
You opened your lab
a month after Nora Allen's murder.
You mind telling me what you were doing
in Central City before that?
I was starting over.
Starting what over?
Well, here I thought we were just
two guys having a friendly drink.
You want answers, detective?
Tess Morgan. Look her up.
MAN [ON RADIO]: Unit 52, this is Dispatch.
Requesting status on the West house.
Hey, Iris.
-Nice, Allen. All right.
-Yeah. Okay.
Hey, next time work on your speed.
Yeah. I'll do my best.
Thawne, Allen.
The unit watching Joe's daughter,
they've been attacked.
Iris is missing.
Go, all right? I'll call Joe.
Let's adjust the impact angle by 0.2 degrees,
up the speed to 838....
Bam.
-Ouch.
-Ouch?
BARRY [OVER PHONE]: Guys, you there?
-Yeah, man. What's up?
Tony took Iris. I need you to do
whatever you can to help me find her.
-Satellites, security cameras, hack them all.
CISCO: We're on it.
What's wrong?
Remember this place, Iris?
So, what's the plan here, Tony?
Finally gonna go for that G.E.D.?
You want a plan?
You used to write about the Streak, right?
-Now you're gonna write about me.
-You just abducted me, Tony.
-Why would I do that?
-Because the Streak is dead.
-No.
-Yeah.
Squashed like a little bug, by me.
If you don't want the same thing
to happen to you, tell the world...
...that there's a new big man on campus!
And I'm just getting started.
You could have anybody
write about you, Tony. Why me?
Because I like you, Iris. Always have.
You should have said something.
[FIRE ALARM RINGING]
You try anything like that again
and I'm gonna leave more than a bruise.
[ALARM STOPS]
Eddie, anything yet?
We have roadblocks on every major artery.
Units are searching.
We will find Iris, Joe.
You don't think he'll hurt her, do you?
Sir. Sir. We got a fire alarm call
at Carmichael Elementary.
SINGH: Dispatch the fire department.
We'll send backup.
-That's the school you and Iris went to.
-And Tony.
Go.
Tony, turn yourself in before
things get worse. It's not too late.
Yeah, it is.
Cops are already looking for me.
So get ready to cover
the showdown of a lifetime...
...because I'm not going out without a fight.
Good, because you just found one.
You just won't stay dead.
Come to save your little fangirl?
This is between us. Let her go.
Oh, I could. But I'd rather make her watch
while I break every bone in your body.
-Wait here.
-Okay.
Too slow, Tin Man.
[SCREAMS]
I've known guys like you.
Peaked in high school, never got over it.
All these powers, and look at you.
Bully then, bully now.
[BOTH GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
He's hurt.
No!
If you do come up against somebody
you know you can't beat, be smart.
It's okay to run the other way.
[SCOFFS]
There goes your hero.
He made it out. Barely.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
-Why did he stop?
-He's miles away.
5.3 miles away.
-Barry, wait.
-No way. He's gonna do it.
Go, man, go!
Supersonic punch, baby! Whoo!
[GRUNTING]
Nice cross.
-I think I broke my hand.
-Me too.
Hey!
What is this? Where the hell am I?
Somewhere you'll never hurt anyone
ever again.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You know who I am.
Allen?
The thing that happened to you, Tony,
it happened to me too.
But it didn't just give us abilities.
It made us more of who we are.
You got strong.
I got fast.
Fast enough to beat you.
You used your gift to hurt people.
Not anymore.
Allen.
Allen, don't walk away from me, Allen!
Hey! Come back here!
Allen! Allen!
[GRUNTS]
CISCO:
Dude. That had to feel great.
-You have no idea.
-Almost as good as proving me wrong...
...about the supersonic punch?
Actually, that part hurt. Like, a lot.
But I couldn't have done it
without you guys.
All I wanna know is, which childhood bully
are we gonna take down next?
-Mine or Caitlin's?
-Oh, yeah.
I vote mine. What? Guys, this is not a joke.
-Doctor.
WELLS: Detective.
Are you here to make more accusations?
I'm here to make amends.
I looked up Tess Morgan.
Sorry for your loss.
You two were research partners
in Maryland?
Yes, we were. We were married to the work
as much as to each other.
After the car accident,
I could not go back to the work.
Could not go back to our lab.
So you moved here.
Where no one knew me.
Where no one could remind me
of what I had lost.
And I've found it difficult.
Starting over, you know...
...rebuilding.
And what took me 14 years,
Tess could have done in four.
Believe me, she....
At the time of Nora Allen's murder...
...the particle accelerator
that I would eventually create...
...was but a notion, much less a reality.
And so whomever,
or whatever is responsible for her death...
...it did not originate from me
or from my work.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
But I hope I can still count on your help.
[CHUCKLES]
-You don't give up, do you?
-Nope.
Not till I get my man.
I owe that to Barry and to Henry.
Barry is lucky to have you on his side, Joe.
[SPOON'S "DO YOU"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Yeah I knew that you saw me
You laughed when I looked back
Hi.
Oh, I thought that you were someone else.
So Joe told me what happened.
How's the hand?
Not broken, so that's something. Heh.
Do you want to get understood?
-I should have believe--
-I'm sorry I said--
I've missed you.
Yeah, I've missed you too.
When I heard Tony took you, I....
I just-- I don't know what I would do
if anything happened to you.
Well, my guardian angel
is looking out for me.
Do you wanna hang out, catch up?
Yeah. I would like that, yeah.
I promise not to talk about
the Streak tonight.
No, I want you to. No, I mean, you can--
I want you to talk about
whatever you wanna talk about.
-I know it's important to you.
-Good, because it's not just the Streak.
There are others out there that are like him.
I've gotten scattered posts about this guy
that's on fire, except that he doesn't burn up.
Okay, wait, wait.
You're trying to find
the Burning Man now too?
Yeah, why not? I mean, a lot can happen
in a week, especially with the Streak.
Yeah.
I've been trying to get answers.
Where does he come from?
How does he do what he does?
But he dodges everything, literally...
...with this super-speed power.
When he moves, Barry,
you don't even see him.
He comes and goes in the blink of an eye,
in a--
Flash?
In a flash.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah. Heh.
Today, I was saved by the impossible.
A mystery man.
The fastest man alive.
Then a friend gave me an idea
for a new name.
And something tells me it's gonna catch on.