Of course I'm really here. Barr.
You sounding kinda strange. You okay?
[WHOOSHES]
[PANTING]
I am now, yeah.
Yeah... okay.
You wanna tell me
what's really going on?
You don't remember either.
[SIGHS]
Thawne.
Uh, he...
He changed things.
Made me think I was crazy.
He took away my life,
piece by piece, until I lost everything.
Thawne started his
own Reverse-Flashpoint.
Joe, you died.
Uh...
well, I'm so sorry
you went through that.
Hey, listen to me.
I'm here now, and I'm
not going anywhere.
I know, it's just...
seeing you again after
everything that's happened...
- [CHUCKLES]
- It's just...
I can finally breathe again.
Nothing like a second shot at life.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Barry, why is there a supervillain
standing in my living room?
Thank you, but I'm not
here to cause trouble.
Damien, how are you still here?
I don't know.
My theory, I was connected
to the time stone you were wearing.
And when you created a portal,
it drew me to 2021 also.
Although I haven't faded
yet, I'm sure I soon will.
- And once you do...
- I die.
But my daughter, Nora, lives.
Only that hasn't happened
yet, and I don't know why.
Maybe if I had the time stone.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
That was handy.
Damien, what you're doing now...
I'm no hero, Barry.
I'm just a dad.
♪
[WHOOSHES]
- Freeze!
- [GUNS COCKING]
- You're under arrest.
- For what, officers?
I haven't even done anything.
Yet.
And do you want to know why?
Because I'm not ready to die yet.
[GUNFIRE]
I can't believe everything
that you went through.
I mean, these last few
days have been so... normal.
Boring, even.
I mean, I'm glad nobody remembers.
And Frost and Chillblaine were married.
- Apparently.
- That's insane.
What about Chuck and
me? What were we doing?
I mean, same as now, I guess.
I don't know, I mean, we
weren't really teammates
in that other timeline, so...
I do know Chester helped build
the energy absorption
tech that saved the world.
Hold on.
There you go.
Holy Ron Mallett. This
circuitry is next level.
Okay, nice work, future me,
but is it okay that I have this?
I don't want to start,
like, a Chester P-point.
I mean, maybe just don't
talk about it on your podcast.
Ah, got you.
Well, Barr, you risked everything
to prevent Armageddon
and gave all of us a second chance.
And we are really damn grateful,
especially me.
Ditto.
You really are a true hero, Barry.
[PHONE BUZZING]
It's Taylor with a news alert.
Thawne is at CCPD.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪
[ALL GRUNTING]
Uh-uh. I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, why did I do that?
Well, I did it to draw out your hero!
What is taking him so long?
You want a hero?
♪
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
You.
You know, normally, I'd be intrigued
to meet the great Green Arrow,
but unfortunately, today,
I don't have the time.
- Where's William?
- Who's William?
Wrong answer.
- [GASPS]
- Oopsie.
That's a temporal fade, pal.
Looks like you're not too
much longer for this timeline.
Too bad.
Now, where the hell's my brother?
Enough with the questions.
Sorry, kid...
[WHIRRING]
But I don't have time for family drama.
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Stay down, Thawne.
Flash.
♪
I didn't come here to fight.
I came here to make a scene, publicly,
so that there would be witnesses
for what I have to ask you.
What is it?
I need you to save me.
♪
So Thawne messed with the timeline.
No wonder I picked up
on his temporal energy.
He must be loaded with it.
Is that why you're here in 2021?
No, I tracked Thawne's scent by mistake.
I was looking for something else.
Maybe we can help?
I'm Chester P., by the way. New guy.
And it is so cool to meet
the future Green Arrow.
Mia Queen,
progeny of Felicity
Smoak and Oliver Queen.
I know all the stories.
Yeah, not all the stories.
Look, what did Thawne mean
when he said, "save me"?
Save him from what?
You see how he's fading in and out?
Same thing happened to me
in his Reverse-Flashpoint.
He's being erased.
Once the process is complete, he'll die.
So when you removed Thawne's changes,
the timeline decided to remove him too.
Yeah.
Okay, but when Thawne died,
he came back somehow after Eddie.
I mean, could that happen again?
No, this is different.
When I reset the timeline,
I used Damien's time stone.
It eliminated all
possible time variables,
restoring a single,
permanent timeline again.
- This one.
- So if he dies this time...
It's game over for good.
Okay. I need to call Frost.
If we're gonna decide
what to do about Thawne,
- we need the whole team here.
- Wait a minute.
You're not actually
considering saving him, are you?
Mia, we know that Thawne is bad,
but we still need to talk this through
before we make any decisions.
[SCOFFS] Fine.
If that's how you guys do things.
But you're making a big mistake.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I will go talk to her.
Can you see if you can find out
how much time Thawne has left?
♪
[PANTING]
You want something?
Mia, you never said
why you came to 2021,
but I'm guessing it's important.
So what is going on?
I'm here to find my brother.
William's missing.
I just hit another dead end.
What happened?
[SIGHS]
It was the night I
decided to put on the suit.
♪
William and I went to see Dad's statue,
but we were attacked.
William!
I haven't seen my brother since.
I've been looking for him for two years.
I'm so sorry.
Found a temporal energy
signature at the crime scene
which led me here, but
every trail goes cold.
Now, this is all I have left of him.
William gave it to me
the night he was taken.
Sometimes I wonder
if it's connected to
why he's still gone.
Have you asked Felicity for help?
She wouldn't understand what
I've had to do to get this far.
What is that supposed to mean?
- Mia, have you...
- Killed anyone?
I will if I have to, for William's sake.
Sometimes, blood for
blood is the answer.
You know, your dad thought
the same thing once.
That in order to protect his city,
he had to take lives,
but all he ended up
doing was ruining his own.
I think you know that,
or else you wouldn't be so
afraid to go see your mom.
You're the one who's afraid.
Thawne killed your dad
and then tricked you
into almost marrying him,
all the while making you believe
you had a choice in it all.
You, Iris West-fracking-Allen.
And now you're too afraid
to give him what he deserves.
You think my life will
be ruined if I kill?
What about yours if you don't?
'Cause it sounds like you'd be
a lot better off if he was gone.
♪
How much longer do I have?
Best I can tell, two hours,
and then you'll fade away.
Two hours until you
save me, right, Caitlin?
Because you, Barry, and Team Flash,
you're the good guys.
You'll do the right thing.
Some of us might surprise you.
Not you. You're a
doctor. You won't kill me.
No, I won't.
But I can accept it when someone dies.
Is that right?
Maybe you forget,
I know the real Caitlin Snow.
You're right where you were
eight years ago, remember?
Living your safe,
orderly life.
Preparing for a perfect future
with your idiot fiancé.
And then... [MIMICS EXPLOSION]
It all came crashing down.
What is wrong with you?
Ronnie was my whole future,
and he is never coming back.
"He's never coming
back." That's what happens.
What about you?
You could've moved on.
I mean, you should've moved on. Right?
But instead, you're
stuck here where you were
eight years ago helping Team Flash
and Barry Allen instead of
getting on with your life.
Fine.
You want honesty?
When I was a resident,
fresh out of med school,
one of the first things they taught me
is that sometimes, you lose a patient.
That death is a part of life.
So guess what?
It's your turn,
because all the speed
in the world
can't help you outrun
what's coming for you.
You'll save me.
You'll save me, Snow.
You don't have a choice.
AND ANOTHER THING: I stayed here
because Barry and the rest of the team,
they're not just
friends, they're family.
And just so we're clear,
what I've been doing
for the last eight years
is hating you.
So if you're looking
for someone to save you,
look somewhere else.
♪
You okay?
What happened?
We need to let Thawne die.
♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
Caitlin told me about your talk.
Something I want to know.
Why did you create a Reverse-Flashpoint,
steal my life?
Why?
It was the best way to hurt you.
Don't you have anything better to do
than trying to destroy my life?
Destroying you is my life. [GROANS]
That still doesn't explain why.
Why what?
What did I ever do to you?
Almost two centuries
from right now,
we meet for the very first time.
For my part,
I'd finally discovered
ways to possess speeds.
Speeds faster than anyone alive.
And just as I was about
to present myself to the world...
[SIGHS]
You showed up
in pursuit of some stupid
case, dazzled the crowd.
Ah, you were dazzling.
And then... and then
you saved the crowd.
A crowd that I was meant to save.
A crowd that was meant to thank me.
You stole my greatest moment.
I admired you.
And you humiliated me.
And it was in that moment that I knew
that I had to get faster than you.
Only a sociopath
would react to something so small
with that kind of rage.
What you call rage...
I call commitment.
So if you won't stop hating me,
what happens once I save you?
I'll just go on with my life's work:
finding new ways to kill you.
♪
You know what to do, Flash.
What are you doing here?
I went to the future to see for myself
whether or not Armageddon
had been prevented.
- Then you know that it was.
- Yes.
But I also witnessed
the return of your rival.
You must know as long
as Eobard Thawne lives,
he can still bring
about another Armageddon.
So what do you want me to do?
Listen to your friend. Let him die.
If you want him dead so much,
why don't you just kill him yourself?
I would,
but he could come back as he did before.
This is the only way to
assure his absolute death.
You know it's the right
thing to do, Flash.
You can't be serious.
You can't just let Thawne die.
I gave him a chance
to prove he can change.
He can't.
So what, we just kill him?
Thawne messed with the timeline,
and now the timeline is fighting back.
I say we let it.
Me too.
Look, Thawne did this to himself,
and it's not like we can save him,
so it's time to let him go.
Look, I know that we're the new kids
and we don't have the
same history with Thawne,
but that's a good thing,
because I don't care who Thawne is.
I care who you guys are,
and you save people.
- I know because you saved me.
- And me, literally.
You're right. You are the new kids.
And so when it comes
to Thawne, I'm sorry,
but you don't get a say.
Iris,
maybe we should think about this.
We already have.
You guys don't understand
what Thawne's capable of.
It's time to keep everyone safe
by finally letting Thawne die.
Barry, Iris, we need to talk.
Now.
Yeah.
What the hell is wrong with you two?
Since when do we let people die?
- Dad, you know who Thawne is.
- Yeah, I do.
And that man came to you for help,
which means you're obligated
to try and save him.
Joe, he killed you.
No, I know you don't remember, but I do.
If we don't let this happen now,
our family will never be safe.
You don't think I want
to see him dead either?
'Cause I do.
If I learned one thing being a cop,
it's that you can't just protect
the people you think are good.
You have to protect everyone.
That's what heroes do.
- I know that.
- Do you?
A hero is not just in the name, Barry,
or in a red suit.
It's the choices we make that decide
who and what we become.
- You know that.
- Dad, we don't have a choice.
Thawne isn't giving us one.
You always have a choice!
[SIGHS]
Now, did either one of you
even try to think of a way to save him?
You already found one.
Yeah.
We could save him if
we take his speed away,
permanently.
Just like Jefferson Pierce did to you.
[SMACKS TABLE]
- Listen, Joe, wait...
- Hey.
Uh-uh.
This decision is for the two of you.
But I can tell you one
THING: if you let Thawne die,
you don't have to worry about
him destroying our family.
[SIGHS]
We have to talk to Caitlin.
Yeah.
♪
The heroes of this world have failed.
But if they won't end Thawne's existence,
then I, Despero, will take
matters into my own hands.
[ECHOING] Mia Queen.
Mia Queen.
And you're gonna help me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Barry, are you sure?
Yeah, look, if we're really heroes,
we can't turn our back on
anyone, including Thawne.
So you want to take away
his speed to save his life?
All right, what if it doesn't work?
It will.
Before the timeline
reset, Jefferson hit me
with enough continuous
voltage to nearly sever
my connection with the Speed Force.
Like blowing a fuse.
And you want to do the
same thing to Thawne.
And once his speed is gone,
A.R.G.U.S. will take him into custody.
We've already called Cisco.
Jail time won't make up for
all the lives he destroyed.
Look, you're right, but...
we can't let Thawne change who we are.
[ENERGY CRACKLES]
You're a fool.
Thawne must be erased from time itself.
Why can't you see that?
Despero, without his speed,
Thawne won't be a threat
to anyone ever again.
Thawne recovered his powers before.
This is your final warning, Flash.
Stand down and let Thawne die
or suffer the consequences.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
No.
♪
Barry!
It's not too late, Flash.
Let Thawne die so Armageddon can end.
Light up, Allegra. We're
going after Flash.
No, Barry can handle Despero.
You two protect Thawne no matter what.
- You sure, Boss?
- Yeah.
If Despero attacks us
too, we need to be ready.
- [SIGHS]
- What if Despero kills Barry?
I mean, they fought before,
and it wasn't exactly close.
Let's hope it goes better this time.
[ARROW BEEPS]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECH]
[BOTH GROANING]
I was right about you all along, Flash.
You are humanity's enemy.
I'm choosing to save a
life, Despero, not end one.
That's what heroes do.
But you've never been a hero, have you?
What are you implying?
What you told me about your home world,
that was all a lie, wasn't it?
You weren't the heroic rebel leader.
You were the despot.
The one who inflicted
pain and suffering.
Who killed to get what he wanted.
- I did what was necessary.
- No, you're wrong.
You've been wrong
this whole time about everything.
You're no hero, Despero.
You're just like Thawne.
Only in your eyes, Flash,
because I know what must be done.
The greater good that must be embraced
in order for this world to survive.
All that remains
is for me to show you.
♪
Chester, secure S.T.A.R. Labs.
Frack, we just lost power.
- What about Thawne?
- That's what's so weird.
Backup system just kicked in,
but only for the force field trap.
What? No, no.
That doesn't make any sense, unless...
It's Despero.
We're under attack.
Get down!
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
Mia, what the hell, girl?
[AS DESPERO] Iris West-Allen.
You and Flash made this decision.
And now you'll die for
making the wrong one.
♪
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
Mia, listen to me. This isn't you.
Mia.
Mia, she's right.
Take my power. Take my strength.
Fight him.
Empath.
You think I'd release
this perfect vessel?
Mia, stop.
I know you can fight this.
- The child is gone, human.
- No, she's not.
Mia, I know you can fight
this because you already have.
Look around... you could've
killed us all, but you didn't.
Mia, she's right.
Fight him.
Impossible.
[GROANS]
♪
Mia, think about William.
Is this the path that he
would want you to choose?
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[GROANING]
♪
[AS HERSELF] Iris.
Allegra, Frost, in the hallway.
I'll go check on them.
I'm so sorry.
[WHOOSHES]
My pawn failed. Your friends survived.
Mia?
What did you do?
Nothing compared to
what I'm going to do now.
I told you Thawne must die, and he will.
That's why I'm taking
matters into my own hands.
I'm going to be the hero
that this world needs, Flash.
Not you.
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so. I... what's going on?
I've got the secondary power
circuits up and running,
but I'm picking up insane
energy readings out there.
I'm talking, like, atomic
bomb level readings.
That's Despero.
He must be willing to
wipe out the whole city
to get what he wants.
He's gonna kill us all.
Just so Thawne will die.
♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- How's Mia?
- She's resting.
Frost is keeping an eye on her.
Thank goodness Iris
got to her before she...
Right, but what in the world
are we supposed to do now?
We beat Despero to the punch.
We whammy Thawne's speed right now,
make him a permanent jaywalker,
before Despero whammies us.
[PULSING]
It's okay, Cecile. We
all decided it together.
- Chester, where are we with...
- Project Whammy?
Well, I still have to
finish calibrating your suit.
Well, how much time do we have
before the timeline resets?
A few minutes, maybe less,
and only if Despero
doesn't wipe us out first.
Look, we are not losing today.
Not our city. Not a single life.
I don't know how, but
there's gotta be a way
to stop Despero long enough
for Chuck to do his thing,
so come on.
We're Team Flash.
What can we do?
The energy Despero's harnessing
is from his home world, Kalanor,
but, I mean, even if the energy's alien,
the flame of Py'tar is still a flame.
You can harness it with a vacuum.
And then disperse it,
but I... I'd still need a way to direct
all that energy into the atmosphere.
Wait, if a delivery
system is what you need,
then I got the ticket.
Okay, so you know how the
P.E.D. redirects energy?
Turns out the materials
in that puppy are damn versatile.
So I took the liberty of using them
to make these.
[GASPS] No way.
Chuck, you're amazing.
Yeah, I can work with these.
♪
They're a perfect fit, Chester.
Thanks. Now run, Boss, run.
♪
Now, Flash, your city dies
so that this planet's
future may survive.
♪
No!
[PANTING]
It's gone.
My connection to the flame!
Damn you, Flash.
It's over, Despero.
Flash, you've no idea what you've done.
I swear by the moons of Kalanor,
you'll pay for this.
This whole planet will.
[SCREAMS]
Flash, we got less than 30 seconds
to save Thawne before
the timeline resets.
All right, get ready,
Chester, I'm on my way.
My speed.
- I need more time.
- You're out of time, Thawne.
Calibration complete. Go for it.
On my mark, lower the shield.
♪
Now.
[SCREAMING]
♪
[GASPING]
There is no trace
of the Negative Speed
Force left in your body.
Barry, you did it.
What exactly... do
you think you've done?
We just saved your life, Thawne.
Don't make us regret it.
You think you saved my life?
You took my speed.
My speed is my life.
You took my life!
And left me in hell.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪
Now this is epic.
[MIMICKING ECHO] Epic, epic...
Wow, I don't know
what's more impressive.
- This place or us.
- Us, definitely.
I haven't been in a place this swank
since my debutante days.
Well, we have the place
to ourselves tonight.
And since Thawne's at A.R.G.U.S.
and Despero's finally gone...
For good, it seems like.
I figured we deserved a night off.
Look, about me going evil
and trying to kill you all...
Already forgiven.
We're just glad to
have the real Mia back.
And that, beautiful
people, is it for shop talk.
Yes, absolutely.
I think we've had enough of
aliens and evil speedsters.
Does that go for evil magicians too?
[TENSE MUSIC]
I know what you did to
Laurel Lance, Damien Darhk.
How about I return the favor?
By all means, go for it.
I thought I'd be a
dead man by now anyway.
♪
[SIGHS] I need a drink.
A real one.
- Damien, I'm sorry.
- Me too.
And now the timeline's
reset, I should be gone.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Damien, I don't know what to say.
You just did.
♪
[SMOOTH R&B MUSIC]
That aroma seems familiar.
Sebastian James?
My favorite scotch.
Did you guys always party this hard
after a successful mission?
[LAUGHTER]
[CHUCKLES] I wish.
By the way, I... I came across something
that might help you find William.
The symbol on the Hozen,
it matches a symbol from some
heavily redacted documents from Berlin.
Only my source couldn't find out more
thanks to some very intense firewalls.
You know, I think I know a hacker
who might be able to help me.
You're going to see Felicity?
You were right, Iris.
I can be the person she
always wanted me to be.
Thank you for helping
me find myself again.
You made the choice to be a hero.
Your dad would be proud.
And hey, you know,
don't be a stranger while
you're here in our time.
Bart and Nora, they drop in on us a lot,
and I think you guys would
get along really well.
- Anyways, cheers.
- Cheers.
[LIGHT JAZZ MUSIC]
♪
I know that look.
♪ Someone's got a crush ♪
[LAUGHING] No.
No, me and Allegra are just...
We're just friends.
- Sure. Sure.
- Yeah. Yeah.
She could be a lot more if you decided
to stop sipping root beer
and go put a move on her.
I'm a lot more intuitive than
people give me credit for.
Come on, go for it.
- Okay.
- You look great.
Moves, moves.
Put the moves, moves, moves.
- Hey, Allegra.
- Hi.
You look, uh... wow.
[CHUCKLES] Thanks, Chuck.
- Not bad yourself.
- Thank you.
Hey, I don't know
what's up with you two.
- What?
- What are you...
We're just standing here.
Like normal people.
- Normal. Normal.
- Both of us, man.
I just mean how you called
me out about Thawne earlier.
Oh, that.
I don't know what got into me.
No, I mean, you guys were right.
That's what I needed to hear.
So I just wanted to say thanks.
- Yeah.
- Cool. Yeah.
Thanks. I mean, you're welcome.
Yeah.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Have a good night.
- Anyway, cheers.
- Cheers.
Damien Darhk?
Are you here to arrest me?
[CHUCKLES] I'm not a cop anymore.
I... I came to say thank you.
You helping Barry restore the timeline,
it's pretty damn selfless.
Well, what can I say?
Being a parent kinda... changes you.
Mm, for the better.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
Agreed.
Yeah, I wish I knew
why I was still here.
I should be gone by now, Joe.
Nora should be in my place.
Well, maybe you still
got a little work to do.
- Are you trying to cast a spell?
- No.
More like a prayer.
Maybe this is my unfinished business.
- What is this?
- It's a gift.
Father to father.
And I think you're
gonna need that some day.
What...
♪
West.
Huh.
Dad?
♪
Nora. It's really you.
Where are we?
Doesn't matter.
I'm just glad I got
to see you before I go.
What do you mean?
I don't understand. You're leaving?
- I thought you were...
- Dead?
I will be,
but I guess I just
needed a little more time.
Wait. Dad, please.
I don't know what's happening,
but you can't leave now.
I just got you back.
I love you, Nora-doll.
When was the last time
we had a night out again?
I don't know. It's been too long.
Is that Nora Darhk?
Barry Allen?
Iris?
What am I doing here?
What just happened?
Where is my dad?
- Barry.
- I...
Please, someone, tell
me what is going on.
You're okay, thanks to your dad.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪
He's gone, isn't he?
Why is this happening again?
Because Damien Darhk promised
that he would do whatever it
takes to save his daughter,
and he did.
Come on.
There's a story I need you to hear.
♪
[CLINKING GLASS]
Sorry, I've never done that.
So a lot's happened
these past few days.
The world almost didn't make it,
but it did,
thanks to all of you
and a dedicated father.
We all survived because...
when faced with the very worst,
it's our choices that define us.
And the choices that we made
are why we're all heroes.
So to making our own destiny
and protecting it.
- Together.
ALL: Cheers.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
Thank God.
Now everything can go back to normal.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --