(Barry)
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
(Barry)
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
(Barry)
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
(man)
Previously on The Flash...
Iris West.
Eddie.
[gasps]
The Man in Yellow,
he took Eddie.
I promise
I'll find him, okay?
Barry.
(Iris)
Think about your best friend.
It could be your wife,
your father,
maybe someone you grew up with.
It's the person you can't wait
to talk to
at the end of the day.
The person who knows
everything about you,
who roots for you.
Now imagine you discover
your best friend has a secret.
No, not a secret.
A universe of secrets.
Would you confront him?
Would you stay silent?
Either way, you know nothing
will ever be the same again.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Where is Thawne?
He took some personal time.
Yeah, Eddie's been going through
some stuff, Captain.
Yeah, aren't we all?
You got anything
on these gold store robberies?
Perps hit up two more
in the last week,
- and we still got nothing.
- We're working on it.
Just waiting on some
final results from the lab.
All right, well,
pick up the pace.
And see if somebody
can contact The Flash.
Maybe he can help
speed things up.
You know what I mean.
Get going.
- Anything?
- No.
I mean, I've looked everywhere.
[sighs]
Keep looking.
Of course.
Yeah.
- Hey.
Uh, I'm heading out
right now.
- What's up?
- Something happened.
And I'm not supposed
to say anything,
but I couldn't keep quiet.
What happened?
The Man in Yellow,
he took Eddie
right in front of me.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
No, no.
Not at all.
- No, I...
- The Flash was there.
He told me to go home
and not to talk to anyone
because he would fix it,
but he hasn't.
I think the police should be
out there searching for Eddie.
No, Iris...
My dad needs to know
the truth.
Uh, I think
that The Flash is right.
Joe and the cops,
they're no match
for The Man in Yellow, Iris.
They would just get hurt.
So you think The Flash
is out there
right now,
searching for Eddie?
I'm sure he's doing
everything he can to find him.
Yeah, well,
I'm finding it pretty hard
to trust The Flash
right now.
Well, then, trust me.
Okay?
Look, I'm so sorry
about all of this. I...
Everything is gonna be okay.
I have to go.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
(man)
Okay, back it up.
[truck beeping]
(man)
Move out.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Get down!
Hey.
You planning on keeping
all those cameras
Wells used to spy on us?
That's kind of creepy,
don't you think?
First rule
of mechanical engineering, dude.
Never waste good tech.
[chuckles]
[computer beeping]
Central City Gold Reserve's
under attack.
Gold? That's the case
Singh wants us on.
- Mm.
- I'll be right back.
[gunfire]
You picked a bad day for this,
pal.
[high-pitched frequency,
groaning]
[panting]
What was that?
Your eye movement is normal.
No signs of neurological damage.
Do you think the thief
might have been a meta-human
who put the whammie on you
or something?
I-I don't know.
When Rainbow Raider
got in my head,
all I felt was anger.
But this was not that.
This was
just overwhelming fear.
(Cisco)
Hmm.
Looks like when you went down,
the thief got disoriented too.
Maybe we both got whammied.
Then you know how it feels.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hi, Barry.
Or should I say The Flash?
Sync and Corrected by GoldenBeard
...www.subscene.com...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
This is one of the few times
I would not want to be
Barry Allen.
I wonder what he's gonna say.
We should absolutely
not listen in.
It's none of our business.
But The Flash is our business.
And Iris did just find out
that Barry's The Flash.
So by transitive property,
Barry and Iris are our business.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I... Wait.
How did you find out?
When I touched
The Flash the other night,
I felt a jolt
of electricity.
The only other time I have ever
felt anything like that
was when you were in a coma
after the accident.
[chuckles]
I can't believe
I didn't figure it out sooner.
I can only imagine how angry
you are.
I'm not angry, Barry.
I'm just disappointed.
Okay.
Does Eddie know?
Yes, he does.
Is that why he got kidnapped?
No, I don't know why Wells
took Eddie. I...
Dr. Wells is The Man in Yellow?
Everything he's been doing,
helping me...
it was all a lie.
Wells killed my mom.
- Is he gonna kill Eddie?
- No, he's not.
I'm gonna get Eddie back,
I swear.
Yeah, The Flash said
the same thing.
Look, Iris,
you have to believe me, I...
There were so many times
I wanted to tell you.
You were the first person
I wanted to tell,
but everything started
getting crazy,
and I thought maybe Joe
was right and I shouldn't say...
Wait, wait, wait.
You're telling me
that my dad knew
and he told you
not to tell me?
He was trying to protect you.
We both were.
[sighs]
Yeah, well, maybe it's time
you both stopped.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Yeah, uh-huh.
Yeah, if we could get
another shipment of the, uh,
computers in here...
Yeah, I don't think that had
anything to do with us.
Nope.
♪ ♪
[mysterious music]
[hatch opens]
Don't suppose
you brought lunch?
Did you know
that human beings
can survive up to two months
without food?
Is that how long you're planning
on keeping me here?
You know...
I doubt it'll come
to that.
You want to tell me
what we're doing down here?
No.
You told me we're related,
that you're from the future.
Prove it.
Yeah, I don't have to prove
anything to anyone.
Well, I think
you're full of crap.
And whatever
you're trying to do,
you're not gonna get away
with it because The Flash is...
[gasps]
Stop talking.
♪ ♪
[distant siren wailing]
I heard you talked to Barry.
So this is what my cold shoulder
treatment feels like.
Look...
baby, the way
I went about things, maybe...
No.
I was wrong.
I was just trying
to keep you safe.
You know, that excuse is getting
really old.
First it was
the police academy,
and then it was dating Eddie,
and now this.
Sweetheart, you know what
The Man in Yellow is capable of.
He killed cops.
He killed Mason Bridge.
Wells killed Mason?
And you're covering that up?
No. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If the world finds out
about Wells,
they find out about Barry.
I'm trying
to keep him safe too.
Did you ever stop to think that
looping me in
would keep me safe?
That if I knew
what was going on out there,
I could prepare for it?
Maybe I could've helped you
and Barry put the bad guys away
instead of being in the way.
Believe me, I asked myself
that question every single day.
Every time
you posted something new
about The Flash on your blog...
Dad, it's not just
about Barry being The Flash.
You knew how he felt about me
for God knows how long,
and you didn't
tell me that either.
That wasn't for me to tell,
Iris.
Well, you know what, if any
of you had been honest with me,
maybe Eddie would still
be here.
He wouldn't have gotten involved
in all of this
if I hadn't been dating him.
Are you saying if you had known
how Barry felt...
What I am saying is that
what happened to Eddie
is your fault.
[phone vibrating]
This is work.
We can finish this talk.
Talking.
Yeah, that'll be new.
[phone continues vibrating]
[sighs]
Yeah, boss?
I just got a call from Joe.
The Central City Gold Reserve
is about to transport
$300 million in gold bars
to their Coast City vault.
Singh told Joe they think
the Man in the Mask
is gonna make a play for it.
Okay, but we still don't know
if he's responsible
for those weird images
you saw.
How are they transporting
the gold?
[ice cream truck music]
♪ ♪
Sorry, no more ice cream.
But your music's playing.
Yeah, it means we're out.
♪ ♪
Come on.
You might want to kill
the music.
We don't want any kids around
if our thief shows up.
[music stops]
[suspenseful music]
[beep]
[tires screech]
Whoa, the truck just got hit
by a land mine.
(Flash)
Is Joe okay?
We don't know yet.
♪ ♪
[gunfire]
Freeze!
Drop your weapon!
Don't make me do this.
♪ ♪
You okay?
Yeah. You?
I didn't want you
to have to shoot him again.
And I'm having
a pretty bad day.
So is this guy.
Let's see what Goldfinger
has to say for himself.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
General Eiling?
♪ ♪
[mysterious music]
What is wrong with him?
(Caitlin)
I pulled a bullet
out of his shoulder.
Which should hurt like hell.
And it didn't even seem like
he felt it.
I did a complete body scan,
and otherwise,
General Eiling
is perfectly healthy.
So why is he just standing there
like a robot?
I just got off the phone
with Argus.
Officially, Eiling is
on administrative leave.
Unofficially?
I spoke with Diggle's wife,
Lyla,
and she said Eiling's
been missing
for the past three months
and Argus is covering up
for it.
Makes sense.
Last time
I saw the general
was when Ronnie and I
broke Professor Stein
out of that military facility.
I'm sure
they're covering that up too.
(West)
So where has he been since then?
General Eiling, why were you
trying to rob the gold reserve?
[suspenseful music]
Maybe he's in some kind
of a trance?
General, do you remember me?
Flash.
Whoa, how does he know
you're The Flash?
I don't know.
General...
Eiling not here.
Eiling bad.
Maybe it's some kind
of psychotic break
presenting itself as
dissociative identity disorder.
Caitlin.
Caitlin good.
Oh, uh, thank you?
Mm.
Forget multiple personalities.
You guys have seen
The Exorcist, right?
You and your movies.
Keep talking to him.
He seems to respond to you.
Uh, why is Eiling bad?
Eiling hurt me.
I hurt Eiling.
Okay, uh,
so if you're not Eiling,
then who are you?
I...
Am...
Grodd.
Fear... me.
♪ ♪
What is a Grodd?
[grunting]
Oh, Grodd is a gorilla.
Five years ago, Eiling and Wells
were working on a project
to expand soldiers' cognitive
abilities during battle.
What we didn't realize
is that Eiling
was trying to create soldiers
with psychic abilities.
What do you mean "psychic"?
Eiling was trying to create
these super-soldiers
with telepathic
and telekinetic capabilities.
But when Dr. Wells found out
about the terrible experiments
that Eiling was doing,
he shut down the entire project.
So our psycho-killer
has a soft spot for animals.
That's sweet.
What happened to Grodd?
We don't know.
After the Particle Accelerator
exploded,
I went down to check on him,
and his cage was empty.
So he could have been
affected
by the same energy
that hit Barry?
When the dark matter hit Grodd,
all the drugs and serums
that Eiling injected him with
could've activated.
Maybe the Accelerator explosion
created a meta-gorilla.
And I think we know
what happens
when a super-intelligent ape
who's pissed off at humans
escapes captivity.
Cisco's right
about the first part.
This is the first brain scan
that I did on Grodd.
Whoa. His primary motor cortex
and Broca's area
are lit up
like a Christmas tree.
From Eiling's experiments.
And this is the brain scan
that I just did on Eiling.
His brain is lit up
in the exact same way.
So Grodd and Eiling
are connected somehow?
I think that somehow, Grodd
is transmitting neural signals
to Eiling's
primary motor cortex.
Mind control, telepathy...
Who knows what Grodd
is capable of now?
What do we think Grodd wants?
Revenge?
I do not like the fact
that Wells rescued Grodd.
I don't think
it's a coincidence
that this gorilla shows up
at the very same time
we're looking for Wells.
Grodd and Wells always
did have a special bond.
It wouldn't surprise me
if Wells was using Grodd
to distract us.
If we find Grodd,
we find Wells.
If we find Wells...
We find Eddie.
And I'm gonna help.
Know anything about gorillas?
I just might.
There have been reports
of some sort of animal
down in the sewers.
Mm. Alligators.
C.H.U.D.s.
R.O.U.S.es?
Am I the only one
who watches movies around here?
Uh, a few months ago,
two sewer workers went missing.
The search party
reported hearing
strange animallike noises
down in the tunnels.
Where exactly did
they go missing?
Uh, Fifth Avenue
and Tenth Street.
There's an access point
to the sewers
about two blocks east
of that intersection.
I'll start there.
Not alone.
I'm coming too.
Huh, wading through miles
of rats, roaches,
and human excrement...
Count me out.
Count me in.
He's your monkey.
Cisco, take the rest
of these flares,
light them, drop them as we go.
It's our path back.
Give me that banana.
Okay.
- Stay close.
- Definitely.
(Cisco)
Not going anywhere.
[ominous music]
Thanks for sticking up
for me.
Of course.
For what it's worth,
Barry feels really terrible
about lying to you.
He should.
You lied too.
Your fiancé?
Ronnie. Yes.
Uh, I thought he died in the
Particle Accelerator explosion,
but turns out
he just...
caught on fire.
Oh.
But he's okay?
Yeah. He is.
Good. I'm glad.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
(West)
I can't believe I'm down here
looking
for a supernatural gorilla.
I'm terrified
of regular gorillas.
[thud]
What was that?
[rat squeaks]
- Oh, oh.
(Cisco)
Whoa.
Hey, hey, guys,
look at this.
Incredible.
(Barry)
Looks like
we're in the right place.
[suspenseful music]
(West)
Somebody want to tell me
what we're looking at here?
(Barry)
Grodd.
He's evolving.
He's getting smarter.
(West)
Getting smarter. Great.
[snarling]
(Cisco)
If I hadn't seen
Jurassic Park,
I wouldn't be nearly
as frightened right now.
[growls]
[low rumbling]
(West)
So if he's getting smarter,
you think he might be getting
bigger too?
[rumbling]
That must have been
a truck passing over, right?
[snarling]
[gasps]
Cisco?
[howling]
[high-pitched frequency,
groaning]
(West)
Barry!
[roaring]
[gunshots]
- We got to get out of here.
- Barry's out cold.
- [roars]
- [screams]
(Cisco)
Joe!
Dad!
[panting]
[breathing noises]
[stomping]
[grunts]
Wh-what are you doing to me?
Help!
Cisco, help me!
(Grodd)
No help here.
I can hear you in my head.
You are telepathic.
Please.
[crying]
No, no, no!
[groaning]
(Grodd)
Father hate gun.
Father.
Father, you mean...
You mean Wells.
Wells?
Is that what you mean?
Where is he?
Not here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here.
Is this what you want?
You can have it.
It's yours.
[roaring]
[shouting]
Grodd hate banana.
[whimpering]
Please, please.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[Grodd roars]
You're experiencing
a spike of activity
in your primary motor cortex.
It's the same thing
we saw in Eiling.
The images you saw were some
kind of psychic attack by Grodd.
First Eddie gets taken
by The Man in Yellow,
and now my dad...
We're gonna save both of them,
Iris.
- I promise you.
- Hold up.
I put a tracker in the tranq
dart you shot Grodd with.
- As soon as it activates...
- No, Cisco.
I can't wait for that.
I will search every inch
of that sewer if I have to.
And what happens
if you find them?
What happens if Grodd
takes over your mind
the same way he did with Eiling?
I don't... I mean...
Can you guys
build me something?
Some kind of tech
so he can't get into my head?
(Cisco)
[sighs] I don't know.
Maybe if Dr. Wells were here.
I don't understand.
Every day you guys
figure out a way to help people.
All of The Flash's powers
and all of this equipment,
and you can't save Eddie
and my dad?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
We'll figure something out.
Fast.
Iris.
I can't get that sound
out of my head.
My dad screaming.
Why did he insist on going
down there with you?
He's always preaching
about being safe,
but not once does he think about
running into danger himself.
- Iris...
- No, Barry.
He's just a regular cop.
He is not some meta-human
with superpowers.
He's not you.
You're right,
he's not me.
And this isn't his fault.
None of this is his fault.
Look, yes,
maybe Joe told me
not to tell you
that I was The Flash,
but I didn't have to listen.
I could've told you...
A hundred times
I could've told you,
and I didn't.
Yes, I should've.
So you're right to be mad.
But don't be mad
at your dad.
Be mad at me.
Okay.
Okay, then explain to me
how the person I thought
I knew better than anyone
has been keeping secrets
from me?
Big, life-changing secrets?
You were supposed to be
my best friend, Barry.
I am your best friend.
How can you say that
when the most important things
in your life,
the things that matter the most,
the things that
you're supposed to share,
you kept all of them from me?
You lied to me
about everything.
I know, Iris.
Look, I know.
But you haven't been
entirely honest with me either.
What?
What are you talking about?
At Christmas,
when I told you how I felt,
you said that you didn't feel
the same way.
But I just feel like...
I don't know,
maybe things aren't that simple.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Am I wrong?
I'm gonna check
on Cisco and Caitlin.
♪ ♪
You know they're going
to find me.
And you. You're not as smart
as you think you are.
Oh, really? 'Cause I'm
a genius where I come from.
Imagine how smart
that makes me here.
- 'Cause you're from the future?
- Hmm.
With a name like Eobard,
I guess you'd have to be.
No, Eobard is
a distinguished name
for a distinguished member
of a distinguished family.
Depressing to think all of my
descendants are as crazy as you.
[laughing]
Oh, no, no, no.
No, the Thawne bloodline
is chock-full
of influential politicians,
scientists,
captains of industry.
Failures such as yourself
are just the exception.
And what exactly
makes me such a failure?
[exhales]
Tough question, Eddie.
Where to start?
Oh, how about your career
as a police detective?
It's spectacularly uneventful.
Yeah.
Well, we'll see.
No, we have seen.
I have seen.
I am from the future.
And you are
the only Thawne
to be all but forgotten
by history.
Waste of a life,
waste of a man.
And...
Oh, no.
[sighs]
You don't even get the girl.
What are you talking about?
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Observe, if you will,
the byline.
Barry marries Iris
and not you.
We're just gonna have to give
this ring
back to Grandma Agnes.
You, Eddie,
won't be needing it.
♪ ♪
An anti-telepathy strip.
It uses magnetic resonance
to neutralize
any foreign
neurological stimulus.
So it'll protect Barry
from being mind-controlled?
That's the hope,
but we have no way of knowing
if it actually works.
- It'll work.
[monitor beeps]
The tracker just came online.
We have Grodd's location.
Iris...
I want you to know, all the
times I imagined you being here,
it was not like this.
Get my dad back.
[dramatic music]
[monitor beeping]
Barry, what's your ETA?
All right.
I'm in position.
Wait for my signal.
So the red, that's Barry?
- Yes.
- And the blue?
Is Grodd.
Okay. Here goes nothing.
[Grodd roaring]
[monitor beeping]
The steam's working.
Grodd's on the move.
I don't understand.
What is the plan?
He's maneuvering Grodd into
a tunnel 5.3 miles from Barry.
So Barry can do what?
Same thing
he did to Girder.
Supersonic punch, baby.
Hit it!
♪ ♪
[Grodd growling]
[Grodd roars]
[grunting]
The supersonic punch failed.
Uh-oh.
Here we go.
It's okay, Cisco.
The headset's working.
Yes. Okay, uh,
try some speed punches on him.
[grunting]
(Flash)
This isn't working.
Okay, what if you try...
- [choking]
- [growls]
Barry!
[Barry grunting]
- Barry!
- Oh, no.
The headset's offline.
Sounded like it impacted
with something.
[grunting]
[Grodd growling]
[high-pitched frequency,
groaning]
Ah!
Human. Weak.
Barry's brain activity
is off the charts.
It's way worse
than last time.
What's happening to him?
Grodd's attacking him
psychically.
He's paralyzed.
Come on.
There's a service train coming.
[grunting]
Do something please!
I can't stop the train.
Barry, you have
to get out of there now.
[screams]
[monitor beeping]
What do we do?
Barry, listen to me, okay?
You have to concentrate
on my voice.
Whatever is happening to you,
you have to fight it.
[Grodd roars]
[screams]
I know you can do this.
I know how strong you are.
[groans]
(Iris)
Stand up to Grodd.
You can do this.
- Please.
- [panting]
[soft music]
Barry, do it for me.
♪ ♪
Iris.
[growls]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
Joe.
Barry.
Please get me out of here.
Barry!
I'm bringing him home.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
Mr. Allen,
how nice of you to visit.
Exactly how long do you intend
to keep me prisoner?
[beeping]
Your brain scan's normal,
which means Grodd is no longer
controlling you.
This prison is for meta-humans,
so you're free to go.
You will get what's coming
to you eventually.
I am not ashamed of my actions,
Mr. Allen.
You've seen what these
meta-humans are capable of.
Soon, your prison
won't be enough.
Not all meta-humans
are dangerous.
Oh, you're afraid that I know
you're The Flash?
[chuckles]
Don't get your tights in
a twist; I've known for months.
I wanted to come after you,
I would've done it by now.
But you think
you're gonna need me.
Harrison Wells turned me over
to that beast.
He used me
like a damn puppet.
So like it or not, we have
a common enemy, you and I.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a gorilla to hunt.
(Caitlin)
I said be still.
You have three fractured ribs.
I'll be fine.
Dad, you need to rest.
I can't believe Grodd
became so violent.
What was his lair like?
Did he eat the banana?
Does he like King Kong?
He's more of a
Planet of the Apes kind of ape?
Uh, terrifying.
No.
And I didn't ask.
Mm.
Do you mind if I talk
to my daughter alone?
When I was with that gorilla,
I thought,
"I'm gonna die down here."
And all I could think about was
how you and me were in a fight.
Dad, I was so afraid that
something would happen to you.
My life started
when you were born,
and sometimes
my incredible love for you,
it blinds me, and I forget...
I forget what
a brilliant young woman you are,
how you're capable of making
your own decisions.
Daddy, I know that everything
that you do is out of love.
So love me enough
to always tell me the truth.
- Yeah?
- Deal. Deal.
Okay.
Come here.
- Ow!
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Oh, my bad.
- [laughs]
Maybe it's a good thing
we didn't catch Grodd.
Where would we put him?
I mean, the pipeline
isn't exactly equipped
to hold a super-intelligent,
telepathic gorilla.
Joe mentioned that
Grodd called Wells "Father."
And Wells must have ordered
Grodd to come after us.
It's why Grodd didn't kill Joe.
I think Joe is right.
Everything Grodd did,
it was just to distract us.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Just thinking
about this headset.
It wasn't strong enough.
You could've been killed
out there, man.
No, dude, your tech worked,
and it proved
that we don't need Wells.
The three of us took on Grodd
and rescued Joe.
Together, we can do anything.
Actually, it was the four of us.
♪ ♪
Hey.
How did you know I was here?
This is your spot.
Yeah.
It's a special spot.
It's where I first met
The Flash.
All those times,
you were standing
right in front of me,
and I had no idea.
I don't even know you anymore.
Iris, what you were saying to me
when I was down the sewer...
You know why
I wasn't afraid?
Because you were there.
Even though I really was scared,
having you there
is how I could stand up
to Grodd.
Every time I falter
or make a mistake,
the thought of you
is what picks me up
and keeps me going.
Look, look,
what I'm trying to say is,
even though
you didn't know everything
about my life this past year,
that does not mean
that you weren't a part of it.
You were.
Every single day.
Without you,
there wouldn't be The Flash.
I've thought
about what you said,
and maybe you were right.
I have been thinking about you,
about us.
But I can't do that anymore.
Eddie is the man
that I live with,
the man that I love,
and he's still missing.
I know.
I'm gonna bring him back.
And after that?
I don't know.
[dark music]
[growling]
[growls]
(Thawne)
So now what?
Now...
I have the key.
The key to what?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Time to go home.
Sync and Corrected by GoldenBeard
...www.subscene.com...