[SERENE MUSIC]
I now pronounce you husband and wife...
- [LAUGHS]
- Again.
[LAUGHS]
♪
[LAUGHTER]
You know, even though future-you told us
about your vow renewals,
like a million times,
- I still got pretty weepy.
- Me too.
I mean, the love in this
room when you two kissed...
We have such an amazing
future ahead of us.
Yeah, if we didn't change it.
I checked with Gideon. No
changes to the timeline.
Everything's fine.
[SIGHS] Well, on that note,
we should be getting back
to 2049 sooner or later.
- Yep.
- Keep the future safe.
You're both gonna make great heroes.
- I already am.
- [LAUGHTER]
I'm gonna make you proud, Dad.
♪
I know.
Love you both.
♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Okay.
Everything seems the same.
It was so good to see Uncle
Jay and Aunt Joan again.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Is it weird that seeing Uncle Jay alive
just made me miss him more?
[RUMBLING AND BOOMING]
♪
What was that?
I-I have no idea.
[DOOR CLICKING]
Okay, kids. I come
bearing cheeseburgers.
♪
Who's hungry?
Uncle Jay.
You were expecting someone else?
[CHUCKLES] Bart?
Are you okay, son?
Oh! Oh, oh.
Okay...
We just... we just
missed you so much!
Aw.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[WHISPERING] He's alive.
Uncle Jay's alive.
Our Uncle Jay is really...
Did we do this? Yeah, we did, didn't we?
[LAUGHS] Oh, this is so crash.
Crash? No. No, not crash...
The opposite of crash.
That was a temporal wave
that washed over us, okay?
That means that when we
went back to help Mom and Dad
stop the Godspeed War,
we changed the future!
Kill the adversary and his allies.
Yeah, but in a good way.
Well, yeah, totally. But
we have to figure out why
the changes happened.
So are, um, Mom and Pops
gonna be swingin' by anytime soon?
Aren't they in Milan
for their anniversary
at La Verità Rustica?
- Right.
- Yeah.
Yes, the anniversary of
their wedding vow renewal.
Hmm?
Um, but the rest of Team Flash
can pop by right?
Well, they're all kind of busy,
which you already know.
Now, why the third degree?
Oh...
- Oh, nothing.
- Yeah!
We're fine. Bart's fine.
I'm fine. Fine, fine, fine.
- [LAUGHS]
- Yeah, thanks to your brother.
When that psychopath
Godspeed came for me
a few months ago, I thought my race
might be finally finished.
But then Impulse saved the day...
Prevented Godspeed from
destroying our total reality.
Just like your dad always does.
That's how I know you'll make
a great Flash one day, Bart.
♪
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
Oh, Aunt Rose...
sends her love.
Her botany club's running late again.
Who's Aunt Rose? [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Rose.
My wife.
[LAUGHS] What is up with you two tonight?
♪
So that's how we did this?
Yeah, when we chased
Godspeed through time
using the cosmic treadmill.
Only, it wasn't built
to handle the energy
of three speedsters at once.
Our tachyon energies must have
caused massive temporal fissures.
[SIGHS]
Oh, this is why Dad
has time-travel rules.
According to this, Uncle
Jay never married Aunt Joan.
[GASPS]
Oh my God.
We erased her.
[GASPING] We erased her!
My gauntlet just confirmed it.
Is... is that part of
those fissures that...
That we caused?
I'm sorry. How far back does it go?
How many are there? Can we fix them?
Wait...
Voice down.
[SIGHS]
Okay, we work backwards
identifying everything
new to the timeline,
figure out where things
first started changing,
and put them back where
they're supposed to be.
Okay.
"Corrupt Mayor Bellows
Jr..." farther back...
"Trickster Invades
Tibet..." farther back...
- Who's Booster Gold?
- Keep going.
"Zoom attacks CCPD Chief
of Police Joe West."
Grandpa Joe wasn't chief then, right?
But he is in this new timeline.
When did he get promoted?
There are no time
fissures before that...
this is where the change happened,
and it altered everything
that follows like dominoes.
Okay, "Detective Joe West
heroically took a bullet
during a jewelry theft the afternoon
of December 31, 2013."
And Dad couldn't help him,
because he was still in a coma.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
If we save Grandpa
Joe from getting shot,
things will return to normal...
and we get Aunt Joan back.
New Year's Eve 2013, here we come.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
♪
What the hell are you wearing?
Something sexy. [CHUCKLES]
It's smart. I'm incognito.
Dude, it's 2013, not 1913.
Oh, look.
There's Grandpa Joe.
Oh.
I... I haven't done this in a long time.
What am I supposed to say?
Breathe, Detective.
- You got this.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm.
♪
Hey, Counselor Horton. How are you?
I am crappy, Detective West.
So if you don't mind, I'm just gonna...
Yeah. Sorry, um,
we are celebrating
New Year's here, and...
Oh, God. Okay. I'ma
stop you right there.
Um, two things:
one, I have a ton of paperwork
back on my desk at the DA's office,
and two... this one's
important; pay attention...
All men are jerks.
No offense.
- None taken.
- Great.
Happy New Year.
Damn...
♪
Sorry, Detective.
Then again, her divorce
just finalized last week.
That wasn't worth mentioning?
I was gonna, but it just seems like
you two would make such a great pair.
Is today the day that
Grandpa Joe and Grammy Cecile
- start dating?
- No.
I mean, I don't think that it is.
Okay, good 'cause stopping
Grandpa Joe from getting shot
is enough fixing for one day.
Okay, remember what we learned in 2049.
We have to stop what happens today,
and we cannot interact with anyone
who's connected to our
family while we are doing it.
Relax.
No one's gonna find out who
we are or why we're here.
Who are you two, and why are you here?
♪
Well?
- How about it?
- Yes, of course.
Here you go, Detective.
Nora Moy and Bart Waid.
We're intern CSIs.
We're here to help out,
because we heard that
one of your CSIs is, um...
- under the weather.
- Under the weather.
So I think that's it...
Just crime fighters,
couple of crime fighters
with, uh, science.
[LAUGHS] Sorry.
It's been tense here since
the accident at S.T.A.R. Labs.
My new partner barely speaks to me.
Get him a cup of coffee.
I find that java really
brings people together.
Yeah.
That is a great idea.
I wanna buy the entire bullpen
coffee from the cart outside.
Aw.
Take their orders. It's on me.
Maybe this will help break the ice.
[STAMMERING] Detective, we have, uh,
so much science to get done today.
So I don't know that we're
gonna be able to, um...
- it's a lot.
- Oh, we do have science.
But we are more than happy to help out,
and we will be back
in a flash, Detective.
Can you leave Detective West's and mine
on our desks while we're out?
Thanks a lot, guys.
The guy. That's...
Tha-tha-that's the guy.
That's the guy that sacrificed
himself to stop Eobard Thawne,
Mom's old fiancé.
- Yes, it is.
- Ow.
And now we are his coffee gophers
when we're supposed to be looking out
for Grandpa Joe.
♪
[GROANS] This is ridiculous.
Can I not just use my
superspeed instead, please?
What part of "don't change the timeline"
do you not understand?
Bart, unless we are
absolutely, 100% certain
that it won't make things
worse, we can't use our speed.
But...
Bart.
I need you to focus on the plan.
I have my gauntlet set
to alert us as soon as
the jewel robbery goes down, okay?
- Okay.
- That is where Grandpa Joe will be.
Right, and then we zoop
in, and we save the day.
That's fantastic. But you do realize
that every second that
we're standing here,
Grandpa Joe could be
getting shot like now.
Or now. Or right now.
- You see what I'm...
- Holy crap! Stop!
No, because Grandpa Joe's
safety is on the line,
and I need coffee now! Oh! I'm so sorry.
- I didn't see you.
- It's called
inattentional blindness.
It's a phenomenon when an individual...
[SERENE MUSIC]
- Hey.
- [GIGGLES]
- [LAUGHING] Hi.
- Hi.
I'm Bart, and you're...
studying temporal dynami...
How do you know so much
about quantum divergence?
Oh, now, that's a surprise.
Tell you what, can you keep a secret?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
I'm from the future.
No way! Me too! What year?
Dude, I'm totally messing with you.
[LAUGHS] Time travel is impossible.
[LAUGHS] Right, yeah, you got me.
But it is possible
though... mathematically,
if I'm reading the title
of your thesis correctly.
Yeah, I'm trying to prove
that Tolman's paradox
can give rise to quantum superposition,
and that tachyon exchanges
between two particles
can generate superposition
and entangle molecular pairs.
Of course, it's the causal paradox
- I'm still trying to solve.
- [ELECTRIC WHIRRING]
Oh my God.
You're like the Elon
Musk of your generation.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure Elon Musk
is my generation's Elon Musk.
- Well, I mean...
- I'm Avery.
And I'm Nora, his sister.
And we should really go. We
have... we have that thing.
Yeah, right. Yeah! We have that, um...
Avery, your research is
bleeding-edge impressive.
Can you tell that to my
boss at Fast Track Labs?
Just once, I'd like
to help her in research
instead of running for coffee,
but, uh, the intern life.
Oh, you know, I'm an intern too!
- No way!
- Yeah!
Actually, we both are.
We both are interns, and
we should really go now.
- That call we were waiting for?
- Yes.
- It just came in.
- Oh, that one.
Um, yeah, it was really
crash meeting you.
Is that a good thing?
If it's a good thing,
and you wanna run into me again,
I make a coffee run every afternoon.
Okay, that's good to
know. Nice to meet you!
[STAMMERING] Oh, this is you... bye.
Thank you. Bye. Bye.
Ba... [CLEARS THROAT]
[ALARM RINGING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
You watch the back
entrance. I'll watch the front.
Backup's en route.
♪
- Drop your weapon!
- Ah! Freeze!
I... this is a real gun
with real bullets inside.
Kid, have you ever
even held a gun before?
Yes. This isn't my first heist.
Listen, most thieves don't
wear what they just stole.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Yeah, I forgot a bag, all right?
Hey, listen. I'm only
taking the ethically-sourced
conflict-free diamonds.
No blood diamonds for me. No, sir.
Listen. Lower your weapon
before you have an accident.
Why don't you lower your weapon?
Yow!
Stop!
If Grandpa Joe was never
supposed to be here,
then the gun was never
supposed to fire at all.
We can't cause another temporal flux.
Oh great, you're just
now mentioning that.
Well, I tried to when we
were in the coffee line,
but someone was too busy flirting.
- What do we do?
- Okay, um,
we need to examine our variables,
and we need to form a plan.
First, we need to consider...
Oh my God, I got this.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
[YELPS]
I am so sorry.
Those things are way heavier
than they look in the movies.
Turn around. Hands behind your back.
- Hands behind your back!
- That was an accident.
Behind your back!
I heard a shot. Are you...
I'm fine, Detective.
You must have a guardian angel.
- [SIRENS WAILING]
- [TIRES SQUEALING]
Aw, you shouldn't have done that.
What? So I moved Grandpa
Joe instead of the bullet.
- What's the big deal?
- This.
Look, now more temporal
particles are in flux.
Bart, you made everything worse.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
[AIR WHOOSHING]
[OMINOUS VOICES SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[ECHOING] I don't get it.
It wasn't even a meta-human with powers.
Now more metas are gonna
be turning up everywhere
now that the Particle
Accelerator exploded.
Meta-human.
Then I'm not alone.
♪
Bart.
The whole timeline's in flux.
You might have changed
the future even more now.
What did I do? I saved Grandpa.
By moving Grandpa Joe
instead of moving the bullet,
you created a new series of events,
changing the timeline.
It's what I would've warned you
about if you hadn't rushed in.
Okay, okay. Why don't we just go back
in time 15 minutes,
and see for ourselves
- what we did wrong?
- Oh, okay.
So you wanna fix our
time-travel screwups
by traveling back in time.
Again!
Well, when you say it like that...
Actually, there is a
way to observe the past
without altering it.
I bet you that's the flash drive
with the surveillance
footage from the shooting.
All we have to do is watch it.
And see what went wrong.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
Follow my lead.
Don't go rogue.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Excuse me, Detective Thawne.
Is that the surveillance
footage of the incident?
The interns. Yes it is. Why?
Hi, by the way. Uh, we just figured
you're doing so much
detecting around here
that we could just take this
back to the police station,
- and then we'll just give it back to...
- Uh, no thanks.
You two should make another coffee run.
Oh, we already did that.
Did you?
Then why am I not holding
a decaf cappuccino?
Let us do this work,
and you two do yours.
Great idea, Detective.
BOTH: We gotta get that footage.
Let me get this straight.
Nobody knows why the
three of us are here?
Feels like we've been set up.
So a woman's voice is in our heads
telling us all that
there's a job tonight.
Now if you two jokers
didn't promise a score,
who did?
[LAUGHS]
Me, big fella.
Pool table.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
The Utopia Casino is
ringing in the new year
with the biggest fête in town.
More guests means more bets
means more cash they'll need to cover.
They'll have 10 mil in the vault, easy.
Not the worst plan.
Party starts in six hours. No prep time.
Will cops show?
I'll know they're coming before they do,
'cause ever since that
Particle Accelerator exploded,
I can hear people's thoughts.
Now I thought I was
the only one with gifts,
until I learned a new word:
meta-human.
[LAUGHS]
It means we're all something more now,
something greater.
And I am done living in fear.
Now, who's game?
I'm sick...
of hiding who I am!
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
So am I.
♪
Watch it, Jack.
[LAUGHS] See?
Doesn't that feel better?
With our powers, no one can stop us,
and if they try, I'll
know what they're planning
before they even think it.
So you're the ace up our sleeve.
No.
She's a Queen.
♪
Hi.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
How are we gonna get that flash
drive without Grandpa noticing?
Watch. Kay?
And learn.
Okay, I get it.
I'm the new guy. You're busy,
and I heard you just lost your partner,
which has gotta be tough.
Plus, one of our CSI's in a coma,
and on top of all that,
you got shot down by Counselor Horton.
Who told you that?
Uh, everyone.
You could try lilacs and crumb cake.
Those are her favorites.
That's good advice.
- Who was that?
- One of our new interns.
They're a little weird.
[THUNDER BOOMS]
Okay. Now we can see
where we messed up.
This is where it happened...
Where Dad was struck by lightning.
[THUNDER BOOMING]
[GLASSES RATTLING]
I got it.
Ooh!
Super-speedy save. [LAUGHS]
But hang on. I know her.
Oh my God. That's Mona Taylor,
AKA The Queen,
as in the telepathic leader
of the Royal Flush Gang.
What is she doing here?
Wait.
Since when is there a
casino heist tonight?
The RFG didn't team up until
way after Dad put the suit on,
after Mona discovered
that there are other metas.
How could she possibly
even know that this soon?
Oh, Bart.
She got the idea to form
the RFG years early from us,
and now 30 people are
gonna die from a bomb.
[SIGHS] No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to stop that heist.
Do you think I don't know that?
But if you start screwing with it again,
we could screw things up even worse.
What are we supposed to do then?
I don't know.
But we'll figure it out
just like we always do.
Dad would've gotten it
right the first time.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
Bart, don't go there.
Why not? It's true.
Listen to me.
Whatever happened,
it's both of our faults.
We are in this together.
Maybe we shouldn't be.
[SNIFFLES] Every single
thing I did today...
Made everything worse.
I am not good enough...
And I'll never be The Flash.
[SIGHS]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
Spoiler alert, Pops.
Your son's a big screwup.
[WHOOSH]
I knew you'd be here.
I let him down, Sis.
Bart, listen to
me. Nobody is perfect.
You are.
- That is not true.
- Yes it is.
You knew when to come back here.
You got the flash drive.
You even helped Grandpa
Joe and Grammy Cecile.
You...
Yeah, you're perfect.
I'm a complete failure.
No...
No, you're not.
I failed a lot too.
For a long time, I
fumbled with my powers.
- I doubted myself.
- [SNIFFLES]
- But that's how we learn.
And yeah, every time I
fell, Dad picked me up.
Just like every time you fall,
I'm gonna pick you up too.
Just remember what Dad always says:
"No matter how fast you run,
life is about the journey."
Bart, we are going to make this right.
It... it just takes time
to think things through.
[SNIFFLES]
Thank you for the pep talk, Sis.
And now, I'm thinking...
to get out of this,
we're gonna need an
expert in time travel.
And I know just where to go.
[WHOOSH]
The rain has not discouraged anyone
from partying in the new year.
After the bizarre events of 2013...
[SIGHS]
[WHOOSH]
Hi...
[STAMMERING] H-how did you get in here?
T-this place has a $12
million security system
and armed guards.
Hi. [GIGGLES] Again, sorry to barge in
on you like this. Uh, we
actually need your help.
It's regarding your theory
on temporal development.
Holy crap.
[STAMMERING] That whole getting coffee
while bumping into me in line...
that wasn't an accident!
It's a classic espionage trick.
You were following me.
[LAUGHS] And now,
you wanna take me hostage
and steal all of Fast Track
Labs corporate secrets.
Well, do your worst,
'cause I'm not talking.
No, Avery, we're not gonna hurt you.
We need your help to stop a crime.
What? Why should I believe you?
Because we're time
travelers from the future,
and we need you to show
us how your temporal theory
can help save people at a casino robbery
without actually changing the timeline.
Wow, that felt so good. Whew!
- I'm calling security.
- No, no wait.
Uh, uh, we can prove it.
I can show you something
about your past or your future.
But if you show her
something from the future,
she's gonna have to
wait until it happens
to actually prove anything.
Uh, is that gauntlet
using integrated quantum circuitry?
- Yes.
- Last I checked.
♪
Liquid processing unit...
AI nano cells...
This is decades away...
You guys are from the future!
We are, which is why we need your help.
Ever since we arrived, we've
caused serious temporal shifts,
and now...
30 people are gonna die.
I-I-It might be worse than you think.
The death toll keeps changing,
but the headline doesn't.
Because now it's solidified
into a fixed point in time.
Excuse me. Sorry, sorry, sorry...
And that means that
the heist and the deaths
aren't causally entangled
like the tachyon particle
exchange in my theory,
which is looking more like fact.
[LAUGHS]
It's too late to stop the casino heist.
But since the casualties keep changing,
they're not fixed in time.
So, you can fix the timeline
and save all those people,
as long as you let
the heist still happen.
- Wow.
- [LAUGHS]
- Okay. Thanks, Avery.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, hold on.
- I'm coming with you.
- Oh, Avery.
We can't risk you getting hurt.
But we will come back.
I promise you.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[PUNCHY MUSIC]
♪
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Ladies and gents. [TOOTS HORN]
I say it's high time
we ring in the new year
with a bang.
[SHRILL RINGING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Well, here's the drill, folks.
If you run, call for help,
or annoy us, my...
ooh, King will pop your
skulls with his bare hands.
So please don't make him kill you.
Find the casino vault. Empty it.
Done and doner.
And if we run into trouble?
Show them the winning hand.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Oh. Okay.
Remember, you need to
get everyone to safety
while I find the bomb,
and make sure that...
- Let the heist happen.
- Yeah.
Stay calm, Bart. You got this.
We got this.
♪
Four minutes to midnight.
My Queen,
a couple was sitting
right there being quiet,
so I turned my back
on them for a minute.
Now they're missing.
Someone is inside here with us.
[GASPS]
[WHIMPERING]
Whoever you are, show yourself,
or my King starts popping heads.
[WHIMPERS]
Bart, I can't find the bomb.
The Queen is gonna start killing people
unless I do something right now.
What? No, no.
You have to get everyone to safety.
No. Time for plan B.
Uh, just get the bomb before midnight.
There is no plan B!
Bart!
[WHIMPERING]
Last chance.
[SCREAMING]
Wait, wait!
Stop! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, okay. Let's all just...
Let's just relax. All right?
No need to lose our heads. [CHUCKLES]
I am the casino manager, obviously.
Isaac is my name, and you caught me.
I am the one that was
helping the customers escape.
But I'm not doing that anymore.
I'm not going to do that anymore.
Um, however, since dead people
aren't great for business,
how about I just look away...
you guys just take the money and leave?
Too late.
Now tell me.
What kind of casino manager
risks his neck on minimum wage?
One who's a really great employee?
Oh, or you're a cop.
Hmm?
Let's see what's inside
that beautiful mind of yours.
[SHRILL RINGING]
No, no, no, no. We gotta fix the timeline
and get back to the future...
- Wait.
- Timeline... Future...
You're from the future?
She's so cute.
Please let her not have a boyfriend.
Avery, you're my future.
My future.
Oh... ha ha ha ha.
That future. Yeah, well...
Love is grand.
Fine. Sit down.
♪
Oh.
Success, Mona.
I mean, my Queen.
$10 million worth too.
Well, then we're done here.
Wait!
My King, my dear, drop the cop.
Drop? You're... Hey, wait a minute...
- [GRUNTS]
- Oh.
If you wanna survive, don't follow us.
Just sit down. Stay put.
Enjoy the fireworks, all of them.
[LAUGHING] All of them.
[GROANS]
[PANTING] Sis...
The RFG's M.I.A.
What's up with the bomb search?
[GROANS]
It's almost midnight.
[BEEPING]
Bart, I found the bomb.
It's counting down to midnight.
But one thermal charge couldn't
level this whole building.
Before she left, The Queen said,
"Enjoy the fireworks... All of them."
- Agh.
- Oh, schrap.
There's more than one bomb!
But we only have like 30 seconds!
Well, King knocked the hell out of me,
broke my arm, and I need, like,
three minutes to speed-heal.
I can't get everyone out in time.
But we don't even have one minute!
It's okay, Sis. You got this.
You can find the rest of them.
But it took me forever to find this one!
Sis! You got this.
Think.
Think, think, think.
[EXHALES]
The heat signatures
in the water tanks...
They... they must be masking
the bombs' thermal signature.
There it is. Now do your thing, Sis!
Get excessive!
♪
Sis, it's almost midnight.
I know. I got them.
There were five.
You got 15 seconds to get rid of them.
- But where?
- Anywhere!
Ten. Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
♪
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
Great job, Sis.
You did it.
We both did it.
[SIGHS]
♪
Every witness at the casino robbery says
says someone "streaked" them outside.
What do you think,
too much champagne?
It beats the hell out of me,
but it looks like we're
here for a long night.
Well, a few Jitters goodies might help.
- Oh, thank you, baby girl.
- Yeah.
Here's to 2014 not being so weird.
Not being so weird.
Hey, uh, you saved my
dissertation, right?
Detective Pretty Boy.
[LAUGHS]
Sorry, uh, that's just
what my dad calls you.
Although, he's not wrong.
You are a boy,
and you are pretty...
and, uh, that did not come out right.
I'll take any compliment
I can get from...
Joe West
or his lovely daughter.
Um, uh, well, do you
have a name, Detective?
It's Eddie.
Okay.
Counselor Horton.
You don't have anywhere
more fun to be tonight?
Uh, yeah, I, um, had to get
an evidentiary disclosure
over to Judge Hankerson.
Um, so, look.
About this morning,
I am so sorry if I
came off a little harsh.
See, it turns out that being a lawyer
does not make getting
divorced any easier.
It's okay.
I know that splitting up can be hard.
Trust me.
Yeah.
So when we bumped into
each other this morning,
I know that you were
about to ask me something.
But...
I'm not ready,
and I'm not gonna be... not for a while.
Of course. I understand.
[WHISPERS] Yep.
[NORMAL VOICE] However,
when I am ready...
whoever sent lilacs
to my office tonight...
oof.
[WHISPERS] He'll be the first one to know.
♪
Okay, so we stopped the shooting,
we fixed the timeline,
and we fixed the mistake
we made fixing the timeline.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Kay.
- Time to head back home.
Interns, you getting in on this?
All right. Everybody, line up.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Happy New Year.
Mm-mm. No. Mm-mm.
Okay, just one photo.
Smile, everyone.
[CAMERA TIMER BEEPING]
♪
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
I'm really glad you came back.
Me too.
Seriously, you haven't
just changed my research.
You changed my life.
Well, I always keep my promises.
You know, I had to. You...
you helped save the day with
all your science badassery.
- I mean...
- [LAUGHS]
which is why...
I...
Um, look.
Avery, um, before I
go back to my time...
I know we just met, um,
but it's New Year's Eve, right?
And I just think that you...
♪
[DOOR WHIRS]
Bart.
Bart, it's been two minutes.
Come on, we really have to go.
See you again sometime, McFly?
I promise.
All right, here we go. Okay.
♪
[SIGHS]
Wait, so I was dead,
killed by Godspeed?
Uncle Jay, I'm so sorry
for screwing up the timeline.
And if that means I
can't ever be The Flash...
I understand.
[LAUGHS]
[STAMMERS] Well, I'm
sorry. Are you kidding me?
If screwing up the
timeline was a dealbreaker,
your dad couldn't be The Flash.
Heck, when I first
started to time travel,
I ended up fighting
Nazis in World War II,
and then lived on and off
in the past for 16 years.
But that was another lifetime.
So you... you're not mad?
I'm alive.
Right? My Joan is back.
[CHUCKLING] Why would I be mad?
Bart, you're on a journey...
Both of you.
You're gonna make
mistakes, and sometimes...
they can't be undone.
But you can always try
to make things better.
Right?
And that's what you did today.
Now, I gotta get out of here.
I got an important meeting
with President Luthor.
[CHUCKLES]
BOTH: President Luthor?
Gotcha.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
[LAUGHING] Oh.
♪
Iris!
Come on!
This brunch reservation
ain't gonna get any later.
Joe, don't worry. I'll
make sure we're on time.
After surviving Armageddon,
we all deserve this.
You guys got any resolutions for 2022?
I decided to forgive Mark
for all of his crime things.
What? He's turned over a new leaf,
and I made him swear to stay
on the straight and narrow.
Anybody know anything
about Caity's new boyfriend,
Marcus? Anybody met him?
No, I hear he's really cute though.
I have a resolution, actually.
Party less. [GROANS]
[LAUGHS]
I know mine:
more family time.
That sounds like a perfect year.
All right people, let's hurry it up.
Look at the face. Joe's getting hangry.
Okay, everybody. Hold hands.
Bundle up.
It's chilly in Paris.
[SQUEALS]
[CHUCKLES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --