Mouse.
I never thought I'd see you again.
When you...
When you disappeared that night...
I'm sorry.
We were supposed to watch out
for each other and then you were gone.
Shining Light sent me here.
Put the needle in my spine
and filled me full of the blue poison.
I should have found you.
No. I'm the big sister.
I should have come back for you, but...
...they made me into...
...a monster.
If that's true, we're both monsters now.
Did it hurt?
I wanted to die.
Me too.
They had one dose left
and they knew it worked on you
so they figured it would work on me.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
These people you were with...
They keep me safe.
They'll keep you safe too.
Or we can go home. Back to the village.
There is no village anymore.
What?
They came for us.
Who?
The Americans.
This hero came shrieking
out of the sky like a demon.
Destroyed the camp.
And all the villages around it too.
There were bodies everywhere.
Everyone's gone.
Then we'll go somewhere else.
Back to Japan.
Maybe grandma and grandpa
are still alive.
You don't care?
That the Superhero split
an old woman in half?
That the entire school caved in
with the kids inside?
That babies burned alive in their cribs
when the propane tanks exploded?
I never wanted this.
But they were right all along.
Shining Light is full of shit!
Shining Light fights injustice.
They stand up for
people without a voice.
They murdered our parents!
This country is an enemy
to the whole world now.
We need to fight back. Fight with me!
You're the boy who nursed
every mouse who lost its mother.
That was a long time ago.
You're still my brother.
Then... you know I have to do this.