[TUNE PLAYING ON HARMONICA]
♪ You're having a hard time
And lately you don't feel so good ♪
♪ You're getting a bad reputation
In your neighbourhood ♪
♪ Don't forget your second wind ♪
[BILLY] Oi, Hughie.
Hughie.
♪ It's not always easy
To be living in ♪
I said, how long we gonna be sulking about
like some poncy,
eyeliner-wearing emo twat?
All right, look.
I will say, I lost me bottle a little bit
when I popped you one.
So, um...
sorry?
There, I said it.
We're all square.
Hey, hey, hey!
- Easy, easy, easy, kid.
- I'll fucking kill you!
- Relax.
- Fucking hell. Kid's stark raving.
No, no, no.
Breathe. Breathe.
Do you mind?
- Fucking hell.
- Kid, breathe.
- Just breathe.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- All right.
- I'm fine.
[PHONE RINGS]
[BILLY] What's the ETA?
[GRACE] A team's on the way.
They'll be a few hours.
- A few hours?
- I'm a civilian.
I can't just push a button anymore.
The target's secure? No one's seen him?
We're three fucking miles offshore, Grace.
What do you think?
I think if there's a way to screw this up
you'll find it.
Look, I just want me wife back.
I know.
Bring Langley the terrorist,
and you'll have her.
Hey, you ever hear
of an old Supe called Liberty?
The fuck's that gotta do with anything?
I'm not sure yet.
How's your crew holding up?
Yeah, all good.
We are having a few laughs here,
I'll tell you that.
The target is the girl's brother?
Yeah, so?
You don't think
it compromises her allegiances?
Well...
if it comes to that...
I'll neutralise her.
The compassion you show your team
is truly touching.
It's just a figure of speech, mate.
You remember in the camp...
you were so hungry
you'd cry all the time
and I snuck into the storage room
to steal you rice?
I took care of you.
I still will.
[IN JAPANESE] I also remember the time
they came after you for stealing.
I said no, it was me,
and they broke my hands.
You might be my big sister.
But I protect you too.
We protect each other.
You know...
the Americans will torture me.
I won't let them.
How will you stop them?
You have to let me go.
I won't attack anyone.
I won't hurt anyone.
I'm your brother...
we only have each other now.
Please.
I'm sorry.
[HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY]
Thank you.
- I gotta go, man. I'm out.
- All right.
- Yo, yo.
- Later, man.
[HORN HONKING]
[GROANS]
[HEART BEATING]
- [BECCA] Breakfast is served.
- [HOMELANDER] Mm.
[BECCA] Want one or two, buddy?
- Just one.
- Yeah, just one.
- You want maple syrup?
- [RYAN] Um...
Yes, please.
Little more.
Mm. Thank you. Love it.
This is nice.
- Mama?
- [BECCA] Yeah?
Quiero Raisin Bran, por favor.
[BECCA SPEAKS IN SPANISH THEN CHUCKLES]
- What is that?
- [BECCA] That's Spanish.
Monday mornings,
we have breakfast in español.
Hey, Ryan.
You wanna stay in here and learn Spanish,
or do you wanna come outside
and have some fun with your old man, huh?
- [BECCA] I think that he needs to...
- [RYAN] Is it okay if I go?
Yeah, of course it's okay. Right, Mom?
- Come on.
- Sure.
There you go, champ.
You guys fucking ready?
Okay, we pan up.
We see Homelander
flying towards Martinez's Miami mansion.
And Martinez makes a run for it.
[SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH] Octavio accelerates,
but Homelander laser-blasts out the tyres.
Bzzt! Unh!
Martinez gets out of the car,
dazed.
Looks up.
HOMELANDER: "You're under arrest."
[LAUGHS] And he slaps the handcuffs
on Martinez. The cops take him away.
Homelander turns to the other heroes:
"We should work together more often."
"You mean like a team-up?"
"Exactly.
All seven of us."
Holy shit.
That is the moment The Seven became...
The Seven.
Rousing music.
♪ Hans Zimmer ♪
Title card. Dawn of the Seven.
Cut to black.
- That is amazing.
- Thank you.
[ASHLEY] Wow, I am very impressed.
[BOURKE] Thank you so much.
And, gang, that's just the teaser.
Look, this is not just a superhero...
You look like shit.
- [BOURKE AND ASHLEY] Yes!
- Had a big night.
And I wanna shoot
the whole thing handheld.
Very Greengrass, very grounded.
I wanna take the audience
and literally put them,
boom, right there in the action.
- What's the plan on Translucent?
- That's a great question.
We're gonna take a stuntman,
put him in a jumpsuit, and CG him out.
And... fuck, I don't wanna jinx this,
but Lin-Manuel Miranda
wants to do the voice.
I love Hamilton!
The world loves Hamilton!
- Think...?
- [STORMFRONT] Excuse me.
- I'm sorry to interrupt this lovefest.
- [BOURKE] No.
- I just wanna be a part of it.
- Understood.
This... Ugh!
- Great work.
- Thank you so much.
This script is a great start.
Really good bones.
I just have a few headlines.
Totally. Listen, we can tweak dialogue
right up to the day of production.
Yeah, it's not really tweaks.
It's more... global.
Okay, yeah. What are we, um...?
What are we thinking?
Oh, um...
Like...
you write all women
as either unknowable Hitchcock bitches
or Michael Bay fuck dolls.
I mean, I get that a lifetime
of jerking off to Transformers
didn't exactly make you popular
with the ladies,
but a little effort would be nice,
you know what I'm saying?
Um, excuse me, but I do have two sisters,
thank you very much.
- Of course you do.
- And excuse me,
but Homelander really loves the script.
- Yes.
- So...
Oh, okay. Where is he?
[PHONE BUZZES]
Ashley?
Um, okay.
Fuck.
Okay. Just, you know,
continue doing what you're doing.
I just have to get to my...
I have to... I have a...
I just have to get to my next thing.
I have a...
I have a noon...
Can someone open this, please?
- Okay.
I got a few more headlines.
Mr Edgar.
Sir, if this is all true,
I will get a strategy together
with Crisis Management and PR.
We're fine for now, Ashley.
Sir, is it true?
- We're investigating.
- What they're saying?
Sir, I have to tell you something.
We have to tell Homelander,
and I have to admit something to you. I...
You don't have the faintest idea
where Homelander is.
He will know when I want him to know.
Just keep the rest of the infants on 99
in check, will you?
[REPORTER] And if you're just tuning in,
we have some major breaking news.
Superheroes are not born but made,
in fact, created by a chemical serum,
Compound V,
produced and administered
by Vought International,
the company that has been
the corporate face of superheroes
for decades.
Now, we don't know...
What did you do?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Oh, come on.
I saw you with the V in your hand.
Yeah, and you let me walk away with it.
So... this is kind of on you too.
If I go down, you come with me.
Pretty sure they'd kill us both.
You don't get it.
You don't fuck with the money.
You never fuck with the money.
We're gonna lose everything.
I mean, cars, houses, bonuses.
There are more important things.
You know, the only people that say that...
are the people who grew up with money.
...proving Vought has been administering
Compound V to children for decades.
Our very own reporting suggests
the parents also received
a very generous payment...
Started when I was 9.
...were treated with Compound V...
I was at the mall.
...Vought scientists throughout
their childhood under the guise...
We, uh...
We passed the pet store...
and I heard the goldfish
begging for their lives.
They were begging.
Then after that, I...
The beach, the aquarium, Red Lobster.
I thought I was going crazy, you know?
But my mom said it was a gift.
That I was born this way.
But it wasn't.
It didn't have to be this way.
I could've been normal.
[REPORTER]...suggests that
the first manifestation of powers
can cause fear and anxiety
in the affected children,
especially if they are not carefully
guided through the process.
So far,
Vought has refused to release a statement.
Likewise, Dr Jonah Vogelbaum,
former CSO at the company,
refusing comment.
He's been in seclusion
- since an undisclosed accident left him...
- Uh, hey.
Is this you?
You did it.
We did it. Um...
Call me.
Call me back when you get a chance.
...on their stock price,
which is already falling today.
Did what?
...huge trend
that could be potentially catastrophic
to Vought's bottom line.
- This news comes just as this company...
- You did this?
- ...was taking in record profits...
- Yeah.
Starlight did, mostly, pretty sure.
But I just gave her an old alley-oop.
- However...
- Hughie.
- Hughie! Yes! Dude.
- Okay.
The kid. Look at what you fucking did!
- Oh, my God.
- You lads touching your tips?
- Look at what the kid just did.
- Me and Starlight, but yeah.
- Petit Hughie?
- The fucking kid.
- Oh, shit.
- Okay, okay.
- Yeah!
- No, no, no.
Nice one.
That's all you got?
We've been trying
to do this shit for years,
Vought's finally fucking going down,
the kid did it, and "Nice one"?
All right, real nice one.
You can't even give me this, can you?
Not one goddamn win.
I'll tell you what.
When we're all done here,
I'll buy you a nice big family-size bottle
of top-shelf lube,
and I'll tickle your balls
till you beg me to stop.
And even then I won't.
I just won't do it.
But right now,
we got a Supe terrorist below deck,
and shit could go sideways just like:
So all of you
keep your fucking eyes on the ball.
Yeah?
Don't worry about him.
Yeah, fuck him.
You did great.
Isn't this great?
Yeah.
[HOMELANDER CHUCKLES]
Your mom ever bring you up here?
- No.
- Nah.
Of course not.
See, that is why a boy needs his father.
Hey, I think it's time.
Yeah. You ready?
Uh, ready for what?
To jump.
Wait, you can't be serious.
I'm not gonna jump.
Ryan, you're my son.
You can fly, just like me.
I don't want to.
You take a big deep breath, you step off,
and your body will just do the rest.
It'll just take over.
But I can't fly.
I'll just fall right off of here.
Hey, hey, hey, buddy.
You're gonna love it. I promise.
I'm nothing like you. I can't fly.
You can. You can.
I promise you can.
Dad, please.
Please don't make me jump.
Aw.
Buddy.
You called me "Dad."
[CHUCKLES]
[SCREAMS]
Ryan? God.
Ryan! Hey, hey, hey!
- What did you do?
- It's fine.
It's a 20-foot drop. Relax.
Inhuman fucking monster. Come here.
- Don't help him up. Let him do it himself.
- Come here. Hey.
Hey. Ryan, I need you to wake up.
Baby? Can you hear me? I'm right here.
- I don't think he's breathing.
- He's fine.
- I don't think he's...
- Mom?
- Hi. Hi.
- Look. See?
- Hi, sweetie.
- Told you.
Are you hurt?
- Does anything feel broken? Let me see.
- For God's sake.
Come on, look at him.
Not a scratch on him.
You know why? 'Cause he's my son.
And you...
You're raising him to be a pussy.
You don't get to tell me
how to raise my son.
I'm his father.
You don't get to say that
after what you did.
What I did to you
was give you a son
that you are raising like a little girl.
[BECCA] Let go of me.
He's mine.
Get your hands off of her!
Good boy.
You see? I told you.
- You're just like me, Ryan.
- [RYAN] No, I'm not like you!
I'm nothing like you!
I fucking hate you! Leave us alone!
Hey, it's okay. I'm not angry.
Ryan.
Go away!
- Buddy, it's okay...
- Leave us alone!
Ryan, this is a good thing.
These are horrible powdered cheese things,
but if you're hungry...
Fuck you.
So you do speak English.
Thirsty?
You know,
the way you talk with your sister
is no sign language I ever seen.
I just wanna help her.
I can help her.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
[IN ENGLISH] You understand?
The night our parents were murdered,
Kimiko just stopped talking.
Can't talk.
She's never made a sound since.
In the camp,
we were alone week after week,
just the two of us, for years.
We came up with a language
so we could get through it.
It saved us.
Both of us.
Will you teach me?
Please.
Fuck you.
I think your sister is very special.
And she loves you very much.
I don't know anything
about this Compound V monkey business.
If someone gave it to my little Maeve,
I sure as hell didn't know.
Bullshit, he didn't know.
I remember this one weekend
where he made me do three mall appearances
and a photo shoot for Teen Vogue,
all to get the cash for my braces,
which he then blew
at the five-dollar table at Circus Circus.
Maybe this is what we've been waiting for.
What do you mean?
They've lied to you,
from the beginning, all of them.
You don't owe them anything.
Maybe this is our chance
to leave while we can.
Elena, if we do that,
you know what'll happen.
I'll call you back.
I'm not, uh, interrupting, am I?
No, of course not.
Great.
It's funny, you know, uh...
of all the people here,
I've known you the longest.
Yeah.
Sometimes...
it just seems
like you're the only person I can lean on.
Yeah, I... I feel the same way.
You do?
Of course.
You...
Oh, fuck.
Life, huh?
It's crazy.
Who's Elena?
Elena's an old friend.
Since when do you have friends?
I was just venting
about all this fucking bullshit.
What bullshit?
Wait, you haven't heard?
Where have you been?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
What the fuck?
[AGENT ON LOUDSPEAKER] This is the NYPD.
This boat's been reported stolen.
You're all under arrest.
I repeat, this is the NYPD.
This boat's been reported stolen.
I thought you said
this boat belongs to a friend.
Well, a stranger is just a friend
you ain't met yet.
- [MILK] Don't fuck this up.
- [BILLY] I ain't gonna fuck it up.
[MILK] Vought's almost toast.
We're almost home free.
I said,
I ain't gonna fuck it up, all right?
Ahoy, gents.
I am the captain of My Big Wet Dream.
I'm holding papers signed by the owner
for the lease of this vessel.
So there must be
some kind of misunderstanding.
Look out!
Get his hands!
Mayday!
Time to go.
- What are you doing? We gotta help them.
- [BILLY] They're already dead.
You don't know that.
They... We have to try.
Literally everyone
is on their way here right now.
We stay here, we die too.
Fuck.
What?
I wasn't the one who fucked that up.
I know how you feel. I'm a freak too.
Oh, you shoot a fucking bow and arrow.
I'm amphibious.
Okay, just give me the phone.
Cancel the call.
Postmating Papa John's isn't gonna help.
How do you know what helps?
You don't know anything about me.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Let's just recite the 15 Tenets together.
No. Fuck you and your creepy shit, Eagle.
I'm hungry.
Deep. It's time.
Time for what?
For you.
It's your time to get back into The Seven.
- What?
- This came from Alastair himself.
Holy shit.
Who?
Alastair Adana. The leader of the Church.
He sits in the first chair.
Cool.
Guys, with everything going on, I just...
I don't think I can do it right now.
No, Deep. This is your journey.
You're ready.
You have been ready all along.
Now get out there and be a hero.
My dad always used to say,
"Where there's smoke, there's fire."
Vought lied to us about Compound V.
What else are they lying to us about?
We're down 68 percent in morning trading,
20 percent in the last 15 minutes.
- It hits 19, start a buyback.
- Yes, sir.
Jesus. What about the pharmaceuticals?
Pfizer's dismayed at our lack of ethics.
[BARASSI] Investor lawsuits,
breach of fiduciary duty, nondisclosure.
[SKILTON] Exposure for fraud,
assault, infliction of bodily harm.
- All policy exclusions, no coverage.
- We have two options.
Option one, deny. High risk, high reward.
But if we deny and they nail us,
if there's a legit whistleblower,
there's no coming back.
That's bankruptcy, criminal charges,
ten to 15 for everyone in this room.
[BARASSI] Option two, mea culpa.
[PRESTIA] They've called it.
Trading's halted.
Stan.
We gotta put out a statement.
Which one is it?
[SKILTON] Stan.
A power-drink can, Frenchie?
- You're a goddamn idiot.
- I was trying to help her.
Where the hell are your mates?
- New deal. You gotta bring him in.
- Grace, we're three miles offshore.
You just crashed a police helicopter.
Not exactly keeping a low profile.
All right. Where do you want us to go?
CIA safe house, Hazlet. Be there in 30.
- And, Butcher?
- Yeah?
Please be careful.
I will.
Fuck me.
[MACHINE] Please leave your name
and number and a message after the beep.
Hey. Hey, Annie, it's me again.
I was just wondering,
have you ever seen the music video
for that Billy Joel song
"You're Only Human"?
There's this kid,
and he's climbing up a bridge,
and he's gonna kill himself.
But then Billy Joel steps out
with his harmonica and tells him to stop.
"You just have to wait
for your second wind."
And now I feel like I'm that kid...
and I'm gonna drown and...
And thank God
I found my second wind, because it's you.
You're my second wind.
Um...
Look, I know it's exciting
taking down Vought
and being like James Bond and everything,
but you gotta be careful because
that stuff can go to shit really quick...
and you wind up
hurting the people that you love.
Like the way that I hurt you.
Um...
Anyhoo, that's all I wanted to say.
Second wind.
Fuck.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
I know I don't come up to 99 enough,
and I apologise for that.
But times like this tend
to give us clarity, don't they?
You and me are partners, after all.
A symbiotic part of a larger thing,
a living thing named Vought.
And that's how we'll get through this.
Together as Vought.
[A-TRAIN] But, sir...
I gotta say...
we didn't know about this Compound V shit.
None of us.
[EDGAR] Is that so?
Well, we're all victims here, A-Train,
but we'll get to the bottom of it.
I promise.
Right now,
catching this super-terrorist is the...
[HOMELANDER] Villain.
Super-villain.
Sure, whatever.
It must be our priority,
and it changes the conversation.
So you want us to go out there? Now?
I mean, we still need to be prepped
by Legal and PR.
- We'll be eaten alive.
- There's no time for that.
Well, I'm sorry, but I don't think
we have to damage-control your fuckup.
Hey, guys.
Enough.
We gotta pull together here.
- Thank you, Homelander.
- [HOMELANDER] Shh. Not you.
Us.
The Seven.
See, it doesn't matter
who made us or how we got here.
The point is...
we are here.
Together.
Family.
You guys...
you are my real family.
This guy? He doesn't care about us.
We're not his partners. We're his product.
So who gives a shit
if Vought burns to the fucking ground?
You should think
- before you say something you don't mean.
- Really? Should I?
We are not Vought.
You see, companies,
they come and go, but talent...
talent is forever.
The world still needs superheroes.
And that, family, that's what we are.
So let's get out there
and do what it is we do.
Let's take this cocksucker down.
Fuck Vought, huh?
I did not see that coming from you.
Maybe you don't know me that well.
Maybe I don't.
- How far?
- A mile. Right there.
[CRUNCH]
- What the fuck was that?
- What the hell was that?
Take the wheel.
We lost power.
Everyone, off the boat. Now.
Frenchie, grab the winch.
Come on. Let's go, let's go. Get in.
- Come on, come on. Let's go, let's go.
- Fuck.
Come on.
Frenchie, start it up. Go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
Look, there! Head for the storm drain!
[BELLOWS]
Oh, shit.
- [HUGHIE] Butcher! What are you doing?
- Butcher!
Butcher!
[ALL YELLING]
[WHALE BELLOWS]
[GASPS]
Fucking diabolical.
Where's Hughie?
Hughie!
Oh, jeez.
You all right?
Come on, son. We've gotta leg it.
Deep's here,
and The Seven won't be far behind.
Um, you know what? Okay, you guys
go ahead. You guys go ahead. I'm good.
Eh? What?
I'm just gonna sit here and wait,
if you don't mind.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
My second wind.
All right, listen. Come on.
- Come on.
- Get your fucking hands off of me!
Jeez.
All right, fine. Suit yourself.
All right. Come on, let's go.
[GRUNTS]
We can't leave the kid, man.
Pinocchio's staying put. Have at it.
Hey, kid.
What are you doing here?
[GRUNTING]
You ain't going...
I ain't going.
They're gonna be here any second.
Probably.
- Asshole.
- Yep.
This way.
Frenchie.
[MILK] Hey, Butcher.
Petit Hughie.
Hey, the kid's falling apart.
You know that, right?
Well, what do you expect?
He's a fucking civilian.
No, no, no.
It's not just him. It's all of us.
Move the feet.
Just move the feet. Come on.
Move.
We're at our breaking point,
at each other's throats,
and you keep pushing us and pushing.
- It's like...
- Yeah. Right over the fucking finish line.
We just need to keep our shit together
a little bit longer. Okay?
We hand that cunt over,
and I get Becca and you get your girls.
- We're right fucking there.
- Butcher, Butcher.
Hughie's not gonna make it,
and you need that kid,
more than any one of us.
He's your canary.
My canary?
You let your canary die,
how you gonna know
when you've gone too far?
Oh, fuck me. What a load of bollocks.
Look, I tried, all right?
The kid doesn't want a part of me.
So fuck him.
Come on.
Lucy. I promise
we'll harvest your blubber.
Jesus Christ.
Deep.
- Homelander.
- Hey.
- What happened?
- They killed her. They killed her, man.
- What?
I was trying to help out.
I got some intel on the boat.
We started to cut them off,
and they ran right into her.
I'm sorry. I tried to stop them.
I tried to cut them off.
[HOMELANDER] Okay. You're saying
there's people with the terrorist?
Look at me.
You're saying they're not alone.
- I think so.
- Did you get a good look at them?
Not really.
I was too busy worrying about Lucy.
Oh, Jesus. Right. Lucy.
But I think they went off
in the storm drains.
Can't be too far.
Uh, who invited you, exactly?
Starlight.
Listen, what I did was unforgivable.
I'm going to do everything
in my power to renew my light.
Not just for you but for all
the female people I've offended.
Renew your light? Did you just fucking
join the Church of the Collective?
- Maybe.
- You're an idiot.
Hey, easy on the religious persecution,
okay, new girl?
Starlight, maybe one day
you can welcome me back into The Seven,
but I know my road is long and hard.
Are you serious?
There is no fucking way
you're coming back.
- There's no need for language.
- All right, enough.
We do not have time for this.
Look, I am with you, sister, but first
we have to go get the terrorist, okay?
Everyone in the tunnels.
- Yeah, everyone in the tunnels.
- Not you.
Anyone gets eyeballs on the target,
he's mine, understood?
Go get them.
Noir.
All right, you need to hang back a bit.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Still got some work to do with the ladies,
but it's gonna be okay.
- You'll be back in no time.
- Really?
Sure.
One other thing, you...
You ripped your vest.
- What?
- Your gill is showing.
Cover it up.
It's disgusting.
[GROANS AND HEART BEATING]
Come on. Come on.
You okay?
Yep. I just need a little rehab.
I'll be fine.
Yeah.
I know you will, A-Train.
You got my message.
Annie, I...
[COUGHING]
Oh, come on.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
This guy? Again?
- I did not know...
- Shut it.
What, do you got rocks
in your fucking head?
Come here.
All right.
I'd like you to do something for me, okay?
Kill him.
Wait...
No, he... He's wanted.
Shouldn't we take him to the police?
Yes, he is. Yes, we should.
Kill him. Right now.
Chicks. Right, Hughie?
Oh, for God's sakes. Come on. It's easy.
Hands in the air,
like you just don't care.
[CHUCKLES]
Kill him.
Do it.
More incentive? Okay.
You kill him,
or I'll fucking kill you both.
Do it.
Oi, cunt.
William?
What a surprise.
Hey, you know, I had a great breakfast
with your wife this morning.
Pancakes.
Delicious.
Yeah.
Eat this, motherfucker.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Please. Don't.
Come on, Hughie.
Before that cunt gets out.
Come on.
Please.
I love you.
[IN JAPANESE]
I love you, too.
Hey, guys!
Call the foul!
[GIRL SCREAMING]
Dad...
Dad, are you okay? Dad?
[ENERGY CRACKLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
Aw.
Can't do your magic little hand thingy
anymore? How come?
[WHIMPERING]
Open your eyes.
I like to see the light go out.
Fucking yellow bastard.
Ugh.
I said he was mine.
You snooze, you lose, Gramps.
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[EDGAR] I know the news of Compound V
came as a shock to everyone.
As you can imagine,
this has been a very difficult day
for the Vought family.
Our focus now will be to learn the truth.
As I said, we are conducting
a robust investigation into Compound V.
But let me be clear.
I had no knowledge whatsoever.
We believe it was the work
of a small disaffected group of scientists
led by former Vought employee
Madelyn Stillwell.
But sadly,
there are more important matters at hand.
Everyone at Vought
sends their thoughts and prayers
to those families
that were affected today.
Though it is important to acknowledge
that this tragic event
could have been far worse.
Today's attack underscores
just how dangerous the threat
of super-terrorists has become.
And at a time like this,
America needs its heroes more than ever.
We live in a dangerous world.
Our brave heroes
were already fighting terrorists overseas,
but now America faces this war
on a different front: right here at home.
These enemies will stop at nothing
to infiltrate our borders
and attack our citizens.
Our superheroes
are the last line of defence.
And today's death toll
would've been much higher
had it not been for the brave actions
of our newest hero, Stormfront,
who stopped the terrorist
before he could take more innocent lives.
I don't want to imagine
what would've happened
if Stormfront hadn't been there...
[EDGAR CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
America is truly blessed to have her.
Ladies and gentlemen, Stormfront.
[APPLAUSE]
[STORMFRONT] Thank you, but we all know
who the real heroes
of this group are, right?
The people you see behind you.
The people who are struggling every day.
Let's give them all a hand.
- [REPORTER 1] How did you know what to do?
- [REPORTER 2] Stormfront, here!
Stormfront, over here, please!
Stormfront, look over here!