BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
...but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
NARRATOR:
Previously on The Flash and Arrow:
I'm just not sure I'm like you, Oliver.
I don't know if I can be some vigilante.
You can be better because you can
inspire people in a way that I never could.
FLASH:
You said you were writing about me...
...to bring hope
to someone you care about.
How would he feel
if that put you in harm's way?
You're giving hope to people.
I'm doing this for them.
Barry, when you met me, Oliver and Digg,
we were this well-oiled archery machine...
...but it didn't start out that way.
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you tonight.
You're worth being on time for.
BARRY:
Everyone on this planet...
...at some point in their lives,
has had a major case of the feels.
Those days when your heart is just too
small to hold the big things you're feeling.
Today's one of those days.
We think of our emotions like
they're these unique personal phenomena...
...that no one has ever felt what we have felt.
There is a basis in science
for every emotion we feel: anger, love.
As a scientist,
I know there's nothing magical...
...about what makes us feel something
for someone else...
...but then I see her smile.
Man, that cannot be science.
Oh, and there's a fresh bottle in the fridge
for when she wakes up from her nap.
Thank you.
Sir? Help you with something?
Thanks.
I'll be just fine on my own.
-Sir, you're not allowed to be back here.
-Nothing to get upset about.
[ALL GRUNTING]
WOMAN:
You're butting in line.
Barry, bank robbery in progress
at Cunningham and Sampere.
FLASH: I got it.
-Wait, that's where I bank.
Once superthieves showed up,
I went mattress.
[GUNSHOT]
EDDIE:
I've already missed the gym.
No. Five more minutes.
-Come on. We never get to sleep in.
-I know...
...but your dad hates tardiness.
[SIGHS]
Buzzkill.
The buzziest.
Another picture of the Flash came in. See?
That red blur?
-How do you know it wasn't Photoshopped?
-It wasn't.
It's not a hoax or a mass hallucination.
You know, every day someone new
accepts the impossible...
...and believes in him.
-Why can't you?
-I believe in what I can see...
...what I can touch...
...what I can feel.
Which means I believe in you.
IRIS:
Mm.
Do you mind? Thanks, man.
-Hey.
-Busy morning.
-Witnesses reported seeing a red streak.
-You should've seen it.
Everybody here was trying to kill
each other. I got here just in time.
It must've been a diversion, because there's
a half-million bucks missing from the vault.
There's a tracer in the cash stacks.
We're trying to find the signal.
Meantime, any idea what could've caused
such mass...this?
A neurotoxin, maybe.
I'm gonna swab some surfaces,
see what I can find...
...but I think maybe they got whammied.
-Did you just say "whammied"?
WOMAN: I got so angry.
I can't believe I did that.
I would never hurt anybody.
-You have to believe me.
EDDIE: I do.
Something is happening in this city...
...and everyone wants to pretend
like it isn't, but it is.
I think we should do something about it.
My boyfriend has decided
we need to eat healthy at home...
...so work is now the only place
I can eat what I like.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Were you saying something, detective?
The Blur, the Flash, the man in the red suit,
whatever he's called...
...he was spotted at the bank this morning.
The bank that was robbed
of half a million dollars...
...where a dozen people
tried to murder each other.
You think our attention should be focused
on catching Santa Claus?
I can't explain how he gets
to and from crime scenes so fast.
We need to figure out who this guy is
and what he wants.
You should ask your girlfriend.
She writes fan fiction about him.
Joe, help me out here.
Sorry, partner. I stopped believing in Santa
when I was about 8.
EDDIE:
Sir, we should worry about....
[EDDIE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, what's going on in there?
I think Eddie's trying
to convince the captain...
...that the Flash is a public menace.
Excuse me?
So after weeks of trying to convince you
the Flash is real...
...now that you believe me,
you're trying to have him arrested?
-What the hell?
-Thanks, Barry.
-Sorry.
-No worries.
The captain shot me down.
Look, I'm not feeling like lunch.
See you later.
He's just jealous.
Of the Flash?
-Should he be?
-No.
I'll see you later.
Barry, you need to get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah, I will, after I eat.
Anger, hate, aggression.
[IMITATES YODA]
A Jedi craves not these things.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
No one is feeling that quote?
Everyone in the bank went total savage
for like five minutes.
-And then they were fine again.
-Anger can be a powerful emotion.
If this metahuman can engender
irrational feelings of anger in his victims...
...he can do a lot of damage.
Detective West helped me get a copy...
...of the CAT scans the hospital did
on everyone at the bank. Take a look.
Look at this.
The emotion centers of the brains...
...are still showing signs
of being overwhelmed.
Particularly the area
that controls executive function.
The part that stops people from doing...
...random and potentially destructive things
that pop into their heads.
How do you think
the meta does it to them?
That's the half-million-dollar question.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
Hey, if you guys figure it out,
just give me a call, okay?
Is the Flash off
to another rooftop rendezvous with Iris?
No.
Yeah, but she probably just wants
to ask me-- I mean, you know, him...
...about metahuman stuff for her blog.
Do you want some advice?
No matter what I say,
I'm getting the advice, right?
Don't get involved, as the Flash or yourself.
You don't wanna be the one to blame
for their breakup.
Okay, I hear you.
[SIGHS]
[AIR WHOOSHES]
FLASH: Iris.
-Flash.
It'd be great to call you by your real name.
FLASH:
You mean like "Ralph"?
Is your name Ralph?
FLASH:
What did you wanna see me about?
-My boyfriend, he's--
-Did you guys break up?
IRIS: No.
-Oh.
IRIS:
He's a cop...
...and he thinks that you're dangerous.
And he's trying to convince his boss that
you're a menace that needs to be stopped.
I thought I should warn you.
Anyways, you should probably go.
You're not going.
CISCO [OVER EARPIECE]: Barry, you there?
-What?
Police got a ping from the tracer
in the stolen cash.
SWAT team's closing in
on the 1600 block of Pass.
Now stop ruining Iris' love life and go.
I've gotta run.
I bet you say that to all the girls.
What other girls?
MAN: He always paid in cash,
never seemed like trouble.
He's on the move.
-Freeze.
CERTO: Hold it right there.
-Hands up.
BIVOLO: Is there a problem, gentlemen?
Certo.
Turn around.
Certo, what are you waiting for? Cuff him.
You don't tell me what to do.
Get down!
[GRUNTS]
Nice mask.
FELICITY: It's comforting to know
that no matter what city you go to...
...Big Belly Burger is always going to taste
like Big Belly Burger.
You mean full of grease and salt?
I thought those were the secret ingredients.
[MOTORCYCLE RUMBLING]
FELICITY:
Oliver's back.
By the way, I gave Oliver
like a half-hour head start.
-Hi, Barry.
-Hey, Felicity.
How you doing, Digg?
You're fast.
-Did you guys not tell him about me?
-Well, seeing is believing.
Or drooling. Heh.
Hey. Thanks for showing up back there...
-...but I had that.
-Uh-huh.
-I was getting ready to make my move.
-What move? The one to the morgue?
-What are you guys doing in Central City?
FELICITY: Working a case.
Suspicious homicide in Starling
where the murder weapon...
...is a boomerang.
Cool.
I mean, awful.
I found traces of iron oxide on it.
Central City has the highest concentration
of iron oxide in the country.
Australian aboriginals
used boomerangs to hunt.
Mainly on kangaroo,
which is a surprisingly low-fat source of--
Ahem. We were following a lead when
we heard the SWAT raid over the radio...
...and I thought that I would come by,
watch you make your move.
I had a cousin got hit by lightning once.
He just developed a stutter.
Huh. Well, my team and I are after a nasty
metahuman who makes people angry.
Cool.
-I mean, awful.
-Since you're here, why don't we team up?
I help find your boomerang man,
you help find my rageaholic.
-We'd love to.
-No.
We'll handle our business
and head home.
The fastest way to find out about
the boomerang is to sic S.T.A.R. Labs on it.
Enough people know my secret identity.
Fine. I'll go. They already know who I am.
You can drop me off,
and I will meet up with you later.
FLASH: How about I give you a lift?
FELICITY: Ooh!
Man, that's not freaking you out?
Let's go.
-So, what'd you think?
-I think--
My shirt's on fire! Oh!
Oh, my-- Sorry.
[FELICITY GASPING]
I'm glad I decided not to go braless.
You guys remember Felicity.
I'll always remember this.
Hi, Felicity. It's so good to see you.
What brings you back to Central City?
-Not Barry.
-No, not Barry. This? Not happening.
We looked down that road and we said,
"No, thank you."
They get it.
Actually, I'm here because of this.
[CISCO GASPS]
Awesome. What are the wings made of?
FELICITY: Not sure. I'm thinking some sort
of composite or high-density plastic.
Reinforced with carbon fiber.
-Oh, that's weird. It almost feels like it's--
-Vibrating.
-Yeah.
Oh, I wanna run some tests,
and I wanna run them right now.
Mm-hm.
You guys come up with anything new
on our meta?
The officer who was affected tonight said
he saw a flash of red before he lost control.
I suspect the meta is inducing rage
via the ocular nerve.
Oh. Dr. Wells wants to see you.
Why do I feel like I just got called
into the principal's office?
Starling City vigilante.
-He calls himself the Arrow now.
-Oh, does he, Flash?
-Wait, what's the problem?
-We don't trust him.
You guys don't even know him.
I know he was wanted for murder in at least
12 different cases dating back three years.
I know there's been two major terrorist
attacks in Starling since he became active.
The cops are cool with him now.
He doesn't kill people anymore.
What about all the criminals that he put
arrows through? Those, what, don't count?
-He's a hero, Joe.
WELLS: You're a hero, Barry.
You offer protection, hope, light.
What that man does
is carry out a dark reckoning for his city.
It is a brutal, violent vision of justice.
One we do not share.
You truly think he's a hero, fine, so be it...
...but he's not the kind
you should be looking up to.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[SCREAMING]
That's my bad. That's on me.
I want that Arrow out of my city...
...tonight.
Do you think he can do everything
really fast?
I mean, how fast do you think he goes
to the bathroom after he's eaten something?
This is you watching my back?
Oliver, the Mirakuru soldiers are one thing,
but this....
ARROW: Whatever he can do now,
he's still the same Barry we met last year.
If you're so adamant against teaming up
with him, what are we doing here?
ARROW:
He's a good kid. And it's just a name, Diggle.
The man who rents this storage unit.
I want his name.
Hey.
The bad guy that you're after, the one who
robbed the bank, his name is Roy G. Bivolo.
Uh.... Thanks. How did you find that out?
The guy's still alive, right?
I'm just asking.
I thought you didn't wanna help.
I'm not. It's just a name.
-All right.
-Hi.
Hey.
One nonfat latte, extra sugar, for Felicity.
And one coffee, black, for Oliver.
I brewed you a fresh pot, so....
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Barry, um, can I talk to you for a second?
-Bye.
Ow. What are you doing?
You did not tell me
that you knew Oliver Queen.
-I know Oliver Queen.
-He's even more handsome in person.
-And his arms are twice the size of yours.
-Technically, they're not twice the size.
IRIS: He's on my three list.
-What's a three list?
My list of three guys
I'm allowed to cheat on Eddie with.
You usually don't meet people on your list...
...but now here he is,
and I just cannot stop staring at him.
[IRIS SIGHS]
Felicity, this is me noticing you staring.
We need to help Barry with this case.
-Why don't you wanna help?
-Because Barry doesn't really want my help.
He only thinks he does.
Harrison Wells and Barry's cop foster dad
both said you were dangerous...
...and a bad influence. Barry defended you.
You're gonna hawk me about this
until I say yes, aren't you?
I'm a hawker.
Okay.
-Okay what?
-Okay, we'll help you catch your bad guy.
-Great. "Metahuman."
-I'm not calling him that, Barry.
Partners?
-Partners.
-All right.
Hey.
You're late.
Barry, how can you have super speed
and still not be on time?
Sorry. I guess the super tardiness
kind of neutralizes it.
So how do we catch Bivolo here?
Oh, no, we don't here. We're here to train.
What? Like Rocky?
I read your friend Iris'
blog post on the Flash...
...and I visited all the crime scenes
you fought at.
-Don't you sleep?
-Last month, you took on Leonard Snart.
We call him Captain Cold.
We can talk about you giving your enemies
silly code names later.
You mean like over coffee with Deathstroke
and the Huntress?
The point is that you engaged Snart
on a commuter train, which he derailed.
Okay, there may have been some damage,
but I got the job done. I was the hero.
Barry, when you approach a new
environment, do you case every inch of it?
You could. You have the time.
But you don't.
You just run in blind.
There's a difference, Barry, between
having powers and having precision.
When I came to you thinking about helping
people, you said I could be an inspiration.
OLIVER:
Living this life...
...well, it takes more than a mask.
It takes discipline.
And since you are probably
as stubborn as I am--
Uh, what is that for?
You're gonna run over there...
...you're gonna come back at me,
and you're gonna get hit with an arrow.
[LAUGHS]
-No, I'm not.
-Heh, heh. Yes, you are.
Okay, fine. I will humor you.
Ready!
Ready.
Nice try.
[BARRY SCREAMS]
What, you shot me?
-I heard you heal fast.
-Aah!
Oh, God.
Hey. What's up?
Eddie's making his case
for the task force again.
I thought the captain
shot him down already.
Well, apparently, he's got a new argument.
The Arrow made another appearance
last night.
And you forgot to tell me
that you got Bivolo's name...
...from shooting that storage guy in the leg.
Technically, I didn't shoot him.
What word would you use to describe
how you got this info?
I'm gonna go with "torture."
I don't-- The Arrow gets results.
He's a crazy man.
Look, I don't actually disagree with you
at the moment.
But we wouldn't have Bivolo's name
if it weren't for the Arrow.
So maybe instead of judging him,
you should just be thanking him.
Two things I won't be doing in this life:
playing professional baseball
and thanking that lunatic.
[BEEPS]
-Stay.
-Have you heard of color psychology?
The theory that changes
in the color spectrum can affect emotion.
-It's nice to have another woman to talk to.
-I know.
I was thinking that if Bivolo uses color
to induce the temporary psychosis...
...maybe we can use light
and color to reverse it.
WELLS:
Miss Smoak.
A word, if you please.
Hey, what's up, doc?
Sorry, that was dumb.
-Remember, I went to MIT.
-Yes, you're smart.
Felicity, I like to surround my team
with known quantities.
That is because I find the unknown
to be toxic, dangerous.
Arrow is unknown.
I can assure you, Dr. Wells,
he's not dangerous.
To us.
Well, of that, I have little doubt,
and yet I find myself with a conundrum.
How can I completely trust a man...
...when I don't even know his name?
And so I was hoping, Miss Smoak,
that you could help me trust him.
Who is he under the hood?
That is not my secret to tell, Dr. Wells.
Of course.
I'll figure it out on my own.
[AIR WHOOSHES]
-Hey.
How'd it go with Oliver?
To be honest,
not exactly the partnership I thought it'd be.
-Did he do the thing with the arrows?
-You knew he was gonna shoot me?
Whoa. It's practically impossible
to tell when Oliver's making a joke.
We just got a ping from facial-recognition
software on Bivolo, a.k.a. Prism.
We have facial-recognition software?
-Happy Hanukkah.
-Where can I find him?
Traffic cameras just caught him
entering a residence at 168 Jarvis.
FELICITY: We should let the Arrow know.
-I can handle this solo. I've done it before.
-Barry, I really think you need to--
-Felicity, I don't need his help.
BIVOLO:
I knew you'd be coming for me.
I could see it in your eyes at the bank.
When I turned those people
against each other...
...it made you angry.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Have some real anger.
No signs of macular damage.
Your retina and cornea seem unaffected.
I told you, I'm fine.
You said Bivolo whammied you.
No desire to go MMA on any of us?
No.
Yeah, I mean, something weird happened
with his eyes for a second.
-Weird thing?
-Yeah, everything went red.
You were right.
Okay, next thing you know,
Bivolo was gone.
Look, obviously,
his powers didn't work on me, so--
It was stupid for you to go out there alone.
You take too many risks.
As fast as you are,
that's gonna catch up with you.
Caitlin, I'm not Ronnie.
You gotta stop treating me like I am.
You're right. You're not.
What?
You are such a lovable dummy.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
It's Oliver. He wants to have
another session.
I'm sure he's not gonna shoot you again.
Maybe you should wear body armor.
BARRY:
Thinking of new ways to embarrass me?
I'm not trying to embarrass you, Barry,
but you went after Bivolo last night alone...
-...and you lost him.
-Pfft.
-And you've never had a misstep?
-Of course I've had missteps.
Barry, I have been living this life
for almost eight years...
...encountering things
that you can't even fathom...
...and I'm still alive.
Not because super speed kept me
out of the ground.
It was because I realized
that I needed to keep learning...
...keep training, keep getting smarter.
And until you get that,
despite your best intentions...
...you will do more harm than good.
I finally see it.
You're a little bit jealous of me, aren't you?
A guy like you, handsome, rich...
...can have any girl he wants...
...jealousy's probably
a new emotion for you...
...so you might be a little slow
to get what it is that you're feeling.
-That's your theory?
-Absolutely.
See, you can train, lift weights...
...climb that stupid bar
until your heart explodes...
...but you'll never be as fast as I am.
You will never be what I am.
And that's gotta hurt
your rock-hard pride, Ollie.
I told Felicity you didn't want my help.
Yeah? You're finally right about something.
Allen. Where are you with the Bivolo case?
-I'm working it.
-Care to be more specific?
How about you answer me
when I ask you a question?
Hey, how about you back off?
Excuse me?
Look, I work just as hard
as anyone in this building.
I don't need you constantly berating me
to do my job.
When it's done, you will have it, all right?
Sorry, captain, he's having an allergic
reaction to some bad medication.
You remind him who answers to who.
Have you lost your mind?
BARRY:
I'm so sick of Singh talking to me like that.
He's still our boss. I know
you're upset about losing Bivolo--
Wait, wait. You're just like him.
Like Wells and Oliver
and everyone else my whole life...
...that didn't think I could get the job done.
You wanna help me, Joe?
You wanna help? Get my dad out of prison.
You helped put him there, didn't you?
JOE:
Barry, I need you to calm down.
Why don't we both take a ride
to S.T.A.R. Labs?
I'm calm, okay?
When I am not calm, you'll know.
Okay. I'll call you back later.
That was the Arrow.
He says Barry is acting strangely.
-Strangely how?
JOE: He's been whammied.
He was acting angry. It was scary.
And his eyes...
...they glowed.
It's possible his body's fighting the effects,
so it's hitting him slower.
When it comes to rage, that's not good.
The longer you suppress emotion--
The bigger the explosion.
Considering what he can do,
how do we even stop him?
A cold gun would come in real handy
right about now.
-Hey.
-I'm just saying.
None of us can stop Barry.
Fortunately,
Felicity knows someone who can.
I think you'd better call back Oliver Queen.
We're gonna need the Arrow's help.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON RADIO]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[STATIC CRACKLING ON RADIO]
Is this your way of telling me
you want satellite radio for Christmas?
[RADIO TURNS OFF]
-Look, I'm not mad at you.
-Good. There's no reason you should be.
Eddie, both you and the Flash care
about protecting this city.
You would both give your lives for it.
You're more alike than you think, okay?
He is not the bad guy.
How do you know so much about him, Iris?
He got in touch with me after I started
the blog, and I've seen him a couple times.
A couple times?
Why didn't you tell me about this?
Given that I think he's a hero
and you wanna put him in jail...
...do you really need to ask that?
How could you ever think
I would be okay with this?
[EDDIE GRUNTS]
I heard you've been looking for me.
All this time you've been trying to catch me,
and I caught you first.
Guess you haven't
read your girlfriend's blog.
Eddie, no!
[GUNSHOTS]
Ooh, see,
I knew the Arrow was Oliver Queen.
I had it narrowed down to a list of 150
people, but he was definitely on that list.
You have a way to stop Barry's rage fest?
I have an idea about how to do that.
Joe, I'm gonna need your help.
We need to find him
before he hurts somebody.
FELICITY:
I have him.
Facial recognition picked him up
on a traffic camera downtown.
Oh, God.
[EDDIE GRUNTING]
IRIS:
Eddie!
Who the hell are you, huh?
You think you can just come along
and get to have whatever you want?
What gives you the right?
What the hell are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What has happened to you?
-I feel fine.
-You are not fine.
How would you know,
because you write about me?
You don't know me!
You don't know who I am.
You never did.
I know that you have risked your life
to help people, to save them.
Someone who does that does not suddenly
turn around and wanna hurt people.
Please.
-No.
FLASH: Unh!
-Run.
-Eddie, run.
You need to calm down.
And you need to hold on.
I hope they turn Barry back
before he kills Oliver.
I'm more worried about what
Oliver might have to do to Barry.
Barry has superpowers,
Oliver has a bow and arrow.
Do you have any idea how many people
Oliver has killed with that bow and arrow?
Recurve bow arrows can travel up to
300 feet per second, so 200 miles an hour.
-Barry can run three times that fast.
-Whatever.
Oliver's been doing this a lot longer.
-My money's on experience.
-My money's on speed.
Please tell me you're not actually
having this conversation right now.
-You missed.
-No.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
Two thousand milligrams
of horse tranquilizer...
...should be hitting you anytime now.
[GRUNTING]
Where are you going?
-We're not done.
-Unh!
Is that all you got?
[ARROW GRUNTING]
Oliver, get up.
[BEEPS]
Fool me once....
[GROANING]
I still believe in you, Barry.
-Is this even gonna work?
-He needs to see the right colors.
Now, Joe.
[FLASH GROANS]
Barry?
You okay?
Oh, this is gonna be
a special kind of hangover.
[CHUCKLES]
So...
...it was a tie.
Oliver, I'm so sorry.
This is not your fault.
But we do still have your metahuman
to take care of.
Anything left in the tank?
Well, if not, there's two of us, right?
Right.
You think this will stop me?
I will make you tear each other to pieces.
-You will all die screaming with rage!
-"Blah, blah, blah, no prison can hold me."
Heard it all before, pal. Adiós, Prism.
I liked "Rainbow Raider."
-Okay, you don't get to pick the names.
-I have a prison like this.
Mine's on a nearly inhospitable island
in the North China Sea...
...but this works too.
OLIVER:
My identity is a closely guarded secret...
...known only to a few,
and if it were to get out...
...will endanger my family, my friends...
...and it would embolden my enemies
to retaliate at me through them.
What Oliver is trying to say is that
he had a lovely time working with you...
...and getting to know each of you...
...and he can't wait to do it again soon.
Right.
It didn't sound
like that's what he was saying.
I may not agree with your methods,
but thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey, if I had a DNA sample
I was unable to fully break down...
...do you think you could isolate
the genetic markers for me?
Sure. What's the sample from?
Canary's murder.
Of course.
Mr. Queen...
...I met your father once. Charity event.
One of the things we spoke of was you.
I think he would be very proud
of the man you've become.
Thank you.
And, please, call me Oliver.
There is something off about that guy.
Captain Singh approved the task force.
You wanted me to believe
the Flash was real. Now I do.
I believe he's dangerous,
and I am gonna take him in.
How do you feel about that?
All I know...
...is how I feel about you.
I will see you tonight.
-Hey.
IRIS: Hey, you guys heading home?
-Yeah. Can you do javas for the road?
-I will hook you up.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
IRIS:
You're welcome.
Um, so listen,
I'm really sorry for what I said in the field...
...and last night in the street.
I wish I could say it was all
because of what Bivolo did to me...
...but I guess I had more feelings bottled up
than I thought.
You can always talk to me.
Yeah. Thank you.
And you were right.
I still have a lot to learn.
There's one more thing,
and you're not gonna like it.
-Does it involve shooting me in the back?
-No.
No, the heart.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
That's not gonna work out for you,
and you need to let her go...
...for both of your sakes.
[IRIS & FELICITY
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Guys like us don't get the girl.
-You ready?
OLIVER: Mm-hm.
-This one's yours.
-Thank you.
WOMAN:
Oliver.
-Hi.
-How are you?
-Good. Good. It's been a long time.
-We never spoke after, and I'm so sorry--
WOMAN: No, I'm sorry.
I heard about your mother and....
She loved you very much.
She did.
-I should get going.
-All right.
-Who was that?
OLIVER: Hmm?
Someone that I used to know.
Hi, sweetheart.
Yes, I'm just getting you a hot chocolate.
Mommy will be home soon.
Got your message.
FLASH:
I wanted you to know...
...last night, that wasn't me.
It sure looked like you.
Yeah. I was affected
by one of the metahumans.
He messed with my head.
But I'm okay now, I promise.
I defended you.
Everyone told me that you would
bring me nothing but danger.
My father, Barry, Eddie.
I didn't listen to them.
I never listened to them.
But now it's time I did.
Don't contact me anymore, okay?
Iris...
...I'm sorry.
Me too.
Look at that. Better than an ATM.
Anyone tell you not to hang out
under the freeway at night?
You're liable to get robbed.
You got the shakes, man.
What are you, tweaking or just cold?
[GRUNTING]
I'm not cold.
[GRUNTS]