My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
(Barry) My father went to
prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
(Barry) And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
(Barry) Last night, on
my way to the morgue,
I saw something.
Taxi! Oh, come on!
I'm gonna be late!
Simon Stagg, remember him?
Hasn't been seen in, like, six months.
You're saying Wells knows where Stagg is.
(Mason) No, I'm saying Wells killed him.
I have evidence in a secure digital file
that will explain everything.
There is a tsunami heading for the city.
You need to get as far
away from here as possible.
I have not been able
to stop thinking about you.
Go!
Aah!
[gasping]
[dogs barking]
No, no...
Taxi! Taxi!
Oh, come on! I'm gonna be late!
Oh, boy.
(Cisco) Hey, what's going on?
- Dude?
- Yeah, Cisco.
I'm...here...
What happened? Why'd you stop?
I just got a little disoriented.
Well, you need to make up some time, man.
You better hurry up.
Hurry? What are you...
Hurry, as in get to the morgue.
The morgue? I was there.
Yesterday.
What are you talking about?
Come on, you gotta go.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[camera shutter clicks]
Hey, Barr. What's with all the water?
Did the sprinkler system
go off or something?
What? No, I checked the sprinklers.
They're all intact.
But the water has ice in it.
And the bruises on the coroner
aren't just on his face.
Check... look at his torso.
Whoa.
How the hell did you know that?
He was killed by hail.
We have to listen to the recording.
Recording?
(Thawne) Joe, we got something.
The coroner's office just installed
an automated dictation system.
Listen to this.
(coroner) Please... no more...
(Mardon) I'll stop when you tell me...
(coroner) Just stop!
(Mardon) Who killed him?
It's Mark Mardon.
He wants revenge.
[screams of pain on recording]
And I really don't wanna go.
He's your brother, Cisco.
Not by choice.
Okay, well, how bad can
a birthday party be?
Um, my folks think
Dante's stink don't stink.
Doesn't matter how much he screws up,
or how many times he gets into trouble.
In their eyes, he can do no wrong.
And yet, they never fail to remind me
that I can do no right.
What if I came with you?
What? Seriously?
Absolutely. You've done so much for me.
Let me be there for you for a change.
And I could look at old family photo albums
and see what little Cisco looks like
without long hair.
I'm rescinding your invite.
Clyde Mardon has a brother?
So, both Mardon brothers
survived the plane crash
and then the dark matter released
by the Particle Accelerator explosion
affects them both in...
(Barry and Wells) Virtually the same way.
That's right.
Only Mark's not like Clyde at all.
He can do things that
you couldn't even imagine.
You mean he's sort of like a...
- (Barry and Cisco) Weather wizard?
- Weather wizard?
Yeah.
[slurps] Mm.
(Barry and Caitlin) Trigeminal headache?
Mr. Allen.
A word please.
Yeah.
(Wells) You ruptured the
time continuum, didn't you?
You're experiencing temporal reversion.
- Yeah!
- How long?
Uh, a day and some change.
It's like I'm living it all over again.
Yeah, well that's good. That means there's
not too much you could've messed up yet.
How did this happen?
I... I don't know. I mean,
I was running faster than I've ever ran,
and the first time that I lived this day
some really horrible things happened.
There was a tidal wave and...
No. Do not tell me.
I do not want to know anything
about the future you experienced. Nothing!
Okay, but Dr. Wells, I...
Barry.
Time...
is an extremely fragile construct.
Any deviation, no matter how small,
could result in a cataclysm.
Now here's what you're going to do.
Everything you did before.
Every word you uttered,
every step you took,
you're going to do again.
And you're not going to tell anyone
this happened.
[sighs]
Good day, Dr. Wells.
Time will tell, Gideon.
Show me the future.
(Gideon) As you wish.
The future remains intact, Dr. Wells.
If anything changes,
alert me immediately.
(Gideon) Of course, Doctor.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey.
What's going on with you?
How'd you figure all that stuff out
at the morgue?
Lucky guesses, I guess.
Look, I'm telling you,
I'm gonna get Mardon if it kills me.
Joe, um...
I gotta run an errand.
I'll see you later. All right?
I didn't know there was
anyone else like me.
(Mardon) I'm gonna break out of here!
I'm gonna create a tidal wave
that destroys your entire city!
(Cisco) So, I still don't understand.
How did you find him?
I just had a hunch.
That's gotta be some kind of record.
[laughs] Yeah.
Well, there goes my excuse
for bailing on my brother's birthday.
Do you have any idea what you've just done?
Yeah, I do.
I just saved a lot of lives.
I warned you not to mess with the timeline.
Dr. Wells, if you would just let me
tell you what was gonna happen,
you'd understand why I did this.
Whatever tragedy you think
you've just averted,
time will find a way to replace it
and trust me, Barry,
the next one could be much worse.
Don Santini, they're here.
(man) Move it.
Oh, love the paneling. Mahogany?
So glad your house is made out of wood.
It's gonna be a pleasure watching it burn.
Aah! Refreshing!
What are you doing back
in Central City, Snart?
This is my city.
Our city.
I told you if I ever saw you again
I'd put the hurt on you.
You stir up trouble.
Trouble is bad for business.
It's time for you
and your family to pack up.
Leave town. Retire to warmer climates.
Finito.
And if we don't?
You will all freeze.
Or burn.
I heard about your guns.
I also heard that you lost them.
So, tell me, Snart.
What the hell are you and your pyro friend
gonna do without your fancy weapons?
This.
[fighting efforts]
[grunts]
Now that was fun!
Fun. Fun. Fun.
Go.
Tell the rest of the Santini family
there's a new Godfather.
And his name is Cold.
[Spanish party music playing]
- Hola.
- Coma esta.
Wow.
Your parents really
went all out with the cake.
Oh, well... it is Dante's birthday.
The most important day of the year.
Mi hijo was invited to play Carnegie Hall
when he was just 13 years old.
They invited the entire band, Mama.
(Mrs. Ramon) That doesn't
make it any less worthwhile.
[chuckles]
Hey. What's up, man?
- Hey.
- Glad you could make it.
Of course.
Hi, I'm Dante.
This is my friend, Caitlin.
Hi, Caitlin.
- Happy birthday, Dante.
- Thank you.
Here, I... I got you this.
- Oh...
- I think you'll really like it.
- It's...
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
[panting] I don't get it.
I've been running just as fast as I was
when it happened, and nothing.
I'm still here.
Any number of things could've
triggered the wormhole
that allows you to repeat your day.
Your emotions, your circumstances,
your cortisol levels, all of the above.
Well, I mean, my adrenaline was super high
since Iris and the entire city...
No, no, no.
No details. I told you.
All right, I'm sorry,
but Mark Mardon's
already locked in the pipeline
and nothing bad has happened.
Yet.
[knocks]
Detective.
Hey. What are you doing here?
So when were you planning on telling me
you took down Mardon?
I... I just haven't had a chance yet.
You got sidetracked, you mean?
No, Joe, you can't be mad.
I'm not mad.
But I am curious. I mean,
you were acting so weird
at the crime scene.
I always act weird.
Okay. Weirder.
Look, Joe, there are just
some things that I can't tell you,
and you're gonna have to trust me.
[phone vibrating]
Hey, Linda. Yeah, I know.
I'm so sorry. I... I lost track.
I'm gonna head that way now.
All right, bye.
I have a lunch date with Linda.
I gotta run.
And I don't suppose you're
gonna fill me in either?
No.
Mm.
[upbeat piano music]
Que linda, Dante!
Well, here is one who was touched by God.
Ah, I was a little rusty.
I haven't played in a while.
Oh, well...
If that was what you sounded like rusty,
I can't imagine what you sound like
when you've practiced.
Oh, for you, I'd practice
morning, noon, and night.
[laughs] That means you'd actually
have to get up in the morning.
So, Mom tells me you're still working
at S.T.A.R. Labs, huh?
Yeah. Why?
No reason, man.
Guess it was just hard
to find another job, huh?
Oh, I wasn't looking.
I actually like working at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And we couldn't do what we do
without Cisco.
Oh, he's loyal.
Just like a dog.
Oh, come on.
Why are you so serious, mi hija?
Happy birthday.
Hey! I am here. So sorry, again.
[exhales]
Well, you get a pass
considering you're never late.
Hey, um...
What's going on with you lately?
Nothing.
Come on.
Give me a little credit here.
[sighs]
I've just been dealing with
a lot of things lately.
I like you, Linda. And we really get along.
Relationships should be more
than just getting along.
Your heart should ache for me.
Does it?
You're not upset with me?
No one did anything wrong.
I really do feel a lot for you, Linda.
It's just...
Just not as much as
you feel for someone else.
Go get her.
"The Flash, speeding his way
into our lives."
It's a little bit on
the nose, don't you think?
I have something to show you.
Simon Stagg, remember him?
Hasn't been heard from in nearly a year.
Hey, Iris. Mr. Bridge, hi.
Do I know you?
Oh, no, we haven't met yet...
fully, you know, um...
Iris, can I talk to you for a second?
Uh, yeah, sure.
- We'll catch up later.
- Yeah.
Nice meeting you, strange young man.
Is everything okay with you and Linda?
Uh... No, that's done.
Oh, I... I am so sorry.
No, no, no, it's okay.
We're gonna be friends.
Um, yeah, no, it's gonna be awesome.
Uh...anyway, are you...
are you free tomorrow?
Do you want to get some coffee
and we can just talk and just
tell each other stuff...
I don't know, stuff we got
rolling around in there, you know?
I don't know.
O-okay, yeah, sure.
It sounds great.
Okay, great. Great!
All right, I'll see you.
I know you think Harrison Wells
had something to do with
Simon Stagg's disappearance,
but you're wrong.
[rock pop music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, man.
Thanks for meeting me here.
Even though... you can't get drunk.
[laughs]
No worries.
So, how was your day?
Great. But...
Linda and I did break up.
That's the first time I ever heard anyone
use the word "great"
to describe a break-up.
I have a feeling that I'm about to
move forward with someone really special.
Okay. Go ahead, Barry.
[laughter]
Hi.
I don't normally do this,
but I was watching you, and...
can I buy you a drink?
Uh...wow.
I mean, I'm really flattered, but I...
Actually, I was talking to him.
Um... I'm... I'm sorry,
you said... you said you were talking to me?
Yeah, I just told my friends over there
that I thought you were cute
and they dared me to come over here
and talk to you, so...
please talk to me.
Yeah. Yeah, I suppose I can talk to you
for a little bit.
[mutters suggestively]
Yeah, no, I was just leaving.
Make me proud.
[clears throat]
I'm Lisa, by the way.
Hi, Cisco.
I'm just in town for
this symposium at Mercury Labs.
Really? You... what do you do?
Oh, I'm a structural engineer.
Why do you look so surprised?
Can't a girl be an engineer?
No, of course. That's...
You just don't look like an engineer.
I can't help how I look.
I... I mean, it's good.
It's a... it's a good look.
It's a great look.
Well, you don't look so bad yourself.
Am I being pranked right now?
♪ ♪
What do you think?
(Cisco) I can't believe this.
The day started out
pretty terrible, but now it's
turning out pretty damn good.
- I'll say.
- Wow.
Look at this.
These are nice things.
Oh, we're just squatting.
We?
Yeah.
Me and my brother.
Hello, Cisco.
What exactly are
your intentions with my sister?
Oh, come on.
I should've known better.
I am not that lucky.
Please don't kill me
for kissing your sister.
You kissed him?
You're not dad, Lenny.
I know. Dad's in jail.
Sterling role model.
What do you want, Snart?
Guns. Heat and cold, to be precise.
There's no way I am making weapons for you.
Never again.
Mick.
[muffled moaning]
I know I would do everything in my power
to protect my family.
The question is, will you?
Dante.
Dante, just keep cool, okay?
- Let me do my thing.
- Oh, really?
And what? You're gonna save us
with your mechanical engineering skills?
Right now, my skills are the only things
keeping us alive,
so if I were you, I would shut up.
You shut up!
Ah! There she is.
I missed this baby.
Here it is. All finished.
You gonna let us go now?
You know, I took the
first gun you made me apart
dozens of times.
Learned how it ticked.
What went where.
Thought you could tamper
with the firing pin
without me noticing.
Nice try, kid.
[weapon whirs]
- Yes.
- Lenny?
Where's my gun?
Girl's gotta defend herself.
Besides, why should
you two have all the fun?
My sister needs a weapon.
Something that suits her personality.
Make me something pretty and toxic,
like me.
How about something with gold?
Gold.
[short laugh]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey!
- Hey.
One incredibly heavy cronut
and one Americano with an extra shot.
- Just the way you like it.
- Just the way I like it.
Yeah, I know.
I know you, Iris.
[clears throat]
So...what is going on with you?
You're acting like Christmas came early.
[laughs] Uh...
Yeah, no, I guess it did, kind of.
Look, Iris, um...
I still think about you all the time
and I know you've been
thinking about me too,
so let's just stop thinking
and start doing.
- Barry...
- I know.
I know that we both have awful timing,
but we were meant to be...
Barry, what are you talking about?
You and me.
We like each other.
Barry, we've been over this.
Okay? Nothing has changed for me.
No, but it has.
How do you know that?
I just...
I just know some stuff somehow.
I don't know, maybe it's like
ESP or something, but...
Barry.
I love Eddie, okay?
I'm sorry, but nothing has changed for me
since Christmas.
And you can't keep springing this on me.
Okay? It's not fair
that you keep making me the bad guy
who keeps telling you no.
[sighs]
[knocks and sighs]
What? No whoosh-in?
I needed the walk.
What happened?
Nothing, uh...
Linda... Iris...
I don't want to talk about it, actually.
Okay.
[sighs]
Have you talked to Cisco?
I've been trying him on his cell,
but he's not answering.
Kind of... worried about him.
He had a rough night.
Trust me, it got better.
[phone vibrating]
Hey, Joe. What's up?
Yeah, Snart's back.
Wait, Cold is back?
(West) Yeah, he was spotted at
the Santini crime family casino.
If he's hitting the Santinis,
we could be looking at
the beginning of a mob war.
[sighs]
Well, this day just keeps
getting better, doesn't it?
[sighs]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
You killed my brother.
You shouldn't have messed with my family.
(Lisa) That's funny.
I was gonna say the same thing about ours.
All that glitters...
[screaming]
[gunfire]
This is sick.
Well, you wanted us
to spend more time together.
[gun shots]
How many times are we
gonna go through this, Snart?
Until the best man wins!
Drop the gun!
We both know you're not
going to do anything to her.
Oh, by the way, meet my baby sister.
Lisa, Flash. Flash, Lisa.
(Snart) Cisco has been very, very busy.
Unless you want me to mail
small, frozen pieces
of him back to his family,
I'd take your hands off her.
Let him go, Snart.
I'll think about it.
Barr.
Witnesses reported seeing The Flash.
They said you had Snart dead to rights
but you let him go?
Why?
Cisco.
Snart and his sister have him.
Oh, man.
Okay. Get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'll get there when I can.
All right.
Allen.
Yeah, Eddie, I...
- [grunts]
- Whoa.
Stay away from Iris.
What the hell is going on here?
Hey, if you two have a beef,
you take it outside.
You know what the worst part is, Barry?
I thought you and I were friends.
[exhales]
So there's Cisco getting
into a car with Snart's sister.
And the license plate is iced over.
All right, Dr. Wells, you were right.
I... I... I screwed with time and
now time is screwing with me.
Cold is back, he kidnapped
Cisco, and Iris is...
Stop right there before
you cause another disruption
to the timeline.
(Barry) Please, Dr. Wells.
Please, I have to talk to someone.
Go ahead.
In the previous version of today,
Captain Singh is seriously injured,
Joe is in danger,
and Iris said she had feelings for me.
And now Cisco's life is on the line,
and Iris has no idea
she confessed those feelings.
But she still has them, right?
The unconscious mind, Barry,
it... it's a powerful thing.
It sounds like it took
this apparent disaster
to jar those feelings loose
and without a disaster, those feelings
remain deeper down.
Unaccessed.
I don't understand.
I thought that I was helping people
by stopping Mardon.
Yes, but this new ability of yours,
Barry, is dangerous.
You only traveled back in time one day.
What if you traveled back decades?
Centuries?
Imagine the havoc you could wreak.
But I will have the opportunity
to travel back in time in the near future
and save my mom.
Or...you're saying I shouldn't?
I'm saying
how many more people could die
if your mother lives?
Did you guys find Cisco?
Most people think
the hottest part of the flame
is the white part.
They're wrong.
[blows air]
You gonna admire those
or you gonna drink 'em?
Both.
[Speaking Spanish]
_
I told her you wanted to become a priest.
Broke her heart.
Why'd you do that?
Because I was jealous of you, man.
I mean, even then I...
I knew exactly where my life was headed.
- Nowhere.
- Dante.
That's not true.
I live at home.
And I work a crap job for no pay.
Yeah, but you still manage
to be mom and dad's favorite.
[scoffs] I don't even know why.
It's because they... they still think of me
as their son, the concert pianist.
But you, man, they never
understood your talents.
Never understood that
you pursued your passion
no matter what.
And me, I was just too scared
to even try.
[speaking Spanish]
_
Dant... Dante...
No!
Aah!
[glass shatters]
[fighting]
Oh!
Mick!
Mick, calm down!
Mick! We need them!
Mick? Baby?
It sounds like you're hungry.
(Lisa) How about you and
I grab some dinner?
I like you, kid.
You're smart.
You pulled yourself up
from humble beginnings.
You seem like a good brother.
You too.
Debatable.
You answer one question for me,
I'll let you and your brother walk.
What's the question?
The Flash. Who is he?
I swear...he always wears a mask.
Aah!
No!
No! Stop!
[cries in pain]
This is first degree frost bite.
Your brother could
recover with proper treatment.
If not, all his tendons,
blood vessels, and nerves
will freeze.
His fingers will need to be amputated.
No more concertos for
the Ramon family holidays.
Now tell me,
who is The Flash?
There's nothing the satellite thermography.
You were right. This is all my fault.
How is this your fault?
Brave heart, Barry. We'll get Cisco back.
(Cisco) I'm back.
(Caitlin) Oh, my God. Are you okay?
We were so worried.
What happened?
How did you escape?
I didn't.
Snart just let you go? Why?
He, um... he tortured my brother.
And he said he was gonna kill him
if I didn't...
if I didn't tell him...
Tell him what?
Who The Flash really is.
(Cisco) I, honestly, man, they...
they could've killed me.
But they were gonna kill my brother.
I couldn't let him do that.
[cries]
Hey.
I'm sorry, Barry.
- No.
- I'm so sorry.
I put you in that position.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Where are you going?
I don't deserve to be here.
I won't be the one to put you in jeopardy.
Not again.
Never again.
Hey.
What?
What a surprise.
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
As big a surprise as Eddie punching Barry
at a crime scene this evening.
Oh, my God. Is Barry okay?
Yeah. He...heals fast.
Look, Iris. This got complicated.
I know. I'm sorry.
Barry was too late. I'm with Eddie.
Let me ask you something.
Who do you love?
I mean, I love Eddie.
Okay. You need to make them believe that,
because right now, I'm not
sure either one of them does.
Okay?
Okay.
Did I ever tell you
how wise and amazing you are?
Not enough.
See you later.
- Bad time?
- Yes, actually.
[sighs]
Don't worry, I'll be out of here soon.
Well, before you shuffle off forever,
may I show you something?
I get it. I failed.
(Wells) No, no, no. Now, you're
an incredibly clever guy, Cisco.
So why don't you tell me
why would I bring you down here?
Because we all failed that night.
But we kept going.
We kept trying to protect each other,
and Barry,
in spite of the setbacks.
Making a choice
between two people you love,
that is the hardest dilemma
you will ever face.
Well, you won't have to worry about me
making the wrong decision again.
All you proved today, Mr. Ramon,
is that you're human.
All you proved today
is that you love your brother.
And the reason that we all want you to stay
is that we love you too.
Now, I am not a parent,
but, in many ways,
you have shown me what it's like
to have a son.
(Caitlin over intercom)
Guys, you should get up here.
Shall we?
The casino wasn't the target.
Then why did he do it?
Casinos keep tons of cash on hand
to cover their markers, not to mention
the money that they make.
But if they're under attack,
the protocol is to relocate
the money outside the casino.
So, that was Snart's plan all along.
- To trigger the move.
- Okay, where is it now?
[indistinct chatter]
Get ready, we got company.
Aah!
[gunfire]
[tires squealing]
[weapon whirring]
Oh!
[crashes]
Good to see you...
Barry.
We have to talk.
(Barry) I know Cisco told you who I am.
Can't really blame
the kid for giving you up.
You or his brother? Come on!
I put him in a tight spot.
Same kind I got you in right now.
Can't really stop me now
that I know who you are.
I could speed you to my own private prison
where you'll never see the light of day.
You could, but then I won't be around
to stop my own private uplink
that'll broadcast
your identity to the world.
So, the million dollar question.
What to do with me now, Barry Allen?
I won't let you keep stealing
whatever you want,
whenever you feel like it.
- It needs to end.
- Can't do that.
It's what I do.
Then find a new line of work.
Don't want to.
Why is that?
The same reason you keep
running after guys like me.
The adrenaline. The thrill of the chase.
I love this game.
And I'm very good at it.
Then go play it somewhere else.
- Leave Central City.
- Can't do that either.
I love it here. [inhales]
- This city is my home.
- [scoffs]
You've seen what I can do.
You know that I can stop you.
You want to keep pushing your luck,
go for it.
But from here on out,
no one else dies.
If you're as good as you say you are,
you don't have to kill anyone
to get what you want.
That's true.
And if you, or anyone
in your Rogues' gallery
goes near any of my friends
or family again,
I don't care who you tell my identity to.
I'm putting you away.
I guess your secret's safe...
Flash.
For now.
Oh, I don't suppose you'd give me a ride
back to town, would you?
The Rogues.
Cute.
[party music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
I...
I am so sorry, pal.
It's not like me to hit anyone.
I don't know what came over me.
Uh... thanks, Eddie. It's... it's okay.
You poor thing. I had no idea.
Is that right? Um...
what exactly did you have no idea about?
I was just explaining to Iris and Eddie
about your Lightning Psychosis.
My what now?
Your Lightning Psychosis.
How your recent odd behavior
is a side effect
of being struck by lightning.
Mood swings, sudden outbursts of affection,
and other lapses in judgment.
He has had all of those things.
He told me that he had ESP.
Yeah, it's a very uncommon
neurological phenomenon.
We're really only just now
starting to research in kerauno-medicine.
That's why Barry's been
spending so much time at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I just... I wish you would've told me.
I didn't... it hardly feels real sometimes.
We're just glad you're getting help.
Yeah.
So, we're good?
Yeah, we're good.
- Coffee?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
[typing]
[thunder rumbling]
Come on. Hey.
(Reverse Flash) Harrison Wells.
What do you know about him?
Ooh!
[whimpering]
(Reverse Flash) What do you know?
Everything I know is in that drive.
I swear.
Oh!
Ugh!
(Reverse Flash) Everything?
Everything! Just take it!
[panting]
You really were on to the story
of the century.
Well...
this century, anyway.
Do you think I made a mistake
letting Snart go?
I think you did what you felt
was right in the moment.
And really, Barry,
that's the best any of us can hope for.
Now, let's be thankful
the timeline remains intact.
Oh! I keep forgetting.
I've been meaning to ask you.
It's about Simon...
You were saying, Mr. Allen?
Uh...
Nothing. Sorry.
- Goodnight Dr. Wells.
- Goodnight Barry.
Barr, what's up?
Why did you want to meet up here so late?
I think that maybe you were
right, about Dr. Wells.
Which part?
All of it.