[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPRINKLER SPRAYING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPRAYING INTENSIFIES]
[TRAFFIC ROARS]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[INSTRUMENTAL "AMERICAN PIE" PLAYING]
[SONG CONTINUES OVER SPEAKERS]
Hi. Welcome to Endless Pasta Week
at Tony Cicero's.
Where the fuck am I?
You're at Tony Cicero's.
No. What fucking city am I in?
[HOSTESS] Uh, Fort Wayne.
Oh, fuck. You got a bit of paper,
something I could write with?
- A pen, anything.
- Uh...
Ah, ah.
[REPORTER ON TV]...closed at 10% below
its record high set last month.
Federal authorities
have initiated a multistate manhunt
for William Butcher
for allegedly murdering
Vought vice president Madelyn Stillwell,
as well as endangering
her infant son, Theodore.
Law enforcement officials have set up
a tipline and are urging anyone
with information regarding
the suspect's whereabouts...
[REPORTER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[GUIZMO'S "INDÉ-STRUCTIBLE"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Boy, girl...
I'm sorry. I do not understand.
All right, I'm off.
[HUGHIE] Where you going?
Going to meet a contact.
- Who?
- Someone who can help us
find this Supe terrorist cunt.
[HUGHIE] Who is the contact?
What is their actual name?
- You'll love it.
- No, I won't. I won't love it.
I never love it. I never fucking love it.
- Noted.
- Not a word from him.
He left us for dead,
and now it's like nothing happened?
You're right. I am sorry.
Sorry that I trusted this lot
was smart enough to save themselves
- like they've done a hundred times before.
- Okay, well, where you been?
Well, technically, I called him back.
He blew up Madelyn Stillwell.
I told you. She was already dead
when I blew her up.
Oh. Great. Cool. Totally.
We're just gonna pretend
like this is normal?
Like we're fucking lemmings?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, who else they gonna follow?
Right.
Hey. You know, my dad?
He had a ball from the '56 World Series
signed by Don Larsen himself.
Pitched a no-hitter in game five.
- Really?
- Pretty cool, huh?
- [BALL THUMPS]
- Oh.
That's okay. Uh, you'll get the next one.
- Yeah.
- [HOMELANDER] Yeah!
[RYAN] Yeah, I'll get the next one.
Okay. Ryan.
Use your powers.
What do you mean?
[GASPS]
I can't do that.
Yes, you can. You're my son.
Has anyone told you
what you're capable of?
No.
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOOR OPENS]
Well, then it's about time you found out.
Ryan. Come on, math time, buddy.
Chapters 12 and 13 in your workbook.
[SIGHS] Yeah. Math, yeah. Sorry, I forgot.
It's your favourite.
I'll be in in a minute.
When I was his age,
I was breaking the sound barrier.
He can't even throw a fastball.
We thought it was best that he have
as ordinary of a childhood as possible.
We?
Who's we?
Look, I just want my kid to be normal.
Then it's a good thing I'm here.
Because my son
is the furthest fucking thing
on this planet to a normal boy.
How long are you planning on staying?
Becca...
we had a deal.
A deal that is alive and well and running
around as free as a goddamn bird.
So let's just try and be civil, shall we?
Did I get them right?
There's... There's no correct
or incorrect answer.
Oh.
What is missing here?
[DEEP] Uh...
Deep. How do you expect
to be welcomed back into The Seven
if you can't be honest with yourself?
- Carol, if I'm being honest...
- [DOOR OPENS]
...I don't know what the fuck
you want from me.
Hey, guys. How's it going?
Can I have a word?
I don't mean to be negative,
but his operating perspective
is functionally non-existent.
I don't think there's a path here.
Leave it to me.
[KETTLE WHISTLES]
[EAGLE] You're just inhibited
by suppressive energy.
That's it. Just gotta realign things.
What is it, shrooms?
Last time I did shrooms
was at a Goo Goo Dolls concert
with some poli-sci chick from Oberlin.
I guess I call it more of a gateway.
[COUGHS]
[EAGLE CHUCKLES]
Are you not gonna drink any?
No. Deep, this is your journey.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[STARLIGHT] Who's revving up
the girl power in The Seven?
Keep watching WDCS,
Cleveland's first and best source
for local news.
[MAN] Quiet, please. Going again.
On the bell. Rolling.
- [BELL RINGS]
- Where should I start?
Are you ready to meet
the newest member of The Seven?
See it here first, WFAK...
- KMFT... WDCS...
- [WOMAN] Cut.
- [MAN] Quiet. Still rolling.
- She's the newest member of The Seven,
and she's taking America by storm.
From Portland to Seattle,
watch what comes next, KMFT.
[WOMAN] Amazing. Do you need to take
a break, or can we power through the rest?
Let's just power through.
- [CROWD CLAMOURING]
- [MAN 1] Turn this way! Look here!
[WOMAN] Over here. Give us a shot!
Gorgeous.
[MAN 2] Stormfront, show us what you got.
Okay, ladies, we have a big day.
Domestic outlets until noon,
ten minutes each.
Foreign until 2. Roundtables until 4.
Print one-on-ones until 6...
If she vibrates any faster,
that stick up her ass is gonna explode.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
[ASHLEY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Hello?
What?
When?
Okay. Thank you.
...positive, we're going female,
thoughtful but upbeat...
- Where...? What?
- [MAEVE] I gotta go.
- What? No.
- I'm sorry. Family emergency.
Is everything okay?
We've never had three women
in The Seven before. This is a moment.
Girls get it done. You're not...
I have a family emergency too.
[PRIEST] A reading
from the book of Revelations.
"And God shall wipe away all the tears
from their eyes
and there will be no more death."
Today, we say goodbye to Susan Raynor.
For though her body rests,
her soul lives on for all eternity,
and one day you will think of Susan
with joy as well as sadness.
They are two sides of a coin
you will carry forever.
And you are blessed to have your family
and your friends to help you carry it.
In the name of Christ, amen.
[CAR LOCK CHIRPS, CLICKS]
You think you can surprise me?
I literally taught you this one.
Hello, Grace.
You promised I'd never see you again.
I promised not to come
to your house again.
A subtle but important distinction.
I assume you sent the Edible Arrangement.
Deluxe Bereavement Bouquet with
white chocolate-dipped pineapple doves.
Raynor would've loved that.
Oi, where you going?
There are about two dozen federal officers
in the church next door.
I'm gonna turn you in for the murder
of Madelyn Stillwell.
Oh, come off it, Grace.
You really think I done that?
You really want me to answer that?
I know who killed Raynor.
Who?
Okay, well, I don't specifically,
technically have the answer to that,
but I know how to get it.
We think Vought killed her
for getting too close to something.
Getting too close to what?
Something to do with a Supe terrorist
smuggled into Jersey
a couple of nights ago.
And that is where we start.
Honestly, it's like asking a cockroach
to not be a cockroach.
It's just your nature.
I know what she meant to you, all right?
We find this terrorist, and we're one step
closer to finding out who offed her.
I'm not getting back in.
And if I were, which I'm not,
it sure as shit wouldn't be for you.
I ain't asking you all the way back in.
Just dip in a little toe, yeah?
Maybe two. Not for me, for Raynor.
You never gave a shit about Susan.
You're only here because you're desperate,
fucked, and you want something.
All right, fuck it. Grace, Grace!
Grace, wait, wait, wait. Wait.
I'll level with you, okay?
Just hear me out.
[OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ I just want you to know who I am... ♪
♪ I just want... ♪
[MUFFLED MALE VOICE] Hey.
♪ ...know who I am ♪
♪ I just want you to know who I am ♪
Hey.
♪ I just want you to... ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
Eagle?
Hey!
In here. Open up.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Bro, we gotta talk.
No, you gotta look at us.
Look at us!
Okay.
Remember Melissa Dabrowski?
The kindergarten teacher you fingerbanged
backstage at the VH1 Educator Awards?
So what?
You were supposed to present her
with Teacher of the Year,
but you bailed while she was pulling
her panties back on.
Yeah, because she laughed at me.
Bullshit. She just put
her hands on your chest.
You never even unzipped your suit.
She would've laughed.
Because that's what you do.
You imagine women will laugh at us,
so you humiliate them first.
No, that's not true.
You can't accept your own body,
so you violate theirs.
Sh...
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up.
Hey, hey. Hey.
- Let me out!
- You can't swim from us forever.
You shut the fuck up,
you ugly pieces of shit.
I have nothing else to say to you.
We won't let you shut
us up anymore, Kevin.
Hey, hey. Hey. Let me out, man.
Just let me out! Eagle!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Let me out, man!
Ride it, brother.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
What are you doing here?
Apparently, your work...
still has Maggie Shaw
as your emergency contact.
Ah, shit. Sorry.
That's okay.
Where else would I score this sweet jelly?
[ELENA CHUCKLES]
I thought it was bad unagi.
Turns out my appendix was about to burst.
Well, there are easier ways
to get my attention.
I kept thinking you'd call.
Yeah. Me too.
- You want me to call your mom?
- [SCOFFS]
Definitely not.
Someone else, like a girlfriend or...?
Seriously? Thanks for coming, but I'm sure
you have more important places to be.
Hey. You could die
from something like this.
But I didn't.
So I guess you don't need to save me.
Yeah, well, I still wanna see the doctor.
Maeve, I'm fine. I promise.
You know, watching Botched
doesn't make you a fucking medical expert.
[ELENA SCOFFS]
I'll wait a while. Let's just see, okay?
Can we get this middle chair out of here,
please? Somebody? Thank you.
Can we get the two on the side
just smushed together?
We lost one of them.
[MAN] Okay, resetting, one background.
- People, quiet on the set.
- Rolling.
Stormfront, congrats on The Seven.
Are you as excited to be here as I am?
[CHEERFULLY] I don't know.
I don't think so.
Can you tell us a little
about how girls get it done?
- [MAN 1]...girls get it done?
- [WOMAN 1]...girls get it done?
- [WOMAN 2]...girls get it done?
- [MAN 2] Let's dish boys.
- Starlight, single or spoken for?
- Uh, single, single. Single.
Uh, single. Definitely single. [CHUCKLES]
[WOMAN 1] Tell us how fun it is
to have all this girl power.
[MAN 2] Can you repeat that but say,
"Strong is the new pretty"
right at the end?
Do girls make better heroes?
[WOMAN 1] Do girls make
better heroes than boys?
Do girls make better heroes?
Look, uh, no offence.
I get you have your talking points,
but why does it matter
whether heroes have a dick or a vag?
I mean, shouldn't we all just,
you know, be competent at our jobs?
I don't think girls do anything better.
Chicks and dicks are in it together.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Oh, that's me.
Sorry, Ashy.
Vought won't let me have pockets
in this thing.
You can see every crease in my ass.
You can see up Starlight's uterus.
You wanna talk about girl power?
Let's talk about getting some pockets.
Starlight, your teammate A-Train
has been out of the public eye.
Mm-hm.
Vought recently revealed that he was
on a top-secret mission in Kandahar.
- Are you worried about him?
- Yeah, of course.
I pray for him every night.
America really is lucky to have
such a brave hero fighting for them.
What if I told you he's right behind you?
Hey! Here comes the A-Train!
What's up?
- Wow.
- All right. Yeah.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
- [STARLIGHT] Wow, welcome back.
- Thanks.
Thank you. Mm.
Stormfront, you know,
it is such an honour to meet you.
- I'm a huge fan. Don't get up.
- [STORMFRONT] Feeling's mutual.
No, yeah.
I'm just gonna relax for a second.
Let me get a chair or something.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [A-TRAIN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
This is crazy.
[HATIN TONEY'S "DAY ONE"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Got a little mama in my ride ♪
♪ They want shooter
They want pride ♪
♪ They want smoke
I'm on fire ♪
♪ See the truth
Tell no lies... ♪
Hey. How are you feeling?
- Fan-fucking-tastic.
- [STARLIGHT] That's great.
We were really worried about you.
- Do you play?
- Nope.
This is Prince's guitar from
"Purple Rain."
When I woke up, I was just like, fuck it.
I want that shit.
Shit, like, what I went through...
really gives you some perspective.
- You know?
- Totally.
They told me you came by my room
every day to pray for me.
- Thank you.
- [STARLIGHT] Mm. You're so welcome.
Yeah, I think that prayer
really does help.
- Anyway...
- Mm-hm.
You should know that everyone thinks
it was a really good idea
that you called me in
for backup that night.
I mean, what would've happened
if I hadn't been there to give you CPR?
- [A-TRAIN] Hmm.
- [SIGHS]
- [A-TRAIN] That's good to know.
- Mm.
How does everyone feel about you helping
your traitor fucking boyfriend escape?
Or maybe you didn't mention that part.
So...
Who did you mention that part to?
[BILLY JOEL'S "YOU'RE ONLY HUMAN"
PLAYING ON PHONE]
[HUGHIE] ♪ You're having a hard time
And lately you don't feel so good ♪
♪ Getting a bad reputation
In your neighbourhood ♪
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Just had a meeting with the colonel.
Colonel Mallory?
You saw her?
That's right, Frenchie.
She's gonna help us.
We get her the Supe terrorist,
and she's gonna get the CIA
to scrub our records clean.
Get the old bill off our asses,
and get you back to your girls.
[HUGHIE] How do we know
you're telling the truth?
734 Central Ave, Newark.
- What does that mean?
- [BILLY] That's the address she gave me.
Linked to the bank account
that smuggled that Supe cunt stateside.
And I'll bet you he's there.
Oh, my Lord. Ain't you twats lucky
that I showed up, eh?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
Ahh.
[GILLS] Melissa Dabrowski was more
than just another fingerbang, you know?
No, no, no. It's not fucking happening.
It's not fucking real.
The way she looked at you.
She was sweet, smart.
Girl like that, you could've been happy.
You deserve to be loved.
Don't fuck with me.
You deserve to be loved, Kevin.
But that starts with you.
Don't fuck with me.
Take a look. A real look.
Go on.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm the ugly one.
- [GILLS] No.
- Yes.
On the inside.
You just don't see what I see.
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
No.
♪ To me ♪
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
I'm not.
♪ You're everything I hoped for ♪
♪ You're everything I need ♪
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
[BOTH] ♪ To me ♪
[DEEP] ♪ Can't... ♪
♪ Can't you see? ♪
[BOTH] You're everything I hoped for
- [GILLS] ♪ You're everything I need ♪
- ♪ Everything I need ♪
[BOTH] ♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ To me ♪
[GILLS] ♪ Yeah ♪
So in short, do not waste
your hard-earned cash
on this shitty, big-titted hunk of plastic
that'll end up in a manatee's belly
when your kid chucks it in the garbage.
Hey, um...
I just gotta say...
I really like everything
that you've been saying about Vought.
Yeah, okay, cool.
No, I mean, I agree with you.
- You wearing a wire or something?
- What? What does that have to...?
Look, I mean this
in the nicest possible way,
but I don't need some fucking
Vought-spy Barbie sniffing around
to see whether I'm a team player.
What? That is not at all what I am.
I used to be a fan. But look at you.
You're like the Voughtiest Vought
in all Vought.
I think, uh, Cyclops Dude's
trying to get your attention.
[STARLIGHT] What happened to your eye?
Oh, Vought is testing a new volumising
dry shampoo for eye irritation.
As if you give a fuck.
Here. I brought you a sample.
Are you kidding me?
I can't take this right now.
I can't get away from this press junket.
- I literally have no pockets.
- You wanted the V, here it is.
If you threaten me again,
I'll make sure everyone knows you took it.
- [A-TRAIN] You tight with Gecko?
- Hey.
Yeah, uh, from Capes for Christ,
back in the day.
- Yeah.
- What'd you just put in your boot?
- [STARLIGHT] What? Nothing.
'Cause it looked like
you just put something in your boot.
Why don't you tell me what's in my boot?
[MAN OVER PA] Stormfront and Starlight,
signing autographs...
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Maybe you shouldn't be hitting the Cristal
with your buddies quite so soon.
Come on.
Let's finish dick-tickling these half-wits
so we can finally do our real job.
Shall we?
[BECCA] All right, kiddo. Here we are.
- Have a great lesson.
- Yep.
[BECCA] Okay. I'll be back in an hour.
I'm gonna have coffee with Miss Bird.
[RYAN] Yep. Um...
Thanks. Bye.
[WOMAN] Hi, Ryan. How are you?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Open the door.
- Open the fucking door!
- [GUARD] Please get back inside the car.
I want to talk to Dr Park.
Go back inside the car.
Goddamn it! Dr Park, now!
[PHONE RINGS]
- [PARK] Hey, Becca.
- What the fuck is going on?
I understand this is upsetting.
I was told I would never
have to see him ever again,
that he would never know
about Ryan or me.
That was the deal.
Homelander is quite upset that this
information was concealed from him.
Corporate has made a decision
not to antagonise him further.
You need to make him leave.
Because if you don't,
I'm gonna take Ryan and I'm gonna run,
and you'll never fucking find us
ever again.
I think we both know
that that's not possible.
You have to protect us.
You have... You have to move us, please.
I'm sorry.
Now that he knows, there's no putting
the toothpaste back in the tube.
You should probably be getting back.
Piano lessons are almost done.
Just keep him calm.
Our best guess,
he'll get bored and move on.
You... You don't know that.
You don't.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
Do I get to keep this?
Maybe. What will you trade me for it?
I will let you take me out to dinner.
Right.
I forgot. We'll need to order in.
Keep it low-pro.
Maeve, what are you doing here
if nothing has changed?
Oh, Christ.
The last thing that woman needs
is another nose job.
Okay, we've done this dance, thanks.
- Elena.
- It's time to go.
Homelander and I went to this Oscar party
for 12 Years a Slave.
There was this producer.
He swapped place cards
so he could sit next to me.
And he chatted me up all night.
Two days later,
there's a fire in his office.
They found his head in one room...
and his torso in another.
What are you saying?
I don't want him to do that to you.
Who?
Homelander?
You think Homelander did that?
The things that I've watched him do...
the things that he made me do...
If he ever finds out about you...
Why are you telling me this now?
I don't want you to hate me anymore.
Cool. Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's crazy
you don't have one already, actually.
I don't really have anyone
to call, though.
Well, you can call me.
You know, Ryan, um, when I was your age,
I didn't have many friends, either.
Mom says being lonely
makes you know yourself better.
Well, that's not wrong, I suppose.
Can I tell you a secret?
Man-to-man? You know?
My dad and I, we never played catch
in the yard with a World Series ball.
Truth is...
I never had a dad.
Or a mom.
Wait, you didn't?
See, sometimes it's hard, Ryan,
being superior to every single
other person on the planet.
It's isolating.
And gods should not have to feel
that kind of...
you know, pain.
Because that is what we are, Ryan.
You and me...
we're gods.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Son, we can do anything we want,
and no one can stop us.
Now, that...
That's a good feeling.
A really good feeling.
And now
you and me can share it together.
I...
I should probably go to bed now, you know?
Sure.
[PATS RYAN'S ARM]
I love you, son.
Now you say it back.
Um, I love you too.
This is nice.
- Your turn, Mom.
- You need to leave.
Excuse me?
You need to get the fuck out of my house.
What happens one day
when Ryan asks
to go to a baseball game,
swim in the ocean,
or eat at a Burger King?
How is he gonna feel when he finds out
that you've lied to him his whole life?
Think he's gonna be happy
that you kept him in this pretty prison?
Or... do you think
he'll fucking despise you?
Hmm?
Let's go ask him.
Don't.
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYING]
You were right.
I'm not gonna get bored and move on.
I'm not going anywhere.
So feel free to tell Dr Park
to go fuck himself.
How about some Jiffy Pop?
Halothane shot.
I only got two of these, so...
[BILLY] Well, we better make it count.
[FRENCHIE] What if it doesn't work
on the terrorist inside?
Then we're right and well fucked.
Are you okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Shining Light Liberation Army.
The ones who kidnapped you?
You know this man?
What is going on?
Kimiko?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
Mouse.
I never thought I'd see you again.
Boy and girl.
Her brother.
That's what she was trying to tell me.
Butcher, wait, wait, wait.
It's her brother.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SILENCED GUNSHOT]
- [ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Kimiko!
Wait!
Hey.
You don't know me.
I'm not a sellout.
Oh, okay. Cool. Congratulations.
Oh, come on.
Why do you care what I think?
Maybe I want to say everything
that you're saying about Vought.
Maybe I think Vought's...
What? What's Vought?
Oh, my God.
Everyone is so fucking stage-managed.
Life isn't actually a PR strategy.
You can say what you think.
[STARLIGHT] What if it's not safe?
You are literally bulletproof.
What the fuck is gonna happen?
Okay.
Who's the greatest superhero of all time?
Hmm. Homelander?
No. Pippi Longstocking.
Pippi Longstocking,
she's a 9-year-old girl,
lived in a house all by herself?
Pet monkey?
Could lift a horse with one hand?
You haven't read Pippi Longstocking?
I guess not.
Hmm.
Okay, well, I used to dress as her
every Halloween,
and all the girls dressed
like Disney sluts would make fun of me.
And you know what I thought?
I thought, "Who fucking cares?"
Pippi didn't care. She never cared
about being polite or cute.
Look.
Fuck this world
for confusing nice with good.
Be a bitch if you want. Be whatever.
Just drop the mask once in a while.
Feels good.
You can finally breathe.
Oh, and if someone sticks a dick
in your mouth, bite it off.
Pippi Longstocking would bite a D.
That's for damn sure.
[FRENCHIE] Butcher!
Hold on, mon ami.
- [MILK] Give me your hand.
- Okay.
No. No, Butcher! No. Easy, easy, Butcher.
The CIA would have locked him up
in a black box forever.
- She'd never have seen her brother again.
- Easy!
Both of you, please. Not now.
Right.
You...
fuck off.
The rest, you're with me.
[DEBRIS CLATTERING]
Well, come on. Don't piss about.
We ain't got all night.
[GUN COCKS]
The fuck you waiting for?
Are you telling me
that her family is worth more to you
than you seeing your own?
No.
I'm not.
But Kimiko is one of us.
I'll find another way.
I suppose you agree, don't you?
Since your tongue is halfway up her ass.
Jesus.
It's like Hughie's infected you both
with a raging case of vagina!
Becca's alive.
What?
She's alive.
Vought's holding her captive somewhere.
Butcher, if you...
No, I'm not stark raving, all right?
I fucking saw her.
She had a little boy with her.
The spitting image of Homelander.
I thought he just wanted to humiliate me,
show me what he'd done to my girl
before he gave me the good news.
Then I woke up three hours later
in a Tony fucking Cicero's.
God knows why.
I gotta find her,
and I gotta get her the fuck out of there.
And I need your help to do it.
Are you fucking with us?
I find the terrorist for Mallory,
she finds Becca for me.
That's the deal I made.
I know what I done to you. All right?
And by rights,
you should tell me to fuck off.
But still...
I'm asking.
[IN JAPANESE]
When you...
When you disappeared that night...
I'm sorry.
We were supposed to watch out
for each other and then you were gone.
Shining Light sent me here.
Put the needle in my spine
and filled me full of the blue poison.
I should have found you.
No. I'm the big sister.
I should have come back for you, but...
...they made me into...
...a monster.
If that's true, we're both monsters now.
Did it hurt?
I wanted to die.
Me too.
They had one dose left
and they knew it worked on you
so they figured it would work on me.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
[CABINET OPENS]
[AIR WHOOSHES]
Who, uh...? Who we sexting?
What...?
What are you doing in here? Get out.
I'd... Okay.
Look, you got me.
I'm having a heavy flow day. It's...
- What are you doing with this?
- This is not how it looks.
Okay? It's just a misunderstanding.
Homelander should have charred your ass
as soon as he found out
that you were fucking Hughie.
Hughie saved your life. We both did.
Your mistake.
Okay, if you just give me a minute,
I can explain.
You know,
I just want you to think about me
when you're getting the skin
peeled off your face, bitch.
You're not gonna tell anyone anything.
Who says that I haven't already?
'Cause then I'd already be dead.
You're not gonna do shit.
Why is that?
'Cause you killed your fucking girlfriend.
That's what you told Hughie, right?
That you killed Popclaw?
You can't prove anything.
Did she suffer?
Did you look into her big, sad eyes
while you did it?
Fuck you.
Yeah, see,
I looked at the Vought forensics report,
and...
[SIGHS] Wow.
All those needles jammed into her arm
at the same time?
I mean, one of them
actually shattered the bone.
Did you know that? Would someone
really do that to themselves?
I mean,
doesn't look like an accident to me.
I mean, Vought's happy to bury it,
but, you know, say, if...
Sports Illustrated found out...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you do that...
I'm gonna take you down right with me.
And then we'll both be dead.
[SCOFFS]
Go ahead.
Fucking try it.
I don't give a shit.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[IN JAPANESE]
These people you were with...
They keep me safe.
They'll keep you safe too.
Or we can go home. Back to the village.
There is no village anymore.
What?
They came for us.
Who?
The Americans.
This hero came shrieking
out of the sky like a demon.
Destroyed the camp.
And all the villages around it too.
There were bodies everywhere.
Everyone's gone.
Then we'll go somewhere else.
Back to Japan.
Maybe grandma and grandpa
are still alive.
You don't care?
That the Superhero split
an old woman in half?
That the entire school caved in
with the kids inside?
That babies burned alive in their cribs
when the propane tanks exploded?
I never wanted this.
But they were right all along.
Shining Light is full of shit!
Shining Light fights injustice.
They stand up for
people without a voice.
They murdered our parents!
This country is an enemy
to the whole world now.
We need to fight back. Fight with me!
You're the boy who nursed
every mouse who lost its mother.
That was a long time ago.
You're still my brother.
Then... you know I have to do this.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[TYRES SCREECHING]
Are you all right? Mon coeur!
Well, cheers, love.
At least someone's got
some sense around here.
You come between me and my missus again,
I'll fucking kill you.
[TALKING HEADS' "PSYCHO KILLER" PLAYING]
Hey, kid. You coming?
♪ I can't seem to face up to the facts ♪
♪ I'm tense and nervous
And I can't relax ♪
♪ I can't sleep 'cause my bed's on fire ♪
♪ Don't touch me, I'm a real live wire ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run
Run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run
Run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You start a conversation
You can't even finish ♪
♪ You're talking a lot
But you're not saying anything ♪
♪ When I have nothing to say
My lips are sealed ♪
♪ Say something once, why say it again? ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run
Run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa, better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run
Run, run, run away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ooh ♪