[light orchestral music]
♪
[whooshing]
Infinite velocity will soon be mine!
And once my ascension is complete,
all will bow before
the might of Godspeed!
Ah!
[dramatic music]
♪
Gideon, let CCPD know I've got Heart.
I'm bringing him in now.
Guess you couldn't run
away forever, Heart.
[grunts]
Never anger a god, little one.
Whoa!
Whoo!
[laughing]
Yo, that was so crash.
What the hell was that?
You just phased through a speedster.
Who didn't see me coming.
Your molecules could have
conjoined on a quantum level.
Do you not know what that means?
No, no, I don't. I don't,
because I'm a freshman in college,
and I don't learn quantum
physics till my junior year.
- You remember that, right, sis?
- Whatever.
Bart, you have to stop
pulling these crazy stunts.
You're still learning how to
control your meta-abilities.
My meta-abilities just saved the day.
You saw that.
Also, I am expanding
my boundaries, right?
Like, who knows what else you could do
if you actually pushed yourself?
Seriously?
Did you not just see my lightning lasso?
Okay, that's really bad.
Warning. August Heart now located
at 5724 Fontana Drive.
The Flash Museum.
You're too late.
Now the future belongs to Godspeed.
- If he gets away...
- We'll never find him, but...
Mom and Dad will kill us, so...
Screw it.
[heroic music]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Wait.
The guy we chased through
time, August Heart,
has no speed and no memory now?
And he has dozens of clones
all fighting each other?
Maybe even more now.
Hey, that was an amazing
story, by the way.
The whole phasing through
the baddies like that?
Oh, dude, amazing.
Bro, I've been working
on that move for a minute.
So epic. I mean...
Thanks, bro. I appreciate it.
Also, I'm Chester P.
Runk, team tech guru,
and it is an absolute pleasure
to meet the kinder of Flash and Iris.
[laughs] Chester, we've already met.
You improved my gauntlet's
efficiency by, like, 2,000%.
You're also the smartest person we know.
I am?
Oh, oh, my God. Yeah, absolutely.
Dude, you help me with my differentials
of mathematics homework,
like, all the time.
All the time.
Don't forget that.
Both: Grammy Cecile!
[laughs] Hi.
Oh, my God.
I feel so much love from you two.
I can't wait to get to know you both.
[laughs] Oh, hey, Caitlin.
Oh, what up, Cait?
Hi. It happened again?
Yeah.
Just wish Iris was here to meet them.
Dad, Mom's gonna be fine. It's okay.
Yeah.
Well, with Nora and Bart here,
at least we've got the
extra muscle that we need.
Uh-uh. West-Allen family rule #1:
Protect the timeline
at any and all cost.
Can't stay.
[soft dramatic music]
Actually, you can.
- Really?
- What?
Look, the Godspeeds are
recharging themselves
in the Speed Force, so as
long as that's the case,
there's no way back.
So maybe you are safer
here with us...
- Oh. [laughs]
- And I don't know.
I mean, maybe you're
the advantage we need
to finally end this
war, once and for all.
Cecile's helping me with the MAD 2.0,
so we can unlock August Heart's
memories, but no luck yet.
Okay, Barry, I think I got something.
[laughs]
Okay, so I was going through
my Pops' old schematics,
and I found this.
It reconverts the atomic mass
of neutrinovoltaic energy cells.
Pops called it a solar
encryption engine.
Cool. What does it do?
It neutralizes
artificially created
kinetic energy sources.
Like Godspeed's artificial speed.
And I already built a prototype.
I just need to charge the battery
with an electromagnetic source.
Hey, have you seen Allegra lately?
No, not since yesterday, when
she said goodbye to Esperanza.
Hmm. We'll find her.
But, with any luck, the S.E.E...
Huh, huh? S.E... you get it?
Will be fully charged and
functional within an hour.
All right.
Dad, with this, we can stop Heart
and his clones in his tracks.
We can win this war.
[sighs]
- [burps]
- Ew.
[both laughing]
It's okay, Dad. We don't bite.
Okay. Yo, check this out.
I got one more.
No.
[hiccups]
[burping]
[laughing] Oh, gross.
Whoo.
Nora, you can just
ignore the family rules
for a minute and rewind that.
Sure. How would I do that?
Wait.
Is this about the other Nora?
You know about her?
- Totally.
- Yeah.
I mean, you and Mom have
told us a ton of stories
about her, and I'm so glad that you did.
I feel like part of her
is still alive in me.
[alarm buzzing]
Barry, we've got more Godspeed clones
southwest of City Hall.
Okay. Time to go to work.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
Let's go?
You mean, like, all three of us go?
Yeah. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, yeah.
All right.
[dramatic music]
♪
Okay. Secure the area.
Make sure there are no
civilians in harm's way.
What about them?
Let them kill each other
and then clean up the mess.
Dad?
Okay. Split up, and keep moving.
We'll run out the clock
until they have to go back and recharge.
None of the Godspeeds are behind me.
Nora, how many are following you?
None here either.
Where the heck are they?
Found them.
All: Kill the adversary.
Strike him down. Kill the adversary.
Circle back. We'll fight them together.
No! No.
I'm gonna lead them away from the city.
No you're not. Now, listen to me.
♪
You all right?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. [laughs]
I mean, yeah.
They couldn't keep up with
the fleet-footed wonder.
They went to recharge, you idiot.
What's your problem?
You were supposed to circle back.
Bart, why do they all
follow you and not us?
What are you not telling me?
All right, which one of you is
gonna tell me what's going on?
All those clones just
tried to kill you, Bart.
They were calling you "the adversary."
Why? What's going on?
Dad, we can't talk about this.
Look, right now, I don't care
about what kind of rules
I have in the future.
I want to know why
every Godspeed out there
just tried to kill Bart.
Because he's my Thawne.
[dramatic music]
Dad, Godspeed is my arch-nemesis, okay?
He's my one big bad to rule them all,
just like you and Thawne.
♪
[sighs]
Bart, Thawne devoted
his entire life to destroying mine.
He murdered your grandma.
You can't just throw his name around
- without knowing what it means.
- I know what it means!
Bart, it's okay.
Why don't we all just
try and take a breath?
[melancholy music]
♪
Maybe we should go train?
If we want to take
on those clones again,
we gotta work on our Fathwoom Boom.
Fine.
We'll be in the Speed
Lab, if you need us.
♪
Oh, thank the universe.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Look, you are not gonna
believe what went down
while you were gone.
Barry and Iris' kids
showed up from the freaking future.
[laughs]
Now it's like we got two Marty McFlys.
You okay?
Yep. Need something?
Yeah, well, the Godspeeds
left to go recharge again,
but the intervals between their attacks
are getting shorter and shorter.
So I need this ready
for when they come back.
Ta-da!
It's my Pops' solar encryption engine.
I mean, I've still gotta
do a few final tweaks,
but I also need a way
to charge the battery.
So you came to the human charger.
Got it. Fine.
Let's go.
- You forgot your java.
- It's fine.
Yeah, but you can just take it to go
and hit it with a microwave blast later.
I already nuked it, Chester.
I just don't want it anymore.
Now, can we get this over with?
Nuked it, huh?
That's when the suspect confessed
to the bombing in Polokistan.
Did Creyke say anything else?
Because Kristen Kramer
died in that explosion,
and that means you're dead.
No. That was everything.
Great. That should be it on our end.
- Car you asked for is out front.
- Great, thanks.
I'm having a hard time trying
to reach anybody in Central City.
It's like the whole
town lost cell service.
- You tried CCPD?
- Multiple times.
No answer, and I need to
get in contact with Cecile.
Hey, anything else
you want to say to the feds?
I've said all I need to say.
Let's get moving.
Bhikkhuni Amala confirms Wally West
is in deep meditation,
handling unrest on the psychic plane.
Which means we're out
of speedsters to call.
Iris? Hey.
[warm music]
How are you here? How is this possible?
Deon was able to stabilize
me enough to come back
until he can find a permanent cure.
Oh, thank God.
I've missed you so much.
It's been impossible
without you here with me.
Well, I'm here now,
and I'm gonna be fine.
With everything that's happened...
The war, you needing to
heal in the Still Force...
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, now that you're
back, it's perfect.
♪
It feels like you wanted
to tell me something.
It can wait.
Iris, oh, so much has happened.
You're not gonna believe this, but...
Our son and daughter are here.
Yeah. How did you...
I was watching from the Still Force.
Deon let me see everything
that happened, and yeah.
They're amazing.
I mean Nora, she's all grown up,
and Bart,
he's already a young man.
It's incredible.
So you were with me the whole time.
Yeah.
♪
So you know
who Godspeed is to Bart
and how much danger he's in.
[dramatic music]
Bart knows what Thawne's done to me.
The pain that he's
caused, so if Godspeed
is Bart's Thawne...
Then what did he do to Bart?
Iris, those Godspeeds
quit fighting each other
to go after him.
I don't think they're gonna stop
until they've killed our son.
♪
Then we can't let him go out
there until the war is over.
[resolute music]
Barry's never gonna believe this.
I can barely believe it either.
In the last 40 days, the
Speed Force saturation
in your body has gone
from 0 to 100, Jay.
[sighs]
You know, a year ago,
I thought I'd never run again,
but then I hit the jackpot.
And just in time too.
Because an army of evil speedsters
is attacking Central City?
Joan, I know I'm rusty,
but Barry needs
all the help he can get.
Fine, but I've got a patient
going into surgery at the clinic.
So when you're out
there please remember...
- Be careful?
- Watch your head.
Doctor's orders.
All right, old man.
Time to get in on the action.
[dramatic musical crescendo]
[dark music]
♪
What the hell do you want?
You, Jay Garrick.
We want you.
[dramatic music]
What gives, Bart?
You can throw stars with your lightning,
but you can't catch a ball
of it in under 20 seconds?
Nora... [heavy breathing]
It's a lot harder than it looks.
Well, maybe you should stop focusing
on being a badass parkouring
off every wall you see.
So you agree I do look badass.
That's it. That's all
that I've ever wanted from you.
Nora, understand, I can do
all the stuff, not... Mom!
Hi! [laughs]
[all laughing]
I told you she'd be okay.
I'm just glad our
family's finally together.
I am so happy to see you guys.
I'm so sorry I couldn't get here sooner.
No, it's all good. Seriously.
Deon already told us
about what happens when...
Never mind. What's up?
- We need to talk to you.
- Oh, can it wait?
We're just... we're
working on a new move
that we're actually
gonna use on Godspeed.
I think you're gonna like it a lot.
It's kind of old-school, which
I think you're gonna be...
Bart, you won't be going into the field.
Yeah, Bart,
your dad told me everything,
and I saw the rest in the Still Force.
Look, it was one thing
when Godspeed was just some meta
that you two were fighting
in the future, but...
He's your Thawne, which
means it's personal.
Yeah. I mean...
Okay, Dad, I am sorry
for how I reacted earlier, but I...
You don't know me...
like that yet.
I can keep my cool. I promise.
I can. Tell them.
I can keep my cool, right?
But you can't.
♪
Bart.
Dad.
I know Bart can be a bonehead,
but he's right.
You've only known him for a few hours.
I've known him for 19 years.
I got this. Trust me.
[warm music]
♪
[sighs]
They are so incredible.
- We make great people.
- Yeah, we do.
[somber music]
♪
Thought I'd find you moping in here.
You always come here when you're angry.
How could you turn on me like that?
You're supposed to have my back.
I still do.
Look, I get why you're angry
after what Godspeed
took from you, from us?
Godspeed... Nora,
Godspeed didn't take Uncle Jay.
He killed him.
He killed Uncle Jay...
Right in front of me.
Yeah, sure.
Dad and Uncle Wally
taught me how to run,
and how to meditate,
and all that's great.
Uncle Jay understood me.
He was the first person
that saw my impulsiveness
as a strength and not as a weakness,
and he would literally tell me.
He'd say, "Bart, sometimes
you have to take a risk.
"Sometimes you have
to go with your gut...
and is it impulsive? Maybe.
But sometimes it's right."
He got me...
[sighs] And now he's gone.
I know.
But you've still got
me, and Mom, and Dad.
How can... can't we just tell them
what Godspeed did?
Like, I feel like if Dad
knew, he would understand
why it has to be me who takes him down.
Because if we did that,
we would be breaking
- the most important rule.
- I know, I know.
I know, I know. I know, I know, I know.
Look, Bart,
Uncle Jay did say that
stuff about taking risks,
but if he were here now,
seeing what we were up against,
what do you think he
would want you to do?
[sighs]
He'd tell me sometimes
you have to take your hat off.
See? I'm always right.
Someti... You are sometimes right.
Look, I will take Godspeed
down for the both of us.
I promise,
but you just gotta stay here, okay?
[heroic music building]
♪
[sighs]
Since the MAD 2.0 isn't working,
we need to try another tactic.
[dramatic music]
♪
Does this remind you of anything?
This seems so familiar.
Are you all right?
Ever since I lost my memories,
I've been trying to understand who I am
and how I ended up like this.
I figured I must have had a breakdown.
Maybe somewhere there's a wife and kids
wondering what the hell
happened to their dad.
I don't know.
Am I ever gonna know who I am?
[machine whirring]
[sighs] Come on.
What's wrong with me?
So I finally finished the
last tweak on the S.E.E.
Now all that's left to do
is to finish charging the
solar panel, and voilà.
[laughs] Oh, man.
My Pops would be so jazzed
to know that this baby's maiden voyage
will be to take out psycho speedsters.
[sighs] You're almost done, right?
How should I know?
Battery's not even 10% charged yet.
With your output capacity,
it should be almost 89% charged by now.
Allegra, are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure? 'Cause, like,
you've been acting...
Chester, I'm fine.
[alarm buzzing]
More clones just showed up.
Is your father's device ready?
Chester's gadget, yes, but
the battery needs recharging.
It needs kinetic energy
to power it, right?
- Yeah.
- Could it be any source?
- Theoretically yeah, but...
- All right, stand back.
Well, hot damn.
Yeah, it's ready now.
I need you two on comms with Iris.
- Wait, Iris is back?
- You heard him, let's go.
[heavy breathing]
I'm in position.
Nora, are you ready?
On my way with the guests of honor.
Now!
Holy shrap. It worked.
[both laughing]
Uh, guys?
Sensors are picking
up a massive increase
in the clones' kinetic energy.
They're recharging.
[grunts]
Nora?
[heavy breathing, grunting]
[heavy breathing]
Nora? Nora.
Flash, we gotta go.
You sure you're okay?
Dad, Mom, I'm fine. I swear.
So how did the Godspeeds
recover so fast,
let alone recharge themselves?
It's like they got
stronger all of a sudden.
I think I know how.
Okay, so the S.E.E. battery
needed 700 nanometers
of microwave energy
to power the device,
but the battery wasn't
charged by Allegra.
- It was charged with...
- My lightning.
Which was equivalent to 5
billion nanometers of energy.
So Barry's lightning
supercharged the S.E.E.
Yeah, when the Godspeeds were blasted,
they got a super dose of
your Speed Force energy too.
Barry, I am so sorry.
Look, I should have seen
this coming, and I...
No, man. No.
You did everything right.
This is not your fault.
Okay, so how long until
the next batch shows up?
45 minutes tops.
But I'll see if I can
get my Pops' device
working again before then.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[sighs] What are you thinking?
Even if we get the S.E.E. working,
we're still outnumbered.
We need reinforcements.
Hell to the yeah you do.
- [sighs]
- How long were you listening?
Not long. Not long.
I mean, just long
enough to hear that Dad
finally realized that
he should tag me in.
He meant me, dumbass.
- No, I didn't.
- Wait, what?
Nora, we almost died out there.
I couldn't protect you.
I'm not putting you
in that position again.
Yeah, but we didn't die, and I can help.
Mom, a little backup here, please?
Nora, this war is unpredictable,
and it's getting more dangerous.
What do you think Bart and I deal with
every day in 2049?
Yeah, come on. We're heroes.
Dangerous is, like,
kind of part of the job.
Not this time.
You don't just get to decide that.
I'm about to turn 30.
In four years.
The point is, unlike Bart,
I'm the real adult.
We're your parents, and
we're saying right now
you're still not going out there.
You can't stop me from fighting.
Okay. Me either.
Mom?
Your father is right.
Well, you can't just
send us back to 2049.
That's not an option,
and we're not gonna go
watch TV at Grandpa Joe's.
We could always lock
you in a pipeline cell
until this is all over.
- You wouldn't.
- [laughs]
We will if we have to.
[sighs]
[somber music]
♪
[knocking]
So battery's not the problem.
I checked the spectrum readings,
and you're not emitting microwaves.
You've been blasting ultraviolet light,
like your cousin.
As far as I know,
you only hit that range from
channeling negative emotions,
like anger or pain.
Allegra, what's going on?
Nothing.
Before, you said you nuked your coffee.
It was ice cold.
And then you called me Chester.
You never call me Chester.
Did you get in a fight with Esperanza?
'Cause you can always patch that up.
Not this time...
Because she's dead.
Allegra, I am... I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault. It's mine.
Esperanza was my family,
and I should have been there for her.
Just like I should be able
to charge this stupid thing,
but I can't.
And now, more people are gonna get hurt,
and it's all my fault.
It's not...
This whole parenting thing
is different this time around.
Yeah, I know.
I always knew our kids
would have a hard life
being speedsters, but I never thought
they'd have to deal with
a Thawne of their own.
It's like there's a curse on our family.
I mean, tragedy follows us everywhere.
Maybe that's our real legacy.
You don't believe that.
This all started the
night Thawne killed my mom,
and I might not know where he is now,
but our fight still isn't over.
And in the other timeline,
Nora's Godspeed killed
her best friend, Lia.
And now, I think this Godspeed
killed someone Bart loved.
History's repeating itself.
[sighs]
Iris, if we beat
the Godspeed clones here, in 2021,
the real August Heart will
never get his powers back.
Which means that when Nora
and Bart go back to 2049,
there won't be a Godspeed
there to endanger them.
We have to break the chain.
We will.
[alarm buzzing]
Okay, the rebel
Godspeeds managed to hack
S.T.A.R.'s communication systems
and send a transmission.
What does it say?
[dramatic music]
Flash.
Turn over the adversary now,
or else the one he loves will die:
Jay Garrick.
♪
- What did Joan say?
- It's true.
Jay got his speed back when
the Speed Force was reborn.
And then those clones took him.
- They're gonna kill Jay.
- I won't let them.
Bart, we've got this under control.
No, you don't.
We're working on a plan.
Just give us some time.
We don't have time, Dad!
Guys, I'm triangulating
the Godspeeds' comm signals now.
It came from Zauriel
Cathedral on Morrison Ave.
- Well, that's where I'm going.
- Bart, wait.
Dad, they knew how Bart would
react if they took Uncle Jay.
He knows he's running into
a trap, but he doesn't care.
You have to stop him.
You have to save him.
We have to save him.
[uneasy music]
♪
Jay.
I won't let it happen again.
♪
Your inability to
suppress your rash nature
shall be your undoing.
[screaming]
You want more speed? Come take mine.
Nora, what are you doing?
Buying you some time. Save Bart.
His primal impulses killed him,
and now he's killed you too.
Bart? Bart!
Can you hear me? Bart?
They're right behind me. Bart?
- Get him out of here.
- Yeah.
That way.
Okay. Put him down.
I say we give them heck, Flash.
On my mark.
I leave Central City for two seconds...
That won't hold them much longer.
Dad, Bart won't wake up.
[machine beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪
I should have stopped him from going.
- Nora, this isn't your fault.
- Yes, it is.
I'm his older sister. I'm
supposed to keep him safe.
This is what Godspeed always does.
He always goes after the
people we love the most.
How's he doing?
He's still unresponsive.
Bart's in some sort
of deep comatose state.
The Godspeeds were feeding off me
when Bart turned up,
and by the time they
turned their sights on him,
I had nothing left in the tank.
How'd you know how to stop them?
Actually, it was my son's idea.
I guess sometimes it
pays to be impulsive.
Can't argue with that.
Why hasn't Bart's
speed healing kicked in?
It has, but is Speed Force saturation's
so depleted that
whatever speed he has left
is being used to keep him alive.
I'll keep monitoring him,
but unfortunately, all
we can do now is wait.
[bell dings]
I don't know. [sighs]
Maybe if I would have
gotten there faster,
Bart would be okay.
No, you saved our butts.
She's right. It's good to see you, man.
It's good to see you.
Dig filled me in.
I figured you could use a helping hand.
Jay Garrick. [laughs]
Look at you getting your speed back.
[both laughing]
- And good timing too.
- I'll say.
Listen, guys.
This war isn't over,
and now, there could be dozens
or hundreds of those things on the way.
I'll keep working on the S.E.E.
Hey, how about we use those gauntlets
to fire another entropy trap?
Synthetic entropy trap.
Unlike Time Trapper, mine are temporary,
and the stronger these clones get,
the faster they're
gonna break out of them.
So we don't have a way to depower them.
We don't have a way to capture them.
What do we have?
We have August Heart,
and we know he went to
the Flash Museum in 2049.
We just don't know why.
But it must have something
to do with why this war
got started in the first place,
which means Heart has the answer
locked inside his mind.
I need to unlock it.
[sighs]
What about the neural hypercollider?
I mean, we used it to project
my consciousness into the future.
So maybe it could project
your consciousness into Heart's mind.
So you want to go inside
the mind of a psychopath?
It's the only option we have left.
If I readjust the tachyon booster
with a neuro-fiber housing,
I think it could work, kid.
Can you guys take care
of things in the field
- while I'm in there?
- Of course.
Central City's my hometown.
I'm not losing her that easy.
Me too; I'm ready to
kick some fakester butt.
All right. Good.
I need you guys to protect this city
while I finish this fight.
So you gonna talk about it?
Talk about what?
That Creyke said that he saw you die.
Just drop it, West.
I spent years letting Adam haunt me
for the pain that he caused,
the lives he took.
Now I can put it behind me
and get back to doing my job.
[car horns honking]
My God.
What the hell?
Looks like the whole
city's trying to leave town.
Kramer, watch out!
[tires squealing]
Oh!
That was close. [sighs]
As soon as I flip the collider,
your synaptic pathways will open,
and then Ms. Horton will guide
your consciousness into his.
Don't worry.
I am gonna be right here
with you the whole time.
Barry, I know
this August Heart seems harmless,
but the real August Heart is
locked away inside of his mind.
- From what we know...
- He's a monster.
Be careful.
The collider's primed.
Ms. Horton?
I'm ready.
[sighs]
Yeah.
August?
If you're not comfortable with
this, you don't have to do it.
It's okay.
I need to know who I am,
even if it's someone I despise.
Yeah.
[sighs] Okay.
[electrical zapping]
Barry's synapses are
ready for transference.
Barry, follow my voice.
Flash.
[mysterious music]
♪
[heavy bass music]
I've been here before.
No, you have not.
This is my mind.
My place.
My future sanctum.
Heart?
Congratulations.
You finally found me.
Well done.
You knew I was coming.
Actually, I expected you
a lot sooner,
but hey, we can't all be overachievers.
You must have so many questions.
Good thing I have all the answers.
[voice distorting]
This is gonna be so much fun.
[dramatic choral music]
♪
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --