♪♪
I'll take this.
Merci.
Sorry about all the...
Oh, don't be stupid. You did us a favor.
What are we gonna do with him?
Ah, we'll take care of it.
The-the, uh, tracking chip.
FRENCHIE: Already disabled.
Sit down and relax, Petit Hughie.
Oi, where you think you're going?
I'm going home. I need clothes.
We'll get you clothes.
I want my clothes.
I'll be right back.
You are, perhaps... in
a state of shock, mon ami.
Hughie, you just arse-bombed
America's sweetheart.
You can't just piss off.
I need to go home.
All right. Frenchie will go with you.
Wait, what? No.
Either he goes with you,
or I break your legs.
Good lad.
Translucent's skin, it won't burn off.
Where you gonna stash it
Homelander can't find it?
Nowhere.
But we can slow the cunt down a bit.
("STOP!" BY JANE'S ADDICTION PLAYING)
♪ No, love teachers! ♪
♪ Lit to pop and nobody
is gonna stop... ♪
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Come on in.
Ms. Stillwell. Hello.
Please sit.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Starlight, that video.
- Ms. Stillwell, please.
- No, no. Let me finish.
The date-rape girl? The victim?
She saw that video on YouTube
and she came forward to thank you.
She could not have been more effusive.
That's... that's good, right?
It is fantastic. You're
polling through the roof.
You have a huge boost with men...
for the ass-kicking, of course...
but with women, too.
They love the empowerment.
16 points with females 18 to 49,
even in the liberal
retreat jurisdictions
like New York and San Francisco.
- I don't know what to say.
- You just have to enjoy this.
This is so good for you.
And it's so great for us,
because it is a partnership, after all.
- This is Seth and Evan from marketing.
- Hi.
They have some brilliant
ideas on how to capitalize
on all the buzz. Gentlemen.
- (QUIETLY): Okay. So...
- Yeah.
Now, small-town Iowa girl,
unexpected child prodigy,
is chosen for The Seven.
LAMBERT: Destiny knocks on
the girl next door's door,
and she answers, to fight
for truth and justice
- side by side with her heroes.
- The Big Apple is rough, tumble.
It's got worms. Muggers and
rapists and thieves, oh, my.
Dorothy is not in Kansas anymore.
Or Iowa. Poor girl gets
knocked around something fierce.
- Kicked while she's down.
- So what does she do?
Does she cry in her milk?
- Does she quit?
- No way!
- (MOUTHS)
- She adapts! She transforms!
LAMBERT: Embraces her
feminine strengths.
REED: Good-bye, Yellow Brick Road...
And hello, Starlight.
I can't wear that.
What?
Why not? It's beautiful.
Seriously?
I-It's just...
It's not me.
ISADORA: I designed Homelander's suit.
- This isn't my first rodeo.
- REED: You're wrong.
It's totally you. It's bold,
it's brave, it's feminist.
- How is that feminist?
- LAMBERT: Empowering.
It says you're confident
in your own skin,
and you're not afraid to show it.
Most importantly, it tells the story.
Of your transformation, of...
of what you're going through.
How exactly do you know what
I'm going through, exactly?
I'm sorry.
I-I appreciate the effort,
I really do, but I'm
fine with my old outfit.
- We're not.
- Excuse me?
Starlight, like I said
before, this is a partnership.
In a partnership, there
is give and there is take.
It's my body.
I have the right to choose
how much of it I show.
That is true. You do.
You just won't be doing it in The Seven,
unless it is wrapped in that.
REPORTER: Tomorrow,
A-Train versus Shockwave.
The race of the century.
The question now, Al, is
can A-Train keep his title
as the fastest man alive?
Or is tomorrow the day
he runs out of track
at the hands of this
fresh-faced young challenger?
Just wait here, okay?
REPORTER 2: Tomorrow,
live on pay-per-view,
the race of the century.
REPORTER: Well, Shockwave...
♪♪
(PANTING)
(HUGHIE SNIFFLES)
Hughie?
Oh, hey, Dad.
Wh... look at the,
- you-you've, this is...
- Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry about this.
I just, I've been meaning
to clean up the Supe stuff
for a while now, so...
What, are you going somewhere?
- Yeah. For a while.
- Where?
Uh, I don't know.
Well, now, you're scaring me, Hugh.
All right, now, I-I
spoke to Dr. Feldman...
- My pediatrician?
- He's still your doctor.
And he's given me the name of
someone you can-you can talk to.
Help you, you know, get back to normal.
There's no normal anymore.
What do you mean, there's... Look.
We've always been very
open with each other, right?
We-We've always told
each other everything.
- Talk to me.
- Stop it.
- What do you mean, stop it?
I have never told you everything.
I have never told you how much
I hate sitting on that couch,
staring at the TV like
we're already dead.
How much I fucking hate Pizza Rolls.
- No, you love Pizza Rolls.
- When I was seven!
I am not seven.
I'm sorry.
My father was bipolar.
One night, when I was ten,
he tried to smother me
with a Hello Kitty duvet.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
- PRISONER: Give him that work!
- Kick his ass!
MOTHER'S MILK: Yo!
What the hell is wrong with y'all?
This is not what we do here, gentlemen.
Now, didn't I tell you,
we take turns at the pong?
Oslo, Deeaygo, tell me you
put your names up on my board?
Apologies, Mr. Milk. No, sir.
Nuh-uh, me, neither, Mr. Milk.
Which means that you have cut in line
in front of everybody else in here.
What else does it mean?
Come on, spit it out.
Means that we're disrespecting
all the other niggas...
Excuse me?
- All our fellow brothers in the unit.
- Now, you both know how to write
in the English language
in a passable fashion.
I know that, 'cause I've
seen to it myself, have I not?
- Yes, sir.
- Then please,
place your John Hancocks on my board.
Yes sir, Mr. Milk. Thank you.
At the bottom of the list.
Oh, hell nah.
What the fuck do you want?
What, I can't visit me old mate?
Rekindle the unbreakable
bonds of brothers-in-arms?
- Nope.
- Come on, M.M.
Bring it in.
Look, if it's all the same,
let's just cut the small talk.
All you're gonna do is lie
and say how you're doing fine,
and I'm gonna lie and pretend
like I'm happy to see you.
Why are you here?
All right.
- How'd you like to come back, have another go?
- Mm-mm.
No, sir. Keep it to yourself.
I don't want to know
nothing about nothing.
I'm a happy man now. Life is good,
- Monique is back, we're good, just...
- Oh, yeah? How is Monique?
Spits on the ground every
time your name comes up.
I can't do that to her again, man.
Not to mention, I'm actually
making progress with these boys.
Yeah, so I can see.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Don't make me come out there!
Well, this is God's work.
I can't argue with that.
But a man of your talents?
- Wasted here.
- Look, Butcher,
we were into some bad shit, man.
Even before the Mallory
stuff. And that, that was...
(SIGHS)
If I'm gonna make a difference,
I just feel more comfortable
doing it on a smaller scale.
I'm a motherfucker with a heart.
Whereas you?
You're just a motherfucker.
Funny you should mention
making a difference...
... 'cause we just dusted a Supe.
Bullshit.
Translucent.
What the f...
Well, come on, you
lime-sucking smart-ass.
How the hell did you do it?
Well...
Big lump of C-4, packed
right up his fudger.
Boom. Claret everywhere,
fucking diabolical.
But before the fireworks,
he coughed up a solid lead.
Spilled the beans in a big way.
Now, we play this right,
we could shake up the
whole hornets' nest,
bring down Seven and
Vought at the same time.
MOTHER'S MILK: Mm-hmm.
You mean do Homelander?
(CHUCKLES)
This is about Becca, isn't it?
It's always about Becca with you.
Oh, you ain't got your reasons?
(SIGHS)
It'll be different this go, all right?
None of that "secrets
and lies" bollocks.
And that Mallory shit ain't
gonna happen this time.
I swear to God.
Are you bringing Frenchie back?
'Cause I can't work
with that motherfucker.
Frenchie? No, I ain't seen him in years.
M.M., you're the only bloke I can trust.
(CHUCKLES)
Since when have you
ever trusted anybody?
Oh, fuck.
CHUCK TODD: Senator Calhoun,
you've gone on the record
- against superheroes in the military.
- MADELYN: Who's a good boy?
- Who's a good boy?
- Why change your tune?
No one's changing their tune.
Uh, it's just I realized that
- it's an issue that affects all Americans.
- (TEDDY BABBLING)
It shouldn't be decided
- Can't you make it... stop?
- by a few congressmen
- hidden in committee.
- He's not crying.
The bill needs to go to the floor.
Oh, okay.
Aw. Aw. (GASPS)
Oh, no. We can't have that...
You know, I heard Translucent's
tracking chip went dead.
- Yeah?
- He could be hurt.
(CHUCKLES) How?
He's got diamond skin.
He's gonna be fine.
My guys are on it.
All right, I forgot to give you these.
Here.
What is it?
Those are your new talking points.
Now that the military
bill is out of committee,
corporate wants to
sell the shit out of it.
Yes. They do.
(GIGGLING)
Hey. Y-You remember when
you wanted me in the red cape
and-and I said, "No. No, no, no.
Make it the flag"? Remember that?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah. I don't need these.
Okay?
I can sell my way into the military.
- (PAPER CRUMPLING)
- Thank you.
You take care of your baby,
and I'll take care of mine.
Mr. Edgar wrote those personally.
So if you want to go to
82 and take it up with him,
be my guest.
(QUIETLY): Oh, yes.
Oh, you're a happy boy now, huh?
Are you a happy boy?
(PAPER RUSTLING)
♪♪
MOTHER'S MILK: A rental,
you cheap bastard?
BUTCHER: Who do you think
I am, some double-O wanker?
In case you hadn't noticed,
we ain't exactly rolling in it.
And you don't think this is conspicuous?
BUTCHER: Conspicuous? No, I don't think
it's conspicuous. I
think a big black van
with fucking "Flowers" on
the side is conspicuous.
This is just another
truck on the street.
(RHYTHMIC KNOCKING)
Bang on time.
Uh, hi.
Hughie.
- (SPEAKS FRENCH)
- Smelly motherfucker.
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
- Butcher, who is this guy?!
- You'll give the game away!
Not until this frog gets what's coming.
Only thing that is coming
- is me on your mother's titties!
- Let me through at him, bitch!
- Hey!
- We had an agreement about him.
We agreed to put a pin in it, all right?
- What agreement?
- There was no pin.
I don't trust this French whore.
I am more American than you,
you racist piece of shit!
- Why are they fighting?!
- Nothing. It is water under the bridge.
You tell that to Mallory's grandkids.
Tell them it's water under the bridge.
- That wasn't my fault, huh?
- Who is Mallory?
All right, the both of you,
knock it on the head, now!
(RINGTONE PLAYING):
♪ Never gonna give you up ♪
♪ Never gonna let you down ♪
♪ Never gonna run around ♪
- Shit!
- ♪ And desert you ♪
♪ Never gonna make you cry ♪
♪ Never gonna say good-bye ♪
♪ Never gonna tell a lie. ♪
(PHONE BEEPS)
Hey, Monique.
How you doing, baby?
Ooh, I forgot to marinade the tilapia.
I am so sorry, sweetheart.
Okay, how 'bout this?
How about, on my way home from work,
I stop by DeLuca's, pick
up two fat tenderloins,
some portobello mushrooms, that
pinot that you love so much.
Yeah, baby.
Okay, I-I got to go.
All right, sweetheart.
Yeah. Me, too.
Baby, I just...
Uh, you're right, you're right.
I love you, too.
Okay. Bye.
- (KISSING)
- (LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Fuck all of y'all, okay?
(BLOWS OUT LIPS)
All right. All right.
Listen, you two knobbers
kiss and make up, yeah?
We got a fucking job to do.
Fuck it. Dégage, huh?
- (KISSING)
- Get out of here.
Who's this guy?
The new lad. Hughie.
Hughie, Mother's Milk.
That's a... nickname?
No, my mother actually
named me Mother's Milk.
- Did-did she?
- So we got
a French whore and a
Stephen fucking Hawking.
- Great job, Butcher.
- Well, it was
Stephen fucking Hawking
who dusted the Supe.
Oh.
She's home.
HUGHIE: That's Popclaw, right?
A-Train's girlfriend?
Oh, Popclaw. Hi.
Uh, you know the-the rent?
- It was due last week.
- Right. Of course.
MOTHER'S MILK: You think
her and A-Train are, uh...
BUTCHER: Yeah, playing bury the bishop.
Didn't hear nothing about it.
I'm usually up on these things.
BUTCHER: According to Translucent,
A-Train knows this bird inside out.
I'll drop the check off ASAP.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- 'Kay.
BUTCHER: All right.
Let's get the bugs sorted,
see for ourselves.
Where-Where'd you get
this shit, Circuit City?
Right? He's a cheap bastard.
You know, we don't actually
need to sneak in anything.
- Eh?
- Look, all I need's her IPv6 number.
Every desktop, every smart TV
in the house has a camera on it.
They probably have one in every room.
- Even in the toilet?
- No, Frenchie,
not in the toilet. Look, I
just need five minutes inside.
I mean, home service is my specialty.
Hello, ma'am, we're
with Bryman Audio-Visual.
We got the new router. I'm...
This is-is Hughie.
I'm Gary.
- I didn't make an appointment.
- Oh, well, your manager did.
- He's upgrading the whole building.
- I just saw
my landlord. He didn't mention it.
I've got a work order right here, ma'am.
HUGHIE: Only takes a second.
And we can get you all the
way up to a thousand Mbps.
That-That's a lot.
Okay. Come on in.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- The computer's right over here
- if you need it.
- Uh, yeah.
I just need to sign on to your server
in order to download
the service package.
- Yeah, sure.
- I have a confession.
We're really big fans. I mean,
Terminal Beauty 3...
Whew. Damn.
Oh. Thanks.
Yeah, that one really came together.
Let me know if you
guys need anything else.
Thank you.
You gonna eye-fuck that all day?
Let's go.
(KEYS CLACKING)
Hmm.
What is it?
Nothing.
(EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES)
This kid is full of surprises.
HUGHIE: Okay, ma'am, all done.
(EXHALES)
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
MOTHER'S MILK: Get your John Hancock?
- POPCLAW: Oh, sure.
- Thank you.
(EXHALES)
Ooh. Excuse me, bud.
What, you want a...
autograph or something?
Haven't we met before?
Maybe.
I meet a ton of people.
Come on, man. My meter's running out.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
- Excuse us, brother.
- Yeah.
You trying to get us killed?
♪♪
(GRUNTING)
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (GRUNTING)
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I'll be right there.
Look, Translucent's
probably just lurking
around a gynecologist's
office or something.
- For two days? Come on.
- (GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE)
I don't get it.
Why is no one concerned about this?
Because if people find out
one of the Seven is missing,
they panic.
Besides, you can't
fucking stand Translucent.
- Give 'em hell, Homelander!
- Yeah, you bet, pal.
Of course. But if
something's happened to him,
then that's a direct
attack on the Seven,
which is a direct attack on me.
You've managed to make this about you
in less than 20 seconds flat.
Hey, I'm not the one who's
down a point and a half.
So I think what you mean to say is,
"Gee, thanks, Homelander,
for showing up out of the blue
and bringing the extra
press to my collar."
Homelander. Maeve.
Captain, you guys are the real heroes.
- We're just glad we can help, right?
- That's right.
- Where's your shooter?
- Shooter's on 31.
All right. Sit tight.
(SIGHS)
Elevators?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
I'm just saying, a missing team member
is more important than
A-Train's insipid race.
(SIGHS) Mr. Edgar wants
us both at the race
to roll out his new talking points.
You know this.
I've X-rayed Edgar, you know.
He is this close to a coronary.
He's got blood like engine oil.
And Stillwell, with that mewling baby...
it's ridiculous.
They're just people.
But they snap their fingers and we jump.
- Why? Why do we do that?
- (SIGHS)
- 'Cause they sign our checks.
- (MUFFLED GUNFIRE)
Can we just cut to the part
where you show up to the race anyway?
(CHUCKLES)
See, that's why I love you.
You're the only one
who tells me the truth.
(CLANGING)
(GRUNTING)
Mm-mm.
(CHOKING)
(SHUSHING)
(WHISPERS): It's all over.
(MAN CHOKING, HOMELANDER SHUSHING)
(WHISPERS): It's all over now.
There you go.
Goddamn it.
That was my collar.
Eh, it still is.
Yeah, well, I can't walk him
on The Today Show like that.
(CHUCKLES) No, that's true.
I got excited.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sure you are.
- (WHISTLES)
You know the drill.
He shot at us first.
Attagirl.
(BLOWS, CHUCKLES)
The things I let you do to me.
Yeah.
We're not even dating anymore.
(QUIETLY): Fuck.
(MOANING)
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES, HISSES)
Want me to do the thing?
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
Okay.
POPCLAW: That's a good boy.
Mmm.
(SIGHS)
Oh, stop. Stop, stop.
(LAUGHS) Tickles. Tickling.
What's the problem?
Shockwave's the problem.
What if I lose?
You're not gonna lose.
You're the fastest man alive.
Until I'm not.
You know what Stillwell told me?
If I don't win, I'm out.
Nobody wants the second
fastest man in The Seven.
Babe.
Compound V. Where'd you put it?
POPCLAW: Oh, you sure, babe?
I mean, that stuff, it...
amps you up something fierce.
Remember last time?
Last time's not gonna happen again.
I'm under control. Uh...
You ran through a girl, baby.
That's not what I would call "control".
That shit's a slippery slope.
Take it from me.
No, I... I need it.
POPCLAW: Honey, I'll still
love you even if you lose.
How is that supposed
to help me right now?
- Uh...
- I have to win this thing.
I don't want to be some
washed up B-squader.
Like me?
No, not like... That's...
(A-TRAIN SIGHS)
I got to go.
Why don't you just tell
me where the V is, please?
I'll come back to see you
tomorrow after the race.
What are you talking about?
I've been meaning to tell you.
Are you kidding me?
I have been getting my hair
done, threading my eyebrows,
waxing my body like a plucked chicken,
so that we could finally stand
up there together tomorrow
in front of the world as a couple.
I mean, it was all cleared
with Stillwell and everything.
A-TRAIN: Um...
You did clear it with Stillwell.
Look, our time is gonna come, I promise,
but I got to get my leverage back first.
Where's the V?
- What the hell is Compound V?
- MOTHER'S MILK: Sounds like
some kind of performance enhancer.
- Steroids for Supes?
- Yeah. Well, whatever it was,
he was juiced on it
when he murdered Robin.
(SNIFFLES)
What are you grinning at?
Oh, I don't know, mate.
Maybe it's 'cause The
Seven might just be a squad
of manky 'roid heads.
Now this is exactly the kind
of malfeasance that Langley
is gonna eat up by the spoonful.
Not until we're sure it
does what we think it does.
If we get a bit, can you work it out?
FRENCHIE: Oh, I can run
some tests, of course.
But there's no way of knowing
unless I try some myself.
Amazing idea.
BUTCHER: We'll cross that
bridge when we burn it.
First of all...
we got to get some.
♪♪
(CROWD CHEERING)
Here's your cover.
You're a mild-mannered reporter.
So, uh...
Butcher tells me he met
you, what, a few days ago?
Yeah.
Yeah, that sounds right.
I don't know. I've kind
of lost track of time.
Talk about a baptism of fire.
I'll mic you up here.
- So, Translucent, huh?
- (INDISTINCT VOICE OVER P.A.)
How the fuck did you pull that off?
I don't know. Just lucky, I guess.
Still. Must have been scary.
You want to know
what's really messed up?
Is, uh...
in some ways...
just right in that moment, it...
felt kind of good.
It's written all over your face, Hughie.
What? How can you tell?
'Cause I know how
this job makes me feel.
When I had the detonator in
my hand, I felt, like, a...
I felt, like, a rush.
I get it.
- Like I felt alive.
- But that rush, Hughie,
is no different than the
shit A-Train shoots up.
Everything comes with a price.
The last thing I ever said to Robin...
was "Don't you ever
besmirch Billy Joel."
That was the last thing that she heard
before she burst into pieces.
And-and I got to live with that
shit for the rest of my life.
The price?
Whatever it is...
I'll pay it.
(DRAMATIC THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
ANNOUNCER: This... is
the Race of the Century.
This... is our legacy and our future.
Athletes achieving at the highest level.
This is what we've waited
for... the showdown.
These men are extremely
powerful and very, very quick.
The Train is ready to leave the station.
He reaches speeds in excess
of 1,000 miles per hour.
The fastest men in the
world are here in New York.
Who will come out on
top? There he stands...
six foot one, but a stature that's such
that he's a colossus
for the whole world.
♪ I'll put his blood in my veins ♪
♪ Ring the alarms, right
until my very last breath ♪
♪ Nothing less, yes, the
best, giving it my all... ♪
- All right, champ.
- A-TRAIN: Mmm.
You got this?
Yeah.
Hey...
Ma is looking down on us both right now.
Putting that wind at your back.
Now, you got this?
- I got this.
- That's what
- I'm talking about!
- I got this. Yeah.
- That's what I want to hear.
- All right.
ANNOUNCER: Introducing the
newest member of The Seven...
Starlight, accompanied by Black Noir.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
MAEVE: I'm tired of
the red tape and the
deep-state bureaucrats.
If the people want us
in the armed forces,
the people can order Congress to do it.
- Am I right? Yes!
- (WHOOPING, CHEERING, APPLAUSE)
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING, WHOOPING)
HOMELANDER: Sorry I'm late.
- You got room for one more?
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Ravishing as ever, my sweet.
Hey, who's ready to see a race?
- Huh?
- (CHEERING)
Let's hear it for my boy A-Train.
(CHUCKLES) All right.
(UNDER HIS BREATH):
You fucking cocksuckers.
ANNOUNCER: Please remain
standing for the singing
of our national anthem.
(DISTANT SOUND OF CROWD)
Thank you for coming.
It was nice to meet you.
(SMACKS LIPS) Aren't you cute?
Is it okay if I get a selfie?
Of course, honey. Take this.
(SIGHS, GASPS)
Look at you!
You really dress the part.
It's your old uniform, but
I'm saving up for the new one.
MAN: Hey, Starlight!
Show us your tits!
- MAN 2: Come on!
- (MAN LAUGHING)
- MAN 3: Come on!
- MAN 2: Baby!
(MAN WHOOPING)
MAN 4: Damn, baby, you look fine AF!
- Lean down a little bit more!
- (LAUGHTER)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You do not need to press
your luck right now, right?
MAN 2: Kick my ass, Starlight!
Sweetie, you know what? Save your money.
I like that one much better.
- Starlight?
- I need a minute.
- WOMAN: Where's she going?
- MAN 2: Starlight!
MAN 3: Starlight, come here, honey.
ANNOUNCER: Let's make some noise!
- ♪♪
- (CHEERING)
Glad you made it.
I had a feeling you might.
Remember when used to just
fly off to Paris, like,
- on a whim?
- Yeah, I remember
freezing my ass off across the Atlantic.
Yeah, those were good times.
Why did we ever break up?
You mind if we not crack open
that tawdry little chapter?
Oh, come on.
(RHYTHMIC CLAPPING, CHEERING)
You know...
- MAN: Yeah, kiss her!
- (WHOOPING)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- (MAEVE GIGGLES)
If I ever really thought
- that you'd fallen for someone else...
- Mm.
I just... I don't
think I could handle it.
- Is that so?
- Yeah, you and me?
- Mm.
- We're different.
We're better.
- Together forever.
- Okay, well...
(CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: Here comes the A-Train.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
All aboard!
The Train is ready to leave the station.
♪ The paparazzi smash
for the best all around ♪
♪ Pound for pound in any class ♪
♪ It's the main event so place
your bets and drop your cash ♪
♪ Like the money team,
CMB, I'm 'bout my cash ♪
♪ Come face your fears in the Octagon ♪
♪ And end up with your
head on my blood... ♪
(CHEERING)
♪♪
♪ Live to fight another day ♪
♪ 'Cause he's a fighting champ... ♪
Ooh!
All right, Frenchie, find
it. You're in the clear.
MAN: Starlight! Starlight!
WOMAN: Starlight!
MAN: Starlight, over here!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Annie?
- MAN: I love your new outfit!
- (OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Annie? Annie!
Annie? Hi!
Hughie?
From the bench the other day?
You're, uh... you're Starlight.
That's... How did I not realize that?
It's actually kind of
comforting that you didn't.
BUTCHER (OVER EARPIECE):
Fuckin' hell, Hughie.
- You know Starlight?
- (CLEARS THROAT)
Well, Hughie, it was...
It was really nice to see
you, but I should get going.
- No, Hughie, we need more time.
- Can I, uh,
buy you an overpriced beer?
You know, if you've-you've...
if you got time.
Throw in some overpriced nachos?
- Lead the way.
- Okay.
(PANTING)
No V. Must have hid it somewhere else.
Fucking find it, Frenchie.
This is just so weird.
I mean, the other day....
- Was it three days ago?
- Mm-hmm.
You just seemed, like... You
seemed so normal, you know?
- And now, it's just...
- Now, I'm a freak.
No. No, not at... No, that's
not what I meant at all.
I just meant... I just... I
wasn't getting Beyoncé vibes,
but... not that you don't have that...
- I'm messing with you.
- Okay.
FRENCHIE: Bad news.
- No V.
- BUTCHER: Great. We're fucked.
STARLIGHT: No, it...
It was really nice to talk to someone
who didn't know who I was.
Once you're behind the scenes, it's...
- it's different.
- Like how?
I don't know... if they
really want you to be a hero.
I think they just want
you to look like one.
(STATIC)
The other day on the
bench when you were talking
about how much you hated
your job, you meant...
you meant this job?
Then, um...
... just quit.
Just walk away.
I mean, you got nothing to prove.
I should probably get back,
you know, before they
send a search party for me.
- (CHUCKLES) So...
- Yeah, totally. Um...
listen, Annie... Starlight.
- What do you, uh... ?
- Annie.
Um, this is insane, but, uh...
I know you're you and everything,
but if you ever just wanted to...
you know, get...
Would you like my number?
Yeah. Yeah, that's-that's, uh...
that's what I was asking.
- Okay.
- Do I call you,
- or do I just commit a crime?
- Probably committing a crime
would get me to you quicker, so...
There's a new young gun in town
and I'm ready to rock the show.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
here comes Shockwave.
- (CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
- ♪♪
You all right?
Huh? Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm fast, baby. Like,
how I roll, you know?
You look wired as hell.
Well, it's just Mom's, uh... Her spirit
is flowing through my body,
you know what I'm saying?
- (GRUNTS)
- BUTCHER: I've got eyes on A-Train.
He's totally jacked.
He must've shot up the V.
(SIGHS) We missed it, boys.
I'm out of here. I'll check in later.
BUTCHER: Where the hell you going?
Just gonna see about a girl.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
please turn your attention to the track.
♪♪
Please, clear the track.
Set.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
WOMAN: Yes!
ANNOUNCER: He's done it again!
A-Train wins!
A new world record for A-Train.
They say lightning doesn't strike twice.
(CHEERING)
The world belongs to A-Train.
A-Train wins.
A-Train wins!
Stunning! Absolutely stunning.
(HORN HONKS)
So, how the hell do you know Starlight?
I don't really know her know her.
Just, uh...
we met on a park bench.
Huh. You get her number?
Yeah.
Hughie?
Uh, yeah. Got it.
Good.
(PHONE RINGS)
M.M.
Popclaw's eyeballing a vial of
V like it's made of Snickers.
What, you think she nicked
some of A-Train's stash?
MOTHER'S MILK: That's
exactly what I'm saying.
Get over here now.
A-TRAIN (ON TV): Well, you
know what? Shockwave ran
a good, clean race, but,
uh, there can only be
one fastest man in the world,
and that's the A-Train, baby! (CHUCKLES)
- Yes, baby.
- REPORTER: A-Train,
how are you celebrating
tonight? Any special girl?
Uh... well, you know me.
I'm always in the game,
but I'm too fast to catch.
I'm open to offers, though, ladies.
There's plenty to go around.
REPORTER: A-Train, how have you managed
to stay on top all this time?
What's your secret?
A-TRAIN: Secret? There's no secret.
It's just about discipline and training
and keeping your head in
the game, staying focused.
(HEARTBEAT THUMPING)
(GASPS)
("GOTTA GO" BY JAMES JACOB
FARRIS AND JONAS SORMAN PLAYING)
(CRIES OUT)
Fucking hell.
- (POPCLAW GRUNTING)
- You said it.
She's been at it for an hour.
POPCLAW: Come and get me!
How'd you know to keep an eye on her?
Okay.
You see that red case over there?
I've been around long enough to know
a fix kit when I see one.
And she told A-Train
that V's a slippery slope.
So she's got experience.
I figured if you wait
around long enough,
two plus two equals nasty.
Sherlock fucking Homie.
Now admit it.
This beats babysitting
delinquents any day, don't it?
- (CHUCKLES)
- (QUIETLY): Fuck...
♪ You never saw the signs... ♪
(GRUNTING)
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
(PANTING)
(CLAWS RETRACT)
Oh.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
- Hey, Popclaw.
- Mr. Lutz. Um...
- house call?
- I'm just here for the rent.
The rent you said you would pay?
You should come in.
You can wait there if you want,
but it's gonna take me a few
minutes to write the check.
I don't bite.
Unless you want me to.
That was a joke, Alek.
- LUTZ: Oh.
- Alek, right?
Okay, let's get that check.
You want a drink, Alek, while you wait?
- You prefer Alek or Alexander?
- Alek.
It's actually short for, uh, Aleksy.
POPCLAW: I like that.
Sounds more exotic.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
(POPCLAW CHUCKLES)
(GLASS CLINKS, LIQUID POURS)
Like what you see?
Huh? No.
Yes.
I mean, it's... lovely.
It's okay.
A lot of guys have a superhero fantasy.
LUTZ: Uh...
I-I'm sorry?
I mean, I... I mean...
(GULPS, EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- You know...
- Hmm.
... there is a world
where we could come...
... to an understanding.
(HEART BEATING)
(LUTZ CHUCKLES)
Stop! In the name of the law.
Oh, no. Popclaw has caught me.
(CHUCKLES, GRUNTS)
I am gonna sit right here
- until the cops come.
- (GROANS)
You're not a cat burglar.
You're a filthy pig. Say it.
You're a filthy pig
who likes to eat ass.
Say it!
LUTZ (MUFFLED): I'm a filthy pig
who likes to eat ass. (GROANS)
(MOANS) Stay still.
You like to eat ass?
- (GASPS)
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- He can't breathe.
- No, no, wait. Wait, wait.
- Hold on. Hey, there. Hey, there. Not so fast.
- (POPCLAW MOANING)
- (GASPS)
- (POPCLAW PANTING)
(GASPS)
Oh, my...
(POPCLAW SCREAMS)
You let that guy die.
And he didn't do anything wrong.
He was dead already.
That's bullshit.
So you can cross a street,
run up four flights of
stairs in ten seconds
like some Supe, can you?
And even if you had've got there,
she would have clawed
your fucking head off.
Now we got her right where we want her.
What? What? What are you talking about?
You're a smart lad, but
you still ain't twigged
the one weakness they all got.
Their reputations.
Come on, Frenchie.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Like you said.
Whatever the price, you'll pay it.
Right?
(POPCLAW GASPS)
Easy. Easy.
We ain't here to hurt you.
We're gonna help you
sort out this little mess.
And all you got to do
is tell us everything
you know about this.
Who are you?
All right, I got your
message. Where is the fire?
No, no, not fire. Water.
Just ask my little guppy here.
You can show her.
Well, a very good friend of mine
- found this.
- It was a porpoise.
A fucking porpoise
found this at the bottom
of the harbor.
Go ahead, don't be shy.
(GASPS)
Oh! Jesus Christ.
Is that Translucent?
Still think we got
nothing to worry about?
How did they even get through his skin?
What kind of maniac...
Mm-mm. Not maniac.
Smart, actually.
Very smart.
Hey, Deep, what can't I see through?
- Zinc, Homelander.
- Correct.
And what's the box made of, Deep?
- Zinc.
- Correct again.
(CHUCKLES): They also knew
that we'd find Translucent...
what's left of him... eventually.
So they were just buying time.
Why do you say that?
I'm so glad you asked.
Whoever it was...
they just declared war.
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ No way ♪
♪ No one ♪
♪ Gonna stop ♪
♪ Now go ♪
♪ Save the complaints ♪
♪ For a party conversation ♪
♪ The world is loaded ♪
♪ It's lit to pop, and
nobody is gonna stop ♪
♪ No one ♪
♪ No way ♪
♪ Gonna stop ♪
♪ Now go ♪
♪ Farm people ♪
♪ Book wavers, soul savers ♪
♪ Love teachers ♪
♪ Lit to pop, and nobody is gonna stop ♪
♪ No one ♪
♪ To get control of a mind like that ♪
♪ Move on... ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly-
- www.addic7ed.com -