You're probably all wondering
why I called this team meeting
at 9:00 a.m.
on a Saturday.
Oh, babe, we should've
brought breakfast.
It's fine. No one's hungry.
[stomach growls loudly]
Ignore that.
I could get Belgian
waffles. From Brussels.
Yum, that sounds incredible.
- Yeah? Should I do it?
- [excited chatter]
Okay, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't... don't do that, okay?
As much as I hate to say it,
waffles can wait.
First, there's something
we really need to tell you.
And we wanted our closest
friends to hear it first.
Are you guys pregnant?
Wait, is this about another big bad?
I'll call Chester and Allegra.
No, no, and definitely not.
What we wanted to say is...
both: We're leaving Central City.
When?
Tomorrow.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So wait, you're... you're moving?
Yeah.
We both realized that
we're ready to start something new.
For me it's my gallery
show in Miami and, babe...
You two remember that guy, Chip Cooper?
Yeah, the A.R.G.U.S.
Director of Technology and Science?
Well, he's been reassigned to C.E.M.A.
The Cosmic Emergency Management Agency.
Wow, I really am the biggest nerd here.
Anyway, Chip's leaving
and thanks to a great recommendation
from Lyla and Dig,
A.R.G.U.S. offered me the job.
The thing is they really needed me
like, yesterday.
Yeah, and I will be
joining Cisco in Star City
as soon as my exhibition is done.
Look,
I know this is
super short notice, but...
they're both great opportunities for us.
And we just hope you guys understand.
Of course we do. Yeah, this is great.
- This is great, man.
- So great, we're so happy.
Yeah.
Well, you guys must have so much to do.
Um, I just have to show
Chester a couple things
and then finish packing but...
All right, well, whatever you need,
- just let us know.
- Of course.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
Cool, thanks.
- [all chuckling]
- Okay.
- All right, congrats.
- Thank you.
- Whoo-hoo. Yay.
- [chuckles]
That went way better than expected.
Yeah.
Sweet Sarah E. Goode.
This room has been here the whole time?
Yup.
And I kinda haven't done inventory
in, like, six years, so...
[laughing]
[cheery upbeat music]
Speed treadmill.
♪
No way.
Yeah.
Yes!
♪
Cool, cool, cool.
- Freeze.
- Yup, mm-hmm.
I don't even know what
this is but it's so cool.
[whooshes]
The thinker's chair.
This is the droid I've been looking for.
[chuckles]
Hey, what's all this?
♪
You got, like, a lifetime's worth
of Comic-Con threads in here.
These bad boys are all coming with me.
- Mm.
- But the rest...
[soft dramatic music]
The rest is all yours.
♪
Whoa.
Dude.
I'm really gonna miss you, man.
- Team Chesco and all that.
- [both chuckle]
Sorry, I know I gotta be, like,
the zillionth person to be
getting all sappy on you.
You know, actually,
everyone else seems
to be taking the news
really well.
Maybe it just didn't sink in yet?
I mean, 'cause, dude,
this is the end of an era.
It is the end of an era.
You are so right, Ches.
This is such a big deal that people just
probably need a little
more time to process it.
Yeah, they just need
to soak it in, you know?
I gotta go pack.
'Cause an hour from now,
we could be knee deep
in Kleenex and tears, am I right?
- Yeah, I bet.
- [chuckles]
I'm just gonna spend
the rest of the day here.
Go for it!
[vocalizing]
[pensive music]
♪
What the...
"Happy to help. Barry."
♪
So I guess that's done.
Wow. That was fast.
Yeah, well, it helps
when your best friend's
The Flash, doesn't it?
Sure does.
Since it's just us...
How you holding up?
You sure you're doing okay
with everything that's happening?
You know, me leaving?
Oh, of course. I mean, come on.
A.R.G.U.S. has not one,
but three bionic neural integrators.
You are movin' on up, my friend.
Yeah, but fancy new toys aside,
if you wanna talk about anything...
Oh, there is something
that I wanted to say.
I knew it. What is it? Lay it on me.
"You suck forever.
But I love you anyway."
It's from Frost.
She's stuck up at Mom's lab.
She's sorry she couldn't say goodbye.
Frost, she kills me.
She really does.
Me, too.
Do you remember how I got stuck
in the cryo-vault my first day?
You would've hacked
your way out of there.
We all knew you were
a genius from day one.
Yeah.
♪
Can I have your ID badge?
Mm. Mm-hmm, yeah.
Sure. Right, right.
Thank you.
And your access codes too, please.
Yes, ma'am. Happy to help.
- Thank you.
- [smacks lips]
So you'd like to open an account.
Actually,
what I'd like to know is,
what would make you happy?
Quitting this job. I hate it.
Then do it.
Live your best life.
You know what? I will.
I'll record an album.
I'm thinking a... an EDM country hybrid.
What do you think?
I think what would make me happy
is a cashier's check for $10 million.
Of course. Right away.
[giggles]
And who shall I make it out to?
Cash.
[printer buzzes]
[chuckles] And there you go.
Oh!
You're the best.
[chuckles]
Now I need you to wait here.
- Kay.
- Say, 30 minutes.
Yeah.
Then you can leave
and never look back.
[both laugh]
- Got it?
- Yeah.
[energetic EDM music]
- [wild laughter]
- Who says money
can't buy happiness?
- How much was stolen?
- 10 million.
But no one stole anything.
Somehow our suspect got Ellis
to give her a cashier's check,
then she strolled out of the bank
and drove off in a blue van.
But Ellis was acting so weirdly happy,
I thought I'd check
to see if our suspect
used a neurotoxin on him,
and found this instead.
Whoa, that's a lot of dark matter.
So we know our thief's a meta.
Now we just need to figure
out how her powers work.
Mm, I can help with that.
She makes people euphoric.
Take a look at Ellis' brain scan.
So she controls people's
cingulate cortexes.
Yes, which is why
there's such huge levels
of dopamine and serotonin in his scan.
These levels are definitely
enough to make him
loopy and susceptible to suggestion.
Oh, yeah, he would've done
anything she asked him to do.
But the good news is
is the blissful effects
of her powers wear
off in about 24 hours.
Are you guys debriefing without me?
Hey.
Yeah, we didn't wanna bother you.
We figured you'd be busy
packing your apartment
and whatnot.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't pass up the chance to solve
one last case together, now would I?
Cisco, this is just a meta
who makes people happy.
I think Barry and I
can handle it ourselves.
Or,
O.G. Team Flash
can make taking her down
part of our last mission together.
Guys, come on.
I wanna do this with you.
Oh, okay.
Well, then that's what we'll do.
Thank you so much. Good news, boss.
Though I didn't get much
from the badge on site,
I did manage to get quotes
from an eyewitness
who saw the perp leave.
Okay, great work.
I will send you my
interview with Stanley Ellis.
Can you start on a copy?
I need 1,000 words ASAP.
On it. I'm gonna need a
photo to run with the story.
Yeah, of course.
I have one of Ellis
giving his statement.
Wait, was Cecile here earlier?
Guess so.
Oh, that's Detective Finn.
Gonna see if he'll chat
on the record. B-R-B.
Hey. Detective Finn.
Hey, so about Cisco and me leaving.
I would've told you earlier. It's just,
we wanted to tell you all together.
No, don't worry. We were all so busy.
Iris, you trusted me to be
the eyes of "The Citizen."
And that gave me the confidence
to take my career to the next level.
You changed my life and
I'll never forget that.
So thank you.
You're welcome.
Now I feel guilty about leaving you
- on such short notice.
- No, it's fine.
Really, really.
No, it's not.
Well, I know you're seeing
new candidates today.
Maybe I can help you vet them?
Yeah. Yeah, that'd be great.
- Great.
- Come on.
I checked out Ellis' brain scan
and I had major déjà vu.
Folks, we've been on this exact
emotional rollercoaster before.
Well, sorta.
Last time, it was Roy G. Bivolo.
But our new meta makes
people happy, not angry.
Enter Rainbow Raider 2.0,
which means we already
know how to stop her.
Using that prismatic light grid I built
to reverse Bivolo's whammy effects,
we can use it to neutralize
her meta abilities.
Just remember. Don't make eye contact.
[chuckles]
Hey, how many gadgets
do you think we've built
over the years, huh?
Really, when you do the math,
that's a lot of bad
guys we've taken down.
You know, when you leave,
you should take all the plans with you.
I mean, I'm sure everything you've built
must mean a lot to you.
Yeah, it does.
[alarms ringing]
Satellite's got a hit on
the van from the robbery.
Let's do this.
One last time.
[wild laughter]
All right, crime spree's over, miss.
Step away from the case.
You think I'm a crook?
Uh...
[scoffs]
Flash, you've got it all wrong.
Nice leotard, by the way.
Thank you.
Mm, who's the sidekick?
I'm Mecha-Vibe,
and you're toast.
[gadget whirring]
[machine splutters]
[chuckles]
Wanna see a real light show now?
[dramatic music]
♪
Oh, it's not exactly
Circuit de la Sarthe,
but let's see how fast this baby can go!
[laughing]
[engine turns over]
- Uh, Flash?
- Yeah, I'm on it.
Where'd she go? Where'd she go?
She had, like, $1
million worth of jewelry.
Mecha-Vibe?
That's my name. Don't wear it out!
[laughs]
Dude, I am so happy
to have you in my life!
Okay, this is happening.
On a very public street.
Oh, man, don't be embarrassed.
Embrace it.
- Yeah.
- [humming tune]
[whispers] We should probably stop.
You know I love you, right? [humming]
♪ I got my dream job ♪
♪ Gonna go to A.R.G.U.S. ♪
♪ And do some science,
science-y science ♪
At least he's not raging
out and trying to kill us.
Why didn't the prism grid work?
My working theory is that Roy used
one color of the spectrum, red,
to induce anger in his victims.
♪ So many lenses! ♪
But our 2.0 version
uses the whole rainbow.
Since that makes her
power seven times stronger
than Roy's, when Cisco
tried using the grid...
♪ And "Miami Vice"! Do-do-do-do ♪
She overloaded it
with vibrational energy
from the entire
electromagnetic spectrum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
[grunts]
Ouch.
Speaking of overloaded,
he's gonna be like that till tomorrow.
I'll have the satellites keep searching
for Rainbow Raider 2.0.
Once we get a hit, I'll meta-cuff her
and give her a one-way
transport to Iron Heights.
Okay, great, but what about him?
Hey, hey!
I'm doin' just fine!
Thanks for asking.
We're gonna need a babysitter.
All those applicants...
I really thought we'd
meet someone you'd like.
Yeah, me too.
I will try again next week.
What was wrong with Kenji again?
She's super talented and
she seemed really nice.
Kamilla, you know
better than anyone that
we don't just cover local
politics and football scores.
We need someone who
can handle everything.
And I get that, but...
I mean, even I couldn't
handle everything on day one,
so maybe expecting
everything from the get-go
is asking a bit much?
Okay, I will keep her in mind.
I just... I want to
find the right person.
Totally.
But she's not the only good
applicant you passed on today.
I said I would keep her in mind.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
I'm sorry. That was harsh.
Uh, no, it's fine.
You don't have to explain.
I gotta go.
[sighs]
[door opens, closes]
So I was thinking maybe waffles?
You know I love waffles!
Oh, yeah, you love those!
What are these doing down here, man?
Dude, you know I'm Mecha-Vibe.
You know I had to upgrade the specs.
But it's only 'cause the
convex filtration coating
on these wore off over time.
[laughs] These poor little buggers.
- I miss 'em.
- Poor guys.
What else you got
going on down here, man?
There's just... there's,
you know, so much stuff!
All that waffle talk made me hungry.
I gotta eat. B-R-B.
No, no, no. [chuckling]
Chester P. Runk. [babbles]
You don't want me to
leave the Starchives.
Okay, fine, look, they
made me do it because...
Shh!
I know
why you're trying to keep me down here.
It's because they wanna throw me
a surprise going away party.
- Uh...
- And to think...
I thought they didn't care.
- [laughs]
Spin move!
No, Cisco, wait!
Come on, Ches!
[sighs] Man.
Satellite's picked up our perp's van
parked right outside Ferris Airfield.
It's registered to a
former collections officer
named Carrie Bates.
There aren't any banks or
jewelry stores out there.
What's she up to?
Surprise!
- Cisco?
- Yeah, sans Chester.
Where all the balloons at?
Am I early? [gasps]
I'm early, aren't I?
No sweat, Boba Fett.
It's all hakuna matata.
I know exactly how to
get this party started.
Okay, get ready, get
ready. I'm almost there.
No, you get ready.
To laugh.
[meowing and upbeat music playing]
♪
[laughs] So cute.
But also so funny!
Turn it off! Turn it off...
- What did you do?
- I just turned
Flash's happy dial up to 11
with a little suit upgrade.
- Cisco, he can't see.
- Yeah, he can.
No, I can't. I can't see.
Whoops, my bad. [laughs]
♪
[yelps]
- [laughing]
- Barry, are you all right?
Cisco, shut it off!
Shut it off!
- Okay, bro-tholomew.
- [music quits]
You all right?
[gasping] I'm fine.
[mumbles, gasps]
Looking for me, Red?
[chuckles]
You heroes, always on a mission.
Well, I'm on a mission, too.
- And you don't want to stop me.
- No.
So be a happy boy and enjoy
some me time somewhere else.
Okay.
[whooshing]
You okay?
Did you stop the bad lady?
Nope.
I didn't want to!
[giggling]
Go, Flash! Go, Flash!
Okay, Barry, why don't we
take a break from the dancing?
Yo! She said "break dancing"!
[hip-hop music plays]
Whoo!
You saw how he slid in like that?
♪ All night to the early morning ♪
- ♪ Can you feel the music ♪
- Okay, okay!
♪ All night to the early morning ♪
[laughs]
Yeah, Flash dance!
- He's a maniac!
- ♪ I got the baddest flows ♪
- ♪ I rock the baddest shows ♪
- Yeah, oh, he's a beast!
♪ I'm the illest MC
that you have to know ♪
Since when do you know
how to break-dance?
Since I sped watched 17
break dancing videos online.
Oh, what up, party people!
- My G!
- [all shouting]
Ay, ay, ay, ay. Oh, oh!
- Send it back.
- Sending it back.
Both: Ooh! [laughter]
Chester.
Chester!
- Oh, right, yeah.
- ♪ Feel the music ♪
Hey, guys, guys.
♪ Say cheese! ♪
Both: Cheese!
[gadget whirring]
[both groan]
How do you guys feel?
Uh, exhausted.
And a lot less happy.
[laughs]
- Chester, how'd you cure them?
- Okay, so I figured
if we focus Carrie's full
spectrum light particles
through a vibrational filter,
the resulting fractal energy
would counteract the whammy effect.
You know, it's kinda like Vibe
saved the day one last time.
Carrie put a Ferris Air logo on her van.
That must be where she's going next.
I think I know why.
You see that airship?
It's a stealth dirigible
with a bleeding edge auto-navigation
and a two-ton payload.
And guess where it just got stolen from?
Ferris Airfield.
Why would she steal a blimp?
Maybe it's okay. I mean, it's not like
she stole the Death Star, right?
No, but it can cloak itself,
making it untraceable by
satellites, including ours.
Cisco, you're gonna be,
like, a boss at A.R.G.U.S.
so maybe they've got something
that we don't that could help us out.
[soft dramatic music]
Yeah.
Yeah, you know what?
Why don't I just show
up to work a day early,
report for duty, and ask them in person?
Why don't I just do that?
♪
I was just...
I need a minute.
♪
[somber music]
Listen, I don't know what's got you two
so ready to get rid of me,
but maybe we should just
say goodbye now and get it over with.
Cisco, we really messed up.
Big time.
You don't...
want to get rid of me?
No, we don't want to get rid of you.
I mean, we're barely
holding it together.
This whole time I thought you guys
just didn't care that I was leaving.
We are so sorry we
made you feel that way.
But when you told us, I mean,
we both decided to
put on a brave face so we could
tackle one last case together
so you could move on.
And your last day
wouldn't be a tear fest.
Caitlin, have you met us?
[laughs]
[emotional music]
♪
We are gonna miss you so much.
[sniffles]
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Honestly, man, I was scared
if we started talking about you leaving,
I would ask you to stay.
And maybe you actually would. [chuckles]
I couldn't do that to my best friend.
From the second I woke up
after being hit by lighting,
you've been there.
You were there every
step of this journey.
There wouldn't be a
Flash without Cisco Ramon.
♪
I did build some pretty rad suits.
[chuckles]
You did.
♪
Do you remember when
Psych made us see our worst fears?
Mine was seeing myself,
30 years from now.
I was still here
with the next gen of heroes.
I still had my long hair.
♪
But it was gray.
And everyone else was changing
and growing.
But not me.
♪
And that scares the hell out of me.
Cisco.
You are a born leader.
You're probably gonna be
running A.R.G.U.S. in no time.
I know.
I am a man on a mission.
♪
What do you say we figure out
why our thief took
that blimp for a joyride
so we can wrap up this
case and celebrate?
I think I actually know
what Carrie's plan is.
♪
Barry, you were right.
Carrie's been fired from six
different collection agencies
- in the last three months.
- What for?
Says here whenever somebody
had a huge medical debt, she'd cancel it
- instead of collecting.
- That makes sense.
Carrie told me she
was on a mission, too.
She didn't steal cash
and diamonds for herself.
She's giving it away
like a Rainbow Robin Hood.
Then what's the blimp for?
[alarms ringing]
[dramatic music]
♪
She's gonna make it rain.
All that money and jewels...
It's gonna be chaos.
♪
As they say,
it's better to give than to receive.
The Gotham Goliaths are
feeling small in Central City,
where the Sharks are leading
by 21 points in the fourth quarter.
As if things weren't bad enough,
20,000 screaming football fans
are about to exit Shark
Stadium all at once.
Drunken sports fans
tearing each other apart,
fighting over diamonds and
cash falling from the sky?
We have to find a way to
stop her before it starts.
What about Chester's new device?
Uh-uh, to counter
Carrie's rainbow blast,
we'd need a much more
powerful light grid...
One the size of Texas.
Good thing we have one.
[dramatic music]
♪
That's pretty high.
You sure you can't just
"fathwoom" us up there?
The ship's hull contains two tons
of compressed hydrogen.
One spark of lightning
could make it explode.
You can do this. You've done it before.
Okay, hang on to your buns.
Flash?
[shockwaves pulsing]
[electronics crackle and beep]
[grunts]
Come on, Red, give me a break.
I'm just trying to help
ordinary people get ahead.
[rumbling]
Go, go.
There's a better way to help people.
Is there?
Because folks are
really hurting right now.
Some people can barely
put food on the table,
let alone pay rent. You know why?
Because the systems left them behind.
[electronics crackle]
Those people need help. Real help.
The kind that starts after you're gone.
That's where I step in.
Because I care what happens, Flash.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
That's why instead of sending you
to Iron Heights,
I'm gonna recommend you work off
whatever sentence you
receive with Mayor Sampson's
economic development committee.
You're right, Carrie.
The city does need you.
From what I've just heard, I'm confident
you're the right woman for the job.
[gasps]
You'd do that for me?
My hero.
[rumbling]
The auto-navigation
control's been damaged.
Looks like that energy
tango fried the system.
Uh, folks, we got less
than two minutes to impact.
[dramatic music]
[crowd cheering]
Flash, please tell me you
can get us off this balloon
before it explodes, 'cause
if I use a tele-sphere
with us moving this fast...
We might all end up
pancaked in the nearest sidewalk.
Look, I can try and phase us out of here
without sparking an explosion.
I never wanted to hurt anyone.
Damn it, this thing's
stuck on autopilot.
[engine rumbling]
Uh, guys, 90 seconds.
♪
Get them to safety and
then evacuate the area.
If this thing crashes, the
hydrogen's gonna flash fry
everything within a two-mile radius.
- No, I'm not...
- Look, Barry,
- there's not enough time.
- I'm not gonna let you die.
I'm not planning on it!
Go!
♪
I got this.
Let's go.
♪
Flash, there's 20,000 people
in there and the game...
Will be over any minute. I know.
[dramatic music]
♪
Chester, what do I need to bypass
a six dorsal propulsion unit?
Uh, I... I don't know.
What do you have up there?
♪
I have me.
[grunts]
♪
Come on.
[electronic beep]
You can do it.
Ooh, come on!
♪
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
[straining] Come on!
You can do it!
Come on!
You can do it, come on!
[shouts]
[shouting]
[triumphant music]
[shouts]
Whoo! Whoo!
[laughing]
[gasps]
Dude, there is no word to describe
how awesome you are right now.
Actually, there is.
He's da bomb.
[breathing heavily]
Hell yeah, I am.
♪
[breathing heavily]
Okay, folks.
Our hijacked airship
is safely back at Ferris Air...
Where in the hell...
Just, go on.
Man, this is supposed
to be my last debrief.
It's... it's cool, it's cool.
Just... just keep going.
Like, just think of it as, uh,
Team Chesco, one last time.
- Um, uh...
- Huh?
Well, looks like the D.A.
is officially on board...
- Mm-hmm.
- With Carrie working off
the rest of her sentence
at the mayor's office.
Yeah.
Also, the Sharks beat the Goliaths,
28 to nothing.
Go, Sharks.
As a bonus,
CCPN is reporting
a wave of donations across the city
inspired by Carrie's
"unique brand of charity."
There is gonna be a
surprise party, isn't there?
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Well, actually, there's gonna be two,
and they're a little last minute,
but Team Citizen is
gonna par-tay with Kamilla
at their office, which means...
That the rest of the team...
♪ Is gonna kick it at the loft ♪
At the loft.
The only missing piece is
the guest of honor, sir.
You.
So you ready to do this thing?
Not yet.
This has
all of my conceptual
designs for S.T.A.R. Labs...
Software fixes, fortifications
for the Time Vault,
Babel upgrades.
[heartfelt music]
You're the man now, dog.
Thanks, Cisco.
This is... wow.
I know I'm leaving this
place in great hands.
[laughs softly]
You wanna drop that
off in your new workshop
- so we can skedaddle?
- Hoo...
New workshop?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
[exciting music]
Okay.
♪
Oh, I know that look.
You're gonna bail on me
so you can spend all night
organizing your stuff in
that space, aren't you?
- Uh-huh.
- Yep.
But I promise I'll be
there tomorrow morning
at the epic goodbye
breakfast at Jitters.
I know you will.
Thanks for showing me the ropes, man.
♪
Keep 'em safe for me, will you?
Roger that.
♪
[chuckles]
[echoing] What are you doing?
He likes this song.
How could you possibly know that?
I checked his Facebook page.
It's like everyone
else is standing still.
The party's here!
Supersonic punch, baby, whoo!
I'll always remember this.
Doctor Wells and I...
Doppelganger.
You'd have to be a Weather Wizard.
Captain Cold. The Mist.
The Turtle. Samuroid.
Now go...
[grunting]
Serve your higher purpose.
I knew you wouldn't let me down.
How did you know what I like?
I had a feeling.
[gasps]
Cisco.
You're a hero, man.
How do you feel?
It's the end of an era.
♪
[laughs softly]
Yeah.
♪
I'm gonna miss you, too.
I'm gonna miss all this.
[cork pops]
Even this drafty old building?
- Mm.
- [chuckles]
Kamilla, you know, about earlier, I...
I wasn't thinking and I was out of line.
It's okay. I totally get it.
I think it was just hard for me because
I'm not just saying goodbye
to a valuable team member.
I'm saying goodbye to a friend.
And I'm gonna miss you.
So don't be a stranger.
You got it.
And, Iris, for the record,
from the moment I first met Cisco,
I knew things would be great,
but I had that same feeling coming here
and getting to know you and Allegra.
So to Team Citizen.
- All: Team Citizen.
- Whoo!
Looks like I'm just in time.
- Hi.
- Now it's a party.
Aw, thank you.
Hey, what's up with you
being at the crime scene this morning?
- Hmm?
- The...
Oh, um,
I was meeting up with an old contact.
There's something I've
been trying to dig up
for a case, and I am
finally getting close.
Oh, hey, what do you say?
Group selfie, ladies.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Ready, one, two, three.
Cheese.
♪
I'm gonna miss speedster
delivery so much.
Like, what am I supposed
to do the next time
we get a craving for Lou Malnati's?
Order online like everyone else?
Like a normie? No thanks.
Well, I guess you're just gonna
have to come back and visit.
I guess so.
So you're buying a place in Star City?
That is the plan.
That's a big step.
But I'm proud of you.
Kamilla, too.
And it goes without saying.
You always have a place to stay here.
Thanks, Joe.
Hey, it's me that
should be thanking you.
All these years, you've
always had Barry's back.
You are a good man, Cisco Ramon.
[glasses clink]
We're gonna miss the hell out of you.
Speaking of,
I have something that
should help with that.
Pour vous.
- Whoa.
- [chuckles]
As a token of how
special you all are to me.
[chuckling]
You wore this on your
first day at S.T.A.R. Labs.
What can I say?
From the beginning,
you made me feel right at home.
All right, it's your night.
What do you want to do next?
Mm-mm.
[Lady Gaga's "Poker Face" playing]
[inhales deeply]
- [laughs]
- Oh, my gosh.
♪
- [laughs]
- This song?
You know, I didn't even
put this as my favorite song
on my Facebook. I
don't know who did that.
- You already know what time it is.
- Don't make me sing.
You know they're gonna compete, right?
This is my jam, though. This is my jam.
This is my jam. [mimics explosion]
[grunting to beat]
♪
Wow.
My gosh.
♪ I wanna hold 'em ♪
♪ Like they do in Texas, please ♪
- Okay.
- ♪ Fold 'em, let 'em hit me ♪
♪ Raise it, baby, stay with me ♪
- Stay with me, huh?
- Both: ♪ Luck and intuition ♪
♪ Play the cards with spades to start ♪
♪ Yeah, and after he's been hooked ♪
♪ I'll play the one that's on his heart ♪
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All: ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ I'll get him hot ♪
- Yeah.
- ♪ Show him what I've got ♪
- That's scary.
All: ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh, oh ♪
both: ♪ I'll get him hot ♪
- ♪ Show him what I got ♪
- Show, show, show, show!
[in deep voice]
♪ Can't read my, can't read my ♪
Take it, take it.
- Dance break.
- Do it.
Both: ♪ Poker face ♪
♪ Salami, loyal money ♪
♪ Can't read my, can't read my ♪
- Yeah!
- ♪ No, he can't read my ♪
[choral voice] ♪ Poker face ♪
[high-pitched] ♪ Poker face ♪
[laughing]
both: ♪ P-p-p-poker face ♪
♪ P-p-p-poker face ♪
Ah!
♪
Babe?
[whispers echoing]
Cecile.
[foreboding music]
♪
- [whispering] Cecile.
- [gasps]
[sing-song] Cecile.
[indistinct whispers]
♪
[unhinged music]
I will find you.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --