- Thomas...
you seem particularly
triggered right now.
Can you tell me
what happened?
- I've had dreams that
weren't just dreams.
Am I crazy?
- We don't use that word
in here.
- Hi.
- Have we met?
♪ One pill makes you larger and
one pill makes you small ♪
♪ And the ones that mother
gives you ♪
♪ Don't do anything at all ♪
♪ Go ask Alice ♪
♪ When she's ten feet tall ♪
- Time to fly.
♪ And if you go chasing
rabbits ♪
- If you want the truth,
Neo...
you're going to have
to follow me.
♪ And you know
you've gone too far ♪
The only thing that
matters to you is still here.
I know it's why
you're still fighting...
and why you will never
give up.
[ grunts ]
- You don't know me.
- No?
[ yells ]
♪ When logic and proportion have
fallen sloppy dead ♪
♪ And the White Knight is
talking backwards ♪
♪ And the Red Queen's off with
her head ♪
♪ Remember what
the dormouse said ♪
♪ Feed your head ♪
- After all these years...
to be going back to where
it all started.
Back to the Matrix.