[UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC]
_
♪
Why is it so complicated
deciding how to have a baby?
The Batsuit isn't exactly baby proof,
but I can't force Sophie
into nine months of
indigestion and swollen ankles.
Sis, you are spiralling.
Do you remember what I told you
when I was your maid of honor?
No, I was busy getting
married, not taking notes.
I told you to stop thinking so much
and to listen to your heart.
If you want to have a baby,
your heart will figure out the how.
And then that sweet little
girl is gonna grow up
and decide that she hates you.
Jenna has been thinking
the worst insults
at me tonight.
Let me tell you something, teenagers...
Do not use the
bathroom. It is occupied.
Really occupied. Thank you.
Allegra! Hey, hey, hi.
So... so, uh, how's, uh, how London?
You calling cookies b-biscuits yet?
Nope, but actually,
I might be moving back to the States.
I got a job offer in Gotham.
Oh, my gosh! Allegra, that's great.
Thanks, yeah, I haven't decided
if I'm gonna take it or
not yet, though, so...
[TAPPING ON GLASS]
If I could have everyone's
attention for a minute.
When you find...
The love of your life,
you're part of something greater.
You're a part of something
wonderful, magical,
beautiful, and frankly surprising
because you never know what
face fate will be wearing
when she knocks on your door
to change your life forever.
And my only wish for you is
that when that face shows up
to change your lives,
that face is as beautiful
as the one standing next to me.
To Iris West,
the love of my life.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
What the hell is he doing here?
You got a lot of nerve
showing up here, Allen.
It's been you this whole time.
Despero, Armageddon, Joe.
Don't you dare say my
father's name, you murderer.
Guys, it's me, Barry.
Iris is my wife.
[SCOFFS]
We've all fought Thawne together.
Oh, my God.
He actually believes
the things he's saying.
♪
I'll show you it's me.
Thawne, what did you do?
You're not the Flash, Allen.
♪
I am.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Team Flash...
suit up.
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
♪
Guys, Thawne is tricking you.
I came here from 2021.
Save it, Allen.
We're not falling for
your mind games this time.
Put him down.
It's a paralysis ray.
No speed for a couple seconds, Allen.
Why are you doing this?
So I can do this.
That was for Ray and for Nate.
And that was for Sara.
And this...
Is for Cisco.
♪
So sorry, Allegra.
But we did put a tie on the door.
What did we miss?
- [WHOOSH]
- [GASPING]
- Get away from me.
- Iris, you have to believe me.
Thawne's not the Flash. I am.
He must have changed the timeline.
You're my wife. This
is our home, our loft.
We even have kids, Bart and Nora.
- Stop, stop, stop!
- Please.
You have to remember us.
Iris, you're my lightning rod.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
You're psychotic.
♪
Iris West is my lightning
rod now, Reverse-Flash.
What the hell did you do?
Nothing you haven't done before.
- You created a Flashpoint.
- Wrong.
I created a Reverse Flashpoint.
I started by doing a little
housekeeping at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and then I took care of the
one father you had left.
Why?
Because after our last encounter,
it was clear to me you
were faster than I was,
and that the only way to defeat you...
Was to become you.
So I ran back to the year 2013
and made sure that I was
the one struck by lightning.
I was the one that Iris West
wrote about as the Streak.
I led Team Flash.
I was the one Iris
West fell in love with.
I stole your life!
And because every
hero needs a villain...
I created that, too.
♪
You wore my face.
It was you that attacked
the city that day.
That's why they don't trust me.
Made you think you were crazy,
crazy enough to beg,
literally beg Jefferson
Pierce to steal your speed.
What's it at now, 5%? Maybe less?
Thawne, what you've
done destroys the world.
It creates Armageddon.
- No.
- No, it's true, damn it!
I would not create a perfect world
just to watch it die.
As a matter of fact,
the only thing that is set to expire
is you.
And do you know why?
Because I finally did
what I set out to do
all those years ago.
I killed you as a child.
You can do that all night long.
But the fact remains, at
the stroke of midnight,
my timeline will solidify...
And you will cease to exist.
And your precious Speed
Force cannot help you now,
because in this timeline, she chose me.
An Iris chose me.
I've won. I finally won.
Who's faster now?
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Earlier today, protesters
gathered downtown
outside the penthouse of Damien Darhk,
demanding justice.
Darhk, who was released
from Iron Heights Prison
on a technicality, was
convicted six months ago
for the murders of A.R.G.U.S.
director Cisco Ramon,
the heroic team known as the Legends,
as well as tech philanthropist Ray Palmer.
Meanwhile, Darhk's accomplice,
the mass murdering
speedster the Reverse-Flash
is still at large.
♪
[HUMMING]
Barry Allen, I was
wondering when my old partner
was gonna come back and say hello.
I hope you've been laying
low somewhere, relaxing.
I need your help again, Damien.
Yeah, of course you do.
Whoa, hmm.
♪
You seem different.
It seems like you're
running on empty, old friend.
What happened to you?
The Flash happened to me.
Now I want payback.
Mm, I like where this is going.
Spill your tragic tale.
Well, after you were arrested,
I fought the Flash and beat him.
Yes!
But before I could drive
a hand through his heart,
he ran back in time,
changed things so he'd won.
He created an anachronism.
Only it wasn't just one event.
Thawne changed everything.
Trying to stop him cost me my speed.
Now we're living in a
timeline he constructed
for his own benefit.
Really?
Well, that's downright villainous.
Hm.
- We need to put him down.
- Yeah, we will, we will.
You know, nobody gets
to rig time except me,
but fixing this won't be easy.
If the Flash created
multiple anachronisms,
the only way to reset the timeline
is to turn everything
back at the same time,
which is why we need the PED.
- The PED?
- The PED.
♪
The Particle Eradication Distributor,
the thing that erases
any type of matter.
You yanked it out of Ray
Palmer's cold dead hands.
Right.
When you've killed as
many people as I have,
you start to lose track.
Huh.
I sometimes forget...
You're even darker than me,
pun intended.
All right, old partner,
here's what we're gonna do.
If we combine the PED
and my Time Stone, any anachronisms
on that temporal plane will be erased.
- So this could work.
- Oh, it gets so much better.
After my arrest, they
confiscated the PED.
Guess where it ended up.
♪
Frost, Chillblaine, and Batwoman are
searching the city, but
no sign of Reverse-Flash.
And I can't feel him anymore.
It's like he magically disappeared.
Then try harder.
Cecile, we know that
you're doing your best.
Yes, of course you are.
What's up with him,
anyway? Has he gone crazy?
I mean, the guy actually
thought he was the Flash.
He's a sociopath.
There's no explaining a mind like that.
Runk, where are we with the satellites?
- Runk?
- What?
- Satellites.
- Right, right, right, right.
Satellites are scanning for
his negative tachyons, sir.
But after analyzing
samples from Robern's,
looks like the Reverse-Flash is running
on limited speed.
Less speed means lower tachyon output.
- Making him harder to track.
- But not impossible.
If we sync the Atom Bracelet's
microsensors to the satellite,
that'll isolate the smallest tachyons.
That will give us Allen's location.
Consider it done, Captain Eo.
Horton, use the Thinker's chair
to boost your empathic scans.
Snow, get the med lab ready
in case there's trouble.
Danvers, Garcia, weapons check.
♪
What are you thinking?
Well, I'm thinking you
should be at home resting up
for our big day tomorrow.
I will.
What?
It's just that Allen seems off.
Baby, he called me his lightning rod.
- Only you call me that.
- I know.
But he's smart. He's attacking our love.
We cannot let him pull us apart.
He won't.
- I love you.
♪
What's the deal with you and Chester?
Nothing, why?
The stolen glances, the nervous energy.
You either hooked up,
you are hooking up,
or you really need to.
Okay, we did once,
but it was ten years
ago, and it went nowhere.
What happened?
We'd been flirting for months,
and one night, we were playing D&D,
and it just happened.
It was a really lusty quest.
Anyway, I thought
something would come of it.
But by the time I
woke up in the morning,
Chester was gone.
- Hold up, he just left?
- Yep.
And by the time we talked about it,
we decided it was better
just to be friends.
Bye-bye!
♪
Hey, do you know how much longer
until my new look is ready?
I'm gonna look so good
kicking bad guy butt.
I'm just making some last-minute tweaks.
- [COMPUTER CHIRPS]
- Okay. Okay, good to go.
Now we can hunt some tachyons.
It's working.
According to these readings,
there's a pocket of negative
tachyons in this room.
Had to ruin the surprise, didn't you?
You find the PED. I'll
take care of these two.
Hello, boys.
Ah, ah, ah.
[LAUGHS]
♪
Of course.
Ooh, Tupac, what an artist.
[PINBALL MACHINE DINGS]
- I've got it.
- Already?
Wow, you and I, what a team.
- Ahh!
- [GROANS]
[HIGH-PITCHED TONE]
Hurts, doesn't it?
Well, so will this.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
♪
Let's go.
Oh, I got a better idea.
Imagine how devastating
it would be to the Flash
to lose his friends on
the eve of his wedding.
Nothing destroys a man
like losing the ones
he loves the most.
[GRUNTS]
What the hell was that?
We got what we wanted.
Killing them wouldn't
have been efficient.
We can kill them later.
Huh.
The Barry Allen I know wouldn't wait,
which means you're not
the Reverse-Flash, so...
who are you?
♪
Don't make me ask you again.
Who are you?
Thawne's the real Reverse-Flash.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Erase me from the timeline
at midnight.
Man, he is good!
I mean, that's like a work of evil art.
The question is now,
what do I do with you?
You could still help me.
"Help me?" No, I'm the bad guy.
I don't help heroes.
But you're also a father,
which means you know what
it feels like to love someone
with all your heart and soul,
like your daughter Nora.
My Nora's dead. I am
done listening to you.
She's supposed to be alive, and she is
in the timeline I'm trying to restore.
In my timeline, a demon was
gonna take over her soul,
but you switched places with her.
You gave your own
life so she could live.
♪
If you're lying to
me, I'll see you burn.
Nora, Nora.
Dad, why?
Because I love you.
And I couldn't watch you
become a monster like me.
♪
It's true.
My Nora doll's supposed to be alive.
I sacrificed myself to save her.
So honor that sacrifice.
Help me restore the
timeline and bring her back.
Let's go to work.
♪
I guess you guys haven't
found Allen yet, huh?
Nope.
And Batwing called from Gotham.
Two-Face turned up, which means...
You have to go.
I will be at the ceremony
tomorrow, I promise.
Until then, take this.
It's a Velocity-Zero gun.
Luke designed it the last time
a certain lady in red
tried to kill us all.
It will temporarily disrupt
Reverse-Flash's connection
to whatever Speed
Force he's connected to.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Now, uh, you want to talk
about your other problem?
I don't know, I've been
working on it since I got home.
Every time I think about
my future with Eobard,
my mind just...
It goes blanker than that page.
Any chance it's just cold feet?
I don't know.
I love Eobard. I do.
But when I think about what Allen said,
I mean, I just, I can't.
I can't get it out of my head.
It's like it's haunting me.
Ryan, I've won two Pulitzers.
Why can't I write my own wedding vows?
[APPREHENSIVE MUSIC]
Iris, tonight you told me
to stop thinking so much
and listen to my heart.
Yeah, okay, I get it.
That's what I'm supposed to do now...
'Cause it works.
Look, tonight I saved a
kid living in their van
near the waterfront, just like I was
before I found the Batsuit.
Some lowlifes were mugging her,
and as I was kicking their asses,
my heart told me what I want.
I want to save a kid like Cora saved me.
So after I dropped their sorry asses off
at the nearest precinct,
I called Sophie.
We're gonna adopt.
Ryan.
I'm so happy for you.
Take your own advice.
Trust me, if Eobard's the one,
the vows will come.
And what if he isn't?
Then I will get you out
of here in a hot minute.
My car drives really fast.
[LAUGHS]
[GENTLE MUSIC]
That's good work.
- Martini?
- Dude.
Right, you don't drink alcohol.
Hey, Chester, why did you ghost Allegra?
- Well, I-I never...
- Oh, here we go.
Ten years ago, the morning
after you two hooked up,
you snuck out while she was sleeping.
First of all, that's not ghosting.
That's called the French exit.
I never ghosted anyone, okay?
I went to get coffee
and blueberry muffins.
Wait, what?
Yeah, I wanted to have breakfast in bed,
watch the sun come up.
I had the whole day planned
because I knew even after
one night that I wanted
to spend the rest of my life with her.
Dear God.
When I got back, she was gone, Alex,
so Allegra ghosted me.
Which is why we always
abide by rule number one:
never return to the scene of the crime.
Why didn't you ever tell her?
I wanted to.
But we were attacked
by the Legion of Doom.
That week was seriously chaotic,
and when the dust settled,
I tried bringing it up again.
But she cut me off,
told me that night was a huge mistake
and that we were better off as friends.
Think I'm gonna get some air. Yeah.
See, this is what happens
when you try and play Cupid.
What is your problem?
Why don't you love "love"?
Okay, love is just a chemical
flood of dopamine and oxytocin,
giving people an addictive
dependence like a bad drug.
Science.
It's taken me years
to help Chuck feel
happy without Allegra.
By telling him to hide his heart?
Now you're gonna give
me a whole greeting card
inspired speech about your perfect wife
and how she's the love of your life.
Okay, all right. All right, fine.
But one day, you're gonna wake up alone,
and you're gonna realize
that you missed out
on the best part of being human.
♪
Look, according to these equations,
I'd have to hit Mach 20 in
order to open a time portal.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And is that a problem?
To reach that kind of
speed, I need 40,000 miles.
That kind of runway doesn't exist.
Yes, it does.
Is that big enough?
Yes, but the Earth
isn't just a solid rock.
It has a molten core.
The kind of pressure I'd be exerting
on its mantle would
cause cataclysmic damage.
We're talking volcanoes erupting,
ice caps melting, earthquakes, tsunami.
It'd be Armageddon.
So in order to save the world
and bring my Nora back...
I'd have to risk destroying it,
just like Despero predicted.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Look, uh, I hate to
break up your pity party,
but we're running out of time.
And, Barry, you have to do this.
Trust me, I want my life and
Iris back more than anything,
but I've run the numbers.
I will have two minutes to accelerate
before my destruction
destroys the world.
Well then, you better run fast.
Damien, the odds of me hitting Mach 20
in two minutes is 2%!
- It's better than nothing!
- You don't understand.
Despero says I cause Armageddon.
This is exactly what he described.
I won't be responsible for killing
every single person on the planet.
And what happens to those
people if you give up?
[APPREHENSIVE MUSIC]
You're leaving 8
billion souls in a world
where Thawne has
everything that he wants
and nothing to lose.
I'm still not fast enough.
Fast enough? [LAUGHS]
How dense are you?
Speed isn't the only thing
that guides you through these things.
- It never is.
- What else is there?
Love, you idiot!
You're the paragon of it.
I saw what you did in the Time Stone.
You restarted an entire
universe with love.
- This should be peanuts.
- It's not gonna work.
- Not this time.
- Really?
Well, it's guiding the
both of us right now.
♪
Why do you think I'm helping you?
You think I want to die?
I don't.
But if sacrificing my
life means that Nora gets
to live the life that
Thawne stole from her,
then yeah, I'm gonna
do it because my love
for her is what keeps me going
every damn day in my life.
I mean, who do you think I
built this whole empire for?
Iris, your family, your friends,
they are what keep you going.
Iris doesn't remember what we had.
Well, that doesn't matter.
You do.
♪
You lied to me about Chester.
Chester loves you.
When he went to tell
you, you cut him off.
Why did you do that?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
You want to know how every relationship
in my life has ended?
With me getting kicked to the curb.
Everyone I've ever loved has left.
When I woke up the next morning alone,
it was like a trigger.
Suddenly, I was 12 years old again,
and my mom was telling me
that my dad left us because of me.
Yeah, she was a bag of crap, too.
The point is, I was crushed.
So when I saw Chester
walking up the street
with coffees and a bag,
I knew what that meant,
how he felt about me.
And I just freaked out,
and I pushed him away.
♪
You know...
My wife is my rock.
But things were not always perfect.
Trust me, putting yourself out there,
it's scary,
but it's also so worth it.
But what if I lose him?
You'll never know unless you try.
Alex, the reason why
I don't love "love"...
Is because nothing scares me more
than putting my heart out on the line.
So I make fun of romantics.
But this whole Don Juan thing
is just an act.
- Really?
- I knew it.
The truth is...
I don't want to wake up
alone for the rest of my life.
Look, Chester's my boy.
And I know what my boy needs.
He needs you.
♪
[ALARM BLARING]
Guys, we got a hit on Reverse-Flash.
Let's go.
[WHOOSH]
I was just thinking about...
[TENSE MUSIC]
I just want to talk, I swear.
You take one more step,
and I'm gonna shoot you.
Okay.
♪
What's wrong with you? Are you dying?
Something like that.
I came here because I'm about
to do something impossible.
And even though it might not work,
I couldn't leave this world
without telling you that...
Nice try, Allen, but
she doesn't love you.
She loves me.
Tell him, Iris, or better yet...
Shoot him.
♪
Iris.
What are you waiting for? Shoot him!
I need you to know,
no matter what happens,
after everything Thawne's taken from me,
he can't take away my feelings for you.
I love you, Iris.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Enough.
♪
Go before I change my mind.
- How'd it go with the missus?
- I don't know.
She let me go. It has to mean something.
Well, let's do this thing.
I'll stay here at your point of origin,
just in case we get some visitors,
but I'll be in touch.
- How?
- Magic.
You'll hear my voice wherever you go.
Now, remember, you've got
two minutes to reach Mach 20
and open that temporal portal.
Damien, thank you.
♪
Get out of here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
We tracked down the
PED and Reverse-Flash.
He's crossing the Atlantic Ocean.
What the hell is he doing?
He's destroying the city.
It's like the end of days out here.
Holy crap, it's not just the city.
Allen's speed wake is causing
the globe to tear itself apart.
It's an extinction
level event in progress.
He's right, I'm tracking at
least a hundred earthquakes.
A tsunami just hit Japan.
Allen really has lost his mind.
He realized he can't win, so
he's trying to kill us all.
I have to go. I gotta go get Jenna.
Guys, Mark and I could use backup!
Go. I'll stay here.
Okay.
Hey, not to be that guy,
but since this could be the
end of the world as we know it,
if anyone has anything to
say, now would be the time.
♪
The Reverse-Flash just hit Europe.
Where is Eobard?
I'm right behind him.
♪
Hey, Flash, you've got company.
[GROANING]
Guess what, Darhk,
so do you.
♪
Frosty, Chill-lame.
Yeah, I'm a little bit busy.
But you do realize my
abilities give me the power
to draw and quarter
with a gesture, right?
[GRUNTS]
Not for the next 24 hours, you don't.
Our friend John gave us
a badass protection spell.
Constantine, I hate that guy.
Yeah, well, too bad.
Looks like we get to kick
this guy's ass all night.
Won't even take that long.
Really? Let's see how that goes.
♪
If boss doesn't catch Allen
in the next 90 seconds...
- Chester?
- 85...
- 84...
- Chuck!
- What?
I love you.
Yeah, well, I love you, too.
♪
When did this happen?
It's not working.
I'm still not fast enough.
I'm trying to save my
daughter here, Allen.
Focus!
♪
Never dance with the devil.
[GRUNTING]
Yeah, I increased the molecular density
on that little toothpick
of yours a thousandfold
at the subatomic level.
Good luck trying to lift two tons.
I hate science.
♪
Then you are really gonna hate that.
[BOTH GROANING]
- Thanks for the assist.
- Of course.
- Hey, nice threads.
- Thanks, man.
- We're running out of time.
- 60 seconds.
Come on, Flash.
♪
You're too late, Allen.
You're too late!
♪
Iris.
Barry, I love you, too.
♪
- _
- [TENSE MUSIC]
You are no hero. You are a monster.
I'm going to ask you one
last time, Ms. Horton.
And if I don't like your answer,
you'll join your
friends in the afterlife.
♪
Now.
The Flash.
Where is he?
I told you, I don't know!
You know what?
I believe you.
[SOBBING]
♪
Ahh!
- [HIGH-PITCHED BEEPING]
- Ah!
No, what is this?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Flash, what did you do?
I went to the future.
Iris was right.
Someone manipulated the timeline
to drive me insane.
It turns out in order to fix it,
I had to start Armageddon.
Only this time, I
didn't destroy the world.
How is that possible?
You left 2031 before the world ended.
What you didn't know
was that Eobard Thawne,
the Reverse-Flash, was chasing me.
He wanted to stop me from
restoring the timeline.
The speed wake created by us both,
that is what caused
the destruction you saw.
If that's happened, what stopped you
from tearing this world apart?
Iris.
She helped me reconnect
to the Speed Force.
Now the future's safe.
♪
I can see you believe it to be true.
And as a traveler in time,
my senses confirm this
world has been altered.
But as for the true reason...
Well, that remains to be seen.
Maybe you should go to 2031
and see for yourself.
♪
I shall, but if you're wrong,
or if I find any evidence that
this world is still in danger,
I will return,
and you will die.
♪
Yeah.
- Gluten free for Cecile.
- Gluten free!
- Here you go.
- Yep.
Where is...
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
Hey, babe.
I would've got you something,
but I thought you were
working through lunch
at the precinct today.
Don't worry, there's plenty.
Got a burger for you, boss.
♪
[LAUGHS]
Oh, I missed you so much.
Not that I don't love this attention,
but where's this coming from?
Barry, you okay?
Something happened, didn't it?
What was it?
Later.
I just want to be here with you,
with all of you.
Okay. Want me to call Dad, Frost?
Dad. I'll call.
Can I call them?
Uh, I mean, yeah, it's ringing, so.
♪
Joe?
It's really you.
You're really there.
[LAUGHS]
♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
Nobody uses time against me.
[DEVICE CHIRPS]
I will live.
I will change what's about to happen.
And you will help me.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --