1
00:00:02,838 --> 00:00:04,631
<i>Hello, I'm Johnny Cash.</i>

10
00:01:36,807 --> 00:01:38,183
I got another 15.

11
00:01:38,350 --> 00:01:40,894
Not today, you don't. 
You're up.

12
00:01:44,439 --> 00:01:45,787
You know the deal.

13
00:01:45,607 --> 00:01:48,777
Successfully complete the mission,
you get ten years off your sentence.

14
00:01:51,738 --> 00:01:53,865
<i>You fail to follow
my orders in any way...</i>

15
00:01:54,032 --> 00:01:57,786
<i>...and I detonate the explosive device
in the base of your skull.</i>

16
00:01:57,953 --> 00:02:00,789
- Good dog.
- <i>We are a black ops unit.</i>

18
00:02:00,956 --> 00:02:03,417
<i>Meaning, nothing you see here
ever happened.</i>

19
00:02:03,500 --> 00:02:04,563
Savant!

20
00:02:04,584 --> 00:02:06,904
<i>Your commanding officer
will be Colonel Rick Flag.</i>

21
00:02:07,045 --> 00:02:09,069
Or would you rather
be called Durlin?

22
00:02:09,089 --> 00:02:10,882
I'd rather
not be called at all.

23
00:02:11,341 --> 00:02:14,223
But I'll do anything
to get out of this hellhole.

24
00:02:17,139 --> 00:02:19,641
Well, welcome to "anything."

25
00:02:23,603 --> 00:02:25,897
So this is the famous
Suicide Squad.

26
00:02:26,064 --> 00:02:28,525
Well, we consider
that term degrading.

27
00:02:28,692 --> 00:02:30,861
The official term is
"Task Force X."

28
00:02:31,028 --> 00:02:32,321
And love 'em or hate 'em,

29
00:02:32,487 --> 00:02:35,115
these are your brothers and sisters
for the next few days.

30
00:02:37,826 --> 00:02:39,828


31
00:02:40,871 --> 00:02:41,872


32
00:02:55,886 --> 00:02:57,596
<i>Captain Boomerang.</i>

33
00:02:58,889 --> 00:03:00,344
<i>Blackguard.</i>

34
00:03:00,891 --> 00:03:02,517
<i>Mongal.</i>

35
00:03:03,393 --> 00:03:04,436
<i>Javelin.</i>

36
00:03:05,937 --> 00:03:07,511
<i>T.D.K.</i>

37
00:03:08,607 --> 00:03:09,920
<i>Weasel.</i>

38
00:03:12,277 --> 00:03:13,800
<i>And, of course...</i>

39
00:03:13,820 --> 00:03:16,156
Hey, guys! Sorry I'm late.
Had to go number two.

40
00:03:16,239 --> 00:03:17,741
Good to know.

41
00:03:18,575 --> 00:03:21,745
Flag. Oh, sorry.
Comin' through.

43
00:03:21,912 --> 00:03:22,870
Hey, Boomer!

44
00:03:22,871 --> 00:03:24,471
What are you doing
back in prison, Harls?

45
00:03:24,623 --> 00:03:26,500
I got road rage. In a bank.

46
00:03:26,708 --> 00:03:28,794
Oh. So sorry. Comin' through.

47
00:03:28,960 --> 00:03:31,213
- Turn it around. There. No.
- There? Here?

48
00:03:31,380 --> 00:03:33,548
Put it in there.
Now you're safe.

49
00:03:33,606 --> 00:03:34,706
All right.

50
00:03:34,726 --> 00:03:36,328
Thanks, man.

51
00:03:36,385 --> 00:03:39,471
Prepare for liftoff.
And away we go.

52
00:03:47,104 --> 00:03:48,414
- Harley and T.D.K...
- Digger.

53
00:03:48,438 --> 00:03:50,875
- ...have they worked together before?
- Not yet. I'm excited.

55
00:03:50,899 --> 00:03:53,114
- What does Savant do again?
- It's Brian Durlin.

57
00:03:53,235 --> 00:03:55,801
He's an expert in weapons
and hand-to-hand combat.

58
00:03:55,821 --> 00:03:58,102
Yeah, well, I'm putting 20 on him
that he's gonna bite it.

59
00:03:58,240 --> 00:03:59,574
Me too. And Weasel...

60
00:03:59,658 --> 00:04:01,052
- ...Boomer and Mongal.
- Yeah, I think...

61
00:04:01,076 --> 00:04:03,370
Is Mongal an alien
or some type of god?

62
00:04:03,537 --> 00:04:05,247
- What are you doing?
- Oh. Hey.

63
00:04:05,330 --> 00:04:06,391
Just making sure
everything was ready to go.

64
00:04:06,415 --> 00:04:07,517
Good meeting, everybody.

65
00:04:07,541 --> 00:04:09,292
Just our normal,
casual morning meeting.

66
00:04:09,459 --> 00:04:10,812
Yeah, I just gotta, uh,
do this thing.

67
00:04:10,836 --> 00:04:12,036
Nothing weird about it.

68
00:04:12,170 --> 00:04:13,410
- Okay.
- Oh, yeah.

69
00:04:16,508 --> 00:04:17,562
Flag.

70
00:04:17,592 --> 00:04:19,112
<i>Yeah, we're T-minus five
from the drop.</i>

71
00:04:19,136 --> 00:04:20,363
Get the whole team safely...

72
00:04:20,387 --> 00:04:21,596
<i>...to that beach, Colonel.</i>

73
00:04:21,763 --> 00:04:24,224
<i>You will receive
further orders once there.</i>

74
00:04:39,114 --> 00:04:41,658
We're in a butcher's
freezer, Harls,

75
00:04:41,825 --> 00:04:45,078
surrounded by dead hogs
hangin' on hooks.

76
00:04:45,245 --> 00:04:46,684
Only they don't know it yet.

77
00:04:46,705 --> 00:04:48,957
Leave him alone, Boomer.

78
00:04:49,499 --> 00:04:52,652
- What does T.D.K. stand for?
- What?

80
00:04:52,752 --> 00:04:55,130
Your name is T.D.K., correct?

81
00:04:55,464 --> 00:04:58,550
- Yeah.
- And it stands for what?

83
00:04:59,676 --> 00:05:02,012
It stands for me.
It's what a name is.

85
00:05:02,095 --> 00:05:03,805
Your name is letters?

86
00:05:03,972 --> 00:05:06,308
All names are
letters, dickhead.

87
00:05:10,937 --> 00:05:12,419
I love your accent.

88
00:05:12,439 --> 00:05:14,566
American women
all love accents.

89
00:05:14,733 --> 00:05:17,360
We do. 'Cause we
don't got none.

90
00:05:19,696 --> 00:05:21,615
- Yo, is this a dog?
- What?

91
00:05:22,240 --> 00:05:23,909
Is this thing a dog?

92
00:05:24,701 --> 00:05:26,203
- A... A dog?
- Yes.

93
00:05:26,369 --> 00:05:28,622
What kind of dog
do you think it is, mate?

94
00:05:28,788 --> 00:05:30,788
I don't know, I'm not familiar
with all the breeds.

95
00:05:30,916 --> 00:05:32,584
I'm gonna go
with Afghan Hound.

96
00:05:32,751 --> 00:05:34,794
Since when does an Afghan Hound
have bloody thumbs?

97
00:05:34,961 --> 00:05:36,838
Oh, my God, is it a werewolf?

98
00:05:37,005 --> 00:05:38,524
I've wanted to
meet a werewolf forever!

99
00:05:38,548 --> 00:05:40,401
- Yo, they sat me next to a werewolf?
- That's not right.

100
00:05:40,425 --> 00:05:42,928
Yo, let me out!
I do not fuck with werewolves!

101
00:05:43,512 --> 00:05:46,848
Hey, hey, he's not a werewolf! Okay?
He's a weasel! He's harmless.

103
00:05:47,015 --> 00:05:49,414
I mean, he's not harmless,
he's killed... 27 children, but,

104
00:05:49,434 --> 00:05:52,562
you know, we got him to...
I think he's agreed to do this.

105
00:05:52,896 --> 00:05:56,024
Whatever the case, just everyone
get into position to drop.

106
00:06:54,541 --> 00:06:57,294
Did anyone check
on whether Weasel could swim?

107
00:07:38,043 --> 00:07:40,086
The Weasel is dead! I repeat,

108
00:07:40,253 --> 00:07:42,088
<i>the Weasel is dead!</i>

109
00:07:42,631 --> 00:07:44,924
Northeast, all clear.
Approach the shore.

110
00:07:45,091 --> 00:07:46,114
<i>Over.</i>

111
00:07:46,134 --> 00:07:48,178
Savant, hold your position!

112
00:07:48,470 --> 00:07:50,055
Roger that!

113
00:07:55,101 --> 00:07:56,519
Amateurs.

114
00:08:09,574 --> 00:08:11,451
Waller, we're
on the beach and dry.

115
00:08:34,474 --> 00:08:36,184
- Blackguard. Get down, you...
- Hey, guys!

116
00:08:36,351 --> 00:08:37,995
There's fucking
soldiers everywhere!

117
00:08:38,019 --> 00:08:39,479
You can come out now,
it's just me!

118
00:08:39,646 --> 00:08:41,064
What the fuck
is Blackguard doin'?

119
00:08:41,231 --> 00:08:42,774
I'm the one
who contacted you!

120
00:08:42,941 --> 00:08:44,585
Is this what's supposed
to happen? What the fuck?

121
00:08:44,609 --> 00:08:46,128
Blackguard, get back
into your position!

122
00:08:46,152 --> 00:08:48,154
Look, look! I brought
everybody, look!

123
00:08:48,321 --> 00:08:49,948
They're right behind me!

124
00:08:50,281 --> 00:08:52,117
Whoa! Hey!

125
00:08:52,283 --> 00:08:54,035
Hey, guys! Whoa!

126
00:08:54,411 --> 00:08:56,746
We got a deal, right?

127
00:08:56,913 --> 00:08:59,958
- Waller, we're made!
- I'm the one who called you!

129
00:09:05,922 --> 00:09:07,507
Blackguard sold us out.

130
00:09:07,966 --> 00:09:11,261
<i>He contacted the fucking
Corto Maltese Army!</i>

131
00:09:11,428 --> 00:09:13,471
<i>Waller, we need to retreat!</i>

132
00:09:14,222 --> 00:09:16,851
Negative, Flag.
The mission is too important.

134
00:09:16,891 --> 00:09:18,039
<i>This is a tough group.</i>

135
00:09:18,059 --> 00:09:19,332
- <i>You can make it.</i>
- Okey-doke.

136
00:09:19,352 --> 00:09:21,180
Waller, with all due respect,
we're in the middle of a goddamn...

137
00:09:21,200 --> 00:09:22,544
Harley, wait!

139
00:10:04,147 --> 00:10:05,920
Zero-two-two-seven
is wide open!

140
00:10:05,940 --> 00:10:08,276
Colonel, dispatch
The Detachable Kid!

141
00:10:08,359 --> 00:10:10,278
T.D.K., two o'clock!

142
00:10:11,988 --> 00:10:14,449
T.D.K. is "The Detachable Kid"?

143
00:10:34,469 --> 00:10:35,947
What the fuck?

144
00:10:36,805 --> 00:10:38,515
I didn't pick
the damn team!

145
00:10:38,681 --> 00:10:41,726
Don't worry, Flag!
I got the bird!

146
00:10:42,227 --> 00:10:44,771
Mongal! Don't!

148
00:11:00,161 --> 00:11:01,362
Strewth!

149
00:11:05,428 --> 00:11:06,643
Boomer!

150
00:11:36,489 --> 00:11:38,408
Savant is off the rails.

151
00:11:38,575 --> 00:11:40,493
Savant, turn back.

152
00:11:44,205 --> 00:11:45,790
<i>Savant?</i>

153
00:11:48,293 --> 00:11:50,879
Savant, I'm warning you,
this is desertion.

154
00:11:53,211 --> 00:11:54,299
Savant!

155
00:11:54,465 --> 00:11:56,843
This is your last chance!
Turn back around!

156
00:11:57,510 --> 00:11:59,596
<i>You are in violation
of your agreement!</i>

157
00:12:01,639 --> 00:12:03,975
<i>Oh, please! No! No!</i>

158
00:12:08,313 --> 00:12:09,611
Damn it.

159
00:12:24,787 --> 00:12:26,300
How's Team Two holding up?

160
00:12:29,609 --> 00:12:31,542
Team Two, check!
Set point bravo!

161
00:12:33,171 --> 00:12:35,361
All troops on the
south beach are engaged!

162
00:12:35,381 --> 00:12:38,051
Team Two is clear to go
on the north beach!

163
00:12:39,260 --> 00:12:41,929
Congratulations, Bloodsport.

164
00:12:54,734 --> 00:12:56,361
How'd you do it, Waller?

165
00:12:57,278 --> 00:12:59,780
There's no soldiers out here
on patrol at all.

166
00:12:59,822 --> 00:13:02,659
<i>Let's just say
they were distracted.</i>

202
00:15:15,875 --> 00:15:18,811
Oh, jeez. Oh.

204
00:15:19,462 --> 00:15:21,022
Here you go, champ.

206
00:15:27,053 --> 00:15:28,353
Excuse me.

207
00:15:30,473 --> 00:15:32,850
Who the fuck is Bloodsport?

208
00:15:33,684 --> 00:15:37,605
Robert DuBois.
A world-class marksman.

210
00:15:37,772 --> 00:15:40,441
In his hands,
anything is a deadly weapon.

211
00:15:40,608 --> 00:15:42,214
His father was a mercenary...

212
00:15:42,235 --> 00:15:45,221
...who trained his son to kill
from the moment he was born.

213
00:15:45,321 --> 00:15:47,929
He's in prison for putting
Superman in the ICU...

214
00:15:47,949 --> 00:15:49,617
...with a kryptonite bullet.

215
00:15:50,326 --> 00:15:53,246
- DuBois?
- Same answer as the last time.

216
00:15:53,290 --> 00:15:54,664
Piss off.

217
00:15:56,749 --> 00:16:00,002
I'm not joining your
goddamn Suicide Squad.

218
00:16:00,169 --> 00:16:01,369
We'll see.

219
00:16:02,296 --> 00:16:04,006
You have a visitor.

220
00:16:18,938 --> 00:16:20,398
They said you got in trouble.

221
00:16:21,399 --> 00:16:23,985
- <i>I stole.</i>
- You stole what?

223
00:16:25,820 --> 00:16:27,905
- <i>A style watch.</i>
- A star latch?

224
00:16:28,239 --> 00:16:32,034
A style watch.
You can watch TV on it.

225
00:16:32,201 --> 00:16:33,961
<i>Why would you wanna
watch TV on your watch?</i>

226
00:16:33,995 --> 00:16:35,454
I don't know.

227
00:16:35,621 --> 00:16:38,165
<i>Next time you wana nick something,
you take a partner.</i>

229
00:16:38,249 --> 00:16:41,252
<i>- And they can be your lookout.
- That's your advice?</i>

231
00:16:41,711 --> 00:16:42,733
<i>Yeah.</i>

232
00:16:42,753 --> 00:16:44,338
- <i>You're a terrible father.</i>
- Hey!

233
00:16:44,505 --> 00:16:46,066
<i>I didn't ask to be a father
in the first place!</i>

234
00:16:46,090 --> 00:16:47,980
- <i>You make that perfectly clear!</i>
- All right? Your mother...

235
00:16:48,000 --> 00:16:49,031
<i>...sprung that one on me!</i>

236
00:16:49,051 --> 00:16:51,762
<i>Well, she's not around anymore,
so you can lay off of her, okay?</i>

237
00:16:51,846 --> 00:16:53,160
<i>Oh, I tried to lay off her,</i>

238
00:16:53,180 --> 00:16:54,900
<i>but then she dragged out
the paternity test.</i>

239
00:16:54,932 --> 00:16:56,747
<i>- Fuck you!
- No, fuck you!</i>

240
00:16:56,767 --> 00:16:58,165
<i>- Fuck you!
- Fuck you!</i>

241
00:16:58,185 --> 00:16:59,395
- Fuck you!
- Fuck you!

242
00:16:59,562 --> 00:17:01,022
- <i>Fuck you!</i>
- Fuck you!

243
00:17:01,105 --> 00:17:02,166
<i>Fuck you!</i>

244
00:17:02,273 --> 00:17:06,160
I can't believe you don't care
that I stole, only that I got caught!

245
00:17:06,193 --> 00:17:07,713
I don't only care
that you got caught,

246
00:17:07,737 --> 00:17:08,966
I care that you got caught...

247
00:17:08,988 --> 00:17:11,971
...for stealing something as stupid
as a fucking TV watch!

248
00:17:11,991 --> 00:17:14,118
<i>It does other things too!</i>

249
00:17:14,285 --> 00:17:16,871
<i>But nothing that your phone
can't fucking do! It's embarrassing!</i>

250
00:17:16,954 --> 00:17:21,292
<i>No, what's fucking embarrassing
is having you as my father!</i>

251
00:17:28,007 --> 00:17:31,114
<i>Yeah, well,
I told you, Tyla,</i>

252
00:17:31,135 --> 00:17:33,888
when I came here that
any goodness I ever had in me...

253
00:17:33,971 --> 00:17:36,570
...had been wrung out bare
by my old man.

254
00:17:36,599 --> 00:17:38,851
And I also told you to go out there
and do your own thing...

255
00:17:39,018 --> 00:17:43,272
<i>...and stay far away from me
or anyone like me, didn't I?</i>

256
00:17:43,606 --> 00:17:45,608
So, why are you here
when you and I both know...

257
00:17:45,775 --> 00:17:48,319
...I have nothing good
to offer you?

258
00:17:50,363 --> 00:17:52,365
<i>Because my court date
is coming up,</i>

259
00:17:53,282 --> 00:17:56,500
<i>and Miss Waller said
maybe you could help me out.</i>

260
00:17:56,702 --> 00:17:58,955
To get me to lead
your shite fucking mission,

261
00:17:59,121 --> 00:18:01,141
you're gonna send
my 14-year-old daughter to prison?

262
00:18:01,165 --> 00:18:02,465
No.

263
00:18:03,376 --> 00:18:05,711
Your daughter is 16, DuBois.

264
00:18:06,003 --> 00:18:07,940
- You're a real father of the year.
- Fine. You know what?

265
00:18:07,960 --> 00:18:09,111
Tyla needs to
grow up anyway,

266
00:18:09,131 --> 00:18:10,651
'cause she's a little ditzy
like her fucking mother.

267
00:18:10,675 --> 00:18:12,698
So, a year in juvie,
no fucking problem.

268
00:18:12,718 --> 00:18:16,180
Not juvie. Being 16
in the state of Louisiana...

269
00:18:16,347 --> 00:18:18,861
...means that under
the right circumstances,

270
00:18:18,891 --> 00:18:20,559
she could be tried
as an adult.

271
00:18:21,125 --> 00:18:22,249
And, if convicted,

272
00:18:22,269 --> 00:18:25,361
could be sent right here
to old Belle Reve.

273
00:18:26,107 --> 00:18:28,255
And in here, well, you never know
what might happen...

274
00:18:28,275 --> 00:18:30,444
...to a frail young
thing like that.

275
00:18:30,611 --> 00:18:32,154
Shames me to say...

276
00:18:33,114 --> 00:18:37,660
...that we have the highest mortality rate
in the entire U.S. prison system.

277
00:18:40,162 --> 00:18:41,282
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey!

278
00:18:41,330 --> 00:18:43,521
You're threatening
my fucking daughter!

279
00:18:43,541 --> 00:18:45,144
I'm protecting this country.

280
00:18:45,251 --> 00:18:47,086
- Everyone stand down.
- Miss Waller, I...

281
00:18:47,169 --> 00:18:49,000
STAND DOWN!

282
00:18:53,884 --> 00:18:55,950
I wouldn't take
such extreme measures...

283
00:18:55,970 --> 00:18:57,680
Oh, extreme?
Oh, yeah, a little extreme.

284
00:18:57,847 --> 00:18:59,787
...if this mission
weren't more important...

285
00:18:59,807 --> 00:19:02,560
- ...than you could possibly imagine.
- Fuck your mission!

287
00:19:02,727 --> 00:19:04,407
You have the military
experience necessary,

288
00:19:04,520 --> 00:19:06,856
and everything in your
psychological profile tells me...

289
00:19:07,023 --> 00:19:08,661
...you have what it takes
to be a leader.

290
00:19:08,691 --> 00:19:11,777
- No, I'm no fucking leader!
- Then I'll make you one.

292
00:19:15,781 --> 00:19:18,784
Are you in... or out?

293
00:19:22,997 --> 00:19:25,748
Good. Let's meet your team.

294
00:19:27,835 --> 00:19:29,503
- Come on.
- Fuck me, man!

295
00:19:30,880 --> 00:19:33,330
- Let's go!
- She was gonna kill his kid?

297
00:19:36,761 --> 00:19:38,763
Each member
of the team is chosen...

298
00:19:38,783 --> 00:19:42,391
...for his or her own completely
unique set of abilities.

299
00:19:42,558 --> 00:19:44,000
This...

299
00:19:44,020 --> 00:19:46,624
...is Christopher Smith,
known as Peacemaker.

300
00:19:46,645 --> 00:19:48,981
In his hands,
anything is a deadly weapon.

301
00:19:49,148 --> 00:19:51,192
His father was a soldier
who trained his son..

302
00:19:51,275 --> 00:19:53,319
...to kill from
the moment he was born.

303
00:19:53,486 --> 00:19:55,346
- Are you having a laugh?
- What?

304
00:19:55,446 --> 00:19:57,174
You just said each member
of the team is chosen...

305
00:19:57,198 --> 00:19:59,700
...for their unique abilities.
He does exactly what I do.

306
00:19:59,730 --> 00:20:00,890
But better.

307
00:20:00,910 --> 00:20:03,096
- I always hit my targets dead center.
- I hit them more in the center.

308
00:20:03,120 --> 00:20:04,723
Well, you can't hit something
more in a center.

309
00:20:04,747 --> 00:20:06,290
- I use smaller bullets.
- What?

310
00:20:06,457 --> 00:20:08,977
They go inside your bullet holes
without even touching the side.

311
00:20:09,085 --> 00:20:11,629
Next up... is King Shark.

312
00:20:11,796 --> 00:20:14,465
- Holy shit!
- What the fuck?

314
00:20:15,216 --> 00:20:16,700
Some people claim
that Nanaue...

315
00:20:16,720 --> 00:20:19,303
...is a descendant
of an ancient shark god.

316
00:20:19,470 --> 00:20:21,577
Whatever the case,
he's strong and deadly.

317
00:20:21,597 --> 00:20:22,640
Does it talk?

318
00:20:22,807 --> 00:20:25,392
<i>- Book read.
- Wow!</i>

319
00:20:25,476 --> 00:20:26,661
<i>Book's upside-down.</i>

320
00:20:26,685 --> 00:20:28,285
<i>See that? It's pretending
to read a book!</i>

321
00:20:28,312 --> 00:20:32,691
So smart, me.
Enjoy book so much.

322
00:20:32,822 --> 00:20:35,319
Be a mite careful,
as he's developed a taste...

324
00:20:35,402 --> 00:20:36,904
- ...for human meat.
- Huh?

325
00:20:36,987 --> 00:20:41,150
Next, we have Cleo Cazo,
Ratcatcher 2.

327
00:20:41,951 --> 00:20:43,400
Settle down!

329
00:20:44,829 --> 00:20:46,348
What, we couldn't afford
Ratcatcher 1?

330
00:20:46,372 --> 00:20:48,624
He's dead.
This is his daughter.

331
00:20:48,791 --> 00:20:52,670
- Cazo, will you be joining us?
- I just woke up.

333
00:20:52,753 --> 00:20:55,080
I don't function well
early in the morning.

334
00:20:55,214 --> 00:20:57,424
My deepest apologies
for disturbing you.

335
00:20:57,591 --> 00:21:01,121
- Hmm, it's all right.
- Get your ass out here!

337
00:21:07,977 --> 00:21:09,261
Millennials.

338
00:21:12,857 --> 00:21:14,157
Oh, no way.

339
00:21:14,900 --> 00:21:17,508
- That's not coming with us.
- She controls rats.

340
00:21:17,528 --> 00:21:19,947
I know, I caught that.
It's a disgusting superpower.

341
00:21:20,114 --> 00:21:22,825
This is Sebastian.
Say hello, Sebastian.

342
00:21:24,618 --> 00:21:26,787
I'm not shakin'
the rat's hand.

343
00:21:28,116 --> 00:21:31,333
And finally,
we have Abner Krill.

344
00:21:31,917 --> 00:21:33,232
What's that 'round his neck?

345
00:21:33,252 --> 00:21:36,338
A power dampener.
They call him the Polka-Dot Man.

346
00:21:36,422 --> 00:21:38,549
Polka-Dot Man.

347
00:21:38,632 --> 00:21:41,118
What's he do,
throw polka dots at people?

348
00:21:42,970 --> 00:21:44,271
He does.

349
00:21:44,847 --> 00:21:47,683
- He throws polka dots at people?
- Hey, Polka-Dot Man!

351
00:21:47,850 --> 00:21:50,416
I was hoping you'd entertain
my kid's birthday party,

352
00:21:50,436 --> 00:21:52,146
you fucking pussy!

353
00:21:54,231 --> 00:21:57,818
- These are soldiers?
- We need to debrief.

355
00:22:06,160 --> 00:22:07,765
Fuck.

356
00:22:08,454 --> 00:22:10,069
Corto Maltese...

357
00:22:10,206 --> 00:22:13,792
...is a small island nation
off the coast of South America.

358
00:22:13,959 --> 00:22:18,130
Over the past 100 years, the country
has been ruled with an iron fist...

359
00:22:18,297 --> 00:22:19,815
...by the Herrera family.

360
00:22:20,507 --> 00:22:24,178
But, a week ago, this guy,

361
00:22:24,345 --> 00:22:27,932
General Silvio Luna,
along with his right-hand man,

362
00:22:28,098 --> 00:22:30,266
Mayor General Mateo Suarez,

363
00:22:30,684 --> 00:22:33,229
took control of
the Corto Maltese government...

364
00:22:33,395 --> 00:22:35,773
...in a violent military coup.

365
00:22:35,940 --> 00:22:39,752
The entire Herrera family were hanged
in a public execution.

366
00:22:40,903 --> 00:22:42,980
Although the United States
did not condone...

367
00:22:43,000 --> 00:22:45,407
...the excesses of
the Herrera regime,

368
00:22:45,491 --> 00:22:48,602
they were non-antagonistic
toward the U.S.

369
00:22:48,702 --> 00:22:52,281
Luna, however,
is virulently anti-American.

370
00:22:52,581 --> 00:22:53,874
So, you want us
to kill Luna?

371
00:22:54,250 --> 00:22:55,550
No.

372
00:22:56,168 --> 00:22:57,484
This is Jotunheim.

373
00:22:58,212 --> 00:23:02,299
A scientific experimentation facility
containing something known only...

374
00:23:02,466 --> 00:23:04,885
...as Project Starfish.

375
00:23:05,052 --> 00:23:10,266
Our intelligence sources tell us that Starfish
is extraterrestrial in origin.

376
00:23:10,432 --> 00:23:12,768
In the hands of
the Luna regime,

377
00:23:12,935 --> 00:23:17,314
it is potentially cataclysmic
for Americans and the world.

378
00:23:17,481 --> 00:23:21,485
Your mission
is to infiltrate Jotunheim...

379
00:23:21,652 --> 00:23:25,322
...and destroy every trace
of Project Starfish.

380
00:23:25,429 --> 00:23:28,993
- How are we supposed to get in?
- Gaius Grieves, the Thinker...

382
00:23:29,159 --> 00:23:31,954
...is a geneticist in charge
of Project Starfish.

383
00:23:32,121 --> 00:23:34,970
After hours, he hangs out
at a gentlemen's club...

384
00:23:34,999 --> 00:23:37,960
...known as La Gatita Amable.

385
00:23:38,127 --> 00:23:40,921
Get Grieves to help you
by whatever means necessary,

386
00:23:41,088 --> 00:23:43,424
and he can get you
into Jotunheim.

387
00:23:44,300 --> 00:23:46,010
Any questions?

388
00:23:47,553 --> 00:23:48,880
What is <i>that?</i>

389
00:23:49,638 --> 00:23:51,807
That is an
overhead projector.

390
00:23:51,974 --> 00:23:54,810
- Do you ever use it anymore?
- No, not really.

392
00:23:54,977 --> 00:23:56,770
So, why don't you
just throw it away?

393
00:23:56,937 --> 00:23:58,237
Peacemaker?

394
00:23:58,897 --> 00:24:01,650
Starfish is a slang term
for a butthole.

395
00:24:01,817 --> 00:24:03,569
Think there's
any connection?

396
00:24:05,779 --> 00:24:07,079
No.

397
00:24:07,656 --> 00:24:09,888
- No...
- Nanaue.

399
00:24:09,908 --> 00:24:12,201
- ...connection.
- Hand!

401
00:24:12,202 --> 00:24:15,874
Yes. That is your hand,
Nanaue, very good.

402
00:24:19,168 --> 00:24:20,422
We're all gonna die.

403
00:24:21,295 --> 00:24:22,595
I hope so.

404
00:24:23,589 --> 00:24:25,674
Oh, for fuck's sake.

405
00:24:49,365 --> 00:24:51,472
Control, we have
a disturbance south of here.

406
00:24:51,492 --> 00:24:53,532
<i>It's just a diversion,
Bloodsport.</i>

407
00:24:53,619 --> 00:24:56,497
All right, we cut through the jungle
to get to Valle Del Mar.

408
00:24:56,663 --> 00:24:58,457
Don't they have blockades
at the city limits?

409
00:24:58,624 --> 00:25:00,980
- That's the word.
- How we getting in?

410
00:25:01,000 --> 00:25:02,566
Especially with
Charlie the Tuna here.

411
00:25:02,586 --> 00:25:05,332
- How the hell am I supposed to know?
- You're the leader.

413
00:25:05,381 --> 00:25:06,695
You're supposed
to be decisive.

414
00:25:06,715 --> 00:25:09,615
And I've decided that you should eat
a big bag of dicks, how's that?

415
00:25:09,635 --> 00:25:10,761
You're being facetious.

416
00:25:10,844 --> 00:25:12,864
But if this whole beach
was completely covered in dicks,

417
00:25:12,888 --> 00:25:14,366
and somebody said
I had to eat every dick...

418
00:25:14,390 --> 00:25:16,997
...until the beach was clean for liberty,
I would say no problemo.

420
00:25:17,017 --> 00:25:20,120
Why would someone put penises
all over the beach?

421
00:25:20,187 --> 00:25:22,665
- Who knows why madmen do what they do?
- Well, you know what I think?

422
00:25:22,689 --> 00:25:25,109
I think liberty is just your excuse
to do whatever you want.

423
00:25:25,275 --> 00:25:27,800
Whether that's to eat
a beach full of dicks...

423
00:25:28,000 --> 00:25:29,320
...or killin' folk.

424
00:25:32,282 --> 00:25:33,582
Oh, yeah?

425
00:25:34,201 --> 00:25:36,870
At least I don't kill men
for money like you.

426
00:25:36,912 --> 00:25:38,477
Oh, here we go.

427
00:25:38,497 --> 00:25:41,040
There's something wrong
with your skin!

428
00:25:41,500 --> 00:25:43,961
- It's just a rash.
- That's a rash?

430
00:25:57,683 --> 00:25:58,984
Oh, no.

431
00:26:03,188 --> 00:26:04,565
You...

432
00:26:05,774 --> 00:26:07,443
...are the only one...

433
00:26:08,527 --> 00:26:10,000
...fit to carry...

433
00:26:11,050 --> 00:26:12,440
...my javelin.

434
00:26:21,707 --> 00:26:23,292
Carry it for...

435
00:26:45,689 --> 00:26:48,817
Carry it for who?
For what? What the heck?

437
00:26:48,984 --> 00:26:50,600
Who am I supposed
to carry it for?

438
00:26:53,280 --> 00:26:54,803
This is so frustratin'!

439
00:26:54,823 --> 00:26:57,244
He just told me I have to carry
this javelin for a reason,

440
00:26:57,284 --> 00:26:59,119
but he didn't say why!

441
00:27:00,954 --> 00:27:03,500
Waller? Waller.

441
00:27:04,000 --> 00:27:05,320
Waller!

442
00:27:14,384 --> 00:27:16,094
All right, we'll camp here,

443
00:27:16,261 --> 00:27:18,242
and tomorrow we'll go
straight through to the city...

444
00:27:18,263 --> 00:27:20,557
...to get to La Gatita Amable
by nightfall.

445
00:28:31,795 --> 00:28:33,297
What?

446
00:28:51,773 --> 00:28:53,567
How deep of
a sleeper are you?

447
00:28:53,734 --> 00:28:56,653
I was having
the most wonderful dream.

448
00:28:56,820 --> 00:28:59,382
If it was you about to be eaten
by King Shark, then you're psychic.

449
00:28:59,406 --> 00:29:01,320
I don't believe
he would do that.

450
00:29:01,408 --> 00:29:03,493
He has very kind eyes.

451
00:29:06,997 --> 00:29:09,082
Hungry!

452
00:29:09,416 --> 00:29:11,126
You bastard!

453
00:29:12,252 --> 00:29:13,962


454
00:29:25,974 --> 00:29:27,476
All right, calm down
with the rats!

455
00:29:27,976 --> 00:29:30,265
- What?
- I have a thing with... rats!

456
00:29:30,312 --> 00:29:32,230
- You have a thing with rats?
- Yes.

457
00:29:32,397 --> 00:29:34,900
- And you're on a team with me?
- Not something I asked for!

458
00:29:36,151 --> 00:29:37,980
What are you laughing at me for, man?
Why the fuck are you...

459
00:29:38,000 --> 00:29:40,197
...in your underwear?
Tighty-whities? Really?

460
00:29:40,364 --> 00:29:41,883
- Now, that's just racist.
- No, it's not racist!

462
00:29:41,991 --> 00:29:45,432
- <i>They're tighty-whities.</i>
- Oh, come the fuck on!

463
00:29:45,452 --> 00:29:47,788
Bloodsport's got
a rat phobia!

464
00:29:48,163 --> 00:29:49,463
What?

465
00:29:50,207 --> 00:29:51,333
You didn't tell me...

466
00:29:51,416 --> 00:29:53,418
<i>...you had a fear
of rats, DuBois?</i>

467
00:29:53,485 --> 00:29:56,254
I'm an assassin!
Why would I share my liabilities?

468
00:29:57,673 --> 00:29:58,753
For fuck's sake.

469
00:29:58,840 --> 00:30:02,594
He's offering you a pretty leaf
to show you he means no harm.

470
00:30:02,761 --> 00:30:04,181
Why the fuck
would I want a leaf?

471
00:30:04,956 --> 00:30:07,461
Just get the rats
out of here!

472
00:30:13,146 --> 00:30:16,233
- Oh, fuck's sake.
- Huh. Cool.

473
00:30:20,237 --> 00:30:22,114
Hey, we gonna kill
Megalodouche now, or what?

474
00:30:22,197 --> 00:30:23,980
<i>Nanaue's the strongest
member of your team.</i>

475
00:30:24,000 --> 00:30:25,909
You need him
to get into Jotunheim.

476
00:30:26,076 --> 00:30:28,471
Yeah, well, we can't function as a team
if we gotta watch our back...

477
00:30:28,495 --> 00:30:30,762
...from one of our own
eatin' our bollocks.

478
00:30:32,332 --> 00:30:34,000
Nanaue,

478
00:30:34,200 --> 00:30:36,753
would you...
eat your friends?

479
00:30:37,879 --> 00:30:40,048
I no friends.

480
00:30:40,757 --> 00:30:42,509
You have no friends?

481
00:30:46,471 --> 00:30:48,598
If you did,
would you eat them?

482
00:30:48,765 --> 00:30:50,058
Yes.

483
00:30:55,355 --> 00:30:57,023
No?

484
00:30:57,774 --> 00:30:59,985
Then, can we
be your friends?

485
00:31:00,902 --> 00:31:03,864
Come on.
He's obviously lying.

487
00:31:06,992 --> 00:31:09,494
If I die 'cause
I gambled on love,

488
00:31:10,912 --> 00:31:13,123
it will be a worthy death.

489
00:31:14,291 --> 00:31:15,709
Friends!

490
00:31:23,425 --> 00:31:25,594
You are a little idiot.

491
00:31:34,352 --> 00:31:38,064
Oh, my God! Oh, my God,
I'm good at my job!

492
00:31:38,148 --> 00:31:40,222
I found him. Check it out.

494
00:31:41,193 --> 00:31:43,111
Look, right here,
a mile north.

495
00:31:44,200 --> 00:31:45,343
Task Force X,

496
00:31:45,363 --> 00:31:47,073
you have an additional
mission directive.

497
00:31:47,240 --> 00:31:50,452
<i>We've located Colonel Rick Flag.
He's been taken by the enemy.</i>

498
00:31:50,619 --> 00:31:53,060
- Rick Flag?
- <i>I know, you both served on...</i>

500
00:31:53,121 --> 00:31:55,749
...special forces in Qurac
that took down Avral Kaddam.

501
00:31:55,916 --> 00:31:58,502
<i>Flag was the one
who initially recommended you.</i>

502
00:31:59,085 --> 00:32:02,047
You had other operatives
in Corto Maltese and didn't tell us?

503
00:32:03,089 --> 00:32:06,259
<i>There was no tactical
advantage. Now there is.</i>

505
00:32:06,426 --> 00:32:09,179
<i>I've uploaded
the location on your MTS.</i>

506
00:32:09,346 --> 00:32:13,016
<i>Terminate his captors
with extreme prejudice.</i>

507
00:32:13,809 --> 00:32:18,188
<i>Kill anyone you see.
These are dangerous people.</i>

508
00:32:18,355 --> 00:32:21,221
<i>Recover Flag
before moving on to the city.</i>

509
00:32:25,987 --> 00:32:27,739
That's where
they're holding Flag.

510
00:32:27,906 --> 00:32:30,075
Nothing like a bloodbath
to start the day.

511
00:32:30,742 --> 00:32:32,369
They call you Peacemaker?

512
00:32:32,536 --> 00:32:34,329
I cherish peace
with all my heart.

513
00:32:34,496 --> 00:32:37,791
I don't care how many men, women,
and children I need to kill to get it.

514
00:32:38,792 --> 00:32:40,794
I thought you were
the crazy one.

515
00:32:41,419 --> 00:32:44,256
- I am.
- All right.

517
00:32:44,339 --> 00:32:45,674
Let's get it.

518
00:32:48,677 --> 00:32:51,500
- Boss?
- <i>Gracias.</i>

520
00:33:04,693 --> 00:33:06,050
No, no, no!

521
00:34:38,578 --> 00:34:39,879
No, no, no, no!

523
00:35:09,567 --> 00:35:12,120
Non-lethal. You lose.

525
00:35:12,320 --> 00:35:14,072
Exploding
compression bullets.

526
00:35:17,867 --> 00:35:19,100
No one likes a show-off.

527
00:35:19,120 --> 00:35:22,163
Unless what they're showing off
is dope as fuck.

528
00:35:24,708 --> 00:35:27,000
Fuck! That's true.

529
00:35:42,350 --> 00:35:44,185
He <i>does</i> throw
polka dots at people.

530
00:35:45,353 --> 00:35:47,188
I'm sorry it's so...
flamboyant.

531
00:35:47,355 --> 00:35:50,025
It looks cool. I think.

532
00:35:50,191 --> 00:35:52,960
I don't like to kill people,
but if I pretend they're my mom...

533
00:35:52,980 --> 00:35:55,405
- ...it's easy.
- T.M.I., mate.

534
00:36:04,456 --> 00:36:07,500
- DuBois?
- Hey, Flag.

536
00:36:08,668 --> 00:36:10,222
What the hell
are you doing here?

537
00:36:10,670 --> 00:36:13,381
Waller told us
that you were...

538
00:36:13,923 --> 00:36:14,924


539
00:36:15,592 --> 00:36:16,985
Are you drinkin' tea?

540
00:36:17,135 --> 00:36:19,864
This is Sol Soria, she's the leader
of the freedom fighters,

541
00:36:19,888 --> 00:36:22,370
the resistance trying to
take down the current government.

542
00:36:22,390 --> 00:36:23,933
They saved my life.

543
00:36:24,851 --> 00:36:27,771
Oh, wow!

544
00:36:29,100 --> 00:36:31,816
Why did my people not alert me
of your arrival?

545
00:36:34,027 --> 00:36:36,300
- We didn't see any people.
- Yeah, I didn't see anybody on the way.

546
00:36:36,321 --> 00:36:38,340
- There's no one out there.
- They were gone when we got here.

547
00:36:38,364 --> 00:36:41,743
I turned them into my mother
in my head and killed them.

548
00:36:57,634 --> 00:37:00,300
Typical Americans.
Just run in,

548
00:37:00,900 --> 00:37:02,388
guns blazing!

549
00:37:02,680 --> 00:37:04,682
I know, it's just messed up.

550
00:37:05,100 --> 00:37:07,644
- These guys, they're...
- What's this one do?

551
00:37:07,852 --> 00:37:09,950
They're...
They're fucking idiots,

551
00:37:09,970 --> 00:37:13,399
but right now our objectives
align with yours.

552
00:37:14,567 --> 00:37:17,261
If Jotunheim contains the technology
our intelligence says it does,

553
00:37:17,320 --> 00:37:21,157
then it could be used on the people
of Corto Maltese as well as Americans.

554
00:37:22,400 --> 00:37:26,329
That's why we need your help
to get into the city so we can stop 'em.

555
00:37:27,497 --> 00:37:29,707
Is that rat waving at me?

556
00:37:35,463 --> 00:37:36,763
It appears it is.

557
00:37:37,882 --> 00:37:39,259
Why?

558
00:37:39,425 --> 00:37:41,678
I'm gonna guess
because it's friendly.

559
00:37:44,222 --> 00:37:47,142
Luna and Suarez
murdered my entire family.

560
00:37:48,726 --> 00:37:51,271
I'd make a deal with the Devil
to stop them.

561
00:37:54,149 --> 00:37:57,720
Your people will have our help
getting to Valle Del Mar...

562
00:37:58,528 --> 00:38:02,157
...to apprehend this...
Gaius Grieves.

563
00:38:17,500 --> 00:38:18,800
Hey!

564
00:38:18,965 --> 00:38:21,342
- What is this?
- You slaughtered my staff!

565
00:38:21,718 --> 00:38:24,012
They were loyal
to the Herreras.

566
00:38:24,179 --> 00:38:26,472
Who are you
loyal to, Thinker?

567
00:38:26,639 --> 00:38:28,700
They call you
"Thinker," yes?

568
00:38:29,392 --> 00:38:32584
All that shit in your face
is to make your brain good?

569
00:38:32,604 --> 00:38:35,106
Yes. Makes my brain good.

570
00:38:35,565 --> 00:38:37,750
Are you being
sarcastic with me?

571
00:38:38,902 --> 00:38:40,695
- Hey! Hey!
- I shall do to you...

572
00:38:40,778 --> 00:38:42,655
- ...as we did to your employees!
- Hey! Mateo!

573
00:38:49,704 --> 00:38:51,289
What is this?

574
00:38:53,249 --> 00:38:54,959
Project Starfish.

575
00:38:55,126 --> 00:38:57,503
It's been the primary focus
of my experiments here...

576
00:38:57,670 --> 00:39:00,381
...for the past 30 years.

577
00:39:06,930 --> 00:39:10,016
Here! What...
What is it doing here?

578
00:39:10,416 --> 00:39:14,187
Ooh! It is having
little babies.

580
00:39:14,354 --> 00:39:16,356
Not progeny,

581
00:39:16,773 --> 00:39:18,336
extensions of itself.

582
00:39:19,567 --> 00:39:21,152
They take hosts,

583
00:39:21,319 --> 00:39:24,889
and those hosts in turn
become part of the central being.

584
00:39:26,532 --> 00:39:29,410
It feeds on
their consciousnesses.

585
00:39:30,662 --> 00:39:34,707
Grows larger, more powerful.

586
00:39:40,700 --> 00:39:42,000
So,

587
00:39:45,510 --> 00:39:47,520
where is this
Project Starfish now?

588
00:40:17,125 --> 00:40:19,460
Marvelous idea, <i>Presidente.</i>

589
00:40:20,712 --> 00:40:22,050
But as I've noted,

589
00:40:22,800 --> 00:40:25,383
I've been working
with the beast for 30 years.

590
00:40:26,217 --> 00:40:30,013
And there's no one but me...
capable of controlling it.

591
00:40:30,555 --> 00:40:31,855
Well, then,

592
00:40:33,850 --> 00:40:35,330
welcome to the team.

593
00:40:42,066 --> 00:40:44,838
- <i>Sí,</i> Camila!
- <i>Presidente?</i>

595
00:40:49,782 --> 00:40:52,640
You are making a big mistake
throwing me down here!

597
00:40:52,660 --> 00:40:54,183
I will be outta here
soon enough,

598
00:40:54,203 --> 00:40:57,061
and I will kill
every - last - one of you,

599
00:40:57,081 --> 00:41:01,002
Colto Maltese-tezios.
Maltese-els.

600
00:41:01,169 --> 00:41:03,671
Malte-multoids.
Colt-a-mults?

601
00:41:03,838 --> 00:41:06,424
Whatever you <i>Mario Kart</i>-racing
d-bags are called!

602
00:41:07,759 --> 00:41:09,059
Please.

603
00:41:09,802 --> 00:41:11,102
Put this on.

604
00:41:23,483 --> 00:41:24,984
Oh, wow!

605
00:41:29,197 --> 00:41:30,826
I'm a princess.

606
00:41:53,638 --> 00:41:56,621
<i>Señorita</i> Quinn,
on behalf of the entire staff...

608
00:41:56,641 --> 00:42:00,186
...of Our Honorable General <i>Presidente</i>
Silvio Eleuterio Luna,

609
00:42:00,353 --> 00:42:01,720
it's a pleasure
to serve you.

610
00:42:03,100 --> 00:42:04,420
<i>Gracias.</i>

611
00:42:05,691 --> 00:42:10,446
My mother said
to count back again.

612
00:42:10,500 --> 00:42:11,989
Ten, nine,

613
00:42:12,573 --> 00:42:14,325
eight, seven, six,

614
00:42:14,826 --> 00:42:16,744
five, four, three,

615
00:42:16,953 --> 00:42:21,290
two, one. Ha!
Coronel, beat that...

616
00:42:27,839 --> 00:42:28,840


617
00:42:28,923 --> 00:42:31,467
Forgive my appearance,
<i>Señorita</i> Quinn.

618
00:42:33,010 --> 00:42:34,000
I have...

618
00:42:34,100 --> 00:42:38,111
...admired you from afar
for many years now.

620
00:42:39,058 --> 00:42:40,358
<i>Señorita.</i>

621
00:42:41,408 --> 00:42:42,708
Me?

622
00:42:42,728 --> 00:42:46,190
You're a hero to me,
as well as to my people.

623
00:42:46,357 --> 00:42:48,734
I think you might
got me confused.

624
00:42:48,901 --> 00:42:51,926
Harley Quinn's fire and rebellion
in the face of American oppression...

625
00:42:51,946 --> 00:42:54,262
...is something to which
my entire country aspires.

626
00:42:54,282 --> 00:42:55,450


627
00:42:55,616 --> 00:42:56,909
I have prepared lunch.

628
00:42:58,600 --> 00:43:00,750
Would you be so kind
as to join me?

629
00:43:02,457 --> 00:43:05,084
I'm so kind, sure.

643
00:44:03,184 --> 00:44:04,560
You want me to what?

644
00:44:06,771 --> 00:44:10,024
- To marry me.
- You're joshing.

646
00:44:10,525 --> 00:44:12,360
Might I be frank, Harley?

647
00:44:13,110 --> 00:44:14,411
You might be.

648
00:44:16,239 --> 00:44:17,823
Good, listen.

649
00:44:17,990 --> 00:44:21,280
Since I took control,
the majority love me. But...

650
00:44:21,300 --> 00:44:23,871
...some find me to be...

651
00:44:24,747 --> 00:44:26,730
...an unacceptable leader.

652
00:44:26,958 --> 00:44:29,819
What kinds of dicks
would find that?

653
00:44:29,919 --> 00:44:31,837
Don't they know
how awesome you are?

654
00:44:32,004 --> 00:44:33,319
Have you shown them
the birdies?

655
00:44:33,339 --> 00:44:37,000
It may sound... archaic to someone
from your part of the world, but...

656
00:44:37,300 --> 00:44:39,277
...my people,
the Corto Malteseans...

657
00:44:39,220 --> 00:44:42,557
- ...they're <i>very</i> old-fashioned!
- Corto Malteseans, of course!

658
00:44:42,723 --> 00:44:44,300
And I am a bachelor.

659
00:44:44,934 --> 00:44:46,920
So they... want you
to get hitched?

660
00:44:47,019 --> 00:44:49,380
My people say you would make
the perfect wife.

661
00:44:50,022 --> 00:44:53,359
Because, you know,
you symbolize anti-American fervor.

662
00:44:54,652 --> 00:44:55,778


663
00:44:56,737 --> 00:44:58,864
But I am a romantic, Harley.

664
00:45:00,241 --> 00:45:02,702
I agreed to meet with you
just to appease them.

665
00:45:03,911 --> 00:45:07,331
However, upon spending
the day with you,

666
00:45:08,416 --> 00:45:11,850
I find myself hardly able
to think straight.

667
00:45:12,753 --> 00:45:16,299
- You are perfect in every...
- You are so freaking hot!

673
00:45:40,948 --> 00:45:42,825
Harley Luna.

674
00:45:44,869 --> 00:45:46,544
I like the ring of that.

675
00:46:11,270 --> 00:46:12,813
That's Jotunheim?

676
00:46:15,483 --> 00:46:16,950
Nazis...

676
00:46:16,970 --> 00:46:19,820
...came here seeking asylum
after World War Il.

677
00:46:21,572 --> 00:46:23,300
They built Jotunheim to...

677
00:46:23,600 --> 00:46:26,494
...continue their
unorthodox experiments.

678
00:46:27,995 --> 00:46:31,499
Until the Herrera family accepted
the bounty on the Nazis' heads...

679
00:46:32,375 --> 00:46:34,584
- ...and killed them all.
- Wowza!

681
00:46:34,710 --> 00:46:37,463
Many years ago,
the rumors began of a beast.

682
00:46:38,464 --> 00:46:42,218
These dark rumors helped
the Herrera family maintain power.

683
00:46:42,385 --> 00:46:45,846
They would send their political enemies
and their families to the fortress,

684
00:46:46,013 --> 00:46:47,348
never to return.

685
00:46:48,307 --> 00:46:51,519
I have... recently learned...

686
00:46:52,353 --> 00:46:54,271
...these were not rumors.

687
00:46:54,438 --> 00:46:56,607
They were murdering
thousands...

688
00:46:56,774 --> 00:47:00,403
...in bizarre experiments
with this creature.

689
00:47:01,737 --> 00:47:04,615
Well, it must be a big relief
to got it in your hands now, huh?

690
00:47:05,282 --> 00:47:06,701
Absolutely.

691
00:47:07,785 --> 00:47:11,455
Now, it is our enemies
who shall be fearful.

692
00:47:12,873 --> 00:47:14,000
If anyone...

692
00:47:14,050 --> 00:47:17,753
...dares to say a negative word
about their new <i>presidente</i> today,

693
00:47:17,920 --> 00:47:22,633
their parents, their children,
and anyone they ever loved...

694
00:47:22,800 --> 00:47:26,347
...will be sent to Jotunheim
to feed the beast.

695
00:47:27,805 --> 00:47:29,473
I'm sorry.

696
00:47:32,351 --> 00:47:35,661
Recently, I made a promise to myself
that the next time I got a boyfriend,

697
00:47:35,771 --> 00:47:38,566
I'd be on the lookout for red flags.
And if I saw any,

698
00:47:38,733 --> 00:47:40,192
I would do
the healthy thing...

699
00:47:41,110 --> 00:47:42,544
...and I would murder him.

700
00:47:45,030 --> 00:47:49,468
And killing kids,
kind of a red flag.

701
00:47:50,995 --> 00:47:52,059
I know, I know!

702
00:47:52,079 --> 00:47:55,100
I know what you're tryin' to say!
"Harley, why not just leave?"

703
00:47:55,124 --> 00:47:57,732
And I'd say, "Why are you
screaming at me? I'm not deaf,

704
00:47:57,752 --> 00:47:59,086
I'm standing right here!"

705
00:47:59,462 --> 00:48:00,940
And then I'd say,

706
00:48:01,630 --> 00:48:05,050
"When your taste in men...
is as bad as mine,

707
00:48:06,385 --> 00:48:09,300
they don't just
go away quietly, they...

708
00:48:10,300 --> 00:48:13,120
...slash your tires,
and they kill your dogs, and...

709
00:48:13,184 --> 00:48:16,950
...tell you that the music you like
ain't real music at all," and...

710
00:48:16,970 --> 00:48:18,481
...all the cruelty...

711
00:48:24,862 --> 00:48:27,198
...tears you apart
after a while.

712
00:48:39,877 --> 00:48:41,687
You were real
pretty and all,

713
00:48:42,630 --> 00:48:47,635
and R.I.P. to that absolutely beautiful
monster between your legs, but...

714
00:48:48,803 --> 00:48:50,304
...all in all,

715
00:48:52,139 --> 00:48:53,944
I think you're
more pretty like this...

716
00:48:54,809 --> 00:48:58,437
...with all those rotten thoughts
emptied from your head.

717
00:49:01,357 --> 00:49:03,192
I can't believe
this thing had a bullet.

718
00:49:07,404 --> 00:49:11,033
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I got it!

719
00:50:20,269 --> 00:50:22,396


720
00:50:27,943 --> 00:50:29,320
What the hell are you doin'?

721
00:50:30,905 --> 00:50:33,637
We're tired, Colonel.
We need a rest.

722
00:50:33,657 --> 00:50:35,326
Goddamn hobbyists.

723
00:50:35,784 --> 00:50:38,805
We cannot stop. We need to hurry
if you're gonna help my people.

725
00:50:38,829 --> 00:50:40,998
Hey! We're not here
to help your people.

726
00:50:41,248 --> 00:50:43,000
But she's right,
we gotta keep moving.

727
00:50:43,167 --> 00:50:45,377
I carry friend?

728
00:50:45,461 --> 00:50:47,713
It's okay, Nanaue.

729
00:50:50,507 --> 00:50:52,551
It's happening
to his face again.

730
00:50:52,581 --> 00:50:55,400
- It's nothing, I slipped.
- Hey! Norman Bates!

731
00:50:56,000 --> 00:50:57,536
If that shit's contagious,
we need to know.

732
00:50:57,556 --> 00:50:58,856
It's not.

733
00:51:00,184 --> 00:51:01,664
- What is it?
- It's a...

734
00:51:04,438 --> 00:51:06,482
It's an interdimensional virus.

735
00:51:08,567 --> 00:51:09,818
Fuck is that?

736
00:51:11,153 --> 00:51:13,344
My mother was a scientist
at S.T.A.R. Labs,

737
00:51:13,364 --> 00:51:16,158
and she was obsessed with turning me
and my brothers and sisters...

738
00:51:16,241 --> 00:51:17,826
...into superheroes.

739
00:51:19,528 --> 00:51:20,983
She infected me.

740
00:51:21,747 --> 00:51:24,583
Now, if I don't, you know,
expel the dots twice a day...

741
00:51:25,376 --> 00:51:26,627
Then what?

742
00:51:28,921 --> 00:51:30,547
They'll eat me alive.

743
00:51:31,924 --> 00:51:34,385
What happened to
your brothers and sisters?

744
00:51:36,512 --> 00:51:39,473
Some lived, some...

746
00:51:41,850 --> 00:51:43,150
...died.

747
00:51:43,727 --> 00:51:47,022
And your mom,
where is <i>she</i> now?

748
00:51:51,527 --> 00:51:53,195
Everywhere.

749
00:52:00,536 --> 00:52:03,265
Okay. Let's move out.

750
00:52:03,372 --> 00:52:06,875
Come on, we must hurry,
or we'll be late to meet my contact.

756
00:53:14,026 --> 00:53:15,736
Nom, nom!

757
00:53:19,990 --> 00:53:21,241
Are you Milton?

758
00:53:22,868 --> 00:53:24,995
<i>Si!</i>

759
00:53:28,415 --> 00:53:31,744
Milton will drive you through town
and to La Gatita Amable.

761
00:53:31,794 --> 00:53:35,255
There are clothes in the boxes
for all of you so you can blend in.

762
00:53:35,464 --> 00:53:38,050
That said,
the walking <i>tiburón</i>...

763
00:53:38,217 --> 00:53:39,802
...is gonna have to
stay out of sight.

764
00:53:40,010 --> 00:53:41,611
I wear disguise.

765
00:53:42,179 --> 00:53:44,973
Oh! You're going
to wear a disguise.

766
00:53:45,100 --> 00:53:46,205
<i>Sí.</i>

767
00:53:46,225 --> 00:53:49,600
- Hey, he's learnin' Spanish.
- And what kind of disguise?

769
00:53:49,937 --> 00:53:52,980
- Fake moustache.
- Yeah!

770
00:53:53,000 --> 00:53:55,234
Fake moustache
isn't gonna cut it, mate.

771
00:53:59,446 --> 00:54:02,157
There's gonna be a lot of soldiers
watching Jotunheim.

772
00:54:02,991 --> 00:54:05,432
- If they discover us there...
- Let's pray they do not.

773
00:54:05,452 --> 00:54:08,205
- Or you will all be dead.
- If they do...

775
00:54:08,372 --> 00:54:10,457
...that'll leave
the palace vulnerable.

776
00:54:12,126 --> 00:54:15,546
Luna and the other generals
will be left without protection.

777
00:54:23,303 --> 00:54:25,639
You're a good man,
Colonel Flag.

778
00:54:29,601 --> 00:54:31,662
You still look
exactly like yourself.

779
00:54:31,728 --> 00:54:33,568
That's the worst fake moustache
I've ever seen.

780
00:54:33,981 --> 00:54:35,861
And if you had fooled us,
we'd have to kill you,

781
00:54:36,024 --> 00:54:39,049
shark-shaped bloke with a moustache
creeping up on us like that.

782
00:54:39,069 --> 00:54:40,529
Fuck!

783
00:54:41,655 --> 00:54:43,365
You, you!

784
00:54:47,619 --> 00:54:48,787


785
00:54:48,871 --> 00:54:51,415
He always wants
to be near you.

786
00:54:51,582 --> 00:54:53,208
I think he senses
good in you.

787
00:54:53,375 --> 00:54:55,210
Yeah, there's no good in me.

788
00:55:00,400 --> 00:55:01,700
Damn!

789
00:55:01,758 --> 00:55:04,199
Supposed to play golf
with Senator Cray this weekend.

790
00:55:04,219 --> 00:55:07,690
- I'm gonna look a fool.
- <i>Waller, come in!</i>

792
00:55:08,807 --> 00:55:09,808


793
00:55:10,709 --> 00:55:11,957
You missed.

794
00:55:11,977 --> 00:55:14,855
- <i>Waller, do you copy?</i>
- We're losing connection.

795
00:55:16,356 --> 00:55:17,657
<i>Waller!</i>

796
00:55:19,735 --> 00:55:22,300
- Fuck's sake.
- <i>Task Force X.</i>

797
00:55:22,320 --> 00:55:24,000
- Waller!
- <i>You there?</i>

799
00:55:24,640 --> 00:55:26,050
<i>The military
must have put...</i>

800
00:55:26,074 --> 00:55:28,160
...signal jammers
around the city.

801
00:55:28,327 --> 00:55:30,954
Your comms are down,
but we can still activate the bombs.

802
00:55:31,121 --> 00:55:33,220
Not to mention what will happen
to your daughter.

803
00:55:33,415 --> 00:55:35,250
So, no funny business.

804
00:55:35,709 --> 00:55:38,367
- <i>Do you copy, DuBois?</i>
- Copy!

806
00:55:38,388 --> 00:55:40,130
<i>Fuck you!</i>

807
00:55:41,089 --> 00:55:44,200
Hey, uh, all that stuff
about his daughter, you...

808
00:55:44,220 --> 00:55:46,303
...wouldn't really
do that, right?

809
00:55:46,470 --> 00:55:49,264
You don't know <i>half</i>
of what I would do, John.

810
00:56:09,701 --> 00:56:11,020
What?

811
00:56:11,745 --> 00:56:14,414
Why are you
so afraid of rats?

812
00:56:16,583 --> 00:56:19,544
Why are you so in love
with them, Ratcatcher 2?

813
00:56:20,754 --> 00:56:22,089
You know what I think?

814
00:56:22,256 --> 00:56:24,800
I think you have a serious case
of daddy issues.

815
00:56:24,967 --> 00:56:28,428
I have no issues
with how much I loved my father.

816
00:56:37,271 --> 00:56:39,398
Although he was a genius,

817
00:56:41,900 --> 00:56:45,696
we lived homeless in the streets
of Portugal 'cause of his...

818
00:56:48,573 --> 00:56:49,950
...burdens.

819
00:56:52,536 --> 00:56:55,372
He built the machines
I employ today, and...

820
00:56:56,790 --> 00:56:59,459
...taught me the secrets
of calling the rats.

821
00:57:03,547 --> 00:57:06,300
They brought us
trinkets to live on,

822
00:57:07,259 --> 00:57:10,887
and they kept us warm at night,
when we would have frozen.

823
00:57:13,849 --> 00:57:16,810
- But eventually...
- <i>Papa!</i>

824
00:57:16,977 --> 00:57:19,980
- <i>Papa, wake up!</i>
- ...my father's burdens...

826
00:57:20,856 --> 00:57:23,066
...became too heavy to carry!

827
00:57:23,233 --> 00:57:25,766
<i>No! No, Papa!</i>

829
00:57:25,786 --> 00:57:29,115
- And he was gone!
- <i>Papa, wake up!</i>

830
00:57:33,994 --> 00:57:36,872
I took his machinery
and came to America.

831
00:57:37,039 --> 00:57:38,710
That is the dream, right?

832
00:57:40,500 --> 00:57:41,950
But I was arrested...

833
00:57:42,711 --> 00:57:45,213
...for armed bank robbery,
do you believe it?

834
00:57:45,380 --> 00:57:47,799
The state considered
the rats a weapon!

835
00:57:51,178 --> 00:57:52,478
What?

836
00:57:55,599 --> 00:57:57,642
You remind me
of my daughter.

837
00:57:58,518 --> 00:58:00,312
The reason I'm here.

838
00:58:01,563 --> 00:58:04,232
Why are you
so afraid of rats?

839
00:58:05,150 --> 00:58:06,735
My old man!

840
00:58:08,153 --> 00:58:09,538
When I was a lad,

841
00:58:09,738 --> 00:58:11,615
if I didn't
finish a task right,

842
00:58:11,782 --> 00:58:13,909
he would dole out
the punishment.

843
00:58:14,993 --> 00:58:19,998
And one day, he just...
locked me in a crate for 24 hours.

844
00:58:22,000 --> 00:58:24,378
And it was
full of starvin' rats.

845
00:58:25,921 --> 00:58:28,632
As imperfect my father was,

846
00:58:32,469 --> 00:58:34,471
he loved me!

847
00:58:37,933 --> 00:58:39,770
I wish I could
give that to you.

848
00:58:43,313 --> 00:58:45,023
Don't you worry, yeah?

849
00:58:45,190 --> 00:58:47,734
I'm gonna get you
out of here alive.

850
00:58:47,901 --> 00:58:50,780
I'm going to get <i>you</i>
out of here alive.

851
00:58:58,036 --> 00:59:01,039
<i>Señores,</i> this is the place.

852
00:59:25,272 --> 00:59:27,550
So, when's this Thinker guy
supposed to be here?

853
00:59:27,649 --> 00:59:29,121
Supposed to be
in the next few hours.

854
00:59:29,151 --> 00:59:32,571
Looks like we gotta find something to do
to pass the time. Uh, miss?

856
00:59:32,654 --> 00:59:34,531
How about some, uh...

857
00:59:34,698 --> 00:59:36,658
What do you guys drink
around here, Fernet?

858
00:59:36,741 --> 00:59:38,094
How about a round of
Fernets for the table.

859
00:59:38,118 --> 00:59:39,182
<i>- Comprende?
- Sí.</i>

860
00:59:39,202 --> 00:59:42,384
Hey, Pissmaker,
we're on a mission.

861
00:59:42,414 --> 00:59:45,667
Easy, Inspector Gadget.
A little drink never hurt nobody.

862
00:59:45,834 --> 00:59:47,294
Except for the
thousands of people...

863
00:59:47,377 --> 00:59:49,713
...killed in drunk driving
accidents every year.

864
00:59:51,423 --> 00:59:53,250
Come on, DuBois,
this could be our last drink!

865
00:59:55,093 --> 00:59:57,659
- <i>Gracias.</i>
- Just one.

867
00:59:57,679 --> 01:00:00,265
- You're gonna be that guy?
- I'm gonna be that guy.

868
01:00:01,113 --> 01:00:02,559
Hey, <i>chica!</i>

869
01:00:03,602 --> 01:00:05,061
Forgot the rat.

870
01:00:09,733 --> 01:00:11,985
Here's to being alive
in three hours!

871
01:00:12,736 --> 01:00:15,155
I'll be alive.
You speak for yourself.

872
01:00:27,501 --> 01:00:30,003
There you go! There you go!

873
01:00:30,295 --> 01:00:32,547
Don't give
any more to Polka!

881
01:02:03,600 --> 01:02:05,926
Go! Go!

882
01:02:17,110 --> 01:02:19,696
That... is a gun.

883
01:02:19,863 --> 01:02:21,197
So, smile.

884
01:02:23,220 --> 01:02:26,286
We're old mates who are gonna
take a trip to Jotunheim.

885
01:02:29,080 --> 01:02:30,381
Yup.

886
01:02:30,790 --> 01:02:34,794
Even with my help,
you think you can get into Jotunheim?

887
01:02:35,629 --> 01:02:38,006
Well, if we can't,
I've got a Great White out back...

888
01:02:38,089 --> 01:02:40,425
...that's looking
for some chum. Now, come on.

890
01:02:43,094 --> 01:02:44,394
All right.

891
01:02:45,430 --> 01:02:46,831
Nice and easy.

892
01:02:52,500 --> 01:02:53,863
Oh, fuck.

893
01:03:13,541 --> 01:03:14,834
No, no, no!

894
01:03:22,409 --> 01:03:23,740
All right.

895
01:03:24,135 --> 01:03:25,533
Take him out
through the back. All right?

896
01:03:25,553 --> 01:03:28,280
Find my coordinates in the pad
and meet me in half an hour.

897
01:03:28,300 --> 01:03:29,300
- What?
- Hey!

897
01:03:29,320 --> 01:03:30,622
Did you hear what I said?

898
01:03:30,642 --> 01:03:32,143
- Yes, but...
- Go!

899
01:03:33,520 --> 01:03:34,854
Let's go.

900
01:03:36,731 --> 01:03:39,070
Hey, calm down!

901
01:03:40,318 --> 01:03:42,165
There's no need to disturb
everyone's night!

902
01:03:42,195 --> 01:03:44,054
I'm right here,
I'm the one you're looking for!

903
01:03:44,072 --> 01:03:47,200
Yep! Us too!
We're his American companions!

904
01:03:47,367 --> 01:03:48,667
What?

905
01:03:48,910 --> 01:03:50,704


906
01:03:56,000 --> 01:03:59,129
Come on! Go!

907
01:04:01,923 --> 01:04:03,223
Oh, God.

908
01:04:04,259 --> 01:04:05,659
Move it!

909
01:04:07,345 --> 01:04:10,105
- Come on!
- Hey!

911
01:04:22,652 --> 01:04:24,884
Your equipment manipulates
animal behavior, clever.

912
01:04:24,904 --> 01:04:27,387
I'm working on something
similar with humans.

913
01:04:27,407 --> 01:04:30,598
- Be quiet, please!
- You are perceivably panicked.

915
01:04:30,618 --> 01:04:33,143
I'm guessing that you are not
the alphas of this battalion.

916
01:04:33,163 --> 01:04:36,249
Do you want a dozen angry rodents
crawling up your ass?

917
01:04:37,167 --> 01:04:38,830
My answer might not be
what you expect.

918
01:04:40,920 --> 01:04:42,221
Go, go!

921
01:04:56,436 --> 01:04:58,111
I'm sorry for you.

922
01:04:58,563 --> 01:05:03,193
But soon you will all be joining
your deranged compatriot, Harley Quinn.

923
01:05:04,569 --> 01:05:07,614
- Is Harley alive?
- Not for long.

925
01:05:07,781 --> 01:05:10,200
Mayor General Suarez
can be rather harsh...

925
01:05:10,240 --> 01:05:12,327
...when extracting
information.

929
01:05:29,803 --> 01:05:31,144
<i>Dim mak.</i>

930
01:05:33,056 --> 01:05:34,856
That's the Cantonese
term for it.

931
01:05:34,974 --> 01:05:36,935
In Japan,
it's <i>kyusho jitsu.</i>

932
01:05:37,685 --> 01:05:40,730
In English, it's simply...
the Death Touch.

933
01:05:41,606 --> 01:05:44,275
How to kill a man
with a single blow.

934
01:05:44,442 --> 01:05:46,300
Of course it's possible...

934
01:05:46,700 --> 01:05:48,463
...to kill a man
with a single blow.

935
01:05:50,240 --> 01:05:54,077
But it's a matter of chance,
and cannot be wielded with certainty.

936
01:05:55,370 --> 01:05:57,472
- That's what they say.
- "They"?

937
01:05:57,914 --> 01:05:59,312
- Amateurs.
- On one?

938
01:05:59,332 --> 01:06:00,632
One.

939
01:06:05,338 --> 01:06:06,965
I don't smoke.

941
01:07:47,690 --> 01:07:48,990
All right.

942
01:07:50,860 --> 01:07:52,654
Let's go to Jotunheim.

943
01:07:54,197 --> 01:07:55,497
Nope.

944
01:07:55,698 --> 01:07:58,076
There's somethin'
we gotta take care of first.

945
01:07:58,201 --> 01:07:59,502
What?

946
01:08:06,250 --> 01:08:11,506
<i>I ain't got nobody</i>

947
01:08:11,673 --> 01:08:16,260
<i>Nobody cares for me, no...</i>

948
01:08:24,727 --> 01:08:26,980
I will ask again.

949
01:08:27,146 --> 01:08:30,780
How many meta-power teammates
arrived with you...

949
01:08:30,800 --> 01:08:32,500
...to Corto Maltese?

950
01:08:34,153 --> 01:08:36,720
- Sixty-nine.
- Sixty-nine?

952
01:08:37,128 --> 01:08:39,909
How could you get
69 troops into the...

953
01:08:56,801 --> 01:09:02,640
<i>I'm so sad and lonely</i>

954
01:09:08,730 --> 01:09:11,232
<i>Won't some sweet momma
Come and rescue me...</i>

955
01:09:33,463 --> 01:09:35,983
You gotta be kiddin' me!
You're gonna risk the entire mission...

957
01:09:36,007 --> 01:09:37,735
...for a mental defective
dressed as a court jester!

958
01:09:37,759 --> 01:09:39,824
This coming from a guy
that wears a toilet seat on his head?

959
01:09:39,844 --> 01:09:41,951
- We don't leave one of our own behind!
- You're okay with this?

960
01:09:41,971 --> 01:09:44,324
No, but I've been around Flag
when he's got a rag in his mouth.

961
01:09:44,348 --> 01:09:46,041
- Best not to tug it.
- Motherfucker!

962
01:09:47,935 --> 01:09:51,049
- Hey, wake up, wake up!
- All right, let's go.

964
01:09:54,317 --> 01:09:56,086
All right, we'll enter
through the third floor,

965
01:09:56,110 --> 01:09:58,362
go to the inner staircase,
and then down to the cellar...

966
01:09:58,400 --> 01:09:59,965
...where they usually
keep their detainees.

967
01:09:59,989 --> 01:10:01,422
Hopefully,
Harley's still alive.

968
01:10:01,949 --> 01:10:04,410
It's not a toilet seat,
it's a beacon of freedom!

998
01:14:10,323 --> 01:14:11,624
<i>Hola!</i>

999
01:14:21,584 --> 01:14:22,626


1000
01:14:42,563 --> 01:14:44,523
Ratatouille, what do you got?

1001
01:14:45,358 --> 01:14:47,318
Third floor hallway's clear!

1002
01:14:47,950 --> 01:14:49,253
Abner?

1003
01:14:49,320 --> 01:14:51,947
There doesn't seem
to be any incoming traffic.

1004
01:14:53,074 --> 01:14:54,374
Bird.

1005
01:14:55,743 --> 01:14:57,620
Nanaue! Stay off the comm!

1006
01:14:59,950 --> 01:15:00,950
Colonel,

1006
01:15:00,970 --> 01:15:03,185
I got a clean shot
on the only one in the office.

1007
01:15:03,209 --> 01:15:04,610
Just give the word.

1008
01:15:13,177 --> 01:15:15,137
Fire on three...

1009
01:15:15,304 --> 01:15:17,151
- Two...
- What are you guys doing?

1010
01:15:18,557 --> 01:15:21,519
I... You... We... We're...
here to save you.

1011
01:15:23,729 --> 01:15:26,190
You were gonna... save me?

1012
01:15:26,565 --> 01:15:28,901
It was a really
good plan, too.

1013
01:15:29,360 --> 01:15:31,837
Well, I can go back inside,
and you can still do it.

1014
01:15:31,904 --> 01:15:33,364
That's patronizing.

1015
01:15:34,240 --> 01:15:35,646
Yeah, no, it's not...

1016
01:15:37,611 --> 01:15:39,537
Uh, what's with the javelin?

1017
01:15:39,703 --> 01:15:41,310
I'm waitin' for God
to tell me.

1018
01:15:41,330 --> 01:15:44,300
- Jesus Christ.
- Yeah. Or Him.

1019
01:15:44,320 --> 01:15:47,283
- Or any of them, really.
- Okay.

1021
01:15:47,753 --> 01:15:49,053
Okay.

1022
01:15:50,214 --> 01:15:51,733
Are you two all right, yeah?

1023
01:15:51,757 --> 01:15:53,068
- I'm so sorry.
- That's all right.

1024
01:15:53,092 --> 01:15:55,511
- Harley Quinn.
- Bloodsport.

1026
01:16:00,433 --> 01:16:03,227
<i>All right, who... who ate
all the fucking empanadas?</i>

1027
01:16:03,394 --> 01:16:05,896
<i>Mine were very good.
I had the chicken.</i>

1028
01:16:06,772 --> 01:16:08,315
<i>All right.</i>

1029
01:16:08,482 --> 01:16:11,298
Here's the deal.
We fail the mission, you die.

1030
01:16:11,318 --> 01:16:14,530
We find out any information
you give us is false, you die.

1031
01:16:14,738 --> 01:16:17,720
If we find out you have
personalized license plates...

1032
01:16:17,740 --> 01:16:19,222
- ...you die.
- What? No.

1033
01:16:19,243 --> 01:16:20,980
If you mismatch blacks...

1033
01:16:21,000 --> 01:16:22,268
- ...you die.
- No.

1034
01:16:22,288 --> 01:16:24,081
If you cough
without covering your mouth...

1035
01:16:24,165 --> 01:16:26,459
Harley! Those last three
aren't things.

1036
01:16:26,625 --> 01:16:28,357
Although, probably
don't need to say this,

1037
01:16:28,377 --> 01:16:30,109
but that isn't
an open invitation for you...

1038
01:16:30,129 --> 01:16:31,277
...to cough without
covering your mouth.

1039
01:16:31,297 --> 01:16:34,200
All right, we're gonna need you to drive
the minibus, with all of us inside,

1040
01:16:34,220 --> 01:16:35,759
<i>past the guards
at the front gate.</i>

1041
01:16:35,926 --> 01:16:37,300
<i>Once through the gate,
we'll use you...</i>

1041
01:16:37,320 --> 01:16:38,613
...to get through
the retinal scanner.

1042
01:16:38,637 --> 01:16:40,848
There are security
cameras everywhere.

1043
01:16:41,015 --> 01:16:42,641
They're being dealt with.

1044
01:16:53,402 --> 01:16:55,571
<i>We'll neutralize
the soldiers there... and enter.</i>

1045
01:16:55,738 --> 01:16:58,370
Once we're inside,
we separate into teams.

1046
01:16:58,407 --> 01:17:00,534
I am walking back and forth!

1047
01:17:00,601 --> 01:17:01,724
Okay.

1048
01:17:01,744 --> 01:17:04,025
You're gonna lead me and Ratcatcher 2
to Project Starfish.

1049
01:17:04,079 --> 01:17:05,974
I'm going with you
'cause I don't trust this guy.

1050
01:17:05,998 --> 01:17:07,350
No, no, no,
you're coming with me.

1051
01:17:07,374 --> 01:17:10,065
Our munitions expertise are needed
to place the explosives,

1052
01:17:10,085 --> 01:17:13,422
starting at the first floor,
going all the way to the top.

1053
01:17:13,500 --> 01:17:15,966
Once we're clear,
we blow the tits off that thing,

1054
01:17:16,133 --> 01:17:17,426
and go home.

1055
01:17:18,719 --> 01:17:21,805
- This is suicide.
- Well, that's kind of our thing.

1057
01:17:22,556 --> 01:17:23,822
Yeah.

1058
01:17:30,231 --> 01:17:32,149
This is insane.

1060
01:18:14,984 --> 01:18:16,360
Yeah, no.

1062
01:18:22,241 --> 01:18:23,993
I love the rain.

1063
01:18:24,159 --> 01:18:26,787
It's like angels are
splooging all over us.

1064
01:18:26,954 --> 01:18:30,082
- It's good for cover!
- Yep, that too.

1078
01:19:45,199 --> 01:19:47,443
You son of a bi...

1079
01:20:07,300 --> 01:20:10,057
Input the emergency code! Now!

1080
01:20:10,349 --> 01:20:11,651
Well, go on then!

1081
01:20:36,750 --> 01:20:38,050
Yo!

1082
01:20:38,919 --> 01:20:40,129
Okay, Pokey.

1083
01:20:40,504 --> 01:20:42,839
You get a bomb,
you get a bomb.

1085
01:20:42,923 --> 01:20:44,822
Harley and I will meet you
up on the second floor.

1086
01:20:44,842 --> 01:20:46,635
Yeah? All right.

1087
01:21:29,511 --> 01:21:31,305
Goddamnit, Nanaue.

1088
01:21:32,389 --> 01:21:33,679
No!

1089
01:21:34,141 --> 01:21:35,684
Quit bein' a play baby.

1090
01:21:36,143 --> 01:21:37,936
Peacemaker.

1091
01:21:38,979 --> 01:21:42,357
It's actually very nice.
Just put it against the wall.

1093
01:21:44,026 --> 01:21:46,987
- It looks nothin' like me.
- <i>Move. Move it.</i>

1095
01:21:49,990 --> 01:21:51,575
This way.

1096
01:22:11,762 --> 01:22:13,096
<i>Sí.</i>

1097
01:22:19,211 --> 01:22:20,400
¡Vámonos!

1097
01:22:20,600 --> 01:22:21,900
<i>¡Vámonos!</i>

1098
01:23:03,814 --> 01:23:06,775
- Good God.
- If God existed...

1100
01:23:07,359 --> 01:23:09,987
...wouldn't this be proof
that he wasn't good at all?

1101
01:23:10,779 --> 01:23:12,406
What the hell is this?

1102
01:23:12,573 --> 01:23:15,200
I thought you were looking
for Project Starfish.

1103
01:23:16,910 --> 01:23:19,162
You've brought us visitors,
have you, Grieves?

1104
01:23:19,329 --> 01:23:21,748
Have you come to save me
from that madman?

1105
01:23:21,915 --> 01:23:23,917
Thirty years
he's kept me here!

1106
01:23:24,084 --> 01:23:25,711
Tortured me!

1107
01:23:25,878 --> 01:23:28,751
Had his way with me!

1108
01:24:08,170 --> 01:24:10,344
I call it
Starro the Conqueror!

1109
01:24:11,089 --> 01:24:12,830
That's meant to be derisive.

1110
01:24:13,592 --> 01:24:15,070
Sorry, old chum!

1111
01:24:15,093 --> 01:24:17,930
These two are here to kill you.
It's out of my hands.

1112
01:24:18,180 --> 01:24:19,890
We need to
help these people!

1113
01:24:20,140 --> 01:24:23,518
Impossible, dear.
They're corpses below those stars.

1114
01:24:24,186 --> 01:24:25,486
Who are they?

1115
01:24:27,000 --> 01:24:29,566
The fodder of powerful men
through every age!

1116
01:24:29,733 --> 01:24:31,526
Dissidents,

1117
01:24:31,693 --> 01:24:33,070
journalists,

1118
01:24:33,820 --> 01:24:35,489
political rivals,

1119
01:24:35,656 --> 01:24:38,158
and their... loved ones.

1120
01:24:40,118 --> 01:24:41,745
Oh, please.

1121
01:24:41,912 --> 01:24:45,165
Unclutch your
fucking pearls, Flag!

1122
01:24:45,332 --> 01:24:48,180
We serve... the same master.

1123
01:24:48,200 --> 01:24:50,337
We were sent here
to stop you!

1124
01:24:50,400 --> 01:24:51,610
Child,

1125
01:24:51,630 --> 01:24:53,674
your government
didn't send you here...

1126
01:24:53,840 --> 01:24:56,635
...to protect the world
from alien technology.

1127
01:24:56,802 --> 01:25:00,611
Your government sent you here
to cover up their part in it.

1128
01:25:00,639 --> 01:25:03,016
You're a goddamn liar.

1129
01:25:03,308 --> 01:25:05,980
American goddamn
astronauts...

1129
01:25:06,000 --> 01:25:09,940
<i>...found Starro!
Yankee-fucking-doodle dandies!</i>

1131
01:25:10,023 --> 01:25:11,525
Although the Cold War
was ended,

1132
01:25:11,692 --> 01:25:14,800
your government saw the potential
in weaponizing...

1132
01:25:14,820 --> 01:25:18,030
...such a powerful beast.
But banish the thought...

1133
01:25:18,050 --> 01:25:21,284
...of any such experiments
being held on American soil.

1134
01:25:21,827 --> 01:25:24,701
Your people have always
been squeamish...

1134
01:25:24,721 --> 01:25:27,200
...about the
sacrifices necessary...

1135
01:25:27,621 --> 01:25:29,292
...for scientific advancement.

1136
01:25:29,459 --> 01:25:30,627
So,

1137
01:25:31,586 --> 01:25:35,070
the United States made a secret deal
with the Corto Maltese government...

1138
01:25:35,132 --> 01:25:37,592
...to conduct their
illegal experiments here...

1139
01:25:37,759 --> 01:25:38,981
<i>...in Jotunheim.</i>

1140
01:25:39,011 --> 01:25:41,179
<i>And they hired me
to oversee them.</i>

1141
01:25:41,346 --> 01:25:45,183
And now, because of
a run-of-the-mill fucking military coup,

1142
01:25:45,350 --> 01:25:47,791
they're gonna destroy
30 years' worth of efforts!

1143
01:25:47,811 --> 01:25:49,111
<i>Yeah!</i>

1144
01:25:49,271 --> 01:25:51,900
- You're the real victim here.
- The hell you doing here?

1145
01:25:51,920 --> 01:25:54,002
You're supposed to be upstairs
plantin' explosives.

1146
01:25:54,026 --> 01:25:55,819
I told ya I didn't trust him.

1147
01:25:56,486 --> 01:25:58,547
Your records are located
in those computers?

1148
01:26:01,491 --> 01:26:03,577
Colonel, what are you doing?

1149
01:26:04,411 --> 01:26:06,020
I joined the military...

1149
01:26:06,050 --> 01:26:08,331
...to serve my country,
not to be its puppet!

1150
01:26:09,750 --> 01:26:11,334
What are you doing?

1151
01:26:14,588 --> 01:26:15,964
Who are you going
to show that to?

1152
01:26:16,131 --> 01:26:19,217
The press. Goddamn people
deserve to know.

1153
01:26:19,384 --> 01:26:21,029
I'm tired of coverin' up
their dirty little secrets.

1154
01:26:21,053 --> 01:26:23,360
This time these sons of bitches
are gonna be held account...

1156
01:26:24,306 --> 01:26:25,642
I can't let you
do that, Colonel.

1157
01:26:25,682 --> 01:26:27,497
- Excuse me?
- I'm truly sorry.

1158
01:26:27,517 --> 01:26:29,300
Miss Waller charged me
with makin' sure those records...

1159
01:26:29,320 --> 01:26:32,147
- ...don't leave this building.
- Of course, I shoulda known.

1160
01:26:32,314 --> 01:26:34,649
Waller's always got a backup.

1161
01:26:34,816 --> 01:26:36,568
Come on, man,
this isn't personal.

1162
01:26:36,818 --> 01:26:39,211
Holdin' a gun on me
is pretty fucking personal!

1163
01:26:40,363 --> 01:26:41,662
What is that?

1164
01:26:42,365 --> 01:26:43,960
I'm gonna need
that drive, Colonel.

1165
01:26:45,577 --> 01:26:47,656
Those morons set off
the explosives too early!

1166
01:26:47,746 --> 01:26:50,350
Hand over the drive!
Let's go, come on!

1168
01:26:51,458 --> 01:26:53,193
They experimented
on children.

1169
01:26:53,293 --> 01:26:55,265
No one is sayin'
what they did was right.

1170
01:26:55,295 --> 01:26:57,375
They experimented
on children!

1171
01:26:57,422 --> 01:27:00,217
That information gets out,
it causes an international incident!

1172
01:27:00,383 --> 01:27:02,677
Keepin' the peace
is worth any price!

1173
01:27:02,844 --> 01:27:05,035
Including the life
of a hero like yours, sir,

1174
01:27:05,055 --> 01:27:06,411
so please,

1175
01:27:07,891 --> 01:27:09,226
don't make me do this.

1176
01:27:48,306 --> 01:27:49,850
What have you people done?

1177
01:28:06,158 --> 01:28:07,659
Sebastian, come!

1178
01:28:41,359 --> 01:28:43,380
Okay, we gotta calm down.

1178
01:28:43,400 --> 01:28:45,802
Let's all just...
Let's just talk about this.

1179
01:28:45,822 --> 01:28:47,470
I understand
where you're coming from!

1180
01:28:47,490 --> 01:28:50,430
I crossed a line!
Okay, I crossed a line!

1182
01:28:50,452 --> 01:28:52,537
I realize that,
but I'm ready to change!

1183
01:28:52,704 --> 01:28:54,539
I am ready to change!

1184
01:28:54,706 --> 01:28:56,970
And I didn't mean
to hurt you...

1185
01:30:46,776 --> 01:30:48,780
You motherfucker!

1186
01:31:28,318 --> 01:31:29,778
Peacemaker.

1187
01:31:31,112 --> 01:31:33,156
What a joke.

1188
01:32:06,106 --> 01:32:07,307
Cleo?

1189
01:32:08,733 --> 01:32:10,485
Give me back the drive.

1190
01:32:31,923 --> 01:32:34,426
I told you that information
can't get out! Fuck!

1191
01:32:34,592 --> 01:32:38,364
So, okay, okay, destroy
the hard drive! Why kill me?

1192
01:32:45,800 --> 01:32:47,605
Because I'm thorough.

1193
01:32:49,816 --> 01:32:52,861
- Oh, my...
- Sorry, kid.

1195
01:32:53,027 --> 01:32:54,505
No, no!

1196
01:33:04,289 --> 01:33:05,687
All right,
troops are coming!

1197
01:33:05,707 --> 01:33:07,877
This floor, and then
nine floors left! Let's go!

1198
01:33:07,917 --> 01:33:09,250
Come on!

1199
01:34:30,250 --> 01:34:32,341
New dumb friends!

1200
01:34:45,431 --> 01:34:47,475
Aw, fizzle sticks. Hold on.

1201
01:35:14,460 --> 01:35:16,651
Has anyone got
eyes or ears on any more?

1202
01:35:16,671 --> 01:35:18,006
They killed Milton!

1203
01:35:20,133 --> 01:35:21,884
Milton was still with us?

1204
01:35:22,051 --> 01:35:23,862
- Where'd you think he was?
- I don't know!

1205
01:35:23,886 --> 01:35:25,364
I thought he stayed
back with the bus!

1206
01:35:25,388 --> 01:35:27,849
- What was Milton gonna do?
- He was helping us!

1208
01:35:29,726 --> 01:35:31,082
- Who's Milton?
- What?

1209
01:35:31,102 --> 01:35:32,854
I don't remember any Milton.

1210
01:35:33,021 --> 01:35:36,316
Fuck! He has been with us
the whole time!

1211
01:35:36,482 --> 01:35:38,980
Somebody named Milton
has been with us...

1212
01:35:39,000 --> 01:35:40,695
- ...the whole time?
- Yes!

1213
01:35:40,750 --> 01:35:42,506
I don't think so.
I think I would've noticed...

1214
01:35:42,530 --> 01:35:44,949
...if a guy named Milton's
been with us. It's...

1215
01:35:45,116 --> 01:35:46,681
It's not a very common name.

1216
01:35:46,701 --> 01:35:49,245
I don't think
I've ever even met a Milton.

1217
01:35:49,662 --> 01:35:51,247
Are you messing
around right now?

1218
01:35:51,581 --> 01:35:52,874
He was a really nice guy,

1219
01:35:53,041 --> 01:35:55,418
and he sacrificed
himself to help us!

1220
01:35:55,877 --> 01:35:57,253
And now look at him!

1221
01:35:57,587 --> 01:35:59,172
He's dead.

1222
01:36:01,007 --> 01:36:04,850
Oh, that guy! Milton, Milton.

1223
01:36:09,098 --> 01:36:11,748
So, when did this great love affair
with Milton start?

1224
01:36:11,768 --> 01:36:14,896
I liked him from the beginning, okay?
I just didn't say anything unt...

1225
01:36:17,398 --> 01:36:19,067
No!

1226
01:38:13,681 --> 01:38:16,058
<i>Harley! Give us a hand!</i>

1227
01:38:25,026 --> 01:38:26,327
Hey!

1228
01:38:37,622 --> 01:38:39,050
<i>Vamos. Vamos.</i>

1229
01:39:22,834 --> 01:39:23,835


1230
01:40:13,342 --> 01:40:15,678
Ah, fuck, fuck!

1231
01:40:18,306 --> 01:40:20,641
Oh, fuck off!

1232
01:40:21,392 --> 01:40:22,435


1233
01:40:42,121 --> 01:40:45,180
- Sorry, kid.
- No, no, no!

1235
01:41:40,221 --> 01:41:43,161
- How?
- Smaller bullets.

1237
01:41:48,500 --> 01:41:50,940
He killed Colonel Flag!

1238
01:41:52,233 --> 01:41:56,070
He wanted to share this with the press!
It's proof the American government...

1240
01:41:56,153 --> 01:41:58,964
...was behind Project Starfish
the whole time!

1241
01:42:33,858 --> 01:42:35,000
Whoa! Whoa!

1242
01:42:50,207 --> 01:42:51,939
I think it's trying
to get out!

1243
01:42:51,959 --> 01:42:53,780
- What?
- Starro the...

1244
01:43:16,859 --> 01:43:18,160
Whoa!

1245
01:44:26,971 --> 01:44:29,140
Cover your faces!

1246
01:45:17,104 --> 01:45:19,800
<i>Si. Si.</i>

1248
01:45:52,598 --> 01:45:54,767
- Whoa!
- What the fuck is that?

1249
01:45:54,850 --> 01:45:56,393
Uh... Hey, guys?

1250
01:45:59,070 --> 01:46:00,731
Oh, shit, there's...
there's... there's...

1251
01:46:19,400 --> 01:46:22,000
This city is mine.

1252
01:46:51,940 --> 01:46:55,041
Uh, Miss Waller,
I think the feed is back up.

1253
01:46:57,413 --> 01:46:59,361
Oh, my God, Miss Waller!

1254
01:46:59,624 --> 01:47:02,209
We've got a freaking <i>kaiju</i>
up in this shit!

1255
01:47:11,427 --> 01:47:14,050
<i>Task Force X, come in.
Are you there?</i>

1257
01:47:17,016 --> 01:47:19,915
- Uh-huh.
- <i>Whatever signal jammers...</i>

1259
01:47:19,935 --> 01:47:22,180
...were blocking our communications
must have been in the building...

1260
01:47:22,200 --> 01:47:23,580
- ...you just demolished.
- <i>Yeah, well...</i>

1261
01:47:23,600 --> 01:47:26,191
...we've got a mite issue
over here, Waller.

1262
01:47:26,358 --> 01:47:28,485
It's Project Starfish,
Miss Waller.

1263
01:47:28,652 --> 01:47:31,030
It's headed towards the city,
and I think it wants to feed...

1264
01:47:31,050 --> 01:47:32,948
...on as many people
as it can.

1265
01:47:37,244 --> 01:47:38,475
<i>Not our problem.</i>

1266
01:47:38,495 --> 01:47:40,831
<i>If you've destroyed Jotunheim
and the records within,</i>

1267
01:47:40,914 --> 01:47:42,416
<i>you've achieved
the objective.</i>

1268
01:47:42,583 --> 01:47:45,085
<i>Corto Maltese
is no longer a U.S. ally.</i>

1269
01:47:45,252 --> 01:47:46,980
If anything, the White House
will consider...

1270
01:47:47,000 --> 01:47:50,205
...fomenting disruption in
a hostile nation a positive development.

1272
01:48:23,791 --> 01:48:25,209
You heard what she said.

1273
01:48:46,438 --> 01:48:47,739
Fuck.

1274
01:48:53,112 --> 01:48:56,115
- Bloodsport is off mission!
- What the...

1276
01:48:57,199 --> 01:49:00,262
- She'll kill you, you know.
- That's her business.

1278
01:49:01,036 --> 01:49:03,872
I knew Sebastian sensed
good in you for a reason!

1279
01:49:04,039 --> 01:49:06,333
Just keep that fucking rat
away from me!

1280
01:49:06,667 --> 01:49:08,722
Ratcatcher
is also off mission!

1281
01:49:08,752 --> 01:49:10,140
Bloodsport, Ratcatcher...

1282
01:49:10,170 --> 01:49:12,673
- <i>...turn around!</i>
- Where go, friends?

1283
01:49:13,382 --> 01:49:14,682
<i>Nanaue!</i>

1284
01:49:16,135 --> 01:49:18,637
I know what I'm carrying
the javelin for.

1285
01:49:28,897 --> 01:49:30,315
Krill, turn around now!

1286
01:49:30,482 --> 01:49:32,693
<i>Turn back now, goddamnit!</i>

1287
01:49:35,404 --> 01:49:36,760
- Open it.
- Miss Waller...

1288
01:49:36,780 --> 01:49:38,080
OPEN IT!

1289
01:49:39,300 --> 01:49:41,201
What are you doing,
Task Force X?

1290
01:49:46,457 --> 01:49:48,041
Fuck!

1291
01:49:50,441 --> 01:49:52,000
Turn around now, goddamnit!

1292
01:49:52,045 --> 01:49:54,756
<i>You dumb pieces of shit!</i>

1293
01:49:54,923 --> 01:49:56,340
<i>Motherfuckers!</i>

1294
01:49:57,644 --> 01:50:00,367
<i>Goddamnit, Task Force X,
this is your last...</i>

1295
01:50:00,387 --> 01:50:02,389
...motherfucking warning!

1296
01:50:06,602 --> 01:50:09,960
Oh, my God!
What the fuck did you do?

1297
01:50:11,523 --> 01:50:13,148
All those people, John.

1298
01:50:14,026 --> 01:50:15,351
Little kids.

1299
01:50:19,907 --> 01:50:21,300
Task Force X!

1299
01:50:21,320 --> 01:50:24,266
The creature is headed
to Calle Principal!

1300
01:50:24,286 --> 01:50:25,601
Avoid Avenida Medrano!

1301
01:50:25,621 --> 01:50:27,581
- There is a swarm of infected!
- Jesus.

1302
01:50:27,748 --> 01:50:31,335
So, your clearest path is...
Calle Aguero!

1303
01:50:31,502 --> 01:50:34,296
Get on the satellite, Dale,
you fucking dickhead!

1304
01:50:34,463 --> 01:50:35,881
Yes, ma'am.

1305
01:51:58,130 --> 01:51:59,423


1306
01:52:04,678 --> 01:52:06,655
Harley! Take the high ground!

1307
01:52:12,894 --> 01:52:16,250
Nanaue! Monster is nom nom!

1308
01:52:16,773 --> 01:52:19,234
Monster nom nom?

1309
01:52:19,600 --> 01:52:20,850
Yes!

1310
01:52:29,494 --> 01:52:32,211
Abner! Do you see
who that is?

1311
01:52:32,950 --> 01:52:35,208
- Huh?
- It's your mom!

1313
01:53:08,121 --> 01:53:10,500
I'm a superhero!

1314
01:53:11,495 --> 01:53:13,684
I'm a motherfucking super...

1315
01:54:03,338 --> 01:54:04,840
God!

1316
01:54:10,595 --> 01:54:14,641
<i>No! No!</i>

1317
01:54:32,075 --> 01:54:33,468
Oh, no...

1318
01:54:41,376 --> 01:54:43,628
THIS CITY...

1319
01:54:43,795 --> 01:54:47,382
...IS MINE!

1320
01:54:48,091 --> 01:54:50,261
This city isn't yours.

1321
01:54:51,261 --> 01:54:53,764
This city isn't ours.

1322
01:54:54,347 --> 01:54:56,475
This city is theirs!

1323
01:55:00,479 --> 01:55:02,022
Oh, hell.

1324
01:56:21,601 --> 01:56:23,264
Why rats, Papa?

1325
01:56:24,354 --> 01:56:28,483
Rats are the lowliest and most despised
of all creatures, my love.

1326
01:56:29,568 --> 01:56:31,194
If they have purpose,

1327
01:56:32,821 --> 01:56:34,531
so do we all.

1328
01:58:20,637 --> 01:58:22,806
I was happy,

1329
01:58:22,973 --> 01:58:24,700
floating,

1329
01:58:24,900 --> 01:58:27,477
staring at the stars.

1330
01:59:00,940 --> 01:59:03,618
<i>A group of escaped convicts
saved a city of millions...</i>

1332
01:59:03,638 --> 01:59:07,459
<i>...on the small island nation
of Corto Maltese today.</i>

1333
01:59:07,726 --> 01:59:09,026
That's my dad.

1334
01:59:10,520 --> 01:59:11,914
<i>Because of these people,</i>

1335
01:59:11,938 --> 01:59:15,066
<i>Corto Maltese will have
free democratic elections...</i>

1336
01:59:15,150 --> 01:59:17,944
<i>...for the first time
in 90 years.</i>

1337
01:59:18,153 --> 01:59:20,947
<i>¡Corto Maltese! ¡Viva!</i>

1338
01:59:21,114 --> 01:59:23,324
<i>¡Corto Maltese! ¡Viva!</i>

1339
01:59:23,491 --> 01:59:25,577
<i>¡Corto Maltese! ¡Viva!</i>

1340
01:59:25,744 --> 01:59:28,246
- That's my dad.
- <i>¡Corto Maltese! ¡Viva!</i>

1341
01:59:36,588 --> 01:59:37,888
Yeah.

1342
01:59:40,508 --> 01:59:41,808
Yeah.

1343
01:59:42,719 --> 01:59:44,993
<i>Oh, that's just a taste
of what's on that drive.</i>

1344
01:59:45,013 --> 01:59:47,307
<i>I've uploaded it all
to a secure server.</i>

1345
01:59:48,266 --> 01:59:50,290
<i>Now, if you kill
any one of us,</i>

1346
01:59:50,310 --> 01:59:52,312
or my daughter ever sees
the inside of a prison,

1347
01:59:52,479 --> 01:59:55,356
it goes public.
If we all go free,

1349
01:59:55,523 --> 01:59:57,442
it never has to see
the light of day.

1350
01:59:59,069 --> 02:00:01,613
I told you I'd make you
a leader, DuBois.

1351
02:00:02,906 --> 02:00:04,282
<i>You got a deal.</i>

1352
02:00:24,385 --> 02:00:25,685
Nanaue!

1353
02:00:41,486 --> 02:00:43,968
Look, I know Flag wanted
to give the drive to the press,

1354
02:00:43,988 --> 02:00:47,575
but we just saved a whole bloody city!
We can't have it all!

1355
02:00:50,495 --> 02:00:53,248
- Flag was my friend.
- Mine too.

1357
02:00:54,999 --> 02:00:56,918
And I haven't got
many of those.

1358
02:00:59,212 --> 02:01:01,422
I could be
your friend, Milton.

1359
02:01:01,923 --> 02:01:04,000
- Not my name.
- What?

1361
02:01:04,843 --> 02:01:07,500
What are you talkin' about?
We just had a conversation for, like,

1362
02:01:07,600 --> 02:01:09,305
three hours about
how your name is Milton!

1363
02:01:09,472 --> 02:01:10,723
Didn't.

1364
02:01:10,807 --> 02:01:13,300
- Yes, we did.
- No.

1365
02:01:13,400 --> 02:01:14,700
Our ride's here!

1367
02:01:18,189 --> 02:01:20,607
- Nom nom?
- Really?

1369
02:01:20,628 --> 02:01:22,652
That is what you're
thinkin' about right now?

1370
02:01:22,819 --> 02:01:25,260
No. That nom nom though.

1371
02:01:25,280 --> 02:01:26,843
No, it's not nom nom.

1372
02:01:28,867 --> 02:01:30,201
No!

1426
02:10:53,973 --> 02:10:55,766
Said they found him
in the rubble.

1427
02:10:55,933 --> 02:10:57,733
They were shocked
his heart was still beating.

1428
02:10:57,852 --> 02:11:00,396
I wasn't certain how safe it was,
shipping him back here.

1429
02:11:00,500 --> 02:11:03,461
But, if anything,
he's shown he's resilient.

1430
02:11:03,774 --> 02:11:07,350
It'll take some surgery, but eventually
we'll get him back up to speed.

1431
02:11:09,280 --> 02:11:11,173
You realize
this is revenge, right?

1432
02:11:11,240 --> 02:11:12,805
Waller knows
we double-crossed her,

1433
02:11:12,825 --> 02:11:16,120
and she's getting back at us
by saddling us with this douchebag.

1434
02:11:16,287 --> 02:11:17,587
Yup.

1435
02:11:17,663 --> 02:11:20,104
I heard he was sort of a hero
down in Corto Maltese.

1436
02:11:20,124 --> 02:11:22,293
Oh, is that what you heard?
Because not quite.

1437
02:11:24,336 --> 02:11:26,046
What do you guys
want him for?

1438
02:11:27,089 --> 02:11:30,200
Just to save the
fucking world, that's all.

