This is not how I wanted
this evening to go.
I know how you wanted
Believe me, this is better.
Who are you working for?
Lermentov, yes?
Does he think...
...we have to go through him
to move our cargo?
I thought General Solohob
is in charge of the export business.
Solohob...
...a bagman, a front.
Your outdated information betrays you.
The famous Black Widow...
...and she turns out to be
simply another pretty face.
You really think I'm pretty?
Tell Lermentov we don't need him...
...to move the tanks.
Tell him he is out.
Well...
It's for her.
You listen carefully.
Who are you?
Get out!
There is sickness here!
My father's not waking up!
He has a fever and he's moaning
but his eyes won't open.
Slow down.
My father...
Like them?