[light music]
Who's hungry?
Hi.
I didn't think you'd
be out of bed already.
Yeah, there was a car fire on Route 220.
And I thought I'd bring
home some breakfast,
but this looks a lot better.
Is that blueberry compote?
Freshly mashed,
and paired with a savory
bacon and baked egg danish.
The Speed Force.
Are you okay, Barry?
You're not still feeling
the effects of Psych's attack, are you?
Nah, I'm good. I just...
I had no idea that you could cook.
Bobby Flay has got nothing on Nora.
You know, it's funny,
cooking is the process
of combining ingredients
with heat to create molecular change,
but this feels like so much more.
- Huh.
- Mimosa?
Sure.
♪
[suspenseful music]
[light music]
Actually, I think I'm good.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So Chester has all the satellites
scanning for the new forces.
There's the Sage Force, Strength Force,
and now the Still Force.
Yeah, uh, so far,
no hits on any of their
isotropic signatures.
Well, it's still good
that you're here with us.
The last time the Forces attacked you,
you almost died.
I don't want to burden anyone.
No, you're not. You
know, in a weird way,
it's like you've been a part
of this family all along.
[playful music]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just, um,
a little worried about the fact that
my powers are glitching again,
especially since I just got them back.
Okay, well, we can call Caitlin
and have her run some more tests.
How do you feel now?
I feel fine, I just...
I don't know what happened.
Actually, I think I'm the reason.
Since I'm here now,
I'm increasing your
abilities as best I can.
It may take some getting used to,
but you'll need it if the
other Forces come back.
[phone buzzes]
Uh, that's work.
- I gotta go.
- I should come with you.
- Oh?
- I'm like your battery now.
- If Fuerza and Psych are back...
- Yeah, no, I don't...
Having you at a crime scene
might not be a great idea.
You've already been hurt once.
I can help boost your speed.
I know, I know, it just...
It might just be, like,
a traffic accident or something,
so, um, just let me find out.
Of course, but don't worry.
If you need me, I'll sense it,
and I'll be there in a heartbeat.
Great.
Okay.
Um, so I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
[sighs] I hope he's okay.
[clears throat]
[somber music]
One count of aggravated assault...
One count of attempted murder...
Two counts of kidnapping.
It's a good thing you never
lived up to your original name.
I thought once you
started helping people,
CCPD dropped the investigation.
Yeah, they did, they did, but...
the State never officially
dropped its charges,
which means Kristin
Kramer has everything
that she needs to put
you in Iron Heights.
I'm gonna find Kramer,
and I'm gonna kick her ass.
No, no, you're not.
Kramer is former Army Intelligence.
Wherever she goes, heads roll. Just...
Look, I'm not some thug anymore, okay?
- I've grown.
- I know that, honey, I do.
Look, I'm one of the
people that you kidnapped.
My advice to you, as your attorney,
is to lay low.
Wait, so...
Frost can't do superhero stuff anymore?
Nope, not out in the field.
Look, Frost, you're an artist, okay?
Just take some time off,
chase those canvasses, create...
just do it all here at S.T.A.R.
Labs, where you're safe.
I just got a life,
and now you're telling
me I can't live it.
For a little while, yeah.
Look, Kramer is appointed
by the governor, right?
She doesn't get results,
she's gonna get reassigned.
Frost, I know this isn't fair,
but it's our best option right now.
- Fine, I'll quarantine here.
- [phone buzzing]
Blazing Bessie Blount,
I just got my first
solo crime scene call.
[excited laughter]
Oh, since Cisco and
Kamilla are away and all,
I'm the only CCPD
tech consultant around.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe it's a 1090.
Maybe it's a 1011.
Oh, snap, it's a 1035.
Frost, I am so sorry but...
It's fine.
Go have your fun, Peralta.
[tense music]
Thank you, thank you,
sorry, thank you.
Holy Baby Grogu,
what happened here?
This delivery van was full of tech,
and was hit by a perp in an ice attack.
Apparently some experimental
microchip was stolen.
Huh, that doesn't sound so bad.
What's all that?
The driver.
[gagging]
Officers. [sighs]
Looks like Killer Frost has been busy.
[suspenseful music]
I know how this looks.
But there are other criminals
that use ice to commit crimes,
like Leonard Snart.
Snart was a man with a gun.
Mr. Runk, you're our
new technical consultant
on meta-human affairs,
What's your take on all this?
Well, um, ma'am, uh...
♪
Dark matter levels... uh,
Dark matter levels here are...
Oh...
Well, they're... they're off the charts.
That doesn't mean it's Frost.
Look, you see the pattern
in these ice crystals here?
They're dendrictic, like tree branches.
Frost's ice crystals
are usually hexagonal.
It's Killer Frost, Officer Allen.
And you seem to know
a lot about her powers.
Yeah, I've worked her crime scenes,
and she's never killed anyone.
Until now, apparently.
Officer Allen is
our department's top
forensics examiner, ma'am.
If there's any evidence here
that we can use, he will find it.
And Killer Frost is still out there.
Captain, I hate to pull rank,
but Governor Williamson
gave me special authority
in order to address this city's
long-standing metahuman problems.
We need to keep public safety in mind.
- Agreed.
- Good.
Because I'm going to ask the DA's office
to issue a warrant for
Killer Frost's arrest.
I'm gonna need you and
your officers for backup.
I'll alert the Meta-human Task Force.
Thank you.
I need to update the Governor's office.
Excuse me.
Joe, you can't be serious.
We all know Frost didn't do this.
What am I supposed to say, Barry?
"Yes, Frost did spend
the evening with Caitlin."
You can't give Kramer her
alibi without admitting
that you've talked to a fugitive.
Dang, that's a real catch-22.
[mimics echo]
[tense music]
I'm sorry, my timing
on that was terrible.
I'm just gonna go tell
Frost what's going on.
We can't let Kramer arrest Frost.
You don't think I know that?
But we gotta follow orders.
So what are we supposed to do?
Frost can't lay low forever.
The only thing we can do, Barry:
find the real meta-human that did this.
All right.
♪
[sighs]
[whimsical music]
♪
Huh. That looks painful.
Chuck, said you had something
important to tell Frost?
Right, okay... Well...
there's a new ice meta in town
who killed an Ivo Labs employee,
but Kristin Kramer
thinks that it was you,
so she kind of ordered Joe
to put the Meta Task Force on alert
while she gets a
warrant for your arrest.
What?
Why didn't Joe and Barry stop her?
Because, technically, she's their boss.
She's also a very intimidating person.
But don't worry.
We're doing everything we
can to get this cleared up.
Me and Caitlin are even trying to fix
one of H.R.'s transmogrifiers
- to work for you.
- Thanks, Runk.
Look,
is there anything else I can do?
I mean, you know, if you need to talk
or vent or get the
weight off your shoulders,
Chester P. is all ears, I...
Go tech-out, Chuck. We'll be fine.
She's starting cardio anyway.
Right, right, okay.
[tense music]
Okay, he's gone. What's the plan?
I'm gonna do twelve miles.
Five years in Iron Heights over here.
You think I can't tell
when someone's lying?
Plus there's no way you'd stay put here.
You're going after Kramer.
♪
No, not that.
You're going after this
new ice-meta yourself?
Yeah, I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
Wha... so you're gonna do this alone?
What about the rest of Team Flash?
I need to handle this myself.
There are places that
Team Flash can't go.
Hell, I used to work at some of them.
And you aren't gonna say a thing.
I used to be a freakin'
car thief, Frost,
I know how to talk to criminals.
I am not looking for a criminal.
I'm looking for a killer.
You want to help me? Cover my ass.
If I need backup, I'll call.
Promise.
♪
You must see a lot of
strange crime scenes
working in this city.
Yeah, yeah... this case is another one.
Usually, I'd find dark matter
dispersed evenly throughout
meta-produced ice.
But from what I can tell,
this ice has dark matter.
It's just...
only on the surface.
What would cause that?
I don't know,
but I'm gonna find out.
I'll let you work.
Thanks.
[sighs]
[static]
Have you been there the whole time?
She admires you.
[stammering] Kramer?
Okay, well, look... She
could be back any second,
not to mention a dozen
other officers, so...
But I thought you were gonna
spend the day with Iris?
Well, I told her I
needed to stretch my legs.
Okay.
You know, it's just like you said,
the ice is different.
The particles inside all this,
I can feel them, they're...
compacted, constrained.
Like on a molecular level.
[suspenseful music]
♪
You know what, I... um,
I need to get this back
to my lab, if I could...
No, hey, hey, hey. If
I can figure out why
this ice is different, it
might lead to the real...
♪
Right, I'm on my way.
Allen?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Um, I'm... I'm, uh, tracking footprints
from our suspect. They
led me out here, so.
- Where?
- What?
Oh, the... uh, yeah, no,
they're hard to detect
without one of these little infrared...
♪
Cutting edge tech.
Yeah.
Impressive.
Keep up the good work.
♪
[static]
I like her.
Yeah, um...
Look, I really appreciate your
help, but I got it from here,
so I'll see you back at the loft, okay?
Of course.
I understand.
[sighs]
[tense music]
[rock music]
♪
The place was a lot more
lively when I worked here.
[scoffs] Here for the ambience?
Looking for a meta who likes ice.
- Ah, a missing relative.
- Ha-ha, funny guy.
Look, I used to do your job.
I know a good bar slinger
keeps his ears open
more than any of these losers.
I might know a few things.
'Cause you're a bartender,
- who tends bar.
- [chuckles]
I'm... looking for intel.
Something was taken from
Ivo Labs this morning.
Do you know anything about that?
No, but I do know a bit about...
science.
If you take a hydrometer
to a bottle of Plymouth gin,
you'll find that it has
a specific gravity...
0.94...
Which means, a liqueur
like, say, crème de noyaux here,
will sink right...
to the bottom.
Ergo, the secret to the
smoothest cocktail...
is density.
[soft music]
♪
That is...
not bad.
The famous Killer Frost likes my work.
I'll call "The Citizen."
It's just Frost now.
Oh.
♪
Turn that up.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
So in light of the violence
at Ivo Labs this morning,
the Central City Police
Department is offering
a $100,000 reward for information
leading to the arrest
of the meta criminal
known as Killer Frost.
If you have any knowledge
on the whereabouts of
Killer Frost, immediately call
the Meta-Human Task Force tip line.
Crap.
[grunts]
[rock music]
♪
- I had him.
- Great.
I guess I wasted an IPA then.
[quirky music]
♪ Hot in ♪
♪ So hot in herre ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
[funky music]
♪ It's getting hot in here ♪
Take a picture, why don't you?
[scoffs] Whatever.
See you around... sometime.
♪ It's getting hot in here ♪
Hey, Frost.
There's a new meta in town.
He's got a thing for experimental tech.
Keeps it all at the old
Wieringo complex off Route 119.
If he's the guy,
you're gonna find him there.
What's that gonna cost me?
How about a second visit?
Just ask for Mark.
♪
♪ Let it just fall out ♪
♪ I like it when you uh-uh ♪
♪
Dude, the 24-hour news cycle picked up
on Kramer's "John Wick" parabellum move.
[laughs] That's a great movie.
"Yeah, I'm thinking I'm back."
I'm thinking we need to focus.
Frost is safe at
S.T.A.R. Labs right now,
but Kramer's not gonna back down,
not until we find proof.
Here, check this out.
Look at these cryo-membranes.
Speed Force was right.
It's way past compacted.
Now if we could just figure out why.
Barry, these computers are
way slower than you are.
I mean, this much data?
It's gonna take all night.
[gasps] Cool, but scary.
I can feel how frustrated you are.
How can I help?
Look, it's okay, we've got this.
Totally, I mean, we are,
like the Power Rangers
of forensic science, basically,
But the Speed... Nora here...
Is omnipotent,
omnipresent, and omniscient.
She's like our Zordon.
Say, can white hole singularities
actually exist... without mass?
Yes.
I knew it, I knew.
Barry, we don't have to
crunch data all night.
Nora can do it right now.
It's our job to find answers.
Of course, but, uh,
y'know, Nora is a
literal force of nature.
He's right, just let me...
No. [clears throat]
No, we need to do this ourselves.
Maybe just this once?
[dramatic music]
♪
[panting]
Anybody else taste pennies?
It tastes like there's
78 cents in my mouth.
Barry, what did you do?
We've lost everything.
What did I do?
I didn't lose the data that
was supposed to clear Frost.
You did... by being here.
- I was only trying to help.
- Okay, I didn't ask for any.
Guys, maybe we should take five?
Barry, you helped me be reborn,
and now you're keeping me safe.
Of course I want to help you.
I keep telling you.
I didn't ask for help.
Look, you chose me to be the hero.
So, let me be the hero.
♪
Sorry about that.
You know what I meant, right?
[radio static]
[tense music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Korber, hey, what's going on?
Kramer's got a location on Killer Frost.
- They're gonna bring her in.
- [line trilling]
I'm calling Frost.
She's not picking up.
♪
Hey, Allegra.
Yeah, is Frost with you?
This is an emergency.
Sorry, Chuck, she's here,
but she's going full
Amazon with her workout.
What's the message?
Okay, tell her Kramer's making moves,
so Frost needs to stay put.
Got it.
♪
C'mon, pick up, pick up, pick up.
[eerie tones]
♪
[electronic trilling]
- Seriously?
- [knock at door]
CCPD, you're surrounded.
Caitlin Snow, I have a
warrant for your arrest.
What's the charge?
Kramer to Task Force command,
hold your positions
around the perimeter,
and prepare for prisoner transfer.
Are you alone, Dr. Snow?
Yes, but I...
I think there's been a mistake.
Joe? What is this?
- Who are you?
- I'm Rene Carpenter.
I'm a clinician with the M.H.E. team.
Mental health evaluation?
Yes, ma'am, it's standard procedure.
I'm just here to help.
Joe, what is going on?
Would you turn around please?
[dramatic music]
♪
Killer Frost,
you're under arrest
for aggravated assault,
attempted murder, and
two counts of kidnapping.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney...
[knock at door]
Okay, so I just talked
to the D.A.'s office.
Kramer didn't find
anything incriminating
in your apartment, so
once your blood tests
come back negative for the meta-gene,
they're gonna be forced to
release you from custody.
Great, this is the first time
I'm relieved that Frost and I
- are in different bodies.
- Yeah.
How did she know to come after me?
Uh... [laughs]
it was an anonymous tip,
which means either somebody
got very lucky, or...
Or... somebody out there
knows that Frost used to be you.
I'm sorry, Caitlin, but
Kramer wouldn't tell me
where the Task Force was headed,
and by the time I knew, it was too late.
It's okay, Joe. This is not on you.
This ain't how law
enforcement's supposed to work.
I'm gonna go talk to Kramer.
Look, I think the next step is...
- [phone buzzes]
- Oh, uh...
- Frost, where are you?
- Across the street.
You and Caity get away
from the north wall.
[stammering]
North wall?
Uh-uh, okay, uh...
I think that Frost is about
to try and bust you out.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Put her on speakerphone.
- Okay.
Frost, what the hell are you doing?
Getting you out of there.
You promised me you would stay put.
Yeah, well, I lied. Now take cover.
- Oh!
- Don't you dare.
You're in there because of me.
I'm here because Kramer
has some sort of grudge
against you, okay?
But you're innocent and so am I,
so we just need to let
this play out, okay?
I'll be fine, I promise.
Yes, yes.
Frost, she's right.
Look, I know this system.
Just let me handle this.
They have no case against Caitlin.
Honey, please. Stand down.
This isn't fair. You shouldn't
have to go through this.
Neither should you, okay.
When Kramer looks at you, all she sees
are the mistakes you've made.
She doesn't see how much
pain you've gone through,
or how much you've grown because of it.
You're a good person, Frost,
and, human or meta-human,
you deserve the chance to prove it.
Human.
That's it. Thanks, Caity.
Thanks for what?
I figured out who framed us.
Now I'm gonna go figure out why.
No, Frost!
Hey...
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪
Sergeant Kramer,
we need to talk.
I'm in a bit of a hurry, Captain.
- Is there a problem?
- Yes, there is.
You mobilized my task
force to harass someone...
Who, from all accounts, is
innocent... off of a phone call.
There's no way in hell I
would have authorized that.
- Captain.
- Sergeant.
We're not supposed to work that way.
That's your point of view,
and I respect that.
But I also respect the evidence.
Dr. Snow matches Killer Frost
in 80 nodal points
of facial recognition.
Their known whereabouts
over the last few months
line up perfectly.
And her prints were all
over that delivery van.
What's your conclusion?
I promise you,
Caitlin Snow and Killer
Frost are not the same person.
And even if they were,
I doubt that they wouldn't wear gloves
as they went on a killing spree.
This evidence, this
anonymous phone call?
It's like someone is
trying to frame Frost.
Okay, then who?
I don't know,
but Frost helps keep this city safe.
Hell, she's saved my
life... More than once.
She's still a criminal.
Captain, you seem like a good cop,
and I know that Dr. Snow
is a friend of your family.
But if you really want
to honor your badge,
you need to think about what is
truly best for the public good.
If you'll excuse me.
[tense music]
[somber music]
♪
Nora's still holed up in the guest room.
I know she's a force of nature,
but as crazy as it sounds,
there's a person forming
inside of her, too.
Iris,
whatever she is, she's not human.
She's the Speed Force.
She powers my abilities.
You don't know what it's like, seeing...
someone like that,
eating breakfast at our table.
That's why you don't
want to call her Nora.
Maybe I shouldn't have
invited her to stay here.
No, it was...
It was the right thing to do.
She needs us to keep her safe,
and protecting her now
is the least I can do.
[laughs] What's wrong with me?
Nothing.
♪
Nothing, Barry, it's just...
I think for you, she's this
all powerful cosmic entity,
but she's changed.
I don't know how or why, but...
whatever she was before,
she's even more now.
Do you remember when I... [sighs]
First came back from
college after freshman year?
Yeah, I was living in my own apartment,
and you moved back in with Joe.
Yeah, it was great, for a while.
I was waitressing and, um, making tips,
trying to write my dissertation,
but, after about a week,
me and Dad started butting heads
over the stupidest things.
Me coming in late at night,
him watching sports all day Saturday
when I was trying to study...
I mean, all we did was argue.
I remember, Joe told me how
bad he felt through all that.
Yeah. And do you want to know why?
Because when I left that fall,
I really was his baby girl.
But, when I got back,
we were both adults.
Different habits, different schedules.
We weren't just...
father and daughter anymore.
[sentimental music]
Finding a new normal,
between the two of you,
is gonna take some time,
and it may get pretty
painful along the way.
That's how relationships grow.
[phone buzzes]
It's Chester.
He's got a lead on the new ice meta.
[suspenseful music]
- I gotta...
- Yeah.
♪
- What'd you find?
- Okay, so I somehow managed
to salvage some of the
ice data that we lost.
Remember how the dark
matter at the crime scene
- had compacted membranes?
- Yeah?
It's because it wasn't
dark matter at all.
It was a half-life variant.
Artificial dark matter?
That means the killer that
we're after isn't a meta.
They're human. Somebody's been fooling us
this whole time.
Somebody who's an
expert at science and...
knows that Frost and Caitlin
used to be one person.
We should ask Frost if...
Wait, where is Frost, anyway?
Fine, I lied, okay?
She went looking for
our baddie by herself.
Frost went full "Fugitive."
If this new killer is
trying to frame Frost,
- they might come after her next.
- I know, it's my fault.
She made me promise not to tell anyone,
but I-I should have said something.
Nah, it's okay, let's just...
Let's focus on finding her
before it's too late.
[dramatic music]
♪
That was fast.
So, Mark...
give me one good reason why
I shouldn't live up to my name.
[sighs]
Well, because Caitlin wouldn't like it.
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
♪
Thirsty?
[scoffs]
♪
All right, I know that you're angry,
'cause I know all about you
and you know nothing about me.
So go ahead.
[satisfied sigh]
- Ask away.
- How did you know?
Oh, that you and Caitlin were related?
I'm an observant guy, sue me.
In studying you, I also
traced your movements.
- Every fight, every battle.
- Stalk much?
Honestly, finding out that
you and Caitlin seem to
come and go interchangeably was...
Well, let's call it
more of a happy accident.
Did come in handy, though.
So you could frame us?
That's why you sent me
to that empty warehouse,
which wasn't really empty, was it?
Very good.
See, I already had the chip.
I just needed one final thing:
A neurogenic scan of you
to perfectly replicate your powers.
Neurogenic?
That's quite a fancy word for a thief.
Uh, yeah, maybe because I'm not a thief.
I simply took back what was mine.
The microchip? You built it.
So you worked at Ivo Labs.
I'm a cryo-geneticist. The best.
Oh, let me guess, your
former employers didn't agree?
Well, they said that the...
experiments I was conducting were...
[chuckles] Inhuman.
So they got a warrant to put
me in a cozy Iron Heights cell
for the rest of my life.
Unlike you, I've been smart
enough to avoid capture.
I'd rather die than end
up in some warm prison.
Have you ever even heard of hypothermia?
[laughs] It doesn't matter.
When I was nine,
I went ice skating up on Central Lake.
It was Christmas, so the ice...
should have been thick
enough, but I fell through.
♪
I was submerged, body and
soul, for over 15 minutes.
And at first, the cold was terrifying,
but then after 20 seconds or so,
you know, it got warm...
hot, even.
- And then I died.
- And the paramedics saved you,
and now you're obsessed
with refrigerators, I get it.
No, you don't.
The ice,
it holds the power of life and death.
A power all too clearly
wasted on you, Killer Frost.
Oh, I've watched you for years,
admiring your abilities,
wondering what I could do with them.
All I needed was for
Ivo to move my microchip
out of deep freeze, so that
I could steal it back again...
And then combine it with
that pesky scan of you.
And now...
I'm as powerful as you are.
Bring it on, Mark,
if that even is your real name.
Oh, Mark Blaine.
Yeah, that was my name.
But you can call me...
Chillblaine.
[rock music]
♪
I kind of like this.
[grunts and pants]
♪
[panting]
You fight like a boy.
[grunts]
What the hell did you do?
Looks like somebody's snow blind.
[suspenseful music]
Guys, satellites just picked up
one hell of a cryokinetic spike
on the southside of Keystone.
Frost said she might be going
somewhere she used to work.
O'Shaughnessy's. Let's go.
Wh... you still want me to come?
After I lied to you?
Someone's gotta convince
Frost to come home.
♪
[dramatic music]
To think,
you have so much strength,
so much power,
but so little imagination.
I guess that just means
I'm a better meta than you.
Actually, Chillblaine...
[winces]
♪
You're not a meta at all.
[groans]
There's one thing your
bracelets can't copy.
- [screams and winces]
- Ice healing.
[groans]
Frost, you okay?
Yeah, I'm... okay, it's just a scratch.
I could use a little
help with this though.
Yeah.
[triumphant music]
♪
Thanks. They broke you down?
I tried, honest.
It's okay, 'cause the only other person
I trusted today just
tried to kill me, so...
arriving with backup...
I'll let it slide.
So who is he?
He calls himself "Chillblaine."
Wow, I'm glad Cisco's not
around to hear that one.
Chillblaine didn't just commit a crime
against good taste.
He also killed the Ivo Labs driver,
and I've got his confession on tape.
That means you're in the clear.
[sirens wailing]
Killer Frost,
come out with your hands raised.
You have two minutes to comply.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[sirens whooping]
[tense music]
♪
Flash, there's a whole squad
of CCPD cars outside of your location.
Yeah, we're trying
to handle it, Chester.
Killer Frost,
there is nowhere to go.
We have you surrounded.
You have one minute.
So what?
Let 'em try.
Or we could try calming down.
Chillblaine here is the real killer.
So I'll go out. I'll hand him over.
I'll let them know you're innocent.
Guys,
I may not have killed that person today,
but I'm not innocent.
- I have to go out there myself.
- What?
Frost, Kramer has a warrant
for all the crimes you committed
before joining Team Flash.
You get arrested,
you're facing hard time,
if there's a conviction.
Uh-uh, that ain't happening.
We can hide you somewhere
while we figure this out.
Right, then you're harboring a fugitive.
I can't let you do that.
Guys, before today,
I never paid for any
of the bad things I did.
Because you were out saving the world.
And I thought that was enough too.
But, if I'm gonna prove
that I've really changed,
then I have to own up to it, as...
painful as that might be.
Frost,
I've been to Iron Heights.
Jails do not make better people.
They're hell. You cannot do this.
I think I have to.
You're not gonna try
and stop me, are you?
- Not unless you want me to.
- I don't.
Frost, please.
What if you don't come back?
Don't worry, I will.
No...
[soft dramatic music]
♪
Time's up, go.
I'm coming out.
Guys...
is Frost really doing this?
It's her choice, Chester.
Something tells me it's the right one.
♪
[shackles clinking]
All right, thanks. Okay, bye.
That was Cecile.
Caitlin is back home.
Now she's trying to
get Frost out on bail
before the sentencing hearing.
What about a trial?
Frost is pleading guilty
to all her old crimes,
so whatever happens to her
next is up to the judge.
Well, at least Chillblaine
will be in Iron Heights
for a very long time.
Yeah.
How does Caitlin feel about it all?
I'm not sure.
I think she was just getting used to
Frost having her own body.
I know how hard it can be,
when a relationship like
that changes in a snap.
[whoosh]
Speaking of which,
I should get ready for work.
Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
No, it's... it's fine.
It's okay, I could feel you listening.
And I-I'm glad. I...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten
so upset at you earlier.
No, it's okay.
I tried to fit in
somewhere I didn't belong.
Being here, in your
home, with you and Iris?
It's not my place.
Yes, it is.
Look, I know...
how much things have changed between us.
You're not the same as the Speed Force
I'm used to interacting with.
And I...
I can't expect you to
be the way you were.
- It's not fair to you.
- To either of us.
Yeah, you're something...
else now, something new.
And it's something I'd like
to get to know better, Nora.
♪
And, look, no more glitching.
I'm almost fully healed.
So now we can take on
all three forces together.
[hopeful music]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --