Just packed up a real money load,
and it's coming your way.
Look for "Rodgers" on the truck's side.
Don't forget my share of the deal.
Shit!
-Tuna on white, no crust, right?
-I don't know. How is it?
Every day, for the last three weeks,
you've come here, asking how the tuna is.
Now, it was crappy yesterday.
It was crappy the day before.
And guess what? It hasn't changed.
-I'll have the tuna.
-No crust?
No crust.
Thank you.
Talk to me, Jesse.
This ain't working, brother.
It's your fuel map. It's got a nasty hole.
-That's why you're unloading in third.
-Told you.
I lengthen the injector pulse a millisecond.
Just tune the NOS timer, you'll run nines.
What's up with this fool?
Is he sandwich-crazy?
-No. He ain't here for the food, dog.
-Chill out. He's slinging parts for Harry.
-I know what he's slinging.
-He's trying to get in Mia's pants, dog.
-What's up, guys?
-How you doing, Mia?
-How you living, girl?
-Hey!
Hey, Dom. You want something to drink?
-He's beautiful.
-I like his haircut.
Vince!
-What?
-Can I get you anything?
You look good.
-Thanks a lot, Mia. See you tomorrow.
-Sure.
-Tomorrow?
-I love this part.
Try Fatburger from now on. Get yourself a
Double Cheese with fries for $2.95, faggot.
-I like the tuna here.
-Bullshit. No one likes the tuna here.
Yeah, well, I do.
Jesus Christ, Dom! Would you get out
there? I'm sick of this shit.
I'm not kidding, Dom. Get out there!
-What did you put in that sandwich?
-That's funny.
-Dom!
-All right.
-Hey, man. He was in my face.
-I'm in your face.
Relax! Don't push it! You embarrass me!
Get over there!
Jesse, give me the wallet.
"Brian Earl Spilner."
Sounds like a serial killer name.
-Is that what you are?
-No, man.
Don't come around here again.
Hey, man. This is bullshit.
-You work for Harry, right?
-Yeah. I just started.
You were just fired.
Hey, Dominic.
I appreciate what you did, in a big way.
Dominic, I owe you.
Brian, you're messing with my business.
When Dominic drives, he's golden.
Kids pour in. They want everything he has.
Every performance part. They pay cash!
-What did Dominic say?
-You don't want to know.
-He wants you out of here.
-He wants me out of here?
-Yes.
-And what did you say to Dom?
-What do you think I said?
I told him, "Good help is hard to find."
Relax.
I need NOS.
-I need NOS.
-No.
My car topped out at 140 miles per hour,
this morning.
Amateurs don't use nitrous oxide. I've
seen how you drive. You've a heavy foot.
-You'll blow yourself to pieces.
-I need one of these.
One of the big ones.
Actually, let's make it two.
And, Harry, I need it by tonight.
Hold up, hold up.
Look at this snowman right here, man.
Sweet ride.
What you running under there, man?
-Going to make me find out the hard way?
-Hell, yeah.
You brave. You brave.
They call me Hector.
I got a last name, too,
but I can't pronounce it.
-Brian Spilner.
-Typical white-boy name.
Know what I'm saying?
See that over there? That's mine.
My baby. I ain't cutting her loose tonight.
-Why not?
-I'm going legit, homey.
Trying to get on the NIRA circuit.
Heard about that?
-Hell, yeah.
-So, what's up with you, man?
-I'm just waiting for Toretto.
-Shit. Better get in line. This yours?
-I'm standing next to it.
-That's funny.
You know,
Edwin happens to know a few things.
And one of the things Edwin knows is:
It's not how you stand by your car...
...it's how you race your car.
You better learn that.
Oh, shit. Here they come. It's on.
-Dom.
-Marvin.
-Hey, Dom. How you doing?
-Hey, Camille. You been doing yoga?
You did? Of course you did. Monica.
I smell skanks.
Why don't you girls pack it up,
before I leave tread marks on your face?
Okay.
-Letty, I was just talking.
-Yeah. Whatever.
-Okay, Hector.
-Yeah? What's up, man?
-Yo. What's up?
-Edwin.
-How we doing this tonight?
-One race.
$2,000 buy-in. Winner takes all.
Hector, you're going to hold the cash.
-Why Hector?
-Too slow to make away with the money.
-Okay. Good luck, guys.
-Hey, wait. Hold up.
I don't have any cash.
But I do have the pink slip to my car.
You just can't climb in the ring with Ali,
'cause you think you box.
He knows I can box. Check it out.
It's like this.
I lose, the winner takes my car.
Clean and clear.
But if I win, I take the cash,
and I take the respect.
Respect.
To some people, that's more important.
That your car?
I see a cool air intake. It's got a NOS
fogger system and a T 4 turbo, Dominic.
I see an AIC controller.
It has direct port nitrous injection.
Yeah. And a stand-alone
fuel management system.
Not a bad way to spend $10,000.
You see that shit?
He's got enough NOS in there
to blow himself up. Period.
-So, what do you say? Am I worthy?
-We don't know yet.
But you're in. Let's go.
-All right.
-Let's go!
-What the hell is going on around here?
-Street's closed, pizza boy.
-Find another way home.
-Goddamn street racers.
Log on, 22. Code 3. Tension is high.
They've b/ocked the street.
Edwin.
This is yours, whether you win or lose.
But if you win, you get her, too.
You're going to win.
I'm going to win.
We had a reported homicide.
187, at Barabian Liquors.
I've got a 187 in Glendale.
Cops are all over it. We're good to roll.
-All right.
-Let's race!
Right.
Go!
Hell, yeah!
Damn, that guy's fast.
Let's go! Mènage!
No! Monica!
Shut up!
Well done, baby!
Come on. Come on. Back up.
Here's what you won, right here.
There you go.
You were racing a bunch of skateboards.
Know what I mean?
My sister holds the money. Count it.
And you're my trophy.
-Hey, Monica. What's up, baby?
-What's your problem? You didn't win.
Fuck you then!
Was that fun?
Got a problem there, buddy?
-What are you smiling about?
-Dude. I almost had you.
You almost had me?
You never had me.
You never had your car.
Granny-shifting.
Not double-clutching, like you should.
You're lucky that 100-shot of NOS
didn't blow the welds on the intake.
-Almost had me?
-You tell him, Dominic. Get out of here.
Now, me and the mad scientist
got to rip apart the block...
...and replace the piston rings you fried.
Ask any racer. Any real racer.
It don't matter if you win by an inch
or a mile. Winning's winning.
Yeah!
A// avai/ab/e units,
we have street-racing a/ong Hawthorne....
Oh, shit! We got cops. Cops!
Go!
Cops! Get in the car! Go!
Toretto, stop right there/
Toretto/
Get in!
You're the last person in the world
I expected to show up.
I thought if I got in your good graces,
you might let me keep my car.
You are in my good graces,
but you ain't keeping your car.
You drive like you've done this before.
Are you a wheelman?
-No.
-You boost cars?
-No. Never.
-Ever done time?
Couple of overnighters. No big deal.
What about the two years
in juvie for boosting cars?
Tucson, right?
I had Jesse run a profile on you,
Brian Earl Spilner.
He'll find anything on the Web.
Anything about anybody.
So, why bullshit?
So, what about you?
Two years in Lompoc.
I'll die before I go back.
-Oh, great.
-What?
It's going to be a long-ass night.
That's what.
Follow us.
I thought we had an agreement.
You stay away. I stay away.
Everybody stays happy.
We got lost.
What do you want me to tell you?
-Who's "we"?
-My new mechanic.
Brian, meet Johnny Tran.
The guy in the snakeskin pants.
That's his cousin. Lance.
So, when are you going to give me a shot
at that Honda 2000 of yours?
-This your ride?
-It was. It's his now.
No, it's not. I haven't taken delivery.
Then, it's nobody's car.
But somebody put in the wrench time.
-What do you think, Lance?
-It's an amazing machine.
Yes, indeed.
Let's go.
I'll see you in the desert next month.
Be ready to have your ass handed to you.
-You'll need more than that crotch rocket.
-I got something for you.
-What the hell was that all about?
-Long story. I'll tell you later.
Let's get out of here.
NOS!
-So, what the hell was that all about?
-It's a long story.
Well, we got a 20-mile hike. Humor me.
A business deal that went sour.
Plus, I made the mistake
of sleeping with his sister.
Take care.
Yo, Spilner.
-You want a beer?
-Yeah, sure.
Oh, shit.
We were all there, right? Falling behind.
-With all that nitrous.
-Yeah.
Yo, Dom. We were just about to go
looking for you, brother.
Where were you?
There were mass cops there. They came in
from every direction. It was orchestrated.
-This your beer?
-Yeah, that's my beer.
Yo, Einstein. Take it upstairs.
You can't detail a car with the cover on.
-Can't even get that right.
-You all right?
-Am I all right?
-It was just a question.
Yo, Dom.
-Why did you bring the buster here?
-'Cause he kept me out of handcuffs!
He didn't just run back to the fort!
The buster brought me back.
You can have any brew you want,
as long as it's a Corona.
-Thanks, man.
-That's Vince's. So, enjoy it.
You.
-Hey, bro. You got a bathroom?
-Upstairs. First door on the right.
He's got no call being up in here.
You don't know that fool for shit.
-He's right, Dom.
-There was a time when I didn't know you.
That was in the third grade!
-Yeah. So, what girls are here?
-You name it. You want mine?
-You need to shut the....
-You want two?
-You don't have anything?
-You look a bit tired.
I think you should go upstairs
and give me a massage.
-Look at all our guests.
-How about you give me a massage?
Crazy lady.
You know you owe me
a 10-second car, right?
Oh, shit.
Did you wipe the seat?
Jesus Christ! Would you cut this shit?
Come on!
-Come on. Let's go get me a drink.
-We were just about to get along.
-So, what do you want?
-Anything, as long as it's cold.
You know, my brother likes you.
He usually doesn't like anybody.
-He's a complicated guy.
-Yeah? What about you?
-I'm simpler.
-You're a shitty liar.
Well, I'll take that as a compliment.
-But there's a problem.
-What's that?
You need to get some sleep.
And you definitely,
definitely need a shower.
Come on. I'll take you home.
Show me your hands.
Very good. Now open the door.
Put your hands on your head.
Behind your head.
Face the front of the vehic/e,
wa/k backwards towards the rear.
Take two steps to your right.
Stop right there.
-What did I do?
-Shut up. He's clean, Sarge.
Damn!
Muse, will you take these things off?
-Shit. You put them on so tight.
-I like realism.
You never know who's watching, Brian.
Nice crib, Sergeant. It's a lot nicer
than the last place you confiscated.
Ain't it? Eddie Fisher built this house
for Elizabeth Taylor in the '50s.
You see, even the cops
are Hollywood in Hollywood.
Okay, here he is,
fresh from Toretto's hot rod heaven.
That was an $80,000 vehicle, Officer.
-You told him what happened?
-He knows.
-Send the bill to Johnny Tran.
-The kid's giving me attitude?
It doesn't speak well
for police/FBI relations, Tanner.
-I walk in the door and the guy's already--
-All right, all right.
We'll talk, okay? Let's talk about it.
Muse, why don't you make us
four iced cappuccinos, please?
-Come on.
-Regular or decaf, Sarge?
Decaf, I think.
Four hijackings in two months,
and we have nothing.
The DVD players and digital cameras
are worth $1.2 million...
...which brings the grand total
to $6 million plus.
We're in the political crosshairs now, Brian.
That's why you're undercover.
You want that detective badge fast, kid.
And you want to know something?
The FBI can help,
if you come through for us.
What does the truckdriver say?
He gave us the same M.O.:
Three Honda Civics, precision driving...
...the same green neon glow
from under the chassis.
Lab says the skidmarks came back
the same: Mashamoto ZX tires.
So, we know it's somebody
in the street-racing world.
If we don't make this case, the truckers
will take matters into their own hands.
I tell them we're close.
Are you going to make me a liar?
Look, what do we know?
We know this world
revolves around Toretto, right?
I'm not saying that he's the one
that's popping these trucks...
...but I can guarantee he knows who is.
It's just a matter of time until I win--
You want time, buy the magazine.
We don't have time.
Just get me something I can use.
Is Harry cooperating?
Like a guy that'll do time
for receiving stolen property if he doesn't.
What kind of vibe
is he getting from Toretto?
He's scared of him,
but he doesn't think he's jacking trucks.
-He's too controlled for that.
-Wait.
Not that I want to contradict
Harry's fine judge of character...
...but Toretto did hard time
for nearly beating a guy to death.
He's got nitrous oxide in his blood
and a gas tank for a brain.
Do not turn your back on him.
Tanner, I'm gonna need another car.
-What about parts and service?
-Hold off on it.
Dom, I don't know what to do with it.
All right, what the hell is this?
What do you got there?
-This is your car.
-My car?
I said a 10-second car, not a 10-minute car.
You could push this across the finish line,
or tow it.
You couldn't even tow that
across the finish line.
No faith.
I have faith in you,
but this isn't a junkyard.
-This is a garage.
-Pop the hood.
-Pop the hood?
-2JZ engine. No shit.
-And what did I tell you?
-I retract my previous statement.
-You know what?
This will decimate all
after you put about $15,000 in it.
Or more,
if we have to overnight parts from Japan.
-We'll put it on my tab at Harry's.
-Yes!
I gotta get you racing again
so I can make some money off your ass.
There's a show down in the desert
called Race Wars.
That's where you'll do it.
When you're not working at Harry's,
you're working here.
If you can't find the right tool
in this garage, Mr. Arizona...
...you don't belong near a car.
He owns you now.
Tell me what you think about this.
Koni adjustables.
Gonna save us about 2 pounds.
And they're gonna give us
better traction for the hole shot.
All right?
This is your basic layout of the car.
And that's pretty much
what it could look like when it's finished.
Red, green.
-You should be going to MIT or something.
-Yeah, right.
No, I got that.... What's it called?
That attention disorder--
-ADD?
-Yes, that shit. Yeah.
You know, I was good in algebra
and like math and shit.
Everything else I failed.
Dropped out of school.
I don't know.
It's just something about engines...
...that calms me down, you know.
-I'm outta here.
-Come on, dog.
-Yo, Dom.
-Vince, get over here and give us a hand.
Looks like you got
all the help you need, brother.
-Mia! The chicken's dry.
-All right. I'm coming out already.
Here you go.
Hey, hold up.
Because you were the first to reach in
to get the chicken, you say grace.
-Dear heavenly....
-Spirit.
Spirit. Thank you.
Thank you for providing us
with a direct port nitrous injection...
...four core intercoolers
and ball-bearing turbos...
...and titanium valve springs.
-Thank you.
-Amen.
-Not bad.
He was praying to the car gods, man.
He's not the best.
-What do you want?
-Practice.
Thank you, girl.
Look who it is. "Old Coyotes 'R' Us."
I thought you weren't hungry, pumpkin.
-You know, I gotta eat.
-He's always hungry.
All right, sit down.
How you doing, Mia?
Here you go.
-Jesse, hand me that chicken.
-Let's eat some grub, man.
-Want some of that chicken?
-What, you rent a movie or something?
Need a hand with anything else?
No, I'm good. You can go join the boys
and watch the movie.
-The cook doesn't clean where I come from.
-I'd like to go there.
-I think we should go out sometime.
-No, I don't date my brother's friends.
That sucks.
-I'll have to kick his ass then.
-I'd love to see that one.
I would pay to see that one, actually.
Wash my car when you get done.
-What was that?
-No, Mia. I'm talking to the punk.
Wear your favorite dress,
'cause when you're done...
...I'm putting you on the street
where you belong, cutie.
Is this thing broken?
What's wrong with this thing?
What was that Cuban restaurant
you wanted to take me to?
The one with the picadillo and--
-With red candles, wooden tables--
-The plantain, food all over the place.
-What it's called?
-Cha Cha Cha.
-Yeah, that's it.
-Yeah.
Well, you can take me there.
Friday night at 10:00. Is that good for you?
-Yeah, it's perfect.
-Good.
-There's no popcorn.
-Make your own goddamn popcorn!
All right. Now that's valet parking.
-Harry. What's up, dog?
-Nice to see you.
Excellent. Come on in, man.
-Check it. It's yours.
-Damn. What do we got here?
-Hired some new help?
-Don't even think about it.
-What's up?
-What's up, Brian? How you feeling?
-Pretty good. What do you need?
-What's up, man?
I need you to hook me up.
Three of everything. I made a list.
Why don't you look that over?
-When do you need this stuff by?
-Tomorrow, today, now.
-Right.
-White boys work fast, don't they?
That's right.
-You said you need three of each?
-Yeah, three of everything.
What do you think about that?
Check this out.
He moans like a cop.
Brian, this is one of those times
you need to be clear about what you say.
Nod if you understand me.
Nod!
Sit up.
Tell me what the hell you're doing
down here.
Shit. What I'm doing?
Dom.
I owe you a 10-second car.
And what this is about,
this is about Race Wars.
I just went in there,
and Hector is gonna be running...
...three Honda Civics with Spoon engines.
And on top of that,
he just came into Harry's...
...and he ordered three T66 turbos,
with NOS...
...and a MoTeC system exhaust.
So, what are you saying?
You're gonna check everybody's shit out,
one garage after another?
Yeah.
Because, Dom, you know I can't lose again.
He's a cop.
He's a cop!
You a cop?
Let's go for a little ride.
Walk!
Okay. You stand watch.
Yo, Dominic.
There's no engines.
What are they planning on racing with,
hopes and dreams?
I don't know, but they're sneaky as shit...
...and they've got enough money
to buy anything.
What?
We got a wolf pack.
/t's Johnny Tran,
and he's coming your way rea//y fast.
All right, we got company. Spilner.
Come on. Move!
Let me ask you a question, Ted.
-Do you see anything wrong here?
-No.
-We got no engines, do we?
-Do we?
-No.
A couple of Nissan SR20 motors
will pull a premium...
-...one week before Race Wars, huh?
-Yeah, probably.
You're a smart fence, Ted.
Maybe too smart.
What are you feeling, Lance?
40-weight?
50-weight?
A 40-weight sounds nice.
Where are they, Ted?
-Where are they?
-Enough!
-They're in a warehouse.
They're in a warehouse, man!
Ted.
Kiss my shoes?
Let's go get our engines.
My superiors are flying in from D.C.,
in two days.
I want something to show.
We've got a fence
with a lube hose in his mouth...
...automatic weapons,
priors on every one of these Asian punks...
...a garage full of DVD players
and generally psychotic behavior.
Tell me why we shouldn't move
on Tran now and figure it out later?
Because all we have is behavior.
Let me get hard evidence,
because what we have now is just--
What we have is probable cause.
And truckers arming themselves for some
good old-fashioned vigilante mayhem.
-Tell us about Hector, Brian.
-Latinos with spear guns. Give me a break.
Hector's still working on the engines,
but the tires don't match.
Will somebody give me a cigarette?
-Get him a cigarette.
-Don't give him one.
-I thought you quit.
-I did. Just give me one.
-Get him a cigarette.
-No!
Tell me about Toretto.
I told you,
I think he's too controlled for this.
Going suicidal on semi-trucks? No way.
Maybe Vince. But he's too dumb to do it.
-I think the kid sister's blurring your vision.
-What did you say?
I don't blame you.
I'd get off on her surveillance photos, too.
Knock it off!
What? Are you going native on me, Brian?
Have you read Toretto's file lately?
-Yeah. I memorized that file.
-Read it again.
No, better still, take a look at these.
Remember I told you about the guy
he nearly beat to death?
Toretto did this
with a three-quarter-inch torque wrench.
He's a model of self-control.
I need a few more days.
Got a TR7 here,
with a ball-bearing upgrade.
What it's going to do is,
it's going to spool up really quick.
-I got this set up for 24 psi.
-Got it.
You got big plans tonight?
Yeah. We're going out to dinner.
You break her heart, I'll break your neck.
That's not gonna happen.
I want to show you something.
Me and my dad built her.
Nine hundred horses of Detroit muscle.
It's a beast.
-You know what she ran in Palmdale?
-No. What?
Nine seconds flat.
-God.
-My dad was driving.