[tense music]
♪ ♪
Back off, lady.
Oh, Deon.
Past, present or future,
you can't run from me.
Who said I'm gonna run?
Maybe I could just snap my fingers,
send you back a thousand years in time.
By the time you get back,
oh, I'll be long gone.
♪ ♪
Now, that is no way
to treat your big sister.
I don't have a sister.
Yes, you do.
Look inside yourself.
Your stillness knows
my speed, little brother.
We're connected, you and I.
I know you can feel it.
Okay, m-m-maybe we are the same.
Okay, who cares?
- I don't know you.
- Yes you do.
We were born at the same time.
What? Lady, you're nuts.
First, you show up trying to kill me.
Now you want to chat
like we're in Sunday school?
Nah. [chuckles]
I ain't falling for that.
Oh, Deon.
We may have come
into this world together,
but this isn't my first time...
which means...
I could kill you at any moment.
And I still might.
Then do it or get out of my face.
[suspenseful music]
You're right.
I don't want you dead.
But I do want your help.
You and I have a common enemy.
Our father, Barry Allen, rejected me,
just like he rejected you.
Tell me something...
How does that make you feel?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Wait, let me get this straight.
I'm a force of nature?
Barry's The Flash,
and you two birthed me?
[laughs] That makes you, what?
My parents?
Something like that.
And I have three siblings?
One who just tried to kill me.
Technically, Alexa, she did kill you.
But your biometrics are stable.
So I think you're fine.
Wait, how did you bring me back anyway?
♪ ♪
We don't actually know.
But according to my initial tests,
the three of you share the same
bio-kinetic genome sequence.
Kind of like how a parent
and their child share the same DNA.
Exactly, except we're
talking about cosmic DNA.
So you can sense their cells
on a quantum level
and vice versa.
So they can sense one another?
That is so damn cute.
Wait, if we're all connected,
can't the other forces
sense each other, too?
If Nora finds them before we do...
She's gonna kill them.
All right, well, where are we
with finding Deon and Psych?
Chester and I are working
on a tracking system
to locate Deon's temporal isotopes
across timelines.
I'm monitoring the data,
while he's out there
setting up the sensors.
And The Citizen is looking into Psych.
We're gonna see if we can
ID his human identity.
We do that, we can find him.
Well, we better do it fast.
I've been seeing intermittent spikes
of Nora's isotopic signature
all across the city.
And there's been a ton of reports
of spontaneous lightning.
Your firstborn is pissed.
She's gonna come after me again.
And if she does, we will protect you.
How? You couldn't the last time.
She's not going to this time.
We're gonna train you
to control your powers.
Wait, you want me
to control that monster?
Think about it.
Nora needed me to help to take you down.
If you could control your powers,
I don't think she'd be
able to hurt you again.
What if I hurt you
or kill someone else
during this training?
[groans]
I can't hurt anyone else.
We'll... we'll make sure you don't.
Let us help you.
♪ ♪
You leaving?
Yeah, Iris put me on Psych duty.
It is an all hands on deck kind of day.
Yeah, this, uh...
this whole fighting Big Bads thing...
definitely not gonna miss it.
[chuckles]
Hey, what do you think about Miami?
Great mojitos, excellent NBA team...
What, are you thinking about
booking a vacation, like, now?
No, I meant to live
after we leave Central City.
I've been submitting my work
to a few art galleries,
and this one in South Beach
is interested.
Plus, I do love a good mojito.
You're already job hunting...
Yeah. Aren't you?
♪ ♪
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, we should probably
tell the team soon.
I got to give Iris enough time
to find a new photographer.
- Bye.
♪ ♪
Fine, just call me when the deal's done.
Caleb...
[chuckles] That's my name, you idiot.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
Who said that?
Who's here?
Caleb.
It seems like your short game
still needs some work.
[laughs]
Who are you?
What do you want?
Aw...
you don't remember me.
Well...
Let's see if I can't jog your memory.
Bashir? How are you doing this?
Eh, it's kind of a long story.
To be honest with you,
it's been a bit of a nightmare.
How about I share it with you?
♪ ♪
[screams]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
That was Caleb Fairweather,
the billionaire tech guy.
What happened to him?
According to the paramedics,
mental distress
and symptoms consistent with narcolepsy.
That was the mayor's office.
It turns out that Caleb
is the fourth billionaire today
they found like this.
Hold on.
♪ ♪
Yeah, I'm picking up a ton
of electrochemical isotopes in here.
Caleb was attacked by Psych?
I don't get it, you both
were attacked by Psych,
and you didn't end up like that.
[cell phone vibrates]
I'm needed at CCPD.
Let me know if you find out anything.
♪ ♪
What are you thinking?
Well, we both assumed that Psych had
an Axe to grind with the system
because he was attacking
banks and the stock market,
but now he's going
after individual people.
Why the change?
Yeah, I know, it feels personal.
Maybe there's something here
that explains the escalation.
I'm guessing that's not
Caleb's college chess club?
No.
More like an Ivy League society.
Wait.
My dad did say that
four other wealthy targets
were attacked today.
If Psych is targeting people
in this group, then...
Start training Alexa as fast as you can.
I'm gonna try to figure out
who's next on Psych's list.
♪ ♪
[distant siren wailing]
[knock at door]
Kramer?
I thought you were headed upstate.
As a result of the Frost case,
the governor wants me
to stick around a bit longer.
Have a seat, Captain.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I'm trying to find the source
of this city's
meta-criminal problem,
and I need your help.
There seem to be a whole lot of cases
where meta-criminals simply
disappear around here.
This Rainbow Raider...
one minute he's in CCPD custody,
the next, missing.
Any thoughts?
None, whatsoever.
Okay, then.
Who else worked these cases?
Patty Spivot, reassigned.
Julian Albert, also reassigned.
Hmm.
Barry Allen's still here.
Can you do me a favor?
Send him in.
Maybe he knows something we don't.
He's on a case.
♪ ♪
I'll see if I can pull him off.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Don't worry.
This force field can handle
just about anything...
speedsters, futuristic meta-villains...
Oh, you've done this before?
[laughing] Oh, yeah.
But you should know
I've reinforced this baby
with inverse surge capabilities.
The harder you push against it,
the stronger it's gonna get.
Even Fuerza can't fight herself, right?
Fuerza? You named it "strength"?
I guess that makes sense. [sighs]
What now?
You initiate a change.
The key is to focus.
Control the transformation
into Fuerza from the start.
So try to stay calm when I change?
[scoffs] You gonna teach me to meditate?
I mean, it's really just
about your breathing.
Focus on that while you transform,
and we'll keep track
of the physiological effects.
You sure I'm ready for this?
If Nora shows up again,
you need to be able to protect yourself.
We'll go slow.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Yeah, I-I don't think I can do this.
Yes, you can.
Just try to remember
how you felt the last time.
- I can't.
- Alexa, you have to.
♪ ♪
Excuse me, Ms. LaSalle?
Hi, I'm Iris West-Allen with
the "Central City Citizen".
If you're looking for a quote
on our recent merger,
you'll have to contact publicity.
No, actually, we're here
because you were
the president of the League of Lions.
Is this for that alumni newsletter?
Here's a quote.
I'm wealthier than the
whole league combined now.
Ms. LaSalle, please.
There's a meta-human that is
targeting members of that league.
And four of your Richie Rich friends
have already been attacked.
We believe you and the other man
in this photo are the next victims.
If you could just tell us his name?
Lucas Sharpe.
He's into apps and
alternative energy sources.
Bit of a do-gooder.
Felicitatem esse virtutem...
Prosperity equals power.
And judging by this empire
that you've built up
for yourself, it appears
that you followed
the League's motto to a T, Naomi.
Congratulations.
♪ ♪
I know that voice.
Smashing costume, Bashir.
♪ ♪
Mm, it's not working.
I don't know how
to bring that thing out.
It's because you're holding back.
- [alarm blaring]
- [sighs]
I've got isotopes downtown.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So, Naomi,
I've been catching up with the old gang,
you know, swapping stories.
It's actually been a lot of fun for me,
and now it's your turn.
Last time I saw you,
you got thrown out of the Yacht Club
because you couldn't pay your dues.
It's true.
The regatta life was never for me.
I was so right about you.
The others thought
you deserved a chance,
but I knew you'd never fit in.
[inhales deeply] Let me guess.
You're broke again, and now
you want another handout?
Sorry, Bashir.
You want help...
help yourself.
Don't mind if I do.
Bashir.
You don't have to do this.
Oh, yes.
I really do.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
Whew!
Back for another round, huh, Flash?
Psych, you need to listen to me.
You're in danger.
There are other forces
out there who are trying to...
Boring.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
So you're Dad?
[laughs] Life is just full
of little surprises,
isn't it?
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Your scans show patterned bruising
from where Psych... Bashir attacked you.
What did he show you this time?
He didn't show me anything,
but his powers are growing.
I mean, somehow he was
able to manifest...
tentacles?
He could move as fast as me.
So...
we've got a fifth comatose billionaire
in the hospital
and an evil magenta sage guru
with tentacles?
Magentacles, if you will?
We're gonna have to change up
our plan, I think.
Well, Iris is trying to
locate Bashir's final target.
We need to be ready.
Right, um, to do what exactly?
I mean, maybe I'm not
strong enough to stop Bashir,
but Fuerza is.
Wait. You want me to fight him?
Hey, uh, just long enough
to subdue Bashir.
So hopefully we can get through to him.
What if I accidentally kill him?
Well, you won't if you can
get a handle on your powers,
which is why we got
to continue your training.
Cisco, are the isotopic arc
radiators still functional?
Uh, they need a couple tweaks but, yeah.
I'm sorry, you want to force Fuerza out?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, we're running out of time.
Barry, you can't push Fuerza out
until Alexa's ready...
it's too dangerous.
Alexa...
this is...
about more than protecting
yourself from Nora now.
If Bashir uses these new powers
on the city,
people will get hurt.
I know you're scared,
but we still need your help.
And this Bashir guy's really bad?
He's pretty much the worst.
[sighs]
Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Bashir Malik... his name was listed
on the League of Lions
member page, class of '08.
He is the adoptive son
of Adrita and Paul Malik,
owners of Malik Hotels.
He was a rich kid.
But it says here the Maliks died
- in a plane crash 13 years ago.
- _
He was orphaned twice?
First by his birth parents
and then by his adoptive parents.
And it gets worse.
When the Maliks' plane went down,
they were $50 million in debt.
They were fleeing the country
for tax evasion,
and they left Bashir behind.
And I thought my family was messed up.
That's why he hates his parents.
They... they abandoned him.
And they weren't the only ones.
Naomi told him he never belonged.
You think when he went broke,
his friends bailed on him, too?
Yeah, that's why he's targeting them.
He felt burnt by his parents,
his friends, and the system
that made him.
Now he's out for revenge.
[sighs] So who's next on the list?
Lucas Sharpe.
I ran his picture and got a hit.
He wasn't at his home or his work,
and all of his social media
accounts were recently deleted.
- He's on the run.
- I called Cisco.
S.T.A.R.'s search protocols
are up and running.
But, Iris, even if we find Lucas,
what's our plan?
I mean, you've tried talking
to Bashir twice now,
and it still hasn't worked.
Well, because I didn't know what to say.
I think I was trying
to be a-a mother figure,
when I should have been a journalist...
getting all of the information
before running a story.
And you think there's more to his?
Yeah. We need to dig deeper.
♪ ♪
[latches click]
Find what you're looking for?
I checked out the armament delivery
you signed for this morning,
seeing as I didn't authorize it.
These bullets contain the
meta-human cure, don't they?
30 CCs each, yes.
If meta-humans are
threatening the public good,
we need to be able to protect
the people of this city.
- This is illegal.
- No.
There's just no precedent
for them... yet.
You didn't get the results
you wanted in court,
so now you're trying
to figure out another way
to eliminate meta-criminals.
Meta-criminals are dangerous, Captain.
The people of this city can see it.
Why can't you?
The last time we talked,
I asked you to make sure
you're on the right side of the line.
Now you're gonna go out there
and shoot up metas with the cure?
When it comes to meta-human affairs,
I have full authority
to use extreme measures
in emergency combat situations.
This is still my precinct.
Around here, we take the time
to de-escalate the situation
before it becomes combative.
That's what this precinct did,
and your city hasn't been safe.
So we're doing things my way now.
I don't think so.
I'll contact the Governor's office.
The Governor authorized the order.
[dramatic music]
I'm still hoping that we can
work together on this, Captain,
but this is the new line now.
Figure out which side of it you're on,
then let me know.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
All right, remember,
the radiators release isotopes
that'll bring out Fuerza,
so you don't have to do anything.
Just try to stay conscious
during the transformation.
That's the first step
to maintaining control.
If I start to lose control,
promise me you'll turn these things off.
Of course we will.
Also...
I've got backup.
You ready?
[machine whirs loudly]
Releasing isotopic waves...
now.
[grunting in pain]
Remember, Alexa, you're in control.
I can't.
I don't want to do it.
You can.
[menacing voice]
I said I don't want to do this.
Guys, her biometrics are spiking.
I'm gonna reduce her isotopic exposure.
Don't.
Alexa, you can do this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [alarm blaring]
- Uh, that's a problem.
Guys, she's getting blue and angry.
It'll take 30 seconds for the
isotopic effects to wear off.
We don't have 30 seconds.
She's overloading the force field.
If we don't shut it down,
this thing's gonna blow,
and then we're all toast.
I'm shutting it down now.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
I told you I couldn't control it.
♪ ♪
[door opens]
Is he gonna be all right?
He needs to rest,
but he'll make a full recovery.
All right, we should get back to work.
Barry, why don't we
take a break on training?
Look, I-I know this is a setback,
but we can't stop.
Lives are on the line.
Don't you know what just happened?
We can't train that thing.
Alexa, we don't have a choice.
Oh, you don't, I do, and
I-I won't be your weapon.
I'm done with this,
and I am done with you.
Wait, Alexa...
- Barry, hey.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- She needs to train.
She just found out two days ago
that she has this force inside of her.
She needs time to process that.
Look, I'm trying to teach her
how to survive.
- Well, she's not ready.
- Well, she has to be.
All right, look, it's my fault
that Nora wants her dead.
That means it's my responsibility
to keep her safe.
Training her is the only way
I know how to do that.
I am not saying that we don't
train her when she's ready.
Right now what Alexa needs
from you is patience.
[sighs]
When you first got your powers,
Thawne spent months training you.
Your greatest enemy
was more patient with you
than you're being with your own...
daughter.
Think about that...
while I try and stop you
from pushing another kid away.
[serious music]
♪ ♪
Kramer's gonna start a war.
She's going after every meta
with a record,
and she's being smart about it.
She's doing everything by the book.
Wow, you almost respect her don't you?
I know that there is a good
cop in there somewhere
that cares about the safety
of people, but...
not like this.
What's all this?
These are all the purchases
made by Kramer
on behalf of CCPD.
I also have former case files
coming from Keystone,
Gotham, Coast City later today.
It's about time somebody
investigated her.
Ugh.
Joe, I just went up against Kramer.
That woman knows how to handle herself.
Plus, she's got the Governor
on her side.
What are you saying? I should back down?
Joe, it has got to be her choice.
Otherwise, she is never gonna back down.
So, until that happens,
what are you gonna do
to help her get there?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Should you be working right now?
- You're still recovering.
- I'm just a little sore.
I'll be all right.
- [computer chimes]
- Oh, my gosh.
That gallery in Miami wants
to schedule an interview.
And you don't seem that excited.
Did you know that I'm qualified
for 7,685 jobs in the U.S. alone?
83 of them in Miami.
And trust me...
I know... [chuckles]
How lucky I am to be able to say that.
[sighs] But if I'm being honest...
I have no clue what I'm
supposed to be doing right now.
♪ ♪
I never told anyone this,
but when we were at Cleary Capital
and Psych whammied me
and Barry and Frost
and he showed us our worst nightmares,
you know what I saw?
I saw myself...
40 years from now.
I was still working at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And that's a bad thing?
No, not entirely.
I mean...
I've learned a lot here.
And I've made family here.
But in this nightmare...
Everybody had moved on...
and I hadn't.
♪ ♪
It was just me.
And I felt this insane regret
for not even trying to do
anything else with my career.
♪ ♪
I don't want that future.
So...
what the hell am I supposed to do?
Babe...
I know this is a big decision,
but you don't have to make it right now.
Just give it time.
The right job will find you.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I know it seems safer...
but running away won't solve anything.
I don't have a choice.
When you turned that machine off,
I could feel that monster
fighting against me
as I was changing back.
It wanted to stay out.
What if I never control it?
You will,
just like I did.
Do you know the meta-human Frost?
She and I used to share a body.
When Frost first surfaced,
she did horrible things.
And I was terrified.
I tried to control her with meta-cuffs.
I didn't even try to understand her.
But then after a while, I realized
that there was good inside
that other part of me.
How'd you do that?
By talking to Frost with this.
It's a mental activity dampener.
It uses neural pathways to connect
multiple consciousnesses.
It's how we talk to each other.
I could hear that thing in my head?
Mm-hmm.
It'll take time.
But I think that's
just what you two need.
Or maybe you just want me
to start training again.
Forget the training.
I should have listened to you
when you said you weren't ready.
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
If you need more time to process this,
you got it.
Whatever you want to do, we'll do it.
Thanks for saying that.
[sighs] I guess what I want to do is...
try to get in sync with my other half.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
[suspenseful music]
Satellites are picking up
Lucas Sharpe's license plate.
He's headed north on I-95.
[engine revving]
Hang on.
Uh, we got Bashir's Force signal
heading Sharpe's way, and fast.
♪ ♪
Fill the jet. I'm ten minutes out.
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
Hi, Lucas.
Bashir?
Oh, my God.
Where have you been all these years?
That's an interesting question.
You know, I guess I could have
been out there trying to find myself,
traveling to Prague or the Amalfi Coast,
really living the dream
like all of you did.
No, but I couldn't do that...
because I couldn't get my friends
out of my mind.
I tried to get in touch.
- I was worried about you.
- You did?
Oh, that's so sweet.
I'm sure you thought about me every day.
Sure, sure, sure.
Hey, listen, now that
I've got you here...
can I pick your brain about something...
for old times' sake?
♪ ♪
Guys, Lucas Sharpe is the last
person on Bashir's hit list.
And if Bashir gets to him first...
There's one more thing.
There's more to
Bashir's story than we knew.
If you can get him to listen,
then I can tell you what to say to him.
- Okay, stay on comms.
- I'm coming with you.
- Alexa, you don't have to.
- I know.
I want to.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Look, Bash, come on, we were friends.
Whatever you want, we can work it out.
Oh, Lucas.
You always were the optimist
in our little cabal
of spoiled, rich brats.
Of course, that's not
going to help you now.
No, no, no. Please, please.
You couldn't stop the others,
so, instead, you watched
them destroy my life.
That makes you just as guilty.
And now you're going to pay...
just like them.
♪ ♪
Flash...
why don't you come out
and show yourself?
Are you afraid?
Do you fear me, Flash?
Ah!
You know it doesn't matter
where you stashed him.
I will hunt Lucas down.
No, you won't.
We won't let you hurt him.
We?
Who's this?
Oh.
I have a baby sister.
- Don't care.
- Bashir, listen.
Iris and I know what
your parents did to you,
but you can't keep punishing
the world for it.
Actually, yes, I can.
♪ ♪
[Flash grunts]
I don't know if you can hear me,
but I'm not afraid of you anymore.
What if Alexa's not ready?
Fuerza might be the muscle,
but after everything she's been through,
I think Alexa might be stronger.
Por favor, Fuerza.
Necesito tu ayuda.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Alexa?
[voices mixed] And Fuerza, together.
You are a very big baby sister.
Not that it's going to matter.
♪ ♪
Bashir, you don't have to fight us.
Yes, I do, Dad.
Can't you see we're just
trying to help you?
Then don't bother.
Bashir, listen!
♪ ♪
It doesn't have to be this way.
Tell him that we're not like his parents
and neither were his friends.
Caleb, Lucas and the others,
they never gave up on you.
That is a lie.
All they ever cared about was money.
No, they cared about you more.
After your parents died,
they started a fund
to help you get back on your feet.
Iris found bank statements
and donation receipts
all in your name... Bashir Adil Malik.
You didn't know because you
pushed them away
when they reached out.
No. No, no, no.
Naomi would never help me.
You're right about that.
Naomi turned her back on you,
so you assumed the others would, too,
but they didn't.
They wanted to help.
So do we.
No, no, no, no, there's no way.
This... this can't be true.
No, it is.
Don't push us away like you
have with everyone else.
You always wanted a real family?
Give us a chance. We can be your family.
There is no such thing.
You don't know my pain.
You're right, Bashir.
They don't.
But I do,
because my past is
just as dark as yours.
[sighs]
I've been clean for five years.
But when I was at my lowest,
I drove away everyone I ever loved.
My own parents won't even talk
to me anymore.
I know what real loneliness feels like.
But at some point, the walls we build
need to come down,
or they will crush us.
And when they do...
the people who still
want to be there for you,
that's real family.
That's us.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
Continue.
We'll wait for you, Bashir...
as long as it takes.
[exhales sharply]
The choice is yours...
brother.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[weapons clicking, whirring]
Okay, thanks.
Bashir's victims are awake.
They're gonna be okay.
What are you guys doing?
Barry and Alexa are bringing
a monster into our house.
- Two, actually.
- Can't be too careful.
That's probably wise.
Oh...
there's a lot of fear in this place.
I like it.
It's okay.
He's decided to give family a try.
For now.
I'm not sure if I'm sticking around.
Hey, you know, those rifles and...
whatever those gloves
are supposed to be,
that's not gonna help you,
you know that, right?
- Just a heads-up.
- Don't make me angry.
♪ ♪
You got lucky the first time.
You want to roll the dice on round two?
- I...
- I got to call Frost.
- I think have something to do.
- I have a thing.
Ah, you guys got this, right?
Yeah.
[cell phone vibrates]
Look, both of you stand down.
We're on the same team now.
Her first.
♪ ♪
Oh, this is new for all
of us, so let's just...
take it slow, all right?
Fine.
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
You wanted to see me?
[sighs] Yeah.
I need to talk to you
about what happened today.
Okay, I'm listening.
As Captain, it's hard
to watch the ideals
that you built your whole career on
get stripped away.
I know.
You're just doing your job.
I respect that.
It's just that I wish...
I wish...
that you could try to understand
what this city really needs...
because here it's not just
black and white...
or even gray.
I do things by the book, Captain.
Maybe.
But it's gonna take
a whole lot more than that
when it comes to protecting
the people of Central City.
Only, you can't see that.
And since your "by the book"...
Is nowhere near mine...
♪ ♪
Do you realize what you're doing?
Yeah.
♪ ♪
I'm staying on the right side
of the line.
♪ ♪
So now you know everything we do.
Okay, so you got four kids,
two of which are so pissed off,
they want to kill you.
This is why some people
shouldn't have children.
[scoffs] You are such an ass.
I'm direct, sis. There's a difference.
Look, the point is Nora
will come after you, too.
Yeah, only if she's
as nuts as you say she is.
She is, trust me.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Either way, I'm not scared of her.
- It's not that simple.
- You're not that simple.
Alexa's right.
We can't underestimate Nora.
As the Speed Force,
she is different than the rest of you.
She's been around
since the dawn of time.
And I thought I was dramatic.
You can't beat her, not alone.
None of us can, which is why
we need to find Deon
as soon as possible.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
Nora...
please.
♪ ♪
You made me do this, Barry.
It's done.
♪ ♪
No.
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -