[CROWD CHEERING]
Um, so it's amazing
to see, uh, everybody here...
...from DC television tonight.
It's kind of crazy to have the universe
represented like this.
Uh, so I'm gonna ask some questions
for a bit...
...and then we're gonna turn to you
and get some questions from the audience.
I'm gonna start with some Gotham
questions, so, Bruno, start with you.
Uh, and Danny. So where--?
I mean, Gotham--
Where did this all come from?
Why start with the death of the Waynes?
Where did you, uh, spark that idea?
Origin stories are my favorite part...
...of the mythology of, uh, the DC Universe,
and origin stories in general.
So actually, when I started talking with Geoff
about doing something in the DC Universe...
...it was just natural to me to start thinking
from the start of the process.
And what is more sort of iconic and seminal
than the death of the Waynes?
JOHNS:
Danny, where'd you get the--?
Like, what was your inspiration
for the vision of the show?
It's so spectacular. It's just a beautiful,
majestic, cinematic show.
Where did you--?
Like, what did you draw from from the lore?
CANNON: It was a dream come true,
as far as a director's concerned.
And it was a dream, um...
...of Gotham, a city that I always wished
I could have visited as a kid.
The comic books I read,
the movies that I saw.
We just had to go back in time and imagine
what that decrepit, decaying, corrupt city...
...was like from the very beginning,
and, uh, I just started sketching.
And it went from there.
JOHNS: And, Ben, so you're like
the only good cop in Gotham right now.
MCKENZIE:
That's correct.
And, Donal,
you're a pretty bad cop in Gotham.
So are you gonna drag Gordon down
or is Gordon gonna pick you up?
I think we're gonna meet in the middle,
probably, right? Heh-heh.
Yeah, Harvey's-- You know, like,
Harvey knows how the city works.
And Jim, uh, believes he knows
how the city ought to work.
And between those two worlds
is, uh, Gotham.
LOGUE: It's hard not to love Ben, so it seems--
MCKENZIE: Ooh, wow, hey. All right.
He's such a do-gooder, he kind of pulls him
to the other side of the equation.
JOHNS: So speaking of the cops,
we'll go to the villains.
Jada, so you're one of the most
charismatic people on-screen...
...and in this,
you bring a real seductive quality--
Like you do right now.
--to everything.
So, what's it like playing this villain...
...who, Bruno, you created.
It's a brand-new character,
so you can really do whatever you want.
We don't know what the outcome
of this character is. What's that like?
Um, it's a very unique experience.
And, you know, to be part of a franchise
like this and have the opportunity...
...to collaborate with someone
like Bruno, Danny...
...to create this character
has just been amazing.
And Robin.
So everyone saw the Penguin.
I think this is the most brilliant
representation of the Penguin.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Ever.
Like, it's really-- And I've read the scripts
that Bruno and his crew are doing...
...and it's extremely twisted. Thanks, Fox,
for letting us get away with that.
Uh, so, what's your inspiration
for Oswald Cobblepot?
Because this is a very different Penguin
than, I think, anyone's ever seen.
-How much makeup is on there?
-There's a lot of makeup on me. Heh-heh.
It's a lot. I mean, you wouldn't think so.
It's very subtle, and I actually really like that.
I mean, you know, not to say that,
you know--
Not to say that I'm not doing anything...
...but, like, once they put all the stuff on,
I feel like half my work is done.
Like, I just feel like
all the pieces come together...
...and it's just, you know, we're there.
-Yeah.
JOHNS: Okay, so, David.
Little Bruce Wayne.
[CROWD CHEERS]
So first off, we were saying
how jealous your friends are...
...that you get to be a Batman in training.
How old do you think you're gonna have
to be before you put on that costume?
I think Batman becomes Batman
when he's 25.
I think so. So hopefully this show will run
until I'm 25.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
Fingers crossed.
And, uh, Carmen-- Camren.
So you're a brilliant Selina.
You're like a little Michelle Pfeiffer. So cute.
Oh, thank you.
You guys are both really young, so where
did you first get introduced to Catwoman...
...and did you know the character
prior to this...
...and what did you, uh,
look to for research?
Well, um, I looked to the comics
and the Batman show...
...with Adam West for research.
I saw some movies too,
but other than that...
-...mostly the show and the comics.
JOHNS: Yeah.
Well, what are you most excited about
with Selina?
Oh, I'm excited about everything.
She's really mysterious, and you don't
really know what she's thinking all the time...
...or whether she's thinking anything at all.
Um, you know, she's a cat lover,
I'm a cat lover.
I feel like we could be best friends,
you know?
JOHNS: Okay.
-So, yeah.
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
So I'm gonna go back to the man
who kind of started this all...
...the powder keg, Stephen Amell.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Who really, with, uh, Greg and Andrew
and Marc, created Arrow...
...and kicked off
what made this all possible.
So thank you so much for that, guys.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Um, so, Stephen--
Like, Mr. al Ghul, that's cool.
-Yeah.
-You guys like that?
That's gonna be awesome.
[CROWD CHEERS]
So tell them a little bit about season three
and what's in store for Oliver.
So season three for all of our characters
is really about identity.
And it's-- Can Oliver be Oliver Queen...
...and be the Arrow?
Uh, does he have--?
Can he do both at the same time?
Does he have to pick?
And we're presented with
a bunch of scenarios in the pilot--
Excuse me, in the premiere.
--that forces him to make a decision.
When you were first thinking
about Arrow, Greg...
...did you think
that you would build a show...
...this big and spin off
something like The Flash...
...and what was that process like for you...
...creating this universe?
Uh, well, first, I just want to say, I think,
on behalf of so many people here...
...thank you guys for coming out tonight.
We're so....
[CROWD CHEERS]
It's past my bedtime.
I don't know if it's past your bedtime.
I especially wanna thank this little gentleman
in the front row, who I think is falling asleep.
I feel bad for him. Heh.
So, no, we were so excited upstairs because
I think so many of us love the characters...
...and love these worlds as much as you do.
And we really do, uh, go to work every day
and pinch ourselves.
I mean, we started just with, you know,
the hope to make an Arrow show...
...that we would wanna watch.
Uh, and that's sort of been
our commitment throughout.
Marc, I know you're a big nerd too.
Uh, so can you tell us a little bit...
...about some more of the characters
from the DC universe...
...that'll be showing up
this season on Arrow?
Yeah, we've got, uh, Tatsu Yamashiro...
...who, as everyone knows,
becomes Katana.
[CROWD CHEERS]
We've got Brandon Routh
playing Ray Palmer.
Who everyone knows becomes the Atom.
We've got a little guy named Ra's al Ghul...
...who we've been hearing about
for a couple years.
Uh, we're finally gonna get a chance
to see him in the flesh.
And, uh, there'll be one other DC character
who we haven't announced yet.
JOHNS:
Can you or not?
What? Should we do it?
-Okay.
JOHNS: Yeah.
MAN: Yes.
Ted Grant. Wildcat.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Coming aboard the show.
And, uh, he's gonna have
a little interaction with Laurel.
Let's just say that.
JOHNS:
Oh.
Okay, so you forgot one. We saw this image
was released, I think, last week.
Arsenal. Colton Haynes.
Yes.
So, Colton, what's it feel like to join
the ranks of the costumed superheroes?
HAYNES:
It's freaking awesome.
I mean, you can't really--
You can't really--
Until you guys see this costume
in its entirety--
It's the coolest costume in the world.
Um, they gave me a butt.
Like, I have a really nice butt in the costume,
so I'm really excited about that.
Uh, but really, it'sjust really cool to,
you know, join team Arrow...
...and to be part of such a great team,
you know? It feels like a family.
And so, Black Canary, how is it to play--?
Your Black Canary's such a badass.
LOTZ: She's pretty cool, right?
-She is pretty cool.
LOTZ:
She's badass.
So, you know, I know the character
is coming back. Can you say anything...
...about how it's been
to play Black Canary...
...and what you were inspired by
for this character?
-She's so wounded and tortured.
-Yeah.
Um, well, of course I read some Birds of Prey
comics and the Black Canary comics.
Uh, which, of course, are written
by our wonderful writers over here.
And mostly I just took it from, you know,
like, she has a really dark past.
And I think that makes her character
so strong...
...but she's so vulnerable with
her connection with her family and stuff.
So it's been fun. And getting to wear
that costume is like....
I mean, come on. It's pretty fun.
JOHNS:
We like when you wear that costume.
LOTZ:
Well, thank you. Heh.
Uh, John, so Dark Archer.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Malcolm Merlyn.
We saw him return, surprisingly.
What's his plan this season? Is he--?
Because he's a villain,
but he's got this strange heroic quality too.
So in your mind, who is this guy?
In my eyes, you know, if I'm speaking
from Malcolm himself, um...
...I'm as much a hero
as Oliver Queen is, actually.
That's the way I see it. And....
[LAUGHING]
HOLLAND: Best laugh ever. Wow.
MAN: Yeah.
But, uh, what's really gonna be exciting
is who, you know--
Who he's gonna face up to this season.
What is gonna happen?
The whole relationship between Malcolm
and his daughter, uh, Thea.
And what's gonna happen,
and how it's gonna be the most amazing...
...the most fantastically dysfunctional...
...father-daughter relationship
on television ever.
HOLLAND: Ever.
-And I cannot wait to get my teeth into it.
It's gonna be awesome. Yeah.
JOHNS: And are you gonna teach Willa
how to shoot an arrow?
You're just gonna have to watch.
You never know. I'll teach her a few things.
-Yeah. Yeah.
HOLLAND: I'm scared.
[LAUGHS]
I'm really scared right now, guys.
-Don't be, darling. I'll take care of you.
-What's happening? Oh, God.
Oh, God.
JOHNS: All right, I'm gonna transition a little
over to Flash.
I'm gonna use it with Emily.
Tell us a definitive answer:
Is it gonna be Oliver and Felicity,
or is it gonna be Barry and Felicity?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa.
-What about Ray Palmer?
JOHNS: Aw.
We just talked-- And he is-- He's a man too.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
-We had-- Heh. Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
-No, he's hot.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
Let me, uh-- Let me backtrack.
Gosh, I work with these guys every day.
This is real bad.
We have Barry's intellect...
...and Oliver's intellect.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
Heh. Oh, I'm just digging myself in a hole.
This is where Felicity and I sort of—-
This is where we zone, because I--
JOHNS:
This is where you're exactly like Felicity.
I don't know.
I am very lucky that I get
to transition over to The Flash...
...and in episodes to come,
we can all look forward to such.
I'm very, very excited.
I don't even have to leave the lot to do it,
which is great.
Um, it'll be really, really fun.
But I am not sure in terms of love interest.
I don't know. Are they interested in Felicity
at a certain point? Who knows?
I mean, it's all gonna change.
We deal with life and death every day.
When it comes-- I'm serious, we do.
Every day.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
JOHNS: So on the brighter side.
-On the brighter side of life.
JOHNS:
Of love.
Uh, Andrew, I know you're like--
It's so funny,
because Arrow can be so dark...
...and yet, you're the guy that walks around
with a smile on his face all the time...
...and you constantly pitch jokes.
Um, what--? Like, what--? Because,
for Flash, I think the heart of it is really...
...something that you help
bring out obviously. It's from you.
And you really got your hands into Felicity
as a character...
...and created that voice with Greg
and everyone else.
But where do you--?
Why so much humor in The Flash?
Why change that when you developed that?
-Did you wanna take it?
MAN: No.
-I can do it.
MAN: Do you.
Okay. Um.... Heh.
You know, first of all...
...we were very conscious of not wanting
to make the same show twice.
And, you know, we assumed you guys
didn't wanna watch two hours...
...of the same show every week.
And, you know, so whereas Arrow has,
you know, a much darker quality to it...
...you know, with Flash we wanted
to do something a little lighter...
...a little brighter, a little bit more blue sky.
And Barry Allen has always sort of had that.
If you read the comics,
he's always been a lighter character...
...and there's always been a lot more humor.
So we were just really excited
to explore that aspect of it.
And of course I walk around
with a smile on my face.
Oliver Queen, Barry Allen, Bruce Wayne,
John Constantine.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
So, uh...
...you know.
JOHNS:
So, Grant, there is, uh, obviously...
...Some darkness and some tragedy
we saw in The Flash's past...
...in that pilot, and yet you bring such a joy
and optimism to the character.
He's got a hopeful outlook.
Where do you find that balance for you
when you're playing Barry Allen?
Like, what do you draw from for that?
Oh, God, I mean, I love Barry.
I love him. And he's just got this--
He's full of hope, he's full of optimism...
...which is the part
that I can definitely relate to.
I try to be optimistic in my life.
I think we'd go crazy with this career
if we aren't optimistic.
Um, so that's something I can draw from.
And as far as the emotional depth
of the character--
I mean, that's what my favorite part
of being an actor is.
Just digging as deep as I can.
I mean, that's when I have the most fun,
is just, kind of...
...the emotional rawness of the character.
So I love that there's both sides to it.
He's an idiot and he's a dork
and it's hilarious, but he's brilliant and he--
And he does have--
There's a lot of depth to him.
And just he's a very genuine character
that I love playing.
And I think that's why he's kind of easy--
He's easy to relate to.
Because he's just so genuine.
Yeah, and, you know, in this too,
you play off Jesse, uh, so well.
That relationship between Barry
and Detective Joe West.
So great, so, Jesse...
...I know that, like, superheroes
probably wasn't the first thing...
...you'd think you'd do next
after everything else you've done.
Why--? Why did you say yes to Flash?
How did that happen?
[MARTIN LAUGHS]
Well, I've obviously played
a detective before.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Thank you. Uh, but when--
When I met Andrew and Greg in New York...
...they sat down and they pitched to me...
...like two puppies that had to pee
and couldn't go outside.
And they were so excited
about the whole thing.
And they saw me fitting in way more
than I saw myself fitting in...
...that I was like, "I'd be stupid
not to consider this, at least."
And I was like,
"Well, let me just read something."
And when I read it, I was like:
"This is absolutely amazing,
and I have to do it."
And as long as I've played a detective,
I never got to shoot anything.
And we're only in the beginning of things,
and I done shot a lot of people.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
So the other father figure--
Uh, we're really glad
you're on the Show, Jesse. You're amazing.
The other father figure, who's an actor.
He played The Flash before,
John Wesley Shipp.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Amazing actor, we were talking earlier...
...like, there was no Comic-Con like it is now
when The Flash TV Show was originally on.
So this is pretty different, I assume,
from your experience the first time around.
Yeah, we shot till 9 a.m.
one Saturday morning...
...and they said
we need to go to San Diego.
And I think we walked through a convention
hall and signed a few autographs...
...and took a few pictures,
and the whole thing took about two hours.
-This is, uh, very different. Very different.
MAN: Yeah.
So, Tom, what's the deal, man?
You stepped up out of that wheelchair.
You tell me, Geoff.
You tell me, Geoff Johns. What is the deal?
JOHNS:
What is the deal?
So, what's Dr. Wells' interest in The Flash?
Can you delve into that a little bit?
Why is he--? How's he know all this stuff?
Heh-heh. Um....
KREISBERG: Say nothing.
-Yeah.
You heard Kreisberg, right? "Say nothing"?
This is like--
Yeah, I'm caught in a tough place.
Uh, I will say that sometimes, Geoff...
...in the comic book world, people are not
always exactly what they appear to be.
JOHNS: I've heard that.
-Ahem. Yeah, that happens occasionally.
And this might be one of those instances.
Certainly, Barry has three,
uh, mentor figures.
He's got his real father, played by John.
Jesse, the man who brought him up.
And then once he gets struck by lightning,
he's got a guy who has a vested interest.
I play that guy. And you know more than me,
so quit asking me the questions.
[JOHNS LAUGHS]
Sorry, I had to torture you a little bit.
CAVANAGH: Understood. Understood.
You owe me though.
Candice, um....
So we know where your character's going,
obviously, coming up in Flash...
...but you know the character
from the comic books, She's a reporter.
So where's Iris gonna go...
...and how is her relationship with Barry
gonna stay the same, change?
Well, I think--
I mean, what I love about Iris...
...is, I mean,
something that we all look for in our lives.
We're always looking for that person who's
kind of our true north and our best friend.
And I think Iris is that for Barry,
and that's fun to play.
But I think it's gonna be interesting
to see how their relationship evolves...
...once he's got these superpowers...
...and she learns that not only
is Barry, her best friend...
...and her father keeping this secret
from her...
...how she deals with that family dynamic...
...and how that changes her relationship
with, not only her father...
...but someone that she's considered
her best friend her entire life.
It's gonna be a little tricky.
It's exciting
to see how that's gonna happen.
I'm at Comic-Con, guys.
[CROWD CHEERS]
-Can we take a moment for that?
JOHNS: You just realized that.
You've been here three days.
PATTON:
Oh, my God. Thanks for inviting me.
So, uh, David. Where's Mr. Goyer?
Hey, David.
So you guys know David,
he wrote all those kickass Batman movies.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Man of Steel.
He made the first good Marvel movie
with Blade.
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
So, David, I know when you sat down
and talked to everybody...
...about what you wanted to do
in television...
...you had your choice
of basically anything you could do.
So after Batman and Superman,
why John?
He doesn't have any Spandex, which is
kind of nice, doesn't have any superpowers.
And we joke that, like, if he--
You know, first he'll try to throw a spell...
...and if that doesn't work,
he might try to pick a fight...
he might try to do a con.
If that doesn't work,
he'll try to kick the guy in the balls.
And if that doesn't work, he'll just run.
And that's, like, a fun character to write
after all this time.
JOHNS: Yeah, very different than Superman.
GOYER: Yeah.
So, Daniel, when, uh, you guys
were casting the show...
...what made you land on Matt Ryan?
Who's tremendous
and he's Constantine embodied.
But how did you know
that you'd found him?
You know, I have to say that I don't know
if an actor has ever worked harder for--
-Where's Matt? I don't see him.
GOYER: There.
I don't know if an actor has ever worked
harder for this role than Matt Ryan did.
We got one self-tape in from this guy
who's worked with Jude Law in Henry V.
And you should've seen the tape we had.
First of all, he was about 10 pounds lighter
than he is now.
He had dark hair, long,
Slicked back completely to his skull.
And he had a beard. And he looked like
Sasquatch. It was this wide, and it was....
RYAN: David said that I was Sasquatch.
-I mean, he looked like a Hasidic Jew.
But, like, Six Million Dollar Man Sasquatch.
But here's the thing, I mean, and I don't
know if it's the Shakespearian training...
...I don't know what it is, but he said
the lines and you could see it in his eyes...
...and you could see it
in the way he owned it.
He looked nothing like this now...
...but it was like,
"This is John Constantine."
What kind of research did you do
for this character?
Because this cha-- He's very unique,
obviously, and you embody him perfectly...
...so, what'd you do to get there?
I read one comic and then, uh,
just carried on delving deeper and deeper.
And after I got the role, I just kind of gleaned
as much as I could from the comics.
And I'm still reading them.
I mean, there's a lot to get through...
...So I'm still reading and still searching...
...and still trying
to get under John's flesh and, uh, yeah.
Are there any other DC Characters--? I know
the answer, but I'd love to hear it from you.
Any other DC characters
gonna show up in the series?
RYAN:
Um....
Yeah, I think there are, right?
There's Jim Corrigan.
GOYER: Corrigan and, obviously,
he turns into The Spectre.
-Yeah.
GOYER: Helmet of Doctor Fate Shows up...
...in the pilot, so....
Yeah, there's lots of Easter eggs in there.
And, uh, we've obviously got Zed.
-Played by the beautiful Angélica.
GOYER: Angélica.
Papa Midnite's showing up
in a few episodes.
-We'll be rolling out a number.
JOHNS: Cool.
Uh, well, I'm gonna open up
to fan questions.
I don't know where the mic is,
but we can take a few questions.
We don't have a lot of time,
but we'll take a few questions.
Well, we wanted to have
one of his most iconic villains in the pilot...
...so, um, but we also knew
that we wanted Jesse to shoot him.
So, you know, fortunately in the comics,
Mark Mardon, um, has a brother, Clyde.
So, you know, somebody
was obviously flying the plane...
...that we saw Clyde Mardon jump into.
So, uh, there is
another Weather Wizard out there.
Um, and we will see him one day.
And, you know, we were very conscious of--
You know, we weren't just doing a show
about The Flash.
We were doing a show about The Flash
and everyone in that comic book.
And Central City and Iris and Joe
and, um, you know, all the villains.
Because the Rogues--
Especially all the work that our very
handsome moderator tonight, Geoff Johns...
...has done in comics, you know, over the last
15 years in building up the Rogues' Gallery.
So we're very blessed.
Wentworth Miller is, uh, gonna be playing
Captain Cold in episode four.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Uh, which will also be the first appearance
of Felicity on The Flash.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Uh, and, you know, the others will,
you know, they'll get rolled out one by one.
JOHNS: You will get a glimpse
of another one in episode four.
That's true.
JOHNS: Yeah, and you will see Grodd.
That cage was not there by mistake.
We heard you guys.
Next, please.
For me, this is, like, completely,
completely surreal.
I grew up loving this genre of, like--
I wasn't a comic book fan necessarily
growing up...
...but I was a huge fan of the
Christopher Reeve's Superman franchise...
...all those movies.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Uh, and so this-- But I also grew up
doing musical theater and, like, tap dancing.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Grew up in Virginia, so, I mean,
this is not only something that--
It's not a dream come true,
it's something I could've never fathomed.
And when I got to put the suit on
for the first time...
...I mean, it blew my-- That's me right there.
And it's nuts. I t's insane. It's-- I'm having
the time of my life, so it's incredible.
MAN: Thanks, Connor.
JOHNS: Thank you.
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
JOHNS:
Well, Gotham kind of takes--
I mean, Bruno, you can talk
about that a little bit.
It kind of takes place kind of in the past,
but also in the present.
Um, yeah, that's a good question.
Again, I would say never say never.
I think at the moment both shows are new.
And one of the things
about creating a TV show...
...is you're trying to, um, create
and find the tone of the show.
And if those two worlds, if those two
DC worlds coincide, then it would work.
But, as you say, I'm not really clear about the
chronology with how Constantine interacts--
Maybe Constantine is only 5 or something
in this universe.
And that wouldn't be very entertaining.
-But, yeah, never say never. Yeah.
JOHNS: Or would it?
You could come up with a story over there.
-Time travel. There you go.
JOHNS: Yeah, that'll fit right in with Gotham.
[HELLER LAUGHS]
I mean, what do you expect me to say?
[CROWD LAUGHS]
I would win.
RYAN: Yeah.
-Choose your words carefully, okay?
JOHNS: Hey, buddy.
BERLANTl: Actually, our episode eight, uh,
this year of Flash is called "Flash vs. Arrow."
So you'll be able to find out, I think.
[CROWD CHEERS]
I feel very fortunate and proud
to play such an intelligent...
...well-written woman on television.
And I--
[CROWD CHEERS]
So grateful every day. Um....
She has a really special place
in my heart...
...and I'm really glad
that she resonated with you.
And anyone else.
Thank you.
Yeah, and I don't know if I could express any
more how much I love playing this character.
So I mean, it's just...
Everything resonates with me.
Every day I love this character more.
Every script I get, I love this character more.
He just has a lot of heart,
and I just love playing the character.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Thank you, thank you.
WOMAN:
Take it off.
BARROWMAN:
AMELL: Well....
BARROWMAN: Take it off, take it off.
HOLLAND:
I think my dad wants your shirt off.
WOMAN:
Take it off.
AMELL: Tune in on Wednesday nights.
WOMAN: I think we should have a vote.
-The panel should vote. I'm up for it. Let's go.
-Am I not shirtless on the show enough?
WOMAN:
Vote. Let's vote. If anyone wants to....
JOHNS:
Wednesday nights.
[CROWD CHEERING]
All right, that-- We cannot top that question,
so give it up for DC Television.
-The stars of DCTV.
MAN: Thank you, guys. Thank you.
[CROWD CHEERING]