Improved & Synced by BanglarBagh
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) No way!
MAN: Yeah.
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH)
This is the Cuban spirit.
(DOM SPEAKS SPANISH)
Dom. Dom.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ENGINE REWING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) You know I can't
make a living without my car.
Not my problem, bro.
Dominic Toretto, I heard about you.
Welcome to my island.
Why you hookin' up
my cousin's car?
He needed money,
I gave it to him.
He can't pay, I take the car.
I just need a few more days.
"Few more days"
wasn't part of the deal.
Come on. You make a deal,
you gotta live up to it.
You make a deal,
you gonna live up to it.
"Gonna" live up to it?
Oh, so you're
one of those types.
You take everyone-'s ride, and
then ship it back to the States?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH)
You watch your mouth.
(CHUCKLES)
Now you got a problem.
I'm gonna keep it
about the cars.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) You want a car,
get it the right way.
How?
Race for it.
I already own it, bro.
Not that car.
Mine.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Dom, his car is the fastest
car on the island.
Do you know what
he has under that hood?
He knows it doesn't matter
what's under a hood.
The only thing that matters
is who's behind the wheel.
You think so?
I know so.
Then race his car.
And we ain't racing
no quarter-mile, here.
We race the Cuban mile.
Done.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I appreciate what
you're trying to do,
but my car is the slowest
car on the island.
Was.
Pull the seats, the
doors, the battery...
If it ain't the motor,
take it off.
Laughing gas?
Nah, Fed.
This is Cuban NOS.
You guys are crazy.
What are you doing?
DOM: Poor man's turbo. Pull
the vacuum line and hold on.
Old trick that Buster used to
play, in case of emergencies.
You know that's way too
much boost for that engine.
DOM: It's gonna be fast.
It's gonna be a bomb.
Only needs to go a mile.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ENGINES REWING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Vamonos!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
(IN ENGLISH) That car belongs
in the trash, bro!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(HORN BLARING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
FERNANDO:
Where are they going?
LETTY: I don't know.
Let's go!
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Ghost him.
MAN: Si.
(PEOPLE YELLING)
Adios, Toretto!
Okay, Buster.
Let's see if this works.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(ENGINE REWING)
That's impossible.
(ALL CHEERING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CHEERING)
(IN ENGLISH) Lookout!
(ALL CONTINUE CHEERING)
A clears a deal.
You won my car.
And you earned my respect.
Keep your car.
Your respect is
good enough for me.
DOM: Yo, cousin...
Sorry about your car.
Yours was too slow
for a Toretto, anyway.
Your Impala?
Are you serious?
(ALL CHEERING)
Look at that smile.
I love it when you smile.
You make me happy.
Mmm, I think this place
makes you happy.
It's like it speaks to you.
You remember that guy,
the racer and his dad?
The one with the boat
engine under the hood?
Yeah!
Yes.
Of course.
I was looking at them, and I...
And I couldn't help
but to imagine
what you'd be like
if you were a dad.
No, no, no!
I'm not pregnant.
Is that what you want?
It's not about what I
want or what you want.
It's about why we haven't
asked the question.
(ENGINE CRANKS SLOWLY)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) What?
You need a hand?
Yeah, I think I do.
Sounds like you're not
getting any fuel. Yeah?
Probably the shut-off solenoid.
Let's see if we can
get some power to it.
What brings you to Cuba?
The same thing that brings
everyone else to Cuba.
Culture, people, the beauty.
What brings you to Cuba?
Work.
Must be casual Friday.
How's that honeymoon going, Dom?
Your fuel relay is missing.
I know.
I love to play games.
I've beaten the best of 'em.
But I'm kind of in a rush, so if
you've got something to say to me...
Oh, this is a very different
game, that I can assure you.
This... There's something
much greater at work here.
This is fate.
I choose to make my own fate.
Not today.
Is this the road you take to
your apartment every morning?
What else is different, Dom?
Was Santiago's closed'?
Did you have to cross two blocks
to go get your Cuban coffees'?
What is it, black, no sugar?
Yeah.
I put a lot of work into
getting you here today.
Well, now that I'm here,
what do you want?
I want you to work for me.
Work for you?
Oh, I could've saved you
a lot of time, then.
See, I don't work for anyone.
You can't walk away
from this, Dom.
We're gonna have this conversation,
one way or the other.
You see, that's the
funny thing about fate.
It's cunning.
It can bring you
beautiful things,
and it can also bring
you moments like this.
Oh, you're gonna want
to work for me.
You're gonna betray
your brothers,
abandon your code,
and shatter your family.
You see, your team is about to go up
against the only thing they can't handle.
What's that?
You.
Oh, and, Dom, I wouldn't
mention this to anyone.
(ENGINE STARTS)
HOBBS: They are gonna be hitting
us with everything they got.
So we wanna engage
with maximum speed.
Neutralize their shooters, and
then move on to our objective.
There's two things
I want you to keep in mind.
Number one,
I chose you for this squad
because you are the most
fearsome warriors on the planet.
And number two,
you go out there,
you do your job,
and you take 'em down.
Everyone.
And I mean everyone.
Mani's and pedi's
at the mall later on today.
(ALL CHEERING)
Huh?
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
GIRLS: Monarchs!
(CHANTING HAKA)
(ALL CHANTING HAKA)
(EXCLAIMS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(WHISPERS) What?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
I don't wanna play anymore.
All right, let's go, girls.
Let's go, let's go!
Final two minutes.
DS ALLAN: Quite
the cheering section.
HOBBS: Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's the moms. They
come out to support the kids.
Except there seem to be
more moms than kids.
Way more moms.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
It's a big soccer town.
Let's go, girls!
So, your intel
was spot-on.
That Damocles 7 EMP weapon
that went missing in the Gulf?
Arms dealers from the Liberation
Front have it in Berlin.
HOBBS: Shit!
This thing can wipe out an entire
electrical grid in a major city.
No lights, no power.
Instant Stone Age.
Chloe, Maya, you can't let
her run by you like that.
Let's go, let's go! Cross!
Agent Hobbs, this is a Class Four WMD.
Do you have any idea
what's at stake here?
Yes, I know exactly what
is at stake here, okay?
If the Pink Butterflies
beat my Red Dragons,
that means we lose
the championship.
Which means
I have 20 little girls
who are crying, and
that's not a good thing.
Which then means I have to spend
a lot of time in ice-cream shops
and a lot of time
at Tay Tay concerts.
Tay Tay?
Taylor Swift. Gotta be shittin' me.
Get it together, okay?
Let's go, girls!
We need you to do this.
It's a lot of lives at stake.
All right, but I need
to be clear here.
The US government cannot sanction
this operation in any way.
You're on your own.
Hey.
If this thing goes sideways,
you don't just get burned.
You go to prison.
And there's nothing
we can do to get you out.
Let me tell you something.
The only thing that I love more
than saving lives is my daughter.
So, if you don't shut up with this
government bullshit right now,
and start showing
some team spirit
and respect for the Red Dragons,
I'm gonna have all 20 of them line up
and kick you right in the tay-tay.
Go Dragons!
Say it again.
Attaboy. Go Dragons.
Go Dragons.
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
SAM: I'm open.
She's open! Go, go!
Yes! (LAUGHING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
That is my daughter
right there. Yes.
Yes, come here.
How did I do?
Awesome.
Nice job, kid.
(HOBBS SIGHS)
Daddy's gotta go to work?
Uh, yeah.
Daddy's gotta go to work.
Now, you're gonna need
to get a team you can trust.
Oh, I already got one.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(SIGHS)
HOBBS: Hey, Dom.
Hey, Hobbs.
I got a job in Berlin and
I need a favor, brother.
No problem. I'll grab the
team and meet you in Berlin.
Thanks, man.
Hi see you soon.
(GRUNTS)
You were only supposed
to create a diversion, Roman.
That was a diversion!
How many of the damn
explosives did you use?
ROMAN: I don't know, Tej.
All of it?
Wait, all of it?
Roman, Jesus Christ.
We got more of
your fan club ahead.
They're still on us!
These guys are
taking this personal.
Roman, we just blew up their
facility and stole their EMP.
Other than
your doctor's cold finger,
I'd say it's about as
personal as it can get.
Phase Two!
Phase Two? So you just gonna
keep that to yourself'?
What happened to Phase One?
What about that part?
Yeah.
Remember the airplane?
Everyone drove
their cars out but you?
I told you, my engine seized up.
It's your balls that seized up.
Just follow my lead, okay?
And, Roman, whatever
you do, don't think.
Huh?
Tel, drop it.
Bombs away.
(BEEPS)
Split, now!
ROMAN: Holy...
(CURSES IN GERMAN)
ROMAN: (OVER RADIO)
Great plan, Tej.
But just so you know,
you missed some.
Oh, just wait for it.
ROMAN: Oh, shit!
I hate you, Tej!
(LAUGHS)
Got your ass.
You good?
I'll see you when it's done.
All right, great job, team.
Let's break off and meet
me at the safe house.
(ENGINE REWING)
A hell of a job, brother.
When we get back to the
base, the beefs on me.
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
You lost your goddamn mind,
Toretto?
Toretto, you put
hands on that thing,
you're gonna have the whole world
gunning for you, including me.
(DOM GRUNTS)
I don't know what you're doing,
but you better think
about this, Toretto.
It ain't too late to stop this.
It is now.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
That sumbitch just crossed us.
What? Wait a second, what
are you talking about?
Dom took the EMP.
Bullshit.
Where are you?
HOBBS: It's too fate for me.
Ger outta here.
Saw that look in his eye,
and I've seen that look before.
Dominic Toretto just went rogue.
TEJ: All right' I got
his phone records, y'all.
It's a whole bunch of calls
to untraceable numbers.
ROMAN: Burner phones, right?
TEJ: Nah, scrambler.
Same number,
but they got some sort of
micro-router
to bury the signal path,
which means Dom is clearly communicating
with somebody that's above our pay grade.
Look, I don't know
Dom as well as you,
but if we just
look at the facts,
Dom's been having highly
encrypted conversations
with some mysterious person.
He took out Hobbs.
He stole an EMP.
Now he's disappeared.
So, what are you saying?
Maybe we should consider
the fact that Hobbs is right.
Dom did go rogue.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
ROMAN: Letty.
LETTY: Before
you judge the man,
remember, you're breathing right
now because he saved your life.
You just gonna let her bump
your shoulder like that?
I'm just saying,
that was a little aggressive.
What you gonna do, email her?
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Check.
(CELL DOOR BUZZING)
Moment, will you, fellas?
Thank you.
Well, this is
an exciting new look.
It's a little tight in
the crotch, as always.
(CHUCKLES)
What boy-band bus
did she fall out of?
It's my new junior associate.
He's working with me on this.
All yours.
Mr. Nobody and I have been given the
authority to get you out of this.
All you have to do is agree
to the terms and you're free.
What's training wheels
talking about? What terms?
Confess to your crimes
in Berlin.
Treason,
international espionage,
massive destruction
of civic property.
You do that, we close the case.
And the DSS blacklists you. And?
Germany loves that.
LITTLE NOBODY: Officially,
you will be a criminal.
MR. NOBODY: Wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You need to work on your
delivery, all right?
Unofficially...
You're off the books.
You come work with me.
I'm not a criminal.
MR. NOBODY: Luke,
come on. Labels.
There is no confession.
There are no backroom deals.
I got myself into this, I'm
gonna get myself out of it.
You know that. I do, and that's
what I told him. (SIGHS)
Well, there you have it.
Good luck in the courts, man.
What about your daughter?
You know, if you're not gonna
do it for your country,
at least do it for your kid.
(CHUCKLES)
Big mistake, kid.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hold on. Luke, Luke.
He's still working
from the manual.
I mean, he doesn't even
really know the rules.
Now, come on, give him a break.
(STRAINED)
Give me a break.
Luke.
(GRUNTING)
Appreciate it.
(COUGHING)
It's good to see you, Nobody.
You, too.
Rule number one...
Know your audience.
I gave you your shot.
You shit the bed.
Now I'm gonna show you
how to get this done.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You're dead, cop. Dead!
INMATE: I'm gonna slice
some bacon off your back, pig.
DECKARD:
Well, well, well...
Luke Hobbs behind bars.
Would you look at that.
The bent cop got his day.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(CELL DOOR BUZZING)
You know, that color
looks good on you.
Yeah, it'll look a whole hell of a
lot better with your blood on it.
Yeah, good luck
with that, Hercules.
Lawman gone bad, huh?
Such a cliché.
Oh, well, welcome to the club.
I wouldn't get
that twisted, son.
We ain't in no club,
we got nothing in common.
And unlike you,
I ain't gonna be here long.
What, you bring
a shovel, did you?
Because it's 38 feet
of steel and concrete.
Or so I've been told.
(DECKARD CHUCKLES)
Better get to digging.
Wanker.
Yeah.
Move.
Say that again.
If I say it again,
it'll be to a corpse.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna enjoy this.
CIPHER: Welcome back, Dom.
Nice job out there.
You excited about tonight?
You're going on this?
You're with me, Dom.
Showing me your shoe collection?
Yep.
A pair for every occasion.
You have enough guns in hereto
outfit a small army, huh?
Oh, this is just
the tip of the iceberg.
You know what I like about you, Dom?
You're a genuine outlaw.
I mean, you're a man
who lives by his own rules.
Which is surprising, because
when I saw you in Cuba,
I heard about a guy who almost
killed you with a motorcycle,
and you let him keep his car?
Oh, that confused you?
Hmm.
'Course I could've
taken his car.
But it's about something bigger.
This way...
I changed him.
That's not your responsibility.
But it's who I am.
Is it?
Let me ask you something, Dom.
What's the best thing in your life?
Family.
No, it's not.
Not if you're being honest
It's the 10 seconds
between start and finish,
when you're not thinking
about anything.
No family, no obligations.
Just you.
Being free.
I gotta tell you,
this whole saving-the-world, Robin Hood
nonsense you've been doing recently?
It's bullshit.
It's not you.
Be who you are.
Why live only
a quarter mile at a time
when you can live
your whole life that way?
(PANTING)
Is that it?
Is that all those bloated-out
muscles will give ya?
All show and no go.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, I got plenty of go.
You must've misplaced that
when I kicked your arse up and
down that office of yours.
Yeah.
Just like you Brits,
rewriting history, huh?
All I know is, it wasn't me that was
thrown out of a four-story window.
Jumped.
I jumped out of a four-story
window, saving my partner's life.
'Cause where I'm from, we don't
settle fights by throwing bombs.
Well, that's funny,
because where I'm from,
we don't need women
to run to our rescue.
I mean, do you really believe
you can stand in front of me
and beat me in a straight-up,
old-fashioned fist fight'?
Let me tell you something.
Me and you, one-on-one,
no one else around.
I will beat your ass
like a Cherokee drum.
Maybe one day we'll find out.
Oh, you better hope
that day never comes.
(DOOR BUZZES)
I said no, Mr. Nobody.
I'm not leaving this cell.
I'll get out my way.
(ALARM BLARING)
The right way!
Hey! Why's the door open?
Get back in your cell!
Relax. It's just
a malfunction.
Get back!
HOBBS: Just a malfunction.
(GRUNTING)
Stop him!
Don't let him get away!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(YELLING)
MILLER: Hobbs!
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Keep waiting, bitch.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Rubber bullets. Big mistake.
(GROANING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Well, that took longer
than I expected.
HOBBS: Two questions.
MR. NOBODY: Yeah.
My daughter?
With your sister.
Toretto?
(CHUCKLES)
It's interesting you ask.
This is my new base.
Welcome to nowhere.
It's a little sterile for you.
(CHUCKLES)
Listen, there's something I
wanna talk to you about after.
Hey, listen, guys.
Thanks...
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What? Handcuffs?
What is this?
It's called abuse of power.
You told me to round them up.
I didn't tell you to hand...
Cut 'em loose. Oh, man.
This is embarrassing.
I'm sorry, guys, really, I...
So, this is how
you treat old friends?
TEJ: Friends? We don't even really
know who the hell this guy is.
Doesn't matter who I am, Tej.
I'm, like, nobody, okay?
Nobody. So, then,
who is he?
Him? He's nothing.
He's, like, less than me.
Clearly, we're getting
nowhere with nobody.
I've been in here for four
hours, and my ribs are showing.
I don't know about y'all,
but I'm out.
I wouldn't recommend that What?
Well, thanks
to your botched Berlin job,
you all made Interpols
Top 10 Most Wanted list.
Top 10.
MR. NOBODY: Mmm-hmm.
That's all right.
Well, not you, Roman.
What do you mean?
You just missed the cut.
You're number 11, so...
I'm... I missed?
Yeah.
ROMAN: That's impossible!
What number did they come in at?
Six, eight, nine, ten.
She's 10?
Mmm-hmm.
That's impossible. There's
no way she's a 10.
Oh, she's definitely a 10.
(SCOFFS)
How about we focus on someone who we're
not gonna find on anybody's list.
We're awaiting
hard confirmation,
but I believe that's the cyber
terrorist known as Cipher.
Wait, no. Cipher's an organization.
Not a person.
Not according to our sources.
What does she want?
No one knows.
Cipher is like
a digital act of God.
They... Well, she can manipulate
world systems from the shadows.
Anything that can be hacked
is hers to play with.
And here's the kicker. You'll never
find her linked to any of it.
Her digital identity is scrubbed
every few seconds, worldwide.
So, basically,
she's the bogeyman.
Damn, she's one of the hottest
bogeymans I've ever seen.
I mean, if y'all know her,
tell her to get at your boy.
(ROMAN CHUCKLES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
What are you, 12?
ROMAN: That was my shin, mother...
Let's just say, people are scared
of the hacker group Anonymous.
But even Anonymous
won't mess with her.
What the hell does any of
this have to do with us?
Probably nothing, Letty,
but I do find it
interesting that,
apparently, for some reason,
she's now working with this guy.
(SIGHS)
He's already delivered a fully
operational EMP into her hands.
Detonate that, they can turn any
city in the world into a war zone.
So, then, what is it
you're suggesting we do?
MR. NOBODY:
Maybe we find Dom, huh?
Well, first, let's catch him,
and then figure out
why he's turned.
So, y'all want us to track Dom.
Yeah, I know, Roman,
it's kind of a big job.
It's impossible.
Which is why I'm bringing
in an extra pair of hands.
Ah, my day just got
a whole hell of a lot better.
Mr. Nobody,
you wanna tell me why
you just put me in a room with this
tea-and-crumpets eating, criminal sumbitch?
What a big mouth
on a small head,
coming from Prisoner 6753.
Don't think we've forgotten
everything that you've done.
We are not teaming up
with this guy.
Let's get one thing clear.
I ain't on your team.
I don't care about you, your
crew, or your little family.
I'm here for Cipher.
What are you gonna do, apply for a job?
Head Asshole?
You know, I think that tight T-shirt's
cutting off the circulation to your brain.
You should get a bigger size.
Cipher came to me first. Wanted
me to steal Nightshade for her.
When I said no, she
went after my brother.
Ah, yes, brother Owen.
Who could forget him, huh?
Former hell-raiser
and current guest
at a nasty
little black site prison.
Cipher corrupted him
and left him for dead.
So, if I get a shot
to take her down,
believe me, Flex, I'm taking it.
You're taking my boot right up
your ass, is what you're taking.
Guys, guys. The fastest way to
find Cipher is through Toretto.
Now, aside from myself, there's
only two men in the world
that have ever managed to actually
track him down with any success.
And guess what. They' re both
standing in front of me right now.
So, like it or not, you two
are gonna work together.
You got that?
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Am I the only one seeing this?
Oh, this ought to be good.
(MUMBLES)
Use God's Eye.
We put our lives on the line,
running around the world trying
to figure this thing out.
It can find anybody, right?
Let's use it to find Dom.
Roman, that is a great idea.
Did you hear that?
"Great idea."
No, no, no, don't tune it out.
Huh?
Mr. Nobody,
let's fire it up, huh?
TEJ: Got him.
He's in London.
Yeah.
(BEEPING)
RAMSEY: Wait. We've got
a second match in Hong Kong.
ROMAN: Beijing and Seoul.
TEJ: And Tokyo.
RAMSEY: And just about every
other major city on the planet.
MR. NOBODY: And so, God's Eye
was where we started.
But Cipher's already
created an evasion
that masks their location by pinging
random spots all over the globe,
but it was
a good thought, Roman.
So, she's made
my program obsolete.
And that, Ramsey,
is why you're here.
See, simple solutions aren't
gonna cut it here, slick.
Why you look at me
when you say that?
Wait a second. Wait, wait. Simple
solutions might just cut it.
You see, in order for God's Eye to
give off all these false pings,
means they have to be
using a FLEA relay.
Watch these two.
Which means it has a
decaying sync randomizer.
Which we can reverse.“
And track it back to the originating
source and find Dom's true location.
I'm telling you,
they got skills.
That was my idea.
That's what I was saying.
Remember in there?
All right, let's try this.
It's working.
Time you wanna check your manual and
start organizing a force response.
Let's get a hold of
our international assets...
He's still green.
Yeah, like fresh baby shit.
As soon as we have Toretto's
location, I want to mobilize.
Let's get a hold of
a better asshole.
No one respects you...
(IMITATES RADIO STATIC) Cover.
Get away from me.
All right, they're not in China.
Or Russia.
Europe's clear.
But this one's not going away.
(BEEPING)
This is interesting.
Why?
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Because that's here.
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(MAN COUGHING)
CIPHER: (ECHOING)
Did you all enjoy that?
Next-generation
concussion grenade.
It scrambles your senses. Don't
worry, it'll wear off in an hour.
(GROANING)
Probably.
Hello, Deckard.
Nice to see you again.
(LAUGHING) Look at this,
body's not even cold, Dom.
Your family's
already replacing you.
You chose the losing team.
I guess your brother
is smarter than you.
(DECKARD GRUNTING)
(BEEPING)
Smart move, embedding God's
Eye into the mainframe.
Irritating to make me have to come all
the way clown here to get it, but...
Let's go.
(ALL GROANING)
Dom!
You're gonna turn your back on family?
Just like that?
Let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HOBBS: You okay?
That wasn't him.
I don't know what
she's got on him,
but that wasn't Dom.
Brian would know what to do.
No!
We can't bring
Brian and Mia into this.
We agreed on that
ROMAN: I know.
DOM: Back there,
was that for her,
for me, or you?
And was it even necessary?
Necessary?
Nothing is necessary.
Everything is a choice.
And I simply made one.
But so did you.
You could've stopped me,
but you chose not to.
I wonder what Letty
thought about that.
The problem with putting
your foot on a tiger's neck
is you can never let it up.
I think I need to remind you
why you chose to be here.
(GASPS)
Elena.
ELENA: Dom?
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have come.
Nothing could have kept me away.
Now she has the three of us.
(BABY COOING)
Do you wanna see him?
See Papa?
(BABY GURGLING)
See Papa.
Papa.
(COOING)
When I realized I was pregnant,
you had just found out
Letty was alive.
So I decided when Letty and you
got back from your honeymoon,
I was going to tell you.
But then she took us
before I had the chance.
(COOS)
His name?
(CONTINUES COOING)
I call him Marcos.
But that's his middle name.
I thought his father should
give him his first name.
I'm sorry, Dom.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
ELENA: Whatever happens,
just save our son.
Your son.
CIPHER: Good visit?
I know. I know
what you're thinking.
I just let the guards go,
so there's only two
opponents in the room.
Rhodes has the gun, so
you'll take him out first.
I know you.
And then you're thinking,
Elena's a cop.
Maybe the two of you can
fight your way out of here.
(WHISPERS) So much
to think about.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Let me make it easier for you.
Do with it as you wish.
Have you heard of
Choice Theory, Dom?
There is a bunch of axioms,
but only two you really need
to concern yourself with.
One, the only person's behavior
we can control is our own.
And, two, the only thing we can truly
give another person is information.
So, let me give you some.
You see these cameras in here?
The moment you make a move,
highly-paid men with weapons
will make their way
into this room
with one very
specific instruction.
It's not to save me.
It's to kill your son.
Now, that's a lot of bullets,
and it only takes one
for you to lose everything.
So, I have to ask you,
because I know family
is so important to you.
Is that really a choice
you want to make?
Because I'm ready if you are.
If I pull this trigger,
and God knows I want to,
if I killed everyone
on this plane,
I still couldn't get in there.
'Cause of your two-man
fail-safe system.
Since I'm alone,
I got no choice!
I didn't think so.
You want to see the old Dom?
Watch.
(SOBBING)
Bitch.
Don't, don't.
Sweet dreams.
Please!
BODY: Damn it.
She wiped it all.
Took God's Eye.
That was the one thing
we could use to find them.
We lost everything.
What do you got, Princess?
Finding Toretto.
But I got a couple
of minutes to spare,
if you want me to send you
to the hospital. Again.
(CHUCKLES) Yo, Rules.
First off, that's not my name.
Little Nobody.
Don't call me that.
Oh, that's definitely sticking.
Great. Do me a favor
and tell Your Majesty over there
that we're gonna find Toretto.
We find Toretto
together as a team.
And when this is all over with,
I'm happy to slap that whisker
biscuit right off his face.
Wait a minute, guys, I think
Deckard's actually onto something.
How do you think Dom and Cipher
got into the country
without us knowing?
Ghost flights.
I thought untraceable aircraft was
all Internet conspiracy stuff.
MR. NOBODY: it's not.
Satellites and radar grids
all across the globe
shift like an ocean.
They've got channels
that open and close.
And theoretically'
if you know the right people
who know the right patterns...
You can fly right through the blind
spots completely undetected.
So you know where Dom is headed?
(LAPTOP BEEPS)
Yeah. New York.
(CHUCKLES)
You see there, Luke?
You guys are gonna
get along just great.
Which proves rule number two,
you never lose everything.
Fire up the chopper.
Well, guys' have a ball
in the Big Apple.
ROMAN: And why are we
traveling like this again?
TEA: Because Dom
took God's Eye,
so we need to stay
of! the grid.
ROMAN: But like this?
(ALL GRUNTING)
ROMAN: Look here, man.
Before I throw up in my mouth,
let me ask you,
what are we doing here?
That's a good question, Roman.
Let me show you.
Welcome to our new
base of operations.
No, seriously.
What is this place?
This is heaven.
It's the agency garage.
They call it the Toy Shop.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LITTLE NOBODY: This is where
we house every vehicle
seized from drug dealers
on the East Coast.
Now, Mr. Nobody said
that if we're gonna have a
chance at catching Dom,
we're gonna have
to be damn fast.
Figured this would help.
We got a tank.
750 horsepower,
6.6 liter,
V8 Duramax engine
with an M153 GROWS remotely
operated weapon station on top.
You didn't get this
from drug dealers.
LITTLE NOBODY: No. No, that, uh,
the United States Army lent me.
See, the Army's developing
machines like this
that soldiers can drive
from a mile away,
so they can stay safe and alive.
But, luckily, there's
a backup driver's seat
for those of us that like
to get more "hands on."
ROMAN: I'm sitting here
wondering this whole time,
will this thing fit in valet
at Cheesecake Factory?
No one is getting
"hands on."
She doesn't go on city streets.
Wow. I'm in love.
Again, no, no.
That's a million-dollar
show car.
The point is to not
draw attention.
It's reverse psychology.
Dom would never see it coming.
It's neon orange.
The International Space
Station would see it coming.
Go choose anything
less conspicuous.
ROMAN: No, no, no.
Calipers are my...
This is ridiculous.
Not happening.
Hey, my man, you can put
that down rig ht there.
This is a gift, a real gift.
I know what you're doing.
(LAUGHS)
I like your beard.
You're Blanta.
Black Santa?
No, I'm serious.
Put it down right there.
What are you doing?
Engine's misfiring.
I gotta check it out.
No, that's not part of
the plan, Dom.
DOM: Clearly.
But unless you want the
engine to seize on the job...
You have five minutes.
(MOUTHING) Five minutes.
I want another visual.
I got an ATM.
I don't like this.
I want to see Toretto.
There are no more cameras.
Then find something!
Punch in on
something reflective.
A car mirror, anything.
Do you know who I am?
It's why I'm here.
Do you know what I'm capable of?
I'll give you until
I finish me cuppa.
And I'm fucking thirsty.
I've got limited time,
so I won't take up
too much of yours.
Oh, no.
No, you've already taken everything
I have of value, Mr. Toretto.
What more could
you possibly want?
To give you something back.
Talk to me.
Somethings not right here.
First time I saw my son was
behind a bulletproof glass.
When he reached for me,
I couldn't hold him.
It's the worst pain I ever felt.
I know you know exactly
how that feels.
Maybe we could change that
Now, why do I think
you're about to suggest something
really dodgy, Mr. Toretto?
It's why I'm here.
Jesus, punch in on something. I'm not
liking this. Somethings not right.
Rhodes, you close?
RHODES: Yeah.
CIPHER: Go.
The delivery truck's moving.
(MOUTHING) I know.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER RADIO)
HOBBS:
"Captain Deckard Shaw
"distinguished himself
by acts of gallantry
“at the risk of his life above
and beyond the call of duty.
“His bold actions saved the lives
of hostages and his teammates.
"Recommendation: Victoria Cross."
Highest honor the British
government has ever given
to a traitor.
Something about this whole thing
that just doesn't add up to me.
Well, that would be
the same kind of funny math
that says a DSS agent who has a
Silver Star for valor stole an EMP.
Sound familiar, huh?
You want to give me a hand?
On three?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You know what, Twinkle Toes?
In another life, I bet me and you
could've done some serious damage.
Yeah, we could've.
Yeah.
Shame I'm gonna have to bounce
your head off the fender
when this is all over.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Ah, well, with
all due respect, Captain,
when this whole thing is over,
we're gonna find a location,
and I'm gonna knock your teeth
so far down your throat,
you're gonna stick a toothbrush
right up your ass to brush them.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Give me God's Eye.
God's Eye, active.
Good.
Let's find us a Russian.
I spy with my little eye,
a Minister of Defense.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Upload those coordinates
to Dom's nav.
Copy that.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
He's in the third car.
(OVER EARPIECE)
It's a Guard Class limousine.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Where's my team?
Where's his team?
There's no sign of them yet.
They're off the grid.
They' re probably just
bunkered down somewhere.
DOM: We're closing in on 'em.
You guys ready?
CIPHER: One thing
I can guarantee, Dom,
no one's ready for this.
I want every chip with a zero-day
exploit in a two-mile radius
around that motorcade now.
There's over a thousand of them.
Hack 'em all.
(ENGINE STARTS)
It's zombie time.
I'd buckle up if I were you.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Hmm?
WOMAN: (YELLS)
What are you doing?
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(HORNS BLARING)
GOD'S EYE TECH:
Safety sensors overridden.
Thank you.
(ENGINE STARTS)
MAN: Whoa.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(WOMAN SHRIEKING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(YELLS AND GROANS)
Hey!
Target the motorcade.
And here they come.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Ouch.
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
GOD'S EYE TECH: (IN ENGLISH)
Police escort down.
Take out the lead
and follow cars.
(ENGINES STARTING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
GOD'S EYE TECH:
Two more down.
They're still under warranty.
(IN RUSSIAN)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
OFFICER: (OVER RADIO) We got an
army of cars driving themselves!
Send backup, send SWAT!
I don't care if you send
the goddamn Boy Scouts,
just send 'em some help!
Now, that's Dom.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
GOD'S EYE TECH: The motorcade
just turned on Seventh.
CIPHER: Perfect.
Make it rain.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Ah!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Target immobilized.
You're up, Dom.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(BOTH GRUNT)
DOM: (IN ENGLISH)
Give me the case.
(IN RUSSIAN)
(TAPPING)
(PANTING)
(RUSSIAN SECRET SERVICE AGENT PANTING)
(IN ENGLISH) Good work, Dom.
Meet you at the pickup.
(TIRES SCREECH)
DOM: I think I know
where my team's at.
Where?
Right in front of me.
This is on you.
Get out of there, Dom.
RAMSEY: (OVER RADIO)
Guys, I know why Dom's here.
Police scanners are saying
he stole a nuclear football.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
It's over, Toretto.
Get your ass outta the car now.
(ENGINE REWING)
So, that's how
you wanna play this?
Let's play-
Don't do this, Dom.
He's going for it!
What are you doing?
It's a trap!
Damn it!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
TEJ: Now I know
what it feels like
to be every cop ever chasing us!
I'm gonna get a little closer.
I'm gonna PIT him.
Oh, so, you just gonna PIT Dom?
Little Nobody has
clearly lost his little mind.
I'm on him.
Easy. Work together.
(MEN YELLING)
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, sh...
I'll take the shortcut!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
RAMSEY: Look out!
Watch those people!
Big Sexy comin' through!
Not this time, Dom.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Watch the drag
or the line will snap!
(GRUNTING)
Stretch him out!
Hold him!
(GRUNTS)
He's gotta have about 2,000
horsepower in that thing.
Try 3,000!
Try five.
Get out of there.
I'm working on it.
CIPHER:
Stop working on it and do it.
No, no, no, this my Bentley!
(YELLING)
No! No!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Get that case and run.
(GRUNTS)
Move.
They thought this was
gonna be a street fight.
What are you
waiting for, Toretto?
(GUNSHOTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
No!
(SIREN WAILING)
(SIGHS)
Letty, stop!
What are you gonna do?
(GASPS)
I don't know why you're doing
this, but I know one thing.
You love me.
And you are not gonna shoot me.
You should've given him the
case, 'cause I won't chase you.
Okay.
I will just take it
from a dead girl.
DOM:
You willing to die for it?
Let's go, then.
HOBBS: Anything?
They're gone.
And DOD confirmed it
was a nuclear football.
He's got an EMP and
nuclear launch codes.
I don't know what it is, but they're
building towards something.
Deckard?
LITTLE NOBODY:
He didn't make it.
(GRUNTS)
CIPHER: (OVER INTERCOM)
I'm disappointed in you, Dom.
When push came to shove,
you were gonna let Letty
just walk away with the codes.
You got the codes!
Rhodes got the codes.
You made the choice
to let her go.
And now I have to
make one of my own.
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(WHISPERING) They are adorable
little things, aren't they?
God, I hope I don't hurt him.
Look, psychotic, I did exactly
what you asked me to do.
Don't do this.
This is your doing.
My doing?
BABY TORETTO: (BABBLING)
Da-dada.
Dada.
Da-da.
Please don't hurt him,
I'm begging you.
I don't want you to beg.
I want you to learn.
Learn what?
I understand why you did what you did.
I really do.
Da-da.
But it was the wrong choice.
This is the consequence of that.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING) No!
No! No!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
Save your son!
No!
(GUNSHOTS)
(CRYING)
(SHUSHING)
(EXHALES)
Can you pull up the footage
from the guy in the alley?
Traffic cams.
I got you.
I knew it.
I recognize that guy.
That's Connor Rhodes.
I met him when I was working
with Shaw's brother.
He wanted us to get
the Nightshade device for him.
Connor Rhodes.
He's also linked to somebody
I'd quite like to forget.
It's Mose Jakande.
Warlord who tried
to get God's Eye.
Which means that's twice that Dom
has messed up Cipher's business.
Everything you're
feeling right now,
this rage, a sense of
loss, it's not real.
Ifs a survival instinct
wired deep into our brains
to ensure continuation
of the species.
When early man would
visit a watering hole,
if they didn't
watch their child,
and it got snatched
by a crocodile,
our brains would create a painful
but instructional memory,
so it would never happen again.
This idea of "family"
that is so core with you,
that rules your world,
it's a biological lie.
You don't have to accept it.
I don't.
Did you really think you could
destroy two of my teams
without any repercussions?
I wouldn't have even looked your
way if you hadn't done that.
You didn't even know
you had a kid.
You can thank me for that and start
doing the job I'm asking you to do.
Help you start a war.
Is that what you think I want?
That's so limited.
I didn't take that football
to start a war
any more than I took your
son to start a family.
Taking your son
got me the codes.
The codes will get me the nukes
and the nukes
will get me what I want
today, tomorrow,
and every day after that.
And what's that?
Accountability.
The second I fire off
one of those nukes,
I put the superpowers
of this world on notice that,
when they cross the line,
I'm gonna be there
to hold them responsible.
Because the truth is, Dom,
to the world out there,
I am the crocodile
at the watering hole.
We've got one last job to do.
DOM: Cipher.
If I were you, I'd kiss my son.
Because whether you value
it or not, all of this,
your plane,
your security, and you,
are still on this earth
because of him.
RAMSEY: The problem we've had with tracking
Cipher is there's nothing to trace.
But now,
we have Rhodes' information.
And we're getting
snapshots of his data
before it's
scrubbed off the net.
That looks like somebody's
bank account,
so why don't we just go ahead...
It's a longitude.
Given the fact that
Dom hit a Russian motorcade,
it's safe to say it's Russia.
Go ahead and bring up the map.
Good. Let's start here
and run the possibilities.
Yalta, Poltava...
it's like they just
threw letters together.
Kronyurt.
MR. NOBODY: It's "Vladovin."
What are you doing here?
What?
Told you I was gonna check
in on you from time to time
to see how you were doin'.
By the way, not so hot.
But there's nothing
in Vladovin. It's just ice.
That's funny.
Could've sworn there was a
secret Russian naval base
where they retrofitted
Cold War submarines.
Well, technically,
it's not Russian anymore.
The base was taken over
by a terror group of military
separatists about a month ago,
and the Russians
haven't taken it back yet,
so there is a little
window of opportunity here.
Russian submarines.
Nuclear football.
It sounds like everything we do,
our legs gonna be blown off.
It sounds like you still number
11 on the list. (CHUCKLES)
It sounds like you've changed
since your little punk-ass
facial hairs done came in.
Guys. Guys.
Hey, we gotta call this in.
All the way up the chain.
That's good thinking, champ,
except unfortunately,
the Russian Minister of Defense
got himself involved in a little
incident on US territory,
and the two governments aren't
talking to each other for a while.
By the time they do,
it'll be too late.
So, any other suggestions?
HOBBS: Yeah. I got one.
How about we just
stop them ourselves?
You're talking about
a Russian military base.
Separatist.
Whatever.
It's suicide.
It's stopping World War Ill.
What's it gonna be, rook?
You gonna close your
eyes on this one, too?
Pray that
the apocalypse doesn't come
knocking on your
mama's front door?
Or, are you gonna
saddle up, be a man,
and save the entire
goddamn world?
You know,
I think I figured it out.
What's that?
Rule number three.
Which is?
There are no rules.
(MR. NOBODY LAUGHS)
What'd I tell you, Luke?
I knew he'd get it in three.
LITTLE NOBODY: Aerial
transport leaves in an hour.
Take whatever vehicle you want.
All bets are off.
All bets are off?
Bets are off?
Do svidanya!
Letty, I don't like
telling you this one bit.
But the game's changed.
Before, we were just trying to catch
Dom, but now, after all this,
I want you to know,
if I have to,
I'm gonna put him down.
Then you might have
to take us both down.
ROMAN: I'm freezing, man.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
This ain't for me.
I come from a different
kind of lifestyle, brah.
Ladies know me. They know
where I'm at with it.
I tried to take a piss, I
didn't even recognize myself.
Man, that's entirely
too much information.
I'm just sayin'.
Well, one thing's for sure.
Dom's gotta be either working
with them or making a trade,
because no one
would be this insane
to hit this place
without a damn army.
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
HOBBS: Speak of the devil.
All right, Dom, you're one step
closer to that family reunion.
400 meters to base.
Prep the EMP. Let's take
these defenses down.
(ENGINE REWING)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Gates are open.
Let's get this party started.
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
EMP is recharging.
How long?
Sixty seconds.
All right, Dom, you have one
pulse left in that EMP.
That sub is heavily insulated.
You're gonna need to be right
underneath it for this thing to work.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(ALARMS BLARING)
CIPHER: Yes!
Two birds with one stone.
SUPER JET TECH:
We've got control of the sub.
Dom, we are good.
Head over to the rendezvous.
Okay, Matty, let's take
this baby for a spin.
TEJ: Damn!
I think Cipher just rebooted that
sub to slave its command system.
What the hell
is he talking about?
In layman's terms, she just
carjacked a submarine.
We can't let it get away.
There's the control room.
If you can get me
into that wheelhouse,
I can tap the network
and counter-hack Cipher.
Keep it from
lowering into the water.
No, what we need to do
is get me on that sub.
I find the weapons room
and I can pull the launch chip
before she can fire
any of those nukes.
That is too crazy.
What you're saying
is too dangerous.
We'll do both.
Knock, knock.
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Five vehicles
just breached the base.
They just don't give up,
do they?
HOBBS: All right, let's haul ass, team.
Double time, double time!
(SOLDIERS YELLING IN RUSSIAN)
(YELLING)
Letty, let's roll!
(GROANS)
Go! Go, go, go!
CIPHER: Change of plans, Dom.
I'm sending you new coordinates.
Head there immediately.
I'm done. I want my son.
I'll tell you when you're done.
Your team is in play.
Now, meet Rhodes and
follow my instruction.
(PANTING)
I've got you covered! Go!
Move, move!
Get outta here! Go, go, go!
(PANTING)
Okay.
How do you like this?
(ENGINE POWERING DOWN)
SUPER JET TECH:
Remote link has been severed.
CIPHER:
I'll take care of this.
Hi, Ramsey.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
RAMSEY:
She's regained control.
Damn it. She's good.
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
TECH: They're entering
the weapons room.
Oh, that's cute.
LITTLE NOBODY:
(EXCLAIMS) Pull! Pull!
Roman, Roman!
We gotta find the chip, go!
Oh, she's slick.
Gonna have to do
better than that, though.
Okay, now you're
starting to piss me off.
(GRUNTING)
(MAN YELLING)
Ramsey, how much time
we talkin' here?
You're smart,
but not smart enough.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
She's locked me out.
(GRUNTING)
Tej, I can't stop her. You're
gonna have to pull that chip.
I can't! This thing's
gone into attack mode!
The door's not gonna open
until you pull the chip!
Tej, we got no idea what the
hell we're looking for.
I got it!
(ALARM BLARING)
What in the hell
are you guys doin'?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me, okay?
It'll be labeled
"Guidance Go."
Guidance Go, Guidance Go...
Okay, I got somethin'.
What?
It says...
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Do you understand that?
(GROANING)
(MAN LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
(SPLATTERING)
(PANTING)
Wow. Nasty.
Hmm.
Quite a show.
We're arming the nuke.
(POWERING UP)
TEJ: (OVER RADIO)
Nuke's going hot!
She's tryin' to fire this thing!
Roger that.
We're moving out.
HOBBS: (OVER RADIO)
Disable the nukes!
Roman, what are you seeing?
Come on, talk to me.
I don't see shit.
I'm holding on!
(RUMBLING)
And we have a countdown.
(ALARM BLARING)
What the hell is goin' on, man?
We're about to launch a nuclear
missile, is what the hell is goin' on!
Pull me damn chip!
(PANTING)
Countdown, countdown!
Look for a countdown!
What countdown?
The missiles need to
activate to launch.
The countdown timer
won't be in Russian.
The countdown...
Let's show the world
what we've got.
ROMAN: No, no, no!
Don't press that!
I got it.
Somethings wrong.
It won't launch.
Get that sub outta there.
Now!
LITTLE NOBODY:
Move your ass, Roman!
(PANTING)
You all right?
There's nothing all right
about any of this!
Let's go!
What about the missiles?
We got the chip.
No nukes for her.
Hell' yeah.
Let's roll.
Guys, we got company.
A lot of company!
All right, team,
here's the plan.
There's a sea lock
at the opening of the bay.
We get there firs!
And close it,
we can stop the submarine
from escaping into open water
and disappearing forever.
I've got the location.
It's 10 miles southwest.
Ten miles? We're not gonna
make it ten seconds!
(GUNFIRE)
Ah!
No, no, no!
This is not good!
What's the matter, Roman?
Forgot your snow tires?
ROMAN: Whoa!
You lovin' that Lambo now?
ROMAN: Whoa! Ah!
(ROMAN EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMING)
CIPHER:
All right, everyone.
We'll deal with
that launch chip later.
Right now, I want that sub in deep
water where no one can find it.
Find me the fastest
route out of that bay.
Copy that.
Why are they shootin' at me?
Maybe 'cause you're in an orange
Lamborghini, I don't know.
Shut up, Te]!
Dom...
(OVER EARPIECE) Do you really
wanna put that' car in gear?
Do it.
Huh?
I didn't think so.
They're heading
for the sea lock.
They're trying to
trap the sub in the bay.
I should have taken care
of this a long time ago.
Rhodes, take his team out.
I'm on it.
Roman, get in front of me!
Okay, y'all wanna play rough?
Now it's my turn.
Yeah, baby! (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
Guys, we got snowmobiles
on the right.
They're gonna flank us!
No, they ain't!
Oh, shit!
(BEEPING)
Tej!
Roman, hold tight,
I'm on the way!
I don't wanna
go swimmin'! No!
Really, Tej?
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, shit!
Roman, grab your door!
ROMAN: Tej!
TEA: Grab the door, Roman!
ROMAN: It's so cold!
Shit!
Oh, shit!
ROMAN: Whoa!
Whoo!
Yeah!
What is going on?
Roman, hang on!
Tej!
Get me off of this thing!
Come on!
Argh!
All right.
I've had enough of this shit!
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(ALL GROANING)
Number 11, my ass!
Yo, shrinkage! We got a sub to catch.
Get in!
What?
Depressurization alert
in the cargo hold.
Drop it to 10,000 feet.
I know how much
these people mean to you.
So I will let you pick
the first target.
I don't pick a target
from a mile away.
I stand face to face
and look 'em dead in the eye.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
The wife it is.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Nice plane.
I'm gonna enjoy having this.
Hey, don't go gettin' any ideas.
You and planes
don't have a good history.
No shit.
Okay, let's go, Scarface.
These assholes
ain't gonna kill themselves.
Pull up surveillance right now.
(COMPUTER TRILLS)
Surprise.
You're supposed to be dead.
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
We have a security breach in the
cargo hold. Take care of it now.
(GASPS)
Jesus, Mum. You're supposed
to avoid the nerves.
Oh, shut up.
Don't be such a baby.
Get to the pilot.
He's got the second key.
Wait for my signal.
Give Cipher my regards.
Did Toretto hold up
his end of the deal?
MRS. SHAW: He gave us
this little thing here.
No, no, no. Don't touch.
You can track Cipher with this,
but you can't do this on your own.
There's gotta be two of ya.
Fine. I've got contacts.
No, you're gonna
take your brother.
Oh, dear...
Yes.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Toretto knows where he is.
He's got this thing.
It can see everything.
It's like... It's called the
Devil's Bum Hole or something.
It's called the God's Eye.
Yeah, well, whatever.
(GRUNTING)
There's no way I'm
using Owen, all right?
He's a lost cause.
He's your brother, Decks.
He's my son.
He's our family.
And our family don't die
in bloody cages. (CRYING)
How can you talk like that about Owen?
I can't believe you.
You've gone and upset me. You've
really upset your mother.
Call yourself a brother?
You're...
Look, come here...
Mum. Okay, okay.
Every time.
Owen.
In position.
Go.
I'm in.
(PANTING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
DECKARD:
I've got the package, Toretto.
All 12 pounds of him.
Ah.
Dada. Dada.
(BULLET RICOCHETS)
(BOTH GASP)
You made me miss my shot.
What you think you're doing?
Looking at you dead in the eye.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GAGGING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(NECK SNAPS)
That was for Elena.
Rhodes.
DOM: He's no longer with us.
Rhodes picked the wrong target.
Congratulations, Dom.
You just killed your son.
You're wrong.
I just saved him.
And you just look your foot
off the tiger's neck.
All right, governor,
it's gonna get noisy.
This is for your ears.
(BEEPS)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
Good?
(COOS)
Let's go.
No! Stop him! Do not let
him get off this plane!
LITTLE NOBODY:
We got another problem.
That truck's got enough
missiles to take us all out.
Then don't give 'em a target.
Everybody, get in front of us,
line up, and we'll take the hit.
What? I need to
switch cars right now!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Roman, here comes the bad part.
What?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(WHOOPS)
Hang in there, guys.
We're almost to the lock.
Ifs easy for you to say
when your ass ain't on fire.
All right, little man,
this might be a little scary,
but it's gonna be a lot of fun.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
How's the music, good?
Ah.
(ALL GROANING)
They're locking on.
Sorry, guys,
I got no tricks left.
What do we do now?
TEA: We start prayin'!
Hell, yeah!
There's Dom!
What, is this guy
on our side now?
Who the hell cares?
He just saved our ass!
Good to be riding
with you again, man.
(CHUCKLES)
Toretto just
cleared the way for them.
Someone, give me something!
Torpedoes are ready.
Then launch them!
Shit.
Take the wheel!
I ain't takin' shit!
Where you goin'?
(GROANS)
This is crazy!
HOBBS: Speed up!
Left and back!
What?
Turn the goddamn wheel
to the left really quickly!
Boom, baby!
(MEN GRUNTING)
Goin' for a ride.
Back in a sec.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Where's that smile?
Ah.
There it is.
You were gonna shoot a baby?
You sick bastard.
You're not gonna wanna see this.
(GRUNTING)
(SNIFFS)
Is that you or him?
Him. Good.
The torpedoes missed.
They're gonna reach the lock
before the sub does.
The hell they are.
Get ready for this.
Oh, shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck.
(LAUGHING)
It's right under us!
Get out the way!
(GRUNTING)
Get us out of here!
Why are you always yelling?
This bitch is crazy!
Lookout!
(GASPS)
(YELLS)
That's not good.
Please tell me there's
nothing to worry about!
We got this.
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING)
That's my girl.
The sub's too close. We ain't
making it to the gate in time.
We're just going
to let it get away?
Not if I know Dom.
You lose, Dom.
I destroyed two of your teams.
I killed your
red-headed boyfriend.
And I put two killers
on your untraceable plane.
You lost the minute
you interrupted my honeymoon.
Now guess who I'm coming for.
Put a heatseeker on him now.
(SHOUTS) Now!
Fire!
That's a goddamn
heatseeker coming at us!
Peel off!
Head to the shore!
(BEEPING)
(ENGINE REWING)
All right.
Come and get it.
No, no, no.
Dive! Dive!
This...
This is for my son.
(GASPS)
Dom!
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(MAN GROANS)
You're out of bullets, Deckard.
Not like I'm gonna need a gun
to take care of you.
How did you find me?
DOM: You want to see
the old Dom?
(BEEPING)
Watch.
Resourceful.
You have a lot to
answer for, Cipher.
What you've put
my family through.
My mother.
I'm gonna make sure
that never happens again.
To anyone.
There is only one flaw
in your plan.
What's that?
Only one of us has a parachute.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(COOING)
Told you this would be fun.
Time to land, boys.
You know I never
left you, Letty.
I know.
And you know I never will.
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING)
I have so much to tell you.
Yeah, you do. And you can
start with that bitch.
Now, that's Dominic Toretto.
Hey, Dom!
I'm just throwin' it out there,
we need to get up outta here
'cause there's all kinda nuclearism
happening under this ice.
Relax. Without the trigger
chips, those nukes are harmless.
Okay. So we good, then.
Let me go on and get
my young selfie levels up.
You realize this is
classified, right'?
Not today.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
Unbelievable.
All right, can we get up outta here, now?
I'm freezin'!
It's okay.
Don't worry.
He's gonna be here soon.
ROMAN: I get it.
Y'all got a lot in common.
Computer hacks, God's Eye,
geeks, nerd... You know.
But we got a lot in common,
too, right?
Like what?
We walk in the room
and we're oozin' sex appeal.
Me and you,
hip to hip, is a problem.
I'm askin' a real
question right now.
Is it gonna be
Revenge of the Nerds
or The Dark Knight? Huh'?
To be honest,
I like both of you.
(ROMAN AND TEJ EXCLAIMING)
But just before
we get into all of that,
let me ask you one question.
You can ask me anything.
Anything.
What's my last name?
When you guys figure it out, then,
I guess you can let me know.
It's gonna be Parker. That's
all that really matters.
ROMAN: Jones.
TEJ: Mrs. Parker.
Right?
Hey, Mrs. Parker...
LETTY: Hey.
Letty.
I wanted to thank you.
No need.
Well...
Ciphers still on the loose. There's
been some reports she's in Athens,
but she won't be nuking
any cities anytime soon.
Thanks to you guys.
So, I got you a party favor.
(MR. NOBODY LAUGHS)
HOBBS: This can't be good.
Your record's been cleared.
Full reinstatement.
You've got your job back.
That is, if you want it.
If I want?
Mmm-hmm.
(LAUGHS)
You know, after 16 years, I figure
it's time for a little break.
Wow.
Daddy's swim' home.
(LAUGHS)
Nobody.
Keep in touch.
Ah. Hang on a second.
This could be interesting.
(SIGHS) What made
you think I'd do it?
Brotherhood.
I saw that look you gave Cipher,
knew you wanted revenge.
Glad I did it.
I can't believe
you went to see my mother.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
All this fuss over you.
(COOING)
Yes.
Elena, I promised
to keep our son safe.
And now, he always will be.
I wanna introduce you to the most
important person in my universe.
One who never gave up on me.
He's beautiful.
DOM: You've heard me say
that you never turn
your back on family,
and I wanna thank you all for
never turning your back on me.
You wanna meet them?
All right.
Everyone,
meet Brian.
(LAUGHTER, APPLAUSE)
(COOING)
HOBBS: To Brian!
ROMAN: Welcome
to the family, Brian.
Okay, I guess
it's my turn to say grace.
We thank you
for giving us family.
We sit here in praise. Thank you
for giving us the strength...
Improved & Synced by BanglarBagh