10-38 on Dayton Blvd. At
Second Street intersection.
- Unit en route.
- [SCOFFS]
Routine traffic stop downtown? Oh, yeah.
Looks like it was a good day
to pull monitor duty, Chester P.
- [LAUGHS]
- [STOMACH GROWLS]
Ooh... snack time.
[PEACEFUL MUSIC]
[IMITATES WHOOSHING]
[LAUGHS]
Damn.
I was supposed to make
the egg salad this morning.
Grandma Runk is gonna be epically mad.
Now I got nada for lunch.
Although...
legally, I am entitled to
a break every four hours,
and it's only gonna take
me, like, four minutes,
'cause the kitchen's
just right down the hall.
Then again, that is time enough
for a nuclear meltdown
and an alien invasion in this town.
- So...
- Hey, Chuck.
Oh! What up, A?
[LAUGHS] I thought you'd be working.
I was, and then I remembered
it's Wednesday, and that
place I told you about
at last week's D&D game, Hershfield's,
today is when they have
their amazing chicken
parmesan sandwiches,
so I thought, it's lunchtime!
Why not surprise you with a treat?
Wow, thanks.
I guess I'm lunch-date-worthy now, huh?
- [LAUGHS]
- Chuck, you are date-worthy
in all the major categories.
I am?
Yeah, definitely...
I mean, that's... that's
good... That's good to... know.
You know? And I, too, think that you
are also, um,
what you just... like, worthy
of what you just said a second ago.
[ALARM BLARING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Holy Alice H. Parker.
Kay, we got a mugging in
progress off Route 119.
And a carjacking at the
Edwards Center parking lot.
And a holdup at Jitters.
And they're all happening right now?
Don't worry, guys. Already on it.
Uh, all of it, boss?
[HEROIC MUSIC]
[WHOOSHES]
[CAR ALARM WAILING]
You heard me!
I want everything in the register
and a triple-shot latte with oat milk!
Not soy!
♪
Think these guys could use
some help finding their cells.
- [APPLAUSE]
- Uh, thanks, Flash.
Yeah.
What's going on out here?
I didn't do nothin'.
- I wanna see my lawyer.
- Yeah.
What they said. And hey!
Any chance Flash brought
that latte I ordered?
Officers, take these
gentlemen to holding, please.
[SCOFFS] Ow.
Captain, hey.
Staff meeting's canceled, Allen.
For the record, you'd have been late.
Sorry, I was just... I got caught up
with a little blood spatter analysis.
But it looks like you've
had a busy morning.
Yeah, and it's about to turn
into a busy afternoon,
evening, and night,
thanks to this generous donation
from the Scarlet Speedster.
Wha... but the Flash caught those guys.
That's a good thing, right?
How can I press charges
when I don't know what
crimes were committed,
how they were done, and where?
Ferg, that file's on my
desk. I'll be right back.
And it's not like we can just
call up the Flash and ask.
Yeah, like on a Flash phone or...
Yeah. That's a terrible name.
Yeah.
But Captain, CCPD's never had
a line to the Flash before.
Yeah, but for once, I
would like to feel like
the Flash and law enforcement
are on the same page,
instead of us just
always playing catch-up.
But since that's not happening,
cancel any plans you have for tonight.
We've got a lot of legwork to do.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪
[WHISPERING] You're welcome.
- [HEROIC MUSIC]
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Sounds like Kramer has a point.
Look, maybe I could do a better job
communicating when I'm
dropping off criminals,
but giving CCPD a
direct line to the Flash?
You don't really think
that's necessary, do you?
I don't know, Barr, when I was captain,
I had a direct line to the Flash.
And, I mean, me too.
When I was district attorney,
if I had a question on a case,
all I ever had to do was
call you and get the details.
That's because you're family.
Which she is not, and I get that,
but what she and I went through
when we were tracking down Creyke...
I... I trust her with my life.
Maybe you should consider
letting her in a bit more.
Give her one of the alert apps
that we all have on our phones.
Joe, look, I get it. She's a good cop.
She's a great captain.
When I first got my speed,
I needed a lot of help,
not just from Caitlin and Cisco,
but from you and everybody at CCPD.
- But now...
- Now you've leveled up.
Yeah.
Which means I can find other ways
to solve Kramer's Flash problem,
like doing extra CSI work
to collect what she
needs for processing.
I mean, that'll ease the
burden for her, right?
- It sounds like it.
- Yeah.
And I get how keeping
church and state separated
is the easiest choice,
but I also know Kramer,
and if she's asking
for a line to the Flash,
she probably has a good reason.
Just sayin'.
Maybe you wanna think about it
before you decide what to do, Barr.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[YELLING] What up, party people?
It's your boy Chester P,
and I'm ready to rock your world
with knowledge for free!
[IMITATING ECHOING] Free! Free! Free!
Hey, today, we have a self-flying drone
based off of an AI algorithm
created by yours truly.
I'm gonna upload the specs online,
'cause here at the Runkyard,
we keep tech openly sourced and classy.
All right, how is this even possible?
I've silenced my phone,
I've turned off all the notifications,
and look at what keeps popping up.
Are those all from Frost and Mark?
Oh, you mean my sister
and her ex-con boyfriend?
Yes, they are. Look
at what they're doing.
Looks cool.
No, it looks dangerous!
Hey, hey, Caitlin.
Do you mind just taking a
wee little step to the right?
[LAUGHS]
- Are you livestreaming?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
WookieLover77 says, "Who's the girl?
Her sister seems cooler"?
Okay, that's it for today.
Smash that like button. [LAUGHS]
[COMPUTER CHIMES]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm just so annoyed.
Mark keeps taking Frost
on all these ridiculous dates.
Well, maybe tonight will distract you.
Don't you have a date too?
Yes. Yeah, Marcus is taking me
to the Spanish Hamper.
How'd he get you guys a reservation
for the hottest place in town?
That's impressive.
Is it turning serious?
I mean, he's really nice,
and I like nice, so...
that's nice. It's nice.
Oh, man, I can see it now.
He doesn't know we're on Team Flash.
But soon, you and Marcus
are gonna fall in love,
and then he's gonna join us for, like,
some crazy adventure, then boom!
He's on the team.
Hey, hey, maybe he'll learn
how to control plants.
It's their third date, Chuck,
so maybe just slow your roll.
Right, right. Reel it... reel it back.
Yeah, speaking of, I
should go get ready.
Night, guys.
- Have fun.
- Bye-bye.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Fancy date night.
- Sounds expensive.
- Yeah, right?
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
Could be fun, though.
♪
- Uh, I gotta type things.
- Uh, yeah, I have to go write.
- Algorithms and such.
- Article.
Mm-hmm.
- Oh, that's a typo.
- Huh?
- No, I was just...
- Oh.
Thinkin' out loud.
[SIGHS]
♪
Hey, Captain, you got a sec?
- I'm on my way to processing.
- These will come in handy.
I cross-referenced the
911 calls from this morning
with the description of the
perps the Flash brought in.
Then I hit the crime scenes...
Fingerprints, security footage,
Korber even interviewed witnesses.
So this should be everything you need
- to wrap up these cases.
- Wow.
- I appreciate the hustle, Allen.
- Yeah.
Just wish it was more
than a Band-Aid on a bullet wound.
Well, you have more than enough
to charge all three suspects.
What about the suspects the
Flash drops off tomorrow?
Or the day after that?
Respectfully, Captain,
I mean, this is the way
we've done things the past seven years
ever since the Flash showed up.
You know, the system works.
From your perspective,
but there are things you
don't need to worry about
as a forensic scientist that
I need to consider as captain.
I understand that, but, you know,
the Flash is just
trying to help this city.
And he does, all the time.
But together, we could
help it even more.
Humans and meta-humans alike.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
- Now, if you'll excuse me.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Oh...
♪
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Time to get to work.
♪
[BOTH SIGH HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
What the hell?
What are these?
They're meta-dampening bracelets.
I've seen these before.
Wakey, wakey, ladies and gents in blue.
Folks call me Goldface.
That's 'cause if it's made of gold,
it's mine to control,
from your dental fillings
to the 0.35 grams of
gold in your cell phones.
Don't even bother
trying to phone a friend,
'cause we knocked out the
nearest cell phone tower.
But if anyone does come calling,
they'll find a couple of
Central City's finest outside
telling them there's a gas leak.
♪
What are you doing? What are you... hey.
Goldface, this is my precinct.
You have a problem,
you take it up with me.
Let my officers go.
[SCOFFS]
Ah...
if it isn't the famous Kristen Kramer.
Loved you on the "Citizentopia" podcast.
- Very inspiring.
- Thanks.
Now, Captain, I'm guessing
you wanna play hero.
Let me let my man Carver here show you
what happens if anyone gets out of line.
[WHISTLES]
Now, you may have all
noticed that you're sporting
a new piece of jewelry.
Well, since Captain Mimic
here outed herself as a meta,
I figured she may not
be the only one of you.
But these bracelets, they
don't just dampen powers.
They also do this.
[DEVICES BEEPING]
[EXPLOSION BOOMS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
You feeling me now, Captain?
Hold on. Don't I know you?
You're that rat that
cost me the organ printer!
The chemist!
Yes. Um, yeah.
Look, I was on a undercover assignment.
Look, why don't you just
tell us what it is you want?
Kay, nobody has to die tonight.
♪
You know my lady, Amunet Black?
Not only is she the finest female
this side of Mississippi,
but she's got some intel
that there are some very rare
and valuable items in your armory.
I want what's in there.
So I'ma go get it.
And if anyone tries anything...
We get the belt.
♪
Good memory, chemist.
Keep an eye on this one.
He smells like trouble.
♪
Seriously, Marcus, I am so sorry.
I cannot believe I made
a dinner reservation
- for next January.
- Please don't feel bad.
Last week at work, I
screwed up the blooming cycle
for the Selenicereus
grandiflorus I've been growing.
You should've seen all the pollen.
[LAUGHS] Thank you.
I mean, really, you're
just such a trooper.
This first round is on me.
This place is a little
seedier than I remember.
It's fun. Plus, they've got karaoke.
Next up, the Ice Pack!
- There's that.
- Yeah.
♪ You're as cold as ice ♪
♪ You're willing to sacrifice our love ♪
Hey. Way off-key, but they're committed.
[FOREIGNER'S "COLD AS ICE" PLAYING]
We need to leave.
Caity?
What a coinky-dink!
What are the two of you doing here?
We were just grabbing a casual drink,
but, um, it's too crowded in here.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, is
this the infamous Marcus,
as in Dr. Ficus?
Um... yes?
Holy crap.
Hey, you two are here.
Mark and I are here.
We should totally make
this a double date.
- Yes!
- Oh, no.
We'll let you get back to it.
Why? They've got great food here.
If you like to live dangerously.
- I don't.
- [LAUGHS]
You wanna stay, right?
We can workshop some plant-y ice puns.
Well, I've heard a lot about Frost.
It'd be nice to have a
person to go with the stories
[LAUGHTER] Whoa.
Great. Let's double-date.
[WHISPERING] I count three hostiles
guarding us here, two at the exits.
[WHISPERING] Yeah, and
Carver's with Goldface
in the armory.
We have the numbers to
take back the building...
except everyone on our side has
a bomb strapped to their wrist.
These things are ultra-sensitive.
Tamper with them, they'll blow.
Same for Goldface's belt.
We gotta do something.
Whatever it is, we gotta do it fast.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Cap, do you have any idea
what Goldface wants in the armory?
All I can tell you, Allen, is...
is if he gets in there,
things are gonna get a lot worse.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[EXPLOSIONS BOOMING]
♪
Open sesame.
According to Amunet's intel,
the target should be...
in there.
♪
I love my woman.
[SIGHS]
Not what you were expecting, boss?
Of course it's not. It's empty.
Go get Kramer!
And her little chemist too.
♪
Where the hell are they?
I don't know what you mean.
The meta-bullets. Remember, Captain?
The ones you had commissioned
for your task force.
One shot takes away any
meta's powers forever.
Am I ringing any bells?
That's what you're stealing?
That's what I'm selling.
The power to take down
any meta in this city,
including... say it
with me... the Flash...
♪
Well, that's gonna
bring me a lot of gold.
But those bullets aren't
where they're supposed to be.
Captain?
Any thoughts on that?
Yeah.
Those bullets belong to CCPD
for only the most severe emergencies.
Also, I'd die before betraying
the metas of this city
and putting them in any danger.
Hmm.
I'm willing to bet you'd
risk your own life, Captain,
but... [GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
How about this fool's?
♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[CHOKING]
Let him go.
Tell me where the meta-bullets
are hidden, Captain.
You have till three.
One.
Two.
I can help you.
Oh, yeah, chemist?
Like you helped me steal that printer?
The meta-bullets have trace
amounts of dark matter.
I've got a scanner in my lab.
Let me guess.
I let you go, you'll go get it
and bring it right back to me.
Allen, what are you doing?
I could adjust the scanner.
It'll find the bullets. They
have to be here somewhere.
♪
[GASPS]
When we first met, I knew
you couldn't be trusted.
PLOT TWIST: you're
not only untrustworthy,
you're a coward.
[SCOFFS] Watch Kramer.
I'm gonna take the chemist
here on a little field trip.
One last chance to live up to his name.
♪
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
All right.
I got a Dark and Stormy for Marcus,
Chardonnay for Caitlin,
and a whiskey for Mark and me...
On the rocks, of course.
Thanks, snowflake.
[GIGGLES]
You know, there's a cactus plant
that makes great cocktails.
The pads of the Opuntia cacti
pair perfectly with an agave spirit.
I bet it would really cover
the taste of strychnine too.
[LAUGHING] Strychnine...
Wow, a genius botanist
who can mix drinks?
I like him already.
[LAUGHTER]
So how did you two meet?
- Oh.
- Well, we met here, actually.
Mark was pouring beers by day and...
Murdering delivery men by night.
What? It's true.
She's exaggerating it.
Well, not exactly.
Okay, fine.
Mark and I each spent some time
on the wrong side of the law,
but I paid for my crimes,
and Mark turned state's witness
against some really bad guys.
Yeah, and the DA expunged my record.
So now, as clean as a whistle.
Well, seems like you've
turned over a new leaf.
[LAUGHS] Hey! Dr. Ficus.
- There he is.
- So good!
Hey, I kind of like that.
Listen, Frost and I are going
skydiving again next weekend.
Double date, round two?
What do you say? I
mean, you seem cool, man.
No, no, I've always
wanted to go skydiving.
- Hm?
- Yeah, I'm game.
What do you say, Caity?
Marcus, did you know
that when Mark got out,
he seduced my sister so
that he could steal a weapon
out from right under her nose?
After he helped us save the day.
And she was so upset
that she just kept moping and crying
and even needed to take a sabbatical.
- Caitlin...
- I apologized for all of that.
- We... we...
- And I accepted it.
Frost, I mean, how naive can you be?
He's already betrayed you,
and yet you're out there
livestreaming the two of
you jumping out of airplanes
and making out on cliffs.
- Remember Mount Shasta?
- Hell yeah.
Frost, what is wrong with you?
You're acting like some stupid teenager
falling in love with this
guy who's already hurt you
and, guess what,
is definitely going to do it again.
And you know what?
When that happens, I am not
picking up the pieces, because I am done
with broken hearts, you got that?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Hey, you know, we get it.
You don't like me.
But Frost is an adult with her own life.
And so long as she's
choosing to spend it with me,
then you need to deal with it.
[SCOFFS]
Are you really gonna let
him talk to me that way?
- Your sister?
- Yeah. I am.
'Cause he's my boyfriend,
and anything else is none
of your damn business.
♪
Hey...
I think I'd like to go home.
I'll pull the car around. Yeah.
♪
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry. Do you mind?
Oh, my bad.
Maybe I should just
take a leisurely stroll
down the hallway. [LAUGHS]
I'ma watch you like a
hawk watching a juicy vole.
♪ We are strong ♪
Do you need to take that?
♪ No one can tell us we're wrong ♪
Baby girl.
What time is it now in Londontown?
You eat a nice, balanced
breakfast like we discussed,
not just the bangers and mash?
Meta-bullets?
Yeah, not exactly.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Yeah, baby, I...
I know the buyer's schedule, baby.
Yes, baby.
No, we just hit a teensy little snag.
But you know me.
I got it all worked out.
Okay.
I love you too.
I said I lub yub tub, Ammy Wammy.
[BABY VOICE] I lub yub tub, Ammy Wammy.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
♪
- I say something funny?
- No.
No, you just... you seem
to have a great relationship
with... Amunet?
Uh, police reports say
you work together now.
Damn right, we have
a great relationship.
- It's because we work together.
- Hmm.
Ammy and I used to have separate crews,
separate heists, separate hideouts,
but it's like Dr. Finkel says.
"If you want your partner
to enter your heart,
you can't just open the doors.
You gotta open the windows."
I'm sorry, you see Dr. Finkel?
Sharon sees us, man. Okay?
And she helped us realize that
we'd never truly committed.
But now, we're not
just partners in love.
We're partners in crime.
And since we've stopped holding
back and have gone all in,
our relationship's never been better...
or more lucrative.
Hmm.
And if I don't have
those meta-bullets in hand
within the next hour,
Ammy Wammy says our buyer is gonna walk.
Yeah, so look, the dark matter
we're looking for is microscopic,
so I'm sorry, I'm gonna need more time.
Nah.
You need incentive. [WHISTLES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Barry, you don't have to help him.
Finish the scanner, now,
or your captain gets
to meet the white whale.
Hell yeah.
She gonna walk the plank, y'all.
- [LAUGHS]
- Ahab didn't...
I'm sorry, do you not know "Moby Dick"?
"To the last I grapple with thee."
What about "Wrath of Khan"?
"From hell's heart, I stab at thee.
For hate's sake, I spit my last"...
[SIGHS]
I bought you a first edition
for your birthday.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
BA in literature from Yale.
Now I'm surrounded by philistines.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Time's up. Waste her.
No! Wait, wait, wait.
Um, look, it might not be perfect,
but the scanner's done.
Now there's that service with a smile
I've been waiting for.
So all you have to do is
touch this button right here.
- [HIGH-PITCHED SCREECHING]
- [ALL GROANING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Put these in. Put
these in. Put these in.
[BREATHING HEAVILY] How did you...
I reset the scanner from
infrared to infrasonic.
Come on. We gotta go. Come on.
- [SCANNER SCREECHING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
♪
Time to make 'em go boom, boss?
Not when she's the
only one who can tell me
where the bullets are hidden now.
Find them!
♪
Nobody hides from Goldface.
Nobody!
[PANTING]
- What's it look like out there?
- Clear.
But it's only a matter of
time before we're discovered.
We need to figure out
our next move fast.
Okay. This is a storage room
for junked equipment, so
let's look for anything
we can patch up and use.
Tools to get these bracelets off.
Anything.
Hold on.
Captain, look.
It's deactivated. How's that possible?
Your powers work by mimicking
the powers of nearby metas, right?
Yes, whenever I'm in
high-stress situations
around other metas, it just happens.
For about 30 seconds,
I gain their powers.
- Why?
- These bracelets release
RNA energy pulses that
repress meta-genes.
Your DNA is constantly morphing
based on your adrenal levels
and your proximity to other metas.
The cuffs weren't designed to handle
erratic gene fluctuation, so...
So my mimic powers
short-circuited the bracelet.
This is great.
Kay, now you can mimic
Goldface's powers and take him down.
He'll never see you coming.
No, I'm not ready for that.
Why not? This is the chance
we've been waiting for.
I said I can't do it, Allen.
Let's just stick with your plan,
find something here that can help us.
We don't have much time.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
Pardon moi, madame.
There room here for
two to pay their tab?
Wouldn't want this fine establishment
to think I'm a thief.
So you disappear when people
want you to stick around,
but you stick around when
people want you to disappear.
I'm all kinds of complicated, Caitlin.
Maybe that's why you can't
see how much we have in common.
[SCOFFS]
Yeah, believe it or not,
both of us care about Frost.
Yeah, and that's why you abandoned her.
I... fine.
I screwed up before.
But Frost is special,
so I'm making up for it as best I can.
I'm even putting time
in with her family.
Yeah, and what do you know about family?
Uh, I know that mine's
dysfunctional as hell.
And the way you went off in there,
you kind of reminded me of them.
Yeah, you sounded just like
my frumpy, backstabbing nana
at every Blaine family reunion ever.
I mean, talk about cold. [SNICKERS]
[SHIVERS]
Congratulations, you
actually gave me flashbacks.
[SOFT MUSIC]
I'm sorry I blew up.
But if you care about Frost
as much as you say you do,
then you'll agree that
she deserves someone who...
Accepts her, warts and all?
Just like I do?
♪
Caitlin, like it or not,
Frost and I are all in.
There's no holding back or
hiding pieces of ourselves.
[SCOFFS] Like you.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
I used to tend bar, remember?
This isn't about Snowflake and I.
This is about you being
more focused on hating me
than focusing on your own date.
You've been holding back all night
'cause you're afraid to
go all in with Marcus.
Am I wrong?
[BOTH SIGH]
Look, it's...
It's okay to be scared.
But at some point, you've
got to take a leap of faith
like I did with Frost and
like she's doing with me.
♪
Trust me, it's the best decision
that either of us have ever made.
Hmm.
And one more thing.
Marcus is a really good guy.
So maybe stop thinking about
what it is you have to lose
and start thinking about what it is
you might gain, you know?
But I don't know.
Thanks.
- For what?
- Gotta go.
♪
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
[SIGHS] Okay.
- You find anything?
- No, not yet.
Let's just keep looking.
Captain, your powers are our
only hope of stopping Goldface.
I told you, I can't.
- Why not?
- Because I can't control them.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SIGHS] Barry, the other day,
I ordered an iced coffee,
but when I picked it up,
it boiled in my hand.
Turns out the barista was a heat meta,
and I mimicked her powers
without even realizing it.
♪
I understand, but you can work
on controlling your powers.
I've tried.
But I can't figure it out,
and no one can teach me.
♪
That's why you've been so anxious
about getting in touch with the Flash?
You want him to train you.
Why didn't you just say
that was the reason earlier?
Because it's hard for
me to ask for help.
And...
When I mimicked that
other meta's abilities,
if they had been more lethal,
I could've killed someone
without even realizing
what was happening.
I was hoping Flash could help me
learn to control them,
but he's out of reach.
I am madness maddened.
Come out, come out
wherever you are, Captain,
'cause if you don't,
I'm gonna do this
the old-fashioned way
and start squeezing
your brave officers until they pop.
[GROANING]
Two minutes, Captain.
Ticktock.
Clock's ticking down, Captain.
Captain, you have to
go down there right now.
Don't you think I know that?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Look, I did two tours on
a Khandaqi battlefield.
I am not afraid of dying,
and I won't let any more women or men
under my command get hurt,
but right now, I don't
know how to prevent that.
You have to use your powers.
Look, I know you're worried
about losing control,
but the military gave you
all the training you'll ever need
to harness your own instincts.
So instead of worrying
about trying to control
Goldface's powers, just let it in.
Let it take over, and then go all in
on trusting your instincts.
Believe me, you can do this.
♪
Even if I could, what good would it do?
It'll give me the 30 seconds I need
to get this cuff off.
- What?
- Oh, Captain, my Captain.
Just stall Goldface
until I can get us help.
Barry, you saw what happens
when someone tries to
take off that trinket.
- Do you have a death wish?
- No, I can do this.
And you can handle Goldface.
You know why?
You are one of the bravest
people I've ever met.
♪
Let's take back our house.
I'm done playing, Captain.
You got 30 seconds to
give me what I want,
or Officer...
What's your name again?
[CHOKING] Korber.
Oh.
Is that with a C or with a K?
A K.
K. Thanks.
It's "bye, Felicia" for
Officer K-K-Korber here,
and for every minute I'm
empty-handed after that,
another person dies.
30!
29.
28.
27.
Boss, you could just skip
the counting and kill her, you know?
You have no sense of drama.
Where was I?
[SIGHS] 27... 26...
26.
- 25.
- Let her go.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
You don't disappoint, Captain.
What the hell?
Give me back my chain!
You want it? Take it from me.
Shh.
Why isn't your bracelet working?
Didn't match my outfit.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Wow.
You have seriously leveled up.
♪
[EXPLOSION RUMBLES]
Looks like the chemist
wasn't so smart after all.
That just leaves you.
Time to bring the pain.
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
Oh, my God. Allen, he must have...
No, he's okay.
I got him out just in
time, thanks to you.
Now, what were you thinking,
breaking into a police station?
Whose bad idea was that, anyway?
♪ We are strong ♪
Seriously?
♪ No one can tell us we're wrong ♪
What can I say?
I'd do anything for love.
♪ Searching our hearts for so long ♪
Can one of you guys get this?
♪
♪ Love is a battlefield ♪
Take this evidence to Processing.
- You're late.
- Yeah, I know.
- Again.
- I'm sorry.
You were amazing.
You went toe-to-toe with Goldface.
So I heard.
I mean, Korber told me all about it.
I held my own, long enough
for the Flash to arrive.
Of course, he left before I got a chance
to say "thank you" again,
but at least I can thank you, Allen.
I never could've stood
up to Goldface that way
if it weren't for your advice.
Nah, it was all you.
I just aimed you in the right direction.
By the way, I gotta ask you,
where are the meta-bullets, anyway?
I had them transferred to A.R.G.U.S.
35 weeks ago.
And you kept that secret the whole time?
Goldface was about to kill you.
It's called a poker face, Allen.
[SOFT MUSIC]
I should get started on the paperwork.
At least this time, I
know what the charges are.
♪
- Can we talk?
- Mark's downstairs.
We have tickets to an underground rave
in Keystone City.
It'll just take a minute. Please.
Look, I acted like a
total bonehead tonight,
and I was rude to you and to Mark.
I am so sorry.
Bonehead? Try jackass.
What is your deal?
I guess I have a lot
of baggage to unpack
when it comes to dating.
Ya think?
The reason I've been afraid
to go all-in with Marcus
is because the last time
I did, I lost everything.
And I think that's why it's so hard
for me to see you with Mark,
'cause I envy how honest
and free and effortless
your relationship is.
Effortless?
I'm sorry, that's not
exactly what I'd call
the roller coaster that is FrostBlaine.
You're aware I stabbed him, right?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
Yeah.
You make it seem easy, at least.
And Mark helped me realize something.
Mark? My Mark?
Yeah.
Mark showed me that if
I'm gonna have a chance
at finding the same
thing, then I need to take
the same leap with Dr. Ficus.
- So I'm gonna do it.
- Hmm.
That's great. I'm happy for you.
Thank you, and I'm
happy for you and Mark,
even though he is... himself.
So does this mean we can do that whole
double date thing for reals?
I need to patch things up with Marcus,
but after that, I'd love to.
Great.
Mark and I signed up for a
roller derby on the weekend,
and we need two extra players, so...
you have a mouthguard, right?
Uh, I could probably find one, maybe.
Cool. Practice starts tomorrow.
8:00 a.m. Don't be late.
♪
[WHOOSHES]
I love what you've done with the place.
It's... it's different
than the last captain's.
Flash, on behalf of
this whole department,
I wanted to thank you.
We couldn't have stopped
Goldface without you.
Hey, if it wasn't for
your smart thinking,
a lot of people would
have been seriously hurt.
So from now on, if you need me,
you can call me on this.
If we're gonna keep this city safe,
we need to do it together.
Which is why I wanna share
something else with you.
My true identity.
Allen, I know it's you.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
Wait, what?
How did you find out?
I found this charred
bracelet in the storage room.
There's only one way
you could've escaped
a bomb exploding on your wrist.
Superspeed.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, Joe was right all along.
You really are a great cop.
And I'd be more than happy to train you
to become an even better meta.
♪
[SIGHS]
Since when do you know
how to make a doro wat?
Did you spend a year in Ethiopia
that I don't know about, or...
[LAUGHS] It's called retirement.
I am learning to cook whatever I want.
'Course, all your little sister
wants to eat is chicken nuggets.
Hey, don't knock the nuggies.
I should check on her and make sure
she's still sleeping, not trying
to make a break for it.
Yeah, I'm gonna pack
Barr some leftovers.
He's working late.
But first, I am gonna
have a little bit more.
[WHOOSHES]
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪
[DOOR SLAMS]
Dad.
[STAMMERS]
Weren't you just upstairs?
Yeah.
And then I went to the
garage because you asked me
to get the files from
the old Scarpulla case.
Remember?
Um...
yeah, I-I must have just,
uh, checked out for a second.
Mm. I get it.
That's a food coma, baby girl.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --