MAN: All right, guys, let’s give a slate.
-Uh-uh.
[LAUGHS]
Look upon the horizon.
All you see will soon be yours.
Simba.
-That's gonna be my new job. Ha, ha.
-What about that dark patch over there?
[WOOFING]
WOMAN: Okay, guys, just stall.
MAN: Oh, action.
It'll accelerate exposure.
Explosure? "Explosure men," I said.
Actually, me and Grant-- Grant.
[ALL LAUGHING]
--finding out about Barry--
[CHOKES, THEN CLEARS THROAT]
Almost choked. Um--
[LAUGHS]
It was amazing.
I'm hungry.
[ALL LAUGH]
WOMAN:
I was like, "I think I'll be able to...."
My God, it's just like Vegas.
[LAUGHING]
It's like I've been making
bad decisions all day.
Three-- Three-- Three--
GUSTIN:
I want the metahumans to go away!
[MARTIN LAUGHS]
[FARTS]
Ronnie.
Tell me your name.
Ronnie Raymond.
Sorry.
[SPITS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Joe!
[ALL LAUGHING]
-Freeze.
-Freeze!
Perfect timing.
MAN:
And....
There's a door.
MAN:
Go!
Don't worry. That'll disappear.
It's almost like you choked on him.
Nope. It's almost like he choked on you.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Check this out. I just got happy.
Physical or-- No. **** me. Sorry, guys.
Barry's-- **** me.
When Professor Stein disappeared he--
The army--
**** me.
[ALL LAUGH]
-That was weird.
-That was very weird.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
[ALL LAUGH]
What if I create a serum that will terminate
the polymerization reaction...
...essentially....
I don't remember
what I'm supposed to do here anymore.
CAVANAGH: Dr. Snow has concocted
a solution we believe will stop him.
Yes, I have created a serum that will create a--
Something around his cells.
Yes. You do that with those cells
and, damn, his **** done packed.
We don't understand if the particle
accelerator's gonna explode or not.
Nobody knows if that **** thing's
gonna explode. You know what I mean?
Ow.
--individual can create a mental nexus
using ga-- Goddamn it.
**** me with a spoon twice daily.
Greg, I farted. My bad. Achoo!
Uch. Yeah, let's go back to ones.
For damn sure.
[WHIMPERS]
Oops. Ha, ha.
That's no good.
-It's a miracle.
ALL: Ha-ha-ha.
What are we waiting for? Are we...?
Your brilliance, your warmth,
your heart, your humor. It only adds to it.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
That's an on-set faux pas right there.
Allow me to introduce myself.
This damn--
I mean, I can't-- This thing won't--
I-- I'm so sorry. I'm Eobard Thawne, but I--
Are we still rolling? Hello.
Joe.
[LAUGHS]
It's the other hand, right? Yeah.
[HUMMING]
I jacked into the, uh, Central City--
**** hell. I don't even know
what I'm talking about.
-Ha, ha. Jacked into that ****.
VALDES: I jacked into the ****.
I never had any reason to look at any areas
outside of the pipeline or the--
-What's this called? Thank you.
-Courtyard.
Because Mardon can control the weather...
-...because he can.... Hmm, hmm.
-Great.
--Mardon can control the weather
is if he taps into the atmosphere's natrical--
GUSTIN: Natrical?
MAN: Yeah.
**** you, Tom.
When the heat gun was fired, it increases--
****ing hell.
-One more time.
-All right.
When the heat gun was fired, it--
[BLEEP]
Mm. It ****.
-So tell me about the Caesar sausages.
-Mm-hm.
-Yes. They're intricately cut sausages.
-Mm.
-Cut.
-They already have grill marks on them.
Ronnie, I love you, but this is a time machine,
not a night bookcase from Ikea.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Now, go ahead. Go ahead, girl.
It's usually what isn't said-- Bluh-luh-luh.
I'm the lead engineer.
I know how to shut down-- Mm.
I know how to operate the shutdown val--
Operate the shutdown valve. ****ing hell.
And once upon a time ago....
-Nope.
-Ha, ha.
-I-- I can feel our connect-- Bleh.
MAN: Let's do that one more time, guys.
You really are very clever, Carl--
Ha, ha. Carlos.
I ha-- Huh, hoo, ha.
Your eyes are beautiful.
Dude, we're not gonna kiss.
Please.
-Do-- What you're gonna do is--
-He has your head down.
WOMAN: Yes.
-You got your position.
Is it "the rest of them or the rest of us"?
"Call us a team and the rest of them"?
-Let's talk about--
-Right.
Professor, can I borrow you for a second?
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
-You know, the door....
-Yeah.
MAN: So we could go back to one?
-Yes.
-Yeah. Your check's done.
-And....
MAN:
It's take one. A mark.
So you and this hood good guy
have history.
Hey. It's okay. Oh, my God.
Let's start again.
The showdown of a lifetime.
[AIR WHOOSHES]
-Out with our fa--
MAN: Sorry.
It's a little premature on the blow.
[BABY CRIES]
[FARTS]
-Ew.
-I'm sorry.
Even your farts smell good.
CAVANAGH: **** me with a spoon
twice daily. Hold on. Okay, good.
GUSTIN: Get that out of my face.
MAN: Sorry.
MAN: One moment, please.
GUSTIN: Okay.
MAN: Sixty-two. Take one.
CAVANAGH: Get that out of his face.
-Copy that. A mark.
I-- It's fine. It--
That happens sometimes. It's--
That's why I have a pri--
That's why I have a friction-proof suit.
-That's why you have a pricture.
-Yeah, yeah.
MAN 1: B marker.
MAN 2: B mark.
[DOOR CLANKS]
Bye.
Okay. Nothing to see here.
GUSTIN: I'm not into anyone else,
and I'll prove it to you.
This, ahem, is a naga jolokia, ahem....
I have to go back up.
I have pepper in my throat.
[SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
MAN:
Let's lose--
Hey, girl, yeah. What you think of my suit?
Well, apparently, he lost his speed
after he killed my mom.
He gets it back sometimes,
but only in spurts.
-Yeah.
-So I was right ab--
**** you.
VALDES: Oh, yeah.
-Ha-ha-ha.
GUSTIN:
Who are you talking to?
-Hi. Hi.
-Hey.
GUSTIN: Who you talking to?
-Just a friend.
GUSTIN:
Oh. Tell him I say hi, from the Flash.
-Oh, hey, uh, the Flash says hi.
GUSTIN: Yeah.
-Have a good day.
-What movie--?
-The Flash.
-Oh.
[CREW LAUGHS]